[BLACK]
I've been wanting to introduce
myself to you for a while.
My sister's really built
up the Legend of Leo.
My timing's been terrible,
and I didn't want to
make things awkward.
[screams]
[LEO]
You need some help?
[BLACK] Sorry!
I can't believe I did that!
--[BLACK crying]
--[LEO laughing]
You all right there?
[LEO]
So, um,
now that we've met
and everything.
I wanted to ask you about White.
About her illness?
I mean, I know she's been in
the hospital for three years.
But, uh, she told me that!
I wasn't snooping!
But that's all I really know.
And I worry.
Her heart is not
her best friend.
But she's been doing pretty
okay right now, I guess.
[LEO]
Oh.
I never should have
taken her out of her room!
I could have killed her!
What was I thinking?
She's sick, after
all, isn't she?
Gah! I'm so stupid!
White's really strong-willed
and kind of self-centered,
and a tomboy to boot.
Must be hard to
be her friend.
I'm sure your hands are
full hanging out with her.
[LEO chuckles]
No, I wouldn't say that.
It's like hanging
with my sister.
Except, you know, different.
Oh, wow.
I didn't know you had a sister.
Mm-hmm. They've both got the
strong-willed thing in common.
[BLACK chuckles]
[LEO]
She always refers to me
as her "tortoise knight,"
whatever that means.
I get the feeling
she's making fun of me.
[BLACK]
The "tortoise" part maybe,
but what's wrong
with being a "knight"?
She knows you've got her back.
I'm jealous of you, actually,
because with me and White,
she's always been my champion.
I got teased a lot at school
for being small
and having four eyes,
but White always defended me.
She fought for me
against bullies
twice her size,
and she always won, too.
And I love her for it,
but it made me feel so
pathetic I wanted to die.
But I survived, somehow.
[LEO]
Of course you did!
[DEMON CUSTOMER 1]
Hey, pipe down!
[DEMON CUSTOMER 2]
What's your problem?
[WOMAN]
Don't get so worked up, Leo!
[LEO]
Yeah. Um.
I mean, how should
I say this?
Look, you're way stronger
than you think, you know.
My boss is always
messing with me
and calling me names like
"pipsqueak" or "squinty,"
and it's not like I like it.
But you can't let that
stuff bother you!
[laughing]
That's good advice.
I'll do the same
thing. Thanks, man.
Sure, I hope it helps.
--[LEO] Huh?
--[WOMAN] Huh?
How are you even
doing that, Leo?
[LEO]
Me? I'm not doing anything!
[WOMAN]
Then why is the coffee
just hanging here?
[WOMAN]
Could you please just
stop doing this weird stuff
in my diner, already?
I didn't spill this
coffee on myself, Vivian!
[VIVIAN] Leo! Hey, jeez,
let me help you.
[LEO]
It's burning me!
I'm sorry.
[BLACK]
It's a family thing,
but no matter what I try,
I'm no good at it.
I guess I knew there were
people with those powers.
I just never expected
to see it up close.
If Black says
I met someone else,
then I guess I believe him.
Hope you're ready to
meet your maker, Chief!
[KLAUS]
Welcome.
Would you like a glass?
Eh, Leonardo?
[LEO]
No.
[STARPHASE]
Oh, good day.
Something wrong?
[LEO]
Oh, you know,
whenever I open that door,
Zapp takes another
stupid shot at Klaus.
It's unsettling how
calm it is right now.
Now that you mention it,
we haven't seen him today.
My vote is he gave up
from a broken spirit.
[LEO]
But it's kind of cool
how he never stops
trying even though
he always gets his
butt handed back to him.
[phone rings]
[LEO]
Ah, speak of the devil.
Someone's ears were burning.
Zapp, where are you?
Hey!
Chief!
Chief, can you hear me?
I've got a big-ass sword
shoved down my throat, Chief!
Please come save me!
Help me!
[ZAPP cries]
[KLAUS]
Hurry, Leonardo!
Zapp is in trouble!
I'm surprised at how much
faith you have in your boss.
Why wouldn't I?
He's never failed me.
Listen good,
you stinkin'
alterworld scumbags!
You want entertainment?
Well, you're gonna get it!
You ain't never seen
a contestant like this
in your sorry,
sad little lives!
[LEO]
Uh, Klaus?
I present to you my
credentials, good sir.
Now where's Zapp?
[grunts]
[BODYGUARD 1]
Enjoy your visit, sir.
[KLAUS]
Thank you.
[LEO]
The hell?
[KLAUS]
What is all this?
[LEO]
It's an underground fight ring!
You know, you bet on fights,
and then they beat
each other down!
[KLAUS]
I've heard of these.
Very interesting.
I wonder where Zapp is in this.
[ZAPP]
This will clear out my debt?
It's a big risk
luring Klaus here.
Zapp, kid, that all depends
on the take tonight,
and if you can handle
yourself like a professional.
Tonight, you better dance
like your life depends on it.
Because tomorrow will be
far too late for ballet lessons.
Hm?
Ladies and gentlemen!
[REFEREE]
This is Libra!
Our very special guest,
Klaus Von Reinherz!
You've found
yourself in the most
savage, bare knuckle
brawl in Hellsalem's Lot!
This is Eden!
Excuse me for interrupting
your work here,
but I'm hoping you can tell
me where to find my friend.
[REFEREE]
Sure thing, sure thing.
Now Eden's got two rules!
Number one:
"No Weapons Allowed!"
Number two:
"All Fights are Single Combat!"
Now you know
how the game goes!
If you fight well,
you'll get to see Zapp.
Whoa! Now you just slow
your roll there, buddy!
Getting rough with
me gets you nowhere!
Especially since you
don't know where he is,
or how many bullets could
burrow through his brain
while you wasted your
time thrashing me.
Sorry for the scrutiny,
but we don't know who
we're dealing with.
We have few rules,
but they must be followed,
so no surprise weapons.
[SPECTATOR 1]
I thought Libra
was an urban legend.
[SPECTATOR 2]
I've never met
one of them before.
[SPECTATOR 3]
That huma looks familiar to me.
[SPECTATOR 4]
He can't be that strong.
He's got a damn scary
face though, huh?
Dude's got a mean
look in his eye.
They all look the same to me.
Looks like my plumber.
Meet your challenger!
Gregor Maximus!
[crowd cheering]
[BOOKIE]
Okay, place your bets, scumbags!
Hey! You're a little
confused, huh?
It's pretty simple.
Just keep your eyes
on the prize, man.
Your life is at stake.
I'm guessing from
the look of you
that you can handle yourself.
That's good.
[GREGOR]
Fists against fists, man.
There's no other fight like
two men duking it out.
You feel me, bro?
Why don't we prove
it to this creepshow?
Give them a fight
they won't soon forget?
[KLAUS]
As you wish.
[LEO]
Why is this starting
to feel like some
kind of a setup to me?
Zapp, you dick!
20 zeros on Klaus, please!
[REFEREE]
Ready!
Fight!
[crowd cheering]
I got no patience
for these weak
huma-on-huma fights.
This ain't playtime!
I'll wipe out your puny
species one by one,
starting with your ass!
You're starting him
against Jugglernose?
This ain't gonna be pretty.
Tell them to hold the bell
and re-take the bets!
[ZAPP]
Call the doctor and
resuscitation team in!
Do it stat!
[OZMALDO]
Why are you so rattled?
It'll all work out,
Zapp. Don't worry.
He's supposed to
pull his punches.
He won't kill your man.
[ZAPP]
He better stick to the plan.
I can't tell looking at him,
but you say he's a pro.
Although,
Klaus is something else.
[ZAPP]
He's built to win!
[bell ringing]
[crowd cheering]
Hell yes!
Your boss has major balls!
[ZAPP]
Aw.
All of Jugglernose's
joints are dislocated
and bent in funny directions.
I wanted to start
Klaus off with a human
so he wouldn't go
full force on your guys.
[OZMALDO]
I've never seen a human
fight so precisely,
so rationally.
He only hit the shell joints
and landed each punch perfectly.
I like this guy!
Look at this! The crowd can't
believe what they just saw!
They're pissing
themselves with joy!
[REFEREE]
Whew! Well that was exciting!
Unlucky for him, you sure made
quick work of our poster boy!
[KLAUS]
My apologies
for having to do that.
Now if you please,
I'd like you to
kindly show me to my associate.
[SPECTATOR 5] Hey, man,
where you think you're going!
[SPECTATOR 6] The main
event hasn't even started!
[SPECTATOR 7]
Next bout!
Send out another challenger
before he gets away!
Surely you don't
want to quit now.
Your fists have
captivated the hearts
of all the wagering
scumbags in the place.
Come on, you can do it!
No.
This isn't getting me anywhere.
It's okay. Just keep fighting.
At least until
they're tired of
watching your ugly mug beat
their buddies into the mat.
[KLAUS]
If I must.
[CROWD]
Klaus! Klaus! Klaus!
Where you trying to go, kid?
Authorized personnel
only beyond this point.
Actually, dude,
you look like you're
probably too young
to be at these fights anyway.
Say, you wouldn't
happen to be here
with that guy in the ring,
Klaus, would you?
Yeah, I, um...
[GREGOR]
So then,
are you friends with Zapp, too?
[LEO]
I totally knew it!
Zapp's behind all this!
[GREGOR]
No!
Er, uh,
all right.
Aw, man, I blew it!
Sorry, sorry!
Well, there's a lot going on,
but it's nothing
you should worry about.
Klaus seems tough
enough to hold his own,
plus our doctor here
will patch him up like new
if he gets hurt too bad.
[LEO]
I'm not worried.
[GREGOR]
Cool.
You seem like you're
taking this well.
[LEO]
What do you think
people come all the
way down here for?
Do they just want
to see some blood?
They can see that anywhere.
It's not exactly like you
have to put much effort
into finding any trouble
in Hellsalem's Lot.
You've got a point.
[GREGOR]
Anyone can take
a step into the street and
with the pull of a trigger
they could bring down an enemy,
or they could push
a little button
and blow up countless people.
Knowing all that, then sure,
I can see what you mean
because the world is full
of efficient violence.
Still,
we can hack at each
other with axes,
slice with swords,
shoot guns at each other,
even curse each
other with magic,
or just fire missiles,
but for whatever reason,
there'd still be this
craving which evolution
just can't shake
from our systems.
Fist fighting, one-on-one.
It doesn't matter the species.
All men are suckers when it
comes to these two simple ideas.
So, sure.
They do want to see some blood.
But it's really something
deeper than that.
And it's afflicted man
throughout history.
[bell rings]
The only name you could give
it is Bareknuckle Fever.
[crowd cheering]
I'm hoping you're as pleased
as you seem, Ozmaldo!
Well done!
You've brought me
the most magnificent
animal I ever seen!
[ZAPP]
Hold on, is this happening?
Yep, it looks like it is.
He's into it!
The Chief's about to
tear this arena a new one!
[bell rings]
[REFEREE]
Winner!
He knocked out the reigning
champ with a single blow!
This is unheard-of!
Awesome! Awesome!
I don't even care if
I'm flat broke now,
I'm just psyched I was
here to see this massacre!
Oh, man, am I
glad that's over.
But it was an even better
night than expected, right?
Okay then. I'll
just be going now.
What?
[REFEREE]
Um, Boss?
It's an honor to have
you here, warrior.
Allow me to offer you
praise and pay respect
to the way you've
fought this evening.
Yes, even I had goosebumps.
Watching you tonight,
I realized that one cannot
be truly sated when he only
cooks with generic ingredients.
You're the full-flavor
feast I've been craving.
And tonight I end
my prolonged fast.
With your savagery
as my ultimate meal!
Will you allow me
this great honor?
[crowd cheering]
No, I refuse.
Don't try to back down!
You've got to accept
the boss' challenge!
Don't you understand what
him challenging you means?
We're talking total ownership of
this fighting den as the prize!
It's started! It's started!
[OZMALDO] He keeps a constant
defense with his left,
while his right is
always ready to strike
from the shortest distance.
He doesn't fight like
any common barroom brawler.
It's as if he's armed
with a shield and spear.
A Spartan defense.
In bareknuckle fighting,
all limbs are weapons.
There's no restriction at all
on kicks, holds, or throws.
Yet he's ruled by
some honor code.
It's illogical, yet so simple
that he sees every move coming.
Where did he learn
such discipline?
Most excellent.
Makes me doubt my own sanity.
But you've got my
bloodlust boiling over
to take you head on!
Ozmaldo's putting his
undefeated title on the line.
And he's not letting go easy,
but maybe all this action
will tune the chief up a notch.
[WOMAN]
So, ya mean Ozzie's
going to win another one?
That's so boring.
[ZAPP]
No, actually, not a chance.
The chief seems too
structured a fighter
to adjust his blows, so
it looks like he's stuck
in the same pattern
when focusing.
But that's just because he
sets his own limitations
and sticks with them until
they aren't working anymore.
When I said this might
tune the chief up?
I was talking about
him switching styles.
[OZMALDO]
His left?
How can that be?
Is that his true strong arm?
I-- I felt that!
Well. This must
not look good.
Uh...
Alright, I guess
I should explain.
Look, I was just
borrowing his corpse.
It's not like I killed him.
Ozmaldo had
enemies everywhere.
[LEO]
Hey, Klaus!
Look out, that's a--
I regret nothing I've done.
It was the only way to give
us some quality time together.
It's been a genuine pleasure.
My dear, Klaus.
Wow, Klaus, thank you
for saving me!
Those bad guys
holding me hostage
got one look at you fighting
in the ring and ran off
in utter terror!
Thank you, Klaus!
[KLAUS]
All that matters is you're safe.
[ZAPP]
What a dupe!
--[KLAUS] My friend.
--[ZAPP] What a super-simp!
[LEO]
Oh, what?
I'm not falling for it.
And I am so ratting you out!
You can't stop me,
you fat cocky jerk!
[ZAPP]
Hey, buddy, it's not like that.
Things maybe seemed a
little out of control to you.
But I don't do anything without
a damn good reason, alright?
[LEO]
Here comes some crap.
[ZAPP]
Just listen to me!
See, man.
The Chief is pretty
worn out, right?
He's just been through a string
of brutal single combat matches,
plus that heavy thump
the Blood Breed laid on him.
[LEO]
You don't say.
Could you just get
to your point?
[ZAPP]
Jeez, the point is.
If I can't defeat him now,
I'll never be able to!
[LEO]
You are absolutely the worst!
This time I've got you, Chief!
[punching, coughing]
[BLACK]
Thanks for the ride, man.
[LEO]
It's totally on my way.
[BLACK]
Wow,
is it really almost Halloween?
[LEO]
I don't get why they bother.
It's been Halloween
in this city
every day the
last three years.
[BLACK laughs]
[BLACK]
One thing you can
say about this place
is the people do love to party.
Halloween's kind of a sacred
tradition back where I'm from.
The kids don't get candy,
but the people believe
on All Hallows' Eve
that this world
and the next world
become joined,
allowing the dead to
come back, and evil spirits
to show their true faces.
Sounds kind of romantic.
It's an old-fashioned idea.
Who cares? I think it's cool.
It's like the first
time I met White.
We were in the hospital cemetery
and she told me she was a ghost.
I almost believed it.
You guys make a lot
of morbid jokes
like that back
where you're from?
No.
[LEO] So, I guess
I'll see you later, then?
[BLACK]
Sure.
I feel bad though.
Sticking you on hospital duty.
[LEO]
Hey, I told you, no worries.
You've got an early day.
[BLACK]
Yeah, but still.
She just gets so cranky
if someone doesn't
look in on her
at least once a day, you know?
[LEO]
I'm just happy I can help
shake up the boredom.
Later then!
[BLACK]
Leonardo!
My sister.
She can say strange
things sometimes,
but really,
she's just an ordinary girl.
She needs a friend like you.
We're both counting on you,
ol' tortoise knight!
[LEO]
Huh? Hey!
Please don't start with that!
[BLACK laughs]
[LEO]
Until next time.
[whistling]
[13 KINGS 1]
Tie, go again!
[13 KINGS 2]
First is rock!
Rock! Paper! Scissors!
On the count of three!
One, two, three!
[MAN]
My, oh, my,
what a welcome visitor!
What's up with you?
[BLACK]
Eh, nothing much.
Hey, shut your holes!
Take a hike!
I've got the next go, obviously.
--[13 KINGS 1] Huh?
--[13 KINGS 2] Boo!
You suck!
So things are finally
getting started?
[BLACK]
Nope.
Not even close,
King of Depravity.
Finally ending.
The moment of My Great Collapse.
To the rescue.
[VIVIAN]
Hey there, come on in!
I guess you're getting pretty
used to it around here, huh?
Of course, it kind
of forces you
to get used to it.
With this much abnormality,
you kind of have
to adjust, right?
Careful, though.
You don't wanna die
before you figure out
you're living in a fool's warped
idea of paradise, do you?
Next time on
"Blood Blockade Battlefront,"
Z's Longest Day. Part 1.
In case of emergency,
or if you're hungry,
stop on by Dianne's Diner!
I'll always be here.
Pretty much.
Like, always.