Takkun, we're surrounded.
It's a full-scale attack.
They've got snipers, too.
Snipers are always
so annoying, you know?
If we move, they'll fire.
But we've gotta do something.
You're right.
I'll draw their fire.
It's dangerous-
[Haruko] That's the idea!
This is your final battle!
Go and die
to prove that you love me!
[Man on TV] Brother!
[Brother] I'm a runaway
bullet train after all.
[Man on TV]
Brother! You can't die now.
[Director] What are all these
pigeons doing here?
Get these stupid birds
outta this shot!
Hey, what are you doing?
Haruko-chan, play nice, now.
Not in a hundred thousand
years will you ever
get anything from me but
a butt full of lead, compadre.
You are so cruel, Haruko-chan.
[Naota]
What's with those clothes?
[Kamon]
Ah, this red jacket you mean?
Why, do you prefer
the green one, Naota?
You like
the other version, huh?
The "Castle of Cagliostro"
version, huh?
When did you become
such a hot shot preppy type?
Anyway, monkey-sensei
prefers the red one, you know.
No matter what he says now,
we can't do anything about it.
Hey, hey where are you going?
Naota-kun. Naota-kun!
[Haruko] What? You're saying I
have personal feelings for him?
I don't think so.
The reason this mission
has been delayed
is because the channel
to N.O. is still open.
It's not about
liking or disliking.
Damn, the connection went dead!
Oh, were you listening?
Why don't you
put on some clothes?
Is there someone here?
How's this?
[Naota] Uh... I meant
normal clothes.
Haruko's "Master the guitar
in one millisecond" class.
Yeah! Sign up now!
Do you find this
difficult to understand?
Grab the guitar and you can be
a pop idol. Chicks dig it, dude!
Pyon!
[Naota] Pyon?
Like Filter or Slash.
Like Red Hot Chili Peppers,
or Rage Against the Machine,
or Richard Cheese.
There's one that doesn't
fit the list, you know.
You have to learn to stand
like a cool rock dude, pyon.
Jimi Hendrix and McCartney
both start out like this.
Haruko, hey!
What are you doing?
It's dangerous to go
waving that thing around.
Use your guitar again.
One more time, Takkun. Kakkin.
You did it so great last time.
Not interested.
I should teach you
how to be a man, Takkun.
Yeah, like you know!
[Haruko] Ya, Takkun,
that's more like it.
[Naota] No.
The horn... it's... the horn.
[Haruko]
Muku-muku my first kiss.
[Naota] Liar. You've already
done it plenty of times,
and you know it.
Naota-kun,
I can't forgive you.
You were making out
and doing perverted things
behind your father's back.
That's not true.
You don't know what-
Right. We will have
a duel of honor.
We must do battle
for Haruko-san.
I'm for it.
Haruko-san! Here's my weapon,
it's all for you.
"Forever the Bullet
of Love and the Plot"
"Brittle Bullet"
[Kamon] Hey hey, what's the
matter with my poor little son?
[Naota] What are you doing?
Geez!
[Kamon] If you're just gonna run
and hide like a scared rabbit,
then your dear old dad's gonna
have to take Haruko-san away.
[Haruko] Oh no, Takkun,
save me, save me.
[Naota] Get off of me.
[Naota] Don't use me
as a human shield.
Those things hurt.
Cut it out.
[Haruko] Save me.
Target sighted.
We are in range.
[Kitsurubami]
It's blue. Repeat. Blue.
[Amarao]
You're sure it's not red?
So the blue is confirmed then.
Alright. I already got Medical
Mechanica's unofficial consent.
We'll take care of it here so
they can't interfere with us.
I have work to do,
so let's do this fast, ok?
But I want it to look cool,
you know what I mean?
Charming in a manly grown-up
kind of way. Get it?
If we screw up, Medical
Mechanica'll be all over us.
Just forget Raharu. She'll
just complicate everything.
Just take care of yourself
'til I get there.
You know, more mature looking.
Something that a woman I haven't
seen in a while would think,
"This guy's really virile, but
also nurturing and supportive."
Something like that.
That's what I'm looking for.
Oh, don't I get
one of those candies?
I wanna get the sweetest one.
Super sweet,
if you know what I mean.
[Kamon]
You're so easy Naota-kun.
So easy.
[Kitsurubami] They seem to be
playing some kind of game.
Looks really stupid.
I'm sure I can
handle this myself.
Huh, who's the girl
he hasn't seen in so long?
What are you doing? You're
supposed to be helping me.
But my guitar's
not plugged in.
Why'd you bring that? Are
you crazy? This is war, gee!
It's squeegee and
bungee and grungy.
We're in trouble, G.
[Naota] Take that.
[Kitsurubami] Blue. Blue.
Blue. Blue. Cobalt Blue.
If 7 of 9 heeds a cy
what do you have?
Cyborg!
Cyborg my butt!
Actually, confusing cyborgs
with robots is a common mistake.
Take that, yah!
"The correct kanji uses
the more Chinese-style 'blue.'"
[Kamon] I'm leaving
the rest to you, TV Boy.
Alright, just
one more and I win.
Wait, wait, hold on!
I get three timeouts, you know.
Don't gimme that look.
Okay, I just made it up!
Naota, you okay?
Did you... cut him up?
Were you hurt?
I'm used to this stuff.
I can handle it.
"Masamune Liquor"
What's this truck for?
[Masashi] Deliveries.
We got a part-time job.
[Naota] Job? You're
in elementary school.
[Masashi]  It's okay, don't
worry. We won't get caught.
We only drive along
the side of the river.
[Naota] You mean you do this
all the time?
That looks cool, you know?
Huh?
It's not that.
He's the one that wanted to.
It's a toy, right?
Does it shoot bullets?
Actually it, uh... uh...
Hey, Canti, go on and
buy the uh, drinks, yeah.
[Naota] And don't
get the sour kind.
[Gaku] So, Naota, didja hear?
[Naota] What?
[Gaku] A rumor.
[Naota] A rumor, about what?
What is it?
[Gaku] That that satellite
was coming down.
That you saved the city.
That you did it, Naota!
Also, there was that whole thing
with Ninamori at school.
That's right.
And everyone says
you're controlling
that killer robot.
[Gaku and Masashi] Yeah!
What's that? I didn't know
it was such a big rumor.
Geez, what do I say?
[Masashi] Yeah, so it's like
you're the pilot?
Like a robot commander
or something.
Is that true?
You're really the commander,
Naota? That's awesome!
It's true.
[Naota] Cut it out.
[Gaku] She's the one
who kissed him. Smooch!
Smooch! Smooch!
--[Eri] I won.
--[Gaku] Smooch! Smooch!
--[Masahi] Really?
Hold on a sec.
--[Gaku] Smooch! Smooch!
[Masashi] Here ya go.
What?
[Masashi]
It's a prize.
It was supposed to be
pay for work, but...
It's nice.
Hey, Sameji!
[Eri] You think they're
actually going out?
[Masashi] She's
his brother's girlfriend?
What's his name, Tasuku?
He's a baseball player.
[Gaku] But that other one
likes Naota, too.
The kiss kiss girl.
He's like... popular!
Pulpy, huh?
Hmm?
[Mamimi] Your drink.
You like the kind
with pulp now, Chief?
[Naota] Well, I don't like
the sour ones, you know that.
[Mamimi] And Haru-san?
Likes the pulp?
I was watching.
I saw you.
It's no big deal. You worried?
[Naota] I don't really
think anything about Haruko.
I guess I don't know how she
feels about me or anything.
But she was just messin' around
today, jumpin' all over me.
But it's always like that.
Well not always
always like that.
I mean that we like
do something like that.
You know what I mean.
It's pretty amazing, really.
You controlling Canti
and then attacking
the Great Lord of Fear
and even saving the city.
You saw all that?
Where were you?
Yeah, you're pretty amazing
lately, Takkun.
Naw, it's no big deal, really.
Although I did actually
save the whole city.
That is true
and everything, but you know.
So, you saw
the whole thing, huh?
[Naota] What?
The water. I me- in the river.
I'm sorry, the attack failed.
I lost the target.
[Kamon] Robots are
different from cyborgs.
It's a horrific enemy.
It flies around like
it's never heard of gravity.
Kitsurubami!
Kitsurubami! What's wrong!
[Hairdresser] Now hold still,
we gotta do the hair color next.
How do you want that,
by the way? Auburn? Chestnut?
Or should we make it
fooly cooly color?
[Amarao] FL CL?
[Haruko] What's with
the eyebrows lover boy?
An attempt at
bushy masculine charm?
Chicks dig the clean-cut look.
That what you were thinking?
Raharu.
Decided to send your
little commando on a mission?
[Naota] Ow!
Why'd you shoot at me?
[Mamimi] There, under your hood.
Is it FLCL again?
You're really
too amazing, Takkun.
You drink the pulp now,
and you do fooly cooly
and you do googly googly
and drooly drooly.
When did you start
to change and grow up
and everything, Takkun?
Is it because of Haru-sa?
Is she changing you?
[Naota] You mean,
ya mean that...
Come with me.
No! Stay away!
I'm not a child anymore.
I'm an adult.
I can buy my own insurance
and everything.
That robot is too dangerous.
If we don't take it out, Medical
Mechanica will make its move.
You understand they're willing
to activate the plan
for that purpose,
and you know what
that'd do to this planet.
And that thing.
When that thing turns red,
it's Atomsk.
[Haruko] Too easy.
[Men in Black]
Hold it! Stay right there!
Don't move!
Don't even think about it!
Quiet!
You can't be real.
[Naota]
Like I said, it's nothing.
She's just like, a really
ditzy girl, that's all.
[Naota] Why are you
pulling me so hard?
It hurts, Takkun.
I mean it.
Ever since she came here,
bad things started happening,
like I never get to just
be with you anymore.
It was better
the way it was before.
"Take a rest here"
So, let's get something here.
Why are you doing this
all of a sudden?
I just wanna hang out
here with you.
What's wrong with that?
Takkun, you're not supposed
to do things like this with me.
[Naota] Why not?
We're here.
[Mamimi] This is
'cause of Haru-san.
[Naota] She has
nothing to do with this.
[Mamimi] You like Haru-sa.
[Naota] How can I like
someone who's insane?
[Mamimi]
How much do you like her?
[Naota] I don't.
You've got it all wrong.
It's you that I-
[Mamimi] Takkun, don't lie.
You like her.
What's the matter?
I thought you liked me too.
I know you do.
Ow, watch where
you point that thing.
[Masashi] Wow,
that can't be good.
Where are my eyebrows?
Look at that!
Medical Mechanica's
transporting these monstrosities
here to destroy this planet.
It's all over.
Don't you see
what's happening here?
You're such a drama queen.
Figure it out!
You're the one
who caused all this.
I don't care, ya got it?
Your guitar's not
up to it, that's it.
You are a million years
under-evolved. Primitive Monkey!
That's discriminatory language
used against
under-developed planets.
[Haruko] Furi-kuri furi-kura
furi-kuri furi-kura
You can't do that here!
Where are my eyebrows?
I gotta find my eyebrows.
Uh, where are they?
[Haruko] Small, as usual.
Guess that's
the best you can do, huh?
Takkun's a lot manlier, pyon.
[Amarao] You're toying
with my feelings again.
Damn you.
What do you see
in that grade school kid?
What's he got
that I haven't got?
[Naota] Hold on!
[Naota] Haruko!
Daikon V! Yeah!
Stop it, Haruko!
Tasuku, help me, sempai!
[Naota] My brother?
[Mamimi] I don't
wanna be here anymore.
Help me, Tasuku-sempai.
Don't call my brother.
Tasuku-sempai, Tasuku-sempai,
Tasuku-sempai, Tasuku-sempai...
[Naota] I'm the one who's here.
--Hey, look at me.
--[Mamimi] sempai, sempai,
sempai, sempai
--I'm the one
who's gonna save you.
--[Mamimi] sempai, sempai,
sempai, sempai
Canti!
Now listen.
My name is Naota.
Don't ever call me
Takkun again.
Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah!
Pyon.
Huh?
Useless.
Chance.
[Gaku] It's falling!
Back up! Back up!
[Masashi]
Huh? Where's reverse?
[Eri] What, what?
Naota's-
wife.
Final round.
"I'm the Hitman 3"
[Masashi] Blockbusters.
I'm all out of ammo.
[Kitsurubami] Commander!
[Amarao] I told you
this was impossible.
[Amarao] This is bad.
He's headed for the plant.
He's going to activate it.
What's that?
It's... It's...
It's Atomsk's...
[Amarao and Haruko]
...Gibson EB-0, 1961 model.
He's really the one.
[Amarao]
It's the real pirate king.
"I'm the Hitman 3"
[Haruko] Atomsk.
[Eri] Ouch.
The sky paints an orange slide.
And pride dangles like a sponge.
Spider... The taste of
capturing something alive.
You don't have to deny it.
I want to dream in color.
Ride on shooting star...
With the voice in my heart,
I sang out like a shotgun.
Grungy hamster--acting adult.
Revengeful lobster--
drag him along.
Sniper... At the edge of
the world, what can you see?
Before I aim I want to touch it.
Ride on shooting star...
I was looking for you.
Through my withdrawal,
I was lying.
Ride on shooting star...
With the voice in my heart,
I sang out like a shotgun.
"Next Episode"
[Haruko] Well, we're winding
down to the final episode,
but there's not
much to talk about.
You must have a lot
of questions by now,
but who knows if
they'll ever be answered.
So, Mr. Director,
how is this gonna end?
Next on FLCL, Episode 6:
"Fully Climaxed."
Hey...
"FLCLimax"
What does FLCL mean anyway?