Yeeah... Ahh!
[yells]
[Haruko] Oh, yeah. Uh-huh.
Thank you, thank you.
[Player] Ah, it's
comin' outta left field.
[sighs]
That girl is brutal.
Every single time at bat,
she had an
out-of-the-park homerun.
"Mars"
You know the last one she hit?
I think it escaped
the earth's gravity.
Where the hell'd
she come from anyway?
"Fire"
Do you know, coach?
[grumbling]
[Haruko] Yes, thank you.
Hey there, do you have
any other hidden talents?
Haruko-san's a
pain in the old rear.
[Long-haired player]
Haruko?
[Shigekuni] It's pathetic.
Pathetic, do you hear me?
That our team, the Martians,
who are supposed to explode
with the eruptions of Olympus,
couldn't get a single run.
[Baseball Player 3]
Situation beyond our control.
With Tasuku-chan in the U.S.,
we're out our best player.
[Baseball Player 4]
Yeah, it's been like this
since they built that
new medical plant thing.
[Shigekuni] You're not trying
hard enough, that's the problem.
[Baseball Player 4] The ability
to try hard's a talent, too.
[Baseball Player 3] We only
had Tasuku-chan's bat.
[Baseball Player 5] The only
help we got is his brother,
if you call that help.
[Players]
C'mon kid, you can do it!
[Shigekuni] Go!
[Umpire] Strike!
[Naota yells]
[groaning]
[Umpire] Dead!
Dead ball!
[Long-haired player]
Who knows if he's any good,
he hasn't swung
the bat all game.
[Baseball Player 5]
So much for Olympus.
This is an extinct volcano.
[Baseball Player 3]
Aw, we need a star player...
to do for our team what
she's doing for theirs.
[flabbergasted]
[Everyone]
Huh?
Is that even possible?
Check it out!
Tomorrow's game is in the bag.
[laughing]
[Shigekuni]
Now we have a secret weapon.
[Everyone cheering]
It looks good on you.
New style? The bandage look?
Whatever.
I don't care about baseball.
You are a big liar.
Cut it out. Hey!
[motorcycle engine]
[Haruko] Anyway...
Nothing can happen
'til you swing the bat.
"Full Swing"
I'm back.
Grub?
Hey, welcome home, Naota-kun.
Dinner'll be ready soon, okay?
[Haruko moaning]
[Haruko] It hurts!
Not so hard.
[chopping]
[Kamon] Ah, I'm sorry,
Haruko-san.
What are you doing to her?
Yeah, right there.
Your chin hair is-
Electric massage really works.
Anything wrong?
You're all sweaty.
You could at least change
out of your uniform.
Your uniform's not
sweaty. Wonder why.
Oh, I'm too tired to
hold a pair of chopsticks.
Why you playing for their team?
You don't even live there.
What's up with that?
Part-time job.
I thought I should help out
with the electric bill here.
[groaning]
[Kamon] Here, Haruko-san.
[Both moaning suggestively]
[Naota] What are you doing?
[Haruko] You're the one
I met first.
[innocently] Hmmm?
[Naota] Just forget it.
Aren't you going
to have dinner?
Come on, we're
having your favorite:
genetically altered
fermented soybeans.
[thud]
[Amarao] Oh man.
Don't hit it with
a baseball bat.
Try a baguette, you know,
a loaf of French bread.
Huh?
[Amarao] This is your home,
right?
And it's also a bakery?
"Super-spicy"
Super spicy, huh?i
Didn't carry this
before, did you?
[distant moaning]
You ever feel like there's
a lot of extra unwanted
stuff in your life?
People should be
more ambiguous.
You agree?
I don't know.
[Amarao] As you force yourself
to eat the spicy bread,
you get addicted to it. Right?
I hate that stuff.
It's terrible.
Really?
But it seems that she's addicted
to you in a certain sense.
[Amarao] Any idea why?
[Naota] Those eyebrows.
Playing it close to the vest?
That means you're smart.
Word to the wise: don't tell
too many people about her.
You'll find out what you're
dealing with eventually.
She's a menace. Enough said.
[Kamon and Haruko
giggling and moaning]
Can I have a receipt for this?
"Mabase"
Older women can have
a very strong effect.
A very painful effect.
[Haruko laughing distantly]
[Kamon] Oh, Haruko-san.
[Haruko upchucking]
[Naota] Adults are
really stupid.
[Mamimi] Did you
have an argument?
[Naota] I'm not going
to argue with her.
[Mamimi chuckling]
That's very mature
of you, Chief.
[Naota] What are you
trying to say?
[Mamimi] Why you in
such a bad mood?
Huh, Takkun?
I wanna leave my mark again.
Batting practice at sunset?
Do you want me
to be your coach?
No, thanks!
I could teach you how.
[Naota] Go play some more
games with my dad.
Leave me alone.
[Haruko] We're in this together.
Your head is the only
one that works, Takkun.
You'll be able to hit
a homerun soon. Promise!
[Haruko] Yeah, yeah, that's
the right stance.
But, you have
to swing the bat.
[surprised]
Hit it into the sky.
Don't hold back.
Before he swings the bat,
a real slugger imagines
an arc inside his heart.
Arching directly to Heaven.
There. That star'd
make a perfect target.
It's kinda flickery
though. See?
[Female voice] Heat tolerances
are above scale.
[Male voice] Tracking sub-light
velocity and gaining.
[Female voice]
Atmospheric approach.
"Outskirts of Mabase"
Imminent.
[Male voice]
Radiation levels
"Immigration Dept. CP"
increased by a factor of ten.
[Female voice] It has
entered the atmosphere.
Minus 2200.
[Kitsurubami] Alright, we have
it on screen.
It's been ten
hours since impact.
We experienced a
total loss of control.
After it cause
irreparable damage
to sectors six through eleven
and displaced all
three antennas,
including the spare,
it made a quantum leap into
the central processing sector
and scored a direct
hit on the core unit.
This is satellite Shiosaki,
it's proceeding with its
self-programmed attack.
Commander Amarao?
No, I'm pretty sure
it's not poisonous.
[Female voice] It's
going into freefall.
"Shigekuni's"
It's Kitsurubami, right?
Can you dispose of this?
Sir?
[Amarao] You didn't know?
Well now you do.
I don't like it spicy.
[Kitsurubami] Those eyebrows.
So, where's it going to fall?
Where'd she go now?
[Kamon and Haruko moaning]
[Kamon] Haruko-san.
[Haruko] Ah, look,
it's so pathetic.
[Kamon] Haruko-san.
[Haruko] C'mere.
I'm gonna stick it in.
[both moaning]
[Haruko] Why won't it stand up?
It's 'cause of this
extra layer thing.
[Haruko gasps]
[yells]
I got it.
We're locked on the beacon.
I knew it.
It's Mabase.
Huh?
[Kitsurunami] Eyebrows.
[Umpire] Play ball!
[Shigekuni] Alright!
Show no mercy!
[Baseball player] My mother
hits better than this guy.
[Mamimi] That must be the
Great Emperor of Fear I bet.
[Naota] What are you
talking about?
[Mamimi] Nostradamus
predicted it,
but he must have got lost.
Don't you think?
[horn beeping]
Haru-san!
The game is already
started, you guys.
Are you doing that
perverted stuff again?
You're the one
who's perverted.
Then let's get ready
and swing the bat.
You want Takkun?
But he's not the type
to actually swing
the bat, you know?
[Naota] I don't play baseball.
[Haruko] It's Canti's
first game today.
[Mamimi] Lord Canti?
[choking]
Wait up, I gotta see this!
Yeah, well those homeruns you
hit yesterday were no big deal.
And I don't want you
coaching me anymore!
[quiet footsteps]
[floor creaking]
[Kamon] Oh, I didn't know
you were here.
[Kamon] Uh-oh. Give me
a break, Haruko-san.
I told her not to
leave any marks.
[chuckling]
I didn't want
you to see them.
It makes... me blush.
You see, it's just
that Haruko-san and I
have that kind of relationship.
What kind?
[voice changing to Haruko's]
Mouth-to-mouth.
Mouse?
[meow]
[Haruko] You're the one
I saw first, Takkun.
[growling]
[Haruko] It has to be you,
Takkun.
That's how life is.
Sometimes you're the cat,
sometimes the mouse.
[Broken robotic voice] See, I
couldn't get myself up before.
It was all covered.
You understand.
But Haruko-san
fixed it for me.
I can walk now.
Now Takkun.
Shut up!
[crash]
Yaaa!
[screaming]
[Long-haired baseball player]
Like I said, she's brutal.
[Baseball player] She's doing
it on purpose, for sure.
[whistling]
[alarm]
Huh?
[Female Announcer] A state
of emergency has been declared
in Mabase City.
All citizens please evacuate
the city immediately.
Repeat. Evacuate at once.
This is an emergency.
[Amarao] Nandaba, Naota.
6th grade.
Mabase Elementary School.
Father Nandaba, Kamon.
Owns a bakery. 47 years old.
Up until ten years ago, he
worked in publishing in Tokyo
where he was the assistant
editor of a subculture magazine.
One month ago,
an unknown woman identifying
herself as Haruhara Haruko
took up residence
in the same household.
You could have hit him
with a loaf of French bread.
I didn't hit him with anything.
That bat must've really hurt.
I didn't hit my father.
Have a drink.
I didn't hit anyone.
[splash]
Here. You like sweet things.
Sweet drinks
taste better, right?
I hit the television,
that's all I did.
You hit the TV.
It was an accident.
[Amarao] Mmm?
So you're the type of person
who can only use your bat
to swing at machines,
not on the field, huh?
On the field?
An older woman.
That's a big mistake.
Swinging my bat
out on the field?
Here you are, fighting
with your father
for a woman who's
not even worth it.
[Naota] Haruko has nothing
to do with this.
[Amarao] Haruko.
You call her by
her first name.
You must be very close.
[Naota] What do you care?
[Amarao] She's your batting
coach, isn't she?
[Naota] I hate her.
[Amarao] Do you like her...
swing?
[Naota] I told you. Haruko has
nothing to do with this.
Then why did you
hit him with that bat?
I didn't! I told you!
[Naota] You hit your
own television?
Yes, because I was--
[coffee spilling]
[Amarao] Because you were
jealous of Dad? Hmm?
Yes, that's it.
You were simply caught
in the middle of something.
I'm sure you've
heard her speak of
the Galaxy Space
Police Brotherhood
and the pirate lord, Atomsk.
Make sure you don't tell anyone
that you spoke to me here
or what we spoke about.
That's very important.
And that includes your father.
Huh?
Well, she is very alluring.
It's not your fault.
You're just her
current victim.
Eyebrows.
[Amarao] What about eyebrows?
[Naota] N-Nothing.
[Female Annoncer] A state of
emergency has been declared
in Mabase City.
All citizens, please evacuate
the city immediately.
Repeat. Evacuate at once.
No fooly cooly.
This is an emergency.
Please proceed in
an orderly fashion.
You are advised to
leave Mabase City at once.
A state of emergency
has been declared.
All citizens-
[buzzing]
[meow]
[yelling]
[freaking out]
[screaming and crashing]
Oh!
Oooh!
[Mamimi] Follow
the trembling thunder!
And the great rumble!
Welcome, Lord of Fear! Hail!
[laughing]
You see, it was worth
invoking his presence,
even after the
prediction failed.
[motorcycle engine]
[Kamon groans weakly]
I guess you prefer your real
father after all, huh Naota?
I wasn't any good
for Haruko-san at all.
She asked if she could use
my head and I gladly agreed,
but I guess
I actually died for a while.
[Amarao] N.O. utilizes
the right brain
and left brain's distinct
thought processes
to open up an
inter-dimensional channel,
capable of pulling
things through,
sometimes from
light years away,
in an instant.
But you can't just
use anyone's head.
You gotta find
the right one.
[Kamon] Yeah, yeah.
Haruko-san is not your
ordinary houseguest.
[crashing and screaming]
[Amarao] What you encountered
was a kind of high-tech
mannequin that looked
like your father.
The equivalent of
a vending machine.
When the chips are down,
few people can
really swing the bat.
Right now, there's
a satellite carrying a bomb,
falling rapidly
toward this city.
It's too late
for this evacuation.
No one will survive.
That's why I want you
to go home and tell her.
Tell her she's gotta hit
one more outta the park.
Tell her it's a request
from a hometown fan.
Yo.
[Naota] What's up with
this robot thing?
[Kamon] I'm embarrassed.
[Naota] Who're you really?
I'm an illusion
of your youth,
a manifestation of the feelings
in your adolescent part.
[Naota] Where'd you get
that line from? Anime?
There's a satellite coming down,
you know.
A double-header
takes a lot out of you.
Tell the hometown fan
that it's gonna be expensive.
I say we file a complaint!
No.
[Amarao] The satellite bomb
was our secret backup
in case of dire emergency.
We can't let it go public.
She really is a terror
though, isn't she?
Raharu.
[Kitsurubami] Raharu?
Haruha Raharu.
Her plan is to penetrate us,
the foreign embassy,
and the Medical Mechanica.
That's why she made
this whole thing happen.
And she's willing to destroy
a whole town to pull it off.
[Kitsurubami] That poor kid.
[yelling]
[Mamimi] If that thing
comes down here,
you think they'll
cancel school tomorrow?
[Naota] Isn't this where it's
heading?
[Haruko] This spot would have
the least amount of damage.
And here we go!
Hey!
What are you doing to me?
[Haruko] Just hold still.
Hey, I didn't know
boys felt like this inside.
[Naota] Ah, don't touch me there
from behind.
Ah, easy!
[screaming]
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up and pop it!
If I rush it won't pop!
Go slow.
What? What's that?
[Haruko] Your bat.
Impressive.
He's only a little kid.
Tracking altitude.
Now entering final descent.
Purge sequence initiate.
[explosion]
[Female voice] It's breaking
through the lower atmosphere.
[Haruko] Now, if you do it
just the way I showed you,
it'll be just perfect.
It's okay?
Hey, here it comes.
Keep your eye on it. Ready?
Ready?
That boy is-
That kid'll never pull it off.
Impact is imminent.
Huh? But... it's impossible.
Haruko? Haruko?
No, it's spinning.
It's a sinker.
Tasuku.
Maybe when the chips are down,
he's too scared
to swing the bat himself.
Depending on what he does,
to all you folks out there,
sayonara!
It's pushing him back.
He swung the bat.
Oh no! It's going to blow up!
Takkun.
He really swung the bat.
[Naota] By the time I realized
it, it was over.
I'd already done it.
The palm of my hand
still stings.
I wonder if Haruko
feels like this all the time.
[laughing]
[Amarao] Crisis report.
[Female voice] All systems
online and functioning
at normal capacity.
The satellite achieved
escape velocity at gamma four,
bomb neutralized.
Satellite en route
to galaxies unknown.
[Amarao] Rat.
Orange no slide utsusu sora.
Sponge no pride burasagete.
Spider... Iketotta
sono yokan wa
kakusanaku tatte ii'n da.
Iro no tsuita yume mitai na.
Ride on shooting star...
Kokoro no koe de sandanjuu
no you ni utai tsuzuketa.
Grunge no hamster--otona bite.
Revenge no lobster--
hiki tsurete.
Sniper... Fuchidotta
sono sekai ni
nani ga mieru'tte iu'nda?
Nerau mae ni sawaritai na.
Ride on shooting star...
Kimi wo sagashite
kindanshoujou-chuu
uso wo tsuita.
Ride on shooting star...
Kokoro no koe de sandanjuu
no you ni utai tsuzuketa.
[Haruko] When you see
a John Woo film,
it's comforting to know how
shallow the world really is.
The full force of
the manly coolness factor,
with a piece of nose hair
sticking out from
the tiny crack between
manly and cool,
exposes the thinness
of the male hormone factor.
Next, on FLCL, Episode 5:
"Brittle Bullet."
It takes an idiot
to do cool things.
"Brittle Bullet"
That's why it's cool.