[Mamimi] Legs spread,
same width as the shoulders.
Body tight, then hit the ball
like you're defeating the enemy.
Here, the pinky
finger is the key.
And then you just
hit, hit, hit.
Kakkin bingo!
[Naota] What are
you talking about?
[Mamimi] He who
conquers the left side
conquers the world, Chief.
Setting the parameters.
That's really the hard part.
[Naota] Are you talking
about a video game?
Hm?
Takkun, what are you doing?
[Naota] Homework.
[Mamimi] Then why don't
you do it at home?
It's not cool.
You can do my homework too,
if you want, huh?
Mm? Your hands are upside down.
Eh? [Mamimi fumbles]
You should play
baseball, too, Takkun.
Why do you always
carry around a bat?
[Naota] Why do you always
hang around here by the river?
Because, you know...
Huh? Now why was it?
You're in a good mood.
Huh?
[Naota] You smell
like cigarettes.
The strong ones.
I haven't been smoking.
[Naota] Mamimi, why do
you always do this?
[Mamimi] Earlobes.
[Naota] Mm? Ow!
[Mamimi] If I don't
do it, I'll overflow.
[Naota] What do you mean?
What'll happen?
[Mamimi] Probably
something amazing.
[Naota] Ahh!
[Naota's voice] Nothing
amazing happens here.
Everything is ordinary.
The huge factory that can
be seen from our town,
the Medical Mechanica plant...
All the adults got excited
when it came here.
Like it was really a big thing.
The white steam that billows
out every day at the same time.
It looked to me like smoke that
signified some kind of omen.
Smoke that spreads out
and covers everything.
"Fooly Cooly"
[Naota] Uh--
You know I don't
like sour drinks.
Pfaaah... Huh?
Oh, look, a mark. Wow.
How 'bout a Band-Aid?
Here.
[Naota] What?
[Mamimi] It's yours, isn't it?
There's more than
half left, Chief.
You know what?
My brother, in the U.S....
Alright! Lunch time!
[Naota grunts]
[Haruko] Already?
Takkun.
[Haruko] Stop!
Ah? Mm...
Hm?
Native girl must stop!
Taro-kun just hit his head,
so you can't move
him yet. Understand?
[Mamimi] Ah...
Ah-- But he isn't Taro-kun...
[Haruko gasps]
He's dead. This young
boy is completely dead,
just as Taro would be.
But he's not Taro, like I said.
--[Haruko] Oh, I killed him.
--[Mamimi] His name's Naota.
--I finally find the SOB,
and I killed him.
--I call him Takkun though.
--I didn't mean to,
it was an accident. Kinda.
--It's kind of cute,
don't you think?
Aw, let's face it;
I definitely,
totally killed him,
just like that.
Bang!
No, more like Bong! Kablam!
Or Kunk-Kunk-Splat!
Yeah. Yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah.
Yeeeah...
Ay!
Ah...?
Come back to life!
Aaah...!
Smooch!
Waaah--!!
Those slow motion scenes
are really tough, huh?
Yeah, you have to hold
your breath until they cut.
You can get cramps
from that, you know?
[Naota] What? I thought
it was a special effect!
You're doing the slow motion?
"It's wrong."
[muffled sounds
from Naota]
Ahh! Alright! And
Taro-kun is back.
He's not Taro, okay?
Oh, really? That
was close, then.
'Cause if it was Taro,
he woulda just turned
into another statistic.
Death by motorbike.
I lucked out!
Round two.
Knock out?
Yo--Yoisho...
Here we go!
It's not coming out.
Guess I better hit him again.
Stop!
He hit his head, alright.
You said yourself you
shouldn't move him.
Tch...
[Naota moans
and groans]
What did you do to me?
CPR.
What do you think I did?
That's not what I meant.
Did she put her tongue inside?
You are useless!
What are you talking about?
Bleh!
[Naota and Mamimi yelp]
She's very fast.
She's at least twenty years old.
You need a doctor?
A stupid adult who doesn't
know how to grow up.
Does it hurt?
Ow! Ow, ow, ow,
ow, ow, ow, ow...
It doesn't look like
a normal bump.
I can't go to the
hospital like this.
[Naota mumbles]
Ow... Ow...
Guess I just need to hold it.
Ah! What'll I do in
school tomorrow?
Ow! Ow, ow, ow,
ow, ow, ow, ow...
[Gaku] Did you hear?
She was around yesterday!
--[Masashi] For reals?
--[Eri] That really
looks bizarre.
[Gaku] Yeah, isn't it awesome?
You're hiding
something, huh? C'mon.
Don't be such a brat.
Naota, Naota, didja hear?
--What?
--[Gaku] The Vespa Woman!
Vespa?
"Vespa: 1. wasp, hornet"
A wasp woman?
She has a guitar.
And a cool Yuusaku bike.
Not exactly.
Some girl in the
other class had her
super spicy curry bread stolen.
Super spicy?
And when she stings,
she leaves a demon's mark
that shows you've been
doing naughty things,
and it never goes away!
What naughty things?
Uh, well...
Like something
really perverted.
Gyah! Perverted?
So, what's that mark?
It's the mark of the demon!
[Masashi] Really? Let me see.
[Naota] There's nothing
to see. Cut it out!
[Gaku] Didja see her, Naota?
[Masashi] Did she sting ya?
[Gaku] Pervert! He's a pervert!
[Naota] What are
you talking about?
[Gaku] Pervert!
[Naota's voice] Nothing
amazing happens here.
Everything is ordinary.
So it's not a punishment, like
when I go see Samejima Mamimi.
It's just something I always do.
It's ordinary.
After school, I decided
to go to the hospital.
I didn't wanna think
about Vespa Woman.
[Haruko] Hmm, yeah,
this is just right.
Has a good feel, too.
So what happened
yesterday after I left?
Did something happen?
Hey, something
did happen, right?
Like something weird?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
What's that? A pimple?
Looks kind of sick. Putrefied.
You're not hiding
something, are you? Ah--
Uh...
"MM Branch Hospital"
[Nurse] Hmm...
FLIctonic KLIpple
Waver Symptom?
Uhh... FL? CL?
Adolescent psychological
skin hardening syndrome.
It's a common disease
where children grow horns
from trying too hard.
That's a lie. I never
heard that before.
[Nurse] Yeah, I lied.
[Nurse/Haruko] So
what is the truth...
[Haruko] ...underneath
the Band-Aid?
[Haruko and Naota yell]
Ah! What are you
doing in the hospital?
Stay right there.
I'm gonna make
you feel all better.
[Naota wails]
It's my special treat!
"Medical Mechanica Hospital"
[Haruko] Huh? Where'd he go?
Hey!
Hey! Taro-kun!
"Bread Shigekuni"
[Naota] Photos?
"Closed temporarily-Management"
I don't need to see that.
No, I'm busy.
I don't care.
Go out with your friends.
[disconnect tone]
[Naota sighs]
Hm?
[Naota] I dreamed
about my brother.
He was batting and I was
dazzled by his swing.
It seemed impossible
that anything
could have been so perfect.
Nao, dinner!
Ahh! It's you, the Vespa Woman!
[Kamon] Why are you yelling?
[Shigekuni] Hurry up
and sit down.
[Haruko] Hi!
[Naota shudders]
[Kamon] Ah, I just hired
her to work for us.
Her name's Haruhara.
[Haruko] Haruko. Pleasure.
[Kamon] I got run over,
you know. Smashed.
[Naota] By her Vespa?
[Shigekuni] It
shoulda killed him.
[Kamon] But instead,
we got you a live-in
housekeeper out
of it, didn't we?
[Naota] Are you
feeling okay, Grandpa?
I mean-- You got a housekeeper?
A housekeeper?
[Haruko] I was watching Taro-kun
who was making out with
a high school girl.
[Kamon] Fondling her yum-yums?
[Naota] I told you,
I'm not Taro!
[Kamon] Fondling her cupcakes?
[Naota] Augh!
[Kamon] Who's the slut
you're fooling around with?
Huh? Huh?
[Naota] Ma-Mamimi. We
were down at the river!
[Kamon] Really, Mamimi?
[Shigekuni] I bet she
does it like a weasel.
She's cursed I tell ya.
[Kamon] Ah, your
brother is away,
so she's sinking her
fangs into you, Naota.
Fondling around. Fooling
around. Fooly cooly!
What's fooly cooly?
[Naota] How should I know?
I'm still in grade school.
You think I'm that crazy?
[Kamon] Ha ha... Ha, ha, ha!
That's what it is,
Naota's Gundam Hammer.
--[Naota] Huh?
--[Kamon] It's that
Tomino-esque thing...
saying it's Gundam,
but basically,
it's giant robot anime, right?
[Naota] I don't know
what you're talking about!
[Kamon] Nao's just like me,
so he must be doing it.
I know he's doing it.
Doing doing and fooly-coolying.
[Haruko] I see, pretty
impressive, little bro.
So, what do you think,
Haruko-san?
--[Haruko] What do ya...
--[Kamon] Oh, cooly cooly,
like that?
--[Haruko] Kool-Aid?
--[Kamon] Not like curry powder
aphrodisiac licked off my desk.
--[Haruko] Death.
--[Kamon] It's this kind of
cooly cooly new modality.
--[Haruko] Noodle?
--[Kamon] I mean like MTV!
--[Haruko] Empty?
--[Kamon] Oh, Former
Assistant Editor-in-Chief!
I didn't know you had such
a lovely young wife.
Ooh hoo hoo hoo! Cooly cooly!
Yeah, it's kind of a
cooly cooly dream thing!
[Shigekuni] Yeah, cooly cooly
is... ya do it like this
with your hands, see?
[Haruko] Oh, right.
I'm already in that kinda
relationship with Takkun here.
[Shigekuni] Relationship?
[Shigekuni &amp; Kamon]
How do you mean?
[Haruko] Mouth to mouth...
M... M-M... Mouth?
[Shigekuni]
Cooly cooly cooly...
[Haruko] I told you to
shut up about that!
[Kamon] So, living
in the same house,
you two are already
fooly cooly, I see.
[Naota] Who cares if
it's fooly or cooly?
[Kamon] But you're
still thinking about
doing it tonight, aren't you?
[Naota] Stop acting like a kid!
[Kamon] With that
kind of perverted
cooly cooly kind of dream,
you must be hiding it underneath
this Band-Aid, aren't you?
[Naota] Aah! I'm not
hiding anything!
Band-Aid.
[Shigekuni] Cooly cooly cooly...
[Haruko] Oh...
[Kamon] I'm stuffed!
--I made a total pig of myself.
--[Shigekuni] This
bread is delicious!
[Haruko, Kamon and Shigekuni
chatter indistinctly]
[Naota] They're in a good mood.
Oh, well... They
say they're making
some kinda medical
machines or something.
Yeah. Uh-uh. I don't
know that yet.
Yes, that's true.
You got a point.
The channel is
imperfect, and the kid
I found here is pretty useless.
Uh--
[meow]
Ask before you come in.
I see the bottom's yours,
so I'll sleep on top.
Really?
Who are you, and
what do you want?
I'm just a wandering
housekeeper.
Tell me the truth.
I'm an alien.
Right, and this afternoon
you were a nurse.
What's underneath the Band-Aid?
[Naota gasps]
You're really...freaky.
Under the Band-Aid,
what's it like? Tell me.
I don't know.
You're lying.
You saw it.
Something strange is happening.
What are you hiding
under the Band-Aid?
You did it, didn't you?
You should know
about your own head.
Because you hit me there!
[Haruko] Let's see it!
[Naota] You came
here with my father!
Why don't you go
stay with him?!
What do you want?
You're the one I
saw first, Takkun.
Anyway, the top bunk
is my brother's,
so no one else can sleep there.
[Naota] That's the way it is.
So, how old is your brother?
Where is he?
[Naota] America.
[Haruko] Why?
[Naota] Baseball.
[Haruko] Oh, he's really
a good player, huh?
Ah! You're sleeping here?
Is this where you're
sleeping, huh?
It's the only place.
The top belongs to
your brother, right?
[Naota shudders]
[Naota] Aw, she's
playin' with my head.
[Kamon] Naota-kun.
[Naota] Huh?
[Kamon] We need to talk.
[Naota] About what?
[Kamon] About Haruko-san.
You're against her
staying here, aren't you?
Do whatever you want.
Hm. I named you
"Naota" for honesty.
So it would appear...
you were run over too.
[Naota] Mamimi was here?
[Kamon] She asked for
some of the day-old bread
we've got on sale.
It's a Mimi type of thing.
A dreamy type of thing.
Is Mamimi's family poor,
would you say? Huh?
[Naota pants]
He's alright.
[meow]
[distant footsteps
growing louder]
[Naota pants]
[Mamimi] He gave me... a lot.
[Naota] Did he
send you a letter?
[Naota] Hasn't he
contacted you at all?
[Naota] My brother. I mean,
how much do you like him?
[Mamimi] It's hard.
You saw the sign at our bakery.
That bread's old.
Watermelon.
[Naota] Hm?
[Mamimi] Or like a
panda with a mean face.
Or like sandals with pressure
points drawn on them.
Or the smell of a
blackboard eraser.
Or a Sunday morning where
you wake up and it's raining.
Well, I like him more
than hard bread.
[Naota] Why don't you stop that?
[Naota] You know, he has a...
Oh, no.
[Haruko moans]
Ah? An American girlfriend.
"I got me a blonde gal!"
[Mamimi groans]
No, I must respect your
brother's privacy.
Huh? Uh-oh.
Hey, what's the matter?
[Mamimi] I'm gonna overflow.
Huh?
[Mamimi] I'm gonna overflow!
Whaddya mean?
[Mamimi groans]
[Naota gasps]
[Naota] Mamimi!
Aahhh!
[Naota wheezes]
[Naota struggles]
Aahh!
[Naota groans, yells]
[Naota shudders]
[Naota] It's getting bigger.
[Naota yells]
[Naota moans]
[Naota] Where's Mamimi?
[Naota lurches]
What's going on?
[Naota wails]
Ah!
[Naota groans]
[Naota moans]
[Naota gasps]
[Haruko sighs]
[Naota coughs]
[Naota coughs] Haruko!
[Haruko yells]
Wow.
[Naota's voice]
As soon as I said that,
I knew I shouldn't have.
In that moment,
just for a flash,
she looked like my brother.
--[Naota] Hey, I'm
stuck on this thing.
--[Haruko] Butta. Butta.
--Hey, come on!
--Where is he?
Unhook me, will ya?
"Store reopened
as of today-Management"
[Naota] Anyway,
the Band-Aid came off.
The horn is gone.
Nothing amazing.
You have to roll
the dough smooth
or the bread'll be lumpy.
--Now get it right this time.
--[Naota's voice] Only the
ordinary happens here.
[Haruko] You call that bread?
[Naota] I gotta go.
[approaching footsteps]
[Mamimi] Hm?
[Naota pants]
[Mamimi] You didn't have
to run all the way. Here.
[Naota] Huh?
[Naota] But I said I
don't like sour stuff.
The sky paints an orange slide.
And pride dangles like a sponge.
Spider... The taste of
capturing something alive.
You don't have to deny it.
I want to dream in color.
Ride on shooting star...
With the voice in my heart,
I sang out like a shotgun.
Grungy hamster--acting adult.
Revengeful lobster--
drag him along.
Sniper... At the edge of
the world, what can you see?
Before I aim I want to touch it.
Ride on shooting star...
I was looking for you.
Through my withdrawal,
I was lying.
Ride on shooting star...
With the voice in my heart,
I sang out like a shotgun.
"Next Episode"
[Haruko's voice] The
advance is hip right now,
but the original has
a place in my heart.
Unlike Pocket, there was
only the plastic gray.
Though color had killer app use
for things like
the sewing machine,
not much use for
virtual anymore, huh?
Next on FLCL,
Episode 2: "Fire Starter."
Prepare to get burned.
"Fire Starter"