[Mamimi] I saw God
the other day.
[Mamimi] By the river
on a rainy afternoon.
He helped a kitten that
was left all alone.
It's a god that only I can see.
A black-winged angel
that came down
from the heavens just for me.
[Naota] What are you doing?
[Mamimi] Huh?
"Mabase Elementary School"
Hey, Takkun!
Why are you at my school?
[Mamimi giggles]
I felt like it.
--Geez, aren't you embarrassed?
--[Eri] Who's that? Huh?
It's his wife.
Yeah, he's married.
To an older woman.
[Mamimi] Takkun...
Are they like, dating?
--Oh--!
--What do you want?
[Gaku and Masashi laugh]
She doesn't look very bright.
[Mamimi] What's that thing
on your head, Chief?
--It looks cool.
--[Naota] Cut it out!
--Let me see it. Huh?
--Stop looking at it.
--Huh? Huh?
--I mean it!
That is so not cool.
[Haruko] Okay, stay still.
Look at this. It's empty.
There's no brain.
Didja loose it somewhere?
You're the one that did this.
Don't blame me if you
go around losing things.
Some kids are just freaks.
Look who's talking, Miss Normal.
At least I didn't sprout a robot
out of my head like some people.
By the way, there's
something new there now.
It's weird. Not normal,
these horns sticking out.
The last one turned into a dumb
robot that's living at my house.
Living here!
What's up with that?
And it's all because I
was run over by your bike.
It's a normal Vespa,
go see for yourself.
And you still haven't
taken those clothes back.
People out there are starting
to think you're a real nurse.
Ah! Hey there. Haruhara
Haruko here. Age 19.
Splendiferous housekeeper
at Takkun's house.
She's older than that.
But my true identity is this...
[drumroll]
[guitar strum]
[Haruko] First Class
Space Patrol Officer.
[Haruko] Uh--
What a lame stage name.
[Naota grunts]
Chill out. We're not
going on Star Search.
That hurt! Why'd Miyu Miyu
get on your case yesterday?
[meow]
Because I'm in trouble.
Lots of trouble.
Because of Takkun,
they're all on my case.
What is this thing anyway?
How does a robot
take x-rays like that?
Because he's a Medical
Mechanica robot, probably.
Didn't you know that?
They make them there.
Why'd he come out of my head?
Yeah, that's what I wanna know.
What's your connection with
Medical Mechanica, huh? Huh?
--Huh? Huh? Huh?
--[Naota] That hurts!
Hey, cut it out!
[Naota's voice] Exactly
where does the truth end
and the lies begin?
Samejima Mamimi
and Haruhara Haruko.
A lot of lies are
flowing around me.
These two new horns
that sprang up...
A true story that
seems like a lie.
"Fire Starter"
[Kamon] Move it. Move it.
Well, since you don't
have any nifty functions,
you can at least make yourself
useful around the house.
Hey! You're using
him outside again?
[Kamon] No, no,
this one goes in first.
The neighbors
have eyes, you know?
[Kamon] You want
it all to yourself,
because you brought it home.
Aren't we being a
little bit selfish?
It's weird having a
robot in the house.
"Fresh Bread Shigekuni"
[Kamon] Don't worry about it.
So there's a robot in our house.
Think of the symbolism involved
in having a humanoid robot
in a normal household.
Contrast by the abnormal
advance of science,
which is thereby
proven to exist.
Consider the significance
of a human family, N.
The robot is a part of
it and accepted into it,
And the social structure, M,
that makes that possible.
And everyone is
buying Initial D,
Robot Detective K, Nakamori
Akina's Young Girl A...
[Haruko] What's he
talking about?
He wrote a whole book on
the deep mysteries of "Eva."
"Ewa?"
[Kamon] ...actual
meaning of the robot.
That robot was walking
around loose yesterday!
There've been a lot of
fires around here lately.
Yeah, like yesterday.
[Naota gasps]
He deserves a little
free time to himself.
Right, TV Boy?
Uh...?
[cat] Na, na, na...
[Mamimi] Mm?
You're in high school. What
do you think you're doing?
I was playing with Takkun
and my shoes floated away.
With who?
--Takkun.
--Na, na, na...
[Naota] That's his name, too?
[Mamimi] Yeah, Chief,
this Takkun is hungry.
Do you have anything for him?
[Naota] Like what?
[Mamimi] Well, not
like chewing gum.
You saved him? A stray cat?
[Mamimi] I'm like a god, huh?
A protector of the weak.
The god of the black flames.
You know, Lord Canti, Chief!
[Naota] That's a game, right?
The one where you burn down
the city and everything.
[Mamimi] Yeah, I'm addicted.
[Naota] You like games, huh?
Hm? You don't wanna play?
[Naota] I'm too busy.
[Mamimi] Yeah,
you're always busy.
[Naota] 'Cause there's
the bunch of people
I have to take care of. See ya!
[Haruko makes engine noises]
Oh? Oh! Aaaaahhh!
[Haruko struggles]
Aahh! Huh--?
Lady! Lady!
What year is this?
I've never seen parts
like these. Whoa!
You can save your breath.
This girl has no brains at all.
Just take a look at her.
Barges into an off-limits
facility and crashes her bike.
It's been bad enough
here lately without this.
Turns out the fire
yesterday was arson,
and the day before that
the nurse at the hospital
was tied up and all her
clothes were stolen.
There's a lot of depraved
people out there, huh?
Gahh!!
Aren't you embarrassed
to act like that?
Who the hell is this kid?
Your brother?
No. No relation.
I'm from planet Earth.
Then get lost. This is no
place for little kids.
Can't you see we're
working here?
[Haruko] This isn't a
place for people to work.
[Naota] Hm?
There's not even a
door to get in or out.
[Haruko] No doubt
you're thinking,
"Why would a grade-school
kid be my guardian?" Right?
Hold on. You're telling me
this kid's your guardian?
Yeah, I have custody.
It's kind of unusual.
[Haruko] So, you
came for me, huh?
[Haruko] The rain stopped.
I'll give you a reward.
[Naota] Hm?
[Haruko] It's even
better than CPR.
[Naota] Hm?!
He's not here yet, huh?
Huh?
Ah! It's a god.
[cracking noise]
[Mamimi] Uh?
Mm?
[Takkun] Na...
Ah...!
It's a god.
I can see him. He's really real.
That time I was saved, he...
[Haruko] So, you
usually don't come out
to the beach like this, huh?
Not in October.
It's too cold.
[Naota yells]
Hey, that's dangerous!
Your driving sucks.
I'm a very safe driver.
[distant yells]
I don't like scary stuff.
And I don't have a helmet.
Hm. You're scared. Even
though your brain is missing.
[Naota yells]
[Naota's voice]
When you're on a bike,
the ocean's a lot
closer than you think.
The autumn soft wind
went right through
into the back of my nose.
And maybe it's because, like
Haruko said, my head was empty.
"Samejima Mamimi (17)"
Anyway, I'm glad I followed him.
Geez, what if someone sees
it going around like that?
"Haruko Haruhara (?)"
I saw him at 7-11.
"Naota Nandaba (12)"
Huh?
[Haruko] He was reading Hustler.
"Naota Nandaba (12)"
When?
"Samejima Mamimi (17)"
It's so nice.
I wish I could have
him at my house.
Oh, yeah, you're not allowed
"Naota Nandaba (12)"
to have any pets there, are you?
"Haruko Haruhara (?)"
Sameji.
Come on inside, it's cold.
[Mamimi] I'm okay out here.
[Naota]
My grandfather doesn't
"Miyu Miyu (12)"
like her dating my brother.
That's why you're keeping
her out of the house?
She said she doesn't care.
"Takkun (4 months)"
[Takkun] Na na na...
[Mamimi] Ah! He's back!
Ah! What are you doing?
[Naota yells]
Lord Canti!
Canti?
Hail oh god of
dark flames, Cantid!
You are late!
"The stupid clerk
at the store was slow..."
[Naota] Why are you
using him to run errands?
Ick! I told you to get
the kind with the pulp!
Huh? What's up with that one?
Hmm...
[Shigekuni] Hm?
[Mamimi groans]
[Shigekuni] Let's see it!
[Shigekuni] I said
to get the one
with the Anna
Nicole centerfold.
Can't you get anything right?
Grandpa too?
It's Hustler.
[Haruko] That robot's useless.
You're the one who
broke it, Haruko.
Haru-san, you shouldn't do this!
Don't you know that
Canti's a god?
What's she on about?
Oh, it's some video game.
In high school, I guess they
have a lot of free time.
It's not just a game.
The black wings prove it's him.
Don't go out anymore.
Or I'll have to chain you down.
[Haruko yelps]
"Scoop! Mysterious UFO!"
[Kamon] Hey, TV Boy.
Did you record the
Thursday night special?
[Gaku] Over here.
[Eri] This used to be
a boathouse? This thing?
[Gaku] Kinda smells.
[Eri] It says "Do Not Enter."
Then don't follow us, Ninamori.
Don't worry, the police
have already been here.
Oh.
[Masashi] I heard it was arson.
--[Eri] Again?
--[Gaku] Arson! Arson!
[Eri] Probably some
stressed-out housewife, huh?
Just too many dirty dishes.
It's not that.
The UFO zapped it.
Focus Magazine had pictures
and all kinds of stuff.
It was foreign agents.
If it was anything like that,
they'd burn something big,
not a boathouse.
[Gaku] That's true, they'd hit
like a school or something.
[Masashi] There was a school
that burned down, wasn't there?
[Gaku] Yeah, but that
was a long time ago,
when we were all little.
[Eri] Someone burned it down?
You can still see part of it.
It's all ashes.
Hey, what's that?
Ah--
What's she doing?
I don't know. I saw some
girls bullying her yesterday.
[Gaku] What uniform is that?
[Masashi] Shinden High School.
[Gaku] Hmm?
She's in high school?
[Eri] At that age,
it's really pathetic.
Hm?
[Naota gasps]
Ah...!
[Naota's voice] "Fire Starter."
It's a hand-held video game.
No one knows how Endsville,
the city of devils, was created.
--But as soon as it appeared,
--[Mamimi] Ah! Takkun.
--it started to grow
--Can you bring me some sandals?
--and slowly eat up the world.
--My shoes floated away.
You are an agent of Canti,
the god of the black flame.
And you must stop Endsville
from destroying the world.
Your only weapon is flame.
Matches, lighters, fire bombs.
Get the weapon.
Outsmart the firefighters.
Hide from the police.
And torch the city.
Purge its devils.
But you must be careful.
You cannot burn everything.
If the entire city burns down,
there will be no place to live.
Thus your battle is endless.
There is no final victory.
The only thing you can do
is burn and burn and burn.
Your highest goal is to receive
the personal blessing of Canti,
the god of black flame.
[Haruko] Yeah!
[Haruko] No, I haven't been
able to get in touch with him.
Well, I recruited one
of the enemy robots,
but he's useless anyway.
You know, the gears are turning,
but I don't know what--
Ah! Oh! Oh! Ow! Ah! Oh!
[distant sirens wail]
Huh?
[Firefighter]
Please, stand back.
The riverbed.
Ah! Where'd she go?
[Naota's voice] I remember now.
The fire at the elementary
school, six years ago.
[Mamimi] He's the
one who saved me.
[Naota] My brother?
Mamimi] The protector
of the weak, Lord Canti!
[Naota's voice] There were
rumors that it was arson,
but they never
found out for sure.
That's the day Mamimi
and my brother met.
[Mamimi] Fooly cooly,
fooly cooly, fooly cooly...
[Takkun] Na...
[Mamimi] Fooly cooly,
fooly cooly, fooly cooly...
[Mamimi] Why'd you
come down here?
It's kind of late.
You dropped something.
[Mamimi] I don't
need it anymore.
You can have it.
[Naota] This is where you and my
brother went to school, right?
[Takkun] Mew?
[Takkun] Na? Na!
[Mamimi] I hated this place.
[Takkun] Naaa!
He's here?
[Mamimi] And so... I wished
that it would go away.
But it's useless.
Even if it burns down,
the wreckage and ash
are still there.
[Takkun] Na na?
[Mamimi] Look,
Endsville is burning.
Now, Lord Cantid,
bless me with your kiss.
Your absolution.
Kiss me.
[Naota] Ah!
[Haruko] Uh?
[Naota] Ah! Ow!
[Naota grunts]
[Naota] W-What's this?
It's bigger than before!
Oh, no!
There's some weird fat
thing coming out of Takkun.
[Naota grunts, yells]
Takkun!
Wha? How dare you
hurt Takkun?! Huh?
[Takkun] Na na...
[Mamimi sighs]
[Haruko yells]
Whoooa...
[Haruko grunts]
Takkun!
[Mamimi yells]
[Haruko grunts]
Ha!
[Naota grunts]
[Haruko grunts]
[Haruko screams]
Haruko!
Mamimi!
[Naota grunts]
[Naota pants]
No! Look out!
[Naota groans]
[Naota grunts, yells]
[Naota] Tasuku!
[Naota grunts]
Takkun?
[Haruko grunts]
[Naota yells] What are
you doing? Let me go!
Wah-- wah--
Takkun is...
He ate him!
[Naota struggles]
[Naota screams]
Stupid! You're not
Lord Canti at all!
Why'd you have to
go and eat Takkun?
Uh?
Ahh...
[Takkun] Cha na na?
Transformation?
[Mamimi whimpers]
[Haruko] Chance!
Huh? Uh-oh.
[Mamimi] Hm?
Ahh...
[Naota groans]
Takkun!
[Naota grunts]
Takkun, you're all sticky.
Ah... Huh?
[Naota] The ashes
are all blown away.
[Mamimi] And something smells.
[Takkun] Nya...
[distant sirens wail]
[Haruko] Ah, shit!
Let's get outta here.
Ah?
[Takkun] Nnna?
Hey guys, why are you
just standing there?
[Naota's voice]
At the time, I didn't notice
the sirens that were
coming toward us.
I don't know where the lies
end and the truth begins.
I asked myself what I
could do for Mamimi.
I decided to stay by her side.
Forever.
Orange no slide utsusu sora.
Sponge no pride burasagete.
Spider... Iketotta
sono yokan wa
kakusanaku tatte ii'n da.
Iro no tsuita yume mitai na.
Ride on shooting star...
Kokoro no koe de sandanjuu
no you ni utai tsuzuketa.
Grunge no hamster--otona bite.
Revenge no lobster--
hiki tsurete.
Sniper... Fuchidotta
sono sekai ni
nani ga mieru'tte iu'nda?
Nerau mae ni sawaritai na.
Ride on shooting star...
Kimi wo sagashite
kindanshoujou-chuu
uso wo tsuita.
Ride on shooting star...
Kokoro no koe de sandanjuu
no you ni utai tsuzuketa.
[Haruko's voice]
Anime directors like cats,
because they don't have
to take care of them.
You know, they can't even
take care of themselves.
Oshii is probably the only
director that loves dogs.
He thinks he's a dog himself.
Next on FLCL, Episode 3:
"Marquis de Carabas"
Guess which one
of the sound effects
is from a real cat at Gainax.
"Marquis de Carabas"