[Secretary smacks lips]
You handled that well.
The mayor was worried
you'd be upset,
but you listened very calmly.
I guess. Anyway, this is
between the two of them.
[Secretary] You're very
mature. It's impressive.
When I was your age, I didn't
understand things like this.
If they both want to split up,
then there's really
nothing I can do about it.
Well, that's very
level-headed of you.
Don't worry.
I won't do anything
to ruin your
father's reputation.
I promise.
It's okay. I'm not worried.
You seem like a smart secretary.
You slept over last night,
but you put on a different
suit this morning.
Well, well, that's
very observant.
[Secretary] And, uh,
you have extra clothes too.
Why's that?
[Eri] It's a costume.
For the school play.
I got the lead role!
"Marquis de Carabas"
[engine revving noise
in the background]
[Naota moans lightly]
[Naota grunts lightly]
Hey, housekeeper-wannabe.
Cleaning woman.
Maid!
Bottom-feeder!
Evil alien.
Huhwhat?
[Naota growls] Can you clean
up your mess in my room?
[Haruko] What for?
The whole store
is stacked up with
papers anyway.
[Naota] Is he printing
more of those dumb zines?
[Haruko] Well, after all,
Mon-chan is a journalist.
Mon-chan?
"Kamon"
[Haruko] He says
it's a mini-zine.
With no readers.
[Naota yells]
[concerned chatter]
[Haruko coughs]
What a junker.
[Haruko] These parts
are in perfect shape.
How can they just
backfire like that?
Very strange.
Hm.
[Naota yells]
Have fun today!
That hurts! Let me go!
I see you're wearing your
ugly hat to school again.
[Naota struggles]
[Haruko] Don't make such a fuss.
[Naota blubbers]
[Haruko] I just love the way
these feel. So soft and fuzzy.
They make you feel
all snuggly, ya know?
[Naota] Keep your hands off me.
So, what's up for supper?
[Naota] Huh?
[Haruko] You're probably going
to insist on curry again, right?
I hate spicy stuff!
That's why we're going to buy
you "Little Prince Curry" brand.
[Naota sighs]
[Haruko] It's for kids.
--[Eri] You're late.
--[Naota] Hm?
[Eri] I told you we had
rehearsal this morning.
You know you were
supposed to be there.
Naota, you're the lead role.
No, you're the lead role.
Anybody can play
my part. I pass.
We voted for the cast. And you
got voted in to play the cat.
"Komine Nandaba 1 5 23"
[Naota] The cat.
Do not miss the
rehearsal after school.
By the way, that
hat's really bizarre.
"Outdoor shoes forbidden"
Why's she so into this play?
[Miyaji] Cats, or felines,
love to be babied
when you rub their ears.
They have the amazing ability to
lick any part of their own body.
The cat family includes
tigers, manxes,
and animated cats, such as
Doraemon and Tom and Jerry.
Uh, is this...
Is that cool or what?
Found it in Sakai.
It was at some store,
right out on the rack.
Store that still
sells Crystal Pepsi.
Pepsi?
[Gaku] You know, the one
that Van Halen did
those "Right Now"
commercials for.
You there. What are
you whispering about?
[Masashi shudders]
Miya-jun.
Demerit! Demerit!
Grade 6, class 1 is
officially banned
from bringing in any more
reading matter of low taste.
Plus, reading something
like this secretly
is impolite to Ninamori-san!
[Eri] Huh?
[Miyaji] Just think about
Ninamori-san's feelings...
[Naota's voice]
Kids can't choose
the adults in their lives.
They can't choose their parents.
Ninamori's father is
the mayor of Mabase.
I don't really get it, but it
must make it tough for her.
Of course, that didn't stop me
from ditching the
rehearsal after school.
Playing a talking cat
is really too dumb.
[Mamimi] Okay, here we go.
[Naota] That hat.
[Mamimi] You finally
ditched school, too, Takkun.
Just like me. Meow.
[Naota] Is it a cat or what?
[Mamimi] You're a delinquent.
[Naota] It's after school.
Anyway, practicing
for a school play
isn't a regular part of class.
[Mamimi] I used to
be in school plays.
It was really dumb
and embarrassing.
But I was kind of happy too.
Mom and Dad both came
to see me together.
So, it's a good memory.
Hey, everyone!
The king's ears...
--[Naota yells]
--...are really...
--...donkey's ears!
[Naota yells]
[Takkun] Na na?
Huh?
[Naota] Wah! Uh...? Hah!
[Mamimi giggles]
[Naota gasps]
[Kamon] Got a lot of
response, didn't it?
Well, investigative journalism
is the key to community reform.
My mini-zine of justice,
"Come on Mabase,"
will bring in so many
new customers,
I'll bet you'll even sell
out of your backlog
of old Crystal Pepsi.
Ah, well, gee.
What'll we do, huh?
So, how 'bout it? More copies
while I've still got 'em?
How 'bout a hundred?
Let's say 80.
Hm? See? Someone
wants a copy already.
Hello?
Yes, here you are, Sweetheart.
[Mamimi] I like your head.
You just never know what's
going to come out of there next.
Like Lord Canti
and these kitty ears.
Takkun, you're almost
as cute as Doraemon.
[Naota] He doesn't have ears.
[Mamimi] Anyway,
you saved me, right?
[Naota] Hm?
[Mamimi] The other night,
when you piloted Lord Canti
and fought that evil robot.
You were super cool, Chief.
[Naota] Eh?
[Naota's voice] I could
hardly even remember
what happened that night.
After I got
swallowed up by Canti.
[Haruko] Canti! Canti!
Would you bring in
the laundry already?
What's that?
It smells. Uh--
I'm counting on you!
"Ninamori"
[indistinct chatter]
[chatter grows more intense]
[Secretary yelps]
[Eri] Uh?
You're also smart
about running away.
That's 'cause I'm a grown-up.
I really like your boots.
Perfect for a nouveau
riche princess.
[Eri scoffs]
[Secretary] Goodbye!
[intense chatter in background]
[Eri] I don't have a
home to go back to.
All I have is my cat.
[Naota] Ah-hah!
The class president hanging
around town like a derelict?
Uh...
W-What're you doing
ditching rehearsal again?
[Naota] Should I tell
everyone where I found you?
[Eri] Naota, I swear
sometimes I think
you really are like a
delinquent or something.
[Naota] Could be.
[Eri] But that
hat's still bizarre.
[Naota] So... is there
like a major scene
at your house right now?
[Eri] I don't care.
[Naota] It's just some
tabloid thing anyway, right?
So don't worry about it.
[Announcer] The 5:37 train
for Nagano will depart from...
[Eri] Anyway, it's
all true, you know.
[Announcer] ...platform 2
in a few moments.
[Eri] But hey, I have
a lot of money.
Yeah, I'm a nouveau
riche princess.
Huh?
So, you wanna go somewhere?
Right now, you mean?
Yeah, you're Puss-in-boots
and I'm your owner.
So you just purr
and follow my lead.
[Naota] You talking
about that play?
I don't wanna be a dumb cat.
Anyway, I'm waiting for someone.
Huh?
[engine revs]
Ah, there she is.
Who's that?
Our housekeeper.
[Eri and Naota scream]
--Huh?
--Nya.
[Haruko] Whaaaa! Ow!
[Eri and Naota scream]
[Eri screams]
[Haruko groans]
That cat almost killed me.
[Eri groans]
Naota! Hm?
[Eri] What's this?
[Haruko] Don't touch it!
[Eri] Uh?
[Haruko] A young girl like
you shouldn't touch it
with your bare hands.
What is it, anyway? Hello?
Yeah, I... guess it's an ear.
What kind?
[Haruko] Cat, looks like.
Kitty kitty, meow.
Ow, ow, my stomach.
[Eri groans]
[Haruko] I told you
not to touch it.
Is that my fault?
"Shigekuni's"
[Kamon pants]
[Kamon gulps]
Pretty good.
It's Manhattan style, see?
"Little Prince Curry"
goes to New York.
Mild for kids.
"For adults: Little Prince
Curry 50X Hot"
[Naota screams]
It's spicy! I don't care
if he goes to New York!
[muffled moans from Naota]
You're just being a kid.
It's an adult taste.
[Naota] What?
Why doesn't he think it's spicy?
[Eri] Why is this robot eating?
What is it?
That's just our television set.
[Shigekuni] Ah! Water!
[Naota] No fair, yours
isn't even as hot as mine.
Why is it walking?
Uh... Because it's a
TV Walkman, that's why.
Sony brand?
But it was eating curry.
[Naota] See, yours
is milder. Look.
"Little Prince Curry Very Sweet"
"Light spice."
Would you like chocolate
icing on your curry?
Hey, Canti, I want
a glass of water too.
Go get your own water.
You're supposed to be
the housekeeper here!
Yes, but only for Takkun.
Ah, soda. How did
you like the soda,
Miss Mayor Ninamori's daughter?
Soda?
How do you know about Ninamori?
Well, her father's a
famous person now, right?
No. I don't think
it's any big deal.
Haruko hit her. On her bike.
She ran her over?
Hit the mayor's daughter?
That's why she
started feeling sick.
Oh? Oh, no.
I don't think it's any big deal.
Please don't tell people our
bakery's motorbike ran you over.
Uh, but you got run over.
How's your stomach?
That's kinda rude, Takkun.
I don't think it's any big deal.
Hey listen, she can stay
at the house tonight,
since her family's in this big
awful scandalous mess right now.
What are you saying?
Uh, what I meant was:
why don't you stay over
tonight and get a good rest,
and forget about all of the bad
things that have happened.
Things like getting run over.
I don't think it's any big deal.
See, she says it's no big deal.
I can call your father and
mother to see if it's alright.
That's okay. My parents
are separate people.
If my father divorces my mother,
or gets arrested by the police,
it's up to him.
It doesn't matter to me.
[Eri's stomach makes
noises; Eri groans]
After effect.
[Eri] Restroom?
[Haruko] Over there.
[sound of toilet flush;
Shigekuni grunts]
[Kamon] Are you okay?
How's your stomach?
I don't think it's any big deal.
[Kamon] You think
I'm a bad person?
I'm glad you did it.
It finally got rid
of that secretary.
She had to go.
[Kamon] You're so
mature for your age.
Here. This'll keep the
soap out of your eyes.
[Naota] What? No,
it's not like that.
Don't worry. Ninamori's very...
she's very grown-up.
[Naota] Oh. Glasses.
Our secret.
I wear contacts.
[Naota] You've been
hiding things.
Oh, look who's talking.
[Naota] Mm?
Look, your pajamas?
They're way too short for me.
Can you see?
Hmm. So you're really
sleeping over?
Aah!
Well, we already called.
Er, your father did.
[Naota] Man, he's only
considerate at times like this.
[Eri] But we
wouldn't tell anyone
at school about this, right?
Of course not. People could
say all sorts of things.
Starting tomorrow,
don't hang out with me
for a while, alright?
Yeah, but tonight it's okay?
Uh?
[Naota screams]
Oh, I mean, not in that way.
[Naota grunts]
[Naota] You know what?
Go home! This is weird!
What's really weird
is your ears.
[Naota gasps] You saw 'em?
I was told I
shouldn't touch 'em.
So, what are they?
What do they look like?
Like cat ears.
Perfect to play a cat.
Why do I have to be
the one to play the cat?
[Eri] 'Cause.
I rigged the votes.
So I play the lead,
and you play the cat.
You didn't figure it out, huh?
See, no one would suspect.
They wouldn't think
the class president would
do a thing like that.
You mean you cheated?
You're not mad, are you?
You wanted to play
the lead bad enough
to do something like that?
Who would understand
better than you?
You're Puss-in-boots,
the one who tricks the prince.
He hides who he really is
and pretends to be
someone else forever.
But in time,
he becomes that person,
so his lie becomes
the truth, see?
He transcends the mask.
Well, don't you get it?
That's how he finds happiness.
That's pretty good, right?
[Haruko] You really think so?
How long were you there?
The whole time.
You were listening to us?
Course not. Anyway, why
would I care if you cheated
to get the lead role and
made Takkun a pussy cat?
[Eri] Who is she, really?
That's what I wanna know.
[Haruko] Pretty tricky
getting him to act in a play
by blackmailing him
about his ears.
[Eri] It's just a play.
I'm not hurting him.
Really? I'm not so sure.
[Haruko] It's not nice to
trick people, you know?
Yeah, tell her.
[Haruko] Honest people
are more popular.
Is that right? And do you
always sleep up there?
Yes, always.
[Naota] Stop it.
You're there every night?
Yep, every night.
Right here, all alone
with cuddly Takkun.
--[Naota] Don't touch me there.
--[Haruko] Furry furry.
--Not the ears!
--Furry furry furry...
[meow]
[Naota shudders]
Mwah!
[Naota yells]
It's a robot?
Is there a person inside?
Eww, she kissed him on
the lips. Did you see that?
--Smooch! Smooch!
--[Naota] What are you doing?
[Naota groans]
--[Haruko] Here.
--[Naota] Huh?
It's your lunch.
Mild curry for your rehearsal.
I don't want it. I'm not
acting in that play.
Whaa!
You still gotta
eat lunch, Takkun.
I'm going home now.
No!
You've gotta stay
for rehearsal today.
You have to do what
Ninamori's telling you, Naota.
That's right. It was a
group democratic decision.
Did she put her
tongue in? Smooch!
[Naota] Shut up. You
can't tell me what to do.
[Gaku] Smooch?
I'm not going to
let you go home.
I don't wanna do the play.
I told you that.
It's already been decided.
Why you so uptight about it?
Everyone's going to see it.
A few people are gonna see it.
I want them to see it.
'Cause you're show-off.
My parents are going
to see it together.
School plays are
for little kids.
We are kids. Including you.
I'm not gonna play a cat.
It's embarrassing!
You think that's embarrassing?
With a head like that?
Smoooch?
What's that, ears?
They're cute.
[indistinct chatter]
Aaah!
Yeah? You're the one who
cheated to get the lead role!
[Eri yells]
Huh? Hey, wait!
Huh?
What's this?
What's happening?
[Eri cries in pain]
[Eri yells]
[Eri grunts]
[indistinct chatter]
Cha!
[Miyaji] Stop this now,
Ninamori-san!
[Naota yells]
[Gaku] Waah! Ninamo'.
[Haruko grunts]
Haruko, cut it out!
Ukulele no good.
Canti!
Let's get outta here.
[Haruko] Nya nya nya!
[Naota] Ninamori, get away!
Wah! Whoa!
[Naota yells]
[Miyaji] Demerit! No running
in the hallways! Ooohh...
Huh?
[Gaku] Miya-jun!
It's hit and run!
[Naota] Ow! Ah!
[Naota groans]
Alright, this is perfect.
Got it just where I want it.
Quit playing! It's got Ninamori.
[Haruko grunts]
[Haruko snickers]
[Naota yells]
Haruko, no! Aaah!
[Haruko grunts]
Canti!
Nya nya!
[Naota yells]
Out of my way! Heh!
[Haruko] Nyaah...!
Wha--?
It ate Takkun's curry.
Where did it go?
[Gaku and Masashi yell]
[Gaku wails]
Miya-jun's car!
[Masashi] She's still
paying off the loan.
[Girl] Miya-jun is messed up.
[indistinct chatter]
What? No indecency! Demerit!
[Haruko] Restroom? Over there.
Heh.
[Mamimi coos]
[Naota's voice] In the end,
Ninamori's father
wasn't prosecuted, and he
didn't get a divorce.
Ninamori said she
didn't care either way.
Then she smiled.
There was a rumor that she
was going to change schools.
But she's still here.
Ninamori-san, break a leg!
Oh, look, glasses.
They're fake.
The sky paints an orange slide.
And pride dangles like a sponge.
Spider... The taste of
capturing something alive.
You don't have to deny it.
I want to dream in color.
Ride on shooting star...
With the voice in my heart,
I sang out like a shotgun.
Grungy hamster--acting adult.
Revengeful lobster--
drag him along.
Sniper... At the edge of
the world, what can you see?
Before I aim I want to touch it.
Ride on shooting star...
I was looking for you.
Through my withdrawal,
I was lying.
Ride on shooting star...
With the voice in my heart,
I sang out like a shotgun.
"Next Episode"
[Haruko's voice] Ichiro came to
the U.S. to meet Tommy Lasorda
after a second year as a
professional player in Japan.
And then after playing
a few rounds, he was told
that if he wanted to come
to the Major Leagues,
he'd have to have bigger arms.
Next on FLCL,
Episode 4: "Full Swing."
See ya at the ball game.
"Full Swing"