[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Class is done for today!
But don't slack off
on your homework!
Treat it as though your
life depends on it!
Begone!
[KAZUMA grunts]
You actually stayed
awake though class.
I don't think there's
anybody who could sleep
through all that guy's
overdramatic yelling.
Ah, point taken.
Have a great night! I'll see ya!
[KOENIG sighs]
[COCYTUS]
Hey Demiurge,
there's somewhere I wanna
stop on the way home.
[DEMIURGE]
That's fine with me...
So, what's her deal?
Huh?
She leaves the
second class is over.
What's up? I thought she
walked home with you.
Well, she probably just needs
a little time to herself.
I bet that makes you feel
pretty lonely, though.
Not really. I actually enjoy
my own company, thank you.
C'mon, you're a
little girl, right?
"Oh, poor me, I'm so lonely.".
That's how you feel
deep inside, huh, Beako?
Next time the words
"little girl" come up
in your creepy conversations,
I'd prefer it if you kept my
name outta your mouth!
[SUBARU] You'd have more
fun if you'd play along.
[BEATRICE] I'd have more
fun if I busted your jaw.
Honestly, I'd be really be
lonely without you, Subaru,
so let's go home!
[SUBARU]
Oh, well there's an invitation!
I've got nothing going
on after school, so yeah,
that works for me.
How 'bout you, Emilia?
I don't have anything
keeping me here,
so I'll be happy to
go with you guys.
Okay. I say we should
hit up the butcher shop
on the way back home.
Hold on.
You comin' with us, too?
If you're getting croquettes,
then I'm willing to go with you.
Of course, you can't just say,
"I would love to go with you."
Sounds familiar. Huh, Beako?
[BEATRICE] You can stop name
checking me, you cretin!
[RAM]
Come on, ya loser, I'm hungry.
Right. Guess I'll catch up
with you guys tomorrow!
Bye everyone.
See you later!
[SUBARU] Hm? So, you're coming
with us, Beako?
[WEISS gasps] That guy is
really popular somehow.
Yeah. It seems that way.
--[MEGUMIN] Kazuma.
--[KAZUMA] Yeah?
I found a brand new spot.
It's the perfect setting
for my explosions!
Come and check it out with me!
Cool.
[DARKNESS]
Now hold on just a minute!
Kazuma was supposed to
win a stuffed animal
for me at the arcade.
No way! I told you that
they're having a sale
on veggies at the
supermarket today!
You promised you'd go with me!
Relax, ladies. There's enough
of me to go around.
[MEGUMIN]
Boom! Boom!
Later! Catch ya tomorrow!
See ya!
See ya later, guys!
[AQUA] H-Hang on Kazuma!
I'm getting my stuff!
That guy. Is really popular too.
Hey sad pants, seems like
you've kind of been in a funk
since Valentine's Day.
What are we gonna get today?
Croquettes or some
chicken wings, maybe?
I'm down for menchi-katsu !
I can smell the fryer boiling.
--It's calling my name.
--[EMILIA] Hey, Subaru.
Does she look familiar?
[VISHA]
Thanks for stopping by!
[RAM]
She does.
[ALL]
Huh?
That's 240 yen!
[SUBARU]
Visha?
[SUBARU] And there she
was at the counter.
So you're saying that
she has a part-time job?
Yeah. That's why she
always makes a beeline
to be the first one outta here.
[AINS]
Good morning Tanya, Subaru.
Oh, good morning.
Good morning to you, too.
I was just telling her
that I saw Visha.
[AINS] Hm. That's funny,
we saw her too.
I didn't realize she had a job.
[SUBARU]
Where did you see her?
[AINS] Well, Albedo wanted to
go to the convenience store.
[SUBARU] Really? It wasn't
the butcher shop?
[AINS] Uh, no. Why would
she be there instead?
[TANYA]
Something's going on here.
Check this out, guys.
You'll never guess who we saw
working at the
supermarket yesterd--
[AINS, SUBARU]
Yeah, we know.
[KAZUMA, AQUA]
Huh?
So, you really saw
Lieutenant Serebryakov
working at the supermarket?
[KAZUMA]
Huh?
[TANYA] The reason I've gathered
you all here at this time...
...is to discuss our lieutenant.
Let's go over what we know.
Several people in our class
witnessed her working
a part-time job yesterday.
You verify?
[AINS]
Yes. We spotted her.
We saw it too.
And so did we!
We did too.
I definitely saw her.
[COCYTUS]
Yeah, so did I.
So, where exactly is
she working part time?
[AINS]
The convenience store.
No, it's the supermarket.
The doughnut shop.
Ramen place.
The karaoke club.
[COCYTUS]
The craft store.
Say what?
[AQUA]
Are you getting into crafting?
I think you could make
something really cool!
[COCYTUS]
You do?
[AQUA]
Totally!
Let's try to stay on
topic here, you guys.
She was working the counter
at the butcher shop.
This is getting kinda weird.
[VISHA]
Morning everyone!
Oh, uh, is there something
going on here?
Yes, Lieutenant, since you
mentioned it, there is.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] It's almost
time for us all to join together
under the banner of knowledge!
The spirit of learning!
Or as some might
call it, "Class!"
So sit down and shut up!
Ah, so you found out I
was working part-time jobs?
Sorry 'bout that.
It's cool.
I mean, like, it's not against
the rules or anything.
But we were all
just wondering why.
Well, honestly, it's because...
[gasps]
[VISHA] It's really the only
thing I can think about.
The cafeteria's special menu?
Do you know if anybody's
ordered it yet?
Well, not me.
[AINS]
It's 30,000 yen, right?
Seems like too much
money to blow on lunch.
[KAZUMA]
That's a lotta chili, bro.
[AINS] I'd rather spend my
money on something worthwhile.
How is it not worthwhile?
It's called a special!
It's in the name!
I mean, everybody's
curious about it,
but you're working way too much.
Oh, it's not so bad.
I found if you work at
a place, they feed you.
I just couldn't stop seeing
foods I wanted to try.
[bell beeps]
[CHRIS] Okay, that makes
sense for her,
but why'd you decide
to get a job too?
Well, after hearing her talk
it up, I started to get
curious about what was going
on with this special menu.
Yeah? And now
everyone's working, huh?
Yep. Check out these
awesome aprons.
Subaru and his crew are
at the karaoke club?
'Scuse me! Uh...
--[CZ] Ah...!
--[LUPUSREGINA] Oh yeah!
CZ's doing the death voice!
[SUBARU] I don't have a clue
what you're talking about,
but that is super creepy!
[AUREOLE]
I see, the mysterious Subaru.
Are you working here,
or something?
Not sure where the "mysterious"
nickname came from.
But, yeah! And I
brought your order.
What the...?
How the hell did the
honeytoast just disappear?
[ENTOMA] You probably just
dropped it somewhere,
doncha think?
[SUBARU]
No freaking way.
You'll just have to
make another one, then!
[SUBARU] Hey, what are you
chewing on right now?
Spit it out!
I'm not chewing on anything.
[SUBARU] That's because you
gulped it down! I heard it!
--He's been gone a while.
--[phone rings]
Yes? Keep the room
one more hour?
We've got a single in
room three, boss.
They want another hour.
[TOUGH GUY]
Hm?
Okay, here we go.
--[KAZUMA] Look out!
--[AINS] Could it be...?
Stay on guard!
[ALL gasp]
So what's up?
[AINS]
Nothing, apparently.
[TOUGH GUY]
Here comes the special!
[ALL gasp]
[KAZUMA]
Holy crap!
[SUBARU]
Wait. The buthcher?
[AINS]
It's the convenience store guy!
[TANYA]
You mean the doughnut shop.
[COCYTUS]
No.
[DEMIURGE]
No. No.
[SHALLTEAR]
No. No. No. And, No.
Heh!
[VISHA gasps]
Yay!
Oh, that's something special!
[TANYA] Right, uh, is it just
the size that makes
it special, or what?
Everything else is normal,
so, well, what now?
I mean, we all did
earn a little money.
[AINS] But we don't need to
spend any of it on that.
Agreed.
[VISHA] Oh my god.
This is freaking amazing!
[TANYA]
Coffee's on me!
I feel like I owe you at least
that much for putting up with
my harebrained
subordinate's goofiness.
[SUBARU]
Cool! I'll take an iced, please!
[KAZUMA]
Same.
[AINS] I can't drink,
but I'd like a cup.
Why do you want one if
you can't even drink it?
[AINS]
It just seems sad to me.
I never imagined that
you'd say something cute.
[AINS]
Hey. Don't call me cute.
[REM] I just can't wrap my head
around how she can possibly
eat that much food?
And it can all fit inside that
tiny little body? Like... how?
She's the living embodiment
of the word, "gluttony."
She's terrifying.
[VISHA cheers]
This is the best day of my life!