Once upon a time,
there lived a beautiful girl named Cinderella.
But she was abused every day
by her wicked stepmother and stepsisters.
Cinderella, clean our room.
That's right! Then you need to scrub the floors.
I don't want to.
Crawl on the floor and scrub it yourself.
You want me to crawl on the floor?
I think I'm up for it.
Sister, don't be ridiculous.
You don't understand, I just...
Good. This works out well for everyone, then.
Cinderella, how can you
treat your sister that way?
Poor Cinderella is being abused!
The poor thing.
Poor Cinderella picks up the bucket
and goes to leave the room.
But she ends up tripping and dropping it.
Oh no! Water torture!
Cinderella, this is wonderful...
I mean... horrific!
I'm sorry, sister.
I'll use this to wipe you clean.
I get the mop?
--Hey.
--Are you okay, sister?
--What?
--Yes. Cinderella is just fine.
--Is this how Cinderella goes?
--Cinderella, I'm not talking to you.
--No.
--Oh, I see.
"Wicked Stepmother, It's Your Cue!"
"Episode 12: The Show Begins! Showtime"
Are they going to be okay?
The leader of the Nazarick
Floor Guardians, Albedo, is there.
There's nothing to worry about!
Is she that strong?
Yes.
She's among the strongest of Nazarick's members.
I see!
We call her the big-mouthed
gorilla for a reason.
I have the feeling Shalltear is
talking smack about me somewhere!
Wow!
We'll be on our way, Cinderella!
I'm so jealous.
How come I don't get to go?
Damn it! I bet you're jealous!
Sister, don't swear in the school play.
--So, where are we going again?
--You can do this!
Mother, we're on our way to the ball!
--You can do this, Demiurge!
--That's right.
Hang in there, Albedo!
Emilia! Puck!
Prepare the ice magic!
--Right!
--Leave it to me!
Aqua, can you make lots of water?
What? I'm the Goddess of Water!
Of course I can! Of course I can!
It's like taking candy from a baby!
Yes! For a genius wizard like me,
taking you to the ball is like
taking candy from a baby!
Nobody actually says that.
I bet the one who wrote
that part of the script is...
Emilia.
Yup.
Sacred Create Water!
Well?
I used my full power!
That was too much power, but thank you!
Emilia!
Right!
Puck!
I'm on it, Lia!
Um, Megumin said I'm supposed to
say an incantation...
Lia, it's nice that you do what others tell you.
But I think you're okay
ignoring Megumin right now.
Am I?
Yeah. Okay!
Steel turn to ash,
stone to dust,
as the black gathers and...
That incantation is way too long!
Who told her she could ad-lib?
If we told her to make it short,
she wouldn't do it anyway!
That's right, Ains!
Ora-ora-ora-ora-ora-ora!
What happens if that comes over here?
The school festival will be over.
I don't want that!
I want to see Master be the duckling!
Then fight!
Who are you?
To fight. To struggle.
Got it! Thanks!
Wait, sis!
Youth is a wonderful thing.
Behold this awesome carriage!
I'm shocked that a mere pumpkin
could turn into something so pathetic.
Who are you calling pathetic?
A talking carriage!
Carriages don't talk!
You were made to carry things, not talk!
That's really cruel!
It's a terrible foe, Death Knight!
We should go help!
--Let's go.
--Stay here.
There's no place for us in this battle.
Why?
Because...
This is a battle for maidens!
I'm female.
Cinderella, why are you here?
That's right. You don't belong...
This isn't even a conversation.
--But her brutal mocking laughter
--Hang in there...
--Hang in there, Demiurge!
--is making me...
Raphtalia, Filo!
I'm counting on you!
We'll help!
Thanks!
Attack from different angles
so it can't focus its attacks!
Got it!
Okay!
Wow.
She turns into a really strong bird!
Am I strong? Am I strong?
Yes! Very strong!
Something wrong?
Nothing at all, I wonder.
She thinks you're thinking
naughty thoughts about her.
I am not!
He's right, actually.
No!
What is that?
It didn't have those last time!
It's not the Destroyer you know anymore!
Missile Parry!
Followed by... Counter Arrow!
Thank you!
I'm saving myself for the one I love...
Wonderful! That's wonderful!
Yes! For the man I love, Lord Ains,
I must annihilate the Destroyer!
That is my own diligence!
Love!
And so the two of them fell in love.
High-density magic signal
emanating from the target!
Watch out!
Defensive wall!
Walls of Jericho!
You're good, for a human!
I was trained in hell!
But...
I have to go. Sorry.
Wait!
At least tell me your name.
What is this?
Visha!
I'm at my limit!
I'll protect you!
Like Naofumi does!
She's absorbing it?
That's an amazing power!
Demihuman!
Raphtalia!
Aqua!
Right!
You fit the glass slipper perfectly!
You are the princess I've been looking for!
You're going to pay for trying to
mess with our school festival,
Destroyer!
Taste my wrath!
My rage at not being able to
see Lord Ains' legendary performance!
My sadness at not being able to
eat more chocolate bananas!
My disappointment at not being able to
have more fun at the festival!
I'm disappointed!
Disappointed!
So, it's up to you now, Aqua!
Leave it to me!
And this is for everybody!
--God Blow!
--Please accept the love of me,
--the prince.
--God Blow!
--Yes, with pleasure.
So...
Nothing changed!
So, let's get back to class!
So nothing changed at all, huh?
That's not quite true.
Everything changes.
Only when you come together
can you have the future you want.
Why are you being serious all of a sudden?
As long as you have the will to change it,
you can change the future as much as you want!
It's an invitation from another world!
Ros-chi.
What...
It's an invitation from another world!
...does...
...that...
It's an invitation from another world!
...mean?
Open your books to page 334!
Hold it!
Another world! This is another world!
Strange things await you!
It's another world, like a dream!
It won't let you go, it won't let you head home
You're not going back to your old world
It's a forbidden passport!
It's a story of four nations,
an other world quartet that gathers once a week!
Another world! This is another world!
Now let's head on a dangerous journey?
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?!
Other world showtime!
The bell's ringing to start the day,
whether you like it or not!
There's no telling what'll happen,
just like the real world!
It won't let you go, it won't let you head home
Other world! Other world!
Other world! Other world! Aah!
SHOWTIME!
This story is fiction!
"New Season Coming Soon"
Warning: use only as directed!