The only think I
want is a drink!
Gotta be honest with you.
Life's really not
all that bad here.
But it'd be way better with
some of the good stuff.
Damn right.
Yes indeed.
Wouldn't mind some of that.
[NUEMANN]
Yep.
Too bad, can't buy it in
this world. We already tried.
You want the potion that
makes you feel warm
and forget all your troubles?
[KOENIG] No. I don't
think that's the one.
[TOUGH GUY laughs]
I couldn't really
figure out what the hell
they actually sold there.
[KOENIG sighs] But still,
there's gotta be some way.
Hey, Lieutenant, good news sir.
I was able to locate
some nearby.
[NUEMANN]
Oh yeah, where?
Get this. Here, at school.
I saw it in the principal's
office the other day.
[ROSWAAL]
You're quite the busy bee.
[KURT] I'll be indisposed
for the next two days.
But I'll be back here
the day after tomorrow.
[ROSWAAL]
We'll be waiting for you.
[KOENIG]
Was it the red stuff?
[GRANTZ] Yep, that's what
it was, alright.
We know the principal
was drinking it,
so we can assume that he
keeps it in his office.
[GRANTZ]
It's a safe bet.
What's more, he'll be
away on business.
That'll put him out for the
whole day tomorrow.
[KOENIG]
Huh?
Well, what do you think
we should do?
You know the answer
to that, don't you?
[NUEMANN]
Preach it.
[KAZUMA] Okay, then we need to
start getting our plan together.
[DEMIURGE] It seems that
you're abandoning your duties
as a teacher. Freedom should
be granted as a reward
for talent and
responsibility.
Well, that sounds
exactly like what a
black-hearted demon would say.
As an individual, I have the
right to exercise my freedom.
Including the
right to do wrong.
[DEMIURGE] I have no interest
in the rights of fools.
That kind of thinking only
leads to destruction.
Perfect!
That's just what I want!
Give me destruction!
Oops, uh, seems we're
out of time.
That'll be all
for today, class.
[KOENIG] Okay, let's kick
this plan into action.
Using my "stealth" skill,
we can sneak inside.
Nice.
Here we go.
[AQUA] Hey, what are
guys you up to?
[KAZUMA]
Ugh! Aqua!
Why'd you say "ugh?"
Look, I know you're doing
something that you're not
supposed to, so I wanted to see
if it seemed like an exciting
adventure or just really stupid.
That's the principal's office,
now tell me what
you're doing here?
[GRANTZ] I found out he has
some of the red stuff in there,
and, heh,  we're gonna take it.
[KAZUMA]
You idiot! Why'd you tell her?
Red stuff? The red stuff?
[KAZUMA sighs]
Uh. Should I have kept
my mouth shut?
She doesn't have a problem
with us drinking, does she?
That's not really
the issue, no.
I've been looking
for the bubbly stuff,
but I've had absolutely no
luck finding it anywhere.
So, if there is
red stuff in there.
I'm more than willing
to settle for that.
Let's go inside and take it.
You're in luck, guys!
The Water Goddess,
Aqua, is with you.
I'm willing to help
any way I can!
She's actually cool!
Aw man, you have no
idea how much harder
this mission just got.
Why would that be?
[KAZUMA]
Because... her luck sucks shit.
[KOENIG]
Really?
Huh?
[KAZUMA]
And just like that we're in.
So, anybody know where it is?
[KOENIG] I think it's
in that cabinet there.
[AQUA]
Oh, lemme see.
Yep, right there for the taking!
[KAZUMA] Geez, do you ever
think before you act?
[AQUA]
Jackpot! Looks high quality!
[KAZUMA]
No! Don't touch it!
[alarms blaring]
[KURT]
You impudent fools!
[BOTH gasp]
What's happening?
It's a trap!
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?!
[NUEMANN sighs]
This doesn't bode
well for us, huh?
Oh man, that could
cut something off.
Ya think?
Damn, Aqua!
This is why you gotta
use your brain, you know?
[AQUA]
Hey, back off!
Besides, how would my brain have
known that there was a trap?
[KOENIG]
It's not just you.
This peacetime has
dulled our instincts.
If the battalion commander
finds out about this,
she'll have our heads!
Or at least yell as us.
Yeah.
She'll dress us down till
we're sniveling diaper babies.
Again...
Anyway, it's scary in here,
so let's find our way out!
Look, the entrance is clear.
We need to head that way.
[KAZUMA]
Was there always a door there?
[NUEMANN]
No.
[AQUA]
Huh?
No, it didn't exist before.
Must be a decoy!
[AQUA yelps]
Kazuma! Monster! It's a monster!
Geez, Aqua. Your memory sucks.
[KAZUMA, AQUA gasp]
[KOENIG gasps]
[NUEMANN]
Easy!
[GRANTZ grunts]
[KOENIG]
And... we're done.
I believe every
last trap in here
has been successfully disarmed.
Now all we gotta do is
slip outta this room
and into a tall glass of
this red stuff, right?
Hell yeah!
Something wrong?
[KAZUMA]
Hm. This artwork.
[KOENIG]
What about it?
[KAZUMA]
Well, I don't really know,
just curious about the emblem.
That's the flag of
our glorious Empire.
Oh, really?
Yeah. The principal's one
of the bigger ball busters
at our country's strategic HQ.
Bitchin'. And he set all
these traps, huh?
Sounds terrifying to me.
[NUEMANN]
You're right about that!
[ALL laugh]
Okay.
I think it's just about time for
less squawkin' and more walkin'.
[KAZUMA]
Yup, time to split.
[KURT] You miscreants
aren't going anywhere!
[AQUA] Huh? Oh, no!
What's happening now?
[KOENIG]
Head on a swivel guys.
[AQUA] Seriously, guys,
what is all this?
[GRANTZ]
What the hell are those?
[KAZUMA] Giant toads!
Monsters from our world!
[KOENIG]
Heh. They strong?
[KAZUMA]
They're-- Nah.
[NUEMANN]
Alright!
[KAZUMA]
But... punches don't work.
[KOENIG]
Neumann! Grantz!
[KAZUMA]
Aw man, we are so screwed!
[KOENIG] Still. We have to
protect the red stuff,
no matter the cost!
[KAZUMA] Lucky for us, there are
only four giant toads!
And they can only swallow
one person apiece!
[KOENIG]
I get it.
[KAZUMA] If two of us
sacrifice ourselves so one
can escape with it,
the mission will be a success!
All we wanted to do was to
get that bottle out of here.
Yeah. Let's put
our trust in Aqua!
[AQUA]
Really?
[KOENIG]
He's right.
The hard truth of it is,
this is a man's job.
Aqua, when we make it out of
this, let's all drink together.
Thanks, Horse-face!
Name's Koenig!
[KOENIG]
Go on without me!
[AQUA gasps]
Horse-face! No!
[KAZUMA] Horse-face!
We won't forget his sacrifice.
Okay. Only one left. Go, Kazuma!
Go where?
Whaddaya mean, go where?
You got it all wrong.
There's no way I'm jumping down
that nasty thing's gullet.
[AQUA]
Huh?
I mean, why in
the hell would I?
It's not happening.
Bye-bye Aqua, go have fun.
Stealth Skill. Engage.
[AQUA gasps]
Hey there. You seem nice, huh?
You'll pay for this, Kazuma!
Thanks, gang.
Neumann and Grantz.
Horse-faced guy. Even Aqua.
I'll never forget you
or your sacrifices!
[AQUA screams]
[AQUA] Help! Somebody save me!
Don't just stand there!
This thing's gonna get me!
Help me out, and I'll grant
you my divine protection!
Shield Prison.
[AQUA]
What the hell are you doing? No!
[screams]
[AQUA] I'll bring down
loads of divine punishment
for what you've done!
Divine?
That's what she said.
Well, people that invoke the
divine are never to be trusted.
[screaming continues]
[KAZUMA]
The red stuff is mine!
[ROSWAAL] Well, well.
What do you have there?
[KAZUMA]
Huh?
Who? Me? Uh. Well, I, uh...
I completely understand
how you feel, truly.
[KAZUMA] You ratted us
out to him, didn't you?!
But of course. I mean, I am
on Rozzie's side, after all.
Hello, Grantz. Neumann.
Koenig. Aqua. And Kazuma.
[gasps]
We have rules at this school.
And every single one
of you broke them.
As punishment,
you'll all be detained.
After school!
[KAZUMA groans]
Aw, damn it!