[school bells ring]
[grunts]
Um, who's that?
He just walked off
without saying a word.
Well, most people would nope out
after seeing this class.
[AINS] I can tell you're
looking at me, by the way.
Of course I'm looking at you.
You scared me at first.
Yeah, I remember you
saying something like,
"The hell are we walking into?"
Bet you crapped your pants, too.
That's right. The winning
combo of loud and tardy.
[SUBARU] Hey! Why am I
getting dragged like this?
[AINS] This example proves
that compared to Subaru,
the guy we just saw
is probably normal.
[SUBARU] What the hell is
that supposed to mean?
Mr. Roswaal! The quiet boy.
Yes?
The quiet boy. He's our
transfer student, isn't he?
Well, no. That sullen young man
will be joining the
students in classroom one.
[EMILIA]
Class one?
Yes. I don't recall
his real name.
But you can call
him Shield, kay?
[ALL]
Shield?
Shield? What kind
of name is that?
Okay then. But we are getting
a new student, aren't we?
If not him, then who?
[SUBARU] Yeah, come on.
I wanna know who it is, too!
[KAZUMA] You're not even gonna
tell us when they're coming?
My, what a silly thing to say.
[KAZUMA]
Hm?
Because class two's transfer
student is already right here.
[ALL]
Where?
[ROSWAAL]
Tah-dah!
Meet Chomuske. The newest
member of our class. Say hi!
[meows]
[MOMONGA] Don't say anything.
Just keep your mouth shut!
[TANYA] I'll bite my
tongue and keep quiet,
but somebody is
gonna say something.
They can't let this slide.
[SUBARU] You're just
joking with us, aren't you?
[MOMONGA, SUBARU, TANYA]
There it is!
This cat. What's its name again?
Chomusuke.
[CHOMUSUKE meows]
It doesn't seem fair.
If they're a full-fledged
student now,
then why isn't poor Puck
considered to be one, too?
[PUCK meows]
[MOMONGA, TANYA]
Totally missing the point.
[CHOMUSUKE meows]
I kinda can't believe our
new classmate's a kitty.
Well, we do already have
a couple of demons
and an undead guy in our class.
So is a cat really that
far beyond the pale?
That's right! Not to
mention I'm a goddess.
[TANYA] Geez. You still
expect us to believe that?
[AQUA gasps]
Now I'm not trying to take a
swipe at your personal faith,
but I can't bring myself
to support that kind
of delusional thinking.
I agree. Can you really
call yourself a "goddess?"
Et tu , Darkness? I would
never lie about who I am!
[MOMONGA, SUBARU] I'm not
convinced. Is she or isn't she?
Can you back me up
a little here, Kazuma?
Tell 'em it's not a lie!
[KAZUMA]
I'm sorry, Tanya.
Aqua doesn't quite understand
the difference between
fantasy and reality.
[AQUA]
How could you?
Sorry you have to deal with her.
[AQUA]
You're so mean!
[KAZUMA]
No one believes she's a goddess,
--and that's totally hilarious.
--[ROSWAAL] Focus, people!
Since we do have a new
student joining our class,
it's time for everyone
to change seats!
Guess your easy days
are over, Pinky.
And what does that mean?
[SUBARU] It means you won't be
able to hide behind Cocytus
and slack off anymore.
Well, if I set my mind to it,
anything is possible.
What an amazing thing to say!
Yeah, but not in the
way you think it is.
Point taken. Being able
to see all of your bright,
smiling faces in class
would be good, right?
Take Mare, for example.
Oh, there's no
problem here, sir!
I consider it an honor to stare
at the back of Lord Ains' head
all day, and, I'd just
hate to lose that.
And I'm honored to be
allowed to gaze upon
the right side of My Lord's
strong and handsome face.
Yes, well my side
has the best view!
I'm sorry. But the
best one is diagonally!
Everyone.
Please try and keep in mind that
we weren't summoned here
to slack off. In fact,
it's against the rules.
We're not!
In regards to the
discussion at hand,
I clearly have the ideal seat
because I can admire Lord Ains'
form and pay attention in class.
That is so unfair!
[ROSWAAL]
I said, focus!
We still need to determine
our new seats, yes?
We'll do that by...
[ALL]
...a drawing?
[ROSWAAL]
Correct.
[whines] I'm way too far from
Lord Ains! Ah... Sir, please!
I request we change
seats again--
[ROSWAAL] Now, turn to page one
forty-two and learn all about
dust explosions, okay?
[NAOFUMI] What's going on here?
Is this another Wave?
I don't think so.
Where's Raphtalia and Filo?
[WILHELM]
Hm.
[grunts]
[WILHELM]
I see.
So, you were abruptly
summoned to this world as well?
Yeah.
I was out fighting a monster,
when all of a sudden,
my shield just
transformed on me.
[grunts]
[gasps]
[bell rings]
[WILHELM]
Hm.
My party's gone, both
Raphtalia and Filo.
[WILHELM] Hm... You said your
name is Naofumi, didn't you?
[NAOFUMI]
Yeah.
[WILHELM] I know this
is all very confusing,
but there must be some reason
why you were brought here.
[NAOFUMI grunts]
[WILHELM] Until you
find out what that is,
I think you should
keep going forward.
It may be in your best interest.
[NAOFUMI]
What makes you say that?
It's the look your eyes.
Reminds me of how I once was.
[exhales]
[WILHELM]
You're not drinking your tea.
[NAOFUMI]
I'm not.
[SEBAS] Pardon me, but would
you care to grab some lunch?
Oh! I wasn't aware
you had a visitor.
I'm just on my way out.
[WILHELM]
We shall meet again. I'm sure.
[SEBAS] Hm. I hope today finds
you in good spirts, Wilhelm.
Seeing a boy become a man
never fails to amuse me.
It's entertaining,
if drama's your thing.
Now then, what do you suggest
we we talk about today?
Let's see. The same
thing as every day?
You'd like to continue
our discussion, then?
[BOTH]
Love lives!
[MEGUMIN]
Listen up everybody!
It's time for the lunchtime
announcements.
But first...
Throw!
Yay, Darkness!
You've got this, girl!
[GRANTZ] Captain Weiss.
Second base is secure!
[REM] Yeah. No one
will get to third!
If you're ready,
I won't go easy on you.
[DARKNESS]
Damn it!
[COCYTUS]
Strike.
Missed again!
[COCYTUS]
Strike.
This sucks!
I can't hit anything!
[COCYTUS] You need to get the
bat closer to the ball.
Yes I know. I'm using
every attack I have!
[COCYTUS]
Well, uh...
Alright. Here goes.
Closing time!
A new strategy!
[VISHA] Whoa! Darkness just
threw herself at the ball!
[DARKNESS groans]
That's the stuff. Wait a sec.
Is this a dead ball?
[COCYTUS]
Strike! You're out!
Why? I hit the
damn thing, didn't I?
[COCYTUS] Hitting a ball
with your body like that
is against the rules!
[DARKNESS]
No way!
[SUBARU] Hey guys. We only keep
two pets in here, don't we?
I thought so.
[SUBARU] 'Cause it seems
we've got three now.
Then we'll just get
rid of one 'em.
[DEATH KNIGHT yells]
[HAMSUKE gasps]
Oh no!
Death Knight disappeared,
he did!
[SUBARU] Uh-huh. And that means
we're back down to two,
as we should be!
Hey! Something's not right!
[AURA] Anyone know where
the bird came from?
Who me? Nice to meet you,
my name's Filo!
Have you seen my master?
[AQUA] And who might that be?
What's their name?
His name is Naofumi.
And he's a really great guy!
[AURA] What? I've never
heard of him before.
Ah! Come back to join us,
Death Knight has!
Naofumi! Are you here?
Where could he have gone?
[AINS]
Hm?
A monster!
Hey, slow your roll.
You've been transported into a
whole 'nother world, okay?
Things are a little
different here,
so just put the sword down!
[AINS] Relax, fellow traveler,
we mean you no harm.
[KAZUMA]
He's telling the truth.
Listen, we know this must all
be very shocking and scary.
Because believe it or not, the
same exact thing happened to us.
Was Naofumi sent here too?
[AINS]
Naofumi?
I'm not sure if he's
here with us or not.
So, what can you tell me
about him? Who is he?
You may know him by his title.
[KAZUMA]
And that is?
The Shield Hero!
[AINS] Okay. So he's some
type of hero, is he?
[KAZUMA] Oh, an "I'm so OP"
type guy? Ugh.
[RAPHTALIA] Brave Naofumi
was summoned to save the world
and then cruelly betrayed.
Persecuted for a crime
he didn't commit!
[KAZUMA]
Talk about playing on hard mode.
[RAPHTALIA]
But he's never given up,
and does all he can
to protect others.
[AINS]
Hm...
[RAPHTALIA] But he can
be a little difficult
to get along with,
and he's not really that great
at expressing himself.
[KAZUMA] So hard mode
for everyone else too?
[RAPHTALIA] But deep down inside
he's actually really nice!
[AINS] Is that what
they call a "tsundere?"
[KAZUMA laughs] It sounds
so freaking weird
when you say stuff like that.
[AINS]
It feels weird to say it, too.
I need to find him right now
and this conversation
isn't helping me do that!
Well, we can help you
look for him if you want.
Wow, really?
[COCYTUS]
Strike!
Oh. Hey there Aqua.
What's goin' on here?
[SUBARU laughs]
Run, ya big bird!
Filo?
Uh. You know them?
That's good, I guess.
[SUBARU]
Whoa, hey! Uh...
[BOTH yelp]
[FILO]
Raphtalia, it's you!
[AURA gasps] I want a giant
transforming bird, too!
Is everything okay?
Yeah!
[AINS] This girl is searching
for a hero called Naofumi.
Oh, that's probably the transfer
student in class one, huh?
[AINS]
I'd imagine.
[VISHA]
Last pitch. Take this!
[SUBARU]
Hey! Look out!
[BOTH gasp]
[NAOFUMI]
Air Strike Shield!
[AINS]
What's this?
[AINS, SUBARU gasp]
Second Shield!
[BOTH gasp]
[yells]
[RAPHTALIA]
It's Naofumi!
[FILO]
Master, you're here!
Hey there. You okay?
Yes!
Yeah!
Seems like there are
no other heroes around.
And there's a rule here that
you have to go to school.
[RAPHTALIA]
That's what I was told as well.
[NAOFUMI]
Honestly, I don't understand it.
Still, I'm glad we're
all here together.
I say we just follow the rules
and see what happens.
Works for me!
Whatever you say!
Alright. Let's do this, kay?
[RAPHTALIA, FILO]
Yeah!