The big test is almost upon us.
Too much happens at this school!
[ROSWAAL]
In case you're wondering,
this test will only cover things
we've learned in class, okay?
--[AINS] Is it possible...
--[ROSWAAL] Hmm?
[AINS]
...for one to fail the test?
[MARE gasps]
Lord Ains, please don't worry!
[AINS]
Oh, uh.
My Lord, never fear.
Don't lose faith in
your loyal guardians.
We will not fail!
[AINS]
Um, good.
Even Shalltear possesses
the basic competency
to pass the test.
She's still a floor guardian
of Nazarick, after all!
And we all know the
penalty of failing you!
Yes! I can do it!
Now, I may not be
as wise as you,
still I make this
fervent pledge.
I won't let you down, My Lord!
[AINS]
Excellent.
[MOMONGA]
I was actually more worried
that I was gonna flunk it.
[AINS] I'm not concerned
in the slightest.
But I am curious
as to what effect
it would have on this world.
I was looking for confirmation.
No doubt some here
don't test well.
I feel you staring at me.
[AINS]
Huh?
Do you really believe
I'm some kind of idiot?
And after I gave you a pass
on being a filthy undead.
[AINS]
You've got the wrong idea.
[AQUA]
No--you and me! Let's go!
Who'll get the higher grade?
[MOMONGA] Aw, cmon!
This freakin' sucks!
I never even graduated
middle school!
Huh? Everyone's staring at me!
They need leadership!
What am I gonna do?
I know!
[AINS] Are you certain that
you want to go down this road?
[AQUA scoffs]
Hell yeah!
[MOMONGA]
That backfired!
Ah, I get it now.
What is there to "get" exactly?
[KAZUMA] I'd say I can't
believe you're stupid enough
to challenge Ains,
but I'd be lying!
[AQUA]
I just thought--
You don't pay even the
smallest bit of attention
in class like he does.
How could you think
you'd beat him?
Not to mention your
intelligence stat
is ridiculously low, and it
ain't gonna rise anytime soon.
[AQUA shouts] Why do you have
to always embarrass me?
Just because you're a shut in
NEET with a sucky life...
If you want my honest advice,
it'd be to study hard enough
that you don't
embarrass yourself.
[TANYA]
Now is the time!
[AQUA]
Huh?
Join my two hundred third
Aerial Mage Battalion's
famous test prep course!
[AQUA]
Sorry, not interested.
My short-term training
program's unparalleled.
There are many ways to hone
your skills as well as--
[AQUA]
Sorry, not interested.
[PUCK yawns]
Can I take a nap?
I don't actually get sleepy in
this world, but I do get bored.
You need to work hard,
Puck, and study.
Meh.
You're doing great, Subaru!
I'm so impressed by you!
Thanks! He, he. This brings
back some memories.
[EMILIA, REM]
Huh?
When we studied? Before?
Those were some
crazy times, huh?
Sure were.
So crazy.
Uh...
[SUBARU] What the hell
am I talking about?
When did that happen?
We've never studied together.
Am I thinking about our time in
this room, like earlier today?
Wait a second. How long have
we been stuck in here?
[MARE]
Oh. Is something bothering you?
It's nothing, I suppose.
[BEATRICE] Think long and hard,
but I'd bet my life,
you'll never find the answer.
[EMILIA]
Are you okay?
Huh? Ah, Sorry.
Just lost in thought.
You surprised me by
shuttin' yer trap like that.
[SUBARU]
Nobody says "shuttin' yer trap."
[EMILIA giggles]
Shall we move on?
[REM]
Yes, let's.
[SUBARU]
Roger that!
[CHRIS] So you see, it's because
of this that that happened.
[FELT groans]
I just don't get it!
Chris, wassup?
[CHRIS]
Hey, Kazuma!
Can you lend us
some brain power?
Aqua needs help
studying for the test.
Ah! It's the guy who hangs
with homeboy's friend's dude.
Why don't you just call me
by my name? It's Kazuma.
I didn't know that you
two ever hung out.
Oh, yeah, we're cool.
People were saying
that she's a thief.
So I thought we'd have
something in common,
turns out I was right.
Kazuma's an adventurer,
but he's okay in my book.
I taught him a few of my skills,
so he's actually a pretty
decent thief, too.
[FELT] Very cool!
What's been your best score?
Her panties.
You didn't have to mention that!
[AQUA] Hey, I thought we were
here to get me some study help.
Okay, class. I hope that you're
prepared to start the test!
The questions were written
for us by Mr. Pandora's Actor,
and we appreciate it, don't we?
I'll add that if any of you
are caught cheating,
you'll get a big, fat zero.
So please, don't cheat.
[TANYA] This test is nothing
more than a slap in the face.
Which reminds me.
There much are better ways
to extract information.
I'm sure Ains is just as put out
by this whole thing as I am.
[MOMONGA]
Tanya's looking at me again.
I know she respects
me or something,
but I'm gonna mess
the bed on this test.
No stealing anybody's
answer sheets.
Gulp!
[SUBARU] Uh, did somebody
actually say "Gulp"?
I said "good"
'cause I love tests!
Kazuma won't stoop that low.
He's not as smart as
a Crimson Demon,
but I'm the only one born
with that advantage.
Still, I think his intelligence
is sufficient enough
to pass this test,
at the very least.
So, you're not totally
incompetent, then?
Uh no, not totally.
Well, I suppose I
underestimated you, I'm sorry.
[KAZUMA] She'd be
disappointed if she knew
I was gonna steal her answers.
I think I just
overheard somebody's
guilty inner monologue
going off.
There's no way,
and it wasn't mine!
[ROSWAAL] Okay class.
Let the test begin, now!
[MOMONGA] I spent the entire
week trying to relearn
everything from
elementary school...
...but I don't know
a single answer.
Why did that disappointing
fool make these so hard?
I mean, I would've if I
were asking the questions,
but I still don't like it.
Okay, fine.
If I don't wanna look stupid,
I'll just have to do the smart
thing and, uh, cheat.
I think the best way, would be
to use the eleventh-tier spell,
"time stop."
Alright, here goes...
[AINS]
Time Stop.
[AINS] Now. I'll just
sneak a little peek.
[AQUA] Huh? That's weird.
Everybody froze!
Poke-poke! Hey!
[MOMONGA] Aw, man. I forgot
Aqua's supposed to be a goddess.
She's immune to the time stop!
This is awesome! Now let me
see those answers, Kazuma!
[MOMONGA] Ya know, seeing her
in action like this,
I realize it's not a great look.
You can almost smell
the desperation.
It makes me even more
ashamed of myself.
But what else am I
supposed to do?
I was the one who
stopped time, after all.
[TANYA] Are you behind this
temporal manipulation?
Wasn't me. I can't
do this kinda stuff.
[TANYA] I see. Then I take it
to mean you're not Being X.
'S'why I never said that I was.
[TANYA] Well, anyway.
What in the hell are you doing?
[AINS, AQUA gasp]
It takes a massive set of
stones to so brazenly cheat
in front of me like that.
[gasps] I wasn't cheating,
I just uh--
[TANYA]
Shut your trap!
[MOMONGA]
Why the hell can Tanya move too?
Wait a minute.
Tanya had told me that she
was brought to another world
by a being that
called itself a god.
Maybe there's some
rule that says gods
and people who can talk to
them are immune to time stops?
Never heard that one, but...
[SUBARU] Be quiet! We're in the
middle of a big test right now.
See how still everyone else is?
I mean, they are really
concentrating hard.
[MOMONGA yelps]
[SUBARU] Whoa.
They're not even breathing?
Hey, what's goin' on?
[MOMONGA]
Subaru can move too?
Back in my other world,
hardly anybody can use
eleventh-tier magic!
But this many people here
aren't affected by it?
This world blows my mind!
I should stop before
I get busted.
[SUBARU]
Hm?
[AQUA gasps]
Uh-oh, not good.
[ROSWAAL]
What are you doing Miss Aqua?
[gasps]
[KAZUMA] Why is it so hard
to breathe-- Pencils?!
Alright, Aqua.
[grunts]
Hallway please. This instant.
[AQUA]
I didn't do anything!
[AINS]
Sorry about that.
[MOMONGA] I did the
best I could, but...
[AINS]
Hm...? Hm...? Hm?!
[ROSWAAL] Ains I need
you to shut your trap.
Tests are back now.
[MOMONGA] Pandora's Actor
is eccentric and self-serving,
but I thought I was
talking a risk here.
[AINS] A perfect score,
just as I expected.
It goes to show you,
you shouldn't test Lord Ains.
He's truly invincible.
[MOMONGA]
Yeah, totally cool with this.
I didn't know that Ains
was such a genius.
All Hail Ains! An all-knowing,
all-powerful force of nature!
[MOMONGA]
On second thought,
I am extremely cool
with all of this.