[MARE]
So, have I gotten any bigger?
I feel like I have.
Well, what does it say?
Any change?
[VANIR]
Same weight as last time.
You're still tiny, with
comically oversized ears.
Oh, right.
Physicals. Who knew health
was such a pain in the neck?
It's crazy.
Always something going on.
[RAM] Indeed. I've decided
I'm going to just focus
all my obsession
on Rem's growth.
That's pretty amazing to me.
You two girls are exactly alike.
Almost, besides breasts.
Oh. I'm sorry.
[RAM]
I'm fine with it.
They seem like they can
be quite a burden to me.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] You students!
Give me your attention!
[VISHA]
Yes sir?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
"Sir" is correct!
For I am your leader,
your teacher!
I am Pandora's Actor!
I'm one and all!
But "sir" will do.
[RAM] I see.
Great info, goodbye, sir.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Wait!
[sighs]
Yes?
Is there something else
that you need from us, sir?
Since you're one of Mister
Roswaal's cohorts, I will,
with reluctance, hear you out.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
I appreciate that. Mademoiselle?
Yes? What now? Spill it.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] Well, it's
actually your stylish companion
with whom I'd like to speak.
[VISHA]
Huh?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] Your outfit
is simply to die for.
Extremely cool!
Oh... Yeah?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
My father-- no--
when we're here,
he's my student!
My Ains must be
very excited by it.
Wait. Ains is your father?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] Perhaps it's
more accurate to say he's
"my creator".
So that magnificently
fashionable and chic outfit,
which is so reminiscent of mine,
must be very
eye-catching to him!
[VISHA]
You don't say.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
I do say!
[RAM]
That's good to know, sir.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
My pleasure.
Heh.
[ERICH]
Try to imagine this.
Waking up in a world that
is similar to your own.
But...
[DARKNESS] What's wrong Ram?
Are you alright?
Nothing. Everything's great.
Are you sure? You look
disgusted or something.
I'd be lying if I said
I didn't like it.
[AINS]
Hmm.
[ERICH]
Anyway...
As I'd mentioned,
physicals are this afternoon.
Girls in the nurse's office,
and the boys will all go
to the gymnasium.
If you happen to be on
the health committee,
it is imperative you follow
the nurse's instructions
to the letter.
Right!
Yes, I hear and obey, sir.
I look forward to the task,
inspecting every bit
of Lord Ains' body.
Calm down. You will
be handling the girls.
Why? Just because you hate me?
[ERICH]
Because you're girls.
Weak! Just like your mother!
[DARKNESS] Shalltear,
your rage is incredible!
[MOMONGA]
Sorry about her.
[DARKNESS] Your passion
is like a white-hot poker!
[KAZUMA]
Sorry about her.
And us guys?
Who's taking care of us?
[ERICH]
A class one boy.
You got some kind
of problem, man?
No! But yeah, maybe!
Well, which one is it?
[VANIR laughs] This fool was
hoping he could fix his gaze
upon a scantily clad classmate!
But the shield hero will protect
the virtue of the fairer sex!
If you dare make a move to
storm the nurse's office
to ogle the ladies, he will
stop you in your tracks.
Not really. If you wanna give
it a shot, go on ahead.
But you don't want that kind of
blemish on your reputation.
Trust me.
Oh, well, he's kinda
used to that.
Yeah, it's pretty much my
day-to-day existence--
Hey!
Classic Kazuma.
Actually, you're all wrong.
I'm not a peeker.
But you did try on the
beach trip, didn't you?
Yeah, well somebody had
to be the one, right?
Then somebody has
to this time, too.
That's true.
[KAZUMA gasps]
[AINS]
I'll admit.
I'm curious to see if Kazuma
has the skills to pull this off.
Et tu , Ains?
[AINS] Rumor is you
have the highest luck
of anybody at this school.
Let's test that.
[gasps]
Yeah, sure, okay.
Now, I don't wanna do this,
but if I have to
and if you insist.
I have no choice
but so show you.
Don't do it.
I shouldn't.
[ALBEDO, SHALLTEAR grunting]
You fiend! Release me at once!
I must see him now!
I must bear witness to
Lord Ains' unclothed form!
Yes! This is so wrong!
I have to see him!
You want to look at that human
you lust after as well,
don't you?
Yes. My wish is to be by my
Subaru's side at all times,
and I'd love
to do his physical.
[ALBEDO, SHALLTEAR]
Let's go!
[REM] This simply isn't
the right moment.
So I'm content to wait for now.
At some point in the future,
I'll give him a
private physical.
[SHALLTEAR gasps]
Oh.
I didn't even think about the
option of giving one in private.
One on one? It'd be
a dream come true!
[WIZ] I seem to be having a
little bit of trouble
measuring your
real height, Tanya.
[COCYTUS]
So what's up?
Are you not interested
in peeking, Subaru?
It's not that I'm not
interested, per se.
It's more like...
...I'm just not the type of guy
who goes sneaking around.
[COCYTUS]
The warrior's path.
[JULIUS chuckles]
Perhaps he's learning
what it means to be a knight.
[SUBARU] ...got this
weird feeling that somebody's
looking down at me.
[COCYTUS]
What about your team?
We're the type of guys
who'd rather just have fun
than try to spy
on naked girls.
Only because Tanya
would murder you.
You'd think. But this
may surprise you.
If we don't violate
military code, she's cool.
[KOENIG]
Really. Is that so?
Big surprise.
We'll tell her you
said that, sir.
[NAOFUMI]
Hey, guys.
Just get on the
freakin' scale, would ya?
This one?
[MEGUMIN]
Can't see it.
[REM]
This one?
Can't see it.
[REM]
Because your eye patch is on.
I'm afraid you don't
know what you're saying.
For if this seal is released,
it may unleash hell upon
this nurse's office.
You know that's not true.
[MEGUMIN gasps]
Why must you insist on acting
like you're 12 years old
or something?
Don't you think it's time
for you to grow up?
[MEGUMIN] What the...?
You need to check your attitude!
I'm older than you, little girl!
And besides, I know
I look incredibly cool
with this eye patch.
And I'm not the only one.
Yeah? Some other weirdo
likes it? Who's that?
[MEGUMIN]
Ains!
What?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
You!
The girl with the
incredibly cool eye patch!
[MEGUMIN]
Huh? Are you talking to me?
You think I'm cool?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR laughs]
Yes indeed.
You're the only one with
that dandy eye patch!
That's true. Thank you. You have
extraordinary taste, sir.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Alas, I cannot taste anything.
But I do have amazing taste!
For I am Pandora's Actor! Yes!
By the way,
that cool eye patch.
I can tell it's no ordinary
ocular accouterment.
Ha! I'm surprised that
somebody noticed!
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] If I had eyes,
you could not hope to fool them!
Well then,
I'll let you in on a little
secret in that case.
That the primary function of
this unbelievably stylish
accessory is to seal
away my hidden power.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR gasps]
I knew it!
[MEGUMIN chuckles]
But you take it off
all the time.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Der Alte würfelt nicht!
That was so awesome!
You have to tell me whatever
it was you just said!
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] These powerful
words were taught to me
directly by my creator,
Ains Ooal Gown!
He's a student here, in fact.
And, yes, we share the
same exact tastes!
The most incredible tastes. Yes!
Ains Ooal Gown, you say?
From the name, I can tell
he's no ordinary man.
[GRANTZ] Have you met
another talking skeleton
that's ordinary?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] I'm absolutely
positive that your tastes
dovetail with his
as well. Yes!
Oh really?
I had a strong feeling he was
fit to be my perfect rival!
[TANYA]
Uh...
Ains may be undead,
but at least he has
impeccable taste.
[TANYA] Hm. I may have to
reconsider my opinion of him.
Sorry Filo.
I'm having a little trouble
measuring your height.
[WIZ]
I appreciate your cooperation.
Now, head back to
your classroom,
and then you'll all be free
to go home for the day.
[KAZUMA] Aw. Damn it!
Too late. No!
I'm so disappointed.
He didn't watch?
[AINS]
Now then.
[ALBEDO]
Lord Ains!
[AINS]
Is something wrong?
My lord. I understand
your tastes much better
than anyone in this
world or our own!
I still fit your ideal of
female perfection, don't I?
Just me. I'm the only one.
Not that red-eyed floozy!
With that stupid hat and cape!
I'm the succubus you've
always dreamed of!
[MOMONGA]
Huh? What's with Megumin.
When you gaze deeply
into my abyss,
you'll find something.
You'll find me gazing back into
your own chasm of darkness.
[MEGUMIN laughs]
Heh!