[BETELGEUSE]
Love.
Most beautiful, most noble,
and the most diligent, diligent,
diligent worker of all!
Its day is upon us!
The day you show the ones
you love what's inside.
That day is "Valentine's Day!"
Death!
Valentine's Day, huh?
Indeed. That's what
it's known as.
Kazuma told us about it.
He said you show your love
by gifting cheap chocolate.
Huh?
I don't know. I absolutely
love chocolate.
So If I had some I'd probably
just keep it for myself.
What about you?
Giving chocolate to anyone?
Yeah, to Kazuma.
Wow, you answered that quick.
It would be a pretty big
power move, to be honest.
He told us that his mom
is the only one who's ever
given him chocolate.
Huh.
What about you Emilia, do you
have anyone special in mind?
[EMILIA]
Hm... Puck, maybe?
Yay! And I can give
you some in return!
[EMILIA]
It's a plan!
[PUCK chuckles]
I don't actually think
that's how it works.
Huh? Major!
Hey, you girls aren't
plotting something, are you?
Who, us?
Actually, we were talking about
Valentine's Day just now.
Valentine's Day, huh?
That's one of my
favorite examples
of a true marketplace victory.
Of capitalism beating religion.
[PUCK] Guess that's
one way to look at it.
So does that mean
you're gonna celebrate
by giving chocolate
to somebody?
I'd really prefer not, to be
perfectly candid with you.
If I could expense it,
then maybe.
There might be room in the
budget for a little bit.
It could be considered
as a kind of "duty."
Given as a duty?
Yeah. I mean what
else would you call
giving gifts to those
you're forced to be around?
Like the people
at work or school.
You have to give away
a lot of it, huh?
Don't worry, it doesn't
have to be high quality.
Really just a token.
Good to know.
Well, okay.
I guess, it's my duty
to give some to Subaru.
You're really using
your brain there, Lia.
[MEGUMIN]
Sucks to be Subaru, huh?
Appears so.
[EMILIA, VISHA]
Huh?
[ALBEDO]
Valentine's Day!
Finally those stupid humans
got something right!
They created a holiday
that I can get behind!
I will flavor these
treats with love.
My love. The sweetest love!
You're speaking my language!
Sweeten the flavor with
buckets of blood, sweat, tears,
and every last bit of
love that you have!
[ALBEDO] I agree completely,
Mister Betelgeuse!
Excellent! For I am
the diligent,
untiring servant
of diligent love.
Betelgeuse Romanée-Conti.
Death!
Now then...
There are a plethora of ways
to prepare chocolate treats.
So tell me, which of those
paths will you chose to take?
I think the best way,
given that Lord Ains is the
supreme commander of the undead,
is to lavish him with
dark chocolate
to match his dark spirit!
Ah, I see. So the taste of
dark adult bitterness, eh?
Only the darkest chocolate
is fit for him!
And the secret
ingredient will be...
...love!
Absolutely, positively,
wonderfully perfect!
it gives me immense pleasure
to have such a diligent,
diligent pupil!
I just can't give in to sloth.
I'll work myself to
the bone for my lord!
A truly, truly, truly,
kindred spirit.
A pure and diligent
apostle of love like me!
Yes! Lord Ains has me
in chains of love!
[BOTH]
Death!
[KAZUMA]
Meanwhile, watching outside...
...Kazuma thought, "These freaks
scare the crap outta me."
Who are you girls gonna
give chocolate to?
Come on, to Lord Ains,
of course.
Subaru gets mine.
You're going to give some
sweets to Kazuma, aren't you?
Huh? To Kazuma?
That a no, I take it?
I mean, he's just some guy
in my party, ya know?
[SHALLTEAR]
You sure about that?
[gasps]
No doubt in my mind!
He's not my type!
He's the kind of guy who uses
magic in a sword fight to
tear away my clothes and expose
my naughty bits to the prying
eyes of the world, and then
salivate as he describes all
the ways he wants to
humiliate and demean me!
Yeah, that totally sounds
like your type.
Gimme... chocolate!
I remember it fondly.
It was so amazing!
Wait, I can't remember it!
I've been in this world
so long I've forgotten
the taste of chocolate!
Uh, Captain.
Today is a very special day.
A day when we welcome
the sweet bombardment
of all things chocolatey!
Captain!
Are we not allowed to have a
day filled with decadent joy?
Captain!
What now?
[KOENIG]
That not really how it works.
[WEISS]
Hm?
The girls that like you
give you chocolate,
so we may run into a little
bit of a problem here.
So you get chocolate and
the girls who like you!
Sounds awesome!
Come on, really?
Doesn't get it.
No way.
Jump in anytime, Neumann!
Spell it out in a way that
even this clueless bozo
can understand.
Leave it to me.
[WEISS hums]
Captain Weiss.
Huh?
So, look. It works like this.
Today you can ask the girls
to give you chocolate.
[KOENIG gasps]
Good, yeah?
But you should remember,
you gotta be extremely polite.
[WEISS] Hm? Sounds easy enough.
I know the magic word.
Hey, Kazuma!
What's goin' on, you guys?
[NEUMANN]
Just talking about girls.
Back in your world,
how did you ask a lady
to give you chocolate?
I would say...
..."Give me... choco!"
Eh. Like that.
So, "give me choco?"
Yep. That's how you do it.
Put out your hands and bow.
Then keep asking until you get
all the chocolate you can carry.
Sounds great. Thank you!
I'm always glad
to help, bruh. See ya!
[KAZUMA chuckles]
Not a chance in
hell that's true.
No way.
Yeah, it's a load of crap.
But Weiss is totally
taking it seriously!
Hey, looks like we have
some ladies incoming.
I think so...
Excellent idea.
Huh?
[WEISS]
Give me... choco!
Ah! The hell's wrong with you?
[WEISS]
Please give me... choco!
Get back, eyebrows! You wanna
hurt someone, start with me!
Now give me... choco!
[REM]
Al Huma!
[WEISS groans]
[SHALLTEAR]
So, shall we go?
[REM]
Yes, let's.
But why? All I wanted was
to taste chocolate again.
Ya see?
Yeah, he got creamed!
So this is how you set
the poor guy straight?
[WEISS]
Hm?
Huh? What happened?
Why is Weiss on the floor
in that tattered uniform?
Major.
Come on. Speak up. Explain this.
[WEISS]
Give...
[TANYA]
Huh?
[WEISS]
Give me... choco.
Oh. I'm sorry Weiss.
[WEISS]
For what?
Because, you got bad intel.
[SUBARU sighs]
[BETELGEUSE chuckling]
How splendid.
This is actually, amazingly,
truly splendid!
True love given edible,
corporeal form!
[BETELGEUSE, ALBEDO]
Death!
What are you two doing here?
Suspicious. Hm...?
I'm making chocolate
for Lord Ains!
The ruthless ruler of my heart.
Diligently!
So diligently for love!
I know all too well what
one does for love.
But, who is this man?
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance, sir.
I am the apostle of
most diligent love.
Archbishop of the Sin of Sloth,
Betelgeuse Romanée-Conti!
Death!
[SEBAS] You're trespassing
on school grounds.
Death!
[BETELGEUSE]
Death...!
Well, it matters not.
For I have realized the
thrust of my mission here.
Wait. My diligent love
sense is tingling again.
Pulling me towards a miasma
of love! I must go! Death!
I thank you, love's apostle.
[SUBARU] Huh? 'Sup Albedo?
You whipping up some chocolate?
Yes indeed. By the way,
what do you think of
my Valentine's treat?
All I want is to
please Lord Ains.
[SUBARU]
Uh...
[ALBEDO]
It screams love, right?
I put all the love I
have into making it!
I'd say the overall
design definitely
screams something, alright,
but I believe you.
Maybe that your
love is forceful?
Death.
[MOMONGA]
Look at all this chocolate.
Too bad I'm allergic.