This is madness! Do you even
have a brain in that skull?
[AINS] You're the one who
should have their head examined!
Just stop with all
the yelling, would ya?
Shut up and stay in
your lane, tracksuit.
This does not concern you.
[AINS] I had thought you and
I understood one another.
You understand nothing! Hmph!
[AINS]
Hmph!
What in the hell has
gotten into you?
So you guys like different
stuff on your chicken wings,
big freakin' deal!
Ram and I went to that
li'l butcher shop
down on the corner
the other day.
Their wings were to die for!
Like meaty chunks of heaven.
[TANYA]
Oh yeah?
You thought they
were awesome, didn't you?
Yes, and I'm willing to
bet even Mister Roswaal
would go gaga for them.
[COCYTUS]
They're that good?
They're amazing! And if you
haven't tried them before,
you've wasted your life!
[COCYTUS]
They're that good?
And you call yourself a warrior.
[COCYTUS]
They're that good?
Is that so? Then I suppose
I'll have to try them.
Hey, Ains! Would you like
to go to the butcher shop
with me after school today?
Rumor has it they
have killer wings!
[AINS]
Hm. I must say I'm intrigued.
[MOMONGA]
Sucks that I can't eat them.
[AINS]
What do you think?
I wouldn't dream of
going against the wishes
of a being as supreme
as you, My Lord.
[SUBARU] I'm sorry I put
myself in the middle
of your ridiculous argument.
[TANYA] You're in it now,
so I'll ask you.
How do you like to flavor
your chicken wings?
With some salt and pepper,
or with ketchup?
With mayo.
Looks like I'll be
fighting you as well.
[SUBARU]
Huh?
[AINS]
I can't hide my utter disgust.
Huh? How could anyone with
taste buds not use mayo?
[ERICH] At the risk
of breaking up this
riveting intellectual
discussion,
I'll remind you that
class is in session.
[exhales]
[ERICH]
When people gather together,
it's inevitable that
differences of opinion,
both large and small,
will arise.
It appears this current conflict
centers around the question,
"what do you like on
your chicken wings?"
It sounds even more idiotic
when you say it out loud.
Ahem. I propose that
we clear things up
by conducting a quick survey.
[ERICH] And we've got a
deadlock on our hands.
I thought you ladies would
vote the same way as Subaru.
To share his preference
would bring me great shame.
I usually agree with
everything he says.
But not this time.
It's killing me!
[AINS] You prefer your
wings with ketchup, too?
Who're we to question the
wisdom of one so supreme?
It'd be heresy.
[AINS]
Hm?
[COCYTUS]
Please don't consider my vote
to be a show
of disloyalty, my lord.
[MOMONGA] I wonder if
that can be modified
in the character settings.
So you're a ketchup girl?
No. I'm a Crimson Demon,
so naturally, I choose
the crimson sauce!
What about the cat?
Ketchup, obviously.
[CHOMUSUKE meows]
[KAZUMA] Team Mayo seems
to have the most people.
[SUBARU] Yep. And that's
because mayo absolutely slaps!
End of discussion!
[AINS, TANYA]
It's because you're basic!
Hey now!
[TANYA] Hmph. Once again it
seems democracy has failed us.
[AINS]
Then how do we decide?
Through brute force
and subjugation?
[ERICH]
Perhaps.
Huh?
I propose that this be
our weapon of choice.
[SUBARU]
A ball?
[ERICH] They say, "justice
without force is powerless."
We'll have justice
through dodgeball!
[AINS]
Sounds perfectly reasonable.
Do you agree? Team Ketchup
will take no prisoners!
And team salt will
pull no punches.
In time, you'll rue this day.
If you survive the battle.
Not so sure about Team
Mayo's chances here.
Come on. I'm standing
right here. You know that.
Gird your loins, everyone,
and head out to
the playing field!
[ALL]
Yes, sir!
We'll need to even out
the teams a little bit.
Basically, put your
magic power into this ball,
and who ever it hits is out.
[NAOFUMI]
Hold up!
[ERICH]
Hm?
I would like to know what
exactly we're doing here.
[ERICH]
Ending a debate.
What is that
supposed to mean?
Just go with it, man. We're so
happy to have you on the team!
Hang on. I never
agreed to anythi--!
Thanks, Shield Bro!
Appreciate it.
Salt and pepper for life!
I still don't understand.
Team Salt and Pepper will be
counting on you, soldier.
What is this?
[FILO] Come on Master,
lighten up a little and play!
This "dodgeball"
game looks so fun!
[NAOFUMI sighs]
Okay, fine.
Yay!
[RAPHTALIA]
Hey, Naofumi? Um...
I'm so sorry.
I know I'm supposed to be the
sword to your shield, but...
[chuckles]
It doesn't bother me at all.
[gasps]
[NAOFUMI] I actually like
the fact you chose ketchup.
I feel like you're
making fun of me!
[ERICH]
Alright, let's begin!
[VISHA]
It's a war over flavors!
We'll decide which
wings reign supreme!
I'm Viktoriya
Ivanovna Serebryakov,
and I'll be your host!
Joining me on commentary is your
friendly neighborhood butcher!
Tell me, what is
your prediction?
All I can say, is every team on
the field is hungry for victory!
Ha!
I'd like to see what
these losers can take!
[DARKNESS gasps, sighs]
[SUBARU]
She got hit on purpose, right?
[KAZUMA]
It's that obvious?
Yeah, just like that! Eee!
[COCYTUS]
Idiot.
[ERICH]
Darkness is out.
Are you ready, Rem?
Yes, let's go!
[VISHA]
What are they doing?
We can do that! Come on!
Yeah! Let's show 'em!
Oh, um...
[VISHA] Doesn't look nearly
as easy when he does it!
[AURA, MARE]
And boom!
[NEUMANN]
Aw man!
[VISHA]
And Neumann misses the catch!
[whistle blows]
I declare that move
to be illegal.
[AURA, MARE gasp]
[RAM]
Hmph.
Major!
Here!
[KAZUMA]
Steal!
[TANYA]
Sneaky bastard!
[AQUA] Amazing work, Kazuma!
Now gimme that!
Listen up, everybody.
The Axis Order is a benevolent
and merciful religion.
That said,
I'll smite anyone who gets
between me and my mayo!
[AQUA]
Ha! God blow!
[VISHA]
The move is kinda cool,
but what in the heck was
that ridiculous intro about?
Stand back! Walls of Jericho!
Did you really have to
pretzel-ize me to pull that off?
Meow?
There is seriously
something up with that cat!
My cat is perfectly normal,
thank you!
I've never seen a "normal cat"
do anything like--
[gasps]
Here it comes!
Boop.
[SUBARU]
Appalachian Mountains!
Really! You should
stay focused, I suppose!
Thanks a lot, Bea-ko!
Help me!
I've got this, Lia!
Okay, that is most certainly
not a normal cat!
It's a perfectly not-normal cat!
Sorry!
[TANYA] Shield Man! We can't
lose to the Mayo Freaks!
Total overkill, ya know!
[AINS]
So, then.
I believe it is time to end
this farce once and for all.
Such a cool thing to say.
And speaking of cool...
[AINS]
Hm.
I have an awesome idea for
what our next move should be.
[AINS]
Oh?
[MEGUMIN whispers]
[AINS]
Excellent. I concur.
Check this out, guys!
We drink the blood,
the crimson offering!
[TANYA]
A combo attack?
We feast upon the, uh...
Are you just standing there?
[AINS]
Hm?
You gotta do the chant, too.
Huh?
Just say what I say, okay?
[KAZUMA]
Uh...
Guess I'll just have to
pull out the big guns.
Oh God, thou art an
impregnable armor of faith!
May thy steadfast
protection and thy glory
prevail over these foul demons!
[MEGUMIN, AINS]
Explode! Nuclear Blast!
Defensive shield!
[ALL gasp]
[VISHA] It looks like the ball
completely exploded! What now?
So, you've made your
choice then, have you?
Well...
Does that mean something, or...?
Heh!
[TANYA]
Okay... Game over, I guess?
[AINS]
Seems so.
[SUBARU] I don't actually
remember what we were
fighting about anymore.
Gotta feeling it was
something stupid.
[NAOFUMI sighs]
Yeah, as a matter of fact,
it was something
unbelievably stupid.
[AINS] Forgive me, Tanya.
I was being childish.
It's fine. I'll admit I was
being pretty childish myself.
A childish little girl,
ya' don't say.
Though personally,
I've never heard of an undead
being called that before.
[AINS]
Me either.
Yep, that's a first.
[ALL laugh]
[VISHA] Hey you guys,
since we're all friends again,
let's go out and chow down
on some croquettes!
I'm down! Plus, no one'll argue
about what you put on 'em.
Even I can resist slathering
'em up with mayo.
Really?
Well, I didn't say
"all the time".
I'm not made of stone.
[AINS] Oh, of course.
You agree, Tanya?
Yeah. The only thing they need
is salt and some pepper!
[ALL]
Salt and pepper?