[ERICH]
Your fellow students were caught
stealing from the principal.
Therefore, they are
being punished.
[SUBARU]
Wow, what's the punishment?
They get suspended?
No, we have decided
to detain them.
[SUBARU]
So, like "detention?"
[ERICH] They'll be learning a
lesson they won't soon forget.
[KYOUHUKOU] You've defied the
rules of this institution.
And now it's time for me to
teach you... how to be proud,
upstanding students.
[STUDENTS yell]
[KYOUHUKOU]
My servants are quite ravenous.
But please, you needn't worry.
This is a special world,
so they won't devour you here.
They'll roam through
your internal caverns,
entering through your ears,
mouths, any hole they can find.
Feel them scuttle.
It's cliché, but I have a
bad feeling about this.
I share that feeling.
[ERICH]
Anyway.
When you see them, I ask
that you treat them with care.
[ERICH] Especially you,
Major Tanya von Degurechaff.
I'm counting on you.
[TANYA]
Lieutenant Colonel.
I'll make sure they never
forget their lesson.
[MOMONGA] If they're
trying to use telepathy,
it's not working.
[schoolbell rings]
What do we feed Chomusuke?
[CHOMUSUKE meows]
I was wondering about you!
Tell me. What kind of
punishment did you get?
Did you scream in pain?
Or in ecstasy?
Uh? Hello? Are you there?
Hey! Just gimme
a response, would you?
What in the hell did they
do to you guys in that room?
Well, they... That wasn't
any regular detention.
Yes, they sent the black demons.
Wave after wave of them.
[DARKNESS]
What do you mean?
[MEGUMIN]
Darkness?
What is it?
[MEGUMIN whimpers]
[DARKNESS gasps]
Oh my god! Aqua?
[AQUA]
Huh?
Looks like you've got
something in your hair.
[MEGUMIN whimpers]
[DARKNESS gasps]
[ALL] My brains. My brains.
My brains. My brains. My brains.
[DARKNESS, MEGUMIN gasp]
[DARKNESS] There's gotta be
some way we can save them!
I mean, if they're like
that after one session,
they're not gonna
last much longer!
So they're locked up with
a bunch of tiny creatures?
It doesn't really seem
all that bad to me.
It doesn't?
They've got loads of
little black demons
running all over their bodies.
So scary!
Don't lie. I bet you're
into that, you freak!
Are you kidding? Even a
masochist like darkness
isn't into stuff
that disgusting.
[PUCK]
Really?
So what should we do?
[sighs]
Let's just give up.
[DARKNESS] What?
How could you be so cruel?
What do you want, huh?
After all, there's nothing
we can do.
Hear me out.
We should have a little
talk with Mister Rerugen.
[SUBARU]
Yeah! That's a great idea!
It just might work. Do you
mind approaching him?
No. If I can talk him into
going easy on them, I will.
[EMILIA]
Please, sir.
You think you can find it
in your heart to reduce
their punishment somehow?
[ERICH exhales]
Um, you okay?
[ERICH grunts]
[ERICH] She's such a
compassionate young lady!
The polar opposite of that
demon that wears the skin
of a little girl!
[ERICH] If they perform
some kind of good deed,
then there's a far better
chance their punishment
could be reduced.
So there's a way, Really?
[ERICH]
Yes. A good deed should do it.
I'll speak with the
principal personally, too.
[gasps]
Thank you, sir!
[ERICH]
What a sweet little angel. I--
Hm? What are you looking at?
[DARKNESS gasps]
How'd it go?
Well, he says if they do
some kind of good deed,
their sentences could actually
be reduced a little.
I don't know,
that sounds tough.
[MEGUMIN chuckles]
It's really quite simple!
They're gonna be outta
the hole in no time!
[SUBARU] You're seem pretty
confident about that.
Our next period.
It's science class, right?
[EMILIA]
Yes, why?
[MEGUMIN laughs]
You've got some sort of evil
plan in mind, don't you?
[ROSWAAL] Okay, let the
experiment begin!
[COCYTUS] Hey, girl.
What's wrong with you?
Me? Uh...
[ROSWAAL] Any students
who can use fire magic,
light your Bunsen
burners now, please.
[AINS]
I'll handle this.
Fireball.
So who's gonna light our thing?
Oh. I can ask the spirits
if they would do--
--[CHOMUSUKE meows]
--[SUBARU] Huh?
That cat just breathed fire!
You must be seeing things.
Everyone knows
cats can't do that.
[SUBARU gasps]
Okay. Let's go.
Yeah, sure.
[WEISS]
Hm.
I am Megumin.
What in the hell are you up to?
[AINS]
Tanya.
Yeah?
[AINS] I understand your
desire for discipline.
But you must let them do
what needs to be done.
They're trying to help
our fellow students,
who are suffering in detainment.
But if they cause trouble,
they'll find themselves
imprisoned too.
Mister Roswaal, is he
not gonna stop them?
[AINS] It seems not.
What do you think, Ram?
Despite his general demeanor,
Mister Roswaal is no fool.
[TANYA]
Huh?
[MEGUMIN] ...for when you
implore the explosion,
the explosion magic will
let its answer be known!
Hear my call o fiery force!
Uh-oh.
And unleash... explosion... now!
[ROSWAAL] My, my, my.
You've made quite a mess.
Sorry. We were simply
trying to light the burner.
Yeah, but we screwed up!
I'm so sorry Mister Roswaal.
We didn't mean to!
Quite the blunder, eh?
Well, everybody has bad days.
But as far as boo-boos go,
this one does seem particularly
extreme doesn't it?
[ROSWAAL]
Oh my...
Now, the question is how will
the higher ups respond?
[KURT]
Hm?
Something wrong?
I'm hearing a loud noise.
[HANS] Hm. It sounds like
water rushing to me.
And it seems to be approaching.
[KURT]
It's coming towards my office?
I think so.
What the...?
Sir. Your secret stash of
cigars could be in peril.
We must protect the stoagies!
[KAZUMA gasps]
Hey, You there!
What perfect timing.
I need your assistance.
[KOENIG]
Please Mister Principal!
If we can help
stop the flooding,
will you release
us from detention?
I will. Good deeds
deserve to be rewarded.
[ALL gasp]
Kazuma! Aqua!
Yeah!
Right there with you,
Horse-Face!
My name's Koenig.
[KOENIG]
Alright men, deploy a barrier!
[GRANTZ, NUEMANN]
Right!
[NUEMANN]
Oh yeah!
Kazuma. We'll need to dump
the water once I seal it up.
Yeah!
[KOENIG grunts]
Aqua, on you!
I hear ya. It's really
no problem for me.
I'm the water goddess!
[KAZUMA] Great! Just do
one of your party tricks!
What'd you say? I guess
I've gotta show all of you
why I am the goddess of water.
[KOENIG] I thought she
was just full of crap.
But maybe she does
have some real power?
[NUEMANN]
Yeah. I think she's a goddess!
Here goes! Water, control!
[KAZUMA]
Looks like a party trick to me!
Huh. Whoa...
[PUCK]
Then...
You've all been released
from detention!
What's more, all of you
got to perform a good deed.
[SUBARU] Well, only because
Megumin did a bad deed first.
[MEGUMIN] What? I have no idea
what you mean by that.
[SUBARU]
Sure.
[KAZUMA] Anyway, great work
you guys. Thanks!
Now you just have to really
try not to break any
more rules, okay?
Thanks a lot. I mean it.
No sweat.
But you should really be
thanking your commander instead.
I mean, she could have
stopped us, but she didn't.
Hey, Neumann.
Why don't you go over there
and thank her for us, huh?
Not without some backup.
Don't blame ya.
[ALL laughing]
[KYOUHUKOU] I'm pleased it all
worked out, Mister Roswaal.
[ROSWAAL] Oh, hello there
Mister Kyouhukou, sir!
[KYOUHUKOU] It appears, the
students are closer than ever.
Yes they are, sir. And I pray
that this trend will continue.
[KYOUHUKOU]
Indeed. Oh, by the way.
Would you care to join
me for afternoon tea?
Not happening.