"School Festival"
Are you having fun
at the school festival, everyone?
Yes! We are, ma'am!
I know you're looking forward to
a chance to let loose.
But drinking the water of life
is against the rules. Got it?
Yes. Thus, the probability that Captain Weiss
will cause a problem is now very low.
Yup!
--Hey! I'm not that bad!
--Major! Major!
Oh, Lt. Serebryakov!
Lt. Serebryakov.
Yes, ma'am!
You're having a good time, huh?
Yes! I'm having a very good time!
"Episode 11: It Begins! School Festival"
--Let's go!
--You look really happy.
"Episode 11: It Begins! School Festival"
"Sold Out"
What? They're sold out already?
Somebody tasted too many.
"Muscle Contest"
"School Festival"
Let's have a good time, everyone!
Hey, Seiya, it's a school festival!
Let's go inside!
Let's go inside.
We don't know what danger waits within.
So I'm not going in.
Let's go.
We just got here and we're leaving?
Come on, Seiya, let me have some fun!
You missed!
Ha, ha!
Shut up, Kazuma!
I may not be the best,
but I can at least get one!
The play's about to begin, though.
You're distracting me, so shut up!
Go on, I'll catch up!
--Another miss!
--Let's get going.
Yeah, let's do that, I guess.
I'll stay with Aqua. Go on ahead.
Emilia, you can just ignore her.
Don't say that.
It's fine. I'll catch up.
Okay, if you say so.
See you later!
I'm looking forward to the play!
Emilia's a total angel.
Let me guess what you're thinking.
You don't have to guess. It's "I wish I could
trade her for my party of losers!"
It is, huh?
I guess you really want to
get up close and personal
with my Explosion Magic, huh?
Yeah, something like that.
Matches... Buy some matches, please!
You're disgusting! Don't touch me!
Nobody would help the little girl.
--She can do all these parts herself?
--It's terrible! How could
someone do this to me?
--Amazing!
--I beg you!
--How much time has she spent alone?
--Get lost!
--How terrible! How terrible! I'm so cold!
It's time.
Yeah.
Hey, Kazuma.
Hey, it's the cheater.
You sound like Subaru.
Hey, it's Reinhard the Cheater.
I just said that.
We said the same things, huh?
You're good friends, huh?
Last time I let you guys have the starring role,
but this time, Class 1 will win.
I'm afraid...
...this time we'll win again!
Ains.
Please don't look up.
Just look at me from here down.
From here down.
What is this?
You look so cute, Naofumi!
You're so cute, Master!
This is impossible!
Quit whining, bro!
You guys are looking good!
--Go break a leg!
--That's rough.
--And then break the other leg!
--I sympathize.
--Wait! Why do you sympathize
--And then break the other leg!
--And then a nose! Then a spine!
--with him and not me?
A cute horsey!
Thanks.
You're cute, horsey.
Are we all making fun of me now?
What's up?
I got a message from Albedo.
What is it?
Lord Ains, the mobile fortress Destroyer
has appeared at the school again.
What?
Albedo!
This is the enemy we fought before.
That's right.
That's the mobile fortress Destroyer.
It's got lots of legs and
it stomps on everything,
and for some reason, kids really like it!
I can really understand that!
It's got lots of legs and it's cute!
But it's also heading this way, right?
If we can't stop it,
the school festival is ruined, right?
That's right.
It would ruin the performance
of a supreme being.
That cannot be allowed!
It seems the Destroyer has returned.
What's going on?
Is this another trick of the teachers,
like during field day?
It's not, unfortunatelyyyyy.
What?
It seems this world is even more
complicated than I expeeeeected.
The world never goes like you'll expect.
Of course...
Anyway, let's go stop the Destroyer.
--Yes.
--Yeah. Let's do it.
I'm afraid...
...you can't!
Why?
Because your play is beginning.
You have to do it.
Is this festival that important?
Yes.
I believe it is.
Mr. Ros-chi, what happens
if we protect this world?
Even I don't know that.
But I'm sure a wonderful future
is waiting for ussss...
And is there really nobody in this world
you can rely upon except yourseeeelves?
What does that mean?
There's no need to worry.
We will destroy the Destroyer
before it can interrupt your play.
Correct?
Yes. Let's do it.
Fine.
I'll show you my true strength!
Puck, will you help me?
Of course.
My beautiful daughter.
Then we'll leave it to you.
Albedo, Aqua, Emilia, Visha.
They say they'll stop it.
Madness.
No, it's not.
What?
Emilia's got Puck with her.
And Albedo's pretty tough, too, right?
In terms of simple combat strength,
she's quite powerful.
And you said Visha's good at defense.
If Aqua doesn't ruin everything, we'll be fine.
I was fine a moment ago, but now I'm worried.
Yes. Me, too.
There's no sense in worrying about it.
We have to do our jobs.
Subaru, I understand
your desire to go to Emilia.
We feel the same.
--But...
--Naofumi.
Fortunately, there's time before
Filo and I have to go on stage.
--Can we go help?
--Yes.
I'll go, too, then.
You have an important part.
And... you can't fight like that.
Naofumi, let's entrust everything to them.
Naofumi!
Master!
Raphtalia. Filo.
Just don't do anything stupid.
Yes!
--Let's get going then.
--Yeah.
Well, Class 1 may not need to do anything.
Everyone will be moved to tears
at our performance...
You've got a lot of confidence.
We're pretty good, too, though.
Surreal. This is extremely surreal.
"Dressing Room 2"
I understand.
But Aqua is the fairy godmother.
If she's there...
That's right. Aqua's the only one with a part.
Megumin!
What is it, Kazuma?
You wrote the script, right?
Yes. Why?
Then you know the lines, right?
You take Aqua's part.
I refuse!
I'm not ready...
Megumin, it's an emergency...
I'm afraid I must refuse.
You're right. It's too tough a role for you.
What?
It's got a lot of lines. You're not ready.
No "normal person" could pull it off.
Indeed.
Megumin's a "normal" person.
She would never agree to take such a risk.
You realize that even among the
highly intelligent crimson demons,
I'm considered a genius, right?
Listen, nobody says you have to do this.
Highly intelligent or not, you can't
learn all those lines by the time...
I can! It'll be easy!
Very well!
I shall become the grand wizard,
and guide Cinderella to the ball!
Grin.
I thought it was fairy godmother,
not grand wizard.
Let it go.
All we have to do now
is make the play a success!
You're all ready?
We have to do our best!
Are you ready, Aqua?
I don't like the fact that a devil is
running things, but we have a shared goal.
Let's do it!
Here we go, everyone!
Okay, let's do our best, everyone!
Yeah!
I've got special makeup on today
My boobs are padded 50% more than normal!
I've got a demon's smile on my face
Is it time for my big debut?
I've never done something like this! It's rough!
Time to show everyone how gallant I am!
That's right! Show the whole world my charm!
All right, everyone, let's calm down!
Voices warmed up!
Rehearsal went perfectly!
I'm saying all kinds of crazy stuff,
and my ad-libs are blowing up in my face!
The ditzy girls are about to
put on an amazing show!
Welcome! Come in, sit right down!
It's a miraculous collaboration!
When the four of us get together,
it's a sold-out house!
The acting is terrible,
but the fights are so realistic!
It's a messed-up quartet,
aiming for a happy ending!