"Class 1"
An errand?
Yes. We're all going to be doing
a play for the school festival.
We can do whatever play we want.
So Filo, I want you to pick
the theme for the play.
The theme?
Yes, why don't you go talk to a bunch of people
about what kind of play they want,
and then come up with an idea.
I think you need that experience.
Can you do it?
Okay!
I'll do my best!
I'm counting on you, Filo!
Okay!
It's an invitation from another world!
"Isekai Quartet2"
Another world! This is another world!
Strange things await you!
It's another world, like a dream!
It won't let you go, it won't let you head home
You're not going back to your old world
It's a forbidden passport!
It's a story of four nations,
an other world quartet that gathers once a week!
Another world! This is another world!
Now let's head on a dangerous journey?
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?!
Other world showtime!
The bell's ringing to start the day,
whether you like it or not!
There's no telling what'll happen,
just like the real world!
It won't let you go, it won't let you head home
Other world! Other world!
Other world! Other world! Aah!
SHOWTIME!
This story is fiction!
Warning: use only as directed!
"Episode 9: Investigate! First Errand"
Huh? There's a school festival?
That's what they said.
"Episode 9: Investigate! First Errand"
Mr. Ros-chi never tells us the important stuff.
And all the classes are doing a play?
Yup. What kind of story do you like?
What kind of story...
I want to see a story about my lord!
Doing a play about an Undead
in front of a goddess!
Not a chance!
And stop nodding.
--Death Knight disappeared!
--Again?
--Aqua!
If you want to call yourself a goddess, fine,
but try to get along with others!
I'm not just calling myself a goddess!
I am a goddess!
Well, I think you should be nicer,
but Lord Ains told me to
"be nice to the tsundere."
What does that mean?
It means you're a tsundere.
You're mean to the person you like.
Aqua, the minute you got lectured
by a kid, you already lost.
--Why?
--Oh, Death Knight's back.
Why not talk to more people?
Yeah, I will! Thanks!
It's the skeleton man...
grandpa... skeleton guy!
She tried really hard there.
I'm Ains.
What is it?
Do you need to talk to me?
Um, I'm talking to a lot of people right now!
A play, huh?
Yes.
Hamusuke said he wanted to see
the story of an Undead...
That's wonderful!
A story to tell everyone
how wonderful Lord Ains is!
Truly a worthy gift to a supreme being!
Indeed!
And I can be his empress...
Did you say something, lamprey?
Did you say something, big-mouthed gorilla?
Calm down, both of you.
--Okay!
--Perfect harmony!
Filo, I'm sorry, but we don't
know much about drama.
You'd do better to ask someone else.
For example?
Hmm... How about Kazuma's gang?
Explosion!
Well?
Hmm...
The firepower is concentrated on
a single point, and extremely effective.
Collateral damage is minimal.
An excellent explosion.
What score would you give it?
Forty points.
If you can't shorten the incantation,
it will be difficult to use in combat.
A short incantation is out of the question.
They aren't cool!
What's important is casting time. Not coolness.
Not true.
No, on the battlefield, a single second
means the difference between life and death.
Shorten the incantation time
--Hey, Tanya.
--to efficiently...
Her incantations are a mystery.
We don't even know if she needs
an incantation to cast a spell at all.
She says something different every time.
If I don't use a cool incantation, I will die.
Are you making fun of me?
Is it good, Filo?
It's good!
This is tough.
Everybody says something different.
Hey there.
The girl from Class 2!
You seemed like something
was really bothering you.
Is something wrong?
Um, I'm searching for a theme.
A theme?
Yes. We're doing something called
a "play" at the school festival.
A play at the school festival?
I was asked to find a theme.
So you're going around
to talk to everybody, huh?
But everybody says
something different, so it's hard.
Why not go to the library then?
There's a lot of books there,
so I'm sure you'll find what you're looking for.
The library?
Got it! Thanks, miss!
She's a good girl.
Yup.
Anyway, we have to go find Roswaal and say,
"We didn't hear anything
about a school festival."
Yup.
But, Puck.
Here he's "Mr. Roswaal."
Okay.
"Library"
That book's easy to read. I think
it'll give you some good ideas, too.
"Gentle Fairy Tales"
That book's easy to read. I think
it'll give you some good ideas, too.
"Gentle Fairy Tales"
Now take it and go.
Okay, I'll have Master read it to me.
Thank you, Mare!
Beat...
Beako!
It's not Beako, I wonder!
Bye!
What a rude girl!
Can I ask something?
Yes.
What is it?
Nothing important.
Do you remember how you got to the school?
Lord Ains said he pushed a button.
Lord Ains apologized and said it was his fault.
But he's a supreme being,
so he must have had some reason.
I see.
It's nice to have the person
you believe in right next to you.
Do you not, Beatrice?
Not anymore, I wonder.
What about Subaru?
I can't trust that guy at all!
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I wonder.
What've you got there?
Oh, the wolf girl!
Yup. The wolf girl!
And the girl who's very interested
in what you've got there!
"Gentle Fairy Tales"
This? I got it to help pick the theme
for the school festival.
What about this?
A poor little bird is tricked by an evil man
and turned into fried chicken--
Don't make up stories!
The girls with black hair!
You were told by Lord Ains
to follow the rules of the school.
I'm just trying to see how far
I can bend the rules, is all.
Your name's Filo, right?
You're looking for a theme for Class 1's play?
Yes. And Mare and Beako gave me a book to help!
Mare gave it to you?
Very well. We'll think of something with you.
How about a story where a poor raccoon
is tricked by a man with--
You just did that.
But a normal story is boring!
We're the ones who'll be acting!
It's boring!
And Narberal's a terrible actor--
--A terrible what now?
--Oww! Oww!
But if we're going to act, it would
be better if we could be ourselves.
Though Narberal wouldn't be able
to talk about anything but murder!
--What did you say?
--Oww!
What are you ladies talking about?
None of your business,
you piece of human garbage.
--Scary words from such a pretty lady.
--Yup.
Hearing that from you ugly insects
means nothing to me.
That's it!
The ugly duckling!
The ugly duckling gets terribly insulted
by the other ducklings!
You could just be who you already are!
Yes, that could work in some cases...
It's perfect for you, since you're so violent.
--Who are you calling violent?
--Oww! Oww! Oww!
The Ugly Duckling?
Got it! Thanks, ladies!
And old guys, too!
Yeah, you're wel--
We're not old!
"Class 1"
"And they lived happily ever after."
"The End."
Well, Filo?
Yes, I like it!
Naofumi, this is wonderful!
Let's go with this!
You like it that much?
Yes, I do!
Yeah, it's a great story.
"The real me was actually very noble."
Why are you looking at me when you say that?
Is it okay, Felt?
Um...
Okay, Class 1 will do The Ugly Duckling!
Okay!
Master, I worked really hard!
Yes, well done.
Naofumi, if you'd just asked me...
Sorry.
Next time, I'll have you do something.
Don't treat me like a child!
Jeez...
I've got special makeup on today
My boobs are padded 50% more than normal!
I've got a demon's smile on my face
Is it time for my big debut?
I've never done something like this! It's rough!
Time to show everyone how gallant I am!
That's right! Show the whole world my charm!
All right, everyone, let's calm down!
Voices warmed up!
Rehearsal went perfectly!
I'm saying all kinds of crazy stuff,
and my ad-libs are blowing up in my face!
The ditzy girls are about to
put on an amazing show!
Welcome! Come in, sit right down!
It's a miraculous collaboration!
When the four of us get together,
it's a sold-out house!
The acting is terrible,
but the fights are so realistic!
It's a messed-up quartet,
aiming for a happy ending!