[BEEPING]
[KIM] We're live at
the Xaver Space Center,
where fighters from four
different galaxies
have just landed to take part
in what is being billed as
the first Intergalactic
Martial Arts--
[KIM YELLS]
Tony, did you get that?! Tony?!
Kim here. We'll return
with more coverage
as soon as my cameraman
regains consciousness.
Joining us now is the sponsor
of this unprecedented event:
world famous millionaire
XS Cash. Welcome.
Actually, the credit
should go to my son, Monty.
[MONTY CASH]
Daddy! Daddy! Look at me!
It's for his birthday.
Our psychiatrist loved the idea.
Remember, Daddy, you
promised aliens. Real ones!
[XS CASH] And you
shall have them, my boy!
I have the world's
top scientific minds
working around the clock
to ensure your birthday
wish comes true.
You're going to have the best
space aliens money can buy!
[XS CASH LAUGHS]
Mr. Producer, sir, would
you care to elaborate?
No, your microphones
aren't malfunctioning.
You heard him right!
Mr. Cash is going to
deliver space aliens!
Little Monty's birthday gift
is going to be one the
whole world can enjoy!
[PRODUCER]
The richest man in the
world is about to deliver
the biggest martial arts
championship in its history!
And you don't have
to be out-of-this-world
to join in the fun! Okay...
All fighters,
regardless of age, gender,
nationality, or even species,
can enter the tournament,
which boasts a prize
of one hundred million
zeni for the winner!
[XS CASH]
I don't do anything small!
To that end, the victor will
not only walk away filthy rich,
he, she, or it will get
a chance to challenge
the most revered
champion fighter
ever to step into a ring.
The one, the only,
incomparable...
[HERCULE] Oh yeah!
It's the champ, baby! Yeah!
[HERCULE LAUGHS]
Yes, folks, it's Hercule!
The most powerful man in the
world, possibly the universe!
[CLICK]
[HERCULE YELLS]
Hey, I grabbed some snacks.
There's more in the back
if you guys are hungry.
Did I miss anything?
♪ opening song ♪
[FAN A] Sure, it tastes bad, but
it's Hercule's favorite soda.
[ANNOUNCER]
Welcome to Battle Island,
home to the first-ever
Intergalactic Martial
Arts Tournament.
200 fighters are enrolled
in the preliminary round,
which is now underway
on 8 specially designed
combat stages.
The rules are simple:
on each stage, 25
contestants fight one another
in a free-style battle royale.
Fighters are
disqualified if they faint,
surrender, or
fall into the sea.
The last one standing
on each stage
moves on to the semi-finals.
Killing is prohibited,
of course,
as is the use of weapons.
The combatants
really seem to be
throwing themselves
into the fight,
though not as much
as the audience.
This crowd is out for blood!
But remember, hair like
this doesn't grow on trees.
You need lots of
tender care, and moose.
[KRILLIN YELLS]
Hi-Yah! Yah! Yah!
[KRILLIN LAUGHS]
That's Krillin with two Ls,
and I do accept personal checks.
[CHI CHI] Go, Gohan!
Beat 'em all! You can do it!
Wha...? Gohan's fighting?
But he's a Super Saiyan.
That's not fair.
[PICCOLO YELLS]
Piccolo, too? Where's Trunks?
Make it a full set.
[FIGHTERS YELL]
Huh...?!
[TRUNKS LAUGHS]
Oh, me and my big mouth!
This is now officially unfair.
Chi Chi, I thought you weren't
going to allow Gohan to enter.
He spends hours every day
sitting at his desk studying.
He may be fighting, but at least
he's getting some exercise.
He's definitely
his father's son.
That's for sure.
Personally, I had no choice.
It was either come to
the tournament with Trunks,
or face not seeing
him for an eternity.
I'm just glad
we're all together.
That's the important thing.
It's not so bad.
When Trunks told me he'd beaten
Android 17 and 18
in the future world,
I knew this was coming.
Didn't you ask Vegeta to enter?
Of course not.
Whatever passion Vegeta had
for fighting is long gone.
I don't know what's going
on in that head of his.
Hmm... He hasn't been
the same since Goku died.
[PURPLE MAN YELLS WORRIEDLY]
Yeah, get 'em, Tien!
Ditto, Krillin.
Rah, rah.
Oolong, see any
halter tops down there?
This is insane!
What are you watching,
the fight or the tourists?
[ROSHI] What? You think this
is my idea of stadium seating?
Stop flapping your gums and
keep your eyes on the talent!
[ROSHI YELLS EXCITEDLY]
Ladies!
[GIRLS SCREAM]
Wow, and I thought the world
championship was tough.
Fighting's in your blood.
Unfortunately, you
no longer have any.
The reception's not great,
but at least I get
to watch the fight.
[CROWD CHEERS]
[YAMCHA]
I can't believe Gohan and
Trunks entered the tournament.
Just my luck! One hundred
million beautiful zeni!
Oh, well. It was a nice
dream while it lasted.
[BULMA] Poor Yamcha.
I wonder what's wrong.
He seems to have
lost his drive.
The competition
must be overwhelming.
True. How could anyone
expect to beat Trunks?
Except Gohan!
[BABY TRUNKS MAKES BABY NOISE]
[BULMA AND CHI CHI
GRUNT ANGRILY]
Doskoi! Doskoi!
[YAMCHA SCREAMS]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Out!
Oh, man!
[FIGHTERS YELL]
I heard the World
Martial Arts Tournament
helped hone my father's skill.
Perhaps this intergalactic
version will do the same for me.
[HERCULE CHEWS LOUDLY]
[ANNOUNCER]
Gohan has passed
the preliminary!
[HERCULE YELLS]
[ANNOUNCER]
Trunks will advance.
[HERCULE STAMMERS]
[FIGHTERS YELL]
I wax.
[ANNOUNCER]
Krillin moves on.
[FORK CLATTERS]
And Piccolo is headed for
the semi-finals as well.
[HERCULE STAMMERS]
Lastly, Tien Shinhan
has made the cut.
Doskoi, Udoh, and Sky Dragon
round out the list of fighters
moving on to the semi-finals.
[HERCULE SCREAMS]
Pardon me, Hercule,
what are your thoughts
on the preliminary?
My- my thoughts?
I think, training.
They need more training.
[ANNOUNCER]
Ladies and gentlemen,
the match-ups for the 8
semifinalists have been decided!
Oh, man. I'm fighting Piccolo!
If it wasn't for bad luck,
I wouldn't have any!
[ANNOUNCER] In the first match,
Gohan faces off against Udoh.
[CROWD CHANTS AND CHEERS]
Huh! I'm fighting a baby?
I've got to get a better agent.
Hey listen, kid, I'm not
into beating weaklings,
but the training wheels are
coming off today! Understand?
Yes. I'm ready.
You've got alota guts, kid,
and I'm gonna show 'em to ya!
[UDOH GROWLS]
[UDOH YELLS]
Boo-ya! That's my son!
[HERCULE STAMMERS]
[ANNOUNCER] As we move
on to the second match,
Trunks battles Tien Shinhan.
Hey, Trunks! What do you say we
give these people a good show?
Okay!
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[TIEN YELLS]
They're fighting
in mid-air.
[LOTTA CASH]
Honey, are you sure
they're not using wires?
Tri-beam...
...Ha!
[EXPLOSION]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[TIEN GRUNTS]
[TRUNKS GRUNTS]
[CROWD CHEERS]
[HERCULE GRUNTS FRUSTRATEDLY]
Hercule, sir, can you explain
this extraordinary event?
It's a simple parlor trick!
He made a quick change!
Smoke and mirrors and what not--
[HERCULE AND KIM YELL]
Why, out of all the
tournaments in the world,
did they have to enter mine?
I hate this.
[VEGETA]
Huh... Gimme a break.
[TIEN YELLS]
[EXPLOSION]
Haa!
[TIEN YELLS]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[ANNOUNCER]
Trunks wins the match!
[TIEN BREATHES HEAVILY]
[HERCULE THINKING]
This can't continue!
Uh... Hercule, is
everything all right?
You look
a little pale.
Huh...?
Now that you mention it,
I do have a stomach ache!
[XS CASH]
Relax, it will be all right.
Mr. Producer, take our
star to the infirmary.
[HERCULE]
No, no! That's quite all
right! I can find my own way!
Oh, the pain!
[HERCULE GRUNTS AND GROANS]
I feel a change in the wind.
Time to set sail.
I'd rather flee as champion
than stay and suffer defeat.
Hey, look!
It's Hercule!
Oh...!
Hercule! Hercule! Hercule...!
[HERCULE THINKING]
Oh, the fans love me.
I can't disappoint them!
Good thing I bought
life insurance.
Hercule! Hercule! Hercule...!
[ANNOUNCER]
The third match is about to
begin as Piccolo fights Krillin!
[KRILLIN THINKING]
I can do this!
He's not unbeatable!
Well, unless he uses his
Special Beam Cannon.
Then I'm dead.
[GOHAN] Piccolo!
Go for it! You can win!
Kid should save his breath.
Everyone knows
Piccolo's gonna win.
Ah, humans. They stress
about everything. Pigs rule.
Quiet!
[KRILLIN THINKING]
I may not win,
but I'm going out in style!
I don't believe it.
He's not even gonna look at me?
That's it! I've had it!
I'm nobody's fool!
[KRILLIN YELLS ANGRILY]
[KRILLIN YELLS WORRIEDLY]
[KRILLIN GRUNTS]
Huh...?!
I thought I came for
a tournament, not a freak show!
This is a waste of my time.
[KRILLIN YELLS]
[REFEREE] Piccolo has
forfeited the match!
Krillin wins
by default!
Wow! I guess I don't
know my own strength.
[ANNOUNCER]
Doskoi has advanced and
jumped into the record books
with the longest backward-pivot
throw in history.
How's the fight
going, King Kai?
Any news on Gohan?
Gohan is doing well.
He and his friends have advanced
through the semi-finals.
[GOKU]
That's my boy!
[BUBBLES CHATTERS]
[GOKU SCREAMS]
[GREGORY YELLS]
[HERCULE THINKING]
Hercule, you are a crafty devil.
No one would even think
to look for you down here.
In the clear!
[HERCULE GRUNTS]
[HERCULE]
Yeah, heh heh...
Yeah, heh heh...  Oh yeah...!
I made it! Heh... Heh...
Hercule!
[HERCULE YELLS]
[LOUD THUD]
The infirmary
is back there.
This way leads to the
exit off Battle Island.
I know that!
Can't you see I'm suffering
from a chronic stomachache!
Oh! I must consult
my personal physician.
But Mr. Cash won't like this!
Don't worry about old money
bags! I won't be gone long!
It's just a short boat
ride to the airport
once I cross the bridge, and--
Oh! There's no bridge
underneath me, is there?
I must be sicker than I thought!
Stay back, I'm contagious!
The bridge is missing!
Where did it go?
I can't get off this island!
Hercule! Hercule! Hercule...!
Mr. Cash has decided to spice
things up a little bit
and move the finals
over to Battle Island Two.
We're en route
as we speak.
Ah... Oh...
[ANNOUNCER]
The stage has been set for the
finals on Battle Island Two,
where our four remaining
warriors will compete for
the coveted spot in the
showdown against Hercule!
[CROWD CHEERS]
[CHI CHI]
Gohan, I love you sweetie!
Mom, not so loud!
You own this, Trunks! Get 'em,
and then we can go on vacation!
[TRUNKS THINKING]
Tactful as always, Mother.
Krillin, don't get
yourself killed!
[KRILLIN THINKING]
Oh, I'll survive.
Then it's bacon time.
[ANNOUNCER]
New island, new rules! We've got
4 tunnels running underground.
They lead to special
Battle Zones in each direction.
After the qualifiers
are assigned a tunnel
by drawing lots, they will
be transported to their zones
via rocket shuttles.
There, they will face
our special guests,
fighters from across
the galaxies!
Now, pay attention, here's
where things get really spicy!
Once a fight ends,
the challenge isn't over!
The victor must
take a special lift
and be the first to
return to the center stage,
here on Battle Island!
The winner will then proceed to
the final round against Hercule!
[KRILLIN]
Perfect! It's a race, which
means I'll have the advantage!
[KRILLIN LAUGHS]
After all, I do have
the least wind resistance!
[ANNOUNCER]
Let's begin the countdown!
10!
9!
And 8!
[ANNOUNCER COUGHS]
And they're off!
Viewers can keep up
with all the excitement
by watching the video screens.
[KRILLIN SIGHS]
[KRILLIN]
Oh, no! Ahh! Ahhhh...!!
Ah...! Hmm...?
Ahh...!
[GOHAN LAUGHS]
[GOHAN YELLS]
[SPLASH]
[LOUD THUDS]
[KRILLIN SCREAMS]
Okay. Battle Zone, huh?
Are we supposed to fight,
or have a picnic?
You must be my opponent.
My name is Krillin.
Maybe you've heard of me.
I'm a great fighter/hero,
from Earth.
You'd do well to
stay on your guard.
I've already defeated
Piccolo today.
You might say, I'm on
a winning stre...
[KRILLIN STAMMERS]
Now, don't think you can
tempt me with your beauty.
I have to win first place!
[KRILLIN YELLS]
Hmph...
I think she likes me!
[CROWD WORRIEDLY MURMURS]
K-Krillin!
Doskoi?
[DOSKOI YELLS]
Doskoi!
[LOUD THUD]
[CROWD BOOS]
[BIDO LAUGHS]
Monster!
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
[BUBBLES CHATTERS]
Uh... Umm...
[CROWD YELLS]
This is getting
out of hand!
What a fiasco! I want
an explanation, immediately!
These are not the fighters
that I scheduled!
I've never seen these
creatures in my life!
They're supposed to be
friendly extra-terrestrials!
I wouldn't book this!
They're real!
Mama!
[TIEN] Excuse me.
Oh, no!
[BIRDS CHIRP]
Hmm...
[KOGU LAUGHS]
Watch where you
point that thing.
I might get the wrong idea!
We may be fighting, but this
is still a tournament!
No killing allowed!!
[KOGU YELLS]
[TRUNKS GASPS]
[TRUNKS GRUNTS]
What are you supposed to be?!
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
Someone not to
be trifled with, boy!
[KOGU YELLS]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[KOGU LAUGHS]
Hmm...
[KOGU GRUNTS]
[KOGU SCREAMS]
Uh... Ha, Ha, Ha...
[GOHAN YELLS]
[GOHAN GRUNTS ANGRILY]
[BUJIN LAUGHS]
[GOHAN] Huh...?
[GOHAN YELLS]
Watch it!
You could have killed me!
You have no idea.
[GOHAN CURIOUSLY GRUNTS]
[GOHAN] Alright.
You've got my attention.
[PRODUCER] Hercule!
Please come out! We need you!
[HERCULE THINKING]
He's crazy if he thinks
I'm going out there.
Creatures that can defeat even
the mighty Cell! No thank you!
[MULTIPLE EXPLOSIONS]
[KOGU YELLS]
[TRUNKS YELLS]
[TRUNKS GROANS]
[TRUNKS GRUNTS]
Now surrender!
Fine!
[TRUNKS GRUNTS]
[KOGU GRUNTS]
[KOGU GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[TRUNKS GASPS]
[TRUNKS GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[VEGETA GASPS]
Something's wrong.
[GOHAN GASPS]
Who's there?
[BUJIN LAUGHS SLOWLY]
Come on, Hercule!
Please open this door!
[HERCULE]
Oh, my poor stomach!
Uh... I'm running out
of paper! Y-You got a hanky?
[HERCULE STAMMERS]
[PRODUCER LAUGHS]
[PRODUCER] Uh... Hey Champ!
Hang on a sec there, big guy.
You've got a passenger, Champ!
[KIM]
Is that a new costume?
Ladies and gentlemen,
the wait is over!
We've just gotten
word that Hercule
is on his way to defeat
the space villains!
Keep your eyes peeled!
We're about to see
history in the making!
Hercule! The Brave, the Mighty!
Humanity's Champion!
[HERCULE YELLS]
Quick! Send him
before he gets up!
Yes sir!
W-Wait! Don't I get a seatbelt?
[KING KAI]
Earth is in grave danger.
[GOKU]
From what?
[KING KAI]
You mean who.
Bojack.
[GOKU GULPS]
Uh, Bojack?
[KING KAI]
A dark demon of the worst sort,
psychotic, unstable,
filled with malice and rage.
Long ago, he tried to
destroy every galaxy
within the Dormidia Sector.
[GOKU]
Sounds like King Piccolo.
[KING KAI]
Yes, but far more powerful.
He has an insatiable
appetite for genocide.
We, the Kais, took it upon
ourselves to stop him.
All four of us fought together
and sealed Bojack within a star
at the edge of this galaxy.
[GOKU]
He's trapped in a star?
[KING KAI]
Not any more.
You set him free, when
you destroyed my planet
during your battle
against Cell!
The seal was broken,
leaving Bojack unbound.
Now he has returned
for vengeance.
And it looks like his first
target is planet Earth.
Then he's already defeated!
My son will stop him.
[GOHAN GRUNTS ANGRILY]
[GOHAN THINKING]
Krillin!
Trunks, wake up!
Come on, Krillin!
[BOJACK]
Company. Good.
[GOHAN GRUNTS ANGRILY]
[BOJACK]
It's been so long...
...since I've snapped
someone's neck.
His energy is amazing.
You monsters!
What've you done to
the intergalactic fighters?
They were trespassing.
Earth belongs to my master, now.
[BOJACK LAUGHS]
Oh yeah?
Not while we're
still breathing!
Master Bojack
has no equal.
The universe is
littered with the bones
of those who dared
to think otherwise.
[BUJIN] Master is not patient.
You would be wise to stand down.
Or, better yet, kneel!
We'll pass, thanks.
[TIEN YELLS]
[YAMCHA GROANS IN PAIN]
Let's go.
[BIDO YELLS]
[GOHAN YELLS]
[EXPLOSION]
[BIDO YELLS]
[GOHAN SCREAMS]
[EXPLOSION]
[BIDO GROWLS]
[BIDO YELLS]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[GOHAN GRUNTS]
[BIDO YELLS]
[GOHAN SCREAMS]
[BOJACK]
Impressive.
His level of skill is even
more advanced than I'd hoped.
This should be fun.
[GOHAN YELLS]
[BIDO YELLS]
[LARGE EXPLOSION]
[RUMBLING]
[TRUNKS GRUNTS]
He's in danger!
Gohan, draw strength from
your anger. Get furious!
[GOHAN GRUNTS IN ANGER]
[GOHAN GRUNTS IN PAIN]
Great. Uhh...
Hmm...?
Am I glad to see you!
Looks like you found
a good fight. Mind if I cut in?
Hmm...?
[PICCOLO YELLS]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[BOJACK YELLS]
[PICCOLO GRUNTS]
[PICCOLO YELLS]
[GOHAN YELLS]
Piccolo!
[BOJACK LAUGHS]
[BOJACK YELLS]
Bojack, you will not
take this planet!
[TRUNKS GRUNTS]
[TRUNKS YELLS]
[TRUNKS SCREAMS]
[TRUNKS GRUNTS
WHILE STRUGGLING]
[BUJIN LAUGHS]
[TRUNKS YELLS]
[BIDO GRUNTS]
[EXPLOSION]
Father!
[VEGETA]
Leave him to me.
[BOJACK LAUGHS]
Vegeta.
[VEGETA YELLS]
[BOJACK LAUGHS]
[EXPLOSION]
I don't understand you, Father.
You've withdrawn
into the shadows
ever since Goku's been gone.
And now, suddenly,
here you are defending us.
[VEGETA YELLS]
[BOJACK LAUGHS]
[TRUNKS GASPS]
[VEGETA]
Trunks! Stay back!
Father, let me help.
You're not strong enough.
Don't make me
tell you twice.
Piccolo.
[PICCOLO]
You have to leave me.
I'm no use to you now.
You have to stop them.
Right!
[VEGETA YELLS IN PAIN]
[BOJACK SCREAMS]
[VEGETA SCREAMS]
[BOJACK LAUGHS]
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
[TRUNKS YELLS]
[TRUNKS GRUNTS
WHILE STRUGGLING]
[GOHAN]
Vegeta!
What's your hurry, little boy?
Gohan!
My Trunks!
No, please! Can't I
just sign autographs?
[PRODUCER]
Let 'er rip!
Good-bye.
[TRUNKS YELLS]
[GOHAN STAMMERS]
[GOHAN GRUNTS ANGRILY]
[GOHAN YELLS]
U-Uhh...
I just love a captive audience,
and you're not going anywhere,
thanks to our barrier.
The more you struggle, the more
energy it drains from your body
until you pass out or die!
[BUJIN LAUGHS SLOWLY]
Now, give your father
a message for me.
[GOHAN SCREAMS]
[HERCULE YELLS]
Ah...! Oh...
Oh no! Hercule!
For your sake, I hope
that wasn't the cavalry.
That's it!
[FIGHTING SOUNDS]
King Kai, there's gotta be
something we can do to help!
[BOJACK GRUNTS]
[BOJACK LAUGHS]
[GOHAN GRUNTS IN PAIN]
How ironic that your father's
death was the key to our escape.
I so wanted to
thank him personally,
but now you'll have
to do it for me.
King Kai!
[KING KAI HEAVILY EXHALES]
[GOHAN GRUNTS IN PAIN]
Father.
[BOJACK LAUGHS]
[GOKU GRUNTS ANGRILY]
My son needs my help!
Ah! You can't go,
Goku! You're dead!
[GOKU YELLS]
[BOJACK YELLS]
Wake up! The world is
depending on you, Gohan!
Father.
Believe in yourself, son.
Unleash your true power.
It's the only way!
Yes, sir.
[BOJACK GRUNTS]
Was that Goku?
[GOHAN GRUNTS]
[GOHAN]
I know you're out there, Father.
You came back to save me,
and I won't let you down!
[GOHAN YELLS]
Heh...
I know your kind.
You think you can waltz in
and just take our planet.
[BOJACK LAUGHS]
But you forgot one thing.
I'm my father's son!!!
[RUMBLING]
[CROWD YELLS WORRIEDLY]
[LIGHTNING STRIKES]
[BOJACK STAMMERS]
Bujin! Bido!
[GOHAN SCREAMS]
[BIDO YELLS]
[ZANGYA STAMMERS]
[BOJACK LAUGHS]
[ZANGYA YELLS]
[ZANGYA SCREAMS]
[EXPLOSION]
[BOJACK LAUGHS]
[BOJACK YELLS]
[EXPLOSION]
[BOJACK GRUNTS]
[BOJACK GASPS]
I will kill you!
[BOJACK YELLS]
[BOJACK SCREAMS]
[LIGHTNING STRIKES]
[GOHAN GRUNTS WEARILY]
[THUD]
Yep, that's my boy.
Even though you had to break
the rules so he could do it.
Uhh...!
[GOKU] I'm sorry.
How many have I broken?
[KING KAI]
I don't know. Ask the monkey.
He's the one keeping score.
[KING KAI, GOKU,
AND BUBBLES LAUGH]
[KRILLIN]
"Hercule saves world, twice."
This guy makes front page
while we're in the hospital.
Heh... Say what you'd like,
but if he hadn't crashed
into Bojack and his goons,
we might not even
be here right now.
Yeah, when it comes to freak
accidents, Hercule's a pro!
[OOLONG AND CHIAOTZU LAUGH]
Ahh...
Thanks, Dad.
[OOLONG]
Gohan, you defeated Bojack.
You realize what this means?
With the right press, you
could be as huge as Hercule!
Well, almost.
If you found a big enough wig!
[BULMA]
He doesn't wear a wig!
[KRILLIN] Oh, come on.
Nothing on that man is real!
He probably bought his
chin at a thrift store!
[EVERYONE LAUGHS]
♪ closing song ♪