Be gone, you lazy slutbag!
What good are you to me now?
Bitch, you got no power!
Last time, on
Panty and Stocking.
With Garter Belt.
You couldn't give less of
a shit about killing ghosts.
You wanna show you're worthy?
Go collect your own coins!
No fucking allowed!
Hell no!
Shit.
Ouch!
Oww!
Shit, shit, shit,
shit, shit, shit!
Ow, no!
Just as I thought.
Girl, you've been revirginized.
The good news is you're
no longer a skank;
the bad news is you
have a hymen again.
Hymen? You're fucking
with me, right?
It appears the descendent
of the Hell's Monkey
has been awoken
by an angel's kiss.
Just a little nudge!
Finally, it's mine!
Panty!
Geek Boy!
Why?
I don't understand.
Panty, sugar, how long you
planning to sleep, sweetie?
How's it goin', Panty!
You plannin' on
sleepin' all day?
Maybe!
And so what if I do?
Mornin' Granny!
Well, at least she got
herself outta bed afore noon.
Woo-hoo!
You know.
I've never been so happy.
I don't ever wanna leave here.
Thanks, Granny.
It's perfect.
Now, sweetie.
Happiness is in your heart;
that's got nuthin' at
all to do with me.
But really.
You sure you wanna
spend your life
hangin' out in the country
with an old woman?
Absolutely!
What else could I possibly want?
I mean, I've got you
and Sam with me, right?
I don't need anything else.
All right then.
Just know one day you
might feel differently.
What's this, Granny?
What's what?
Oh, that's just a
silly old photograph.
You know you look just like I
did when I was your age, missy.
Granny! Please,
Granny, talk to me!
Darn it!
Those bikers from the other
side of the tracks are here!
Dear, you have to understand.
It's time for me to go.
Granny?
You see.
My husband's waitin' for me;
now who's waitin' for you?
Oh no! Dying crazy talk!
Look up there, honey.
Geek Boy?
You know what you wanna do,
you just gotta go do it.
No.
I won't listen to my feelings;
they get in the way.
I just can't.
Shut up! Goddamnit.
I'm a dyin' Granny,
and when a dyin' Granny says
something, you listen to her!
Sorry.
A woman is a free creature.
Do what's in your heart.
If you screw up, get a guy to
take care of it and move on.
Not that you couldn't
do it yourself.
But what's the point if some
idjet's willin' to do it for ya?
Adios, my angel bitch.
Granny, no!
Adios, Granny.
Adios.
And, cut!
That's a wrap, folks;
let's pack it up!
Talk about your
high maintenance jobs.
That was rough.
Yeah, it's me.
Looks like everything's moving
according to the schedule.
The girl's on her
way out to you now.
Thanks a lot, Trixie.
Let's roll, Chuck!
Your stubbornness is impressive!
The Hell's Gate
keyhole is wide open,
but the all-important
key won't go in
while you're in such a state.
Allow me to improvise!
Well, this is interesting!
He certainly knows his bondage.
How does that feel?
Not everyone gets to
experience such tightness.
Yes!
It's no use, Corset!
We're stronger than you!
My penis will never give it up!
Dead puppies and Grandma!
You know, you never
stop fucking up, Geek Boy.
What? Panty!
It's the Little
Slut Virgin Who Could.
Lovely to see you
again, princess.
But don't you know
that little angels
who have little hymens
lose all their little powers.
You're just a little bitch, now.
You're right, I'm just a little
bitch, and I'm proud of it.
But, guess what, douche bag.
That's not the point.
Newsflash: I don't need
special fuckin' powers
to beat the shit out of you.
You know why?
Because I'm a bitch
who doesn't give a fuck!
You and your half-dead
face can preach about hymens
and demons and
other weird words
that supposedly mean shit.
But that doesn't change the
fact that if any of you fuckers
get in my way, I'm gonna
kick some twisted-ass ass.
Ya hear me, dick?
I'm a hot bitch
angel named Panty.
And no matter what anyone says,
I do what I fuckin' want!
Adorable!
Well, go ahead bitch angel.
By all means, do what you want.
We'll just sit back and watch.
Well. What's the
problem darling?
Leap on up there!
Sounds like someone's
virginity is getting in the way.
It's horribly shocking, I know.
I think it might be scaring her!
Are you starting to get it?
Freedom of choice
is just a fantasy
whether you're an angel
or a normal ho bag.
Reality's tough.
Wear a cup, bitch.
You should have learned by
now I will never be defeated.
Least of all by a
fallen, powerless angel
who lets a little membrane
get between her and her goals.
Here, let me take
care of it orally!
Hi. Panty.
Hi.
Still as fuckin'
awkward as ever.
Yeah, uhm...
What are you doing?
Finishing what we started, duh.
Don't you want to
be my thousandth?
Though, honestly,
with way I am now.
You're actually gonna
be my first, Brief.
Don't you remember?
I'm a re-virgin.
Stop it!
You bitch!
Panty!!
No!
If the power inside
the key blows its load
or any other orgasmic metaphor,
it will be useless
to me forever!
Demon Sisters!
Stop that bitch now!
Right!
It's that other
disgusting angel!
Stockin', hey!
Hi, Panty!
Congrats, girl!
It looks like you
finally got to a thousand!
Please, bitch, like that
shit's what I'm here for.
I don't want to see
your sexual organs,
so if you could do that not
in my face, that'd be great.
Meanwhile, I'm
gonna kick some ass!
No, no, no!
Oh... oh. ohhhh. Oh, Brief!
I never knew it
could feel like this!
Nice.
We're facing demons,
and she's getting laid.
Once again you
angels are in my way,
and for that you
will surely pay!
You shall both suffer
in an epic fashion!
Yoink!
Oh dear.
Sorry for the wait!
I hope you guys are ready
for a fuckin' party, now!
So, in the immortal words,
of Panty and Stocking Anarchy.
Say it with me.
Repent, motherfuckers!
Holy shit, I feel amazing!
Fucking Brief gave me all
my powers back plus more.
At least it feels that way!
Oh.
Heads up.
We got a Geek Boy falling!
Help me! Panty!
I missed!
Everything's going
according to plan.
She's de-revirginized.
Her hymen has been
thoroughly destroyed,
so she's gained all of
her angel powers back.
God works in mysterious ways.
Well that was close.
Shit! Too close, too close!
Holy moly! This is bad!
Um. I just screwed
Hell's keyhole.
What the shit-fuck?
This isn't according
to plan at all!
Hey, what's up douchefro!?
B dubs, I'm still pissed
at you for kicking me out!
Panty, we have other problems!
Oh my God!
Someone get me
out of here!
You look hilarious
up there, bro!
That's how you awaken
the Hell's Monkey,
you dumb cum dumpsters!
Don't laugh!
Oh, look, Garterbelt has
graced us with his presence!
Fuck off!
So, what's the deal, Corset?
You seriously think you're
gonna open the Hell's Gate here!
Absolutely!
You can thank your boyfriend
for generously penetrating
the keyhole for us!
Happy accidents and
so on and so forth.
Yes!
The Hell's Gate Key will
now open the door to,
you guessed it, Hell!
Release the ancient seal
and fulfill your destiny
once and for all!
Isn't it beautiful?!
Locked away behind this gate,
trapped by God, lies the
ghost to end all ghosts!
Jesus, Mary and Joseph!
Holy motherfucking
goddamnit shit!
Angels, we can't
let this happen!
My, you've transitioned
from brainless
to spineless so
easily, Garterbelt.
Not that I'm surprised.
Feel free to sit back,
and enjoy the show!
So tacky.
Uh huh, for real.
Corset.
You haven't changed at all.
You've always liked tying
everyone up into knots.
Well, dominate this!
Who's whose bitch now?
Me, your bitch?!
Don't make me laugh!
You'll always be the
sub to my dom, Garter!
The weak wear the chains!
And the strong wield the whip!
I'm about to get Marquis
de Sade all over your ass!
What?
This is your ghost?
He looks like a big
old limp dick to me!
Right, Stockin'?
Sounds like it's
circumcision time, asshole!
What the?
This smells worse
than the time Panty
had that masturbation
contest with herself!
Fuck!
That smut motel was
like a second home!
No! That jerk just destroyed
a perfectly good candy
shop slash bakery!
Bastard!
Wait!
Don't be stupid hookers!
You can't just attack it
without thinking first!
I quite agree!
Rather careless to
allow those illiterate,
hobby horse angels
to distract you.
I would have loved to
play with you longer,
but fate just wouldn't have it.
Moving on to the
next opportuni--
What the--
Suck my cock, motherfucker,
you ain't goin' nowhere!
Hey.
Try to pay attention,
my angel hos!
This tiny-dick
compensator is planning
to use that ghost's
power to get into Heaven!
You shut up!
You bitches understand
what I'm saying?!
If this evil skid mark
makes his way up there.
Heaven, Earth, and
everything in between
will be forced to obey
his pussy demon rules!
You gotta stop him!
I don't care how, just
stop this motherfucker!
Hey, Panty?
Is Garter's trying to be helpful
or is he just bein' an asshole?
Who knows?
Though, does it really matter?
I mean, either way
he's still full of shit.
You're not going to get
very far without this.
I don't have to
go anywhere, Corset.
God may not be in this city.
But we've got
two bad ass angels!
Oh my God!
Garterbelt, no!
I'll keep Affie safe for you!
What a delicious
appetizer that was.
Now for the main course.
Dude, Garter.
Backlace isn't
doing shit right now.
We've got a problem, so fix it.
Wait a sec.
Where is he?
He's dead!
Corset squished his heart!
Wow, that sounds like
a painful way to go.
Yeah, but at least
it had some style.
You guys aren't even sad?
What the hell?
You're the worst angels ever!
You're both a couple of bitches.
You're selfish and
really, really cruel!
Why can't you ever be serious?
Um, we're always
serious, asshole!
Especially when it
comes to being cruel.
So, anyway.
We have to do something
about that stench.
Totally.
Plus, creeper dude is
way too fucking cocky.
Can we kill him, please?
I'd love to, but our weapons
are acting like cunts right now.
Will this work?
It seems like it should.
An afro, thank you!
No! Shit!
What the fuck is
wrong with you, man?!
Credit card!
Chuck!
Chuckles!
You need to get serious
sometimes, too, you know!
Fuckin' A!
Chuck, you look sick!
This is awesome!
You know, I never woulda
figured bitch-about-being-poor-
all-the-damn-time
Garter would have
a black Heavens
Express credit card.
And we have unlimited
Heavens with it,
which means we get to
buy anything we want
and even stuff we don't want!
Hurry!
Turn the catalog on, girl!
I'm working on it-this
is the best day ever!
What the fuck is
happening to this place?
Save our city, Lord, and
maybe us while you're at it!
Hey, what's that shiny light?
Is it God?
Or the devil?
No!
It's angels!
This is our moment!
I shall be the vessel
that pours Hell into Heaven!
What the hell is that?!
Oh my God, has anyone
ever told you this
whole nasty demon bullshit gets
really old really fucking fast?
I mean, seriously,
you're evil, we get it.
Can you please just
shut the fuck up?
And don't forget
Earth is our home now;
we're not about to let some
passé cocaine chic S and M freak
job put nipple clamps all
over our hood without a fight.
Okay, it's sent!
O pitiful shadows
and evil spirits born
of those drifting
between Heaven and Earth!
May the thunderous
power from our garments.
Strike down up on you with great
vengeance and furious anger!
May that power shatter
your loathsome impurities
and return you from
whence you came!
No, you can't!
Stop!
If you shoot,
you'll ruin everything!
What?
Hey, Meth Face, at what point
have we ever done what you said!
In other words,
toss my salad, dipshit!
Yeah, we're sorry.
But we're not into your
public masturbation games;
we keep that crap at
home where it belongs!
Don't do this!
You can't!
Who are you people?
Angels.
Obviously.
Hey, Stockin'?
Panty!
Let's do this!
Oh, Corset?
Repent, you mother fucker!
Uh, so that's an oopsie.
Yes! You idiots!
You actually shot it
the wrong direction?!
You really are a special breed
of ignorant, you know that?
Panties?
What the fuck?
She's got stockings, too.
What? I don't get it.
Hurts so good!
That was weird.
Yep.
Mommy?
Garter, they did it.
Panty and Stocking managed
to save Heaven and Earth!
God my oh!
It's all over now.
Yay, I'm alive!
How are you, Mister Stumpy!
He's back to normal!
You didn't fuck it up, angels.
What?
Garter?
We thought you
were in Deadsville!
Thanks to you,
peace has been preserved
in all of Heaven and
certain parts of Earth.
Almost exactly as
I'd planned, too.
Yeah!
Yay!
--Fuck, yeah!
--Yay, yay, yay, yay, yay!
So, apparently, I'm not
allowed to die just yet.
Guess that means I've still got
more shit work to do on Earth.
What the fuck is my
black card doing out here?!
We maxed it out; I mean,
you were dead, right?
Why would you care?
What kind of angels are you?
You're supposed to be emissaries
of God, not fuckin' thieves!
He's so goddamn dramatic.
I guess we're not going
back to Heaven any time soon.
I guess not.
That's cool.
This is more our style anyway.
Wait for me!
On the brink between
Heaven and Hell is Daten City.
A place regularly
threatened by evil spirits.
Only two can wield
a light beyond all
human understanding and
eradicate these shadows.
They are Panty and Stocking!
Home, sweet fuckin' home!
What's for dinner, Garter?
Hey, Panty!
Yeah?
You know how our heavenly
weapons kill ghosts
and shit but don't work
on people, like at all?
Yeah.
I wonder what
they do to angels.
Fuck if I know.
I mean you would
have to try it to see.
That was not according to plan!
Oh my god!
Ow!
She's been cut into 666 pieces!
That's the most hilarious
thing I've ever heard!
Stocking.
Why?
I'm sorry.
But surprise, I'm
actually a demon.
Check this out;
it's gonna be super fun.
I'm gonna make a
trail of Panty's pieces!
Gather them up as you follow
the path, and you'll end up
in the nearby town of Oten City
where the Hell's
Gate Keyhole now lies!
It's a scavenger hunt!
Once you're there, stick
your dirty business
into the open hole just
like you did before,
only then will I return
your precious Panty to you!
I'll be waiting!
God my oh!
Go!
Follow the Panty path!
Brief and Chuck, be on your way!