"Excretion Without
Honor and Humanity."
Daten City, a town clinging
to the threshold between
Heaven and Hell, where the
peace of its human inhabitants
is regularly threatened by
foul tempered, evil spirits.
A fetid darkness lodged in
the cracks of troubled souls
will obstruct this
town today, unnoticed.
Silent.
Deadly.
However, there are some who
wield a light beyond all
human understanding and ascend
their stools of righteousness
to eradicate those shadows
bound by the bowels of hell.
But who could have
been given the duty
of eliminating this darkness?
Are they servants of God
or minions of the devil?
Shit! What the hell is goin' on?
Having a good morning, Panty?
That's your cue
to go, sweet cheeks.
So, I'll call you, and--yeah?
And how you feelin'
this morning, Stocking?
Fuck off.
Don't talk to me until
I've had my goddamn sugar.
Heaven has blessed
us with a clue that
should lead us to
another ghost to take out!
Listen up!
Water closet!
That means bathroom.
We have reports of
people being suddenly
and inexplicably
sucked into their toilets,
almost as if the commodes
are eating them alive.
Taking a massive dump is one of
the most vulnerable positions
a person can find themselves in.
For someone or something
to prey upon that weakness
is a vicious and damnable act!
Woe, this be
the work of a ghost.
All I need out of life
is to wake up
next to some morning wood.
Is there anything hard
you refuse to jump on?
Oh, stop it with the
self-righteous bullshit.
Everyone's got a hobby.
Yeah, that's true.
I'll stick with sugar.
Don't you ever crave protein?
Don't you ever not?
Hey, it's good for you!
Ain't that right, Garter?
Shut up!
First of all,
why the fuck do you think
I know the answer to that?
And secondly, if you don't
want to be stuck here forever,
the only option you
pathetic excuses for anything
resembling angels have is to
buy your way back into heaven
with Heaven Coins you collect
exterminating evil ghosts!
Contrary to popular belief,
you are not here to
collect men or sugar!
So focus and stop
acting like fat ass hoes!
So what're you thinking?
Eh, fuck it; let's go.
Hey, Stockin'?
What is it, Panty?
You ready to roll?
Yeah!
I love how See Through
always gets us
wherever we need to go with
some mother fuckin' style!
Get it, girl!
Get it!
Yes!
It's never flowed better.
Oh God.
You are a master at your craft.
Uh, yeah, thanks.
I'll stop by later
and check up on it.
My, aren't you just
the sweetest darn thing?
But I think you need
to stay a bit longer
cause I've got something
else you can check up on.
Bingo!
Found him!
A toilet and a plumber dude?
Yeah, that's him.
Are you sure?
That's the fucker
we're looking for.
Isn't that right asshole?
Tell me, do you
feel lucky punk?
Well, do ya?
Do ya?
That might not be him.
I don't think it's him.
Color me shocked.
Please stop hitting me.
It really hurts.
I haven't done anything!
Fuck, you're a hot piece of ass.
You are preaching
to the vag, sister.
Hang on to these for me.
Gross.
Well, he's feeling lucky now.
But he was just a plumber.
So true.
And my pipes are totally clean.
How long have you been
waiting to use that joke?
Fuck, it seems like forever.
I couldn't not,
ya know what I mean?
What are you saying?
I don't mind
fucking for a laugh.
Your acting like you
don't even give a shit!
Oh Lord, grant me the patience!
Let's just fuckin' eat.
Shit was that good!
Your curry is unreal, Garter!
That's cuz it's black, baby.
You won't ever go back.
So what's up for dessert?
I'm guessing chocolate
for no reason in particular.
Well, I don't give a shit.
So, I'm gonna go take one.
I'll be in the can
if you need me.
Don't let the toilet eat you!
Oh, screw off!
We should have picked
up some chocolate bombs
from the Meadow Muffin Bakery!
Those plops of gooey
dough just never get old!
Does she even hear
what she's saying?
I just want tasty brown goodness
in my mouth all the time.
Is that too much to ask?
Oh, God!
My mouth is watering
just thinking about it!
Fuck!
Shit!
Stockin'!
Help me!
Goddamnit, Stocking!
Shut up, Panty!
No one wants to talk to you
while you're taking a dump!
That's so disgusting!
I hope you shit your
face off while you're
shitting your guts out if
that makes you feel any better.
Okay.
I get it now.
Okay, you get what now?
Maybe the what's curry.
Oh, yeah.
I get it.
Well we don't get it.
What the hell is that thing?
It looks like a huge ass
scoop of chocolate ice cream.
Hey, I want some!
Yummy!
Freeze, shithead!
Don't make any
sudden movements!
Shit fart doodoo!
Holy shit!
What the fuck are we gonna do?
Oh.
No offense, Preacher Man,
but Jesus God--what is that?
Unfortunately, you be staring
into the brown eye
of an evil spirit.
The negative energy created
by all the plumbers who've
suffocated and died from the
stench of clogged-ass toilets
has manifested
himself into a vengeful spirit.
This powerful ghost utilized
all the fecal matter in the city
to achieve his poodie-poop
physical form!
That's disgusting!
Oh, God!
He's gonna spew!
I don't think I can handle
any more bodily functions.
Suck it up, dude!
Not literally though.
Oh, shit, I'm gonna hurl again.
Please don't tell me
prayer is the only thing
that can get us out of this.
Why the heck would
I tell you that?
God ain't even here right now.
Prayer can go to hell, man.
We got angels!
Panty and Stocking, you're up!
What?
Are you talking about that
walking turdsicle over there?
And that goth chick next to it,
who obviously has daddy issues?
It's time for us
to flush the toilet.
Number one, that was cheesy;
number two, you smell like shit.
How about I buy you a cake
from that fancy bakery and
you manage to do this without
saying another fucking word?
As long as what I'm saying
now doesn't count, I'm in.
Then let's make this fucking
fucker pay for covering me
in this fucking shit;
okay you can reply to that.
Let's rock.
O, pitiful shadow
lost in the darkness.
O evil spirit born of those
drifting between
Heaven and Earth.
May the thunderous power from
the garments of these holy,
delicate maidens strike down
upon you with great vengeance
and furious anger, shattering
your loathsome impurity
and returning you
from whence you came.
Repent, you motherfucker!
This blows!
Good Angels.
You got a coin.
All that for just one?
Yeah, one closer,
so quit your bitching.
"The evil has been vanquished!"
So rings the bell.
At least I'm assuming
that's why it's ringing.
Now, keep your promise
and go buy me that cake.
I need sweet stat.
Yeah, yeah.
Look, I found a tasty
little treat for me, too!
Whatever you say, ma'am.
You're an angel!
You still have a
punishment to face.
Oh, like what?
Bondage?
What would I get out of that?
Uh, yeah; I've got plans, so you
can leave me the hell alone.
Shit!
Death Race 2010!
Come on, are you
fucking kidding me?
Faster does not mean
better, you asshole.
Dude. You're one
hard-core angel.
You get my motor running.
How is this fair?
Look how many
times you've cum!
I've only squirted once
and it wasn't that far.
You know what, babe?
You're more like a
devil than an angel.
Real fucking profound.
You're too old to rock
leather pants, by the way.
Seriously.
You look like
Mick Jagger's grandpa.
Whoa, what's going on here?
This is an incredible
turn of events!
If you're just joining us, an
unmanned sports car is somehow
running wild--
That thing looks like it
might even be faster than you!
No way! Nothing can outrace
my ride! Wait. What?
Hey, is that Stockin'?
The police are
currently redirecting traffic--
This is Panty.
Where are you at?
I am, uh, visiting the
elderly at a nursing home.
Don't lie to me!
You're at that immoral hotel!
Shit! Whoops.
I got another call!
Panty! Are you watching TV?
Nope. So what's up?
You diddling
another douche bag?
Get your skank ass
out here and help me!
Fine. I'll go.
Jesus, calm down!
It's not like this guy is
rocking my world or anything.
I wasn't kidding.
My bike is wicked fast.
Yeah, guess what, fuckface.
A little technique doesn't hurt.
Oh thanks for the ride.
Get outta the way, losers!
That means I'm gonna
run your asses over!
And no one can stop me!
He's run over
everyone in his path,
spilling the blood of
numerous innocent victims!
It's an alarming
case of road rage!
Come on!
Aw, are you trying
to catch me, kitty cat?
Well, bring it on, bitch!
But, to be honest,
I don't think you're gonna be
able to handle what I'm packing!
That means I have a big dick!
Nice!
These boots are fantastic!
Hah. Bingo!
Now, one of your
salespersons talked me
into buying this
atrocity yesterday.
They had me convinced
it looked good,
but I resembled a sideshow
circus freak in it. I would
like to return this horrible
outfit for a full refund,
and I want an apology!
Yes!
Not even close!
Hey, what's up, shit pickle?
So where are you off to
in such a fucking hurry?
Who the hell cares where I'm
off to, as long as I get off!
Oh, yeah, good one.
That means
ejaculate, specifically!
Yeah, I got that.
Trust me, queef breath,
if there's anything I
understand, it's the big 'O'.
It's about time.
Did you mount everything
on your way over?
You two know each other?
I did not.
But I'll be sure to make
that happen for you next time.
Get a load of this.
Take it all!
I bet you like it
rough, don't you?
Oh, yeah!
That's what you
get for being late!
Shit!
Where did Backlace go?
What's on my face?
Hey, who turned
out the lights?
My gun is on your face!
Well, technically,
it's my panties.
Shit! On the bright side,
it does smell like
I'm going really fast!
Stop licking that right now!
Bet you've never
said that before.
Move over!
Go, See Through! Go!
It looks as though the Anarchy
Sisters, Panty and Stocking
have finally joined forces
and are determined
to catch this unruly roadster!
Wait, we may not need our
angelic assassins, after all!
A convoy of police
cars is closing in on
the creepy coupe from behind!
What the hell?
You're totally stealing
our job, ya thiefs!
Take this!
And this!
That means suck it, coppers!
Opa!
Are you trying to
create a barricade?
Against me?
You idiots!
Who the hell do
you think you are?
The Spartan army?
I'm gonna gladiate the fuck
outta you donut-eating dipshits!
I'm outta here!
Ah, life in the fast lane.
Just makes you finish quicker.
That means you're dead.
Wait!
Chill the fuck out;
I gotta get my panties first!
Later suckers.
Jump here and I am in!
That's not good.
Now you do realize
this is all your fault?
I'm aware, thanks.
That doesn't mean you can
destroy my panties though, okay?
Not being made of
fiberglass is awesome!
It's time for payback,
you scumbag pigs.
Which I'm saying
'cause you're all cops!
Hey, fat ass!
I have an idea!
Why don't you let me help
you lighten your load?
Are we rolling?
You got nothing!
Shit, except that!
Goddamnit!
Stop, that hurts!
That means ow!
Mother fucking ow!
Sonofabitch you're brutal!
Ugh gross.
Gunpowder smells
like old hag stank.
What's wrong?
Hey dick angel, are
you giving up already?
No way.
Is this a challenge?
What, are you playin'
chicken with the rooster, bitch?
I give you credit though.
You've got some massive balls!
Shove it up your exhaust pipe.
That means ass!
Let go of me!
It's not my fault
you look like Hitler!
Shut up!
That's the last time
you sneak in here
on my watch, you punk kid!
Yeah!
Fuckin A!
Rad.
Let's collect the coins
and get out of here.
Did you ruin my panties?
They were expensive as hell!
You owe me a new
pair if you did!
Hey, we killed
the damn ghost.
The bell should be ringing.
That's how it works.
Yeah, that's weird.
I'm not dead yet.
Not even close!
Round three?
Seriously?
Now we're talking.
I can keep going
all night, buddy.
Ask around.
It's true.
She's a giant slut.
All I need is to get
a hold of Backlace
so I can finish
him off for good!
Hey!
Get me up to him, and I'll
give you a flash of my panties!
What?
Your panties?
Fucking go!
We can't air this!
Can we?
We're airing this if
I have to blow someone!
Do what she said!
Let's get him, See Through!
That's what I'm talking about!
Now!
Oh, fuck, yes!
I'm almost there!
I'm so close!
Yes!
I'm gonna blow.
Oh God, don't stop!
I'm about to explode!
Yeah!
Climax to the max!
This is it!
Oh, yeah!
This speed is amazing!
I haven't even used protection!
No brakes!
Pedal to the metal
the whole time!
Yeah, baby!
That means I never--Let--Up!
He's so disgusting.
Oh yeah!
Chuck.
You know, I just now
realized something.
With men, it's not
about quantity or speed.
It's about how
stretchy they are!
Ready?
Where you goin'?
Don't you worry.
I'm coming back!
Oh ouch!
Yeah, I'm done here?
It's not me; it's you.
Repent, motherfucker!
Shit!
Is this my stop?
How many are there?
Three Heavens!
Cheap and disappointing.
Really?
Because you seemed to
be enjoying yourself.
Meh.
Everyone likes to go fast,
but without good technique,
what's the point?
Gross.
I'm so never
wearing these again.
Is the gospel told
by these angels filled
with the light of hope
or the darkness of despair?
The people live their lives
unaware here in the city located
somewhere between
Heaven and Earth.