"InnerBrief!"
Okay, angel-wangels.
It's happy, happy milky time!
Would you quit fucking around?!
You're gonna drown us both
you giant little ginger bitch!
Oh my.
Who's a greedy little girl?
Okay, Panty, one more drink
but then it's no
more milk for you!
Ahhh!
You can't mock us
just 'cause we're tiny!
Oh, and look at your
tiny arms and legs!
I could just eat you up!
Problem solved, bitches.
Garter!
The Heaven Encyclopedia says the
drug should wear off in an hour,
and the only lasting effect is
a slight tingling in the cooch,
p'haps a rash.
So we're fine.
But why do you
cock-gobblers have to fall
for them demon sister
tricks every time?
Can't you tell the difference
'tween a Vodka Red Bull
and a shrinking serum?
I'm glad you won in the
end but can you try to use
those meat-clumps in your
skulls you call brains?
Fuck you, fuck you, fuck
you, fuck you, fuck you...
Heh.
You can't even pull off
cute when you're tiny.
Aw don't listen to him.
I think you're precious!
And I'm gonna keep
you nice and safe
until you're back to
normal, oh yes indeedy.
Stop it, that tickles!
Hey no! Not there!
That's extra tickly!
You're killin' me, tiny angels!
Oh my God, what have I done?!
I've swallowed
Panty and Stocking!
Oh, angels forgive me!
Now then.
Be a good boy and
drop your draws.
What?!
What's the matter?
Do you want me to
pull them off for you?
No, I certainly do not!
Then take them
fuckers off yourself
and get on this
toilet at once!
Don't worry, I'll be
watching you the entire time.
I can't take off my clothes
while you're watching me!
Look the other way!
So you have a problem with your
natural human figure Brief?
Hm?
There some secret
you're trying to hide?
A third nipple, a monoball?
Are you freaking kidding me?
No, I just don't like being
naked in the bathroom
with another man!
It's embarrassing, okay!
I see. Yep.
You got the
psychological problems.
No I just like being
alone when I poop!
You're the one
who's not normal!
I really have to go!
What? I'm absolutely
normal, Brief.
Well normal except
for the gargantuan,
and horse-like
size of my package.
Okay, damn it!
I can't hold it in any longer!
Oh no!
I just flushed
Panty and Stocking!
Go, Chuck, go!
Garter here.
Hey Panty, where
your ass at right now?
Where the Hell
do you think I am?
Would you shut up!
I can't hear you,
but it doesn't matter.
Just stay on the line.
May the thunderous
power from the garments
of these holy, delicate
maidens strike down upon you
with great vengeance and
furious anger, shattering
your loathsome impurity
and returning you from
whence you came.
Repent, motherfucker!
My hand just moved on its own!
Blam! Blam! Blam!
This is not a good thing.
What?! What's happening to me?!
We have two minutes
until the serum wears off.
If we don't get them
out of you by then,
your belly's gonna burst like
a hand-grenade-filled piñata.
There's only one choice.
What the what?
Don't move or this'll hurt.
Actually it's gonna
hurt either way.
Huh?!
What are you gonna
do with that finger?!
Just have faith in God, me,
and a whole lot of Vaseline.
Sweet mother of--!
Oh god, find my happy place,
find my happy place!
Here comes the cavalry.
NO!!
I feel so dirty.
This isn't how I thought
I'd lose my virginity.
Be proud, Brief!
You were born with
a precious gift,
and we're meant to share our
gifts, not hide them in shame.
If I could. I'd do things
with your gift that would
blow your little mind.
Ah man!
That Roller Coaster of Death
through the small intestine?
The motherfucking
bomb, am I right?!
Uh huh!
But that last freefall
was even better!
And then that Thunder
Crash Mountain ride
in the rectum,
I mean holy shit!
Yeah totally!
My insides are still
doing somersaults,
I'll prob'ly throw up!
You're so mean, my darling.
But I can't help it, I still
love you and you were inside me!
That was fucking amazing!
No. That was fucking
awkward as hell.
Awkward as fuck.
You girls should be a
little more understanding!
A clue.
Someone must've inserted
it while I was busy
you know, doin' that.
You hear that, ladies?
Panty and Stocking are needed!
Jesus, he's being a fuckwad.
His anal beads
must be stuck again.
Afro dick.
"Chuck to the Future!"
"Chuck to the Future: Part Two!"
"Chuck to the Future: Part 3."
♪ My name is Panty,
the crazy sexy blondie ♪
♪ and I'm not dumb ♪
♪ I'm breaking the
news, now boys! Us girls ♪
♪ we're full-time
horny too! ♪
♪ Hey, check out that hot
one damn he's got a big one ♪
♪ [BLEEP] delicious ♪
♪ It's time to get dirty now,
so will y'all excuse me ♪
♪ read the air! I'm busy! ♪
♪ Garterbelt! Again
you've dialed D-CITY 2-900 ♪
♪ Pantsu line! Copy that!
Clear the city! ♪
♪ Anarchy! Everyone
wants to be me! ♪
♪ Anarchy yeh!
Get it up so I can see! ♪
♪ Anarchy! Let it
flow wild and free! ♪
♪ Anarchy yeh!
Y'all ready for the gig?! ♪
♪ By the way, my name
is Stocking, I spill venom ♪
♪ stinging eros ♪
♪ And I got sweet tooth
for rolling pops (lollipops) ♪
♪ rolly goth, I lick good! ♪
♪ These stripes will
strip you down ♪
♪ I got no mercy
for chiralism ♪
♪ My fans they all love
me cuz I kick it real tasty ♪
♪ I get high being nasty! ♪
♪ Garterbelt! You keep
slappin' my butt around ♪
♪ Pantsu line! Freaky
girl comin' your way! ♪
♪ Anarchy!
Everyone wants to be me! ♪
♪ Anarchy yeah!
Standing ovation please! ♪
♪ Anarchy! Shake that
thang wild and free! ♪
♪ Anarchy yeah!
Steady ready for the gig?! ♪
♪ I know you know...
those wings inside of you ♪
they do get naughty too ♪
♪ Before I go... there is
something I wanna say ♪
♪ Your sleepy anarchy...
Wake it up! Wake it up! ♪
♪ Anarchy!
Everyone wants to be me! ♪
♪ Anarchy yeh!
Get it up so I can see! ♪
♪ Anarchy!
Let it flow wild and free! ♪
♪ Anarchy yeh!
Y'all ready for the gig?! ♪