"Raiders of the Nasal Dark."
Daten City, a veritable
vortex of necessary waste.
A place where people
are always digging
for the newest,
tastiest nugget of gold.
But trends, like bodily
functions, happen.
What's passionately
picked one day is destined
to be flicked to
the side the next.
Small chance of
rain today, folks,
so watch out for that
high pollen count.
Tell me you're not
picking your nose in public.
It's called Oscar
Picker Therapy,
and it's officially a thing;
here, check it out.
Fuck yeah, mucous membranes!
Get fingered!
Look, sugar tits,
everyone is doing it.
Nothing personal,
but you're an ass.
Could you stop?
I'm trying to eat.
That shit looks
like what I'm picking.
Who's an ass now?
You should try some,
ya nose whore.
They just put it on the menu.
It's gooey goodness that
still has enough crunch to
get stuck in your teeth.
It's awesome.
It's made from
this extra-thick,
one hundred eight
percent egg cream.
It's a goddamned
sweet revolution!
Sticky little nougat,
I love you so!
See, they look exactly the same!
That's sick!
I think you need some water; all
that picking has dehydrated you.
Probly.
Weird.
It's filled with a
crazy amount of gas.
Christ balls what are
you doing here, Geek Boy?
Nobody invited your lame face.
Oh, sorry.
It's kinda setting
off my ghost detector!
Really?
'Cuz you're setting off my "get
the fuck away from me" detector.
Well, God fucking
bless that guy, shit.
Oh, ladies, ladies, hello!
Where have you
been all my life?
Tell me, my lovely customers,
how are my sweets treating you?
Sorry babies,
I didn't mean to be rude.
I own this sexy café.
My name is Oscar H. Genius.
And what, may I ask,
should I call you two beauties?
Panty!
Stocking!
Erotic monikers;
that is so my style!
Now, you sensual little
minxes, how would you like
to join me for a celebratory
party on my airship?
We're gonna have cake!
Believe it or not babies,
it's the Oscar Group's one
hundred and eighth anniversary!
That's cool.
Um, let's talk about
what kinda cake?
Trust me, babies,
you will love it!
All these people are here
just to go to my shin dig
and you two are by far
the hottest tootsies,
so you have to go.
C'mon we're having a
smorgasbord of sweet treats
as part of the orgy of fun.
Smorgasbord of sweets!
Smorgasbord of orgy!
Oh shit, that
mofo is flying away.
We're too late.
Don't worry, babies.
It's cool.
The goober gases will
get us there no problem.
See what I mean?
Everybody's doing it, babies!
It's show time!
Calling all my babies!
Welcome to the Oscar Party!
So sweet!
My mouth is so
fucking happy right now!
Yeah, well, my lips got nothin'.
If your snatch ass
doesn't hurry up
and snatch some,
they'll all be gone.
I can't eat and pick
at the same damn time.
So, I'm just gonna
stick with picking.
That's funny;
I can't not do both!
Hello, Miss Panty.
So glad you made it, babe.
Care to join me in VIP?
Fuck yeah I do!
Later, Stockin'!
See?
I told you this
would be amazing.
It is.
Oh my God, faster!
Go faster!
You like that hot stuff?
You're driving me crazy.
I've got something
special for you.
I call it the Pleasure Twister.
Oh my God!
Yes! Don't stop!
Yeah, that's the spot isn't it?
You're tighter than
I thought you'd be!
Why does everyone
always say that?
That was a-fucking-mazing.
I had no idea my hole
exploration was so limited.
And I do not say that lightly.
Well it's new.
I'm on the cutting edge of
everything, especially sex.
Sticking one's boogers into
another's nose is--Fuck.
Fuck.
Fuckchoo! Fuckchoo!
Curses! There's only
one kind of booger
that can make me
Fuckchoo like that!
You little devil!
You're an angel!
I can't stop!
What's happening?
Feels so good!
Oh my God!
I can't stop picking!
Stocking's getting upset!
Fuckchoo! Fuckchoo!
Look what your disgusting
boogers have done to my mucus!
My crispy critters
are turning to snot!
Fuck.
You're actually a ghost?
I can't believe
I let you finger me.
Well, looks like
my secret is out.
But you're too
late to stop me now!
Oscar H. Genius is actually
a snot burgling ghost!
We've figured that out.
Where the fuck
did you come from?
Your momma's ass; now
can we please focus
on that giant booger
eating ghost outside?
Check out that read!
Is he the ghost of
someone who died
from eating too
many nose goblins?
Nah, he's just a guy
who slipped on some snot
and broke his neck.
Like it matters, ya big dildos.
Watch out for the
dust he just released;
once a person inhales it, they
won't be able to resist the urge
to pick their nose, causing all
the moisture in their bodies
to be converted
into nasal waste!
I must have snorted the
dust out of habit!
Damn it, it's too late for me!
Save yourself!
This ghost sucks balls!
Oh no, the ghost's
nose is bleeding, too!
The force of the gas
on top of the rush
of nosebleeds will
turn us into a snot rocket
heading straight
towards the moon!
I just burst my own nose hymen!
What?
This is bad!
We all going to die!
Must. Stop. Picking.
The ghost was planning
on using nosebleeds
to propel us forward
the whole time!
And that means--
If we all pop our nose
cherries at the same time,
we won't be able to stop!
Move it snot wagons!
I gotta get away from myself!
No way!
Stop right there!
Hold it in!
We're nearly out
of the atmosphere!
At this rate, I don't see how
we won't crash into the moon.
We're all gonna die!
Wait, what about angel boogers?
Hey, that's it!
He was allergic
to Panty's mucous!
We just need to get
some inside his nose
and make him sneeze
before we crash!
I did it, you guys!
I found the only way out!
That was my idea!
Get back to picking!
We need your boogers!
There's nothing left.
It's all nosebleed!
We don't know if mine work!
Stop it!
Well I don't want
any more of my holes
to get unnecessarily
stretched out!
Oh drop the act,
you nose whore!
Jesus.
Here.
Um, you can, uh,
use this if you'd like.
Well, that's gross.
Are you kidding me?
You actually collected
all of my boogers?
Is that weird?
Not if you're a twisted
piece of shit stalker!
And you wonder why
everyone hates you!
Okay, Stockin', watch my back!
I'm heading straight for
that fucker's nostrils!
Be right there, Panty!
I'm gonna make sure the
passengers are freed first!
Time to kick some snout!
So apparently the cabin
isn't part of the ghost.
Look up! Look up!
This ghost is a bitch.
This ghost is so a bitch!
Fucking shit.
I forgot I'm wearing shorts.
Damnit, I can't get this
belt off with just one hand!
Stockin'!
I'm on it!
Your cooch just
made us go faster!
So I gotta hot hot-pocket.
Well, that worked
for us well enough,
but I hope they'll be okay.
Your snot rocket to the
moon is landing early!
Fuck!
Why do you always have
to milk the foreplay?
Here, hold that for me, will ya?
That's better. Thanks!
Ohmigahd, gross!
Your crusty sinus
juice touched my face!
Shut up and take the right.
I'll take the left.
Ew, it's stuck to my sword!
Your boogie is not cooperating!
I'm gonna find your
spot now, snothead!
Yeah, I'm coming!
No, Panty!
Oh!
No!
Fuck. Fuck.
Fuck.
Fuckchoo!
God bless me.
It's out!
If it's good, you might as
well stick with it, am I right?
"Vomiting Point."
Daten City, synonymous
with extremes:
love, hate, decadence and,
uh, the opposite of decadence.
To the west of
this mixed up town
is a mixed up little area
called Little Tokyo.
In this ghetto, shit place,
ghetto, shit people seek,
ghetto, shit happiness.
As they live out their
ghetto, shit lives.
Now Lord, may you shower--
--your ghetto,
shit fortune upon 'em!
Nightmare.
This weather
is so gross.
But I'm not.
Terao, I didn't want
to bring this up again.
To be honest, I never
want to bring it up.
You know that.
Okay, you didn't
meet your quota again.
You only locked down two
contracts this month.
I know, I'm sorry.
Omori is doing better than you.
And that guy is easily the
stupidest person I've ever met.
Sorry, sir.
Yeah.
You're always sorry, but
apologizing isn't your job.
Sorry.
Have you thought
about retiring, maybe?
It's just the same
discussion every month,
and I know it's hard for you,
but imagine my position.
This isn't fair to
either one of us.
Chief Nishi,
call on line 3.
Excuse me a sec.
Yes? This is Nishi speaking.
Oh!
Yes, sir, I remember her.
She's the blond one with
the big ass titties, right?
Yeah.
Yeah, the bouncy ones.
Oh, I don't know.
I spent my stripper budget for
the whole month that night.
I don't know what
I was thinking.
No, sir; I couldn't let you pay.
You're right,
yes I can. I'm in.
Definitely.
Man, d'you hear
Terao gettin' it earlier?
Yeah, it was harsh.
That dude is old;
I feel bad for him.
Don't; he was only hired
because he knew someone in HR.
Sexually?
God, no.
Jesus.
Idiot.
It was his father,
ya sick pervert.
Terao's old man was the
captain of our CEO's unit
during the war
or some bullshit.
Oh, I get it.
That's why they won't fire him.
And he's a shittier closer than
even me, am I right, Sugita?
It's kinda sad if you
think about it, though.
I mean, he's over fifty
and still just a peon.
Can you imagine living
your whole life like that?
Blech.
Oh, shit, you guys.
Terao, how long have
you been standing there?
I'm just gonna go now.
Terao, wait!
Be sure to get that thing we
talked about for tomorrow.
Okay.
You guys are a couple of grade
A dipshits, you know that?
What? We didn't know he
was standing right there!
He scared the Christ out of me.
He's like a ninja.
Yeah, right.
When I see Terao, I think,
"there goes a ninja."
Next stop.
Last station.
Would you put your paper away?
We're trying to have
a nice dinner,
it'd be great if you'd join us.
Sorry.
Hey, Daddy!
Did you know that tomorrow's
going to be my birthday?
Yes, I know.
It's the wonderful
day you were born.
Will you get me a meeting
for them for my present?
Meeting who?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Daddy!
Panty and Stocking.
Who? Panty and--?
Repent, mother fuckers!
Suck on this, asshole!
Fuck!
Those are not sweet words,
and we do not use them
at the dinner table.
Sorry.
Oh, Mother!
Why don't you just ask for help!
You spilt that all
over the place.
See, you upset your
Grandmother with that language.
But Mama, Daddy asked.
Mother!
Will you knock it off
with the sauce already?
And now it's time for
the Midnight News Show!
Who's this city's
favorite duo again?
Panty and Stocking.
Oscar H. Genius,
the pharmaceutical company
CEO and snappy dresser...
Oh, I see.
They're super heroes, huh?
Come on, Mika, what's wrong?
Whoa.
What the hell is this thing?
Look at that shit.
Please tell me that's
not supposed to be
what we got Mika
for her birthday.
Yeah, Terao bought it!
God fuckin' knows why he'd think
she'd like something like that.
What are you guys talking about?
Guess what?
My birthday cake is
the bestest cake ever!
That's nice, honey, and
daddy will have your present
for you when he gets
home later tonight, okay?
Really?
Thank you, Daddy!
I love you!
Wow, this is kind of depressing.
I'm sorry.
I don't know why I'm crying.
It's okay.
I am just a temp anyway.
What's going on?
What's the matter, Mika?
This is all my fault.
I told Terao that she
liked antiques and stuff.
I should've been more specific;
I had a feeling he'd find
a way to screw us over.
Man!
Yeah, this gift is total shit.
Oh no.
I don't know what's
wrong with me.
I think I might've gotten my
wires mixed up again, somehow.
I'm sorry.
Please forgive me, Mika.
No, it's cool.
It's my fault.
I never should have asked
you to get something
for someone so difficult!
I have an idea.
Why don't we all just
go out for a drink!
Yeah, our treat.
How about it?
That should cheer you up.
Yeah!
You wanna?
Hey!
Terao.
What's that drink
you call a drink?
Oh, it's nothing, it's just I'm
not a big drinker, you know?
Well, shit, look at yourself;
you need to develop
a habit, pronto!
Yes, thank you.
I, uh, have somewhere to be,
so I should be going.
What?
You're going?
The hell you are!
Sit down.
Hey, you!
That could've hit--!
Oh, my goodness.
You're the one who made
Mika cry, remember?
You think you can just walk
out of here, huh, willy nilly?
You're drunk.
No!
Fuck that, old man!
You're shooting from the tower!
Sir.
Really, I'm not a drinker.
You don't drink, don't gamble,
don't cheat on your wife!
What the hell?
What do you do?
It's my daughter's birthday.
You know whats your problem is?
You don't make
your career seriously!
You're the worst employee
in this whole company
and in this whole bar!
I can't even squint
achyou right now, man!
You disgust me!
I'm sorry, sir.
I'll get to drinking right away.
--Wow!
Nice.
Incredible!
Thank you.
I'll just be off now.
Terao, are you alright?
Happy Birthday, honey!
Congratulations, Chi!
Oh! Do you like it?
Happy birthday...
Oh wow! It's so pretty!
Where'd the lights go?
Happy Birthday, baby.
Way to go!
Terao!
Oh good!
Hey!
Welcome back, my man!
Can you hear us?
Yes?
Oh, thank God.
You old bastard, you had
us scared half to death!
Come on; wake back up.
Daddy might not make it.
I'm sorry.
So sorry.
Are you fucking kidding
me with this shit?
I just bought this outfit,
and now it's covered in puke!
You ever heard of a
little thing called karma?
Fuck karma, man!
And fuck that barfing
hurl bag piece of shit.
Fuck him right in his lady ass!
Oh, Jesus, please don't!
Ew, gross! Can you imagine?
Um. Excuse me...
Uhm... Hello?
Yeah?
Um.
Yes, it's just.
It's my daughter's birthday,
she's a big fan.
So, I--
Look, gramps, I've got some
shit to take care of, sorry.
Quit hitting on
old people, Panty!
We got shit to take care of;
and I want to get back
before my pie burns.
It's not always
about pie, ya know!
Okay, panties,
you know the drill.
After we eliminate
this human excrement,
we'll have taken
out the big three.
We're so good.
Repent, mother fucker!
Ridiculous.
Only one Heaven?
Yeah, he was pretty disgusting,
but, I guess he
wasn't very strong.
Excuse me.
What?
My daughter.
She's a big fan.
And it's her birthday.
I thought he was gonna
try to get us into
his white van to help
look for his lost puppy.
I know.
What, are we supposed
to talk to every fan?
Well, when you're as famous
and fuckable as me,
what can you expect?
Chi, honey!
Can you do me a favor?
Granny can't hear me;
will you please go get her?
Okay!
Granny!
Open your fucking ears!
You know, Terao.
I didn't want to
bring this up again.
To be honest, I never
want to bring it up.
I'm sorry, sir.
But it's been another
month in a row
that you haven't
met your quota.
I'm sorry, sir.
You're always sorry!
It's the same
discussion every month,
and I know it's hard for you,
but imagine my position.