"The Turmoil of the Beehive."
One more time with feeling!
Daten City.
Sometimes it feels like
a vacuous place
where everyone
wants to be number one.
Especially in high school.
The guys want the
girls to want them,
and the girls want the other
girls to want to be them.
However, sometimes, being the
best means being the worst.
Good morning, angels!
It's so nice of you
to grace us with
your most malcontent
presence today.
This is who I'm
waking up to? Asshole.
I'm not gonna stop
what I was doing,
so you only have
yourself to blame
for what you're about to
smell, preacher douche bag.
I'm gonna ignore
that and keep talkin'.
Alright, Tartlettes.
We have a grave
situation on our hands.
Yeah, I'll bet.
Let me guess: it's another
rogue glory hole shit storm.
The only shit storm here
is the one coming out of
your mouth on a daily basis.
But I prepared for it this time.
Ladies and Panty,
meet our new client,
the principal of Daten
City's academic institution.
We only have one
here, apparently.
Client for what?
I don't do old dudes.
Oh well that's just,
oh, never mind.
The thing is our
students are missing--
or rather,
they're going missing.
Ouch!
Some of them are still there.
I've called the police,
but they can't figure it out.
And there must be a
ghost behind it, right?
Can I go now?
It's more than a ghost!
It's the Devil himself!
Please, save our school!
Oh Jiminy that feels amazing!
Just a little to the left and--
Leg rape?
Way to have him
ask for our help
like we fucking have
the right to say no.
I knew you'd agree!
All right, ya hookers,
go wash your asses in the sink
and get to high school
before that ghost swindles
any more students.
Remember, you're incognito
so resist the urge
to be yourselves.
Are those celebrities?
Are we in a music video?
We're angels, dick!
Uh, you do know what
incognito means, right?
It's the opposite of that.
Who'd've thunk the
Earthly high school boys'd
be just as pervy as
those assholes in Heaven.
That was convincing.
For a minute I actually
believed you had some idea
what schools might
be like up there.
I specifically said the perverts
at the schools, Stockin'.
I wouldn't know that
if I actually wasted time
in a class now would I?
True story. All right,
let's get this over with.
Where should we go first?
What in the fuck? That's not
suspicious or anything.
We didn't even have to
go looking for trouble.
Ugh. Was that necessary?
Whoa. Holy Mary Mother 'a--
That all you got?
Hey! Here's a thought!
Let's take this one
home and call it a day!
Yeah, we'll say he's a geeky
Bee Ghost or something.
I'm down.
Help! I can't see
and my face hurts!
Oh, Briefers, Darling?
You're not really running
around so carelessly
with my precious beehive
on your head now are you?
It's Barby!
I'm so sorry!
But it's not my fault I swear!
Aw that was a
good look for you.
Why'd you take it off?
So, hey. What the fuck is that?
Ew gross. Is that
Barby wannabe I smell?
I have no idea who you are or
who you're pretending to be,
but allow me to share
something really important
with you--this
school belongs to moi.
You the fuckin' janitor?
Yeah 'cause we met the
principal and he's hotter.
My name's Barby.
You may also refer
to me as Queen Barby,
Her Majesty, or Goddess.
Allow them to demonstrate.
Hail Barby! Queen Barby!
Her Majesty! Goddess!
You're working
way too hard here.
Did she seriously refer
to herself as Barby?
Like the out-dated
fetish doll
with a zillion
lame-ass occupations?
She did and I'm
allergic to plastic.
Let's get out of here
before we catch "Slut-Face."
Oh no.
No one walks out in the
middle of my being worshiped!
And how dare you
call me plastic!
I guess I was
just born with it!
Look how hot I am as a
scientist. Hard on!
--Go!
Go!
Kay?
Take notes my nerdlings.
Man, those Panty
and Stocking babes
totally deleted Barby
from everyone's playlist.
Consider her beta test expired.
Yeah, right. I don't
know what that means
but I'm ready for a new
mental image for my flesh light.
Bye Bye Barby!
My brother nerds!
The time has come to assimilate!
We must wipe our hard
drives clean of that nasty virus
and hail our new
splendiferous royalty!
I know I didn't just hear
what I think I thought I heard.
Try that again, suckers!
Listen up, maggots!
You're still
practically embryos!
And that means if you
have sex you'll die!
I mean it!
And death is permanent!
Check this shit out, Stockin'.
Could you just die?
It even moves when you
stick a finger up her.
Third Base
Panty--Collect all four.
You're just into
this for the uniform.
And your point?
Is that gum? Thanks, bro.
Hey! What are you girls doing?
What the fuck, sphincter?
Oh, hey Geek Boy.
Didn't see ya there.
You've gotta do something!
All my friends
are disappearing,
and by friends I mean
the people in the halls!
What's that?
This is the work of a ghost!
They're gonna kidnap us
all and eat our brains!
They're gonna what now?
Dude, slow your fuckin' roll.
I can't understand you.
You may not believe this, but
I am an expert in the occult.
Plus I got this Proton
Pack for my birthday
last year and it's awesome.
Those things are for real?
Man, I hope whoever gave you
that thing kept the receipt
because it's either broken as
hell or just part of their plan
to make you look like
a comic-con dee-ouche.
So, what exactly were we taking
when we decided to follow
the Ginger Freak-fro-show.
Sorry, it usually works!
Proton Pack of Shit!
Wait, no! There it goes!
It found something!
I knew I could fix it!
Well, isn't this a delight?
I was afraid I'd never
see my favorite
slut cankles ever again!
Aren't you supposed
to be in the trash?
That entrance is
way too big for you.
Please.
I have the biggest entrances
in the whole school!
That's a lot of
information about you
I did not need to know.
Booger flick in your face.
Aw. That was almost adorable.
I'll give you something
to flick when you see
what I've brought
here for you.
I'm terrified beyond the
capacity for rational thought!
Could this have been any
more fuckin' predictable?
Nope, she's a queen.
She's a bee.
She's a queen bee,
we fucking get it.
I hope you both have
something good to turn in
to Teacher Barby
because stupidity
results in death
in my classroom!
Introducing, Brain Slushy Barby!
This better not take forever.
I need a candy bar!
True that mess.
Who's ready to play?
Barby Blast!
They certainly have experience
playing with balls, don't they?
It was all a dream.
Oh, thank goodness.
Heads up, Ginge!
Just who are
these helmeted men?
Make my day!
Bee gone!
My head hurts.
Was I just a bee?
Uh not exactly.
Random House Barby
decided to put
bees in your ears
to control you.
So you know what that means.
It's Extermination
Day, bee-itches!
Panty, I'm gonna need you
to stop making bee puns!
It's about to get all
Bring It Barby in here!
Get your asses out there
and give them poison!
Did she just shoot
bee butts at us?
I see London.
I see France!
You're up!
We girls can do anything!
Ain't that right, Barby?
Barby Dream Cemetery
sold separately!
Repent, motherfucker!
But I'm vintage!
That's it?
Cheap bastard.
Here come the geeks.
Holy shit you guys
are real ghost hunters!
I'm so excited I'm itching!
Oh! But in places
I shouldn't be!
Wait until people
hear about this!
A few of them will want to
be friends with me, I know it!
Hello smorgasm-bord!
Whose face should I play
'rocking chair' with first?
Oh, I guess you've earned it.
Line up, boys.
I need some sugar.
Don't put your finger there!
Please don't put
your finger there!
I must exorcise this demon!
What the fuck are you doing?
Put your finger back!
Touch down!
Yeah, let's go into overtime!
"Sex and the Daten City!"
I don't see no ghost.
Who you gonna call,
mother bitches?
Coming, this winter.
All I want is for him
to tell me I'm 'the one'.
Is that too much to ask?
I'm sorry but he's
just not that into you.
Girlfriend, fuck you!
That's it, Panty!
Work it, baby, yeah!
That's it! Be the
tiger! Be the tiger!
Meow.
Great! That's a wrap!
You were un-effing-believable
today, Panty!
Tell me something I don't know.
When can we go shopping?
That's going to have
to wait til next week.
Right now you have three
commercials for hair products,
a talk show with
four bitter lesbians
and then you need to make
an appearance at a party.
Careful not to flash
the naughty bits.
Fabulous. I'd also like
to break a window
and design a cheap,
trashy teen fashion line.
That's the best idea I've
ever heard in my entire life!
I'm gonna pencil that
shit in right now!
Meeting with Bubbles
next Tuesday,
and it's Blossom's
birthday week.
Send a Louis with a card
signed, "Love, Panty."
You know what else?
I want to make a CD!
I'm tired of all
these rumors starting
and sick of being followed
and I need to sing about it!
Oh! I can't think
of a better way
to get the public to
leave you alone!
We'll get Timber
Brand to produce!
Take that, America!
Yay!
'Innocent, yet sexy' are
the words most commonly used
to describe the luscious
young sex symbol
who has recently
made a comeback.
No more dangling babies over
balconies or breaking windows.
Panty has made
a fresh new start!
Shitballs-- She is not
that innocent! Ugh.
Come on.
I just had a pudding-gasm!
Best sticky goo
in my mouth all day!
She's here.
Ten thousand years
later. Whore.
How's it going
over there, Panty?
Just dandy.
Hey remember that time you made
a really fucked up commercial?
Glaze my donut!
Eat my donut!
I've got a donut for you!
Fuck me with a chainsaw!
Girl, that was hilarious!
Suck a cow tit, skank!
Only if you're serving it
with your glazed donut holes.
Too bad you got fired.
I wasn't fired.
I just refuse to sell out
unlike some whores I know.
I prefer to keep it on the DL.
I don't want to fuck up
our premiere, unlike you.
Fine.
Sit there and flick it
while my pampered white ass
gets famous without ya.
That reminds me, make
sure to warn the ushers
at the movie
to leave an extra seat
for that pampered ass
to spread out.
Thank you so much for
coming here tonight!
We've both been looking
forward to this day! Mwah!
Some might say we're
just in it for the money,
but that's only partly true.
We do it for you guys!
Can you believe it,
ladies and gentlemen?
Roman Polanski
was released from prison
just so he could
direct this risqué film.
Sex and the Daten
City is a real hit!
And as a bonus,
tonight also marks
Miss Panty's on screen debut!
Did you just suggest that
this was my first time
for anything,
schlong breath?
You know who I am?
I make movies all the time!
This is number two, ya dick.
Bring it on, Chuck meister.
What did you just
pull out of your ass?
Oh please.
Like you don't know.
Here, why'ncha throw this on.
And next time do some
mother fucking research!
Debut my ass! Fuckwit!
Wait.
I forgot to put
on panties today.
What a strange coincidence.
I'm not wearing anything
under these jeans either.
Oh, then I guess we'll
have to fuck, won't we?
Fuck me proper! Fuck me proper!
Not a whole lot of
actresses in this town
can handle a role that huge,
but the director knew
I had what it takes.
We're gonna need
some hush money!
Oh make me work for it!
Make. Me. Work! Oh... yeah!
The director said I'm
the best he's ever had.
They're talking Oscars!
Cannes Festival!
Even 24 Hour Video Races, which
is great if you're into that
and I'm pretty sure I am.
Hey, how jealous of
me are you right now?
What the fuck?
Put it back on!
Seriously. He's about
to hog-tie me.
You don't wanna miss it.
What the hell were
you thinking, Panty?
My god, were you
even thinking at all?
Betsey Johnson!
Your "debut film" is porn!
You made a sex tape!
What! Serious?
As genital warts.
So it was just
"direct to video"?
Well, that explains why
I haven't won an Oscar, yet.
That's not it!
There's a bigger problem!
You don't understand--
I'm not any good?
Is that what you're
trying to tell me?
Oh no, you're very good, honey.
That's not the point.
What the fuck is the
point then? Shit!
The point is you have
three brain cells left
and they're all fighting
for your attention.
Why would you play
your crackerfied porno
during our movie premiere?
Now it's all anyone
can think about.
I hate to be
the one to pretend to
hate to be the one
to break it to you,
but leaking sex tapes is
known as career suicide!
So it's over?
No more group sex?
No more naked men
covered in sushi?
No more spring break body shots?
God, I hate it here!
I know, why don't
you go shoplift--
it'll take the edge off?
Hold the ball sac,
I've got an idea!
Fuck it! The whole
thing never happened!
That was easier than
I thought it would be.
I do love happy endings!
You stupid constipation!
That was one copy!
Someone already put
that shit on the internet!
Can you imagine
fucking that ape in HD,
or better yet, how's
Blu-ray sound to you?
Dammit!
How slow can you possibly be?
God just did not design
you for thinking did he?
Either that or He put
your brain in your clit.
I don't know what the fuck kind
of shit you're trying to say
but I know it reeks
of asshole, asshole!
Why don't you just admit
that you're jealous?
It kills you to see my
classic bone structure
and ass that won't
quit on the big screen!
No need to clean up!
My maid will get--
what the fuck?
Guess your ass-that-won't-
quit was too much for them
or maybe they don't
want their careers
to sink along with yours.
Send me some post
cards from Has-Been City.
I mean, why give up porn for a
legitimate movie career, right?
Maybe I over
reacted a little bit.
You really are
the sweetest,
smartest little shit
in the world.
Have I told you how fuckable
you are to me right now?
Seriously. Everyone should
have a sister like you.
Creepy.
I'm only doing this for
the movie, by the way.
Of course. What's the plan?
I managed to grab
a list of buyers
from your porn distributer
and we are going to pay a visit
to every single perv on it!
You are one brilliant bitch!
Great donut hole!
It's Panty Anarchy!
Baby squirrel tits!
I can't believe
Deep Throat Pantella of
'Hot and Horney
Baby Doll Bitches'
is actually in
my room right now!
You breathe one word
of this to anyone
and I'll come back here and blow
your freaky loser brains out,
and I mean with a gun!
You want that, fucknut?
I don't!
You haven't made any copies
of that shit have you?
No ma'am!
Right answer!
Let's go, Stockin!
Eat it! It'll put
hair on your chest!
That's bullshit!
If you don't eat the
red ones, you'll die!
More bullshit!
And if you don't eat the
orange ones you'll go blind!
Bullshit!
Bye! See you later!
What the fuck?
Are you serious?
You're selling this
masterpiece for two bucks?
I'm worth more than that!
Mmm. Nothing like a
wine break to refresh.
So Giza's next? Where the
fuck is that? Florida?
Egypt.
Ooh yabba ya ali baba oble
moogle ya ya curry rice...
Gross! He hid it in
his camel's face!
I saved the day again!
Panty! We can leave now!
Ha ha!
Yeah!
Fuck me proper! Fuck me proper!
Open wide, Chucky.
I found it!
It's over here!
Got it!
That jackwagon had five copies!
Ugh where were you hiding this?
It's covered in goo but
I'm pretty sure this is it.
So where did you
say the last one is?
Oh fuck!
How 'bout that? You're
in a space spank bank!
Whatever.
At least it's over with.
You know, it wouldn't
hurt to keep just one.
Yeah, I mean it
was your film debut.
Give it to me and I'll keep
it somewhere safe for you.
If anyone has my porn,
it should be you.
One more time!
Some might say we're just
in it for the money,
but that's only partly true.
You see the real reason
we do it is for you guys!
This glorious movie also marks
Miss Panty's on screen debut,
isn't that right, darling?
Yes, that is correct!
I've never done a film or
sex tape before this one.
Fantastic.
Well then it comes as
no surprise that this is
Miss Stocking's
first movie as well.
Thank you!
Doing this film with my
sister as been amazing!
Actually, funny story; Stockin'
started out as my co-star.
Charity and what not.
But then we realized she didn't
fit the theme we were going for.
You know, we wanted
bright and shiny glamour,
yet all she brought
was dark and moody goth.
So I did everyone a little favor
and made myself the only star!
I knew you guys would
prefer it that way,
and since you all
mean so much to me,
I made sure you got
what you wanted!
And mad props should be
given to our talented CG staff
who took the time
to go back and delete
every scene Stockin' was in.
Now you don't have to
gag while watching her face!
That's just the first fantastic
thing about this movie!
You guys are
going to love it!
I love it here!
Who wants body shots?
The name's Panty, boys.
No cock-carrying specimen
is immune to my sexy powers.
Watch yourself!
Panty? For real?