"Lez Diaboliques."
It's "Lay", Panty.
Oh, okay.
Les Diaboliques!
Ugh! Can a sister
get paid, for realz?
Right?
How many of these
fuckers have we killed?
Way more than the shit change
we've been getting for 'em.
Dude, Little Miss Garter
was full of shit.
Easy money, my hot ass.
Not that I mind
being completely bored
all goddamn day
in a high school,
but I mind being completely
bored all goddamn day
in a high school.
I mean, Jesus.
Remember when
killing ghosts was fun?
It's like whenever I do anal,
great in theory but
so not worth the pain.
Too much information.
It'd be different if
I was having some fun.
But these ghosts are lame.
Lame-O!
Hello, screamer!
Now, that's more like it!
Okay this guy is pathetic.
I don't know if he
should count as a ghost.
I don't give a shit as long
as it knows how to holler.
That's what she said!
Ew. That was gross.
You asked for it.
Having fun yet?
Fuck that.
I'm not sticking
my fist in there.
Not often you get to say that.
Well played, hooker.
By the way,
bitches, I'm a girl!
Oh no you di'n't!
You asked for it, shit stain!
Eat toilet!
Damnit!
She got away!
What kind of fucked up
asshole hides in toilets?
This sucks balls bad.
How can it already be morning?
Hey, so, uh, why aren't
you guys wearing uniforms?
You must always
wear proper attire.
"Proper attire?" Are we
fucking at a prom or something?
Dude it's not our rule.
The new school queens told
us to start wearing uniforms.
What?
We're the school queens, dick.
Yeah, not anymore, babe.
If you're planning
to live past today,
then you two should probably
go home and change clothes.
Maybe this is some
sort of bad prank.
You know how desperate
they are for our attention.
Geek Boy! What's the deal?
Uh, what ever could you mean?
Sounds like these Daemon
Sisters are a piece of work.
All their nazi morality rules
and terrorist uniforms
make me wanna gag.
Yeah but they're
the mayor's daughters,
so ya know, they do what they
want and no one says anything.
What? Stop the car.
Okay what kind of morals
are we talking about here?
Like can't text in class or
like we can't give blow jobs
or hardcore finger
bang each other
under the lunch table anymore?
What the hell kind of
fucking school is this?
Everyone freak out!
The Daemon Sisters are here!
Shit!
It's Scanty!
Don't forget about Kneesocks!
Hail to Miss Scanty.
And also to Miss Kneesocks!
Oh my heavens,
Kneesocks, is it just me
or do you also sense a musky
irregularity in the air?
Indeed, sister.
It appears we have two
unregistered girls
with us at school today.
Well, they certainly have
horrible taste in perfume.
Why would anyone
wear that fragrance?
Smells ammonia based;
like cat urine.
Oh, how silly of us.
I think they simply
forgot to wipe.
Bitch!
We hear you've been
bossing around our slaves.
You can't come in here
and take over our school.
That's bullshit!
Did that weasel just
lay a threat upon us?
I think they might be hoodlums.
Hoodlums?
What's that?
They're trying to say
we're ghetto, which is
a crock of shit!
They're the ones
who are fucking up the school
with their so-called rules!
Hell yeah!
We have the right to party!
Try to keep up, ninnywits.
This is a lesson on
how the moral climate
in this academy has
plunged drastically!
You call it freedom,
but it's a perverse anarchy!
The only way to return
this pathetic school
to the standards of which
it's fully capable is simple.
We rule it!
Give students a new sense
of respect through rules!
Wearing school uniforms keeps
them focused on scholarship!
We, as leaders, bestow upon
them a new sense of self worth!
I adore the sound of it
coming from your mouth!
Rules keep behavior in check!
Suppression keeps thoughts in
check and physical training
keeps them from looking
like fat enchiladas!
These things bring about
perfection and beauty!
Yes. Yes.
Calm down, dear.
Your face is terrifically
red at the moment.
Oh goodness how embarrassing.
I'm too fragile; I blush easily.
But wait, your faces
are both red all the time.
Oh no! They don't
mean anything by it!
They must've just stayed
up all night last night!
Ew, what the fuck is
going on in my mouth?
Nasty.
Blame the Daemon Sisters
for that one, too.
They're making everyone
eat healthy sludge.
What kind of
hippie shit is this?
There's not even cake.
Who doesn't have cake at lunch?
Fuck cake, we need
ketchup or mustard
or hot sauce or even
jizz to jazz this shit up.
If I don't carb up I'm gonna
pass the fuck out, am I right?
Oh yeah. Definitely
sleepy town.
No! We can't quit until
we give them an ass-kicking
they won't ever never forget!
You rhymed!
Fuck, they're here.
Great.
Please kill me.
Well, look at what we have here.
It's the Toilet Sisters.
You troglodytes might want to
be mindful of over saucing;
you don't want your bellies
to turn to jelly, do you?
Ugly and fat are no longer
tolerated at this school.
It's against the
new rules, you see.
Allow me to recommend
some calorie control.
Look at us. It's
how we've managed
to keep our figures
perfectly extraordinary.
Oh, have you heard this
delicious new rumor?
Apparently, there are
two genuine angels
attending this
academy as we speak.
It's said they spend their time
on Earth vanquishing ghosts!
Indeed.
Sisters, even.
Now, wait a minute,
you and I are sisters.
They couldn't possibly
mean us, could they?
Don't be ridiculous.
No, you're right.
Who could ever call us angels?
Otherworldly, fulminating
and impeccable perhaps,
but there's no way
that rumor is about us!
How scandalous!
Agreed!
I've heard these parasites
manage to destroy
everything in their path,
like chemical warfare.
Or gonorrhea.
I think that's the
blond one specifically.
We may need to issue rubber
gloves and masks.
I feel just awful for
the other creature.
You know, the fleshy one.
That's it!
Who are the hell are
you calling fleshy?
I gave up fat like
ten ghosts ago!
And what in Christ's name
is wrong with being an angel?
Oh, like you're so
much better than us?
"Hi, our daddy's the mayor,
and we're full of shit!"
Yeah what she said!
If you want to rule the school
let's do this shit right!
Oh.
You're still there.
Well, that certainly
explains the smell.
Hold on.
What were your names again?
Potty and Cellulite, right?
I'm gonna rearrange your face!
Your vociferous ramblings
are becoming incoherent.
You are so about to lose
some short and curlies!
Explain the purpose of
this embroilment, please?
Uh, what?
Yes, what are the parameters?
Per-- wha?
We see you want to
fight, but for what?
To determine the school's
leaders, perhaps?
In that case.
This won't take too long.
That's right!
This is bad! This is bad!
Or are you having
second thoughts?
Shall we commence?
We'll permit the first
challenge to be your decision.
Let's see.
Manners, perhaps?
Boo!
Beauty?
Gracefulness?
Boo!
Physical proportion?
Status?
Boo!
Education?
Eyesight?
Boo!
Audibility?
It seems unfair, though.
We're already
superior in everything,
so I don't understand how
they're going to challenge us.
What do angels do--save
lives and blow horns?
How cute.
I have an inkling blowing
is the tawdry one's specialty.
Bitch!
Don't you judge
my blowjob skills!
So you know, I was
ranked 69 on BJ dot cum!
Panty stop, you're
making it worse!
By the way, we
win automatically.
Why fight when that's
one of our new rules?
There, are you happy?
Our time has been pilfered and
you've nothing to show for it!
We are still in
charge of this school!
We're intelligent
and pulchritudinous,
and the students here
will always worship us!
This is getting tedious.
See you two next fall.
Whose garbage disposal
did we just jump down?
This is fucking nasty.
I think we might be in hell.
Look at all the homeless people.
Smells like ass.
Hi Panty!
Good morning!
Weird.
You try to fight
them too, geek wad?
No, of course not.
They just sent
you to Loser's Lair.
It's where they send people
when no one else wants
to hang out with them.
Oh, great.
Yeah, that makes it better.
Well since you're new and stuff,
I'm an excellent tour guide.
Color me black and
white and so surprised.
What are you doing here?
Hey.
I fucking killed you!
Oh come on.
Panty. Is that the
best you can do?
How 'bout how are you?
And 'what a nice
thought--we don't have
to rot alone in the
smelly spunk junk!'
First of all, that
laugh is annoying.
Second of all, we're
not moving in here.
How the hell are you
still alive, anyway?
Please girls, let me be.
I'll do whatever you ask of me.
Nope. Too late.
We're pissed now.
Please don't kill me!
I know things about
the Daemon sisters.
I promise to share!
I know you care!
Talk.
Free me first!
That's the deal.
Tada!
Plunge on in, me uglies!
I'm not jumping in a shit hole!
Don't be a bum,
it's actually fun!
What's fun about
sliding down a toilet!
Just close your eyes and
throw yourself into it.
Pretend that it's
watersports; you'll be fine.
This is different.
Yeah, we don't have
a jet ski or anything.
Don't forget your rubbers!
So, whaddaya think?
This is it!
This is what?
Curiouser and curiouser.
Fuck me!
Is this a ghost factory?
Worm!
What are you doing?
Sending pics to Garter
so he knows what's up.
You have his number now?
You guys are
sexting aren't you?
Figures.
Oh, hey, man. This is Brief.
That thing is a ghost plant!
You must destroy it immediately!
They'll all activate if you
don't hurry your ass up!
Ugh.
Hard to get motivated when
you're surrounded by shit.
Look what's happening
at the top of the plant!
That's a Ghost Stone!
It collects all the nasty bits
of evil from human souls
and then uses them
to mass produce
some serious asshole ghosts.
Dicks!
So that means we have to
destroy the entire plant
if we want to get rid of them.
Give that boy a sticker!
The fuck?
I want a sticker!
Keep your eyes open!
There's only one team of baddies
that can use the Ghost Stones!
Which means they must be
behind this mother fuckery!
Yeah, who's they?
We don't understand you.
What the?
Oh holy hell!
Why?
Well look at what
the fat cat threw up.
If it isn't everyone's
favorite rancid sewer rats.
Oh, I'm sorry,
I meant Toilet Angels.
How disappointing.
You should know by now
this area is off limits.
Uh, hi excuse me.
What happened to
your rules and morals?
This looks like
pretty shady business.
What are you hagalicious
whore bags hiding?
I'd be delighted to
explain things to you.
What you are observing,
my little unctuous troll,
is the headquarters to a
very crucial undertaking.
We took our experiment
for a test drive yesterday
and are now implementing mass
production beginning forthwith.
Soon enough, you revolting
malodorous angels
will be unable to surmount
any ghosts you encounter,
due to sheer volume!
Tis only a matter of time
until this Earthly realm is just
pervaded with ghosts!
Did you drink a
thesaurus this morning?
I don't know what you're saying.
Not that we don't support
your little dreams and all.
But I really need
some chocolate,
so we're gonna go ahead
and kill you now.
O, pitiful shadows
lost in the darkness.
O, evil spirits born of those
drifting between
Heaven and Earth.
May the thunderous
power from the garments
of these holy, delicate
maidens shatter your ill will
and loathsome impurity and
return you from whence you came.
Repent motherfuckers!
That was so kick ass!
Those recalcitrant little
popinjays just will not give up.
Sister, I believe it's
time for us to give them
a schooling and sometimes
the most inestimable lessons
are the most laborious.
True.
Shall we, Scanty?
Break, O Earth.
Dry up, O Sea.
Burn out, O Sun.
Grant us power, Earthly leaders
and gate keepers of Hell.
Guide us, makers
of the underworld!
We are high-class
demon commanders!
I'm Scanty!
And I'm her darling
little sister, Kneesocks.
Fastener!
You're shitting me!
They're like for real demons?
Well fuck me in the keyhole.
Oh, great and beautiful
demon princesses!
Forgive me!
I'm at your service!
I have no idea who
those creatures are
but they shoved me down
a toilet and make
me speak in awful rhymes!
What?
Check it out!
It's the happy freedom dance!
Too bad you didn't catch me
while you had the chance!
All ghosts must be
trained and disciplined
before they can be
useful on our missions.
Helena Bonham Carter!
After this I get chocolate.
Attack!
What?
Oh shit! I'm hit!
Half a coin!
That's angel abuse!
Fuckin' A and
predictable, like them.
Panty, is it?
Let me share something
I've learned with you.
It's sweet to believe
good will always prevail,
but Scanty and I are demons.
And by design, we're
impossible to defeat.
This is about to get so
embarrassing for you.
By design, we're about
to kick your demon asses.
I'munna laugh my ass off.
Let's get it over with.
Girl, you ain't
gotta tell me twice.
Bring it!
Let's do this!
I think you guys are
going about this all wrong.
Isn't the point to
try to get the stone?
Oh yeah, that does
make more sense.
It's gone!
Holy stink!
Why'd I smell it?
It's an army of artificial
dark night ghosts!
What the fuck are you doing?
Get out of here! Run!
Oh no you don't!
Where are you going?
Then the other girl, her friend,
I don't remember her name,
she just stuck it in her mouth
and kept it there
the whole time!
So I just went
at it like "Yeah!"
Sorry! I didn't see anything!
Oh yeah.
He was hung like a thimble.
I didn't feel anything but from
the photos you couldn't tell.
He kept taking pictures
from this angle
that made it look hu--!
You sure do know your way
around a toilet, don't you?
I never knew there were
so many different exits.
Hey, you're the one who likes
to hang out in the sewer.
Fuck, I just do my
business and go.
Okay, Brief, you can do this.
Just be rational:
What would Indiana Jones do?
This is taking too long.
You're so dramatic.
Get in the car.
No, it's okay you
don't have to do that.
I'll be fine.
Well, then ya better
get out of the way.
Are you okay?
No!
Why won't you die?
I should be safe
here for awhile.
There you are!
No!
Give me the stone!
Yo.
Last chance, darling.
You may have the stone
but do you have the stones?
Hello there.
I wouldn't come any closer.
But feel free to test us.
Nothing would
make me happier than
to destroy your mingy
rodent boyfriend here.
Yeah, like I give a shit.
Do whatever you want
with that turd pie.
Maybe he'll distract you.
Make it easier for us to
stomp your sunburned asses.
Panty, please don't!
You'd sacrifice your friend
for your own perseverance?
You're angels!
Uh huh.
We're also tired,
irritated and over it.
Stockin's fucking jonesin'
and she can't eat until
you two are tits up.
I guess that means
killing Geek Wad, too!
Been fun, kid!
At least say my real
name before I die!
You two are the most
disgusting creatures!
What angel
doesn't have morals?
Hello?
This is your friend
I'm about to kill!
You're kinda supposed to care!
Uh, no.
But straddle his face
and give him a last meal.
How dare you,
you rancorous whore!
What the French toast?
Nerd Bomber! The stone!
Here!
Total spinner!
My dick!
I'm a size queen. So wha---!
Don't get too comfortable.
That was simply a warm-up.
We'll let you off the
hook and call it a draw!
But only because we're late
for an important appointment!
Don't think it's
because we're finished
with you gross parasites.
Keep practicing
because we'll be back!
Well, I think we handled
that like pros, don't you?
And I mean who doesn't wanna
watch their school explode?
Yo, Ginger Crust.
You did a good job today.
Speaking of which,
why don't you come here and
let me give you a reward.
Huh?
Like what?
Oh don't be such
a fuckin' prude.
You know what I mean.
Drop trou' and climb up.
What? You can't be serious!
That's not how it works, is it?
I haven't even been tested yet!
And you probably haven't either!
And shouldn't we hold hands
or kiss or fall in love first?
I mean, I would love for my
first time to be with you but--
Jesus!
I'll just find someone else.
Way to fuck it up, pansy.
I've never been more ashamed.
How are we ever
going to marry you off?
But I--
Tripping up against
a lesser opponent
out of sheer carelessness.
Scanty and Kneesocks,
you have failed me.
We beg of your
forgiveness, Mr. Mayor.
The plan was to extend your
influence inside and out.
But it was too much
for you, wasn't it?
You've given me no choice.
I've prepared a punishment
apropos to your failure today.
Please sir.
Don't send us back there!
Oh!
It smells abhorrent down here!
I think I just swallowed
something fecal!
I'm going to be ill!
Still, what imprudent
angels they are.
Of course, I'd
expect nothing less
from creatures raised by
that imbecile, Garterbelt.
Yes.
It appears that the real
fun is about to begin.