"If the Angels Wore Swimsuits."
You know how there
are those times
when you go see a
movie and ya think,
"I don't care what that's about;
I just want to see something
blow up for christsake and
squeeze my date's business.
Is that so wrong?" No!
In fact, it couldn't
be more right.
Today we've got a beach,
barely-there swimsuits,
and the obligatory
ghost-slash-monsteers
to help keep things exciting.
And that's about it.
Why are beaches so
fucking infested
with douchey horn balls, huh?
You smell that?
It's like this stanky
ass nose-cocktail
of sweat, pizza and
greasy desperation.
I'm gonna go ahead
and declare this
the day you learned
that I'm always right.
Yeah, okay.
A private resort
would've been better.
Oh no! I spilled my drink.
Wow, can guys be fucking stupid.
I had a feeling you
guys were lying to me!
That is so not cool!
What are you doing here?
Doesn't the heat irritate
your acne or something?
Yes. It does.
You said you were too busy
to work the church stand
so I went and picked up
all the meat for you!
Yeah, we are busy.
Come eat my wieners!
So big and dark and juicy fresh!
Everyone says that
they're the best!
Dress them up and
suck them down,
my wieners are the
best in town!
Everyone loves my
thick dark wieners!
I can't service all
these people by myself.
Come on, you're angels,
you gotta help me!
That's so weird.
I could've sworn we
were busy on the beach
being hot and
getting hammered?
Perfect timing.
Get your nerdy ass over here.
You want me to go over there?
How come?
Because you need to
rub oil all over me.
I guess I will
if you want me to.
I mean, are you sure?
Hurry before my buzz
wears off, fire crotch!
Goodness.
The pollution level
on our beach
has certainly escalated
since we've been away.
Never mind.
It's just those
moron angels again.
Are you saying our lungs
are currently insufflating
the same air as them?
Disgusting.
What the fuck are
you doing here?
You had your moment!
Perhaps we should
ask you the same thing,
you see, the point of
having a private property
is that you get to keep
unwanted cretins out.
You own the beach?
Fuck that.
You can't just claim a
beach you whore-noceros.
Your ignorance is
failing miserably
at its attempt to be endearing.
We purchased this
spot months ago
because we were overdue
for a superlative vacation.
We figured keeping you
two out was worth the price,
but it doesn't
seem to be helping.
Fortunately for us,
we have other means.
Stop, drop and roll!
What's wrong with you?
No civilized person would rebel
so against legal restrictions!
Why is it that following simple
rules is so difficult for you?
Is it that you don't understand?
Are we simply speaking too
fast for you, ignoramuses?
Shut up!
You want us to go?
Then fuckin' make us!
Don't just stand
around bitchin,' bitch.
That would require me to touch
you and I'm allergic to slag.
Hooker say what?
Yes, fighting is
strictly prohibited
during vacation periods.
Please don't forget this.
It's one of our most vital--
--rules.
Fuck the shit out of all that!
Talk about your limp excuses.
You don't wanna fight
cuz you know we'd own you.
Why don't you just admit
that you're awesomely disgusting
and we can call it a day?
Ugh. You're talking, but
all I hear is flatulence.
You know, I think we can
solve this predicament
without compromising our rules.
There's a time-honored
method we demons use
which will serve us
rather wonderfully.
First point goes to Demons!
So we're gonna solve
this shit with volleyball.
Can't we just cut these bitches?
Well, it's the only
ball play those snatches
have a prayer of beating
me at, tell you what.
Are you through denigrating
our fine activity?
This game presents a
challenge to advance
both endurance and
gracefulness.
So maybe this wasn't terribly
fair given your common looks
and your--how shall I put this--
chemically unbalanced
personalities.
Panty!
One point, Angels!
I'm sorry, was that too
"unbalanced" for you?
Are you guys always that red
or is that just what
burned looks like?
They're not as
blunderous as I'd like.
Their adequacy will
just make our victory
that much more rapturous.
Yeah!
My wieners are all getting cold.
Where everyone at?
Damn angels.
Coulda used a couple
bikinis to draw in business.
What the hell's goin' on?
Game point and
Angels win the match.
Oh no, did we do that?
Aw yeah, we're just
getting warmed up!
How 'bout you not piss
off the red people, 'kay?
Ass dance! Ass dance!
That's not helping!
Angels!
Alright everyone final bets!
Demons verses angels!
Who's it gonna be?
Oh yeah, I totally
got this one!
Shit. What the hell happened?
How did it get back over there?
What's going on?
Boo!
Mother fuck!
You stupid ho!
Boo!
Fuck that!
You can't just suck one minute
and then turn into
Gold Cup winners!
I don't know what
you're talking about.
We merely have
devilish technique.
How very typical.
You're simply
trying to distract
us with you ill-conceived
accusations.
All right, you
asked for this shit.
We are in the middle of a
game you Sulfuric Dollymop!
You can't abuse the rules
just because you're losing!
What?
This coming from a
cheating, yeasty hag troll
who turned her pet rat
into a fucking game ball?
If that's how they
want to play, then fine.
Balls up!
You're gonna get it!
Keep your rodent off this court
or I'll sue you for
spreading rabies!
Then sue your fat ass and your
nasty sister while you're at it!
Are you through
coming up with excuses?
We've been going easy
since you're hampered
by your heavy hamhocks
and miniscule IQs.
However if you'd
like to play for real?
Bring it on, ho bags!
Now, of course,
this isn't just a means to
get you off our property.
The loser will have to pay
some additional penalties.
Whoever fails has to
get completely naked.
So the audience has to suffer?
Yeah, why punish
everyone else for your loss?
At least throw some bleach
on your ass so we don't
catch skankitis!
You guys might want to pull out.
They look pretty mean right now.
Shut up!
Safe-Guard With Wings!
Demonic Tight Spinner!
Cradle in the dark!
Vibrating Butterfly
and Rabbit Destroyer!
Final Climactic
Double Angel Slammer!
You can't get this
shit on ESPN, bro.
I can't see, dammit!
Ang--Dem-- wait!
It's going too freaking fast.
I can't change the scores!
Who? What? Dammit.
What is happening here?
Final point!
You ready?
Go!
Fly, Sister!
Well this has been
rather diverting
but it's time to wrap
things up, what do you say?
Stockin'!
Got it!
Perfect shot!
Game over!
You're about to
get hardcore served!
Repent, bitches!
Wait.
Does this mean we lost?
Crum cake.
Well.
Which one of you wants to
get butt ass naked first?
Your fans're ready to
make it rain up in here!
Take it off!
Take it off! Take it off!
Take it off! Take it
off! Take it off!
Take it off! Take it off!
Gotcha!
Maybe they can make
some ghost sushi.
You really have the most
delicious sense of humor!
I hope there aren't any
hard feelings, of course.
We had a great time!
Bye bye now!
We'll see you two later!
Wait!
Get back here!
No, Panty!
Just hold on, I'll save you!
After I get this seaweed
ghost off my face!
And I thought
I had crabs before!
Let me go!
Stockin', what the fuck do you
think you're doing?
It's so tight I can't move.
You're sick!
Shit! Stupid fucking starfish!
Fuck! Stupid sea urchin!
Well that was a
most triumphant day.
Everything went precisely
as you had planned
and I was actually starting
to enjoy myself playing
with those nimwits,
can you believe it?
What's the matter?
Sea whores!
Why did we ever allow
them to defeat us like that?
I hope they enjoyed
every second of it
because it will never be
permitted it to happen again!
Next time, they die!
That's the self-destruct button!
What is the point
of that button?
Who would choose to use it?
Ew!
Is everybody okay?
Get the fuck off!
Oh, that's sensitive.
What is? Oh boy.
Who's flippin' them green
backs lookin' like a pimp?
A sperm whale ghost?
No way!
"Ghost: The Phantom
of Daten City."
Okay, well then
what about that guy?
He's hot enough and
looks like he's packing.
Packing gen'-warts maybe.
Plus I can see his
man-boobs from here.
I don't think so.
What?
Back-Pack Dude then?
You mean Awkward Dude?
He's the one that learns all
his moves from old-school pornos
and wants you to
call his junk by name.
What about him?
Geriatric.
Jesus. Him?
Virgin!
What the fuck?
You can't tell me you
wouldn't grease his pole.
Not even if it was covered
with buttercream icing.
Where are your standards?
Oh I'm sorry.
Should I wait to see how they
fare in the talent competition?
Look, it's all the same when
you're face down anyway.
Great. Then you go get
you some, Helen Keller.
I'll stay here
and wait for someone that
doesn't make me want to hurl.
Your call.
But I say you might
as well give your vag
to Goodwill if
you're not using it.
You just have to
set the nookie bar
a little higher if you
want ultimate satisfaction.
What? When you're as
sophisticated as my ass,
that bar don't mean shit.
You wouldn't understand
sophistication
if you were bound
and gagged with it.
Now that's some hot shit.
Ladies, babies, mommas!
C'mon, just a quick stick.
I promise, I'll go easy!
How 'bout I take you out and buy
you something pretty after, huh?
What do you say, girl?
Just the tip?
Gross.
Being a nasty ghost is bad
enough but that one looks like
he probl'y found his face in
a blender full of donkey shit.
Ew.
He's fucking farting!
And P.S. he's
trying to get laid.
I say we put him
out of their misery.
Where'd you go?
Seriously?
Hotness!
What the fuck?
You're dating a fucking ghost?
Damn straight!
Is there something
wrong with that?
Gee.
Lemme think.
Everything is wrong with that.
It was love at first smell.
Uh... Say what?
I mean first sight.
I knew from the
moment I saw his face.
We hadn't spoken but
something inside me felt like
I had known him my entire life.
It was magic!
We were made for each other!
Hi!
Have you been waiting long?
Yeah.
Forever.
I was about to leave your ass.
Lucky you made it.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to make sure
I looked perfect for you.
Lemme break this to you slow.
I don't give a fuck
what you look like.
Ah.
He's so sexy!
Here, try one.
I know it's not your thing,
but most people like them.
Did you wash your hands?
I don't want germs, you know.
Yeah right. You're a girl.
Girls like to lie and
make food mixed with germs.
C'mon, say 'Ah!'
So fragrant!
Smells like love.
Tastes like old cheese.
Get it out of my sight.
Don't you chicks know my momma's
the only woman who can cook?
Maybe if it had a
little more salt.
I love you!
A whole lotta "fuck that"!
Yeah, I heard
they're gonna adopt.
What are you all looking at?
Fuck me!
Stockin'!
Get your ass out here!
This is an intervention, dammit!
You're making a mistake!
He looks like an
inside-out ass hole,
smells like egg
salad, and oh yeah!
You're supposed to kill him.
Everyone's laughing
at you which means
they're laughing at me
and that is no bueno!
Now that there is
one impressive angle.
My own sister, trying
to shit on my joy.
She's just jealous cuz
none of her relationships
last longer than a blowjob.
I know you can hear me, bitch.
Don't even front.
Okay, check it out.
I know it's not about his looks.
I get that you're not in love
with the smell or the
fat or the warts.
It's who he is 'n shit, right?
Well let me remind
you that he's a ghost!
He shouldn't be allowed
to exist much less fuc--
Shut up!
True love has no restrictions!
Even so. I don't think I can
keep this angel thing from
him very much longer.
Why do I even watch
that turd munching team?
It's like they flipped
on TV one day and decided
"Hey, I can play sports"
and some moron put
them on the field!
Hell, I'm just
watching it now to see
if someone breaks their
neck so I can laugh.
Know what I mean?
Yeah.
Hey, can we talk?
I haven't exactly been
honest about who I am.
I'm sorry.
Okay?
I hope you can forgive me.
I'm actually an angel.
What's this about anal?
No, I said I'm an angel
on a mission from Heaven.
Our whole purpose
here is to kill ghosts.
Meaning you.
I should've killed
you at 'hello'.
Whoa! Wait! Hold the door!
I never asked you to tell
me about your anal thing.
There's no need to kill me!
No, you big lump.
I'm trying to tell you
I don't care about my duty!
I love you, that's
all that matters!
Even if it means I have
to give up being an angel!
I want you to run away with me.
You mean.
You want to elope?
Yes, and I don't
care what the cost is
or if I ever get back to Heaven.
It's worth it if it
means I can be with you.
Well, shit, she's not leaving
me much of a choice here is she?
Looks like you beat me.
You been waiting long?
Something kinda came up.
But ya know after that I took
a cab and rushed to get here.
Uh. Oh yeah, I'm gonna
need you to pay the dude.
I'm strapped.
Don't tip him too big
though. I'm starving.
I need some wings
before we take off.
In fact, fuck the tip, you
probably want to eat too, right?
You really know how to
charm a girl don't you,
you waste of space loser.
If you're that hungry,
then I've got some
lead you can chew on,
so open up, stank cheeks.
Who are you? What's going on?
I'm your worst nightmare.
My name's Panty, and
I'm Stockin's big sister.
Bad news, you guys
are breaking up!
She couldn't have told
me that over the phone?
Hard to date someone if you're
just a dead-ass shit stain.
Ain't it?
Now repent, motherfucker!
You hurt him
and you'll feel three times
his pain, I swear to crap.
Oh come on.
Sis, I'm just trying to protect
you like I always have. Right?
Don't say that!
We're not sisters anymore!
I'm my own person!
You're shitting me!
There's a fuck ton
of guys out there.
You don't need to boil
rabbits about a ghost!
Stop saying it like that!
He's more than
just a ghost to me!
You wouldn't understand!
You're too busy fucking
to know what love is!
What? You think that's love?
I may not know what love is
but that sharter doesn't either!
He treats you like ass!
It's not true!
I do love her!
I'm sorry. I know I haven't
been good at showing it.
I'm not a very smart man.
But I know what love is, Panty!
Oh gross.
Omigosh no way!
The pawn shop let
me get it on layaway.
I love you, Stocking.
I always have.
Ditto.
I object! By reason of--
Oh don't act like you approve
of this all of a sudden!
Simmer the fuck down, hooker.
I can't explain it but
it's so clear to me now,
the reason I was put here.
I was never going
to find happiness
until it found me--
until you found me.
You complete me.
You make me want to be
a better man, Stocking.
See ya.
Good-bye.
There are those who
live their entire lives
without experiencing the
love of another person.
We call them bachelors.
Their loneliness and
regret combined
to embody that pitiful ghost.
Even though it was
only for a short time.
Finally letting himself love has
allowed him to rest in peace.
Cheesy much?
God, I'm glad he's dead.
You in there, Shitterella?
It's time to go
kill some ghosts!
I'll even let you bang
a few if you hurry!
Fuck that. She can
stew in it for a while.