We know not where
they come from,
only that they both are
searching for the same force.
For a time, they
lived in harmony,
but, like all great power,
some wanted it for good,
others for evil.
And so began the war.
Brief, are you kneeling
before me to offer God
your service or are you
just, you know, offering?
I'm sorry.
I don't understand the question.
I was hoping maybe.
He could help me stop Panty
and Stocking from fighting.
They're stressing me out.
You see what I mean?
It just never stops!
This isn't autoerotic
asphyxiation,
I'm trying to kill you, so don't
get all snail trail on me.
Okay, you're officially
going too far!
I really hate watching
you two fight.
You never tickle each other or
have pillow fights or anything!
Fuck off, dip shit!
Those crazy hookers
is out of control.
Unexpectedly, the sky
turned an ominous red
as two meteors
crashed into Earth.
What the what?
What. Is. This?
Ohmicrap, I think
it's a meteorite!
At the end of this day,
one shall stand.
One shall fall.
It's like one'a those 'bots
from that cool old
cartoon slash crappy film!
I can't wait to post
about this on the forum;
they'll be so jealous.
Welcome alien-toon!
My name is Brief!
Hello. I'm Cocktimus Prime.
I'm here to end the battle.
Wow, I guess God
really does exist.
So you were sent here to
stop the girls from fighting?
No, you are mistaken, human.
I am not here, alone.
Wait, did he say
Cocktimus Prime?
My name is Minge-atron,
and I've come to this planet to
make this war my bitch, bitches.
Dude, this is awesome!
And at what are you looking,
tiny gothic creature?
A delicious marshmallow!
It's not a marshmallow.
As superior robotic life forms,
our cores are naturally on
the outside of our bodies.
What you're looking
at is my heart.
What the fuck?
You shithead!
Yummers!
What part of "that's my heart"
did you not understand?!
I am known as
Gothatron Stocking,
and I will settle this
score once and for all.
That was so fucking bad ass!
Did that just happen?
Hey, I like your
new look, Minge-atron.
What the hell?
No!
Gross, this tastes
like ass balls.
My name is Rottenass Panty!
The time has come to make
a motherfucker suffer!
No, you guys!
This is way worse than before!
And Okay, Rottenass
Panty's room.
Soundnoise trans-home!
Lovechair trans-home!
Spinbed trans-home!
Cattlehorn trans-home!
Condoms trans-home!
Gothatron Stocking's Room!
Torchfire trans-home!
Sugarscream trans-home!
Cage trans-home!
Skullmuncher trans-home!
Giantdildo trans-homo!
The Pantybots have
seized the kitchen
and surrounded the
refrigerator!
Remember, Stockin'
is a fatty wannabe.
All we have to do
is take possession
of her disgusting sweets,
and victory will be ours!
The radar!
Commander, I think
something is inside the--
Snatchet!!
And away we go!
I've already eaten all
of the sweets, Slagbot!
Fuck!
That was a dick move, Stockin!
Do you have any
last words, Panty?
None that you'd want
to hear, Megatwat!
The battle between Pantybots
and Stockingcons continues!!
Later, outside the bathroom.
Goddamnit, get out of the
bathroom; I really gotta pee!
I hope you piss your face off
while you piss all over yourself
if that makes you feel better.
I'm sorry, what show
am I narrating again?
Wait, Something's up,
she didn't call me a whore.
Ha!
You're not just a whore;
you're a stupid whore!
You and your lame ass
fucking dick moves!
I should have seen that coming!
The Stockingcons escape
trouble by donning diapers!
When it comes to war,
anything goes!
Kill the Bitch!
What will Panty do?!
Pantybot base: in the chapel.
This whole thing is a fucking
disaster; I feel like ass.
Trans-home!
Sorry I'm late, Commander!
Late?
I don't even know
who the fuck you are.
What can I do to
make you feel better?
I can think of a
couple positions.
We're gonna train!
Panty drags the recruit
into a private room.
It's time to screw.
Erection, trans-home!
Oh my God!
Yes! Right there!!
Screw me baby.
Screw me proper!
Don't stop!
Meanwhile, at the Stockingcon
base in the residence tower!
It's only a matter of
time until this church
is yours Gothatron Stocking.
My spybot should
have screwed Panty
into a throbbing
metal slit by now.
A little fuck can't be the
end of our problem can it?
Look at the pussy with
the giant fucking balls!
This planet's not big
enough for the both of us!
Follow Rottenass Panty's lead!
Commence Stockingcon take down!
Why throw away your life
so recklessly, you prick?!
That's a question you
should ask yourself!
It's you and me, Stocking!
No, Panty, it's just me!
Now that is the kind of dialogue
I was expecting to hear!
As the battle between Pantybots
and Stockingcons continues,
the Earth bears the
brunt of their violence
and bitter rivalry!
The powers of
gothness are greater
than anything your pathetic
sex toys can muster!
Powers of gothness, really?
You're threatening me
with bad hair and eyeliner?
Oh no she didn't!
Oh, uh, I mean.
Stockingcons, don't just
stand there; do something!
The final showdown has come!
Pantybots!
Trans-home and rollout!
I fuckin' hate taxis!
Give it up, Yawnatron!
If I want to know
what's on your mind,
I'll splatter it on the
wall and see for myself!
You want a piece of me?!
No, I want two!
Who will be the victor
in this epic battle?!
Thank God, it was all
just a horrible nightmare.
Excuse me, but you are
standing upon my head.
Get your foot off
my face, human asshole!
I'm so sorry!
Wait, if you guys are still
alive, you can stop them, right?
Not gonna happen, kiddo.
Our existences as superior
robot life forms are at stake.
An overzealous goth
and an oversexed whore
will decide the battle
between us for good.
Well, that hardly
seems responsible
for so-called higher life forms;
I mean, they wouldn't be robots
if it weren't for you guys!
Weren't for us?
They ate our fucking hearts!
What about your accountability,
did they eat that too?
This isn't about
accountability, mom;
this is about a species
that prides death
in battle above all else.
Look at us, we have no bodies,
our deaths are inevitable,
but what we can still
have is a finale to the war
we've waged since four
years after time began!
So you're cool with
a couple of chicks
finishing this
epic battle for you?
Pretty much.
Will you look at this disaster?
Can you see that?!
They're disgusting!
I don't want to see
them tickle each other
or pillow fight at all!
This is what you want the end
of your existence to look like?
Personally I always did
want it to be sexier.
Indeed, they are quite hideous!
Brief, that was a
really good speech man.
Cocktimus is correct;
you did well human asshole.
I am overcome by how foolish
we've been
to have warred all this time
against each other simply
to allow those two
to fuck it all up.
As of this moment, we hereby vow
to stop acting like
silly Japanese drawings
and declare an
immediate ceasefire.
Come, Cocktimus, let's
put our heads together,
and find a way to salvage what
little dignity we have left.
Yeah, if you work side
by side as friends,
everything'll be cool.
I bet that's this week's moral!
I have an excellent
idea, friend.
I think we can call it our
first official joint effort.
Yay!
We shall seek out the
lesser life forms
inhabiting this planet.
And?!
And make them bleed
like the pussies they are!
Oh, shit!
Oopsie.
Heroes never die!
Rottenass Panty can
never be conquered, bitch!
Hey, guys!
We're all gonna die!
What the fuck is that?
I dunno, but Jesus it's huge.
That's a ghost, stupid angels!
How have you not figured
that shit out by now?
It's obviously a grudge
born from extraterrestrials
who have been fighting
each other since four years
after the beginning of time
and never managed to finish
their war because they perished
when their home world
was destroyed,
which was caused by their
very own violent battles,
that has now taken the
form of an evil spirit
bent on seeking
revenge on this planet!
I know we're angels and stuff,
but how can there
be a God and aliens?
Much less alien ghosts.
Off the top of my head, I'm
guessing faith is the answer.
What do you think, cocksucker?!
O, pitiful shadow...
...lost in the...
...dark...
O evil...
...spirits... uh...
Heaven and Earth...
Uh... something about maidens...
...and striking down with great
vengeance and furious anger!
Returning you.
Somewhere for something.
Super God Robot Force!
Hell yeah, who's more than meets
the eye now, mother fucker?
Damn fuckin' skippy, it's about
time we get rewarded for realz!
This could get us back and forth
to Heaven a kabillion times,
so I can keep on getting
my Earthly gummy bear fix!
Yeah, shoulda known it
was too good to be true.
Hate to shit in your
cornflakes, girls.
But this is alien currency,
and with the exchange rate
it would take a thousand
to equal one Heaven.
What??
What a relief, right?
I was worried there
for a hot minute, girls.
But I think we all
learned a valuable lesson
about not fighting
and being friends.
Or not?
Shut up, human asshole!
I really hate that name.
Whore!
I swear females more
trouble than they're worth.
Crazy hoochies need some xanax.
We know not where they
come from, only that both
of them are searching for
the same force type thing.
For a time, they lived in
harmony, but, of course,
some worked it for good,
others worked it for evil.
And so the war began.
Who wrote this shit?
"The Stripping."
You both need to stop
spending money on bullshit;
you're angels, not hipsters!
Hey, cock jockeys!
I'm not just talking to
fucking hear myself!
You've spent over
three million dollars!
Fish flavored lube.
Titty Enhancer.
Toys that ain't sex toys!
And who the fuck
orders that much food?!
You bitches eat so much
you gonna start
sweatin' bacon grease!
Garter, if you're gonna act
like a baby, you might as well
crawl back up inside your giant
vagina where you belong.
You're the ones
acting irresponsible,
so you crawl into my vagina!
You're gonna need
somewhere to live.
This church is fallin apart and
I can't afford any more repairs.
Whatever!
We work our tits
off killing ghosts,
so enough with the pretentious
preaching, preacher man.
Don't make me
throw Chuck at you!
You don't earn Earthly
money for killing ghosts,
you get Heaven coins!
And when you take out
the motherfucking city
every time you take out a ghost,
I have to pay for it
with my Earthly cash!
Jesus, chill the hell out, yo!
Dude.
You are being such
a pussy about this,
but if us earning
money will get you
to shut your douche face, okay.
Did you say you were
gonna earn money?
That's hilarious!
You two earning money; Like
you have a single skill
between you anyone
would pay for!
We do too have skills, asshole!
How much were you bitching
about us spending again?
What was it,
three million dollars?
Hell, just give three days!
This would be tragic if
it wasn't so fucking funny!
Please tell me
you're going to put
"sits on ass and farts
all day" on your resumes!
Holy shit!
Very well, then;
I challenge you
to earn three million dollars
in only three days time;
however, when you fail, you must
swear Heaven's Unbreakable Oath
that you will never
waste money again,
and you know what will happen
to you if that oath is broken!
However, when
we win, you fucker,
you're not allowed to complain
about our shopping habits again!
You gotta deal!
It's on now!
Let's go make us
an ass ton of money!
Any idea how we're suppose
to make this money?
Meh.
I just figured we'd
take it from someone
who looks double loaded;
you know, like rich and drunk?
Um, I'm pretty sure
that's against the law.
Maybe you should just
try finding a job.
Yeah, we could do this shit
with our fucking eyes closed.
This is not sanitary!
Dude, working
can fucking suck it.
Can you believe people
actually do this all day?
How much have we made so far?
It's gotta be at
least a million.
Uh, actually you two
kept getting fired.
So you haven't
made anything yet.
Don't fuck with me!
We're supposed to make
three million, so try again!
Million dollars?
Yeah.
Our goal is three
million in three days.
Okay, well then
you'll need to average
at least a million
dollars per day,
so there is no way
in hell that's possible.
I just made three
million bucks in one day!
I'm a cash pirate!
Hey there, daddy;
you really made three million
smackaroos in one day?
You better believe it,
sexy bunny girlies.
I'll even let you stroke
it if you're nice!
It's so gorgeous!
Poopsie, would you mind telling
us how exactly you got it?
Probably from you
rubbing my chest.
Oh, you mean the money?
I'm a gambler;
I got it from a casino!
A casino!
Of course!
Thank you.
Stop right there!
It's too hard to make
money at a casino!
Nothing personal, but you've
got to have a lot of skill
and talent to make
money as a gambler!
Yeah, nothing
personal, but fuck off.
Stockin' and I have
somewhere to be.
We're getting in on
the action, right?
Please, don't do it!
You could end up
losing everything!
I watched a thirteen
hour documentary
on casino slot machines
and tricks of the trade.
These things are designed
to keep you from winning.
You got three sevens
on your first try?
Did you see that?
These girls are incredible!
And hot.
I got dibs on the
dark haired one.
She likes bondage.
I've never seen anything
like this before;
you must have a special
angel luck or something.
Maybe some of your
magic will rub off on me!
That five bucks was all
the money I had to my name!
Oh my. Sorry to alarm you,
but apparently he
was all played out.
Played out patrons
aren't really patrons,
so we like to have
them forcibly removed.
Harsh.
I doubt you'll have to
worry about that, though;
hopefully we'll both continue to
get lucky as the night goes on.
Perhaps you'd like to
join us for a game
of roulette in the VIP room,
where the stakes are
higher and more private.
So we can get even more?
Definitely.
After you.
Our collection of human money
is progressing smoothly, sister.
Yes, apparently.
Just look at how considerably
our little guy has grown.
As long as he continues
to gorge himself
on that disgusting
Earthly currency,
he'll reach his complete
form which will trigger
the largest financial
meltdown in history,
throwing the human
world into chaos.
I know you already know this;
but I like to hear it out loud.
Perhaps that will give us a
chance to redeem ourselves
from what could very well be
the worst debacle of our lives.
Our darling little ghost plant
taken out by that
tawdry pair of angels.
Their detestable images still
flash in my mind, mocking me.
Just like so, with their vulgar
personas and vacuous faces.
What the devil are
they doing in here?
Do you think they might
be attempting to thwart us?
Judging by that
ludicrous expression,
I would venture a "no."
It's far more likely those
obtuse twits are here to gamble.
Then, by all means,
we should take advantage
of this opportunity
to eradicate them.
Collect yourself, Kneesocks.
The last thing we want to give
them is a perfunctory death.
Of course, what was I thinking?
We must pay them triple the
insult they so rudely handed us.
'Tis a Scanty and
Kneesocks rule!
I have a sublime thought.
Since they're already in our
midst, we might as well
provide them with a genuine
gambling experience.
Amazing, Panty. Have you
ever been complimented
on your incredible
skill set before?
Definitely.
Hey, Panty, we're
supposed to be making
how much for Garter again?
I totally forgot.
Oh, who gives a shit?
Let's have some fuckin' fun.
Ugh.
Goddamnit, why I thought
you'd know is beyond me,
but I'm pretty sure we've
already made our goal.
Awesome!
Now shut your trap and
roulette some shit, okay?!
What the whore said, sir.
I'd like to roulette some shit!
That's the mother
fucking spirit!
Dealer change.
Sugar bear. Your
face is really red.
Are you maybe drunk?
Someone's got Asian hotface.
I do not.
I simply blush
easily, that's all.
Dude, no judgment here.
Now, let's play!
Yes, lets.
Place your bets, please.
Let's make this interesting!
No more bets, thank you.
Oh, no.
Well, no one can
win every time.
Good point.
Let's roll again Hotface!
No more bets, thank you.
What a shame.
Hey, I'm just getting started!
Place your bets, please.
No more bets, thank you.
Too bad.
Shame.
When did the wheel
turn into a cunt?
Seriously, quit fucking around!
Bravo, Kneesocks; bravo!
Continue your assiduous assault
until those hackneyed angels
are broke, shame them
into the depths of despair,
and then annihilate them!
Fuck.
Holy fuck.
We don't have any money left.
Checkmate, harpies.
Ah, hell no!
About time we use
our fucking resources.
Hey boys!
One of you wants to
buy this, don't you?
I'll take it!
My, what a pitiable display.
Over here!
Try this!
And that!
How tediously long do they
intend to keep up this charade?
But, if they continue
to remove their clothing.
They're going to wind up
in the nude, completely.
And without a stitch,
they'll be without a weapon.
This day keeps getting
better and better.
Enjoy this fellas!
Fuck!
Lucky number seven's
it's up to you!
Please win!
Or we'll be naked!
Take it off!
Take it off! Take it off!
One more garment left.
Once Panty removes her
panties, they'll be helpless!
Finally!
The fated war betwixt demons
and angels will come to an end!
At the very least,
these angels will perish!
Hey. Cover up, wouldja?
You're so immodest.
Heh, I'm modestly
freezing my ass off.
We did it!
Fuck yeah; we're back baby!
Whoo!
Shit.
No fair.
Kay.
What the hell is that thing?
I think it might be a ghost.
This day just gets
better and better.
Let's kill this mother fucker
and earn some Heaven coins, too!
That was mortifying,
absolutely wretched!
Remove us from
this hellish place!
Toodle-oo, imbeciles!
You stupid bitches!
Tell me you are not
responsible for this!
Hell yeah we are.
Dude, twisted fucks will pay
anything for random shit.
You idiots!
Have you no shame?
Those are sacred
weapons from Heaven!
You should sell your
skid marked business too.
Here.
Three million.
I can't take your filthy
dirty, coochie cover cash!
Quit being a drama queen!
That cash didn't come close
to my snatch, ya sick fuck!
What?!
The price keeps going up!
Twenty thousand more!
I have to!
I can't let anyone
else have them.
I've gotta protect Panty
or something like that.