"DC Confidential!"
Daten City.
A burrow beloved by demons.
An enduring chaos
thrives in this place,
yet is sealed away from
the rest of the world.
However, that 'good book'
so many humans
rely on says it best,
"for there is nothing covered,
that shall not be revealed;
and hid, that shall
not be known."
The problem is finding the key
to unlock that detestable seal!
The bloodline of the Hell's
Monkey is the only solution.
A descendent must be
located immediately.
Excuse me.
Sir, is everything all right?
My apologies.
Continue with your report.
Yes, Sir.
We would like, at this
juncture, to move forward
onto the second portion of
our annual Ghost Report.
Ghost number 36, also
known as Big Brown Eye.
This was a metaphysical
manifestation of grudges
held by plumbers who,
crushed by copious amounts
of fecal matter clogging
drains throughout the city,
suffocated to death
as the waste
tragically obstructed
their intake of oxygen.
This manifestation
then proceeded
to disgustingly possess
all the feces in the city.
Its hideous essence
left witnesses
and all would be attackers
helpless to do anything
but vomit uncontrollably,
making it a rather
impressively potent ghost.
However, the theme I
am sure you have,
at this point,
perceived, pervades.
Those unabashedly crude,
hopelessly delusional,
horrifyingly idiotic ne'er
do well angel trollops blasted
our Big Brown Eye to bits.
Of course they did.
Don't tell me you honestly
put significant faith
in fecal matter.
Oh.
Sir, no, of course not.
How comforting.
Continue.
Yes, sir.
Ghost number 37, also known as
The Fast and Not So Furious.
This specter was the
manifestation of a grudge held
by a speedy and overly
ticketed taxi driver,
who accidentally
drove off a cliff.
In the end, he
was blasted to bits
after what could be referred
to as failing to yield.
He was the very definition
of idiocy in action.
What a mockery.
Continue.
Ghost Number 38.
Also known as Queen Bee.
She was the manifestation of a
female student's lust for power.
Once reigning over the school
as its most popular attendee,
or queen, she was attacked
and killed by pet bees
belonging to a nerd on
whom she frequently picked.
Her plot to reclaim
her crown was thwarted
by those horrendous angels
and a geek named Brief.
She also was blasted into bits.
As though being the most
popular girl in high school
is the pinnacle of power.
Doomed from the start
by flawed assumption.
She was a waste of a ghost
if ever I've seen one.
Right.
So.
Ghost number 39, or
Little Red Riding Hood
and The Big Bad Wolf, are
the manifestation of grudges,
held by a prostitute
and her pimp.
Apparently they were eaten
by a wolf while soliciting
sex in a park.
Yes.
Now that is something to behold.
Tighter, tighter.
Kneesocks?
Is it just me, or is there
something wrong with the mayor?
I don't know.
Perhaps he's acting
in such a fashion
because he's discovered a way
to dispose of those
revolting angels.
Yes, perhaps!
Enough chatter!
Shall we continue?
Yes, sir.
Ghost number 40,
who is, well are,
actually a group
of demon semen.
Not of the sea but of the sperm.
They felt mistreated, so
they manifested themselves
into nasty little creatures
and raided the tissue plant
in an attempt to avenge
their pointless deaths.
Sadly, they were overcome and
blasted into tiny, tiny bits.
Sperm can't be trusted.
There are strong swimmers
and weak swimmers.
So true, sir.
Moving on.
Ghost number 41, The Diet Ghost.
She was the amalgamation of
the bitterness found in women
who put their faith
in fad diets,
only to end up
atrociously obese.
One of our more
impressive attackers,
she opened a cake shop serving
specialized fat enhancing treats
and even managed to turn
one of those floozy angels
into a gargantuan abomination!
But alas, she was
blasted like all the rest.
Corn nuts!
Master?
At this time, do you
have any comments for us?
No. Just continue.
The mayor is not in
the best mood, Sister.
Let's just get
through this, shall we?
Yes, that is my
current objective!
Next, of course, is Ghost number
42, the Fabulous Lingerie Ghost.
He was born from the grudge of
a teenage lingerie fanatic who,
after some of his more popular
peers stole his underwear
during the school's first
"unmentionables run,"
died when lightning mysteriously
struck his bare penis.
Quite by accident, he managed
to put those loathsome angels
in a precarious position,
but, yet again, that
"Brief" boy assisted them,
and the tackier of the two
angels blasted him to pieces.
So, next we have Ghost
number 43, Oscar the Snot.
This disgusting--
This is pathetic.
How many inconsequential
mediocre ghosts
can we have in one year?
At what point did our ghosts,
ghosts belonging to demons,
sink into a pit of inadequacy?
When I was young,
they still kept the spirit
of primordial chaos alive!
They were tough,
creative, strong,
and silent creatures of power!
But, now, apparently
those days are over!
Just look at this disaster
laid out before me!
These ghosts don't even
understand the meaning of chaos!
It makes me long
for my younger days.
If I had a heart,
it would be sad.
Let us end this
nonsense already.
By which you mean?
By which I mean.
You don't plan to
continue wasting my time
with these useless
reports of yours, do you?
Because I have better
things to do with my time
than sit here and listen
to your repetitive failures!
No, sir.
Of course not.
Putting up with his
mood swings is worse
than dealing with
those angel bitches.
Sister!
Your language!
Please!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
You're quite right.
All this reporting and anxiety
has loosened my tongue.
You know, like after fellatio.
Far too loose, dear.
Fastener, darling, would you
bring us a sofa?
Oh and some wine, too.
While you're at it,
a little caviar,
blue cheese and crackers
wouldn't hurt.
Kneesocks, finally!
It's us!
Devil, we're gorgeous.
Look at you, Sister!
You're so shiny!
Oh, you are always
so sweet to me.
But, if anything, your beauty
radiates as intensely
as the dark sun of Hell.
Gross. It's that nerd, again.
He's like a little puppy,
traipsing after them
wherever they go.
You know what they say, fools
only attract other fools.
What is it about them?
Well, their vocabularies
are spectacular.
Oh, dear.
If I laugh too much, my
cheeks will start to hurt.
Would you like for me to rub
them for you, my darling?
No, stop that.
My face will be as red
as yours, you drunkard!
I was born this way.
And if anything, I'd say
yours is a brighter crimson.
Do you think so?
I am rather flushed.
And you're burning up.
Here, allow me to
take your clothes off.
Oh! No... No...
You don't like that?
Are you sure?
I thought it was your favorite.
I prefer caviar.
"Stay true to your curiosity."
That is our Rule!
Oh my!
That's an interesting
place for it.
I've also got an oozing ripe fig
from the Diablo Orchard
for you, sister dearest!
Oh, yes.
That's not all that's
oozing and ripe, is it?
I just remembered!
I have something for you, too.
Do you remember that creamy milk
from the black goat
at Satan Fest?
Do I!
Rub it into every fold!
Every single one!
Shut up!
Well, look how free
and uninhibited you are.
I would be proud if I thought
you had earned such privileges!
You misunderstand, sir.
This is simply an
evaluation of our skills.
Exactly, as well as
an elaborate training
simulation relating
to future developments.
Oh! I forgot to ask you one
critically important question:
what has your research
into the Hell's Monkey
blood-descendent revealed?
The Hell's Monkey descendent?
Uhh, well.
We, um, are currently
investigating the matter
to our utmost ability.
Oh girls, it isn't nice to lie.
Give me a little
credit, will you?
Why don't you go reflect
upon your ineptitude?
Mister Mayor, no!
Anything but that!
Ghosts.
Demon Sisters.
All completely useless!
I still know nothing concerning
the Hell's Monkey descendent.
Oh god, find my happy place,
find my happy place...
It appears that in
the darkest despair,
there can be found
the darkest hope.
"Panty and Brief!"
Repent, Motherfucker!
Mothershit.
It's practically raining
ghosts out here these days.
Well. Whatever,
that just means more Heaven
Coins for us, ya know.
Panty?
Thanks, yeah.
I'm good!
Fuck me!
Jesus!
Panty!
Goddamnit! Will
you quit screwing
everything in sight and,
I don't know, help me!
Why?
You seem to have it all
under control just fine.
I've got other shit
going on, anyway.
So. Believe it or not,
I've had a side project going on
ever since we got down here.
I can't wait.
This is so fucking huge, you're
not even going to believe it!
Okay, I'm totally gonna do
one thousand Earthly dudes
before I go back to Heaven!
Holy shit.
Your brain is rotting.
You really do have syphilis.
Great, another Godblessed
bullshit mandate.
What the fuck?
Panty!
Yeah, right there!
I don't care; just do it!
Selfish bitch!
For a good time, call me!
You don't even have
that many holes!
Congratulations, hooker angels!
You have finally collected
your Heavenly coin quota!
Now that your mission on
Earth is complete, you are free.
So, there you go.
I'm guessing that means you
can probably go back to Heaven.
Seriously?
The time has come
to get the fuck out.
Move your asses over here
and kneel before the alter.
So this is goodbye to
all my Earthly fuckin'.
Wow.
That side project just
prematurely blew up in my face.
You really are totally
lame, you know.
You half ass everything.
I mean, you couldn't give less
of a shit about killing ghosts.
Why would a thousand
dicks be any different?
Oh.
Guess what.
I have bad news, Panty.
Heaven is less than pleased
with your actions as
a degenerate whore.
You wanna show you're worthy,
go collect your own coins.
Until you've proved yourself,
you shall not pass!
Fuck!
This is such bullshit.
So I'm a slut, big deal.
Who are they to judge?
And why in fuck's name
do you seem happy about
all this, Flaccid Face?
How could I not be happy?
Panty and Brief are
back together again;
it may not be a big deal to you,
but I've never felt more alive!
You can call me
Smegma if it helps.
All right, you want it so bad?
You can have it; kill all the
ghosts you want, Geek Boy.
I'm fuckin' outta here.
Hey!
Panty, come back!
I don't wanna see your ass
until you've collected
some Heaven Coins!
No fair!
Nine hundred and
ninety nine fucks.
Goddamn it!
I figured I'd be at
a thousand by now.
I did not appreciate
that at all.
Well, look at who's here.
You better have
some fuckin' Heavens.
How could I?
I'm just a human;
I don't stand a chance against
that many ghosts all by myself!
Fuck that!
Don't give me excuses.
Dude, you are the most
useless guy I've ever met.
That is not true.
Oh, hey.
Hello, this is Briefers.
Hold on.
Again with the party?
No. No, I told you.
I don't wanna go!
On top of that,
I don't even know her!
I don't care about your stu--
So close-just one
more guy to go.
'Kay, now where the
hell am I gonna meet him.
Fuckin' A!
This place is out of control!
Okay, tell the truth,
how did a giant loser dork
like you get invited
to this party?
You're not so bad, after all!
Hey.
Where the fuck d'he go?
Hold on.
Yeah, this is Panty.
Where you at, slut?
I'm out hunting for ghosts
like I'm supposed to be doing.
Don't fucking lie to me, bitch!
The only thing you're
out hunting for
is more cock to bang, hell!
Shit!
Cross your legs and
focus for a second, Panty.
There's something
important about this
solo coin mission
I forgot to mention.
Oh, great. Like what?
How should I put this?
Uh... No fucking allowed!
Hell no!
That's a horseshit move, Afro.
I only need one more
dick to reach my goal,
and your ass knows it!
So, fuck you and
fuck your rules, too
You'll obey whether
you like it or not.
What the fuck, dude?
Are you kidding me?!
Damn it!
I just want to take a
moment to thank you all
for being here tonight
at the Rock Foundation's
celebrity event.
But, more importantly.
I have an announcement to make.
The daughter of my
good friend, the mayor,
is engaged to be married
to, none other than,
my own cherished son,
Briefers Rock.
Briefers!
Where are you, son?
What are you doing out
in the audience, son?
Come up to the stage and greet
your bride to be immediately.
I can't do that, Dad.
I'm sorry, but I refuse to
marry a girl I don't even like.
Excuse me?!
I mean it, Dad.
I'm not gonna be
your puppet anymore!
If you're trying to embarrass
me, son, you've succeeded.
I don't care!
You can listen
to me for a change!
That's the girl I want to marry.
Not her!
Why does she always
have to ruin everything?!
Sister, please.
We need to move on to Phase Two!
How can you do this to me in
front of all these people?
I can't believe my fiance's
been stolen by a trollop!
Darling, reconsider!
Grody! Get off of
me; no means no!
How dare you?
You're just a disgusting human!
How dare you cast me aside!
Sister, no!
Your horns are showing!
I don't care!
This is taking too long!
Fuck.
Bitch, what are you doing here?
We should be asking
you the same question!
It appears there is no need
to carry on this ridiculous
pretense any longer.
Now once and for all.
You will realize
who is in control!
You freaks are way too
impressed with yourselves.
Bring it.
Because I'm in the mood
for a demon massacre.
Don't say I didn't warn you,
red twats; you're going down!
That creature
doesn't comprehend
the situation she's
in, does she?
I'd cry if it wasn't so funny.
Who's laughing now, bitches?
Say ta ta to that
neck of yours.
Come on!
Backlace, what the fuck?
Why aren't you working?!
Yeah.
That shit's fucked up.
Jesus!
Get it together!
Oh my dear.
Don't you realize a
mere angel doesn't
stand a chance in
hell against us?
We're demons!
That truth has existed
since the dawn of creation!
It is our favorite rule.
Enjoy purgatory, you harlett.
You let go of her!
Pardon me?
No, I don't think I will!
I can't see anything, Scanty!
Where are you?
Let me go!
Stop!
I said stop!
That hurt!
What the fuck, dude?
Oh.
Sorry about that, Panty.
It's just I don't think you
stand much of a chance
against them without Stocking.
How the hell do you
know about Stockin'?
Hold on a minute.
Why are you acting like
you've forgotten who I am?
I'm Brief!
It's me.
Geek Boy? That's you?
Get the fuck out!
I didn't need your damn help!
Not to be rude, but yes you did.
They were gonna kill you.
I couldn't just sit
there and do nothing.
Now come on.
Let's get out of here
before they find us!
Fine.
Fuck!
Seriously, See through!
Oh, come on.
Start already!
Motherfuck!
Not you too, girl.
God, this blows.
Well, at least we
should be safe out here.
Panty, did you know
you're touching me?
Yeah, I know.
I'm not sure why,
but I needed to.
Don't worry. I promise
I'll protect you!
There's no way I'd let
the woman I love get hurt.
You know I love you, right?
I mean, it's kinda weird
to say like this,
but I figured you already knew.
I've loved you ever
since we first met.
Please stop talking.
I wanna see your face again.
Hi, Panty.
You are so damn awkward.
But one thousand
might as well be you.
Shit.
Ouch!
What?
Wait!
Everything's fine; We'll
just try a different position.
No.
Doggie style?
Oww!
Shit, shit, shit,
shit, shit, shit!
Ow, no!
Why does it hurt?!
Whoa. Garter?
What are you doing here?!
Just as I thought.
Girl, you've been revirginized.
Yeah. The good news is
you're no longer a skank;
the bad news is you
have a hymen again.
Hymen?
You're fucking with me, right?
No, I'm not fucking
with you, and,
by the way, you should
count your slut blessings
Brief didn't actually
get all up in there.
A failure!
I'd expect no less from
an angel raised by you.
However, It was rather kind
of your protégé to assist
with the boy's awakening.
What are you
doing here, Corset?!
It's been a long time;
hasn't it, Garterbelt?
In truth, we haven't met
since "then," have we?
Mayor?
I didn't know that
you knew Garter.
Oh yes. Now, my boy,
come to me.
It appears the descendent
of the Hell's Monkey has
been awoken by an angel's kiss.
Just a little nudge!
Finally, it's mine!
How wonderful.
Do you know how
long I've wanted you?
Why do you want my stumpy?
Go, Panty now!
Hurry up and get
Brief out of here!
Right!
You're not going anywhere!
Oh, look who it is, Sister.
The angel whore who can't
even have sex properly.
Do you believe she
thinks she can save him?
I don't believe this
one thinks at all!
Enough!
You're here to escort
the Hell's Monkey.
Yes, sir!
Toodle-oo.
We'll see you in hell.
Hah!
Panty!
Geek Boy!
Why?
I don't understand.
Oh, it seems we have
one less angel among us.
You're in for a hell
of a time, cupcake!
Who will protect you now?
Heaven doesn't want you, and
you've already failed your city.
You are powerless!