13 Months Ago
[KEN] This is G1.
[FEMALE VOICE] This is ISO HQ.
We have bull's-eye.
[MALE VOICE] Excellent.
Coordinates?
[KEN] 34 degrees north, 140
degrees east.
This is it.
The nuclear aircraft carrier
hijacked by Galactor!
[gasp]
Bird... go!
Bird... run!
Well, what do we have here?
Galactor's new toys?!
[flinch]
Now what?
[grunt]
Who in the hell are you?!
[leaping grunt]
[kicking grunt]
Hm?
[startled grunt]
[crowd concerned murmuring]
Hey! Are you okay?!
Good afternoon.
Oh, I thought you were a goner.
Geez. You didn't even slow down!
Look.
Huh?
[gasps]
What in the world...?!
Watch out, Princess!
Come on!
[grunting]
Are you okay, Princess?!
[gasping, panting]
[YOROI] This is exactly what
happened before...
[gasp] Seriously?
[startled gasp]
[YOROI] [panting]
[gasp]
[grunt]
[YOROI / POLIMAR] [grunt]
[lifting grunts]
[GATCHAMAN] Are you hurt?
[EMI KAIDO] Good afternoon.
[GATCHAMAN] I just asked you a
question... Are you hurt?
So I take it you're not one of
the bad guys here.
[punching grunts]
What is this? A superhero show?
[grunts]
[gasps]
[TEKKAMAN] Tekksetter!
[GATCHAMAN] Identify yourselves,
now!
We'll talk later!
[grunt]
[fighting grunts]
Hiya!
[grunts]
Wait... I see what you're
after...
...It's this!
What's so special about this-
Stay out of its way!
You know, don't you?! You know!
[grunt]
[wincing]
[gasp]
[small gasp]
[car horns honking]
[KEN WASHIO] And you two guys
are...?
We're just two guys.
I guess you could say we're...
heroes, okay?
[KEN WASHIO] Heroes?
They don't exist, so you can
drop it.
Hey, I need you to take me back
to my world, ok?
There's no world for you to
return to.
What!?
I knew it would turn out like
this.
The same exact thing happened
to me... about a year ago.
This isn't a joke!
My comrades are waiting!
I have people to protect!
[JOJI MINAMI] We're no different
from you.
We're asking for your help.
Speaking of which, what's your
name anyway?
I'm Emi Kaido.
My name means laughter.
I'm Ken.
Takeshi. Nice to meet ya!
I'm Joji.
[grunt]
I'm Tetsuya.
[JOJI] He developed a device
for inter dimensional travel,
and journeys across worlds,
destroying them, one after
another.
[TAKESHI YOROI] So Professor,
what's his name?
[JOJI] His alias is the last
letter of the alphabet,
fitting for all the death
and destruction.
[TAKESHI YOROI] Z.
[JOJI] He destroys using the
Case.
[KEN WASHIO] Case?
[JOJI] The Case... changes the
possibilities of all worlds.
[TAKESHI] It grants its
wielder's every wish,
making it the ultimate weapon.
[JOJI] Some have even said
it's a reflection of its
wielder's soul.
Resting in Z's hands is a
blazing manifestation
of that power.
I witnessed it! I saw how that
sun consumed my entire world!
[JOJI] The Case is no longer in
his possession.
[KEN] What?
[JOJI] It has now taken the form
of that pencil.
[EMI] Huh?
[KAIDO] In a reality
identical to our own,
I found several other worlds
you and I were a part of.
-But every time...
-Daddy?
[KAIDO] ...there was an
incident, an accident,
or illness.
And in every one
of these worlds,
you died as a young girl.
What's this?!
Emi's death is all but
guaranteed.
No it can't be! That can't be
true.
I know...
A world without Emi is... It's
impossible.
Initially I was certain that
your life would cease to exist.
I thought there was nothing I
could do about it.
But suddenly...
...it fell into my hands.
I had the power to manipulate
possibilities.
It granted me my deepest wish.
So, you mean the...
Yes. The Case.
I proclaimed my wish to the
Case.
I wished for my daughter to
live.
You did? That was... your true
wish?
It was.
[KAZUMICHI KAIDO] After that,
I used the Case...
to diverge the future.
Diverge?
[KAZUMICHI KAIDO] At any moment,
people face a number of choices.
A world where one turns right. A
world where one turns left.
The Case gave me the power
to create a world
with new possibilities.
Like this one.
The world you inhabit now...
The world you live in... is the
one that I have chosen for you.
It's the world where...
Emi Kaido doesn't die.
Emi...
Kaido's been destroying worlds.
That way, Emi never has to die.
So if we shut down Kaido, Emi
could potentially die?
I will create my own
possibilities.
With every step I take, I know
the world will be there.
[KAZUMICHI KAIDO] Why won't you
stop?!
This world will guarantee your
happiness forever!
[small chuckle] You're wrong,
Dad.
This world... would give me
everlasting life but...
There's more to happiness...
than just a beating heart!
I'm not afraid. I want to choose
my own way.
[gasp]
[whimper]
Why are you doing this?
I will carry on... of my own
free will!
[gasp]
Emi...!
[attack grunts]
Ken...!
What are you doing!?
Why the hell are you here?!
I brought company.
[Polimar attack yell]
[attack grunts]
[panting]
[grunt]
[charged up cry]
[GATCHAMAN] You've gotta fight,
Emi.
You can save your father. It's
not too late!
Everything... is for Emi.
[CASSHAN] Let's go!
Hyper destruction beam!
Tornado Fighter!
One-Handed Vacuum Spin!
Vol... tekka!
[gasp]
[scream]
[grunt]
[breath]
[YOUNG EMI] Daddy...
[gasp]
See? I'm not a little girl
anymore, Dad.
Emi.
You're all grown up.
Finally, you see me, just as I
am.
The truth is, you never stopped
thinking about me.
That makes me smile.
Emi...
I love you, Dad.
[giggle] Hey, look!
Emi... you have to wish.
I wish...
...that they'll come back...
All the worlds...
...that have been lost...
...every last one!
All of the other worlds...
they're restored as well.
We're all free to go back now.
I guess we all have some
journeying to do.
[gasp]
Hey, wait!
[KEN WASHIO] Don't cry, Emi!
Be tough!
Get stronger!
Keep growing!
[small sob]
[pop]
[gasp]
Ah!
[screams]
Watch out!
[grunt]
[small grunt]
[gasp]
Where... am I?
[KEN WASHIO] Long time no see...
Ken!
How did you...?
There's something that I need
your help with.
What are you talking about?
We can chat later. Let's go!
[gasp]
[GATCHAMAN] The operation
failed.
You need to evacuate, Doctor.
[DR. KOZABURO NAMBU] I'm going
to use Nexus.
I'm making the final
adjustments now.
No! Please wait!
[DR. KOZABURO NAMBU] Mankind
must win.
[panting gasps]
[panting]
Doctor....
Dr. Nambu, please stop!
That was our last hope.
We'll freeze them so
they can't move...
Then we'll turn them over
to ballistics for research.
There's no other way now.
There's gotta be a way!
As long as we keep on fighting!
As I recall...
All of your team members died,
believing that same thing.
The Galactor have no will of
their own.
Their only goal...
is to exterminate all
intelligent life.
[gasp]
But you already know that.
We must use this power... if
mankind is to survive.
[angry grunt]
My team members...
fought to the very end for the
future of humankind.
They died for it!
That's why...
that's why I will never let
you go through with this!
[gasp]
[fiery explosion]
Ken...
[gasp]
[painful grunts]
Ken...!
[panting]
Ken...
No....!
[gasp]
[SASAOKA] This part of town used
to be so young and vibrant.
It's hard to believe what it's
become.
I wish we could bring Shibuya
back to what it once was
even if just for the sake of
reviving the economy.
That'll never happen, as long as
it exists.
[SASAOKA] Perhaps...
Isn't that why you're here?
Why else would a prominent
member
of the Japanese government
be interested in
meeting with me
...an ordinary scientist?
You're far too modest.
You're no ordinary scientist to
the people here.
You're a hero to them. You saved
their world.
Hm.
Six years ago, the inorganic
life forms of Galactor...
came to this planet.
They were relentless. A threat
to all intelligent life.
Our weapons proved to be
ineffective against them,
and then suddenly,
mankind was on the
brink of extinction.
...That is until Nexus appeared.
Humans had been reduced to
cowering in fear.
Our species needed its power.
But we have new problem.
How do we manage that power now
that the threat is gone?
So you're not happy with my
management... is that it?
No sir. The Ministry voted to
put you in charge of Nexus.
I admit not everyone agreed.
Some people... still oppose the
decision.
But that's not the issue I want
to talk to you about.
[sigh] International pressure.
The demand for us to hand over
data keeps increasing
on a daily basis.
There's no point for us to share
any of our data.
You know that...
We cannot move Nexus to another
site.
That's the problem.
There's so much military power
in our possession
right here in this very spot.
We're hardly in any position
to tell the world they
shouldn't worry.
I suppose not.
Also... more people are becoming
aware of its power...
...and aware of its unique
feature.
If that should... become common
knowledge...
That is exactly the reason... to
keep control of it ourselves.
You agree, don't you?
This situation requires one
supreme power
with a steady hand.
It seems your plan to make Nexus
independent from federal
negotiations simply raises
too many concerns.
And as always,
the Ministry of Defense is
reluctant to lend personnel.
I understand...
The top brass is feeling
pressure from abroad.
Things will change when public
opinion does.
Surely that will happen.
You're an idealist.
And your idealism undeniably
empowered our nation.
That said... I hope it won't be
your downfall.
Well you needn't worry about
that.
Fair enough.
I trust all the preparations...
are in order for
today's ceremony?
Yes and it will be
well attended.
Many young people are anxious
about our country's future.
Hopefully, my speech...
will convince them that
they should unite
behind our shared goals.
[cell phone vibrating]
Please excuse me.
And it's not coming from Nexus?
Investigate right away.
Doctor, we have intruders on
Security Level 3.
What the devil...?
Why weren't they detected
earlier on Levels 1 or 2?
[SECURITY GUARD] It seems...
they just appeared out of
nowhere in Level 3.
Out of nowhere?
What does that mean?
It's eerily quiet here.
Not a single person around...
Joji... learn anything yet?
[JOJI] There's a Singularity in
the center of the dome,
that's for certain.
It looks like it's about ten
meters below the ground.
It should have formed at the
point where Emi and
the Case became separated
but it's slightly off.
It's also possible that
space-time is warped
in this world.
[KEN WASHIO] Is it too risky for
Emi to get close to it?
I don't have enough data yet.
The dome is under government
control.
There are sensors and security
cameras all over it.
[TETSUYA AZUMA] We're being
watched.
Cheese!
Awe gimme a break.
[JOJI] This might be
more trouble than it's
worth right now.
I think maybe we should gather
some more data first.
[alarm sounding]
Hm?
It looks like there are two vans
coming toward you.
They're probably security.
Now what?
Now what? We've come this far.
Might as well get it over with.
Hang on. Let's wait and see.
No need to rush, Princess.
Dr. Nambu?!
Ken...
How did he...
You know this guy?
Yeah...
The doctor here... originally
created the Science Ninja Team.
Be ready.
Yes sir.
Doctor Nambu, listen to me.
I'm not the Ken you used to
know.
Now it makes sense.
So that's what's happened.
Oh wow. You catch on fast there,
don't ya?
Hey Gramps,
it's nice you found a friend but
can we hurry it up now?
Don't call me "gramps!"
Let's just cut to the chase,
okay?
This man is-hey stop wait a
minute...!
You have it, don't you?...
The Singularity?
It's in there, right?
We're gonna get rid of it.
Doctor?
"The Singularity...?"
To put it simply,
it's an abnormal accumulation of
energy from a certain source.
I understand...
So that's the term you're using
for it then?
You know about it?
By a different name.
Why are you so interested in
getting rid of it?
It's dangerous. It could cause
this world to become imbalanced.
We have to destroy it.
Hmm.
Ken, ask about the purpose of
the dome.
Huh?
[JOJI] Ask him now.
Uh... Roger that.
Doctor, what exactly is that
dome for anyway?
Well well... it appears we're
going to be enemies.
What?
Bird Go!
I know I already
asked this but...
you sure you know this guy?
Capture all of them.
Here they come.
Yeah, I can see that.
From this side, too.
[gasp]
Wait up! Why can't we talk?!
I think it's a bit too late for
that...
Change! Polimar!
Doctor!
What's this?
[grunt]
[painful grunts]
[fighting grunts]
[attack grunts]
Hiya!
-Watch out!
-[EMI] [shouts]
Bird Go!
What the hell?!
[gasp]
[panting]
Activate N-mode. Now.
Amazing...
Where did they pick up
that kind of tech?
[attack grunts]
[attack grunt]
[POLIMAR] They leveled up fast!
Damn!
They have power systems built
into their suits.
Be careful.
Pegas, Tekksetter!
Roger.
[attack grunts]
Reinforcements, huh?
AI Center, change the settings
to full-auto on troops who've
lost consciousness.
[angry breath]
[attack grunts]
[angry grunt]
[attack grunt]
Joe...? Joe, is that you!?
[attack cry]
[sigh]
[attack grunt]
[attack grunts]
[gasp]
You're determined to see me
dead, aren't you...
...Joe the Condor.
Joe...!
What are you doing - [grunt]
Ken!
[fainting sigh]
I've got the girl.
Take her to the van.
[DR. NAMBU] Step on it.
Emi!
I'm pulling back.
You should come with me.
But, Emi... [grunt]
[painful pants]
[gasp]
[panting]
[grunts] This way...
Voltekka!
[panting]
panting]
[grunt]
[attack yell]
[attack grunts]
[panting]
[groaning in pain]
[grunts]
That's enough.
[punching grunts]
[gasp]
[frightened gasp] ...Okay!
[painful grunt]
Hey...!
Okay, here's the proof.
These lowlifes are linked to the
enemy.
That should make things easier.
[grunt]
Watch it...
Get a hold of yourself, Joe!
[grunt]
[punching grunt]
[fighting grunts]
Damn you!
...Joe!
[DR. NAMBU] Sounds like a lively
exchange.
[KEN] I'm sorry, Doctor.
Now I know how schoolteachers
must feel.
[sigh]
What's wrong?
I don't understand...
Why bring Joe onto the Science
Ninja Team?
Hmm?
[sigh]
I'm not going to deny the guy's
ability as a fighter...
...and he is smart.
But the thing is...
He doesn't have what it takes...
to truly understand
right from wrong.
I'd say that's probably true.
However... the information he's
always able to obtain
has certainly made
our work easier.
Yeah but it's not about that!
[chuckle]
Your righteousness knows no
bounds, Ken.
And that's funny to you?!
There was only one person
I thought worthy of the
title Gatchaman...
...And that's you, Ken.
Gatchaman is a symbol of hope
for people.
That's why it's perfect for you.
...Joe witnessed the murder of
his parents as a child...
...but he turned his pain into
the power to fight evil.
You could call it a dark form of
justice.
But Ken, if you are to shine the
light of hope upon the world...
Then naturally... someone must
become the shadow.
We need Joe. All of us need him.
But, in my opinion... you
need him most of all.
[weak grunts]
Oh, you're finally awake.
Hey good morning, gramps.
Actually... I take that back cuz
it's not exactly good.
[grunts] I'm okay. It's nothing.
It is really you, right? You're
the real Ken I've always known?
Yeah. You never came back, so I
went looking for you.
Not that I knew where to look.
We searched through every world.
And only one had an
gravitational abnormality.
That's what led us here.
[JOJI] So, Ken wasn't the only
one from his team pulled
into another world by Kaido.
[JOE] Yeah... I remember being
swallowed by the sun,
and then waking
up in this world.
...It was a hell of a shock.
Especially since,
there was another version
of me already here.
Wow that sounds really bizarre.
What was it like to actually
come face to face with yourself?
No big deal... same as looking
in a mirror really.
What about me?
And what about the rest of the
Science Ninja Team?
Why aren't they with you now?
Because the Science Ninja Team
of this world...
They're all dead.
What?
Ken...
So are you.
What the hell happened out
there?
Before I answer... I need to ask
you...
You know about Nexus, right? So
what is it?
You mean the Singularity?
All I've heard is that it's a
super dense energy.
The Ken and Nambu
of this world...
They tried analyzing its powers,
to find out what is was.
They were never able
to figure it out.
Where do we start?
It will be difficult to
understand without
first talking about
what the Case is.
Case?
It's a supernatural object
that gives the power
to manipulate possibilities.
It's important to note that...
the Case came from this world.
And eventually the
Case was stolen...
by this dude named Kaido.
Then we came together.
Our group started fighting
Kaido over the Case.
The Case itself was...
endowed with an enormous
amount of energy.
As long as the Case
remained as it was,
that energy kept this
world stable.
But... what happens when you
remove the Case?
Naturally the empty space left
behind becomes unstable.
So it tries to absorb energy
from its surroundings.
That's exactly what happened
here in this world.
The surrounding energy
compensated
for the missing Case.
[TAKESHI] In other words, now
you've got this massive clump of
energy sitting there where
the Case used to be.
[JOJI] That's the Singularity...
or what you call the Nexus.
In our computer projections,
the world achieves a state of
equilibrium via a cycle
of accumulating and
diffusing energy.
But now we have an abnormality.
Energy that accumulates
perpetually.
In this world, they tapped into
the Singularity's energy.
Because it's only
absorbing energy,
it doesn't reach
equilibrium.
That constant influx of
energy has warped this
world's gravitational field.
I imagine that's also why those
who are stuck here,
can't return to their
original worlds.
I understand.
It all makes sense now.
It's why this world is teetering
on the brink.
What the hell?
[gasp] What is that?
[JOE] The side effects of Nexus.
[TAKESHI] Wait... really?
[JOE] Before all this Nexus
business,
this world was under attack by
invaders called Galactor.
[KEN] Galactor? That thing?!
[JOE] I know. It's completely
different from the Galactor
we knew in our world.
Couldn't they simply be
two different entities
that share the same name?
With several worlds, it's a
possibility.
Whatever they are...
this world's Science Ninja Team
had been battling them for ages.
[sigh]
But it didn't matter what we
tried.
Nothing seemed effective against
them.
Until Doctor Nambu had the idea
to turn that mass of energy,
the Nexus, into a weapon.
I'm amazed that kind of thing
was even possible
Well I can tell you...
we knew it would work.
I'm sure that researching
the Singularity...
must've brought about a
technological breakthrough.
This isn't only about Nexus.
Apparently, he used Galactor
technology too.
That's what powers the new Bird
Suits you saw.
The thing is though... Nexus
energy comes at a cost.
It creates an abnormality
in the world,
each time that it gets used.
[gasp]
[JOJI] I suspected as much.
The Singularity's a
concentration
of this world's energy.
When that energy has all been
spent...
it causes a shortage elsewhere.
Poor bastards...
As you can imagine, Galactor
was totally wiped out...
[gasp]
...but in exchange came
catastrophic weather,
hardly any kids were born...
The birth rates hit an all time
low. [sigh]
If it keeps up this way...
it will result in the
death of this world!
But you knew that
this was possible?
And we fought it! Ken and I did!
But... but in the end Ken was...
Ken was killed by Nambu.
He killed me? Nambu?!
Even with Galactor defeated,
Nambu refused to stop.
And even right now, he's still
exploiting the energy of Nexus.
In the beginning, you had to be
near Nexus to use it.
But now he's got portable tech.
You can charge it and take it
with you like a battery.
...Can you imagine what he could
do with that power?
[gasp]
That's why I have to end it once
and for all.
Nambu has to die.
How can you say that?!
Where're you going?
I know exactly where he'll be
today.
It's time to settle this.
Joe! Wait!
Joe!
Joe, wait!
Think about where we'd be
without Doctor Nambu
and his support. You
can't just go out-
It isn't him. He's not the
Dr. Nambu we knew.
This is the only way.
Stop it. I won't let you do
this.
Oh, yeah??
Doctor Nambu trained us to fight
for justice! Both of us!
We stand for it.
You sound exactly like
the Ken of this world.
He talked like that
till the end...
'Till he got himself killed.
[gasp]
[NEWSCASTER] This afternoon, a
solemn ceremony is being held
in memory of the victims of
the Galactor invasion.
Peace Park, the site
of the ceremony,
was recently completed inside
the Nexus district's
first security area,
where entry is usually
restricted
for ordinary citizens.
People say prayers...
not just for those
they have lost...
but also for themselves.
Having now achieved peace,
what should we turn our
attention to next, hmm?
[struggling grunts]
Should we mourn those we
couldn't save?
Agonize over our helplessness?
A well-trodden path, but a
mistaken one.
To my mind...
It's anger that we truly
require.
Anger?
We avoided destruction. How long
can that be sustained?
When another enemy like Galactor
appears, I wonder...
will mankind be able
to confront them?
What are you talking about?
Who knows if another
enemy will even come?
[struggling grunts]
But when they do, it'll be too
late!
In the meantime...
the people's will to fight must
be carefully nurtured.
What do you mean?
People only stand and fight...
in the face of a threat.
So until a true threat appears
again...
I guess...
I'll just have to play
that part myself.
As far as Nexus energy
weapons are concerned,
this one's on the weaker side.
But it can detect the unique
vibrations of the Galactor
and will fire automatically.
[small gasp]
[blows]
Of course...
it is only a prototype and those
do tend to malfunction.
Its issues are very well
documented.
But as you can see, we lack the
budget to dispose of it,
let alone repair it.
So the whole thing is simply
neglected.
[gasp] My god, you're totally
insane!
You said earlier that you can
"get rid" of Nexus.
Your words... gave me a lot to
think about.
Nexus is a natural phenomenon.
It's existence, fundamental.
To unmake it would be a miracle.
Can you work miracles?
If so, go right ahead and try to
stop this.
When you do, I'll be more than
happy to make your power my own.
Hey, wait! Wait...!
[struggling grunts]
[EMCEE] And now we ask, if you
are able to stand, please rise.
...Let us pray...
One year ago, The Galactor,
a threat to all mankind,
were defeated.
However, for me I would describe
this victory...
as a rather bittersweet
experience.
Even now... that feeling remains
with me.
What is victory?
As you are all aware,
I was the one in charge of the
Science Ninja Team...
Five brave warriors who
protected mankind.
Each one of them faced the
Galactor head on.
Sadly... they all perished.
So with the defeat of Galactor,
those warriors will never
come home to us.
When I lost those
precious comrades.
I knew for me there
could never be,
such a thing as victory.
[sobbing]
And yet, I had to keep going.
I had to keep fighting
no matter what!
So... now I want to
make sure that
no one, including me,
will ever encounter
such loss again!
I promise you!
That's the reason...
the only reason
I seek power!
That menace is gone now, people.
But I continue my research
on Nexus...
and its potential use for
military applications
despite knowing there are
those who voice fierce
opposition to my actions.
[alarm sounding]
[gasp]
[struggling grunts]
Do not forget...
When the Galactor first
appeared from space,
we had no warning that
they were coming.
So... what guarantee do
we have that another
such threat will not appear?
You can see our battle is not
over yet.
We must stay strong... and keep
fighting.
As long as we live we cannot
stop fighting!
Power is essential. That's a
fact.
But so is the people's will!
You all have gathered
here today...
out of the love for those
that we've lost...
However... I must be very frank.
Thinking of those who
are no longer here...
amounts to nothing.
Furthermore, prayer is simply a
means to console oneself.
Let's move on.
Let's advance forward and
forge our own future!
Bird Go!
I can give you...
each and every single one
of you the power to fight!
[frightened gasp]
[murmuring]
[frightened screams]
[gasp]
[frightened cries]
[screaming]
No, stop! Please, stop it!
[gasping breaths]
No! Stop this now!
[struggling grunts]
Ken...?
[sigh]
[small grunt]
Hm.
Huh?
Hang on.
A little good luck charm from
yours truly...
[frightened screams]
[DR. NAMBU] There is nothing to
fear!
Listen to me.
We only have to unite in
opposition to this threat!
If you have the will, step
forward! Come on!
[gasp]
You don't need any
special training...
nor do you need any techniques
to fight in these suits.
All you need is the desire
to wear them...
and then, the suit
will do the rest.
There are three Galactor.
We'll work in teams of
three to subdue them.
I feel so light!
[grunts]
Ken, there's no need to rush in.
They've been kept
frozen in storage.
It drained all of
their strength.
Those amateurs'll do fine.
[KEN] Are you sure? Seems risky.
No need to worry-let them have
their fun.
[JOJI] We might be able to use
the advanced wave generator
from Blue Earth's
braking system.
Advanced wave?
Mm. See normally...
a wave moves outward from
its point of origin.
But in contrast,
advanced wave generation moves
in toward its point of origin.
Professor... simplify it for us
will you.
No problem. An advanced wave
cancels out...
a normal wave it collides with.
In Blue Earth, when we executed
the dimensional jump,
we used advanced waves to brake
by offsetting our momentum.
We can use a similar method to
block the energy
being supplied by Nexus.
[TAKESHI] Sounds good, but how
do we do that?
Those intruders from this
morning are back.
You can use your railguns now,
and you can fire at will.
Ready!? Fire!
[POLIMAR] This time they have
guns and they're using them.
Railguns.
Initial velocity Mach 2. They're
not very powerful.
Plus they're using practice
bullets.
It shouldn't penetrate your
Polimar suit.
That is... unless you're at
point-blank range.
[CASSHAN] Professor...
Tetsuya that goes for you as
well.
[loud sound]
[CASSHAN] Yeah, that's pretty
strong.
[POLIMAR] Hey, dummy, he said be
careful!
We don't know enough about Nexus
yet...
...how it supplies energy to the
Bird Suits. It's a mystery.
[attack grunt]
[JOJI] However... when it does,
it ends up warping the
gravitational field.
...Considering that, we
can have the computer
create a theoretical model
of the energy waves.
In other words, we use the shape
of the vessel to predict...
what's inside?
Precisely.
[attack grunts]
[fearful gasp]
Tsk. He's too nice.
[grunt]
It's Gatchaman!
I thought he was killed by
Galactor!
[gasp] That's not the real
Gatchaman, dammit!
He's an invader from
another world.
Stay back, he's dangerous!
[running grunts]
[panting]
Use your railguns on them!
But we shouldn't just execute
them!
[groan] AI Center,
set the new recruits Bird
Suits to full-auto.
And then Set G1 and G2 as the
main targets.
What's happening?! My body's
moving... on its own!
[stammering]
Doctor, N-Mode is down.
What!?
[JOJI] Ken, I've initiated
advanced wave generation.
It's just like we thought:
The energy supply has
been obstructed.
Within two minutes, it will stop
completely.
The cause is unknown.
Nexus is sending energy at a
normal rate.
But somewhere along the line,
the energy is being drained.
Huh?
[grunts]
[nervous gasps]
Cut out the energy feed
immediately.
If you cooperate, you will not
be harmed!
[gasp]
[grunt]
[groaning]
[grunting]
[gasp]
Let go.
Don't kill him.
You know that's not the way that
we do things.
I don't care.
You should care...
Kids are watching.
Protecting the people is the
duty of a hero.
Don't lose sight of what is
right!
This is why you're the leader.
[SASAOKA] I have no time for
your personal grudges,
Joe the Condor.
I shouldn't have to remind you,
your job was to secure Nambu.
Who are you?
[JOE] She's my boss.
[GATCHAMAN] Huh?
I'm a government
representative.
But I can't tell you
for which country.
I'm here to carry
out a resolution
from the United Nations.
With Nexus in Nambu's control,
I could only wait
for him to stumble.
[grunt]
But I would never have imagined
this.
Oh I see...
You were only helping
Joe in order to stop me.
I figured working with her would
give me the best odds.
Looks like I was right.
Dr. Nambu...
At an emergency board
meeting this morning,
your removal from
office was decided.
They're currently getting final
authorization.
I guess that explains the Prime
Minister's absence.
Your cohorts in these
illegal activities
will be dismissed, too.
Listen up! You have a new
commanding officer now.
We are taking Nambu into
custody...
with the consent of the
Japanese government.
Understood.
[grunting]
[long exhale]
It looks like there nothing's
happening.
[small exhale]
I don't get it.
If I had to guestimate...
there's not enough power.
What? Are you kidding me?
C'mon, are you serious? It ran
out of power?
So something's changed since
Kaido?
The original power of the Case
was scattered back then.
Only fragments remained with
Emi.
Actually it's something more
like echoes.
Yes but... when I was back in my
own world...
Emi-it can create
miracles but...
but only in your original world.
For now, that's the extent of
the Case's power.
Then that means...
There's no way to undo this.
[groan] Let's think!
There's got to be a way.
What if we destroy the device
extracting energy
from the Singularity?
Yeah but... that'd be a
temporary fix at best.
Energy is no longer being
extracted.
So if the energy flowing in
starts to fill it up
and stays there,
the Singularity will
begin to diffuse.
And then it's possible....
It might become small enough
for Emi to extinguish.
Let's hope so.
You went too far. I warned you.
You could've taken
a different path.
You could've used Nexus to
create other military weapons,
like the one that brought
down Galactor.
But instead you focused on
creating a more versatile
Bird Suit for mass-production.
And why?
Because the threat you
were envisioning...
always included
humans beings.
Sleek, mobile suits were the
perfect choice...
for counteracting an
invading force.
And I suppose...
just as useful if you are to
side with the invaders.
You are a frightening man.
Did you actually think other
nations would ignore
someone like you?
My country however...
is ready to make a deal
with you right now.
Without... UN involvement.
So you want a part of the
profits then?
It's not fair for one country to
have all the power, is it?
A deterrent is necessary.
That's my line.
Do you want to remain locked up
for the rest of your life?
Or will you accept our
proposition?
It's a rather simple question.
My wish has always been to
strengthen mankind.
Your proposition is beneath me.
You can't sacrifice
other countries and
take the moral
high ground.
Not everyone is destined
to have real power.
Those who are...
Well, they must accept the
responsibility to wield it.
Hm...
Hm.
[small gasps]
What's the matter?
Did you guys just...
hear a voice?
Nah. I think you're imagining
things.
How'd you get here?
[finger snap]
[gasp]
[grunting]
Emi! Hey Emi! Are you okay?
I think... I think I'm hurt.
Bird... go!
What is he up to?
Damn it all! He's tapped in
directly!
[grunt]
[painful grunts]
[fighting grunts]
Hey! Are you okay?
Be careful. It's stronger this
time.
[gasps]
Pegas... Tekksetter!
Roger.
[fighting grunts]
[grunts]
[panting]
[fighting grunts]
[grunts]
Stay here and try not to move.
Trust me, moving's the last
thing on my mind.
Joe...!
Don't get involved. I know
you're set on killing Dr. Nambu.
Leave the situation to us.
Dumb-ass. Quit wasting time.
[shouts in pain]
[grunt]
[gasp]
I'm asking you to back off,
Doctor.
You cannot keep using its power!
This world can't take it... You
know what'll happen!
Yeah... He's way too far gone to
care.
Bird... Go!
[fighting grunts]
Don't you remember...
You formed Gatchaman...
because you wanted to
protect mankind.
So what are you doing?!
Nothing about my objective has
changed.
What?
[grunt]
But I didn't know how weak I
was.
Until I lost what I valued
most, my precious comrades!
That may be true...
but the man I knew was
righteous to his core!
You know nothing!
[fighting grunts]
Of what value is righteousness?
Do you know what
it feels like...
to watch your team members be
killed off one by one?
To be totally overcome by
helplessness?!
[panting]
I could've protected them with
this power. But I was too weak!
[attack grunt]
Now! Super Destruction Beam!
[fighting grunts]
[wincing]
[fainting gasp]
[groaning]
[grunt]
[POLIMAR] Bastard-!
[fighting grunts]
You know... you're such a
coward...
What?
You can't overcome your fear of
loss, so you throw a fit.
You're like a scared kid.
[grunt]
[fighting grunts]
It's pathetic. The thought that
I followed a guy like you...
makes me want to puke.
Maybe I can't understand
how you feel...
But... when I look at you
now all I see is a weak man!
And that's not the kind of man
you were before this!
Be quiet.
The one who gave me the name
Gatchaman...
The one who taught me the
meaning of the word hope...
Where is he now?!
I said quiet!
[fighting grunts]
[weak grunt]
Ken... [gasp]
[VOICE] Stop....
Who are you?
[VOICE] Stop it!
[gasp]
[running breaths]
[grunt]
What're you doing? Stop!
[strained grunts]
Emi, no!
[gasp]
[grunt]
That was crazy. What were you
doing?
I don't know, but it's what the
Case wanted.
What? What do you mean?
Hey...
It's okay... I think.
So this is Nexus...
Something's there.
Is that a bird?
No... It's Gatchaman's Bird Run.
[gasp]
[painful grunt]
[grunt]
[painful grunts]
[gasp]
[VOICE] Please, stop... Dr.
Nambu.
That light...
Does the power of the Case live
in that Bird Run now?
Huh?
[grunting]
Impossible...
[gasp]
Ken! Get that Bird Run!
[attack grunt]
[grunts]
Hiya!
[grunt]
[groaning in pain]
[gasp]
[grunt]
[attack yell]
No, don't...!
[screaming]
[panting breaths]
[stunned gasp]
Get back!
[panting]
[grunt] Get back here!
Joe! Hold up!
[gasp]
[panting]
[grunt]
The Singularity's energy is
dropping fast.
What should we do now?
It's been reset.
But as it reaches
its equilibrium,
it'll cause a massive
counter-current.
Wasn't that the original idea?
No. The energy flow is too
rapid.
Okay... What does that mean?
Too great an energy flow... will
drain the surrounding area.
At this rate, the entirety of
Shibuya will be drained.
It'll crumble to ash.
Is there anything we can do?
[JOJI] This kind of reset should
only be temporary.
...We just have to ride it
out...
What about that building that
was hit by the Nexus weapon?
There might still be some people
at the ceremony site.
[grunt]
[bewildered grunts]
[panting]
[JOE THE CONDOR] Nambu!
[grunt]
[attack cry]
[NAMBU] [Groan]
This better end right now.
The only thing we received in
exchange for his release
are these guns.
[SASAOKA] We're far from done
with him.
...So the best thing you can do
is put down your weapon.
So that's how it is.
You wanted Nexus all along from
the very beginning.
Dr. Nambu is currently
the only one...
who knows how to convert
energy from Nexus.
The world will slide into
chaos without him.
Letting him live is
the right thing to do.
It's always the same old thing.
Humans can't help but lust for
power.
"The right thing to do"
Really?
[small chuckle]
That's not my style.
[gasp]
[grunt]
[SASAOKA] That's enough! Cease
fire!
[dying grunts]
[grunt]
[struggling breaths]
[gasping]
Bird Signal?
Hey Joe, is that you?
You okay?
Joe!
Joe...
Hey...!
[dying breaths]
Why, Joe?
[gasp]
[JOE] Still... shining...
Hang on...! Joe!
[GATCHAMAN] Joe...!
...Joe!
[sobbing]
[angry scream]
[JOJI] You're really going to
stay here in this world?
[KEN] Yeah.
The Nexus is still here. So I
can't leave now.
The doctor may no longer be
around,
but eventually someone'll show
up who wants it for evil.
That's cool then. I suppose
someone ought to be guarding it.
The device draining the world of
energy is finally gone now.
[JOJI] From now on, it'll be an
easy ebb and flow.
[JOJI] Over time it will
stabilize.
But... realistically that
could take many years.
Once people here can
live in peace
and the Nexus can finally
be eliminated...
Then I'll return to my world.
Alright. We'll keep an eye on
your home world for ya,
until you're ready
to get back there.
Yeah?
We'll take good care of it.
Thank you.
[TAKESHI] Emi! Hey, this is
goodbye ya know.
Don't you want to
say anything to us?
I hate that stuff.
And why are you
always like this?
Why do you have to do all
the heavy lifting?
You never ask for help. It's
really annoying.
[chuckling]
[laugh] I'll be fine.
[shy laugh]
[happy sigh]
[KEN] You'll see.
[gasps in amazement]
[NEWSCASTER] It's been nearly
three months since the incident
caused by Kozaburo Nambu
and the Ministry's
announcement shortly afterwards
about the elimination of Nexus.
Despite knowing the dangers
posed by Nexus,
they allowed Nambu
to have sole authority
over its management.
As to the responsibility of
the government...
[grunts]
[gasp]
Are you going to kill me? Tell
me now.
Heh. That's just not how I
operate.
[explosion]