[FROLAYTIA] We now have
satellite confirmation!
They've brought out another
spare Object weapon against us,
but this time, it's the
Break Carrier's main cannon.
The high-output rail gun!
[BOTH gasp]
Come in Princess!
You're in close range
of their gun,
but it's also within
reach of our main gun.
Unleash the thunder, Princess.
Before they fire on us!
[MILINDA] I can't get
a good line of sight.
[gasps]
Princess, look out!
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR scream]
[coughs]
Havia?
Havia!
[HAVIA]
The freakin' road caved in!
Watch your step, Qwenthur.
I promise this overgrown
pot-hole ain't worth the trip!
[QWENTHUR]
Thanks for the advice!
[HAVIA]
Sure!
Look, I don't think
I'll be able to climb out.
I'm gonna try to
find another way.
[QWENTHUR]
Roger that! Don't get killed!
[HAVIA]
Back at ya!
Baby Magnum. Status report?
[MILINDA] I've been pinned
down by the rubble.
I'm a sitting duck!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[MILINDA] Qwenthur, if you
could blow the rubble off
my electro-static repulsors,
I'd appreciate it.
[QWENTHUR]
I can certainly try--
[screams]
[groans]
[MILINDA]
Oh, no! Are you all right?
[QWENTHUR]
Y-Yeah.
Dammit.
[STACCATO] Come in Baby Magnum,
this is Burning Alpha.
Looks like you could use a hand.
Or more accurately,
some 500 kilogram bombs,
but you get the gist.
Burning Alpha,
the enemy has a fully
operational spare Object gun.
They most likely have
anti-air lasers set up!
Flying in that kind of airspace
will only get you shot down!
[STACCATO]
Don't I know it, baby.
Here goes.
[STACCATO]
The trick is to fly a path
that makes it impossible
to lock onto me.
[STACCATO gasps]
[STACCATO]
Sure, it's practically suicidal.
But every now and then, I wanna
shot at bein' the hero too!
[QWENTHUR yelps]
You tryin' to kill me,
Hotshot? Not cool.
I suggest you stay
down, Qwenthur.
I'm firing on the
enemy gun battery!
[QWENTHUR]
All right.
Time to toast that
crazy powerful rail gun.
Hold on a second.
Is it even possible?
Could firepower
of that magnitude
be stabilized by a
bunch of anchors?
Look at what happened to
their sub-weapon rail guns.
They all toppled over.
If you take a main gun with
that much power behind it.
Of course. That's it.
If there really were
another Object,
they wouldn't use their
rail guns like this!
Even with a
half-operational unit.
So that means there's
no Unknown X.
Instead, if they have anything
at all, it would be...
Princess!
The rail gun is actually a trap
set just for the Baby Magnum!
Don't panic, but I think they
buried a prototype reactor!
You have to get out
of there, now!
[FROLAYTIA]
Let's cut to the chase.
You're going to accept his
request for intervention,
aren't you, Lieutenant
Colonel Farolito?
Yes. And I'll be
perfectly frank.
Whether this sparks a war
between your Legitimate Kingdom
and the Capital
Enterprise or not
has no impact
on the Intelligence Union's
decision whatsoever.
Yes, the railgun technology
on the Break Carrier
is absolutely unprecedented,
but what you're suggesting
is simply not worth it.
[LENDY]
You misunderstand.
This has nothing to
do with the railgun,
though it is a nice bonus.
No, what we're after
is the actual Mass Driver
space technology itself.
[FROLAYTIA gasps] Is that
supposed to be a joke, Lendy?
Your space transport program
should be capable
of using the same laser-driven
Orbital Elevators we use.
Why go after something
so outdated?
You should know the fragility
of conventional doctrines.
The laser system may
be superior today,
but you never know when some
as-yet-undiscovered problem
might rear its head.
Contingency plans will
always be necessary;
which is why sifting through
all the acquired data,
even that which seems
of little use,
will be the key to our survival
in the ever changing
battlefields of the near future.
You see, each bit
of data is a thread,
insignificant
on its own,
but woven together,
it becomes a net,
making the desired fish
easier to catch,
as well as keeping out any pests
the world might throw at us.
Perfect Browsing intelligence?
It's a total pipe dream, and
you'd plunge us all into a war
for a sliver of a chance
to make it happen?
[LENDY]
Yes.
[FROLAYTIA]
Hmph. So be it.
We'll be forced to eliminate
Sladder Honeysuckle
with extreme prejudice and deny
you any possible reason
to intervene in our
nation's affairs.
Then you had better hurry.
We're in the final preparation
stages for the upcoming battle.
And as I'm sure you realize
if the Mass Driver Foundation
is able to destroy your
Object in the field,
you'd be left with nothing
which might deter the full
force of our onslaught.
[laughs] I give you half
an hour, 45 minutes tops
before I've wiped you all out.
[QWENTHUR grunting]
You all right?
[MILINDA]
Yeah. You?
I'm fine.
Somehow avoided being barbecued.
[MILINDA] I won't be
mobile anytime soon.
They damaged my feet
pretty severely.
And because of that,
the countdown has started.
[QWENTHUR]
The countdown?
What for?
The self-destruct system?!
[MILINDA]
Yes.
I'm sifting through subroutines
to cancel the command.
Just hope I can move
faster than the system.
[QWENTHUR]
And if you can't?
Does that mean the Baby
Magnum is gonna blow up?
[MILINDA] Unlikely. The system
is probably in Pattern B,
which means it'll eject the
Elite, then enter standby mode
ready to respond to a
remote detonation command.
[QWENTHUR]
Uh...
[MILINDA]
I'm so sorry, Qwenthur.
I know that if I
lose the Object now,
our entire army is going
to suffer for it.
[QWENTHUR]
Hey, it's okay!
We're the ones who made you
fight in the first place,
even though you were
already damaged.
Don't let it bother
you, Princess.
Thank you.
[QWENTHUR]
Forget it.
Let's just worry about
getting away for now.
Do you know your estimated
landing point after ejection?
[MILINDA] Yeah. Sending
the coordinates your way.
Showing one hundred
seconds to ejection.
Following coordinates.
See you at your LZ.
[QWENTHUR]
Our people are scattered.
There's no use in asking
for reinforcements,
and I haven't heard
anything from Havia.
That bastard better not
have gone and died on me.
What if this was their plan?
Force a self-destruct,
set up anti-aircraft guns,
anticipating the
pilot's trajectory?
[QWENTHUR]
The hell was that?!
Looks like... a steel net?
It's blocking the
ejection hatch.
If the Princess ejects with
that thing in the way...
She'll smash into
it at high velocity!
It'll cut her to ribbons!
Listen close!
You've got to cancel
the ejection countdown!
[MILINDA]
What?
[QWENTHUR] Someone's
deliberately blocked the hatch
with a steel net! If the system
activates with it in place
you'll get shredded
by the wires!
[gasps]
[QWENTHUR]
No time to even respond.
Damn!
[MILINDA] Subroutine 1134 B
to bypass the command signal.
No good...
Disable security on 1157 C.
Enter debugging mode.
No good!
[QWENTHUR panting]
[MILINDA]
No good!
[radio static]
[QWENTHUR yells]
[sighs] That was close.
My hero.
Uh?
[MILINDA gasps]
Qwenthur!
Uh?
[SLADDER]
Legitimate Kingdom, I take it?
Looks like the little
miss is well liked
by those serving under her.
And who might you be?!
[SLADDER]
Sladder Honeysuckle, boy.
Military advisor to the Mass
Driver Foundation's ex-chairman.
Capital Enterprise
top-tier investor.
Oh, and world-renowned
Object designer.
The man your Legitimate Kingdom
military superiors want dead,
priority number one!
And since you haven't
returned fire on me,
I assume you don't have a gun.
Better hurry up and kill me
before the Intelligence Union
and the Capital Enterprise
come rolling through here
like they own the place!
Just surrender!
You can try bluffing, but I
know you're out of Objects!
The high-output rail gun
and the test reactor?
You used them
springing your trap!
You're out of moves!
Says the pessimist.
News flash: the Intelligence
Union'll be here soon.
I've requested asylum with them.
How do you think they
deal with rats like you?
Sure, go with them
and get tortured
for the rest of your short life!
A bastard who sells his
own country's intel?
No way is some other country
ever gonna trust him!
Just saying, in case
you didn't know.
[SLADDER]
Hmph. Maybe you're right.
If the Mass Driver tech's
the only gift I come bearing.
[gasps]
[SLADDER] What did you think
this elaborate setup was for?
Our Rizolette's firing range
maxes out at three
thousand klicks.
If we'd really wanted to,
we could've taken out your
Object from the very beginning
while it was still on standby
in the Antarctic Ocean.
[QWENTHUR]
Rizolette?
That must be the Break Carrier's
official designation.
So what are you playing at?!
The death of
conventional doctrines.
[QWENTHUR]
Uh!
[SLADDER] Objects have become
synonymous with war.
Victory or defeat is calculated
before the fight
even begins according to
quantity and unit specs.
These have been the rules
of modern warfare
since Objects first arrived
on the battlefield,
and quite a few people would
like to see this trend
finally meet its end.
That's what I'm after.
[gasps] Don't tell me...
[SLADDER] To defeat an Object
without using an Object.
The naysayers have been dreaming
of that possibility for years.
And to demonstrate that
it can, in fact, be done.
The time had come
for me to take action.
Like the anti-tank
positions in Antarctica
built from a surplus
of small arms.
Or the trap with the
high-output railgun as bait.
And the resulting
point-blank explosion
from the prototype reactor.
I also collected a
sizable amount of data
which might prove so useful
to the Intelligence Union,
they grant me asylum.
Furthermore, this research
has given me insight
on a major breakthrough
that's promisingly attainable,
but still slightly incomplete.
When it comes time
to negotiate,
it'll be more effective than
intel on perfected technology.
And since my innovation
is theoretically sound,
yet incomplete,
torture's not a viable option.
[QWENTHUR]
So that's it.
He's planning to use
his potential research
as a last ditch Ace in the hole.
Instead of spending resources
to build Objects,
if you could crush an enemy
with just the parts,
war would be a
fraction of the cost.
No,
it would be a fraction of
a fraction of the cost.
Whether it's even viable
or not isn't important.
By making them think
such a method
might possibly be within reach,
he strengthens his
bargaining position.
And to do that...
You let the Break
Carrier be destroyed
and let them think
all that's possible!
Break Carrier? Ah.
That was your side's
codename for the Rizolette?
To tell the truth, it wasn't
that pre-meditated.
After the loss of the Rizolette,
I realized my plans
would need to change.
The promise of a tech
that destroys Objects
without Objects would be the
key to my bid for asylum.
So what I'm doing
right now is basically
the "Plan B" that I'd
set up in advance.
Just between us?
If we can continue developing
Mass Driver technology
the way we see fit, we don't
care about the rest.
Whether that means a
free-for-all war breaks out
between three armies, or people
come to their senses,
and shift away from modern
Object-centric warfare.
The world must choose,
and those giants are only
good for creating death.
I'm afraid you and I will never
come to an understanding.
[SLADDER]
Enlighten me.
People like you let Objects
and Elites wage your wars,
while you just sit there
counting your money.
But when the time comes,
and your Object is defeated,
you have no qualms pointing
your finger at the pilot,
saying "It was all this
bastard's fault!"
"We just built it!
We didn't do anything wrong!"
[QWENTHUR] Then again,
if things go south here,
the brass might end up
saying the same about me.
[SLADDER] At least I'm not
completely delusional.
You try to avoid casualties
out of some sense of honor.
A misguided wannabe destroying
the very Objects he hopes
to one day design.
Right?
Engineer Qwenthur Barbotage?
What the...
[QWENTHUR] How does this
bastard know my name?
[QWENTHUR]
He's charging.
[QWENTHUR groaning]
[SLADDER]
You're more famous
than you give
yourself credit for.
Yes, you.
Especially among the
Object making community.
They've grown tired of you
destroying the best
they can create!
[QWENTHUR screaming]
How dramatic.
It barely grazed you.
I'm an engineer,
first and foremost,
so I'm practically an
amateur with firearms.
Nicking you was pure luck.
Which means I plan to kill you
the second I get the chance.
Hey, now should be perfect!
I can't miss at this range!
[QWENTHUR]
Do it.
Or you can waste your
opportunity by gloating.
You've had more than enough time
to empty that entire
magazine, you coward!
Because you have to prove
how clever you are,
you get taken advantage of
and lose the upper hand!
Uh!
Don't bother aiming,
you've run out of time!
[SLADDER]
How dare he!
Hold on, that switch...
Is it even connected to
those bombs on his chest?
Or something else...?
[SLADDER groaning]
[HAVIA]
Freeze, scumbag.
You're supposed to be a genius.
You should know when to give up.
Not too bad,
looks like I showed up
in the nick of time!
[QWENTHUR]
Yeah.
That's checkmate.
[HAVIA]
I'm glad that's over.
And it looks like the
Mass Driver Foundation
is gonna answer for their crimes
under Legitimate Kingdom law.
Well, everything was technically
resolved within our borders.
[FROLAYTIA]
The Capital Enterprise and the
Intelligence Union both came
to Amazonia with the intent
of extraditing the fugitive
Sladder Honeysuckle.
But we have no intention
of obliging them.
And what about Honeysuckle?
What happens to him?
[FROLAYTIA] They're bickering
over that as we speak.
If you'd shot him dead,
then and there,
it would've made things
much simpler in general.
But you didn't because of...
your similar circumstances?
Honestly, I don't
really know why.
It's just...
Everything we did,
we did to stay alive.
I thought, "couldn't the
same be said of him?"
With him disarmed,
he didn't need to die.
[MILINDA] They've estimated
repair time at about two weeks.
Looks like I'm grounded
until they're finished.
You did a great job.
I mean it. Thanks again.
You did good work, too.
But we cut it close, didn't we?
[HAVIA, FROLAYTIA]
Heh.
[QWENTHUR] The death of
conventional doctrines. How?
[HAVIA]
Huh?
Forget about it.
Something Honeysuckle said.
We're not the only ones, now.
Others are showing
up, devising ways
to destroy Objects without
using an Object themselves.
Soon, they'll be
as successful as us.
[HAVIA]
Isn't that the way of things?
The history of warfare's
full of soldiers
devising new ways to
defeat their enemies.
So tell me. Is that
cycle a good thing?
[HAVIA]
Beats me.
But y'know, our
style of fighting,
with the focus on Objects
results in minimal casualties
during dispute resolution.
And, hey! On that topic,
we had an all-right record
on this excursion!
First, we blasted the
Break Carrier into pieces,
and yours truly prevented
the destruction of the dam.
Oh! And the cherry on top, we
captured the enemy leader alive!
Yeah! Havia's right!
Lots'a meritorious conduct!
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA]
Boom!
What are you fools
talking about?
The Princess was the one
who actually finished off
the Break Carrier, as I recall.
And if you want to bring up
what happened at the dam,
know that Corporal
Saronna's plan,
playing by the books, was right.
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA]
Huh?
Even the capture of Honeysuckle,
it wasn't a solo action,
but part of a larger operation
run by the battalion.
So thank you for doing your
part in our unit's success.
Now let's move on to where
you idiots screwed up.
First, you went out
of your way to save
the Capital Enterprise's
Major General
at his vacation home on the
moon, that's a big minus.
[QWENTHUR]
Huh...
Next, I heard you
had tea and crumpets
on the coffee farm
down at the op site.
Receipt of goods and services
from non-combatants
during an op is against
regulations: another minus.
Come on!
[FROLAYTIA]
And to top it off?
Qwenthur thought it would be fun
to give me a surprise
breast-fondling.
Insulting a superior officer
is the biggest minus of all!
Bastard! How'd you pull
it off? I'm so jealous!
[FROLAYTIA] Looking at
the whole picture, though,
the plusses stand out
more than the minuses.
But you still have to be
punished for your infractions.
Three hundred lashes seems fair.
You're gonna flay us from head
to toe after all we've done?!
You can't hold that kind of
grudge because of your cans!
They were incredibly squishy,
but I think the price
you're making us pay
for your rockin'
rack is too high!
[MILINDA] After every ten
lashes, we'll switch things up
and drip ten candles
on your tender parts.
[QWENTHUR]
No deal!
That doesn't even come close
to mitigating our punishment!
I don't wanna wear a weird,
wax chastity belt!
Whatever happened to letting
the punishment fit the crime?
I didn't even get
to honk your hooters!
No fair givin' me
the same punishment!
[QWENTHUR] Please, I don't
handle candles well!
Rope and a horse?
[HAVIA]
What is this, a rodeo?!
[QWENTHUR]
I don't wanna die!
Oh, so you'd like a way out?
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR gasp]
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
Then you should go
get some results,
and try to win back my trust.
And it just happens
I've got the perfect job.
You'll love it.
It involves a quick jaunt
to the ends of the earth
to bring another "invincible"
Object crumbling down.
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA]
What?!
"The Graveyard of Junk
is a Mountain of Rare Metals."
[MILINDA] "Interception at the
Site of the Alaska Battle I."