[QWENTHUR]
Apparently, all of this began
in the first half of
the 21st century
when the United
Nations broke down
into a million little pieces.
That's why the world map
of today looks like,
as one cynical journalist
liked to describe it,
a shattered stained
glass window.
[QWENTHUR] There's always
some country on the verge
of inciting hostility
with their neighbor.
Inevitably, this constant
state of tension
could only create
a world riddled
with small-scale conflicts.
For example...
[VILLAGERS groaning]
[VILLAGERS scream]
[LITTLE GIRL sobs]
[QWENTHUR] They're forcing
our hand. Let's do it!
[OCEANIAN SOLDIERS gasp]
Please, just mistake them for
mortar rounds or something!
[OCEANIAN SOLDIERS scream]
Damn! Ah!
[OCEANIAN SOLDIERS groan]
Let's hope they retreat
before they realize
there's only two of us!
[OCEANIAN SOLDIERS chattering]
[HAVIA]
Yes!
[OCEANIAN SOLDIER D]
Fall back!
[OCEANIAN SOLDIER E]
Where are they shooting from?!
[OCEANIAN SOLDIER F]
Retreat!
[OCEANIAN SOLDIER H]
Behind us!
We're surrounded!
[OCEANIAN SOLDIER H]
They're everywhere!
Come on! Why aren't
they retreating?
We had 'em on the run,
why are they stopping now?
'Cause they're pinned down
by that damn sniper!
He's cutting off
their escape route.
They've got no choice but to
fight back with all they've got!
[QWENTHUR]
Uh. Uh!
Damn it, this might be the
end of our fun and games.
[OHOHO] Little Miss Loutish
Legitimate Kingdom First Gen.
[MILINDA]
Standard.
Which is just another way
of saying outdated.
[QWENTHUR]
We gotta do something
before an enemy detachment
comes looking for us.
Can we rig up some explosives
to booby trap their path?
If we-- [grunts]
[QWENTHUR grunts]
Intelligence Union military.
We're Mechanized
Infantry Squad 4.
You are Legitimate
Kingdom, right?
[HAVIA]
Mm... Mm-hm.
Just sit tight. We've got
a powered suit unit.
They'll have things cleaned
up in less than five minutes.
Thanks for the save.
But... damn.
I'm only seeing this up
close for the first time.
The ugly side of war.
Even innocent women and
children, killed for no reason.
There's a sniper on
that other ridge.
He's who started
this engagement.
'Preciate the warning.
You boys can just
leave the rest to us.
[HAVIA]
Not all of it.
You get the village, we'll
take care of the sniper.
I'm not gonna be happy
unless I get to take a
couple o' cracks at him.
[door opens, closes]
[footsteps]
So, then, Mr. Seawax.
You claim to be a professional
photojournalist, do you?
[SEAWAX]
Hmph.
[FROLAYTIA] You are aware this
is an interrogation room,
and that your actions earned you
a well-deserved invitation here?
I don't have to say a thing
without my attorney present
but I'll do you a favor
and tell ya this.
You have violated
my human rights.
So I advise you to
uncuff me at once.
Are you so upset
about the sniping?
Don't tell me you're gonna
charge me with murder
just because I'm not
in the military.
[HAVIA growls]
Try not to beat
yourself up too much.
That girl who was killed
wasn't the same one we met.
How's that supposed to
make me feel better?
[SEAWAX] It's your job to pump
those tyrannical bastards
of the Oceanian forces
full of lead, right?
Well, you weren't doing your
job, so I took it upon myself.
You corrupt tax thief.
[SEAWAX]
Proof they're monsters.
How could the Oceanians do
that to such a young girl?
[FROLAYTIA]
They didn't.
Huh?
[FROLAYTIA] It was your bullet
that killed this little girl.
And that's not all.
Due to your thoughtless
adventuring,
a great massacre is
about to happen.
What do you mean?
[FROLAYTIA]
The Oceanian forces
have been eagerly waiting
for the media to arrive.
They want the cameras to capture
the massacre of their villagers.
That's ridiculous.
Why the hell would a country
plan to massacre its own people?
[FROLAYTIA] Because they
want to pin the slaughter
of their poor villagers on the
invading multinational forces.
Painting themselves as victims.
They want sympathy
for their cause.
Their sick goal is
to sway the opinion
of the international
community to support them.
You're wrong!
And how dare you
blame me for this?!
I'm a conscientious journalist!
[FROLAYTIA] You have a naïvely
distorted idea of reality!
It was the trigger on your
rifle that led to the defeat
of the Oceanian
extermination squad!
It all played out in front
of the media like they wanted!
What scheme do you think
those bastards will do next?
You've already given
them a leg up.
The next massacre is
bound to be enormous!
They'll wipe out a village
and call it collateral damage!
And I can promise
you that this time,
they'll use their
Object to do it!
It may be old. Just
a Half-Gen, in fact.
But that hardly matters
when it's turned on
flesh and blood humans!
This is not my fault, damn it!
I'm just a journalist!
All I wanted to do
was pursue the truth!
[FROLAYTIA]
The truth?! Listen!
I'm telling you!
This is the truth!
The lives of all those villagers
are worth less than nothing
to the dictator of this country!
A massacre to them
is no more than
a strategic political move!
And that's exactly why we were
trying to keep the media away
and bring all of this
to a conclusion
before they could pull the
trigger on their plans.
[SEAWAX whimpers]
[FROLAYTIA] But thanks
to your interference,
we are right back at square one.
Understand?
No, that's... You're wrong.
[FROLAYTIA] The estimated
body count worked out
by the Digital Simulation
Department is thirteen thousand.
Are you satisfied now that
you've got the truth?
Well, Mr. Conscientious
Journalist?
[SEAWAX cries]
I, um, just wanted
to say thanks.
Y'know, for letting
us observe that.
It won't happen again.
I understand.
So how much more time
do you think we've got
before the massacre begins?
Who knows?
But there's no doubt they're
gonna send their Object
after a village. That'll get
them the attention they want.
And that's precisely why
we gotta find their Object
before they do.
[FROLAYTIA]
But we're not.
We've got orders
from the higher-ups.
What?!
[FROLAYTIA] Our only chance is
to wait for the enemy Object
to give us a strip show
and shimmy out of its
concrete shelter.
They want to find out
which water storage plant
it's hiding in, and they're
observing via satellite now.
We can't risk blowing our golden
opportunity by tipping them off
with some clumsy
reconnaissance beforehand.
Wait, they're gonna risk
letting the massacre happen
just to get intel?
You know the carnage an
Object is capable of.
Thirteen thousand
dead, remember?
We're only looking to
confirm which storage plant
it comes out of. Trust me.
We'll stop them before
they get to the massacre.
I won't let them to
claim any more victims.
Not one more soul.
The Oceanians have to
realize we've got satellites
trained on them.
They'll be expecting--
[FROLAYTIA]
Look.
I would much rather send you
two to destroy their Object.
But we've already got our orders
and it's too late to
do anything else.
[ADJUTANT]
The Gatling Oh-Three-Three
is currently in
Stage 2 maintenance.
The pilot is now
72% revitalized.
Any word from the
Legitimate Kingdom?
[ADJUTANT]
Nothing so far.
[LENDY]
I see.
This ridiculous farce might drag
on longer than I'd expected.
[AYAMI]
Princess! Princess?
Milinda Brantini!
Oh. Yes, ma'am?
[AYAMI] I need you to
move the turret for me.
I gotta get at the
control box beneath it.
Sure.
So, there haven't been any
casualties reported yet, right?
There was a skirmish on
the front line last night.
But no one has
said anything about
any casualties on our side.
You do know you can check
the roster for yourself?
Yeah.
[AYAMI]
Well, the roster only shows
the names of those
who were killed.
I understand. I'll
look into it for ya.
[MILINDA]
You will? Thank you.
[AYAMI]
You're just looking to find out
if anyone was wounded, right?
Uh, yeah.
[MILINDA]
Please be okay.
[HAVIA]
Oh, c'mon.
We have to pick one of these and
just hope it's the right answer?
It's like a quiz.
Well at least we've
got it narrowed down.
Their Object is in one of these
plants. We have to find it.
[HAVIA] They managed to hide
something as huge as an Object.
Which means they must've
had a wide enough
path to get it there.
So, a water storage plant
connected to a major road.
Ah, that cut down
our options some.
But it looks like the higher-ups
already had the same idea.
They've been prioritizing
the destruction of plants
along major roads
this whole time.
So our only option is to
scout them out one-by-one?
[QWENTHUR]
So we reverse the search.
What?
There was only ever
one confirmed sighting
of the Half-Gen.
Two years ago,
when it was built.
After that, they hid it away
to never be seen again.
It vanished.
Here's the thing,
after they hid it,
couldn't they have just planted
trees around the water plant?
Good point.
Their forest growth project?
It was all genetically modified.
Two years is plenty of time
for those trees to fully grow.
And that would totally
erase any evidence
of where they've stored it.
So going by that logic,
the most likely spots
would be surrounded
by new-growth forests.
Leaving three candidates.
It's a good start, but we
need more information.
Then let's ask the
Princess what she knows.
An Elite is bound
to have more intel
than they dole out to us grunts.
[QWENTHUR] Uh, actually,
I lost my cell phone.
I dropped it in the
skirmish last night.
Wait. You haven't talked to her?
This whole time?
I didn't have anything
to tell her.
Ah! You idiot!
[QWENTHUR]
Why're you freaking out?
[sighs] You can use mine.
Just contact her right away.
Sure, but--
--[alarm blares]
--[BOTH gasp]
They're mobilizing!
Have they pinpointed
the Object's location?
We've pinpointed
the Object's location
to the Great Sandy Desert. Do
everything to bring it down.
And how did we authenticate
the exact hiding location
of the target?
The Satellite Team.
They were able to detect
the energy signature
of the Object's power
reactor activating.
After all this time waiting,
they're finally sending
their Object on the hunt.
It's strange. They've been so
careful hiding it up until now.
Yeah.
But they know we're looking,
so they can't hide a huge
energy reading forever.
As soon as it's
out in the open,
they've gotta know our
Objects are gonna attack.
And they can't win
that fight. So why?
Oh, crap. It's the
trial reactor!
And what is that?
When Objects are
being built,
it's standard practice to build
a trial reactor to test it out.
What if that's what they
actually fired up?
It would make for a
perfect diversion.
Aren't you overthinking this?
[QWENTHUR]
It'd be great if I am,
but... if what I'm
predicting is correct,
that would make the reading
in the Great Sandy a trap.
You mean the same way a cute
girl might try to lure you in
by flashin' you a little panty.
[QWENTHUR]
If we just roll up on it,
they might be planning to
detonate the trial reactor.
And that'll take us
out, Objects and all.
It's basically the same
as a 200 kiloton bomb.
[gasps] No way!
The Princess and the others
are already inbound!
Speed it up.
If we take too long,
the Princess is a goner.
[QWENTHUR]
I realize that.
[HAVIA] We know for a fact
that Jumbo Jugs was in here
earlier for a strategy meeting.
[QWENTHUR] Fingers crossed they
left some documents behind.
Anything at all that can help us
narrow down our
three candidates.
[SEAWAX]
I can help.
[HAVIA gasps]
Who's that?
Wait, that voice...
It's the photojournalist.
[SEAWAX]
The name's Seawax.
I overheard the strategy
meeting from here.
Up there!
The duct's connected to
the interrogation room.
[HAVIA] Wha-- Huh?! How
could they be so dumb
as to connect the interrogation
and conference rooms?
[QWENTHUR]
They mainly built this base
for Object maintenance, so I
doubt they put too much thought
into the possibility of
capturing prisoners.
I get the feeling they rushed
to put that interrogation room
together just for this.
That doesn't make
it any less stupid!
Crooked tax thieves.
[SEAWAX]
Listen.
You guys are trying to find the
Half-Gen's location, right?
Your commanding officers had
it narrowed down to two spots
and then decided which
one to focus on.
It was either gonna be the
Great Sandy or the Tanami.
[HAVIA]
The Tanami!
That's one of our
three candidates!
[QWENTHUR] Why did
they rule out the Tanami?
Because of the energy signal.
The reading from the Great
Sandy made it seem obvious.
They forgot all about
the Tanami once that hit.
It's exactly like you predicted.
This is bad.
Yeah.
If that's where it's hiding,
never mind the nearby villages.
This base is in danger.
And...
There's no doubt that
the Great Sandy's a trap.
Oh, crap, the Princess.
Let's call her back.
[QWENTHUR]
No.
She's acting under
direct orders now.
We can't ask her
to violate that.
Not based on such a vague hunch.
Then what do we do?
As usual, we've gotta
handle it on our own.
It's back into the
jaws of hell for us.
[SEAWAX]
Hey, take me with you!
What?!
Get real.
Like hell we're
helping you escape.
I just want to make amends.
All of this?
I caused it to happen, right?
Objects take all of
the attention in war.
Thanks to that, no one
hears about the tragedies
that occur in the field.
I came here because I found
that fact unforgivable.
But, the truth of it...
My idealism did nothing but
ruin the professional work
that your people
were doing here.
I tried to save people and
only made things worse.
I'm begging you!
Let me atone for what I've done!
You can use a rifle, right?
Just hang on and
we'll bring you one.
Last thing we need is
some excess baggage
that can't defend itself.
Of course.
Thank you.
Truly.
I'll be waiting.
And I'll go...
with you.
And I'll make it right.
[HAVIA]
So, you straight up lied to him.
[QWENTHUR]
If we brought that guy with us,
he'd try to die a glorious
death on the battlefield.
He pisses me off,
but that doesn't mean
I wanna watch the dude
die right in front of me.
Of course you don't, hero.
Now let's focus
on staying alive.
I don't wanna watch
us die, either.
[OHOHO] Did that gentleman
not join us on the mission?
What gentleman?
[OHOHO] The one who seemed to
know so much about Objects?
No clue.
[QWENTHUR] Check one, check two.
Conducting microphone test.
[LK SOLDIER A]
Who is that?
[LK SOLDIER B]
Is that to the whole army?
[HAVIA]
Okay, hope you can hear me.
Greetings, my fellow hardworking
Legitimate Kingdom soldiers!
I hate to disappoint you guys,
but the target you're going
after is most likely a dummy!
The real thing's in
the Tanami Desert.
That reading from
the Great Sandy?
That's most likely a trial
reactor and not the Object.
He's okay.
[QWENTHUR]
Not only that.
There's a good chance they're
luring you into a massive trap.
They might be planning to
detonate the trial reactor.
That explosion would
be more than enough
to take out both Objects.
Don't let them fool you.
There's a chance this
is an enemy ploy.
[HAVIA]
Nobody's responding.
[QWENTHUR]
Damn it.
[OHOHO] I'm hoping you have
some kind of concrete evidence
to back up that story. [laughs]
It's G Cup!
No evidence.
There wasn't time to verify it.
We had a secondary source,
but their reliability was
a bit too questionable.
[OHOHO]
Then why should we--
And that's why I'm suggesting we
strike at both of the targets.
We know one of
them's the real deal,
and the other one's the dummy.
We've got nothin' to lose
if we destroy 'em both.
Princess.
Huh?
[QWENTHUR]
I'm willing to bet my life
that the Great Sandy is
nothing more than a trap.
So try to keep some distance.
Take it out with
long-range artillery fire.
I've got no doubt
that you can do it.
[OHOHO laughs]
I'm a tad insulted that
you wouldn't trust
me with that task.
Your main guns are serial swift
beam gatling guns, aren't they?
You'd crush it in
close-quarter combat,
but you know you don't
have the precision
for a long range
target like this.
Just let the Princess have
her turn in the spotlight.
I'll do everything I can.
[HAVIA] There's your
confidence boost, Princess.
I can practically feel your
gutsy energy out here.
Like we said, we think
the real Object's
stationed in the
Tanami Desert.
And we're on our way to check.
If we're right on this,
will you back us up?
[FROLAYTIA]
Hey, hold on a second.
I'd like to know who the
hell gave you the order
to head to the Tanami Desert.
[HAVIA] Uh-oh, sounds
like a court martial.
How 'bout we make a bet?
If the Great Sandy turns
out to be the real target,
you can toss us in the brig.
But if it's actually the Tanami,
I'd like the beautiful lady
to stomp all over me
with her soft, supple soles.
[QWENTHUR]
While I would like free range
to take advantage of the
beautiful lady's armpits.
[FROLAYTIA] Quit making
a mockery of this war
by trying to turn it into a
wager for your weird fetishes!
So I guess that means you
don't wanna hear the rest?
I didn't even mention your
nostrils or earholes.
I have no intention of
placing these bets,
so you'll have to
screw yourselves.
[HAVIA]
Right. But practically speaking,
you might wanna start groveling
just in case we destroy
the enemy Object on our own.
Who knows, we could just become
your superiors, Miss Frolaytia.
I don't know about that, Havia.
Let's be realistic here,
we are disobeying
the military's orders.
There's a good chance
we might forfeit
all of our past accomplishments.
You idiots!
You've proven yourselves
too valuable!
I can't just sit back and let
you get yourselves killed!
[FROLAYTIA]
It may be a Half-Gen.
But it's still an Object.
At least wait for us to send one
of our Objects to back you up.
[QWENTHUR]
Well.
We're already on the move.
If we stop to wait, the enemy
Object might take action.
And then it's:
"hey, we got fooled and the
villagers got massacred."
Not a very good punchline.
Unless you think the
entire allied forces
losing face is funny.
Throw in a demotion
for yourself, too.
We're doing this on
our own initiative,
so you can lay the
responsibility on us
for whatever happens.
[FROLAYTIA]
Are you serious?! I can't just--
Take advantage of
her armpits, huh?
[QWENTHUR] That's not as weird
as the soles of her feet.
[FLIDE] The finish on
these is quite impressive.
How long until they're
ready to ship?
[RESEARCHER A] Six months,
if everything goes well.
We have plans in place
for three large wars
in the next year alone.
Put a rush on it.
There's a call from
the Oceanian front, sir.
It's still too early for
the operation to be over.
[inaudible]
[FLIDE]
Qwenthur and Havia?
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR] "The War of
the Ant and the Grasshopper."
[MILINDA] "The Invasion of the
Oceanian Military State III".