[TV CREW A] So one squad's
heading to the radar site
to upload the sabotage program,
while the other attempts
to hack the UAV signals.
This operation hinges
on two units?
There's a third.
The Baby Magnum has completed
the floatation parts exchange,
and is moving to Point Three.
[TV CREW A] I see. In your
professional opinion,
when will the Object
showdown begin?
[FROLAYTIA]
Wars are unscripted chaos.
There's no way to be
completely certain.
[MONICA]
Oh, man! This really sucks!
There's no green room,
and no one here to
help with my make-up!
Hey! The war isn't going to
start for a while yet, right?
Don't you have any snacks
to help me stay perky?
[YOUNG SOLDIER A]
Here you go.
[MONICA]
Uh...
Ah! I hate it! I hate it!
I hate this stupid place!
I despise this military theme!
That sleazy manager!
Telling me I need to
differentiate myself,
how it's going to make
me more marketable!
But that's not the
only reason I agreed.
When he suggested this,
I said okay,
even though it didn't
interest me at all.
I came here for Qwenthur,
but that know-it-all is
nowhere to be found!
How am I gonna rub his nose
in my great comeback,
if I can't find him?!
Is that stupid smarty-pants
Qwenthur trying to hide from me?
[FROLAYTIA]
Huh...?
[gasps] Qwenthur.
You aren't hurt?
All thanks to this thing.
Charles wasn't so lucky.
What about Nutsray?
[QWENTHUR]
He disappeared.
He was... I saw his smirk.
[CHARLOTTE]
Traitor.
Or he's a spy.
Nutsray destoryed the PC
with the sabatoge progam.
Now that we can't upload the
sabotage program to the UAVs,
we can't continue the operation.
We need to contact HQ
and the unit headed to
Point Two immediately.
They have to know.
[CHARLOTTE]
Unfortunately, my comm unit
is sending out sparks right now.
[QWENTHUR] Perfect.
Without piggybacking
on your unit,
my comms don't have the range.
As things stand, we have
no way to communicate.
[CHARLOTTE]
That's not our only concern.
A UAV will have heard the
gunshots and must be on its way.
Hold on. We can't
let Nutsray escape.
He left footprints.
[CHARLOTTE] There's no
time to track our prey.
We can't allow ourselves
to be captured or killed.
That traitor has to be reported.
How exactly do you propose
we evade the enemy UAV?
Don't worry about it.
I've found a route that the UAV
won't be able to follow us.
Uh!
[QWENTHUR]
The entrance to the mine shafts?
[CHARLOTTE]
The UAV requires regular updates
to its flight plan.
That's the one place
that it can't go.
This just went from
bad to worse!
Damn it! How did the bloody
Wing Balancer end up
practically sitting
right on top of us?
Well, the Baby Magnum's
to our rear.
It's time for them to face off!
That's bad!
The Faith Organization's Object
is supposed to be in a standoff
with Indigo Plasma, our
plan was relying on it!
Maybe something happened,
and our friends have already
started retreating back to base.
What if they saw this operation
failing, and decided to book it?
[HAVIA]
Failing?! Qwenthur, you idiot.
Did you totally screw this up?
What are we gonna do now?
Hightail it! That's
a hostile Object!
That leviathan has
us so outgunned!
There's no way in hell we
could hope to take it on!
This is no time to panic!
[COOKMAN groaning]
Calm down. Let's think about it.
We can tie a white
handkerchief to the muzzle
of one of our rifles,
but I doubt the enemy
will give us a pass!
You're right. Sorry.
I just... I'm good now.
All right.
[HAVIA]
What a damn mess.
Giving pep talks to my
squad-mates before they crack?
Not part of my job description!
Hang on, I just
remembered something.
If it's where your
ex-girlfriend's birthmark is,
I'm not interested.
Something I overheard
back at base.
The analysts were saying
the Wing Balancer
might have bridge-making
equipment built into its design.
[WESTY]
You mean that monster
can just build any
bridges it needs?
[COOKMAN]
That's right.
And if the Wing Balancer is
going after the Baby Magnum,
which is right behind us, it'll
have to cross these cliffs.
When it does, it'll use
its bridging equipment.
Then we sabotage it
while it's distracted,
and send it plummeting to
the bottom of the gorge.
[MYONRI] We're actually
planning to fight it?
There's nowhere to run.
We might as well make a stand.
[WESTY]
What good are these peashooters
against a behemoth like that?
Anti-tank missiles are like
spit wads to an Object!
[HAVIA]
While it's busy extending
its bridge-building equipment,
it should be up on its
tippy-toes, right?
[MYONRI] So, we have to wait
until it's off-balance,
then we'll swat it down
with a focused barrage.
[COOKMAN]
It's focused on our Object,
not a bunch of ground troops.
So now's our chance.
Once it realizes we're
a threat, it's game over.
[COOKMAN] Keep the bastard's
center of gravity in mind!
On my mark, we all
fire together!
[WESTY gasps]
Big surprise.
Doesn't matter who
they team me up with,
I end up fighting for my life!
Here we go!
[COOKMAN]
It can fly?!
[HAVIA screams]
[MYONRI screaming]
[COOKMAN, WESTY screaming]
Cookman!
Westy!
You okay?
You think you can move?
Myonri!
[whimpers]
We have to help them.
Westy and Cookman.
[MYONRI]
We have to hurry....
They need our help...
Have to rescue them...
[MYONRI gasping]
Listen, Myonri.
The others, they're--
I saw what happened.
They're all gone.
But we should at least go
recover their dog-tags.
It's not possible.
I'm telling you.
Now, we can't spend any
more time on the dead.
We're surviving, the two of us.
You're delusional if you
think we'll survive this!
Even if we escaped
into the mine shafts,
those are Faith
Organization facilities!
That's right.
It might stink,
but it's a hundred times better
than fighting an Object!
And it won't be as cold.
[OPERATOR A]
Incoming Satellite data!
Energy reading detected at
peninsula Point B One Seven.
It's assumed to be an Object.
Didn't expect the Wing Balancer
to make the first move.
Did you hear that?
They're confident. But why?
[FROLAYTIA]
Since Baby Magnum's a First Gen,
they might not be
taking us seriously.
And our plan?
Nothing changes. You
stay alert out there.
And if the Wing Balancer
suddenly shows up,
I suggest you try
shooting first.
[MILINDA]
Received.
[HAVIA]
This is strange.
[MYONRI] There isn't a single
soldier on guard duty.
[HAVIA] And there weren't
any security cameras
covering the entrance.
[MYONRI] This is a military
coal facility, isn't it?
[HAVIA]
Yeah. It's supposed to be.
[MYONRI]
How strange.
These are all written in the
Legitimate Kingdom's language.
[HAVIA] "Thank you
for the clean water"?
Why even have these books?
Are they trying to
learn our language?
[HAVIA]
Then it must be a facility
where they train their spies.
You can't be serious.
Yeah, right?
The work is too sloppy.
This is our country...
digging a well?
[MYONRI] It must've been built
with the money donated
by the people working here.
There's even a detailed account
of the amounts donated!
Okay. I think this isn't
just a coal mine.
If anything, this may belong
to an anti-war group.
That means our
intel was way off.
[HAVIA grunts]
But what happened? Where
did everything go wrong?
[QWENTHUR] We've been going
down for quite a while now.
[CHARLOTTE] We've probably
descended 200 meters or so.
Actually hearing how
far we've gone
just made me feel a thousand
times more exhausted than I was.
[CHARLOTTE] Coal mines go
down roughly a kilometer.
Though in certain instances
they're over four klicks deep.
This area is still
just the entryway.
[clattering]
[gasps]
[QWENTHUR]
A first aid kit?
[grunts] Please,
you have to stop!
[CHARLOTTE]
Move it!
[QWENTHUR screams, groans]
[GIRL A screams]
Care to explain yourself?
[exhales] There's no way that
girl was military personnel.
More likely, she was a civvie
pressed into service.
She wasn't in uniform.
She was also carrying a first
aid kit instead of a rifle.
And what makes you so sure
she wasn't carrying
a weapon inside it?
And besides,
she must've run off to report
our presence to the others.
That means we'll be swarmed
by the enemy any moment now.
Or was it something else?
This is a modern war, you know.
There's no room for a
misguided sense of chivalry
when it comes to
female combatants.
If you don't wanna
draw attention,
shooting guns and
piling up bodies
seems a bit counterproductive,
don'tcha think?
Is that your official stance?
In that case, you should
have taken her prisoner
instead of fumbling with me.
Just because you
let a civilian go
doesn't mean the enemy
will return the favor
if they get their hands on you.
[QWENTHUR]
I know. I apologize.
[CHARLOTTE]
For emergencies,
consider it a loaner
on my authority.
Much appreciated.
[CHARLOTTE] It's not to
make you a combat asset.
It's for suicide.
[QWENTHUR]
Oh.
[CHARLOTTE] This new risk
has arisen as a result
of your decision to let
that woman escape.
Choices have consequences.
You may learn that
lesson the hard way.
[QWENTHUR] Don't you think
it's a little strange?
[CHARLOTTE]
What is?
[QWENTHUR] The entire point
of our mission was to reduce
the supply of fuel
to enemy Objects.
And for this purpose,
there are three Objects
deployed between both sides.
[CHARLOTTE]
That's correct.
And if Nutsray is a
Faith Organization spy,
I find it strange that he blew
his cover the way he did,
without finishing us off.
Expending an operative
who was so deeply entrenched
seems rather foolish.
What makes this mine so
important that it's worth
the loss of such a
long term investment?
[CHARLOTTE] These aren't
meant for people to ride.
Must have been used to transport
the coal they were mining.
No. Something tells me
they weren't mining coal.
Why's that?
Can you see this clear granule
poking out of the rock?
[CHARLOTTE]
So what is it?
[QWENTHUR] Basically,
it's a lump of carbon.
Which is more commonly
referred to as a dia--
[yelps]
[CHARLOTTE gasps]
[HAVIA]
Yo! Qwenthur.
What the hell are you
doing down here?
Where'd you come from?
[HAVIA]
Cookman and Westy are dead.
We got torn to ribbons
because you screwed up!
Give me an answer,
and if I like it,
I won't shoot you
anywhere vital!
[CHARLOTTE]
It was Nutsray.
We had a Faith Organization spy.
He killed Charles
before turning on us.
I take partial responsibility
for not seeing
through his cover.
It's a mistake to unilaterally
take things out on Qwenthur.
You expect us to
kiss and make up
just cause you said
so, Four-eyes?
If you insist on this course of
action, you leave me no choice.
Oversight is my duty.
Factors that violate
military regulations
and cause the operation
to deteriorate.
I'm sworn to eliminate
with extreme prejudice.
My mistake. I needed
an opening to back down.
Sorry you had to
force it to happen.
You weren't really serious
about shooting him, anyway.
[HAVIA]
Heh.
[QWENTHUR sighs]
[MYONRI]
So what?
Are the four of us
the only survivors?
[HAVIA] If you count the
traitor, that makes five.
And I imagine it's turning
into a quagmire up top.
The Princess and
the Wing Balancer.
Rumor is, they go head to head,
she hasn't got a chance.
It's time for a war
council, Qwenthur.
You better spill all
the intel you've got.
So, um.
What is that thing you're
holding there, Mister Qwenthur?
What? Oh, this?
Just raw diamonds.
Found you!
Preemptive strike!
I need to anticipate
where it'll land.
No way.
Whoa, pump the brakes, dude!
So what does that mean?!
This place was never a
military coal facility,
cause they were too
busy mining diamonds?
[QWENTHUR]
The Legitimate Kingdom military
must've found out
the truth about
what they were
really mining here,
and decided to attack
the Kamchatka Peninsula.
And they sent us out to fight
this stupid war for resources.
Few places produce diamonds.
Oceania, Africa, and South
America are the leaders.
However, if a completely
new supply source
were suddenly discovered,
it would massively upset
the balance of the worldwide
diamond market.
It's worth trillions.
The major powers would do
anything to control it.
To top it all off, the people
who were working here
aren't with the
Faith Organization,
but an anti-war group making
money intending to donate it
to the poor in the
Legitimate Kingdom.
Which totally makes us the
bad guys this time around.
That means the Wing Balancer
and its pilot...
They're fighting
to uphold justice.
Think about it.
It's protecting
pacifist civilians
from the Legitimate
Kingdom's military.
Who in this case,
are basically bandits
trying to steal the diamonds.
Okay. I quit.
I didn't come here to be
a minion of evil, y'know.
Wait! Don't go!
[HAVIA]
What's up?
Don't you think something
strange is going on?
If the enemy wanted to
keep this mine safe,
why would they wait
for our Object
right in the middle of it?
The collateral damage
would be incalculable!
[gasps]
Furthermore, they should've
predicted that our forces
would invade from our
nearby bases in Alaska.
The textbook thing to do would
be to draw a defensive line
in the Bering Sea.
Perhaps it's because
this semi-artificial,
sawtooth coastline
is a perfect match
to take advantage of the Wing
Balancer's superior mobility.
There's a more practical
reason, I think.
The people working in
this mine are a rare breed.
Even within the
Faith Organization.
They belong to an anti-war group
that wants to engage in
dialogue with other countries.
In the eyes of the
war-mongering higher-ups,
a group like this must be
a real thorn in their side.
[HAVIA]
Wait, you can't be serious!
These people are a nuisance.
Why not just eradicate
them entirely
by putting them in the middle
of two battling Objects?
If so, the diamond
intel was just bait.
They used it to pull the
Legitimate Kingdom military
in to do their dirty work.
That's a possibility.
Wait! Hold up guys!
This is still conjecture, right?
Do we have any proof that
what Myonri guessed
is actually happening?
The Faith Organization
is all about ideology.
And with that mindset,
they aren't very fond of
differing points of view.
I guess not.
Their High Command prefers to
keep fanning the flames of war.
That's bad news for those
against it, those who wish
to seek out peaceful
resolutions to conflicts.
That ideology is threatening
to the generals.
If those in command were
to take it upon themselves
to massacre the pacifists
and purge the dissenters,
the antiwar movement would
only gain sympathizers.
But it all changes
if the pacifists are killed by
a Legitimate Kingdom Object.
By the very people they were
offering an olive branch.
And if they were
destroyed by someone
they were trying to help,
such an atrocity would make
their populace boil with hatred.
[gasps] This is bad!
[HAVIA]
Whoa, hey.
I know the situation
sounds bad, but chill out!
Just shut up and run!
[HAVIA]
What the--?
Hey! Qwenthur!
What made Mister Qwenthur
suddenly freak out?
Let's follow!
[HAVIA] Hey, Qwenthur buddy!
Got time to explain?
It's the Princess versus
the Wing Balancer.
Word is she hasn't got
a chance of winning
a head-on battle, right?
But the Wing Balancer's victory
still hasn't been announced
by the Faith Organization!
Why do think that is?
Maybe the Princess is
working her butt off!
[QWENTHUR]
An Object's power is absolute.
In combat between two of them,
there's no room for miracles.
But what if the
enemy's objective
isn't to destroy
the Baby Magnum,
but to lure it to a target
location instead?
[HAVIA]
I smell what you're stepping in.
But what, specifically,
do you plan to do?
The way things are going, the
people working in this mine
will all be killed
in the ensuing chaos!
[QWENTHUR]
We continue the mission.
[MYONRI]
What?
[QWENTHUR]
We head for Point Two,
and upload the sabotage program
to the radar facility directly.
So then, we stick with
the original operation.
But the enemy forces
already know we're here!
[QWENTHUR] Doesn't matter,
we've gotta move it!
Unless, of course,
you'd prefer we bull rush
that 200,000 ton war machine.
Oh, come on, really?!
Why can't you make the
sensible call for once,
and just tell us it's
time to run away?
So that's how you
wanna play it.
[FROLAYTIA]
What's your gameplan?
There's no purpose in continuing
this game of tag.
I'm going to target
the mine instead.
Of course!
Even without defeating
the enemy Object,
if we capture the mine,
we win the battle, right?
[FROLAYTIA]
Classic strategem:
don't attack directly,
go after what they value.
[FROLAYTIA]
Be on the lookout, Princess.
The enemy must've anticipated
that we'd eventually
attack the mine.
As soon as I've locked
onto the coal mine,
the enemy Object should
land to intercept me.
Given equal footing...
[QWENTHUR] Please don't
charge in blindly, Princess!
I know you can be
surprisingly short-tempered.
Just don't let yourself
be provoked this time!
[MYONRI screams]
[HAVIA screams]
[QWENTHUR screams]
[CHARLOTTE gasps]
A freakin' powered suit?
[HAVIA]
Damn it! What the hell is that?!
It's not a worker.
That much is certain.
[QWENTHUR]
I know it's you, you coward.
I can practically
feel you smirking
behind all that steel armor,
you arrogant traitor.
[QWENTHUR groaning]
Stop it!
[HAVIA]
Qwenthur!
Forget it, Havia!
That gun...
It isn't strong enough to punch
through his armored plating!
You'd only get killed
by all the ricochets!
But, dude...
Don't shoot him, Havia!
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA] "The Coal Mine
Littered with Stacks of Money".
[MILINDA] "The Kamchatka
Peninsula Nighttime Blitz III."