[QWENTHUR] Everything in this
life has a beginning and an end.
But those stories that say
"they lived happily ever after"
are misleading, at best.
The story doesn't
really end there.
In reality, those
great victories
are bogged down
in the aftermath.
Repairing damaged bunkers
is one of those things.
Then there are the delicate
political negotiations
with hostile nations
to take into account.
This was supposed to be a
routine mission like any other.
But, life is no fairy tale.
This time around,
we would be held accountable
for every action we've taken
leading to this point, and we
would pay for them dearly.
As for "the Prince
and the Princess
lived happily ever after" trope,
somewhere along the way we lost
that innocent part of ourselves
that believed the fairy
tale ending was real.
[QWENTHUR]
Wow.
It's incredible!
Flowers as far as
the eye can see.
You hear about it,
but this is the first time
I've seen the real thing!
Idyllic splendor.
As long as you take the two
Objects ruining the scenery
out of the equation.
Cause with them here, it kinda
ruins the mood for a picnic.
[QWENTHUR] This meeting's
just to exchange the hostage.
It should go smoothly.
So really, Objects
just come out here
to pose and posture
in front of each other.
It's more formality
than anything else.
[HAVIA]
Yeah.
[QWENTHUR]
If that's true,
there's no reason to
be nervous, right?
[HAVIA exhales]
I guess not.
But ever since I started
pal-ing around with you,
I've picked up the bad habit of
being suspicious of everything.
Right back atcha, tough guy.
[QWENTHUR]
Did you say hostage exchange?!
[FROLAYTIA] Yup. We meet
with the Intelligence Union
to trade a hostage
we took prisoner.
[exhales] For fitting
compensation, of course.
We'll mainly be trading
for technological intel.
Our human bargaining chip's
a VIP named Guru Klondike.
[grunts]
[QWENTHUR]
Guru?
[HAVIA]
I've heard of the guy.
He's this old monk dude
who preaches a platform
based on nonviolent
civil disobedience.
[FROLAYTIA]
That's correct. [grunts]
He started off as
a prominent figure
in the Faith Organization.
Now he's become
quite the player
on the stage of
international politics.
His influence now transcends
traditional borders,
and he has vocal supporters in
all four of the great powers.
[QWENTHUR groaning]
The guru's teachings are more
ideological than religious.
It's closer to
philosophy, actually.
And because of that, he was
kind of the "odd man out"
back home in the
Faith Organization.
Yeah. That makes sense.
Because he liked to
rock the boat back home,
the Faith Organization is in
no hurry to take him back.
But like I said, he's
internationally popular,
so they put up the
pretense of caring.
She's right. Taking
the guru is good PR,
but then he starts
spreading certain ideas so
the government panics
and detains him.
But an execution creates
an international incident,
so they just wanna drop him
off with another country
as soon as they possibly can.
[FROLAYTIA]
Ad infinitum,
sometimes it's months
sometimes it's years.
But the guru gets
passed back and forth
between the four great powers.
You make the whole thing
sound like a card game.
It is! The game's
called Old Maid.
Pretty much.
Now it's the Intelligence
Unions turn
to take the "old maid"
off our hands.
[QWENTHUR]
Why would they do that?
[FROLAYTIA]
Who knows?
But hey, with the intel they're
providing as compensation,
you won't hear us complaining
but you can bet your butts
we're making this exchange.
Considering the delicate
nature of this,
the Faith Organization will
have an Object of their own
some distance away. Acting
as overseer of the trade.
[FROLAYTIA] And with three
of the great powers gathered,
the Capital Enterprise was
sick of feeling left out,
so they sent an Object to
watch things unfold as well.
[HAVIA]
One old religious geezer
can bring representatives from
all four great powers, huh?
That sounds bad.
Objects from all four
powers gathered together
sounds really bad.
[FROLAYTIA] If we carry
this out textbook smooth,
there's fundamentally
no danger.
You boys just keep your
heads on your shoulders,
and carry on with
your mission, okay?
[BOTH sigh]
[QWENTHUR exhales]
[QWENTHUR]
Hm...
[QWENTHUR] Just keep my
head on my shoulders, huh?
[MILINDA]
What are you up to?
[gasps]
Hi! I'm using CVD to treat
the replacement mirrors
for your secondary guns'
targeting system.
CVD?
[QWENTHUR]
Yup.
[QWENTHUR] Specifically, the
ones nearest your main guns.
They regularly have to withstand
massive temperature
and pressure changes
because of their proximity.
And so, those particular mirrors
have to be switched out
after pretty much
every battle you fight.
Check it out,
it's about to start.
CVD means chemical
vapor deposition.
As you can see, it's spraying
the powder used for the coating.
[MILINDA gasps]
Then turns it into plasma,
glazing the surface.
It can turn pretty much anything
into a high quality mirror.
Oh, wow
Let me see that.
[QWENTHUR]
It's for you.
[MILINDA sighs]
My gift.
The mirror on the compact
you take into the cockpit.
I remember you saying it broke.
I hope this'll do the job
until your replacement comes.
You mean...?
Is this a present?
[QWENTHUR] I just made it
from stuff I had on hand.
So it's no big deal.
It's wonderful. Thank you.
[QWENTHUR]
Yeah?
It was totally worth it
to hear you say that.
[AYAMI]
Come on, it's almost that time!
Baby Magnum needs to
get ready to mobilize!
[gasps]
Ciao! Thanks again!
Sure thing.
All right. That's our
cue, guru. Shall we?
[KLONDIKE] What a shame it is
to part ways, dear Frolaytia.
You took hold of my mic
with such a passionate hand.
Until I nearly exploded from the
intensity of your performance!
For as long as I live,
I'll never forget the
sweet music we shared.
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA]
Huh?!
Guru, please!
[QWENTHUR] Look, I know
you like to push the limits
but seriously, this guy?!
[HAVIA] When you've got two
beefcakes standing right here!
Enough!
I was assigned to keep
an eye on the guru
while he was at
karaoke last night!
It was an evening
aflame with passion.
I'ma puke
I guess babysitting old dudes
is part of an officer's duty.
Getting promoted isn't
all it's cracked up to be.
Excuse me, young man.
Are you that Qwenthur Barbotage
fellow I've heard about?
Uh. Yes, guru. That's me.
[KLONDIKE laughs]
Hm...
I had heard there was a hero,
an ordinary man slaying giants.
Nice to put a face
to the legend.
[QWENTHUR] I don't know
if I'd call us heroes,
certainly not legends.
That much is true.
But if you really wanted
to be a perfect hero,
you would have found
a way to save the lives
of the other Elite pilots whose
Objects you destroyed.
Those other Elite pilots
were trying to kill us.
It's easy to make
moral judgments
when you're not busy
trying to survive.
I'd hoped you weren't
one of those people
who think nothing of
sacrificing one life,
if that sacrifice can save the
lives of tens of thousands more.
[QWENTHUR]
But that's not...
[HAVIA]
Anyone can do that math, Gramps.
Yes, Anyone indeed.
But don't you think
it's precisely that kind of
subtraction that perpetuates
our species' endless cycle of
misery and self-destruction?
Will the two of you
learn what it takes
to be true heroes one day?
Please, sir.
[KLONDIKE] Because I look
forward to seeing that.
A message to the pilot of the
Legitimate Kingdom Object.
From this point forward, we will
be running in Red Alert mode.
If you make any
suspicious moves,
we won't hesitate to open fire.
You've been warned.
To the Intelligence
Union Object pilot.
Warning acknowledged.
We'll enter into Red Alert
with the same conditions.
[OHOHO]
It's you again, isn't it?
They've got you on
guard duty? Ah, ha, ha.
[MILINDA]
I could say the same,
since we captured
your Object, and all.
You're lucky they didn't kick
you out for incompetence.
So if you're here,
does that mean that clever
blonde gentleman came along?
Yes, in fact he gave me
a present earlier today.
[OHOHO]
A present?
[MILINDA]
A handmade accessory.
Well isn't that nice?
Ah, ha, ha.
[MILINDA]
Yes. It was. Ah, ha, ha!
[OHOHO gasps] Was that supposed
to be an imitation of me?!
[MILINDA]
All I did was laugh. [laughs]
Again with these two.
Sounds like they're at it again,
"clever blonde gentleman."
The new Rush unit.
It looks pretty much the same.
But I find it doubtful they'd
bring the exact same model
captured by us to the face-off.
There must be some
kind of modification...
[HAVIA]
Yo, gentleman!
Qwenthur!
Uh. What is it?
[OHOHO]
In a different setting,
I'd do the world a favor
and blast you to pieces.
[MILINDA]
I'd like to see you try.
[OHOHO] Oh. Big talk from
someone in an antique!
Whoa, slow down
there, Princess.
What do you think you're doing?!
[MILINDA]
She tried to provoke me,
and I accepted her challenge.
Nothing more, nothing less.
Well that's not gonna work.
This is supposed to be a
peaceful mission, remember?
[MILINDA]
It is what it is.
But if you insist, I'm willing
to let it go this time.
Uh. You there?
Princess, come in!
Milinda! What's wrong?!
[HAVIA]
Mm-mm?
Miss Frolaytia come in!
I had contact with the Princess
but the signal was
suddenly cut off.
[FROLAYTIA]
We're confirming the same.
It's not just radio contact.
All telemetry data has stopped
transmitting as well.
A malfunction?
Something tells me
it isn't that simple.
We've found the reason.
Someone's deliberately
interfering with
the symbiotic link
between the Princess
and the Baby Magnum.
Hence the communication
breakdown.
[HAVIA]
Interfering? But who?!
We're not sure.
The Princess should be digging
through various subroutines
to get around the problem.
But we have no idea what's
going on inside the cockpit.
What we do know, however,
is the source of the signal is a
quantum key-enabled radio tower
in a resort town roughly
15 klicks southwest.
And that's all.
For the moment,
there's no real damage
beyond the obstructed
communications.
But you never know, I want
this dealt with ASAP.
And if we start carelessly
moving troops around
during the exchange,
we may stir up trouble,
which we don't need.
So with that in mind...
I understand.
We're on our way now.
[FROLAYTIA]
Thank you.
Let's go, Havia.
Whoa! Hang on!
How dare you casually volunteer
me for this stinkin' mess!
What's gonna happen if you and
I run into some massive army?!
[QWENTHUR] The exchange
meeting goes up in smoke,
and we probably
end up as corpses.
Or somethin' like that.
That sounds great!
I hope you're not
doing this just cause
of the Guru's little
hero pep-talk!
Okay hero, maybe
you can clear up
some confusion for
me on the drive.
Don't Object comm systems use
eighth gen encryption
with quantum keys?
So, how is it possible for
someone to interfere with that?
I've been trying to figure that
out for myself, and I can't.
All I know is that I've got
a bad feeling about this.
[beeping]
This is Qwenthur.
We'll be arriving at the
target location shortly.
[CHARLOTTE] It's been
a long time, hasn't it?
I'm pleased to hear
you're alive and well.
Uh?
[CHARLOTTE]
Charlotte Zoom speaking.
That's the scary
black uniform lady!
They're the worst!!
[CHARLOTTE]
Hey!
She was the oversight lady
who held me at gunpoint
back in Kamchatka.
Oversight, huh? Those
people creep me out.
[QWENTHUR]
Look, uh I really appreciate you
calling me but unfortunately,
I'm in the middle of
a mission right now.
[CHARLOTTE] I'm well aware.
That is the reason I called you.
I heard that the 37th Mechanized
Maintenance Battalion
was trying to quietly
deal with a cyber-attack
against the Baby Magnum.
There's also the possibility
this sabotage might involve
former Councilor Flide.
I believe the two
of you already met.
[gasps]
Oh, yeah, I remember
hearing about his escape
before our fight
with City Slicker.
But if the story ended there,
I doubt she'd be calling us.
There's more.
[CHARLOTTE]
Naturally.
I've been working a particular
case for some time now.
It has no direct correlation
to either of you gentlemen,
though I thought it
might interest you.
Because Flide is
definitely a part of it.
So then I dug deeper.
And I discovered there
was some sort of nefarious
plan being devised.
[CHARLOTTE]  From that point on,
I began tracking his movements.
And recently learned that he
illegally entered the region
where your operation's
being held.
Damn it! This is the worst!
Flide's the worst? Explain.
[CHARLOTTE]
It's a big problem.
Flide was in charge of the
Elite training facility.
That means he had access
to top-secret data
on Milinda Brantini
and the Baby Magnum.
If a guy like that were to try
hacking the Baby Magnum,
he'd already have access
codes and overrides.
[gasps]
[QWENTHUR]
But what's his end-game on this?
What's this case of yours about?
I'm sorry, but you don't
have the clearance.
There is some intel
I can divulge.
We believe his goal is
to take over an Object,
sabotage the hostage exchange,
and trigger the worst
imaginable scenario.
[gasps]
This hostage exchange is
already under scrutiny.
The four great powers have
amassed to point their Objects
at one another. It's the
geo-political equivalent
of a powder keg stacked
inside an oil refinery.
[QWENTHUR]
Strike a single match,
and there's no telling
what might happen!
Pedal down!
[CHARLOTTE]
I'm counting on you.
Aren't you going to tell
them about the List?
That's the nice thing to do.
Nobody asked you.
[FLIDE]
The plan is now safely underway.
It'll all be over in a few
minutes or more accurately,
that's when it will all begin.
You helped me when
I was penniless.
Thank you, my friends.
I'll never be able to pay
back your generosity,
but your cooperation
was appreciated.
[MALE VOICE A] Cooperation?
More like extortion.
I certainly hope you realize
the caliber of enemies
you've made today.
[FLIDE] I do, and I take
full responsibility.
[exhales]
[FLIDE]
Let them come.
What I've done should
safeguard the ideals
held by my confederates
of the List.
After they've experienced
this quagmire war we're
about to spark off,
where the four great powers
break into a free-for-all.
Then the world will have
a newfound appreciation.
They'll miss the old days.
Where Object count determined
a conflict's outcome
without the need to
engage in combat.
I understand their hesitance,
though, having been enthralled
by the prospect myself.
Nothing can be done to
hold back true hatred.
The survivors in war learn
that the game is rigged.
[FROLAYTIA]
Roger that, sir.
We will complete the hostage
exchange immediately.
[WOMAN A]
We're going through with it?
But we still haven't taken
control of the signal source.
[FROLAYTIA]
The brass made the call, morons.
Guru, shall we go?
Let's boogie.
[BOTH grunts]
Freeze, scumbag!
Well, well, if it isn't
my old friend Havia.
[HAVIA growls]
[QWENTHUR]
Uh!
[FLIDE]
And Qwenthur, too. Welcome.
I'm afraid you came too late.
[gasps]
[MILINDA gasps]
[FLIDE groaning]
[HAVIA grunts]
[QWENTHUR]
No! Damn it! What did you do?!
The fault lies with
you and your friend.
[QWENTHUR]
Uh!
[FLIDE] War is one of the
more primitive instincts
deeply rooted in
the human psyche.
That's exactly why we must
control it with rationality.
Wars controlled digitally via
the hard math of Objects.
The international
standard of raw power.
Those aren't real wars at all.
They're a safety system.
To keep the body count low.
To a world predicated on that
assumption, you two are poison.
The very worst kind of poison,
and that is all you'll
ever end up being.
Prepare yourself for a taste
of your own medicine,
and it's long overdue!
[MILINDA]
Huh?
I wonder what
that was all about.
[FROLAYTIA]
Baby Magnum! Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Thank goodness. I'll
send someone right over.
You just stay put for now.
That's an order.
Baby Magnum, acknowledged.
Is there some kind of issue?
[FROLAYTIA] Nothing much. Just
a little communications glitch.
Artillery strike requested
by the Major.
Arming systems.
I didn't call in a strike!
Milinda come in!
I want you to stand down!
Where's she aiming?
Both of you, get away
from the house right now!
There's Incoming!
What, incoming?!
Damn! C'mon let's move!
The key?!
I'd leave now if I were you.
The Baby Magnum already has
these coordinates locked in.
It's time to go, Havia!
He plans to incinerate himself
right along with all
this hacking equipment!
[gasps]
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR grunt]
[BOTH yelling]
[BOTH scream]
Milinda, cease fire!
Power down right now!
That's an order!
[MILINDA] Don't worry,
Frolaytia. Target destroyed.
Now it's time to eradicate
the enemy Object.
[FROLAYTIA]
Uh?
What sort of move do you think
the Legitimate Kingdom
forces are trying to pull?
[LENDY] Unknown.
Don't let them kill the guru.
You're free to return fire!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Even this paradise must
be baptized in flame.
[FROLAYTIA]
Get down!
Adjusting target coordinates.
Damn it!
[FROLAYTIA]
Notifying all units!
Battle has broken out between
the Rush and the Baby Magnum!
[HAVIA]
Is this for real?
[QWENTHUR]
We've gotta get back, Havia.
[HAVIA]
All right!
The Baby Magnum
went out of control?
[SLADDER]
It seems the hacker is dead.
And the Mirror of Truth
has been implemented.
[CHARLOTTE gasps]
An Elite perceptual
interference program.
Designed and developed
by the Intelligence Union.
It interferes with the process
of perception and thought.
It deliberately induces a state
of distorted perception
with a specific slant.
You bastard! How dare you?!
An example, there's the phrase
extend them every courtesy.
Other than its normal,
word for word meaning,
there's a slang usage which
means "to beat them to a pulp".
Right now, she's in a mode
where she interprets all
information as the latter.
And takes it in a
negative direction.
It's not just words.
Data, Visuals, too.
All incoming information
is converted by the interference
and translated negatively.
The key to undoing
the interference
was likely lost along
with Councilor Flide.
She can't be restored now.
The fuse has been lit
with the bomb, which is
the death of the guru.
The powder keg is sure
to go up in a big bang!
If you want to stop this,
you'll have no choice but to
destroy the Baby Magnum.
[SLADDER]
Mirror, Mirror, on the wall.
Who will bring about
Snow White's fall?
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA]
"A Requiem
for the Flowers Blooming
in the Field."
[MILINDA] "The Battle to
Destroy the Baby Magnum II."