C'mon!
Hurry up and detonate
the bombs already!
We're not lounging in a
pool with a bikini team!
I wanna go back to my mansion
filled with hot maids!
I'm with ya, Partner.
The fruits of our labor.
Time to unwrap those
gifts we left behind!
[BOTH chuckle]
It's fine.
Come on! We planted
enough explosives
to take out an entire
mountain range!
Ugh! What the hell is it gonna
take to sink that monster?!
Ahh! I'm ready to
chuck these bombs
and start swimming for home!
[gasps]
--[FROLAYTIA chuckles]
--[QWENTHUR] Miss Frolaytia!
Have you been out
here this entire time?
More importantly, where did you
manage to find that lifeboat?
And where the hell did
you get that cheese?
There's no way that's
standard rations!
Job well done, boys.
Go ahead and climb aboard;
your mission is complete.
That's it?
Did you eat all of that cheese?
Wait, did you say we're done?
We've gone over all this.
Your only objective was to
buy as much time as possible
for the Princess to make
her grand entrance.
As far as I'm concerned,
our role here was done
when you blew those
tanks to kingdom come.
And now we've passed
the baton to the Princess.
So, mission accomplished.
[BOTH gasp]
[FROLAYTIA] The rescue chopper
should be here any moment.
All that's left for us
to do is grab the rope,
get pulled up, and fly
back to the mainland.
[gasps]
[MILINDA gasps]
What the...?
Something's off.
[FROLAYTIA]
Climb into the boat already.
It'd be a sad state of
affairs if a shark ate you
after what you've been through.
[gasps]
If you're gonna pull us
up dressed like that,
I'm bound by the pervert's
code to wobble the raft
for an opportune view.
Huh?
[HAVIA gasps]
Why am I such a gentleman?
Guess I'll look the other way.
[HAVIA]
Fine, don't look!
I'll gladly go first!
[FROLAYTIA]
Hmph.
Too late.
You missed your chance.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[sighs]
[QWENTHUR]
Sorry, Princess.
We weren't much use this time.
[HAVIA]
Who cares, man?
I'm just amazed we survived a
second one of these missions.
This should make the top
brass reconsider things.
In the end, Alaska was a fluke.
Objects are still at
the top of the pyramid
when it comes to warfare.
Things should go back to being
more relaxed after this...
...for you two.
[QWENTHUR sighs]
[HAVIA] Somehow that makes
me feel both relieved
and, like, a disappointment.
Hey, hold on.
Something doesn't look
right with the Princess.
What's the problem?
It looks no different than
any other unpredictable,
giant war-machine battle.
No.
There is something off.
The Princess's tempo
of attack has dropped.
It's like she's passing
the opportunity to fire,
even when the Tri-Core's
in her sights.
Why would she do that?
Look!
That's why!
[grunts]
[gasps]
They're aiming at her guns?!
[QWENTHUR] It's gonna
be a drawn-out battle.
So their strategy is to
reduce her main firepower.
[HAVIA gasps]
[QWENTHUR] The only way
an Object can take down
another Object is to
penetrate its armor.
And that requires
multiple direct hits
to the same location.
Though they're equipped
with up to 100 guns,
the only ones powerful
enough to do that
are the few
classified as main guns.
[QWENTHUR] But due to
their power, the main guns
are the one thing that can't
be shielded with thick armor.
All it takes is
a few direct hits
or even just one
close-range strike.
That's enough to put them down.
[FROLAYTIA] Hitting those
main guns is no easy task,
but the enemy's
got the upper hand.
The Tri-Core's built
for naval warfare.
Not to mention it's
got the power reserves
to fire indiscriminately.
The Princess doesn't
stand a chance
if they succeed in taking
out all her main guns.
[HAVIA] She'll be
completely defenseless!
--Another!
--[QWENTHUR gasps]
[QWENTHUR grunts]
[HAVIA]
Don't even think about it.
I'm starting to develop
some kind of intuition
for how your mind works, but
there's no way that's possible.
At this rate, the Baby
Magnum is gonna get sunk.
We've gotta do something
to help the Princess
before it's too late.
[HAVIA growls]
We've already done everything
we could, remember?!
We snuck onboard,
blew up those giant tanks,
and that monster
couldn't have cared less!
We hit the weakest
spot we could find,
so where do you wanna
put the bombs this time?!
We've gotta try, otherwise
the Princess is dead!
[gasps]
And did you somehow forget
about what happened in Alaska?
If we lose our Object,
every troop in those
bases are dead as well!
Just remember--
Objects aren't invincible.
If something is made by a man,
then that means it can
be destroyed by a man!
All right...
What's your plan then?
We can't approach on
this slowpoke chopper.
They'd shoot us down
in no time at all!
I know.
Who said anything
about the chopper?
[HAVIA gasps]
[HAVIA]
Don't be an idiot!
Damn it!
What the hell does that
maniac think he's doing?
[HAVIA] Are you trying
to get us killed with you?!
[PILOT 5A]
What's the call, ma'am?
Do we pick him up again?
No, remain airborne!
[QWENTHUR]
Now, then...
All I've gotta do is find an
actual weakness this time.
But where do I find that
in a super-massive Object
with three power reactors?
It'd sure be a lot simpler if
there was some kind of defect.
--[HAVIA] Don't be stupid!
--[groans]
[HAVIA]
You're not gonna find a defect!
We looked everywhere earlier,
and it was a waste of time!
That monster was designed for
naval warfare and nothing else.
Its only damn
weakness is dry land!
I realize that!
But, still-- [gasps]
It's specifically designed
for naval warfare.
So you would think that--
[QWENTHUR]
I got this feeling earlier, too,
but its movements seem
pretty basic and crude.
They don't exactly
seem combat savvy.
Wait, that's it!
Hey, the Tri-Core was moving
clockwise earlier, right?
[HAVIA]
Uh....
I know it was.
I'm certain of it.
It's only turned in
a clockwise direction
since the fighting started.
They're applying thrust
to vary their pace,
but the moves are the same.
[QWENTHUR]
Now we're onto something!
[QWENTHUR] I'm betting
it hasn't made a single
counterclockwise
turn this entire time.
[HAVIA gasps]
[QWENTHUR]
An Object made for naval warfare
couldn't possibly lack
such functionality.
It must have some kind
of mechanical problem.
Are you sure?
It looks fine to me.
There doesn't appear to
be any abnormalities.
No change in the floats
and air cushions
and its equilibrium is
perfectly maintained.
If there is something wrong,
I can't confirm it from here.
[QWENTHUR]
But...
There is definitely
something wrong with it,
which would mean...
The problem is somewhere
that can't be seen
from the chopper.
Underwater!
Qwenthur, wait!
What the--? Where the
hell're you going?!
You're swimming straight into
the path of the Tri-Core's
clockwise course!
[QWENTHUR]
That's what I'm trying to do!
I've figured out the
Tri-Core's weakness!
[BOTH gasps]
[FROLAYTIA]
This is crazy!
Get back here, Qwenthur!
There's no stopping
that white knight
when he decides to
save the Princess.
Trust me, he's not
gonna listen to reason.
Then what's your plan?
--[metal scraping]
--[HAVIA grunting]
Heads up! Here comes
your trusty steed!
Hey, Don Quixote!
Good luck chasing windmills!
[QWENTHUR] You have my
gratitude, Sancho Panza.
[HAVIA chuckles]
[motor starts]
[QWENTHUR]
Now let's ride, Rocinante!
[QWENTHUR] There it is--
The shark fin keel.
The length of the shark
fin keels adjust to match
the Tri-Core's tilt and
shift its center of gravity.
The whole point of them
is to keep the craft from
flipping over, no matter
how fast it's going.
[QWENTHUR grunts]
[QWENTHUR]
Now's my chance!
[QWENTHUR grunts, yells]
[QWENTHUR] From an engineering
standpoint, they'd get more
speed without such high-drag
objects attached to it.
The fact that it's still
got these shark fin keels
means that they're completely
indispensable to this beast.
[QWENTHUR]
But this one's impaired.
There's no way that it
can function properly
with the net of the Goal
Tape tangled around it.
[QWENTHUR] And that's why
they can't go counterclockwise.
They can only turn
in one direction.
Its mobility has
become this limited
from a single keel
being impaired.
If I can disable
just one more...
That should do it!
[QWENTHUR grunts]
[QWENTHUR] If the Goal Tape
bombs still haven't detonated,
they must be pressure sensitive.
And considering the conditions,
it must take some serious
pressure to trigger the fuses.
It's been a rat race between
the development of sensor
technology and the tech
that's used to counter
and deceive those sensors.
As a result, recent mines
have come full circle,
reverting to their
simplest designs.
So all I've gotta do is apply
the pressure of an explosion,
and they'll detonate for sure!
She took a hit!
[MILINDA yelps]
Just one gun left!
[QWENTHUR]
Yes. Got everything rigged up.
[QWENTHUR grunts, screams]
[gasps]
--[gasps, coughs]
--[HAVIA] Hey!
Did you rig one of the shark
fin keels with Hand Axe?
More or less. I set it up so
the explosion would trigger
all the mines
tangled around one.
[HAVIA]
That's the big strategy
that sent you
charging in there?!
You know how thick
that thing's armor is!
There's no way those mines could
even leave a scratch on it!
Don't tell me that you seriously
think they're strong enough
to break off one of those
huge shark fin keels!
Look! The Tri-Core!
Qwenthur!
Damn it. You've managed to
get their attention now!
Dive underwater while the
Princess tries to distract them!
Princess!
[HAVIA] I'm still
shocked you would think
some Hand Axe could
destroy a shark fin keel!
[QWENTHUR]
I already told you.
Wha?
[QWENTHUR] I'm only using
the Hand Axe to detonate
the net of mines
tangled around the keel.
It goes without saying the
weight of an average Object
is astonishingly heavy.
But the scale of the Tri-Core
is nearly triple that size.
And that mass exerts
a phenomenal amount
of kinetic energy.
The shark fin keels keep
that energy in balance,
but if they become useless...
The mass will irregularly shift
towards the center
of the Object.
And as a result, that strain
will tear the Tri-Core apart!
That's right.
It's basically the same
method behind Aikido.
Use your opponent's own
weight against them!
Ha, ha! How ya like that, huh?
First, Alaska, and
now that makes it two!
Man, how many medals
do I get for this one?
It's still not over yet!
We've gotta get
you out of there!
[QWENTHUR]
Huh? But...
I took care of the Tri-Core.
[gasps]
Really?
Come on!
[yelps]
[QWENTHUR]
I'm so dead!
[QWENTHUR groans]
--[gasps]
--[explosion]
[MILINDA]
Good morning!
How's it feel to catch a ride
on one of your beloved Objects?
[chuckles]
[sighs]
[laughs]
[helicopter whirring]
[chuckles]
Nothing like ending a day
full of near-death experiences
with a burger to remind
you you're still alive.
I can't believe I'm
asking this, but...
C'mon, Miss Frolaytia,
can't you cross your legs
while you're wearing
a pencil skirt?
Please consider the
feelings of the guys
--sitting across from you.
--[FROLAYTIA chuckles]
What, you don't like?
I went out of my way
to give you an eyeful.
Is the contrast between
torn black stockings
and red underwear too
much for you to handle?
No, it just doesn't do it for
me when it's that flagrant.
I mean, it's like
you don't even care!
It just feels condescending,
like you're patronizing me.
But... damn it to hell, those
are some sexy red panties!
And your pale thighs are still
slick and shiny from the ocean!
Yes, I admit, I like it!
[FROLAYTIA]
Time to freshen up.
I feel sticky from
all that seawater.
I do believe a shower and
a fresh change of
clothes are in order.
I can't show up on base
smelling like a fish.
Uh, it's not like there's
a shower on the chopper.
So I guess that means
you're just gonna have to
wait until we get back.
Please, Qwenthur.
I know what I'm doing.
[BOTH gasp]
Damn it! That single white
sheet is like a torture device!
[QWENTHUR]
Mm? Oh, yeah, right.
Exactly what you said.
Why do you sound distracted?
Bastard!
You found a gap in the sheet
and you didn't tell me?
Nope, don't know what
you're talking about.
No gap over here, heh, heh.
[FROLAYTIA]
Qwenthur...
My tolerance only goes
so far as my underwear.
If you don't come clean,
we'll have to visit
the interrogation room
when we get back.
[QWENTHUR screams]
Oh, crap, she's onto me!
Just as I thought! You traitor!
[QWENTHUR]
Hey, stop! You're too late!
[HAVIA]
Shut up and get out of my way!
[QWENTHUR]
Jeez, get off! You're heavy!
[groans]
[FROLAYTIA humming]
Man...
I must have somehow wronged
the god of lucky pervs
in my past life.
Oh, come on, you don't have
to get depressed about it.
[HAVIA]
Oh, sure...
That's easy for you to say.
You got to see exactly
what I'm dying for.
[chuckles]
--[phone vibrates]
--[gasps]
[chuckles]
Poor Princess has
got some rough going.
[QWENTHUR]
No joke.
It'd normally be a short trip
by transport plane for her.
But to get the Object all
the way back to the base,
she's gotta inch
along by land and sea.
[FROLAYTIA]
It's part of the job.
There's a theory by one
scholar of war studies.
He proposes that our
constant state of war
is due to the means being
mistaken for the goal.
Since everyone is struggling
to claim and control
the most efficient
routes to transport
our massive war machines to
battlefronts across the globe.
Straits like this are
particularly desirable passages.
Well that was an unexpected
theoretical discourse.
[FROLAYTIA]
Just to prepare you,
our exploits here are likely to
garner you some recognition.
[HAVIA]
Huh?
I am not going to another
commendation ceremony.
[FROLAYTIA]
Oh, really?
You are aware of the
military statutes?
I don't care! They can go ahead
and dish out their worst!
I will gladly take a
dishonorable discharge
at this point!
Wrecking two Objects on our
own should be more than enough!
Now let's be honest here.
I feel like Qwenthur did all
the wrecking this time around.
I know! He found the
gap, it's not fair!
What are you talking about?
You're not making much sense,
but there's no reason to cry.
If it makes you feel any better,
I'll still stomp on you later.
[HAVIA sobs]
That does make me feel better.
[FROLAYTIA]
Well, good news for you.
There won't be a
ceremony after all.
[QWENTHUR]
Seriously?
[HAVIA]
Yes! We get to go home!
[FROLAYTIA]
Home? Negatory.
[BOTH]
Huh?
A military state in Oceania who
had been keeping a low profile
just made some big moves.
And now that you boys have put
down two whole Objects in a row?
Well, it seems you've made
one hell of an impression
on the top brass. They're
even requesting you by name.
It looks like you fly directly
to a new battlefield.
Next stop: Oceania.
Oh, hell no, let me off!
There's no way we'll
get lucky a third time!
[HAVIA] Don't make me
hijack this damn chopper!
[QWENTHUR]
I'm so sorry, okay?
I shouldn't have been so cocky!
Just please don't make
me fight another Object!
[BOTH]
You damn jerks!
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA] "The War of
the Ant and the Grasshopper."
[MILINDA] "The Invasion of the
Oceanian Military State I."