It altered her perception?
[CHARLOTTE] That's the effect
of the Mirror of Truth program.
He says it takes incoming
information and distorts it.
Flide set up a
psychological back door
at some point in the
Elite education process.
[HAVIA]
So what, he hacked the Princess?
And now she's been set
to full rampage mode?!
There's no way we could
have prepared for that.
Uh. Hold on a second.
You said "he says,"
but who is he?
[gasps]
[SLADDER]
She was referring to me.
Qwenthur Barbotage.
You were so good to me
back in Amazon City.
You're kidding. Is that
Sladder Honeysuckle?!
What are you doing with him,
Charlotte?! He can't be trusted!
That's Classified.
[HAVIA]
Oh, Crapburgers!
What the hell is going on?!
Is the Legitimate Kingdom run
by a bunch of damned lunatics?
Do you think they're trying
to start an all-out war?
[WYDINE]
Who knows?
Of course, the one time we get
assigned a simple mission,
it devolves into this mess!
There's some kind of debris
up ahead. Is that...?
[gasps]
It's the Master!
[QWENTHUR gasping]
[WYDINE]
Someone! Call a medic!
Hurry!
[DOCTOR A] Need four additional
units of O-negative.
Preparing to intubate.
[DOCTOR C]
Heart rate is growing erratic.
[DOCTOR B]
Blood pressure's dropping!
[DOCTOR C]
EKG shows arrhythmia.
[DOCTOR B]
BP plummeting!
[NURSE A]
He's in v-fib!
[DOCTOR A] Prep
the electric countershock.
[DOCTOR B]
Charging!
[DOCTOR A]
Ten seconds without a pulse now.
[DOCTOR B]
Charge complete.
[DOCTOR A]
Clear!
[NURSE A]
Still no pulse.
[DOCTOR A]
Charge to three hundred joules.
[DOCTOR B]
Charging!
[HAVIA] Hey. What
happened to my partner?
He was in the crash.
Where'd you take him?
[MEDIC A]
He's in surgery.
His condition was listed
as critical due to shock,
but I'm told things
are looking better.
Looks like our good luck
hasn't run out just yet.
Damn it.
You better not break
our lucky streak now.
You hear me?
[QWENTHUR groaning]
[OHOHO]
Up and at 'em, sleepy-head!
Ah, ha, ha!
Ohoho?
Man, what a drag. I forgot the
boobzookas were an illusion.
[gasping] What are
you doing here?!
Is the battle still-- [groans]
Just as reckless
as ever, I see.
They say that your heart stopped
at one point. Slow down.
But if you're here,
then does that mean...
Did I miss the battle?
[OHOHO]
No.
The unit keeping your Object
busy is an unmanned,
AI controlled model. [laughs]
The AI the Indigo Plasma
used to manage
its dummies was primitive.
Especially when compared to the
intricately woven tapestry
of code we've created
in this latest version.
That's how we can
control it remotely.
Remotely? That's
why you're here?
Uh! Look, I don't want you
gettin' the wrong idea.
I can't very well have you dying
before I've repaid
you for Alaska.
I just came down here to
see how you were doing.
[laughs]
And Havia.
What about him?
[LENDY]
He's fine.
His injuries were minor, and
have already been treated.
And you are?
Lendy Farolito, I'm in
charge of operations
for the Object your
people call the Rush.
There were people
stuck in the middle.
My battalion commander
and the guru hostage
we were there to trade.
Any word?
They're alive.
For now.
Milinda, disengage!
You have to back off,
do you hear?!
[MILINDA]
Don't worry, Frolaytia.
It'll be okay. I'm
here to rescue you!
You're the only one
who wants to fight!
Stop shooting! We're all right!
You're under duress.
I know the enemy is just
forcing you to lie to me.
I've come to save you.
[LENDY]
Unfortunately, I've been told
they're both injured and
completely pinned down.
[QWENTHUR]
So mount a rescue.
If one of the Objects
accidentally ran over them,
it would be a disaster.
Both the Capital Enterprise
and the Faith Organization
have Objects observing
from the sidelines.
If the guru is killed,
then we're looking
at a long, ugly war.
I don't want that.
But you're suggesting
we put ourselves
between two battling Objects.
It just isn't realistic.
What if you withdrew the Rush?
Then there would be nothing left
standing between your confused
friend and this base.
I'm afraid we simply
can't allow that. Ha, ha!
Now that you've been
brought up to speed,
maybe I can ask you
a couple questions.
First, what the hell
is going on out there?
Because it seems like
the Baby Magnum's Elite
is trying to start
a major world war!
You're wrong!
[groaning]
The Princess isn't like that.
She's just fighting
for all she's worth,
like she always has.
Doing whatever it might take,
to protect everyone.
[gasps]
[QWENTHUR]
But she...
She's not really the same
Princess right now.
Her perception's been distorted.
She can't control her actions.
That doesn't sound good.
[LENDY]
"Distorted" how, exactly?
It's hard to say.
Hey, Professor Shades! Why
doncha just let me in already!
I'm his freakin' partner!
[growls] Damn!
[LENDY]
The Mirror of Truth?
You're certain that's
what it's called?
I'll say this; you've definitely
piqued my interest.
But I want to hear it
from this source of yours.
[chuckles]
Then you'll need to
give me back my radio.
[QWENTHUR]
Hello, Charlotte? Qwenthur here.
Uh! It's good to hear from you.
When your comm cut out abruptly
earlier, I feared the worst.
[QWENTHUR] I've managed
to stay alive so far.
Now please, let me talk to him.
I want to pick his brain.
Sladder Honeysuckle
and I need to chat.
[gasps]
[LENDY]
Sladder? It can't be.
[SLADDER] Was there something
you wanted to ask me, Qwenthur?
Or was this just a social call?
What's this "Mirror
of Truth" program?
[SLADDER]
I told you, didn't I?
It's a perceptual
interference program
developed specifically for
Elites. It's quite clever,
the groundwork theory
was pieced together
using AI research from
the Intelligence Union.
[BOTH gasp]
So how can it be stopped?
Well, let's see...
Best bet is to defend against or
flee from the distortion vector.
I'm sure it would
cease its assault
if you could give it
a stop command.
But, as things stand, it's
locked into attack mode.
And the key to changing
that was lost with Flide.
If you hope to
stop the fighting,
you have no choice
but to destroy her.
Fortunately, destroying
the Baby Magnum
shouldn't prove too difficult.
Though, I'm sure you're
aware of that as well.
[QWENTHUR growls]
[SLADDER]
First, there's its suspension.
It's equipped with an
electrostatic propulsion system
that's prone to water damage.
It doesn't even have to be a
flood, or anything extreme.
If there's a relatively
shallow pool of water.
You can bring the whole
thing to a standstill.
You do that, she's
a sitting duck.
Another option would be to
simply attack the cannon support
joint on the unit's back.
It's the Achilles' heel
of the main guns
in one convenient location.
Hitting it there should
cause a massive explosion.
After that, there's the
revolving gun magazines.
If you're able to plant charges
on the exposed part,
they feed into the
guns automatically
when loading the next round.
Then the bomb is inside the
barrel of the Object's gun.
The explosive would
then detonate on firing,
taking the unit with it.
There are a few other ways
if you're interested.
[QWENTHUR] These aren't the
answers I was looking for.
[SLADDER] But you want
to stop it, don't you?
With an Object infected
by the Mirror of Truth,
the only choice
is to destroy it.
I believe the Intelligence Union
might have a better grasp on
this, if you want to ask them.
The truth is,
we've actually been aware of
this program for some time now.
Somehow, our research
was leaked illegally.
It operates with an
interference feedback loop
delivered by a
subroutine installed
in the Object's mainframe.
It was intended for where an
Elite might refuse a mission.
Or if the Elite were in a
standalone environment
due to communications jamming.
It offered a way for us
to control the Elite.
It was developed for
experimental purposes.
[QWENTHUR]
Damn it!
[WYDINE]
Lendy.
We ran Perfect Browsing based
on the variables provided.
But the solution
Romeo deems viable
is the Baby Magnum's
neutralization.
There were no other
options. That was all.
[LENDY] In order to resolve
our current situation,
we have no other choice but
to destroy the Baby Magnum.
I'm Sorry. It's the
only logical step.
[SLADDER]
What are you going to do?
Fighting and destroying Objects
is your specialty, isn't it,
Qwenthur the Giant Slayer?
Shut up, another peep out of you
and I'll blow up the prison
you're being held in.
[SLADDER]
Oh, how scary!
Well, I look forward to hearing
about which choice you make.
You do your best
out there, hero.
[CHARLOTTE] Don't be goaded into
acting without authorization!
The Legitimate Kingdom
Council is in session.
They're forming an
official position.
Saying that the Baby Magnum's
Elite has gone rogue.
They're planning to ask
the other three powers
to take the Baby Magnum
out of action.
And a first gen Object
can't stand against
that kind of barrage.
The directive from up top is
to do nothing until then.
If you disobey,
all insubordinate parties
will be court-martialed.
Understood? Don't
do anything ra--
We can only count on
ourselves, this time.
You said there's
continual interference
coming from the Object, right?
Then if we can drag
her out of the Object,
would that undo the
perceptual interference?
Yes, In theory. But you're not--
[QWENTHUR grunts]
Hang on. You're going?
But you can barely even walk!
[QWENTHUR groaning]
You want to inflict
enough damage
to make the Object
eject the pilot.
But not enough to
actually kill the Elite.
And to do it all on purpose?
That's almost impossible,
even for me!
Have you already
thought up a plan?
[QWENTHUR]
Nothing yet.
But, I have faith.
Anything that was made
by man's hands...
can also be taken apart
by a man's hands.
I'd be dead now if you
hadn't treated my wounds.
You have my gratitude.
[OHOHO]
You don't really think
we're going to let you
leave so easily.
Or did somebody forget that
he's a prisoner of war?
Ah, ha, ha!
Well then, tell them I escaped
after knocking you
out from behind.
I have a proposal for you.
You're aspiring to be a
licensed Object designer,
isn't that right?
[QWENTHUR]
Mm. Uh-huh.
Okay, so why not defect
to the Intelligence Union?
If you work as my
maintenance engineer
with the on-the-job experience,
and my glowing recommendation,
you'll be a designer in no time!
Then you can personally
design my next Object!
[QWENTHUR] Wow, that's
a very enticing offer.
Awesome!
[QWENTHUR]
But I can't.
[OHOHO growls] You'd give up
everything for that girl?!
You must really care
a lot about her.
Objects have become the
representatives of modern war.
And the Elites show
how twisted it truly is.
They're the ones burdened
with the outcome of wars.
All alone.
Building walls between
themselves and everyone else.
As thick as the outer
shell of an Object.
The Princess has
always been isolated.
Even now, she's there
all by herself
surrounded by those thick walls.
Despite that, she continues
to fight to protect everyone.
[gasps]
No way in hell I'm
letting her die alone.
[QWENTHUR gasps]
[QWENTHUR]
A mirror!
[QWENTHUR] Listen I'm begging
you! You've gotta help me!
[OHOHO]
What?!
I'm going to save the Princess.
But if I'm going to do that,
I need the absolute
cooperation of an Object!
You told me I owed you for what
happened in Alaska, right?
Once we've settled this mess,
you can do whatever
you want with me!
I need your help!
So you're willing to put
your life on the line here?
I am.
[OHOHO]
Get on your knees and promise.
[QWENTHUR]
I swear.
By the rapier of
sanguine victory,
that hangs over the heads
of the Kingdom's soldiers.
[OHOHO laughs] You really make
manipulating you far too easy.
[gasps]
You're just trying
to do what's right,
but a real man should never
bend his knee so willingly
to an enemy.
[laughs]
[HAVIA] I've already established
contact with our base zone
and Ohoho's agreed
to work with us too.
That just leaves...
You're late, Prince Charming!
I've been brought up to
speed on the details.
It's time to roll out.
There's a Princess
that needs saving.
[QWENTHUR]
You understand what'll happen
if you go with me, right?
You'll get court-martialed
and then you can kiss the future
you've been working for goodbye.
He says, fully intent
on going himself.
Yeah.
Then I don't have a choice.
We've come way too far
to just give up like that.
Right, partner?
[QWENTHUR grunts]
[HAVIA]
Let's do this!
[LENDY] The Legitimate Kingdom
Council has come to the decision
to abandon the Baby Magnum.
Now the Capital Enterprise
and the Faith Organization
are preparing to mobilize.
They should be approximately
15 minutes out.
Is that enough time?
If I know Granny, she'll find
a way to make it work.
[AYAMI] We could funnel
all of the base's power
into this sucker, and the output
wouldn't even hit ten percent!
This modification is the
toughest job you'll ever do.
I'm only asking you guys to do
it perfectly in record time!
And if anyone can get
it done, it's my crew!
We're only going to
get one chance.
Frolaytia, I'd like to thank you
for authorizing this mission.
It means a lot.
We should've ignored the idiotic
decision the Council made
and shot that traitor Flide in
the head when we had the chance.
But why don't we get
down to business
while the guru and
I are still alive?
After all, the men and women
of the 37th Mechanized
Maintenance Battalion
have to stick together
till the bitter end.
Right.
I'll wait for her to move into
the designated location
and then you want me
to start blasting at her
with my guns, right?
[QWENTHUR]
Yes, please.
[OHOHO]
Then I'm on my way!
Princess, come in.
It's me.
[MILINDA]
Qwenthur!
[QWENTHUR] You've done great.
Are you all right?
[MILINDA] Yes. It's dragged
on longer than I'd like,
but I'm just fine.
I can still keep fighting.
[gasps]
If all I had to do was
score a direct hit,
this would be simple
but to be told not to.
I have my work cut out for me.
This might actually
be fun! [laughs]
Don't you worry, Qwenthur.
I'm heading in to rescue
Frolaytia and the guru.
Just watch, I'll
protect everyone!
Uh?
[gasps]
[QWENTHUR]
No good!
And we were so close to
drawing the Baby Magnum
into the target zone,
we're gonna have to
change things up!
Punch it, Havia!
Are you freakin' kidding?
[QWENTHUR]
There's no time to argue!
We have to act as a decoy
and guide the Princess along!
[HAVIA] The decoy?! We're dead
the second we go out there!
[QWENTHUR]
That new remote controlled
Rush model is equipped
with an advanced jamming system
that throws off targeting data.
She'll be busy splitting
her attention
between the two
different Rushes,
we should move in pretty close.
Move in, huh? Closer?!
Stop whining and just do it!
[HAVIA]
Why'd I volunteer?!
I thought fields of flowers were
something you're supposed to see
after you've kicked the bucket!
[QWENTHUR] Princess, do you
see the car approaching you?
[MILINDA] The jamming is
pretty bad, but there it is!
[QWENTHUR] Listen to me,
Havia and I are in that car.
Don't shoot, no matter what.
[gasps] So you're saying
you want me to fire all
of my guns at once?
[QWENTHUR] That's right.
No matter what, Milinda,
do not shoot.
Listen up, hard left on the
count of three, you got it?
[MILINDA] Hey, Qwenthur
when this is all over,
we should do something
fun together.
I would love to.
What do you say we get
this pain-in-the-neck
battle over with already,
so we can do something
less stressful for a change!
Now!
[MILINDA]
You won't get away!
[QWENTHUR]
I love you, baby.
[gasps]
That was strange.
No dangerous
substances detected.
You'll pay for what
you did to my man!
She's gonna shoot!
Did the plan fail?!
[QWENTHUR] No, it didn't fail.
Here comes the grand finale!
[gasps]
Now do it!
You actually pulled
it off, hero-boy!
[HAVIA laughs]
[HAVIA]
And a heave-ho!
[OHOHO]
But how?
We use a special vapor
deposition process
called CVD in our work.
Object's sensors don't view the
gas as a dangerous substance,
so everything
functioned normally.
After firing,
the main guns vent
to take in air and cool
down between shots.
So when they did, we made
them suck in the CVD powder.
With the energy generated
by the next firing,
the powder in the barrels
underwent electrochemical
vapor deposition.
Turning the interior of
the barrels into mirrors.
After that, the guns would
no longer function normally.
With factors like thermal
reflection and turbulence,
they couldn't
handle another shot.
Yeah, I already
knew all of that.
But, I was curious
how you managed
to survive that initial barrage.
Well, your guess
is as good as mine.
[QWENTHUR] Maybe it was just
pure chance that saved us.
Whatever it was,
we're alive, and so
is the Princess.
[QWENTHUR] We couldn't
have done it without you.
Thank you.
You know, of course. I shall
consider this a favor you owe.
And next time, I will make
you surrender to my charms.
I'll make you mine,
just wait and see!
[laughs]
[gasps] Qwenthur!
[QWENTHUR laughs]
[SLADDER laughs]
[CHARLOTTE]
Why are you laughing?
The boy surprised me.
I wouldn't have guessed he'd
hit the jackpot so easily
considering I gave him a one
percent chance of saving her.
Battle's going to turn this
boy into quite the monster.
All those big shots whose
names are on the List,
they must be quaking in
their boots right about now.
[KLONDIKE] The duality
of destroying the Object,
and saving the Elite.
Heh. They can do it when
they put their minds to it.
[FROLAYTIA]
I don't know about you,
but they had me
sweating bullets!
This could be it, a sign.
[KLONDIKE]
Those young folks
are a sign of the
changing times.
Though whether those
times are changing
for the better, or the worse,
no one can say for certain.