[AYAMI] Keep it comin',
keep it comin', come on!
A little further now,
keep it comin'!
Listen up!
We're about to set
2,000 tons afloat here!
And I expect an even more
delicate touch than usual!
[TRAINER 4A]
Okay.
We can start with your
routine physical rehab now.
Sure.
[TRAINER 4A]
Brace yourself, this is cold.
[MILINDA gasps]
[TRAINER 4A]
Hmm...
Your right shoulder is raised
by about two millimeters.
You need to distribute tasks
evenly between your arms.
Did you forget?
I've just... been
writing a lot of emails.
[TRAINER 4A]
Oh, yeah?
I did see a report that said
you've had an increase
in correspondence.
Lemme guess, boyfriend?
[gasps]
[MILINDA]
Just a friend.
[TRAINER 4A]
Really?
[MILINDA gasps]
He rescued me.
No, it was more than that.
He saved my life.
He's a real friend.
[FROLAYTIA]
Qwenthur!
Hm?
[FROLAYTIA] We're approaching
our mission destination.
Your cell phone will
have to wait for now.
So...
What kind of miracle
are they expecting us
to work this time,
Miss Frolaytia?
I'm hoping for some
"deep undercover action."
Deep under the covers with y--
[HAVIA groans]
[FROLAYTIA] Our target is an
Object presumed to belong
to the Intelligence Union,
who provide support
to known terrorist groups.
Codenamed the Tri-Core,
this monstrosity is equipped
with three power reactors.
Whoa, three?
It's a Super-Heavy class?
Hold on.
"Presumed," you said?
Well, considering its purpose,
they're not exactly
advertising the affiliation.
You see, it seems this behemoth
has the ability
to drill for oil.
It operates all over
the western coast of Africa,
disregarding international
and territorial water borders,
and then distributes that oil
amongst terrorist organizations.
But why are they stealing oil?
I mean it's not like Objects
run off the stuff.
Because the terrorists
sell it to the countries
that secretly
support them, of course.
Objects may not require it,
but the base zones
that maintain them
still utilize vast
quantities of crude oil.
[FROLAYTIA]
So there you have it.
Your official orders.
Stop this crude oil thief
preemptively at Gibraltar,
the entrance to
the Mediterranean,
and recover the oil before they
pass it onto a terrorist group.
That is all.
Say what?
[BOTH]
Recover it?
[HAVIA] They want us
to procure the Object
instead of just blowing it up?
Look what our genius has done.
The bar is set
unrealistically high now.
Sorry.
But as your on-site C.O.,
and someone who knows you two
are far from being geniuses,
I'll give you some slightly
more plausible orders.
Blow it up right along
with the crude if you have to.
Just make sure
you stop that Object
from making it
through the strait.
Fair enough?
That's a little
more reasonable, sure,
but still almost as impossible.
Hey, no fair!
We're still getting
basic wages, right?
Where's the extra
money for the extra mile?
[HAVIA gasps]
Are you picking a fight
with your superior, Havia?
If you are,
then come at me already.
Oh, come on, don't tease me.
One stomp on my crotch
with that slender leg of yours
would be enough to--
--[thud]
--[HAVIA yelps]
Ow!
[slap]
[HAVIA]
Total fail.
Even with her leg hiked up,
I still couldn't catch a
glimpse of the promised land.
Y'got quite a
dismissive attitude
about our impending doom.
[HAVIA]
I do not!
My debauchery is what's known
as a coping method, okay?
Whatever it takes, Havia.
Though if you've
found a way to cope,
I guess you're on board?
[BOTH gasp]
Here, have a look.
There's a Goal Tape
stretched across
the entire
Strait of Gibraltar.
Basically, it's an enormous net
rigged with a ton of mines.
And supposedly, it's going
to prevent that steel giant
from entering.
Truthfully though,
it's just a flashy Band-Aid
and a waste of taxpayers' money.
Which is precisely why
we were given the orders
to throw the Princess's
Object at it head-on
while you make a stealth
attack from behind.
[HAVIA] So the odds are
that we'll get shot to pieces
by our own Object.
[FROLAYTIA] Then it's
fairly simple: Don't.
Come home safe and sound
and I'll do you the favor
of stomping on you
nice and soft, hm?
A reason to live! Wait...
Do you realize you just set me
up to die a tragic death?
You can't give
a guy that much hope!
Not before battle!
The more ya wanna live
the more you're gonna die!
[HAVIA]
Oh, man.
This sucks.
Right off the bat, they're
stickin' us front and center
of this freakin' battle!
[FROLAYTIA] Our mission
is to blockade the strait.
Is there somewhere other
than in the thick of it
that you can be effective?
Hey. You know that medal?
Was that an advance
on the double promotion
you get after death?
Hell if I know.
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR]
Back to the battlefield,
just like a
couple of suckers.
Hey! You're not here
for sightseeing.
Now stow your things and get
to your posts, on the double.
Not to add any pressure,
but the brass are watching
this operation with a close eye,
so you don't wanna screw it up.
Right.
Even if we do
somehow screw up,
I doubt things could get
any worse for us. Or...?
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR]
We're toast.
[SECRETARY 4A] It appears
the two soldiers in question
have arrived in
Gibraltar on schedule.
[FLIDE]
So they made it in time.
[SECRETARY 4A]
Yessir.
If the intel we've gathered is
accurate, it won't be long now.
Alert me as soon
as there's movement.
[SECRETARY 4A]
Sir.
[FLIDE chuckles]
[HAVIA]
How's it look, man?
I still have no idea
why they swapped out
our standard issue explosives
from C-4 to Hand Axe.
Doesn't that stuff cost even
more per gram than platinum?
[QWENTHUR] Drop of hot water
in a cold bucket.
Doesn't matter what it is.
None of it's gonna come
close to leaving a scratch
on the armor of an Object.
That's true.
And this Object's
a triple beast.
Let's be real here.
Do you think we have a
shot in hell at succeeding?
I know the brass expects us
to just pull something out
of our butts like last time.
[HAVIA]
Mmm...
But, hey, it might
work out better than we think.
How?
[HAVIA] First of all,
the Princess's Object
is in solid condition this time.
And unlike Alaska,
we've actually got backup,
instead of having
to go it on our own.
You think that's enough?
[HAVIA]
Yeah. It'll have to be.
Look at that!
It was a rush job,
but they did manage to get
30 Object Maintenance Zones
built around the base.
So at least
we're well prepared.
Even if we lose a couple of 'em,
they'll still be able to keep
the Baby Magnum operational.
Way I see it, we've just
gotta put on a good show
while Her Highness
does all the heavy lifting.
And that really ups our
odds of going home alive.
Good point.
We might actually
be all right after all!
[HAVIA]
Whoa!
I know I said it was
a rush job, but damn!
This one better be more sturdy!
[QWENTHUR]
Snap out of it, you idiot!
It clearly got attacked
by the Tri-Core!
[HAVIA]
Oh, clearly.
[alarm sounding]
[HAVIA]
It's already attacking?
We just got here!
[HAVIA]
Oh, you cannot be serious!
That thing's freakin' huge!
I can't even comprehend
how it's capable of moving!
If I had to guess,
prob'ly a combination
of air cushions and water jets
and fighting spirit?
Holy crap, what are we,
target practice?
Shouldn't it have hit
the Goal Tape by now?
[BOTH]
Uhh...
[QWENTHUR] We shouldn't
be surprised, right?
We knew that there was no way
the Tape was gonna stop it.
[HAVIA]
Damn tax thieves!
They could've
at least let us think
it would work for a little bit!
[QWENTHUR] Have all
the false hope you want.
But realizing you've been lied
to will be your last thought.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[HAVIA]
Damn it!
The real bitch about all this
is we're gonna get blown up
just for being
too close to the battle.
Whoa, hold on.
Where the hell is the Princess?
This might be a
good time to return fire!
[FROLAYTIA]
What? Really?
Don't tell me you two
haven't heard.
[HAVIA] Well that's
a foreboding question!
[FROLAYTIA]
She's not dead.
The Princess is at
a naval land base.
Maintenance is still outfitting
her Object with floats
for combat at sea.
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR]
Huh?
You're surprised?
That's exactly why you two
goons were summoned here.
You're the only ones
who can put up a fight
without an Object,
so you're holding it off
until the Princess shows.
[HAVIA]
You can't be serious!
It's like they somehow
got us mixed up
with spandex-clad superheroes!
It's impossible!
Look, really!
Just hurry and
raise the white flag.
It's the only way
we're gonna survive!
I'm afraid I can't do that.
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR]
Why not?
[FROLAYTIA] Simply put,
the white flag only works
when you cede the
territory and retreat.
This time around,
we've marked out our territory
by blocking the enemy's path.
[FROLAYTIA] So even if
we raised the white flag,
it's not going to
stop that monster
from destroying
our base zones.
On top of that, for this
particular operation,
I wasn't even given the radio
code to raise the white flag.
In other words, our orders
are to defend this place
with our lives.
[HAVIA]
What?!
[FROLAYTIA]
Come on, already!
You either stop that thing
or we all die!
That's why I issued those
ridiculously expensive
explosives to you!
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR yelling]
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR] There's no
way in hell we can do this!
[gasps, coughs]
Damn it!
We were way too optimistic!
This is the last time I ever
get sent to the front lines
to fight an Object!
[HAVIA gasps] Forget the Object,
this suit is so heavy, I'm--
[coughing]
I'm gonna drown!
[HAVIA coughs]
I'm sinki--!
Mind if I ditch
the explosives?
[QWENTHUR]
Yes, I mind!
You are not knocking our one
percent chance down to zero!
[HAVIA] It was zero percent
from the start.
[HAVIA] Is it just me,
or is that beast
heading straight for us?!
[QWENTHUR] Looks like they're
planning to leisurely pick off
the leftovers and break through.
[FROLAYTIA]
Then do something!
We cannot allow
them to deliver that oil.
They've got another Object
that's currently grounded
due to lack of maintenance.
That oil will put it
back in the game
and give them
immediate reinforcement.
They're already doing
enough damage with one.
Think we could swim
out of the way in time?
[QWENTHUR]
There's no way.
Not even a roided-out
Technolympic athlete
could swim that fast.
Then bust out
the brains, schoolboy!
What the hell do we
do to survive this?
[QWENTHUR] We can't evade it
by going left or right.
So where else can we try to go?
Today, maybe?!
[QWENTHUR]
Wait a minute.
[HAVIA yells]
Come on!
[QWENTHUR]
Put these on!
We're diving down!
Even that behemoth can't
extend too far underwater!
[QWENTHUR] Wow.
I guess that worked--Whoa!
A shark fin keel?
[QWENTHUR]
Damn it! Are you serious?
The Goal Tape!
What was left of it
got caught on the keel!
[QWENTHUR] And what kind of
trigger do those have?
Magnetic? Water Pressure?
Acoustic? Oh, man!
At this rate, it's my life
that's gonna cross
the goal line!
[QWENTHUR]
Don't tell me...
He's actually planning
on climbing up there
and boarding the Object?
[HAVIA]
Ugh, jeez.
I'm all sticky and gross.
"Can't extend
too far underwater!"
You almost got us killed, jerk!
You asked me
for a way to survive,
and you're alive
to bitch about it,
so the plan worked.
At least for us.
Do you think Miss Frolaytia
made it out okay?
No idea.
Although she's
probably just fine,
since I'm pretty sure she's
got the luck of the devil.
And built-in flotation devices.
[HAVIA]
Let's move.
[QWENTHUR]
Right.
[HAVIA]
Speaking of huge...
[QWENTHUR]
Yeah, the scale of this thing
is downright staggering.
Freaking Tri-Core.
[HAVIA]
Right? It's absurd.
On top of that...
I can't believe it
actually drills for oil, too.
[QWENTHUR]
Yup.
These must be
the tanks it stores
all the crude in
for delivery.
[HAVIA]
Like an oversized pizza joint.
[QWENTHUR] All right. I'll rig
up some extra over here.
But... Do you really think
we can sink this beast
with explosives?
The only reason
it worked in Alaska
is because we used their
maintenance schedule
against them.
Come to think of it,
where do you think this monster
stops to get its maintenance?
[HAVIA]
Hey man, check it out.
[QWENTHUR]
A giant warehouse?
I get it.
They've got their whole
maintenance facility
built right onto the Object.
Pretty clever, really.
And it could only work
on a craft this size.
No, moron!
The guards!
Forget about the
maintenance hangar,
this place has fully-armed
infantry on patrol!
--[HAVIA] Time to go!
--[QWENTHUR] Wait!
We're safer here!
We're in the middle of
a bunch of oil tanks, right?
[HAVIA] Is that why
they're not unloading?
Guess they'da
made mincemeat of us
if they weren't worried
about blowing up their cargo.
Now what?
Should we head for the
maintenance hangar?
Like back in Alaska?
It's not quite
the same situation.
Then figure out a weakness!
We're already here,
we've gotta do something!
Just check the data!
Damn!
I'm not really getting
any reception here!
[HAVIA]
Just make it work!
Who knows how many
guards we're up against!
[HAVIA]
Crap!
We gotta move!
We're dead if they surround us!
Leave behind as many
gifts as we can
and get the hell out of here!
[HAVIA]
So? You figure out its weakness?
[QWENTHUR]
Sure!
'Cause I've had so much
time to think about it!
It's not exactly pay dirt,
but this is the closest
I've found to a weakness so far.
Take out the whole base, huh?
Well, considering the
hulking size of this thing,
if we blow out the bottom,
it probably will sink
under its own weight.
[QWENTHUR] Yeah, guess it
comes down to how powerful
this Hand Axe stuff
actually turns out to be.
Damn! They've got more
troops searching for us!
We've gotta scram, man!
I don't feel like getting
a double promotion
via a bullet in my brain!
[QWENTHUR]
One more second.
[HAVIA]
No more seconds!
[HAVIA] It'd be nice
if you cared about
not dying for a change!
[ENEMY SOLDIER 4A]
There they are!
[ENEMY SOLDIER 4A yells]
[HAVIA]
Come on!
[QWENTHUR]
Princess!
[ENEMY SOLDIER 4B]
Cover! Take cover!
So the Princess
is saving the knights.
How's that for a twist?
This is bad, man!
This is really bad!
We're about to get
caught in the middle
of an all-out artillery
battle between two Objects!
Targeting enemy
Object for destruction.
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR]
We're dead.
We are so... dead!
I guess Objects are
the only things that matter
in battle anymore!
They don't give a damn about us!
That can't be it!
The Princess probably
doesn't have a clue
we're even on board!
Then what do we do, genius?
Only thing we can do
is try and let her
know we're here,
and tell her she needs to switch
her primary weapons to lasers.
That should be some improvement
over the armor-shredding
physical rounds.
Baby Magnum, come in!
This is Qwenthur!
[QWENTHUR] Baby Magnum!
Do you read? This is Qwenthur!
Havia and I are
currently on the deck
of the Tri-Core.
We need you to make a
temporary weapons switch
until we can get outta here.
WL3B2! I repeat.
Switch primary weapons to WL3B2.
[MILINDA]
Amazing.
He actually boarded
the Tri-Core.
Right, the code.
Let's see... It was WL3B... 1?
Killer Squall?
B1 is the anti-personnel laser,
but he must have some
trick up his sleeve.
Roger. Here goes!
All right, that should
give us the cover we need.
[BOTH yell]
How is this
any freakin' better?
I'd rather still be in a
gunfight with the guards!
It's the wrong setting!
I said B2, not B1!
Princess!
[MILINDA]
Yes!
Hope that gives them
the backup they needed.
[HAVIA] We wasted all
that time placing bombs
when we should've just been
swimming for our lives!
[QWENTHUR]
Damn it!
I refuse to get killed
by friendly fire!
Okay, no more.
There's no way
I can live through
that kind of stress again.
[HAVIA]
Hey!
Hurry and detonate the bombs!
With how many times we
risked our lives today,
I need to see some results!
I'm with ya, partner.
The fruits of our labor.
Time to unwrap those
gifts we left behind!
[BOTH chuckle]
It's fine...
Come on!
We planted enough explosives to
level an entire mountain range!
What the hell is it gonna
take to sink that monster?
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA] "Tom Thumb
Races Through the Oil Field."
[MILINDA] "The Battle of
the Gibraltar Blockade II."