[QWENTHUR]
In the end,
mankind could never sate
the appetite for war.
Nearly every inch of Earth
had been developed
and claimed by
one nation or another.
High-powered lasers regularly
lobbed shuttles into space.
There was even a small
group of the world's elite
that took to building their
vacation homes on the moon.
Yet still...
Even amidst these wonders,
mankind couldn't eliminate
the inherent urge for conflict.
[QWENTHUR]
Yep.
Although, there was one change.
All those people intent on
pointlessly killing each other?
Well, they perfected it.
[QWENTHUR]
The super-large-scale weapon.
The Object.
The body of this new weapon
measured over
50 meters in length.
And with its arrival,
it completely rewrote
the conventions
of modern warfare
that had come before it.
[QWENTHUR]
This enormous weapon,
first introduced by
a certain island nation.
It took a barrage of fire
from the allied forces
of fourteen nations.
And kept going.
Not only that,
but it fought them off, too.
Its shell was
modeled after an onion
with layers upon layers of armor
forged by patiently
mixing in a powder
of high-performance
anti-fire reactant.
The armor plates
were then laminated
with conductor
and insulator materials,
enabling them with a
printed transmission system
that could transfer
power throughout the object.
Power from the
reactor at its core
to the external armament.
All without laying
a single line of cable.
The innovation and cutting edge
technology were boundless.
Traditional craftsmanship
combined with
precision machining
were all poured into
creating this ungodly machine.
It was the twisted apex
of the intelligence of man.
[QWENTHUR] Ultimately,
it was submerged in a baptism
of nuclear fire,
but it withstood the attack.
With half its body
melting like ice cream,
it proceeded to
wipe out the allied fleet
with its remaining armaments.
To this day,
that awesome spectacle
can be found in
our history books.
Naturally, in the wake
of such obvious success,
Objects have become
synonymous with war.
After the breakdown
of the United Nations
in the first half
of the 21st century,
a large number of countries
and sovereign republics
collapsed or underwent
a drastic reformation.
As a result
of this breakdown,
the world became divided
into four separate coalitions.
But the division of territories
was about as jumbled up as a
shattered stained glass window,
which resulted
in different powers
sharing borders
across the globe.
This inevitably led
to a constant rash
of small scale border
skirmishes and local wars.
[QWENTHUR] You could say
that the Objects
were a natural
byproduct of this world.
Necessity gave birth
to her most warped invention.
Which brings us to now.
[QWENTHUR]
The fight for sovereignty
amongst the coalitions
carries on,
but they're now
determined by "clean wars"
solely conducted by the Objects.
[QWENTHUR]
So then...
What about everybody else?
[QWENTHUR grunting]
[sneezes]
[HAVIA groans]
That's it, I quit!
I'm a freakin'
radar analyst, dammit!
I didn't join the army
to just shovel snow!
Busy work is all that's left.
I mean, every other aspect
of conflict in the world
is left up to Objects.
But we're livin' off
the taxpayers' dime,
so we've gotta at least look
like we're working, right?
Oh, yeah, right.
Freezing our butts off
working in the snow!
No one cares about us
lowly soldiers, huh?
Well, those are just the
hard knocks of modern warfare.
[QWENTHUR] Now it's all
up to the Objects
and the Elites who operate them.
That's the thing!
How am I supposed to feel
motivated to do anything
when all we have to do
is meaningless busy work?
We're totally worthless!
You've got a point.
We're about as useless
as fighter planes
going up against Objects
equipped with anti-air lasers.
Isn't the kill ratio
something like 1 to 500?
[HAVIA] Pretty sure
it's worse than that.
Jets are about as powerful as
horseflies up against Objects.
And ground-based armored units?
They're about as
effective as ants.
Everything's equally useless
in the shadow of Objects.
[QWENTHUR]
No, a tank could be useful.
[HAVIA]
Huh?
[QWENTHUR]
Right here.
Just mount a huge shovel
to the front of
one of those bad boys,
plow it through,
and we'd be done
before you even know it!
What the hell are we
doing with our lives?
[QWENTHUR]
Look at it this way.
Thanks to the Objects,
at least we don't
have to see combat.
[HAVIA] Probably not
something a soldier should say,
but that is a good thing.
There's nothing cool about
getting your head blown off
in battle.
[QWENTHUR]
Oh, hey.
You're nobility,
aren't you, Havia?
Yeah, born with blue blood.
All that means is I have to
prove myself even more.
Otherwise I won't have the
stature to inherit the estate.
Oh, thank you.
And that's why I'm here.
Racking up achievements.
So how heavy's that
cross you've got to bear?
You came out to
this frozen wasteland
just to study abroad?
Well, I'm just
a commoner by birth.
Only chance I have to
make it is to learn a trade.
So the idea's to
become a licensed designer
focused on Objects, right?
Hey, ya can't beat
on the job training.
I'm well on my way
to becoming a millionaire.
[HAVIA]
Maybe so,
but that doesn't make
this awful army food
taste any better.
[QWENTHUR] What, were you
expecting a tax-subsidized
four-course gourmet meal?
But you're right,
it's terrible.
I'd so much rather catch
one of those deer out there
and grill it up
than eat this crap.
Now that's some
brilliant commoner thinking!
You really are a genius, y'know.
Uhh...
[QWENTHUR]
Let's just forget this.
We'll catch hell
if our CO busts us.
And besides, can you
even take down a deer?
We're talkin' about
a target that moves.
[HAVIA]
No problem.
That's why I loaded up
on plenty of smart bullets.
As long as I aim in
the general direction,
the bullets will
do all of the work
and we'll have us a
tasty four-legged buffet. Ha!
[QWENTHUR] Good grief,
those are some expensive rounds.
[QWENTHUR] Even if we were
suddenly faced with combat,
it's not like the
decorated senior officers
would do anything other than
drink coffee in a warm room
while waiting for the Object
to make its victorious return.
[QWENTHUR]
Such a tough job they've got.
Not that I'm one to talk.
Hey! You comin' or what?
[QWENTHUR] I'm gonna try going
after some different game.
I'll leave the deer to you.
[HAVIA]
Ha. Whatever.
Now this is the
golden age of Objects.
Talk about a waste
of taxpayer money.
[gunshot]
[QWENTHUR]
Sounds like Havia's going at it.
I can't imagine the
taxpayers would be too happy
to know those costly bullets
are being shot at deer
instead of people.
[QWENTHUR] But at least
it's another peaceful day.
[MILINDA]
What are you doing out here?
We're having barbeque tonight.
I'm catching some fish and
Havia's hunting down a deer.
This is a dumb question
since I suggested it.
But is deer meat even tasty?
I've never tried it before
so I'm starting to get worried.
You need to eat some
vegetables with your barbeque
or you'll eventually give
yourself a heart attack.
[gunshot]
[chuckles]
And where are you
off to today, Princess?
The Object's in
for routine maintenance.
I had a little time to kill
so I went for a walk,
but then I heard gunshots
and started to get curious.
Oh, crap,
you can hear the shots
from inside the base?
We're gonna get
chewed out for sure!
I don't understand
why you would do something
when you know it's
going to get you scolded.
Remind me...
You came here to
study Objects, didn't you?
I did.
[MILINDA] What made you
choose this base?
I'm just trying to
make sense of your logic.
You know what kind
of Object I operate.
Well, of course,
it's a first gen multi-role
comprehensive Object.
In other words, it can
be operated in any region
across the world and under
any weather conditions.
It's the most standard
super-large-scale weapon
operating today.
Yeah, exactly, it's standard.
Which is just another way
of saying outdated.
That's the thing
with second gen Objects.
They don't greedily aim
to operate everywhere.
They're specialized for
certain places and objectives.
[MILINDA] Which means they
can easily outperform
generalized Objects.
[HAVIA]
Stupid deer!
Limited to this
region of snow and ice,
there's a very real chance
my Object might not win.
[QWENTHUR] But you're not
gonna stop, right?
Piloting that Object?
I mean, the Baby Magnum
is your Object.
Only because I
have no other choice.
[QWENTHUR] Wait, why am
I getting all mesmerized?
She's only got pale blue eyes
from constant exposure
to laser irradiation.
[QWENTHUR]
I mean...
They're not
naturally that pretty,
it's just from the
eye-controlled input device,
which is how I feel
I should feel.
And why is she dressed
so lightly out here?
Sure, the suit's got a system
to regulate body temperature,
but it's still a
skin-tight one piece!
[MILINDA] You conduct
maintenance on the Object,
I'm sure you understand
what I'm saying.
So I'm confused why
you chose to study here.
I guess it's a
difference in values.
Being a soldier,
you're concerned
about whether or not
the Object is strong enough.
But I don't see things
that way 'cuz I'm a student.
[QWENTHUR] Knowledge of
a standard, basic unit
will always come in handy
because it's a
fundamental design.
In other words,
I'm getting a more
universally-applicable education
by focusing on your
boring, old Object
than some specialized unit.
Has anyone told you
that you're lacking in tact?
[QWENTHUR]
Of course, all the time.
But I don't see it that way.
--Because I'm a student.
--Because you're a student.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[chuckles]
[MILINDA] Overconfidence can get
you killed on the battlefield.
Well, I'm trying
to climb the ladder
with a get-rich-quick scheme.
And confidence can
be useful on that front.
So you've got
the future all figured out?
Think so.
Do you really?
[gasps]
What was that about?
[FROLAYTIA]
I doubt I need to explain
why you've been summoned,
so don't play stupid.
This is your fault, Havia.
I told you we should forget it!
Don't pin this on me!
More importantly, she's only 18?
How are her boobs
so incredible?!
So then Qwenthur, Havia.
[BOTH gasp]
I know that it
may not seem as vital
as your days spent
hunting for provisions,
but I've got a lot on
my plate as well, you see.
Not only do I oversee
this Alaska base.
I also have to
remotely direct operations
on a small island
in the Pacific.
[QWENTHUR]
Uh, uh, right.
[FROLAYTIA]
This board in front of me?
All it takes is a
couple of simple marks,
and I deploy an
Object on standby
to blow away a guerilla base
with long-range artillery fire.
Sounds like an
easy enough job, right?
Well it is, right?
[BOTH]
Yes ma'am!
[FROLAYTIA]
Well it's not!
I'm in simultaneous command
of multiple base zones,
which makes me very busy.
And now you two
idiots just have to go
and pick the worst time possible
to make me even busier.
Can you even imagine how I feel
about the two of you right now?
[HAVIA]
Yes, ma'am!
But it's making me
really uncomfortable!
[QWENTHUR] I'm guessing that
you're extremely aggravated
with us, Miss Frolaytia!
Oh, good guess.
I'm so blessed to have
such keen subordinates.
Isn't that right?
Nod if you agree, you morons.
So then.
Let's talk about
the fruits of your labor.
You're not the only ones
sick of eating
the giant edible erasers
that pass for rations, y'know.
[FROLAYTIA]
Nicely done.
We're eating barbeque tonight.
I'll let you off with a 12-mile
run for your punishment.
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA sigh]
Oh, and Qwenthur?
[QWENTHUR]
What? Why do I get more?
Do I need to remind you
that you're a student
abroad on deployment?
I've got no choice
but to hustle you
over to the hangar
for your studies.
Otherwise I'm the one
who's gonna get yelled at
by the old bat
in charge of maintenance.
I didn't even realize
I skipped out on it!
[FROLAYTIA] Havia, you can take
care of the snow shoveling.
Make sure the runway
is clear for use by sundown.
Oh, wow!
Snow shoveling and a
12-mile run, aren't I lucky?
Yeah! Now you better get to it!
Well it's about time, boy!
Grab your tools and
get your butt up here!
[QWENTHUR]
Aw, man.
I'm sorry I'm late!
What's my punishment?
Just get results!
Prove yourself worthy
of the maintenance crew!
[panting]
[AYAMI]
I swear...
I wouldn't even be using a lazy,
work-dodging boy like you
if we weren't so damn
busy and short-handed.
So act grateful!
[MILINDA]
You showed up.
Get tired of hunting?
Yeah, I deserve
whatever you dish out.
Shut your mouth
and pay attention, boy.
You're workin' on the
emergency evac equipment today.
Nobody else wants to do it
because they
think it's bad luck.
Uh, roger that!
[QWENTHUR]
That reminds me...
I've always wondered if
the Object's painted white
for superstitious reasons,
or is it just
straight-up camouflage
for fighting in the snow?
The Objects were
originally painted with camo
to match their surroundings.
But the brain trust finally
realized there's not much point
in trying to hide
a walking mountain,
especially when
it's that costly.
Paint don't come cheap
so we left her all white.
And besides, there's no reason
for the king of beasts to hide.
So it's white for
practical reasons then,
not superstitious.
Oh. In that case,
what about the rapier
hanging from
the ceiling up there?
[AYAMI] Now that one
is a good luck charm.
[MILINDA] For guaranteed
victory and deadliness.
[QWENTHUR]
Oh? Good luck, huh?
When you're out
on the battlefield, you--
[yelps]
I can't breathe!
[QWENTHUR] Ah!
Something seems off over here.
[AYAMI]
Oh, you moron!
Don't go messing
with the belt adjustments!
Are you trying to kill her?
[QWENTHUR]
Aw, crap!
Can't breathe!
What the hell
was I just doing?
I'll go find something
to cut her out with!
You yank on those belts
so she doesn't suffocate!
Don't let her die!
I'm so sorry!
As long as I don't die,
I don't care.
So help!
[whimpering]
[QWENTHUR] I've gotta worm my
fingers in under the belts
to pull on them,
but that pretty much leaves me
with no choice but
to cop a cheap feel.
And y'know, for such a slender
girl, she's pretty stacked.
I'm about to die!
[QWENTHUR] Quit thinking
about boobs, dude!
Her life is on the line!
This is all your fault!
Now pull your crap together
and redeem yourself!
But still, jeez,
look at those boobs!
No, shut up, you creep,
this is not the time!
She's dying right
in front of you!
Do not let the Princess die!
Take this seriously
and save her boobs!
[QWENTHUR]
I can't do it!
This is not a helping hand!
I can't let it anywhere
near the poor girl!
Activate emergency protocol.
[QWENTHUR]
Whoa!
[sighs]
That boy's worthless.
[MILINDA]
Funny.
I've never had
to bail out before.
[FROLAYTIA] I heard you
pulled a real doozy
in the hangar earlier.
[QWENTHUR]
It was pretty bad.
Did I rack up
even more punishment?
[FROLAYTIA] Looks like the
old bat already got to you,
so... you're all right.
[QWENTHUR chuckles]
I've been dreaming
about this meat
and it's stinging
the cuts in my mouth!
I'd be happy to eat it
for you if you can't handle it.
No!
After all the crazy crap I
went through for this meat,
I will enjoy it!
Fair enough.
You did good work
with this, Havia.
The folks over
in the Aviation Corps
should be proud
to have you with them.
[HAVIA laughs]
Nah, really, it was nothin'.
But of course,
practically speaking,
we don't need anyone
from the Aviation Corps.
Yeah, I figured,
but thank you so much for
reminding me of that fact!
Damn it, I'm eating!
I'm regaining every single damn
calorie I lost shoveling snow!
By the way, Qwenthur,
is it true that you
spoke with the Princess
outside the base zone?
[QWENTHUR]
Uh, yeah.
I was worried
that might be a problem.
She and I talk in
the hangar sometimes.
So I didn't think
anything of it.
Sorry.
[FROLAYTIA]
Don't worry, it's fine.
The amount of
stress she's under,
she could use
someone to talk to.
[MILINDA]
My Object might not win.
Hey, um, Miss Frolaytia?
Have you ever lost a battle?
[FROLAYTIA]
Yeah, of course I have.
So what do you do if
your Object gets beat to hell
and smashed up?
[FROLAYTIA]
What do you do?
Raise the white flag
and move on.
[QWENTHUR]
Huh?
The idea of an all-out,
fight-to-the-death war
is a thing of the past.
If one of the
Objects breaks down,
the battle is decided
right then and there.
And the victor's
not gonna bother
to chase after
helpless infantrymen.
I mean, there's no formal
treaty stating anything
to that effect.
But if you promptly
withdraw your troops
and surrender the territory,
it's more or less a given
that you'll
at least get to live.
Lovely, huh?
But that's the beauty of
the safe and clean wars
the Objects provide us with.
So we sit around
as our guns get rusty
and my face breaks out
from eating greasy food.
[HAVIA]
Huh...
I figured you'd have
more problems
with your bra breaking.
Feel like shoveling
snow tomorrow, Havia?
[HAVIA]
What? C'mon!
No. Please!
I see what she's saying.
[QWENTHUR]
If you've got an Object,
even someone spoiled by peace
like me could wage war.
[QWENTHUR]
Right.
But you have to have
an Object first.
[QWENTHUR] So then,
what about everybody else?
[HAVIA gasps]
[QWENTHUR gasps]
Princess, no!
[QWENTHUR] Nobody imagines
they'll find themselves
in this situation.
I know I never did,
but here I am.
It's just not the kind of thing
that should happen to a person.
[QWENTHUR] No one should have
to go up against these monsters.
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA] "Rank and File
Soldiers Who Tie Down Gulliver."
[MILINDA] "The Snowy Deep
Winter Battle of Alaska II."