[CITY SLICKER] To my esteemed
brethren of the friendly forces
of the Legitimate Kingdom.
This is the Elite
of the glorious
24th Mechanized Maintenance
Battalion speaking.
Prizewell City Slicker,
the Magnificent!
The Legitimate Kingdom I know
and love has grown stagnant,
and do you know the reason?
Even though we have
such a useful tool
as our nation's
official language.
Inferior languages are being
used, causing interference.
Keeping us from
understanding each other.
In order for our Legitimate
Kingdom to be victorious,
we must find a solution
for this problem!
This is my goal. To bring
purity through eradication!
This is a military exercise.
Our objective is located on
the eastern part of the island.
With a seven Object show of
force, you'd best stand aside.
An exercise?! That's
such an obvious lie!
Wait, let me see
the projection map.
That puts them on course
to attack the city!
[HAVIA] Hold on, I think
you missed something.
Our base zone's in the way too!
[gasps] Major Frolaytia!
[FROLAYTIA]
All personnel evacuate!
I repeat, all
personnel evacuate!
Get as far from
the base as you can!
Let's go! On the double!
[CITY SLICKER]
Those with a command
of the proper tongue
shall be subjects.
Those unable to command it,
but willing to learn,
will be servants.
Those unable to speak, and
unwilling to learn will die.
Only then will our kingdom's
greatness rise from the ashes.
Thus, we forge the path
to a prosperous future,
through glorious victory.
[FROLAYTIA]
We were given plenty of time
to evacuate before
they attacked.
Making a show that
they're not hostile.
Qwenthur, Havia! I need
a sitrep on those Objects!
[HAVIA] The Snow Quake's
been badly damaged.
I think the Elite ejected.
[QWENTHUR] The Princess
is still hanging in there.
But she's taken some hits.
Her drive system got tagged,
but it looks as if she
can still maneuver.
[FROLAYTIA]
Understood.
Search the rubble for any
salvageable material!
Load what you can
into the vehicles and
get ready to roll out.
Those traitors are
gonna roll full tilt
on the immigrant settlement.
We'll repair the Baby
Magnum before that!
[SOLDIERS]
Roger!
[MAINTENANCE A]
Bad time to be hard to reach.
What's going on?! Come in!
You two. What's wrong?
We can't seem to find
the maintenance chief.
You mean... did she get out?!
Oh, yeah, she was with
us when we got out.
But now--
Granny wasn't originally from
the Legitimate Kingdom, was she?
As I recall, she migrated here
from Japan in the
Capital Enterprise.
Yeah she told us.
[FROLAYTIA]
What about her family?
Let's see now...
She mentioned a daughter
and a granddaughter.
The immigrant settlement...
I could have guessed.
Heh.
[HAVIA]
There we go. First aid complete!
[SOLDIER A]
Thanks a lot.
Glad I could help.
[QWENTHUR] Wha--?
What did you say? Seriously?
Granny went by herself
to save her daughter
and son-in-law from
the immigrant city?
[FROLAYTIA]
I swear, it's a good thing
the black uniforms are
on a separate assignment.
If she'd been caught by them
they would have
shot her already.
Never mind. I'm sending
these trucks your way.
You two get things ready
for the Baby Magnum
to get her needed repairs.
[QWENTHUR] Do you think
we'll make it in time?
The 24th Battalion's
traveling with infantry,
which means they have to match
speeds with their vehicles.
If we can get the Princess's
propulsion system fixed,
we might be able to catch up.
So if we want to save Granny
and the settlement,
we're working on a
limited timetable...
We've got to finish
those repairs
while there's still time!
Hang on don't be rash.
I don't like it either,
but I think it's time we
consider saying "too bad,
but we might just have
to give up and go home."
[QWENTHUR]
Just listen for a second, Havia!
As we stand here arguing
about giving up,
the 24th Battalion
keeps marching.
Do you really think there's time
for wishy-washy deliberation?
There's no time to hesitate,
we have to act now!
Get offa me, man!
Didn't you see?
They brought out seven
Objects for a fight!
Even if we take out one,
what have we accomplished?!
[HAVIA gasps]
Think about it Havia.
Do you really think we're going
up against seven whole Objects?
[gasps]
How many people maintain
the Baby Magnum?
Just to keep her operational?
If they were really operating
seven full Objects,
how much would
that cost in terms
of funding for facilities
and personnel?
How many Elites do
they really have?
Do you have any clue
about the effort
that goes into training one?!
[QWENTHUR growls]
[HAVIA grunts] Fine! So what
the hell were those things?
I seriously doubt they have
the financial resources to
field a cutting-edge Object.
Likely, they're cheap
half-gen prototypes.
Their aim was to create dummies
that would throw our
forces into a panic.
You've got nothing
to corroborate!
This is all just guesswork!
[QWENTHUR] Then I'll
have to prove it to you!
[HAVIA]
Hey, wait! Where're you going?!
C'mon!
[grunts]
Fine!
[QWENTHUR] The basic
dimensions of the floats
put them at 100 meters long
and 20 meters wide and
about ten meters high.
What about hull thickness
and quality of materials?
Let's see...
Hey, man what're you playing
with that tablet for?
Float volume. Even if
it were empty inside,
at its size, it isn't
buoyant enough
for 200 hundred
thousand tons.
At best, I'd give it
50 thousand.
You see what I'm gettin' at?
[HAVIA]
Then...
[QWENTHUR] You could never put
a real Object on this float.
That formation is a bluff.
There's no way they
have the firepower
of seven whole Objects.
What, for real?
[QWENTHUR]
The thickness of the armor
is less than a quarter
of what it should be.
If they're skimping
on things like that,
they wouldn't have done
the anti-fire reactant
treatment, either.
Its effectiveness as onion
armor would be compromised.
Their reactor output is
questionable as well.
The entire reason that they're
moving together with infantry
might be to conceal the fact
that they can't go any faster.
If that's the case,
it begs the question.
How many of them can do anything
other than fire their main guns?
Even without the aid
of an Object,
there's a chance we can
punch some holes in them
with conventional
anti-tank weaponry!
[HAVIA] So basically,
if we were to destroy
seven Objects in one fell swoop,
they'd pretty much have
to give us a medal!
[QWENTHUR]
Yeah.
[HAVIA sighs]
[HAVIA] Okay. You can count me
in, but this is the last time.
I'm doing this to gain prestige
as the future head of
the Winchell family!
And then I'm done!
This is the last time I let
you put me in a situation
where I gamble with my life!
[QWENTHUR]
Then let's not waste it.
We won't let them lay one dirty
finger on that settlement.
[HAVIA]
Yeah.
Get down!
No fair!
We get pinned down right
after you convince me
to do something
heroically awesome!
We can do it.
Let's use that car.
[HAVIA sighs]
No choice.
[HAVIA]
Medium range sniper rifles.
Plus a portable
anti-tank missile?
This level of boned
is off the charts!
We'll have to ask for permission
to sneeze from now on,
or get drilled full of lead.
[QWENTHUR] Wait. Why are
they dressed like that?
[HAVIA]
And check out that gun.
What's the Capital
Enterprise military
doing all the way out here?
[WYDINE] Okay, enough whispering
for now boys, thanks.
Hm...
They're as good a gift as can
be expected, given conditions.
hey'll do, or else we'll
have to kill 'em.
We're also starting
to run low on rations.
If we don't get something
in the win column soon,
we're in trouble.
That's correct.
And there's nothing
more we can do
until rescue comes
for us anyway.
[QWENTHUR]
Who the hell are you people?
And what are you all doing
here, for that matter?
We're agents of the Battlefield
Cleaning Service.
[BOTH] What the hell is the
Battlefield Cleaning Service?
A PMC you know,
like mercenaries?
[QWENTHUR]
But dressed like that?
Hey, there's a market
for everything.
Oh, and it seems we've
run out of business cards
please forgive us.
Damn Capital Enterprise
money worshippers.
[WYDINE sighs]
Things have actually
been pretty tough lately.
We'd planned to send
in our Object after
the Legitimate Kingdom
and Intelligence Union
wore each other down.
We could've taken
out both armies,
and we would've
gotten away with it
if it weren't for
you meddling kids.
Instead, your side
was victorious,
and has been cementing their
hold on Alaska ever since.
Which time?
Are you talking about
when the Princess
fought Ohoho and the Rush?
The Rush, huh?
You Legitimate Kingdom
types like to give things
some weird nicknames.
Thanks to that, things got
rather dicey for a while.
The withdrawal operation
was absolute chaos
so we missed our chance to
catch a transport out of here!
Enemies all around us!
Nowhere safe to sleep!
It was so not cool.
Look, if all you want is
hot soup and a blanket,
why not surrender?
If we did,
the reputation of our company
would start to suffer.
We're the Capital Enterprise:
where one's civil rights
are directly linked with
one's bank account.
They say there's no such
thing as bad publicity,
but we have an image to uphold!
Then what're you gonna do?
[WYDINE]
That.
I hope you don't mind pretending
to be a maintenance crew,
and getting the Elite
to eject for an emergency.
Tell her the reactor has
been severely damaged
and looks like it's gonna
blow or something, I dunno.
After that, we'll take
the Elite into custody.
I think I have a
pretty firm grasp
of the situation on
Victoria Island.
The seven traitorous Objects
are the last ones
the Legitimate Kingdom
has in the area.
But those units leave
for the Atlantic soon.
Once that happens, this place
will be completely undefended.
The Capital Enterprise military
will move into the region again,
we'll get extracted and all
our troubles will be over.
Now, if it's not
too much to ask,
can you get your Elite to eject?
So you people...
fight for pay?
That's right, we're a private
military corporation.
If you'd like to hire us, please
fill out the appropriate forms
on our dedicated
secure website!
There's no time for that.
I'll hire you and your people
right here, right now.
Qwenthur?!
If you take a contract with us,
then we're allies, aren't we?
[laughing]
[QWENTHUR groans]
You don't seem to know what
our services are worth,
little boy.
There's no way you
could afford to hire us
on your weekly allowance.
A fee is remuneration
that is paid in earnest
for services rendered.
Any attempt at haggling
would be beyond insulting.
Tantamount to saying that
the combined value
of our lives is subject to
whatever's convenient
for you at the time!
[QWENTHUR]
Heh.
No one's insinuating
anything of the sort.
Don't you mess with us, mop top!
[QWENTHUR grunts]
[WYDINE] Looks like someone
still doesn't fully understand
the position they're in.
That someone's you.
I'm a preferred customer,
I'll have you know.
[ALL gasp]
[QWENTHUR] If you're
from the Capital Enterprise,
I'm sure you're familiar.
Or are you so focused on cash
that you can't even recognize
precious gemstones?
Check it!
[QWENTHUR]
They're from the military mine
that was on the
Kamchatka Peninsula.
The one the Faith Organization
was keeping secret
for their rainy-day war chest.
[CHARM] These diamonds are real!
They're in the 15 carat range!
From first glance, the color
and clarity are excellent.
Like top quality good.
[ALL]
All of them?!
[QWENTHUR]
That's the just the advance.
I have two more boxes
like that one stashed away
near the maintenance base.
If you help us out here,
I'll give you the rest,
regardless of the
mission's outcome.
So, how much do
mercenaries go for?
How many missions would
you have to live through
to earn this much?
You should've led off with
the diamond offer, Master.
We'll help you however we can!
[WYDINE] Come right this way,
please make yourself at home!
I apologize in advance
for the cramped quarters,
but I promise to do our utmost
to make you feel comfortable.
This APC smells
surprisingly girly. Hm.
We still have what
we need to make tea,
don't we, Charm?
There's some leftover tea leaves
we've only steeped
two or three times,
and we can melt snow
for potable water.
What about snacks?
Well, we have the crackers
that come with our rations.
You mean those lightly-salted
pieces of plywood?
Sounds like rations
taste like crap
no matter where they come from.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Wydine Uptown,
pleased to meet you.
If you need anything from
recon and artillery support,
to shoulder rubs and manicures.
Say the word and
we'll get right on it!
Yeah? Awesome.
I guess for starters,
maybe we should make for
the immigrant settlement,
to lend a hand.
We have our orders, ladies!
Full speed ahead!
Next stop, the immigrant
settlement!
If they're willing
to do anything,
let's have 'em do it all,
know what I'm sayin'?
I wouldn't mind getting
my ears clean,
with my head in the lady's lap.
No one asked your
opinion, fart-face,
so just sit there and keep
your ugly yap shut.
Why the harsh treatment?
It's the difference
between a customer
who's already compensated us,
and a worthless freeloader
who hasn't coughed up
a single penny!
You should be grateful
we even let your
goldbrickin butt on board!
[HAVIA] Okay, fine I won't
ask for anything!
But you should know,
when I feel cold eyes looking
down on me with contempt,
I'm the kind of guy
who gets turned on!
[laughs] Now, what should
our next move be?
[WYDINE]
What seems to be the problem?
Of the seven units,
six are likely to be dummies
that are half-gen or even less.
But they can still
use their main guns.
And then our main opponent,
the second gen Indigo Plasma...
It's an honest-to-goodness
monster weapon.
I wanna know how they
managed to get six Elites
trained enough to operate
all those things?
We're most likely dealing
with Strategic AIs.
Why do you say that?
Lemish, would you be so kind
as to enlighten our client?
[LEMISH]
Gladly.
This shows their movements from
when the six units came ashore.
They're represented
by the red arrows.
Does anything stand out to
you about the way they move?
They're running along
perfectly straight lines.
And here comes the dummies'
leader, the Lily Maria.
I think your people call
it the Indigo Plasma,
but watch what happens
when they come
within a five klick radius
of their leader.
[QWENTHUR] The movement
of the dummy units changed.
That's right, their maneuvers
would be managed by the AI.
But within this proximity,
the leader is given access
to manually fine-tune them.
And your Object at sea, they
had to make a sneak attack
or else they never would have
brought it down so easily.
First, the Intelligence Union,
then the 24th Battalion.
Sounds like developing
strategic AIs is the trend.
If they're really AIs, couldn't
we just apply the Angelina List
and bring them to a standstill?
When we fought the Rush,
the enemy's attention was
focused on the Princess.
That's the only reason why
we were able to take action,
now we don't have that luxury.
If we make any kind of move,
they'll point their guns at us.
The key thing to remember is
the five klick signal range.
Where it switches
from total AI control
to the pilot's
manual adjustments.
Outside of that range,
whatever signals they
use to control them
are no longer reliable.
But if we can get
inside that range,
we might be able to use that
signal to turn the tables.
[WYDINE]
We're a PMC, valued customer!
We have weapons, demolitions,
jamming equipment,
everything a mission
might require.
And if there's anything
you need from us, sir,
please don't hesitate to ask.
We're about to square off
against seven Objects,
including a second gen.
And their commander, Prizewell
City Slicker, is demented.
Even if we raised
the white flag,
he still might roll
right over us.
When we mobilize to strike,
there'll be no turning back.
Long as there's enough
financial compensation,
we'll do anything.
And you've more than paid
for our services in advance.
Shikibu, Iekazu!
Can you hear me?
[HUSBAND A]
Hey!
[WIFE A]
Watch out!
Shikibu!
Iekazu! Aren't you here?
[SHIKIBU]
Yes, yes, hold on a second.
I was just in the other room.
Mom, why are you here?
[AYAMI]
Is Iekazu home? And Orihime?
It's the middle
of the day, so no.
He's up at work, and
she's still in school.
[dial tone]
[AYAMI]
Useless,
I thought there might be a
chance with the landlines,
but they're still
not working either!
The phones are out, too?
The TV cut out hours ago,
but I thought they were
just doing maintenance,
but then the internet
died on me, as well.
What am I supposed to do
for my lunch recipe now?
[AYAMI] The homeland must have
shut all communications down
to prevent a panic.
They're most likely cutting
the lines down now,
starting with the
thickest cables.
[SHIKIBU] Panic? What are
you talking about Mom?
[AYAMI] Shikibu! I need you
to stay calm and listen to me.
You're the one who's
flustered, Mom.
Objects will be here soon,
to attack this city.
Huh?
[AYAMI]
The Legitimate Kingdom military
won't be able to stop them.
We've got to get out
of this city, and fast.
Before monster weapons
turn this city
into a sea of flames and ash.
[SHIKIBU]
Uh.
[radio static]
[MAINTENANCE C]
Propulsion system repairs!
I repeat, prioritize
propulsion system repairs!
Enemy formation is headed
for the immigrant
settlement as we speak!
If we fall behind now,
we'll never catch up!
What is this?!
What's happening?!
I have to let my next
door neighbors know!
I have to tell them to run!
Mother.
We don't have the time.
Once the panic starts,
traffic will freeze up
and everybody will die.
So just leave them?
[AYAMI] As long as you survive,
you can hate me for it.
I never imagined I
would do something
so cold-hearted.
That's enough. You're not
responsible for my sin.
It's my fault.
My unit was supposed to stop the
enemy before they got this far,
and we failed!
Who's closer, Iekazu or Orihime?
If I had to guess,
I'd say Iekazu!
All right, we'll go pick him
up first. You Navigate!
Mother, Shikibu told me
the gist of it. But I...
No time to discuss
this in committee!
[SHIKIBU]
Ah!
[IEKAZU]
Mother!
I refuse to sit by
and do nothing,
I won't let Orihime die while
this world tears itself apart!
[IEKAZU] Watch out! Slow down,
or we'll crash!
[AYAMI]
Be quiet, you fool!
[SHIKIBU, IEKAZU screaming]
Iekazu! Get Orihime!
And if any of the staff try to
get in your way, show them this.
Just don't pull the
charging handle back.
If the chamber stays empty,
it can't discharge a round.
[IEKAZU]
Uh...
[AYAMI] Now bring her
here as quickly as you can!
Move it!
[IEKAZU panting]
[explosion]
It's over I didn't
make it in time.
But Mother...
We're already within range
of their main guns.
It can't be.
I failed.
I'm sorry. I wasn't fast enough.
[radio static]
[HAVIA]
Hey, Granny, you still alive?
Galahad is on the scene!
You know, Qwenthur.
This thankless job just
keeps taking and taking.
Just cause we've beaten
an Object or two before,
doesn't make tackling seven at
a time a reasonable request!
[QWENTHUR]
Just relax, Havia.
This is our moment
in the spotlight.
Let's knock it out of
the park one more time,
and end up heroes again.
So, business as usual,
in other words.
And then we'll chalk
up another victory
to the mighty
Qwenthur Barbotage.
Not without you.
You always grumble, but you've
saved my life countless times!
You two? What're you doing here?
[QWENTHUR] I can't let you
go and die on me, Granny.
There's still far too much
technical knowledge
I need to learn
from watching you
in your element.
The loss of such a
talented engineer,
it would hinder me from
achieving my dreams.
And besides.
He can't stand to see the
Princess sulking over you.
She says can't get motivated
unless you're the one
doing her maintenance.
Thank you, boys.
[QWENTHUR]
We're about to engage
the 24th Mechanized
Maintenance Battalion.
The objective of our mission
is to defend the immigrant
settlement from attack!
Demolish anything
that stands in our way!
[ALL]
Consider it done, sir!
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA] "You Can't
Put a Price on Honor."
[MILINDA] "The Critical Running
Battle on Victoria Island III."