[QWENTHUR] The large carriers
of old were designed
to be capable of maintaining
70 to 80 aircraft at a time.
However, it's only on
rare occasion these days
that calls for the need
for so many aircraft.
So the nature of the carriers'
missions has greatly changed.
That's right.
Another change to accommodate
the world of Objects.
[FROLAYTIA] Captain, we
appreciate your assistance
on this operation.
[CAPTAIN A]
Of course.
It's a nice change
of pace for us
to have the opportunity
to move a landing ship.
The days of overseeing delivery
of aircraft to battlefields
are over. Now our primary duty
is facilitating the maintenance
of Objects at sea.
And to provide
security and defense
during those repairs, of course.
The world is certainly
a different place
than the one I came up in.
[QWENTHUR gasping]
[AYAMI] Ya can't get
any work done clinging
to your safety line
with both hands.
[QWENTHUR]
Uh?
What's the point of
climbing up here
if all you're gonna do is whine?
[QWENTHUR]
What do you expect?!
We're so high up and
the scaffolding's shaky!
And why am I the only person
bothering to wear
a safety line?!
[AYAMI] 'Cause there's no reason
to attach your safety line
unless you're in actual danger.
I don't see how this is a skill
that a future designer needs.
Uh? What's that up there?
Oh, that? It's a mini
fridge and a microwave.
They're goin' in the cockpit.
[QWENTHUR]
Uh... A fridge and a microwave?!
Wait, no fair!
The only rations we
get look like erasers!
But now the Princess gets to
eat casseroles and hamburgers
and fried chicken?
It's perfectly fair.
The course of a battle depends
on the power of
her concentration.
So call it professional
courtesy.
But that means the Princess
can heat up some fried chicken
whenever she feels like it,
and eat fried chicken anytime
she wants fried chicken!
Fried chicken!
[sighs]
So, care to tell me about this
enemy you're in pursuit of?
Sure. We're after the
Mass Driver Foundation.
I imagine the name
should ring a bell.
[QWENTHUR] It's life and death
just doing maintenance.
By the way, what's the
Mass Driver Foundation?
[HAVIA]
Context clues, dude.
They're a corporation
of fat cats
with the best Mass Driver
construction tech in the world.
Frolaytia sure is
taking this seriously.
She's putting more time than
usual into the logistics.
Are they really that dangerous?
[MILINDA] Well, It's a
tangled up political mess
in a lot of ways.
[QWENTHUR]
U-Uh!
[HAVIA] Why are you sunbathing
in your combat suit?
Keep explaining.
Uh. Oh, right.
They used to be part of
the Capital Enterprise,
focused on the rate business.
But recently, they started
investing their capital
like crazy in cutting
edge companies.
Ones that were conducting
promising R &amp; D on technology
required for Mass Drivers.
[QWENTHUR]
Mm.
In case you're not familiar
with mass drivers,
they're like giant rail guns
aimed straight toward the stars.
But instead of ammo,
they fire shuttles and
containers up into orbit.
It's supposedly more efficient
than space shuttles.
Yup, yup.
That suit looks hot...
Uh! So uh, why is this mega
rich foundation our enemy?
None of that sounds
out of the ordinary.
Well, they basically went rogue.
They rebelled and broke off
from the Capital Enterprise.
The whole thing was handled
like a coup d'état.
[MILINDA]
They're apparently executing
a massive stealth migration
of their people to keep the
Capital Enterprise government
from seizing their assets.
[HAVIA] And it's rumored
they've got their own Object
stashed away somewhere.
Which would make them
ready to wage war.
[QWENTHUR] Okay, but why
would they even bother?
[HAVIA] It's the result of a
simple tech adoption skirmish.
[QWENTHUR]
And what does that mean?
[HAVIA] The shuttle's
expensive to operate.
To solve that
massive cost issue,
people have been looking for
a suitable replacement
for a long time.
The two options that were
deemed the most viable
were the Mass Driver method and
the Orbital Elevator method,
which utilizes laser technology.
Trouble was...
[MILINDA]
The Capital Enterprise
ended up going with
the orbital elevator.
The Mass Driver
Foundation panicked.
They tried to get the
Intelligence Union
and the Faith Organization
to adopt their tech,
but the Capital
Enterprise interfered.
There's no way in hell
they were gonna let other
world powers profit
from their own
homegrown technology.
So they boxed 'em
in on all sides.
I guess they were feeling
kinda claustrophobic
'cause they blew their top.
These guys don't negotiate.
It's likely to be all-out war.
And it won't be easy for us.
I'd recommend preparing yourself
as much as possible.
Huh. Then I'm gonna have to
get me some fried chicken
Come on!
I'm talking to you about
a potential war here
and all you can think
about is fried chicken!
What? Think about it.
Are you telling me you
don't want a hot, crunchy,
greasy drumstick
battered to perfection?
With just a bit of
lemon for zest--
Cut it out!
You know I love lemon zestiness!
Oh, what have you done, I can
feel the craving taking hold!
[MILINDA]
Then go get some.
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR]
Huh?
[MILINDA] This carrier that
we're on, the Charlemagne,
had its fifteenth
anniversary today.
There's all kinds
of food leftover
from the big celebration
party they had.
[QWENTHUR]
We're too late!
The party's already over, man!
Not so fast, Qwenthur!
There's not much but
there's still food!
Nice!
It's cold.
[BOTH]
Don't you judge us!
[FROLAYTIA]
Too late for that.
I should've known you'd
sniff out the food.
She always beats us
to the good food.
I guess just add that
to the list of reasons
to follow her around.
Time to eat!
Right!
[QWENTHUR]
Nuggets?
They've only got nuggets?!
Damn it, so close!
That still counts as
fried chicken, right?
I want bone-in,
not processed lumps!
[FROLAYTIA]
If you want fried chicken,
there's some right here.
[BOTH]
Uh?!
Aw, Miss Frolaytia!
You are the best!
Yum!
It's gotten cold and a little
bit too soggy from the juice,
but it's still delicious!
I wish there was
some lemon zestiness,
but heym I'm not complaining!
Hey. You know pole dancing?
Like how strippers
dangle from a pole?
[QWENTHUR] Well that really
came out of nowhere.
Why the hell'd you
bring that up?
Do you know how it works?
[QWENTHUR] Well, yeah.
It's pretty simple.
They just wrap around
the pole and contort.
[HAVIA]
No, that's not what I meant.
[FROLAYTIA]
If you want specifics.
The body's basically held in
whatever position you want
by the friction
between the brass pole
and the person's skin.
To give you an example...
[FROLAYTIA]
It goes...
[BOTH]
Oh, wow!
[FROLAYTIA]
A little, like, this.
That's incredible!
How did you get so
good at doing that?
[FROLAYTIA] There's been
a few victory parties
after some successful missions
where I had to display
a hidden talent.
[FROLAYTIA] Uh! Also,
the soldiers on-site
seem to get more motivated
whenever I do this.
You're normally supposed to
do it with bare legs though.
[QWENTHUR] Yeah, but the
stockings ain't too bad.
Watching her wrap herself
around a pole like that,
she could be wearing a
potato sack for all I care!
Our Princess over there's
not too shabby with
the pole, either.
[BOTH]
What?
I can try.
Oh, man, with her slender frame.
It'll be a completely
different viewing experience
than with Frolaytia.
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR scream]
[QWENTHUR]
C-C-Cold!
[HAVIA]
What the hell?
This is NOT how it's
supposed to work!
Here's a question...
What is the Mass Driver
Foundation getting out of this?
Why the hell would they
try to hijack a satellite
from a probe robot in Antarctica
to attack a vacation
resort on the moon?
I was planning to cover this in
the briefing we have scheduled,
but now is fine.
They were targeting
the Capital Enterprise
major general at the resort.
He was in charge of overseeing
their military satellites
and stations.
And he was a staunch
advocate for laser-driven
orbital elevators instead
of mass drivers.
They were looking for payback?
This all sounds like
one big power struggle
within the Capital Enterprise.
Wouldn't it be better
if the Legitimate Kingdom
didn't get involved?
[FROLAYTIA] Well that's
not really an option.
The Foundation is in the middle
of a massive migration effort.
They're frantically
high-tailing it
to the Iguazú region
of South America.
[gasps] If I remember correctly,
there's a Legitimate Kingdom
space science base there.
And our launch system
is the laser method.
Yup.
And the last thing that we need
is them targeting us
like the lunar resort.
So this war is about
protecting ourselves?
All there is to it.
Prepare to commence Iguazú
Region Beach Landing!
Your objective...
Annihilate the Mass
Driver Foundation,
which we expect to make
an inland incursion.
Time to move out, Qwenthur.
We've gotta wait
for the Princess
to lockdown the coastline.
Then, it's our turn.
[QWENTHUR]
Mm.
Have we got any
intelligence confirming
the Mass Driver
Foundation's Object yet?
[FROLAYTIA] We were able
to confirm a giant shadow,
but it could be a dummy,
like in Oceania.
Okay, but we do have
their location, right?
[FROLAYTIA] Honestly,
we're uncertain on that.
The Andes Mountains have an
elevation of over 6,000 meters.
And they're filled
with mines, too.
The southeast trade winds
coming off the Pacific
are crazy this year,
and there's mineral dust
drifting inland with the clouds.
Which is the long way of
saying that our satellites
aren't really much use to us.
[FROLAYTIA]
Well, wherever they are,
it's important to keep
in mind that mass drivers
are built to shoot into orbit.
We cannot let their main
guns score a direct hit.
And what is she
expecting us to do?
Oh, you'll want to be prepared
for the secondary
shock waves as well.
Do what you can to guard
your ears and internal organs.
It's been a while,
Major Frolaytia Capistrano.
Well, look at this.
[WORKERS chattering]
[QWENTHUR]
Say, Havia,
why can't we just stand
by at sea for a change?
Seriously?
The battlefield is inland.
How can the Princess land
if the tech team doesn't
take those floats off?
I guess there's no
getting out of it, then.
[MILINDA]
I am bored out of my mind.
[QWENTHUR] Waiting's better
than killing, right?
[MILINDA] No, waiting for
you people is killing me.
[sighs]
[QWENTHUR]
Uh?
[MILINDA]
Hey, Qwenthur,
are you still trying to decide
on your Object research topic?
How about you come up with
some new propulsion method
that lets you move from land to
sea without exchanging parts?
Geez, Sounds like the Princess
is in a pissy mood, huh?
[MILINDA] I just got a request
to take part in a mock battle.
Well, it was more of an
order than a request.
They're holding it in
Normandy one month from now.
[HAVIA] Oh, right in the heart
of the Legitimate Kingdom.
Should be a good
performance, right?
[MILINDA] Not if you're
the designated fall guy.
Have either of you ever
heard of the Bright Hopper?
[QWENTHUR]
Think so.
It was pitched as the
Legitimate Kingdom's
next cutting edge Object, right?
It's supposed to be equipped
with an intensive array
of laser beam weaponry.
Are you saying that
it's been completed?
[HAVIA]
Not only that,
but the Elite Pilot is the
eldest son of a prominent noble.
What's the problem?
You just gotta fight sloppy
and take a dive, right?
[MILINDA]
It's not that simple.
If I lose that easily, the media
will analyze the numbers
on the spec sheets and
say that the Baby Magnum
should've been able to
put up more of a fight.
Oh, wow.
Setting you up to fail.
And in front of everyone.
I'm thinking about
changing it up,
and at the last minute
fighting as hard as I can.
[gasps] Scan of pertinent
area complete.
Metal detected at multiple
points throughout the mountains.
Wait, did you say
multiple points?
[COMM OFFICER A]
Come in, Baby Magnum.
This is the Charlemagne.
Our analytic reports
show the mountains
contain large
deposits of iron ore.
Something to consider
in your assessment.
[MILINDA]
So, that's what's showing.
But... how do I know?
[COMM OFFICER A] Our current
satellite feeds haven't found
any sign of armored vehicles
or infantry in the area.
[MILINDA exhales]
You heard the man.
But, are you sure?
[MILINDA grunts] We've got the
go ahead so we're going ahead.
[QWENTHUR]
How about this?
If you're so positive
the metal being detected
isn't a hidden barrage
of gun batteries,
then you'll have no problem
making a Bavarian cream mold
of your boobs if you're wrong.
In a live presentation
of course.
[MILINDA]
No response.
Looks like the coast
really is clear.
[QWENTHUR]
I'm holding you
to that Bavarian
cream mold if it's not.
[FROLAYTIA] Quit clogging
the channel with chit-chat.
I'm giving the go ahead based
on the Princess's report.
All personnel, take the
hydrofoils to the shore.
Construct the base zone.
Remove the floats from the
Object for inland maneuvers.
Did you see those
flashes up there?
[SOLDIERS scream]
[QWENTHUR]
Ha, ha! Bavarian cream!
[HAVIA]
Why are you celebrating?!
We're getting shot
at, you dumb ass!
[QWENTHUR groaning]
[HAVIA]
This sucks!
A little help, Princess?
[FROLAYTIA]
Continue to make for shore.
You'll be just fine as
long as you don't die.
Did you hear that sadistic glee?
It's almost like she gets
off on ordering us to die!
And you seem to get off on
her giving you that order,
so you two really would
make the perfect couple.
So you think any of
this heavy firepower
is coming from the Mass
Driver Foundation's Object?
Nah. It's probably
just like Antartica
where they're using spare object
guns mounted on the slopes!
[FROLAYTIA]
No electromagnetic readings
or human heat sources.
So there's no threat
of civilian casualties.
You're clear to blast
those mountains to hell!
[HAVIA] How's it okay to
blow away a foreign shore
we've got no jurisdiction over?
[QWENTHUR] Yeah, who
is the Iguazú territory
affiliated with?
[HAVIA]
They're unaffiliated.
It's one of those
weird blank zones.
No political power
has claimed it.
Don't even have their
own government.
[QWENTHUR] And here come
two random world powers
to invade their land
and blow the crap
out of their mountain
range with Objects.
I can't see how the locals
would like us very much.
[HAVIA]
That's not just here.
I don't think any country wants
to be a battlefield for Objects.
[radio static]
[SOLDIER A]
Platoon Charlie.
No enemy combatants discovered.
All we've found are rail
guns buried in the soil,
connected to thick power cables.
Platoon Hotel: It's
all clear on our end.
[FROLAYTIA]
Platoons Echo through Hotel.
Expand the search radius to five
clicks and continue looking.
The rest of the platoons
will head back to shore
and construct the base zones.
No baths or beds without a
base so you better get to it.
[QWENTHUR] At least
we didn't get assigned
to constructing the base zone.
[HAVIA] You say that now,
but knowing our luck,
we'll stumble into the Mass
Driver Object any second.
You don't happen to know why
this area's called
the Iguazú, do you?
It's named after
the Iguazú River,
one of the biggest in the world.
Look at this.
No sign of an Object
passing through anywhere.
Doesn't make sense.
Platoon Hotel here.
We've investigated
the area as directed,
but haven't seen any indication
of the Mass Driver Foundation
Good work everyone.
We have a little bit
of time to figure out
what our next move will be.
I guess I'll grant you
the rare privilege
of sitting down to rest.
Enjoy a nice long break.
Relax and get your stamina back.
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA]
Ah...
[QWENTHUR] This is not
helping my stamina.
[HAVIA]
Hey, Qwenthur.
Where do you think they could be
hiding that Mass Driver Object?
Let's see.
I was looking at the map earlier
and there's a coal
mine around here.
Don't know if it's big enough to
hide a 50m-class Object, though.
But it's not like we ever
managed to find the Object
in Antarctica that was
supplying the power.
I wonder...
Could they really
have a Stealth Object
that can't be detected by radar?
--[footsteps]
--Huh?
[HAVIA]
Over here, Qwenthur.
I just somehow managed
to get invited to tea
by an elderly farmer couple.
[QWENTHUR] Tea in the
middle of a battlefield?!
[HAVIA] Well, it's not
a battlefield to them,
it's their land. Their daughter
and her husband don't visit much
so they seem kind of lonely.
You are being way too chill,
they need to evacuate!
Sure, of course,
right after tea.
C'mon, man, just relax.
Unless you'd rather
eat those rations.
They're not drinking coffee?
Look dude, you can
have tea or styrofoam.
[QWENTHUR]
Holy crud.
This is like a beautiful
vision of world peace.
War really does get in the
way of all the nice things.
--[radio static]
--[BOTH] Uh?
[HALREED]
Legitimate Kingdom,
37th Mechanized
Maintenance Battalion.
This is Major
Halreed Copacabana.
Legitimate Kingdom,
52nd Mechanized
Maintenance Battalion.
[HAVIA]
Aw, crap.
[QWENTHUR chuckles]
What does Halreed want?
Who's that?
He's the Bright
Hopper Elite Pilot,
and also a member
of the nobility.
The one the Princess
is getting forced into
the mock battle with?
[HALREED] Your battallion's
coming from the Amazon region?
We'll plot a course through
Central America to rendezvous.
It would be optimal
if we could team up
to vanquish the Mass Drivers.
Would that be feasible
with our schedule?
[FROLAYTIA] This is Major
Frolaytia Capistrano speaking.
I've confirmed your
plotted course of travel.
I'm worried it's too far.
Your cooperation would be
a boon to the mission,
but if we can't wait
we must commence with the
operation as scheduled.
[HALREED]
Roger that.
Pity.
That leaves me no choice
but to hope for your failure
in destroying the
Mass Driver Object.
That would force it
to flee northward
where we will then
finish it off.
Is it just me, or is he
demanding we wound it
and leave the final blow to him?
[FROLAYTIA]
Unfortunately, unlike the 52nd,
we don't have the
surplus manpower
to chase it around the country.
If we have the chance
to kill it, we will.
I'm sorry to let you down, but
I hope you won't be too upset.
[HALREED] Frolaytia, if you
want my personal opinion,
I would advise that you
meekly accept my wishes.
Public and private.
What the hell was that?
They've actually got some
history with each other.
But it doesn't sound like
Frolaytia's very
happy she knows him.
Ya know?
[QWENTHUR]
It's weird to hear Frolaytia
let someone get
to her like that.
[HAVIA]
No kidding.
This has that distinct air
of aristocratic nastiness.
I guess the beautiful
noblewoman's
got troubles of her own.
Hold on, Miss
Frolaytia's nobility?
[HAVIA]
Yeah, it's common knowledge.
Uh, to who?
[FROLAYTIA]
Qwenthur. Havia.
Change of plans.
Get back to the base,
double time.
I want to settle
this mission quickly
before the Bright
Hopper can interfere.
They're not screwing
up our operation.
Oh, you will be a
fun one to tame.
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA]
"Three-Legged Mountain-Climbing
Is Life-and-Death".
[MILINDA] "The Artillery Battle
in the Iguazú Mountains II".