[HAVIA] Seems like they
should've changed the name
of this place to the
Tanami Jungle by now.
[QWENTHUR] It's that whole
GMO fertilization deal.
They can grow an entire forest
in as little as two years.
We should try to
pick up the pace.
That Half-Gen's gotta be
around here somewhere.
Let's find it before they set
off the trap in the Great Sandy.
--[rumbling]
--[HAVIA gasps]
What's happening?!
An earthquake?
[BOTH yelp]
Yeah, prob'ly not
an earthquake.
Let's hurry.
[HAVIA]
Yeah.
[alarm blares]
Hey, so, um...
I think this might
be the dummy plant.
And here it comes.
I really wish Frolaytia
had made that bet.
Yeah, right?
We managed to hunt
down their Half-Gen.
[QWENTHUR]
Their one and only Object.
That cable?
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps] Hit the dirt!
[BOTH groaning]
Did they spot us?
Oh, dude, we are
freakin' dead men!
[QWENTHUR]
No. They weren't aiming for us.
They're just doing some
shakedown testing.
You're sayin' that
was just a test?
Doesn't matter how obsolete that
thing is, it's still an Object.
Destruction follows in its wake.
[QWENTHUR groans]
But we made it in time.
Now let's stop these creeps
before their massacre begins.
'Kay, why're they just
going in circles?
[QWENTHUR] It's been at least
two years since they've
fired it up. They're
doing warm-up exercises.
Gotcha, touch your toes and turn
the coil gun from side to side.
[QWENTHUR] All right.
We've found its location.
Now we just gotta destroy it.
Hold on, dude.
I know it's old but aren't you
taking this kinda lightly?
Don't tell me you're planning
on charging it with Hand Axe.
Give me a little more
credit than that.
[QWENTHUR]
Attention allied forces
invading the Oceanian
Military State.
Uh!
[QWENTHUR] We have a
sighting of the enemy Object
at a hydroponics base
in the Tanami Desert.
I repeat. We have a
confirmed sighting
of the enemy Object
in the Tanami Desert.
[OPERATOR A]
Signal ID registers
as Legitimate Kingdom, ma'am.
Then it is Qwenthur Barbotage.
The LK's vaunted
Object-killing Boy Hero.
[QWENTHUR] None of their
technology has been upgraded
beyond the Half-Gen level.
A single blast from one of
our Objects will put it down.
Requesting backup.
From any force.
Just please send an Object.
It's first come, first served.
Better hurry or we're
gonna have to keep
all the medals for
ourselves again.
I'm on my way, Qwenthur!
[FLIDE] No reinforcements will
be sent to the Tanami Desert.
This is a direct order.
[gasps]
[radio static]
What's happening?
Our signal's being jammed.
[HAVIA]
Huh?
Let me repeat.
No reinforcements are to be
sent to the Tanami Desert.
These men, Hayvia and Qwenthur,
are acting on their own
initiative, based on
incorrect intelligence.
That can't be true!
[OHOHO laughs]
Do you make a habit
of ignoring your superior
officer's orders?
Councilor Flide is the CO of
the Legitimate Kingdom forces.
You have no allegiance to him.
What do you care
about his orders?
[OHOHO] Oh-ho! You're right,
I don't, although...
I have been given
specific orders
that are unfortunate for you.
I was instructed to
thoroughly inspect
the Legitimate Kingdom's
Object, you see.
Now, I could easily accomplish
this fighting side by side.
But I could also learn plenty
by picking a fight with you.
[laughs]
[static]
Damn it!
Now they've blocked us entirely!
Like an old geezer's bowels.
--[click]
--[BOTH gasp]
[FLIDE] Oh, Qwenthur and
Havia, my dear boys.
That voice.
Yeah, it's Councilor Flide.
I'm afraid the two
of you have deviated
from our carefully plotted path.
Your plotted path, huh?
Are you telling me
we've screwed up
your election campaign
or something?
War has become rather
straightforward these days.
Simply knowing the
quantity and quality
of your enemy's Objects is
enough to determine the outcome.
"Well, we have one Object,
but they have three.
There's no point in fighting,
so we better surrender."
It was more or less
an accepted system
that allowed ones
opponent to give up.
[HAVIA]
A faulty system at best.
Just take a look at the
current predicament.
Oceania's got no intention
of surrendering.
[FLIDE] That's no
one's fault but yours.
What?
[FLIDE] The boy heroes
Qwenthur and Havia.
You've proven miracles
are possible.
And you've unleashed hell
on earth as a result.
And you want us dead so things
go back to the way they were.
If we get slaughtered
by an Object,
that's all the proof you need
miracles are not possible!
[FLIDE]
We have to crush this idea
that humans can defeat Objects.
Your accomplishments in
battle have only served
to inspire guerillas
and terrorists.
They're now emboldened to wage
their wars even without Objects.
We must have
Standards of Practice.
But your reckless
dismissal of protocol
is prolonging these wars
and increasing the number
of needless deaths.
[smack]
[QWENTHUR] That's a load
of crap and you know it!
If you allow us to die here,
that Object will kill
thousands of villagers.
Are you really gonna tell me
those aren't "needless deaths?"
You coward!
You're just protecting
your own interests!
Everyone knows the countries
with the most Objects
hold all the power,
and you want it
to stay that way!
[FLIDE] Go on and
believe what you'd like.
Hm. You'll be dead soon
so it hardly matters.
After the Half-Gen successfully
attacks the village,
it'll come under fire
from our Objects
and the war will be over.
The balance will be restored.
The world will realize Objects
are the only controlling factor.
Oh, you think so?
Then how 'bout a wager?
If the Half-Gen is able to wipe
us out, the world can be yours.
But if we can get to
the Half-Gen first,
you admit you're finished.
[FLIDE]
Hmph.
The bastard hung up.
I couldn't even deliver
a parting shot.
I guess that means we shouldn't
expect any reinforcements.
[HAVIA]
Guess not. Wanna turn back?
What, give up and
just let the Princess
and the others fall
for an obvious trap?
Sure, and we can just stand back
and let all the villagers
get massacred.
We could.
Or we could make sure
none of that happens.
Yeah. Besides, nothing's
gonna kill me
until I've punched
Flide's teeth in.
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH scream]
Holy crap. Think
they spotted us?
Maybe they picked up
our walkies. Or, um--
Who cares how?!
Let's get outta here!
[QWENTHUR]
Havia! The missile!
You know that's not gonna do
jack squat against an Object!
We're running, damn it!
Listen to me!
Aim it right there!
Guessing there's not enough
time for an explanation?
Nice! We made a blind spot!
Okay, good plan.
We're clear to get away now!
Great thinkin'! We're saved!
Wrong way, man!
[HAVIA gasps]
You mean we're not running?
[QWENTHUR]
That's what they're expecting.
It'll be safer if we
do the opposite.
You can't be serious.
Hiding right under their
asses now, are we?
[QWENTHUR]
It's right under their noses.
[HAVIA]
I know the damn saying!
You make me sound like an idiot
when you correct me like that!
[HAVIA]
Hey!
Damn it!
Wait for me, hero!
[QWENTHUR]
'Kay maybe not just a test.
That'll wipe out any of our side
who didn't retreat in time.
[HAVIA]
I'm glad I listened to you.
If we'd fled into those trees,
we would've been
burnt to a crisp.
But if we stay here, they'll
still find us eventually.
[HAVIA]
Whadaya think the odds are
that backup will arrive
before they find us?
[QWENTHUR]
Nil, I'd say.
Not after Flide's transmission.
Only ones who can
save us, is us.
Damn you, Flide, chicken!
I say we get inside the hangar.
Maybe we can find the Object
schematics or something.
[QWENTHUR]
It's so quiet.
There's not a sign of anyone.
[HAVIA] There hasn't
been this whole time.
There are usually
soldiers running around
to guard the Object,
but not here.
Ugh.
You smell that?
[QWENTHUR]
Yeah. How could I not?
Some kinda burning stench.
[gasps] Dude, wait.
[gasps]
Well, this explains
the lack of soldiers.
They've all been
reduced to ashes.
There was an alarm sounding
when we got here.
Now we know why.
[QWENTHUR]
This is terrible.
They were electrocuted.
[HAVIA]
Seriously?
[QWENTHUR]
I'm guessing they tried to use
an electrical booster to
raise the core temperature
of the Half-Gen's
power reactor.
It's basically the opposite
of the plug system
the Intelligence
Union's Object uses.
[HAVIA]
Oh, man.
So, the emperor tried
on his new clothes,
then let out a fart that
killed all his men.
Talk about tragic.
But this could give us
our chance to win.
How?
[QWENTHUR] That's a
weakness we can exploit.
[QWENTHUR] Ordinarily, when it's
supplied with surplus power,
it should be built to discharge
that power externally.
So I'm guessing the mechanism's
not working too well.
Y'know, considering all of
these soldiers are dead.
All we need to do
is send another massive surge
of electricity into the Object.
[HAVIA]
Right, that should be enough
to make the power
reactor go haywire.
[gasps] You get no sympathy.
Your dictator caused this war,
and you picked your side.
There's a real thin line
between victim and offender.
Hell yeah.
This condenser's still alive.
[HAVIA] Hey man, I
found the part we need.
So the only question now is how
are we gonna connect
it to the Half-Gen.
[QWENTHUR]
I saw a forklift outside.
Maybe we can use that.
[HAVIA]
Use it how?
[QWENTHUR] By remote
control or something?
You don't seriously think
it can be that easy.
Oh, just get it, will ya?
C'mon, thinking on our feet
is our specialty, right?
I'm pretty sure most people
would call it
frantic scrambling.
[HAVIA panting]
[HAVIA]
Oh, man.
Why can't we at least have
a reconnaissance drone?
[gasps]
[grunts] Qwenthur, no!
[HAVIA panting]
You better not be
dead, you jerk.
[QWENTHUR]
Havia.
Get out of here.
Oh, you lucky bastard!
[QWENTHUR whimpering]
[QWENTHUR]
I'm stuck. I can't move.
There's no way in hell I'm
letting you give up that easily!
You can die after we
knock Flide's teeth out!
I'm doing this.
The game's live or die,
and it's time to play!
Havia, what're you...?
Here's hoping it's still blind
from the mud on its left side.
Hey, Emperor Gasbag!
Have a big fat taste
of your own fart!
[HAVIA screams]
[HAVIA grunting]
[QWENTHUR]
Havia!
What do I do?
Was Flide actually right?
Flesh and blood humans
defeating Objects...
was it nothing more than
a couple of flukes?
Wait, the water tower...
[HAVIA] Destroy the evidence
and eliminate the intruders.
You really do like
multi-tasking.
[QWENTHUR]
Havia, can you move?
Climb the water tower!
Right away!
What? Why?
Because this facility's
not just for camouflage.
It's a fully operational
hydroponics plant as well.
[yells]
Qwenthur.
The cable may not've
been long enough.
So we'll have to use something
else as a conductor.
[FROLAYTIA]
Attention, fellow soldiers,
we've just received
a satellite report.
[gasps]
And I'm pleased to announce,
the enemy Object is destroyed.
The pilot and supreme commander
of the Oceanian forces
have been terminated.
Major, what should I do?
[FROLAYTIA] The Baby Magnum
is to head to the Tanami
and rescue our men.
[MILINDA]
Uh!
You made a promise, right?
[FROLAYTIA] Now that our
target has been dealt with,
we'll shift the objective of our
forces to a cleanup operation.
The situation's changed.
We can't well shoot them
in the back now, can we?
[laughs] Understandable.
I've found something
more interesting anyway.
More than that outdated
Object, at least.
Hey, buddy. You still alive?
[QWENTHUR]
Yeah, barely.
Ha, ha. Well,
aren't we tenacious?
Hey we can't die, yet.
Not until we've turned Flide's
face into ground meat.
Damn straight.
[SECRETARY A] The facility's
been invaded by an Object.
It's the Baby Magnum.
It's a First Gen, right?
Send our Second Gen to greet it.
Make it look like an
accident during testing.
When an Object
takes evasive action,
it's not dodging the actual
mortar rounds being fired.
It analyzes the aiming process
and preparatory maneuvers
in order to preemptively
evade the attacks.
But the main gun of
the Second Gen Object,
the Exact Javelin, perfectly
conceals its strategic movements
with a randomizing algorithm,
and furthermore,
it warps light with
polarizing wires.
[MILINDA]
No! It's homing in on me!
Damn, no good.
I can't get a target lock.
No Object can possibly
evade the Exact Javelin.
[FROLAYTIA]
Excuse me, sir.
I'm here regarding
the orders given
during the invasion of Oceania.
Who let her through?
I'm rather busy.
Someone sicced a hussy on me and
I'm trying to dispose of her.
I'd like to confirm
something with you
for the report I'm
putting together.
It's in regards to
the transmission
that you willfully interfered
with when my men discovered
the enemy Object in
the Tanami Desert.
[FLIDE] I doubt that
a commanding officer
such as yourself would
understand this,
but it's due to the fact
that Objects reign supreme
that the wars in our
world can be handled
in such a safe and
efficient manner.
And the existence of your
two men upsets that balance.
I made a tough choice
for our safety.
The safety of not just our
country but the entire world.
[FROLAYTIA] You can keep
yapping all you want.
I don't give a damn.
You see, I'm the type of CO who
goes out of her way to take care
of the brats who've got families
waiting for them back home.
I don't care about
your excuses.
A bastard like you?
You deserve to be put down,
right here and right now.
[FLIDE]
Do you realize the clout I have
with the police and
the government?
You honestly think
a mere on-site CO
could level a verdict
against a Councilor?
[FROLAYTIA] That's why
I'm court martialing you.
If it's related to the military,
we can bring a verdict against
you in our playing field.
[FLIDE]
Mm.
You sent your
transmission to both
the Legitimate Kingdom forces
and the Allied Forces,
and that was a big mistake.
The IU and the other
countries involved,
they're all demanding
an explanation
concerning this operation.
I already told you.
It's the people who
control the Objects
who also control the world.
Polarization is warping
your line of fire.
Your lasers are fine.
I've nailed down the pattern.
Here comes the data.
It'll be okay, Princess.
I know you can do this.
That thing may have
experience in years,
but I'm the one with
experience in combat.
[SECRETARY A] Sir. The Exact
Javelin has been destroyed!
Ejection of Elite confirmed.
[FLIDE] Impossible!
Against a measly First Ge--
[HAVIA sighs]
You do remember our bet?
[FLIDE whimpers]
Our deal was,
if we lost to the Half-Gen,
the world was yours.
But hey, we won, so I guess
that means you're finished.
I have supporters
in the military!
You'll come to regret this!
[QWENTHUR]
Doubt it!
Uh!
This world of yours
where the strongest
are always the ones who win,
where the side with the most
power always comes out on top.
That world can go screw itself!
Well spoken, partner.
Now then, you're coming with us.
[FLIDE growls]
[QWENTHUR sighs]
Nice win today, Princess.
With your help, Qwenthur?
[QWENTHUR]
Huh?
I won't lose.
Ever.
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR]
"In an Obstacle Course Race,
It's Normal to Get
Covered in Mud".
[MILINDA] "The Battle for
Supremacy in Antarctica".