[HAVIA]
Qwenthur!
Hey! Look!
Are you ready to leave yet?
[HAVIA]
Here, check it.
That nice ol' lady gave us
some cookies for the road.
I feel like we should be
pushing them to evacuate.
[HAVIA]
It's no use, man.
This is their home.
They said nothing's gonna
make them leave it behind.
[QWENTHUR]
Well, in that case,
we should at least get as far
away from here as we can.
The battlefield is
basically wherever we go
so that should help
keep them safe.
Thanks.
So, hey.
What do you know about
this Bright Hopper Object?
How powerful is it?
[QWENTHUR] It's a 2nd
gen ground combat unit.
Rumor has it that not even three
Baby Magnums could beat it.
It maintains a
constant high speed
of 7 to 800 clicks per hour.
[QWENTHUR] Not only that, but
it's a Specialized Object,
which means all of its
main guns are lasers.
Essentially, it's a
laser-spitting hurricane
on the battlefield.
It strikes at
super-high speeds,
firing a barrage of multi-sized
lasers at its opponent's legs,
completely incapacitating them.
Then finishes it off
with one high output laser
shot from its main guns.
[HALREED]
Only those lacking in honor
have the option of running away.
The Legitimate Kingdom's nobles
are men of great pride.
We attack head-on at full speed,
and reduce our enemy
to a pile of ash.
We've received some new intel.
It's been confirmed that chaff
missiles have been fired.
They were launched
from 50 clicks north,
in Paraná's mountainous region.
What are chaff missiles?
[FROLAYTIA]
When they explode,
they seed the clouds
with fine particles,
creating a shield
against laser sensors.
Our satellite's surveillance
network is currently useless.
[QWENTHUR]
But wouldn't that mean
the Mass Driver Foundation's
main force is somewhere
in the vicinity from
where they launched?
Why risk us tracking their
location like that? Y'know?
They're prob'ly more concerned
with hiding their Object
from our spy satellites.
Now they've got time to escape.
Yeah, that could be it.
But what was supplying power
to those rail guns on
the mountains earlier?
Maybe they're not just trying
to disable the satellites,
maybe there's more to it.
There could be some other
practical reason beyond fleeing.
Maybe...
[HALREED chuckles]
[HALREED]
Chaff Missiles?
So they plan to hide?
I would expect no less from
such a group of cowards.
Though it doesn't matter
in the slightest
how advanced their Object is.
With a single burst
of glorious light,
I shall cut them dow--
[gasps]
[QWENTHUR]
Whoa, what the hell?!
[COMM OFFICER A]
Charlemagne to all units!
The Bright Hopper has
taken heavy damage
while en route to our
location! I repeat.
The Bright Hopper has
taken heavy damage...
Hold on a sec!
That's a mountainous region.
Did they blow away the mountains
in between to hit it?
[FROLAYTIA] It was a
high-angle trajectory.
They fired the rail gun
at a sharp upward angle
and let the round fall.
[COMM OFFICER A]
Major. It's unconfirmed
as to whether Major Copacabana
successfully ejected.
There's no trace of an
emergency distress beacon.
They cannot be serious.
That much damage from one shot?
[COMM OFFICER A] The Bright
Hopper's power reactor
appears to be destroyed.
The estimated velocity
of the shell...
is Mach 25?!
What?! Impossible!
Mach 25 would launch the
shell straight into space
without ever coming back down!
[FROLAYTIA] They must
have somehow modified
the artillery shells in order
to bend the trajectory.
That's the only explanation.
The scale is off the charts.
Those chaff missiles
they fired...
they weren't fleeing.
They were using them to conceal
the timing of their shelling.
We're dead if they get
us in their sights.
A shell flying at us at Mach 25?
There's no dodging that.
How was it even possible
for them to zero in
so accurately from
that distance?
Well, considering that
they used chaff missiles,
we know they weren't relying
on military satellites.
So how could they...?
Hold on.
They're using the clouds.
[HAVIA]
How?
[QWENTHUR]
The chaff missiles create clouds
that deflect signals, right?
But they can also emit a signal.
If they aim that
signal off the clouds,
it allows them to accurately
lock on to their target.
Which keeps their location
perfectly hidden.
[QWENTHUR gasps]
That means--
Qwenthur to Baby
Magnum, come in!
Run for it!
[gasps]
[HAVIA screams]
[QWENTHUR groans]
[COMM OFFICER A]
No longer operating!
[HAVIA]
Damn.
[COMM OFFICER A]
I repeat!
Baby Magnum damaged!
Main Guns 1 through 3
no longer operating!
[MILINDA]
I'm not dead.
Not yet.
Still got 7 Main Guns and I
only need one to keep going.
[COMM OFFICER A] Propulsion
system malfunctioning.
High-speed maneuverability
may also be compromised.
[QWENTHUR]
Accidental detonation?
Was the Mach 25 speed too much
for the artillery
shell to withstand?
You think that was
the end of it?
[QWENTHUR]
They're not done yet.
[HAVIA]
What?
They wanna make sure
they finish us off?
Not quite.
There's something off
about their strategy.
[COMM OFFICER A]
Maintenance crew!
Inspect the Baby Magnum's
suspension system!
No!
That's their next target!
The base zone!
[FROLAYTIA]
Qwenthur.
Wake up.
Are you all right?
What the hell?
What's going on?
Where's Havia?
I don't know.
But he was... Wait. What?
What about everyone else?
Luckily, most of the
personnel managed to flee
into the bomb shelter in time.
Right now, only minor
injuries have been reported
So then they didn't
score a direct hit?
[FROLAYTIA]
Maybe their technology's flawed.
It seems like the shell couldn't
withstand the air resistance.
It detonated midair,
just before impact.
[QWENTHUR]
All this from an indirect hit.
I'd say there's a
very real chance
their main gun is
just a prototype.
[QWENTHUR]
But still,
they took out the Bright Hopper
with one shot from 500 clicks.
It's all about the trajectory.
The shorter the distance between
the gun and the target,
the tighter the parabolic arc.
And that would put a
strain on the shells.
Then... why would
they get closer?
[FROLAYTIA] Our presence is
cutting off their supply route.
The Mass Driver Foundation
is trying to draw us
into a short war by directly
targeting the Princess.
With nowhere to retreat to,
and no way to sustain themselves
in a long drawn out war,
it's their only option.
So these Mach 25 shells.
They lose their accuracy
if fired at a target
from close range.
[FROLAYTIA] Regardless,
I'm calling off this mission.
I hate to admit defeat,
but we don't even have
the means to engage them.
As of now, we're evacuating.
Until then I have
to keep searching.
[QWENTHUR]
That won't work!
Using the aircraft carrier
to escape isn't safe!
It'll never make it beyond the
range of an Object's main guns.
[FROLAYTIA] The wounded are
being sent out to sea
on the hydra foils, not
back to the carrier.
But what do you plan to do
about the Charlemagne?
That's not up to me,
that's the Marine's call.
The officers aboard the flagship
will have to make that decision.
And, besides,
it's not like the hydrofoils can
outrun the main guns either.
It's a no win situation.
But that's still
our best chance.
Can you stand?
[QWENTHUR]
I think.
[groaning]
[FROLAYTIA]
Hm. I don't feel a break.
It looks like it's a sprain.
Come on. Let's go.
[QWENTHUR]
What?
Wait, I might be
able to manage...
Didn't you hear me?
My first priority
is our wounded.
And that includes you.
[radio static]
[BILANY]
This is the 52nd
Mechanized Maintenance
Battalion.
Corporal Saronna with the
Forward Reconnaissance Platoon.
[HAVIA]
All right, then.
I'm pretty sure you
should be safe in there
with the current
placement of the clouds.
Let's just keep you hidden till
they fire off more chaffs, okay?
[MILINDA]
Any word from Qwenthur?
[HAVIA]
I keep tryin' to raise him,
but I still can't get through.
Knowing him, I bet
he's perfectly fine.
[radio static]
[BILANY] Hailing 37th Mechanized
Maintenance Battalion.
Baby Magnum.
This is the 52nd Mechanized
Maintenance Battalion.
Corporal Saronna with the
Forward Reconnaissance Platoon.
One of Halreed's officers, huh?
[BILANY] I propose that our most
likely chance for survival
is for our battalions
to work together
and devise a strategy to ensure
that Baby Magnum destroys
the Mass Driver
Foundation's Object.
Have you received authorization
from Major Capistrano for this?
[BILANY] Her whereabouts
are currently unknown.
Being that time is critical,
I'm asking to be placed
as ranking officer
and allowed to devise
the mission plan.
Concerning strategy,
it's advised you follow
the Bright Hopper's tactic.
You mean try to take
out the enemy's legs?
And then lay into them
with the main guns
once they're on the ground?
[BILANY]
Correct. However,
we realize that the Baby Magnum
is incapable of the same
high-speed maneuvers,
which does limit the plan.
[MILINDA] Then how do we
immobilize the enemy Object?
There's a giant dam
in the Iguazú region.
Destroying it would cause
the area downriver to flood,
thus bringing a ground combat
object to a standstill.
[MILINDA]
That can't be your plan.
[BILANY]
Of course it is.
[HAVIA]
No way in hell!
That plan is not acceptable!
Do you realize what'll happen
if we destroy that dam?!
You'll be murdering tens
of thousands of civilians!
Collateral damage.
Besides, they're not
citizens of the LK.
[HAVIA] Either way,
your plan is worthless
if the Baby Magnum
doesn't help you!
It won't accomplish anything if
you bastards destroy the dam!
[BILANY]
This mission is moving forward,
with or without the Baby Magnum.
You'll be advised later when we
intend to strike. That's all.
[HAVIA panting]
Crap!
She's got some
nerve sayin' this
has anything to do
with survival!
[QWENTHUR]
It connected! Havia!
[gasps] Qwenthur.
Have you been under
a rock, man, or what?
You won't believe this,
we just had the most insane
plan ever dumped on us
by the leftovers of the
Bright Hopper's battalion.
Yes it was broadcast on an open
channel so we heard it, too.
Do not participate
in their mission.
The Baby Magnum will not
be mobilized for them.
Hopefully they'll realize
that there's no point
without our participation.
Yeah, don't hold your breath.
[FROLAYTIA]
Why not?
[HAVIA]
'Cause I'm pretty sure
the only thing these
guys're concerned with
is getting payback for
the Bright Hopper.
I get the feeling all rational
thought went up in flames
with their Object. It sounds
to me like they're gonna
blow up the dam no
matter what happens.
Unless someone heads down
there to physically stop them.
Havia. Let's talk.
Sure, Qwenthur,
this seems like a great time
for a serious conversation.
[FROLAYTIA growls]
I'll handle the dam situation.
Right, I'll take care
of the enemy Object.
[BOTH] And I'll leave things
over there up to you!
Stand down. I will
not allow that.
It's too reckless for you
to go out on your own.
Uh?
[QWENTHUR]
In that case,
all you have to do is
simply make a report
that you were unable to find me.
I'm nothing more than a
student on deployment.
Which means what I choose to do,
well, the last thing I
want is for my actions
to impact your stature
in the military.
Listen, Qwenthur. You can't.
[QWENTHUR]
Please, let me do this.
I know this isn't
my job description,
but I've got the experience.
And I can't stand the
idea of just retreating.
[FROLAYTIA]
Hm. Now, look.
I'm the superior officer here.
The final decision
is my responsibility.
[QWENTHUR exhales]
Now we could say you
were still missing.
I'd have no choice but to
continue searching for you.
Wait, I'm sorry, what?
[FROLAYTIA] You can't do
anything with that leg.
You'll only die if
you go at them alone.
[QWENTHUR]
Uh...
So this is what we'll do.
We're in this together.
No matter what the
consequences are.
Just remember, even though I
have to act like your crutch,
you're still my stubborn,
troublemaking subordinate.
[FROLAYTIA] I'm hoping you have
some kind of plan worked out.
I'll need the Princess's
help for it to work.
But the very first
thing we need to do
is determine which
route the enemy Object
will take to intercept us.
The satellites are still down.
So it's up to us to
determine their location
then report it back
to the Princess
so she can make a
pre-emptive strike.
Let's review all of the options.
Projections show they're
likely to thread the mountains
and come down a gorge.
That gives them three
possible routes.
[FROLAYTIA] There's no need
to stake out all three.
The sound will give away
the general direction.
The Object's drive noise
is the one thing they
can't conceal. Uh?
Fingers crossed it still runs.
Just sit tight a moment.
[QWENTHUR] Uh? It got blasted
this far in the explosion?
[gasps]
[QWENTHUR]
I'm really sorry
for all the trouble I'm
putting you through.
[FROLAYTIA]
Yeah, you better be.
You owe me a shoulder rub
that'll make your hands bleed.
[QWENTHUR laughs]
--[radio static]
--Uh?!
[COMM OFFICER A]
This is the Charlemagne.
We're attempting to
reach Major Capistrano
in regards to the Mass Driver
Foundation's main gun.
A few details have come to light
as a result of our analysis.
Please reference the diagrams.
We've uncovered
that their main gun
is a combination of rail gun
and rocket technology.
They use a rail gun to fire
the oversized artillery shell,
and the shell then immediately
splits into three.
Furthermore, just before impact,
it appears to eject
around 10 submunitions
in a ring formation.
[QWENTHUR]
The Princess will be killed
if a single one of those
submunitions strikes her.
[COMM OFFICER A] The shell
is fired at a high angle.
But its trajectory
is rather peculiar.
After climbing to
25 hundred meters
almost directly
above the target,
the missiles arc suddenly
goes into a nosedive.
[QWENTHUR] They must be
manipulating the trajectory
with some kind of tail assembly.
[COMM OFFICER A] The kinetic
energy of the shell's trajectory
is concentrated on detachment.
But after the missiles
split the rear rocket engine
is programmed to ignite
thus allowing it to
achieve Mach 25.
Our assumption is that
it changes trajectory
with adjustable grooves.
End transmission.
[FROLAYTIA]
Mass Drivers,
rockets, submunition technology.
There you go.
It's like a Frankenstein
hybrid weapon.
Cutting edge as you can get.
Don't forget the chaff
missile targeting method.
Actually employing the clouds
to reflect the locked-on
guidance signal.
You can't get much
more intricate.
The creator of this thing
is either a genius
or entirely freakin' nuts.
Oh, are you feeling
a tinge of jealousy,
Mister Budding Designer?
Not quite.
I'm a little busy not
crapping my pants.
We'll need to come up with
a provisional codename
now that we have confirmation
of their Object exists.
Hm... How does "Break
Carrier" sound to you?
[QWENTHUR] Something that
speaks destruction?
Sounds 'bout right.
[FROLAYTIA]
What are you doing?
I'm just adding some bookmarks.
All the mountains around here
are littered with a large
amount of tunnels.
It's a labyrinthine of mining
and transportation networks.
When everything
starts to go down,
it'll be helpful if we can call
up these maps with one tap.
Figured I'd program it
while I have the chance.
Try not to go overboard, though.
It's not gonna do us much good
if the Break Carrier's people
pick up your signal.
Uh!
[FROLAYTIA] I can't help
but feel so nervous.
[sighs] Hey, Qwenthur.
Why don't you tell me
something about yourself
to keep my mind off things?
Are you trying to sound
like some corporate manager
pressuring me to reveal a
hidden talent, 'cause you do.
You're a student, what do you
know about the corporate world?
Thanks for boring me.
[exhales]
[QWENTHUR]
Actually, I heard a rumor.
Is it true that you're a
member of the nobility?
[FROLAYTIA]
Mm...
The Capistrano family.
We have an extremely
desirable genetic trait.
To be honest, I'm surprised
you haven't heard about it.
But then again, you're
not an aristocrat.
What is it?
We only produce males.
It doesn't matter who we
marry or how we reproduce.
Our children are born male
almost 100% of the time.
And having male heirs, well,
that's what the
aristocracy is all about.
The right to inherit.
Y'know, all of that.
Not a subject a commoner like
you is too familiar with, huh?
Yeah, all the stuff about
pedigrees and lineages.
It's a little too much for
me to wrap my head around.
I mean, why not just marry
the person that you love?
I don't get it.
But, hey. What do I know,
I'm not nobility.
The idea of marriage is
still pretty abstract to me.
Lucky you.
I'd be lying if I said
I didn't envy you.
But here I am,
saddled with this
genetic disposition.
But... that doesn't
really make sense,
if your family only has
boys 100% of the time.
What about you?
You are all woman, right?
Yeah, I don't
understand it myself.
I'm a noblewoman, guaranteed
to give birth to boys.
Trust me, there are
plenty of men out there
who've had trouble
conceiving a male heir.
All I am is a natural resource
they're clamoring to acquire.
Desperate to breed me like
I'm some sort of prize horse.
[QWENTHUR]
So, then...
It'd be like a marriage
of convenience?
That kind of thing?
[FROLAYTIA] It'd be legitimate
in the family register,
but in practical terms?
I'm nothing more
than a tool for them
to maintain succession
of their legacy.
As long as the female comes
from the same social class,
that's all that matters.
They don't dare dilute their
aristocratic bloodline.
Who knows? Maybe I'm lucky.
I guess there are
worse things, right?
When you have a mountain
of requests from men
that only want you for something
you have no control over,
all you can do is try
to stay positive.
It was bad enough being
born with this trait,
but the way they talk...
"That Capistrano girl
can produce a boy at
the drop of a hat,
it doesn't even matter
if the man is sterile".
They basically bounce back and
forth between talking about me
like I'm livestock
or a miracle cure.
The list these days.
It ranges from impotent
elderly gentlemen
to pervy letches from
who-knows-where.
Each and every one of them
bidding like crazy
for the privilege of
wedding and bedding me.
And that's the reason I
prefer to take my chances
on the battlefield instead
of a safe nation.
If I retire from the military,
all that's waiting for me is the
highest bidder and a big bed.
And he's probably
some middle-aged man
I've never even met before.
Oh, speaking of.
I'm guessing you heard
that transmission
from the Bright Hopper pilot,
Halreed Copacabana?
Yeah.
[FROLAYTIA] He's about
number three on the list.
He's actually considered one
of the kinder candidates,
if you can believe it.
When I heard the report about
the attack on his Object?
To be honest, I was relieved.
But one or two candidates
dropping out?
That would hardly put
a dent in the line.
It's no big deal.
I just have to spend my life
fighting in the Military.
At least until I become an old
hag and cease to be useful.
Basically, living and
dying on the battlefield.
That's the closest I
can come to freely living
my life the
way that I want.
Well, all of that aside.
Even out here you sure
do smell really nice.
[laughs] Huh?
That's really what
you have to say
after I pour my
heart out to you?
Well, honestly, I don't think I
could ask for a better reaction.
[explosion]
[FROLAYTIA gasps]
Which way is it?
[QWENTHUR]
I can't tell.
It's reverberating too much
through the mountains.
[QWENTHUR] Which of the
three routes is it on?
We're screwed if
we misread this.
We've only got one chance.
Which way...
Which direction is it?
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA]
"Three-Legged Mountain Climbing
Is Life-and-Death".
[MILINDA] "The Artillery Battle
in the Iguazú Mountains III".