[HAVIA] Rock climbing is fun,
but you do have a plan, right?
[QWENTHUR]
Yeah, kinda.
Might need to break
somethin' along the way
to extend repair time.
[HAVIA]
Better find it soon.
[QWENTHUR]
Oh, crap!
[HAVIA]
Qwenthur!
That was way too close!
I wonder what tipped her off,
maybe it was the radio signal?
Sensor units and other
delicate instruments
were incorporated into
the design in a way
that minimizes damage
from shock waves.
Taking shelter here
was the right call.
Now, this is where
the real show begins.
Though having said that, I don't
think I could even carry enough
Hand-axe to make a dent
in this monstrosity.
There we go.
For an Elite, the Object is like
an extension of themselves.
Sensor discrepancies would
be like wearing glasses
with a slightly-off
prescription.
[QWENTHUR]
It might not seem like much,
but any factors that distract
her from her mission
are unacceptable.
In the middle of a pit stop,
every single second counts.
[MAINTENANCE CAPTAIN A]
Seeing to the main gun exchange
as we speak.
[OHOHO gasps]
Apologies, Ma'am, but adding
that job to the docket
would result in a delay
to our timetable.
Your sensor readings...
[QWENTHUR] She seems the sort
to try adjusting it herself.
[QWENTHUR]
When she does, I'll be ready!
[QWENTHUR] Pop star knockers
as big as my head, here I come!
[OHOHO]
Uh!
[QWENTHUR]
Pardon me, Mademoiselle.
No! You've gotta be kidding me!
No, dear. Oh! Can't believe
your eyes, Blondie?
I am the Elite chosen by
the Intelligence Union
to pilot their finest Object!
[laughs]
What happened to the G cups...?
[QWENTHUR cries]
[OHOHO] Are you seriously
crying, you big baby?
Haven't you heard good things
come in small packages?
[laughing]
You're still confused.
The 'me' you see on-screen
is a real-time,
3D rendered dummy projection.
But they look so natural!
I hope you realize how
fortunate you are!
Back home I'm a super
famous, singing, dancing
pop star Elite pilot!
[QWENTHUR]
I don't know what to believe!
Oh, ho! In the IU, truth
is the essence of justice.
Lies are evil.
But as an outsider,
I have zero obligation
to shoot straight with you.
You liar! Your chest
is as flat as a board!
Get a grip! You shriek
like a little girl!
You took away my innocence!
Led me astray from the
G-cup promised land!
You're a designer.
Can't you appreciate
how aerodynamic I am?
[QWENTHUR] Enough talk.
Time to continue my mission.
First thing's first,
close all the bulkheads.
I'd rather not have to end your
singing career, so get started!
My multitude of fans
and I thank you
for taking my voice into
consideration. Ah, ha, ha.
[QWENTHUR]
Like I thought,
with the bulkheads closed,
I can't use the radio.
[gasps]
[QWENTHUR]
Juliet? Is that her real name?
[OHOHO]
Full disclosure?
Our conversation has been
transmitting to the men outside.
Which means we ought to be
completely surrounded by now.
[laughing]
[QWENTHUR]
That doesn't matter.
You're the only one who can
pilot this Object, right?
If you make any rash decisions,
I can end this battle with
a quick flick of my wrist.
So, what's our next
move, handsome?
Is there somewhere in particular
you'd like me to blast off
the face of the planet?
Don't do anything.
We'll wait here until the
Princess has you in checkmate.
One way or another, you lose.
[OHOHO]
Oh, my! [laughs]
This Object has
a mind of its own.
If I wasn't here to hold
the reins, the Gatling 033
would run wild
like a raging bull!
Run wild...?
[groaning]
[MAINTENANCE CAPTAIN A]
Gatling Zero Three Three!
Mobilizing with an enemy
combatant on board
is too dangerous!
Haven't you noticed we're
in the middle of a battle
where everything
could turn against us
in the blink of an eye?
You'd rather raise the
white flag in surrender?
Sorry, you don't have
that authority.
[MAINTENANCE CAPTAIN A]
I didn't--
[OHOHO] The Gatling 033's
sensors are off-kilter,
and I refuse to operate it
under those conditions.
I think I'll let our Strategic
AI "Juliet" take it from here!
[QWENTHUR]
Strategic AI?
[MAINTENANCE CAPTAIN A]
No! It's not safe
to give full program
access to an AI!
[OHOHO] Since we're
facing another Object,
I can set Juliet's programming
to engage only targets
on a scale of 50 meters or more.
That should take care of any
problems! Ah, ha, ha, ha.
It's impossible. No AI can
out-pilot a living human.
That kind of technology
doesn't exist yet.
[OHOHO] You must be thinking
of the Legitimate Kingdom's
vaunted "Angelina List."
[laughs]
Oh please, that treatise
was written by an AI skeptic
based on the writer's own bias.
Running wild, freezing up,
difficulties in its
learning process.
Test after test was conducted,
each citing weaknesses and
failures of AI programs.
It's malicious list full
of negative thinking.
[QWENTHUR]
The Angelina List.
It's the wall that
Object-class strategic AIs
have always run into.
[OHOHO] Ah, ha. If the Object
was completely unmanned,
the limitations would
be problematic.
But here on the Gatling 033,
the Strategic AI Juliet
handles the basic controls,
while I respond to various
errors that crop up,
and handle fine-tuning
adjustments.
Using this method, we can
compensate for its shortcomings
while maximizing the AI's
high-speed processing.
So yeah, without me
keeping Juliet in check,
this machine'll go totally wild.
Let me demonstrate.
[QWENTHUR screams]
[QWENTHUR groaning]
Oh dear, that simply
won't do at all.
Your rhythm was way off.
How do you expect to keep up
with my dance moves?
[QWENTHUR]
This is what Elites really are.
Humans whose bodies have
been altered to withstand
the strain of piloting Objects.
[OHOHO]
Now, then.
I already have everything
I'd hoped to gain.
Guess it's time to bring
today's business to a close!
[laughing]
[QWENTHUR groaning]
[MILINDA]
Enemy craft rapidly approaching.
Baby Magnum moving to intercept.
[OHOHO] Ah, ha, ha.
Look who's come out to play.
[QWENTHUR]
Damn it.
How far along did repairs
get on the Baby Magnum?
[OHOHO] Appears she only has one
main gun operational. Ah, ha!
They only fixed
one of the seven?
Not looking too good
for your side, is it?
This must be her last resort.
Ah, ha! Oh, Little Miss Loutish
Legitimate Kingdom First Gen?
The offer stands: raise
the white flag now,
and I promise to let you leave
the battlefield with your life.
I'm afraid I can't oblige
your generous offer.
Regulations prohibit
the white flag
from being raised before an
Object has been destroyed.
That way works for me, too.
I'm under no obligation
to show you mercy.
I'll gladly blow you away
with my performance!
[pop music plays]
[singing in Japanese]
[QWENTHUR screaming, groaning]
[singing continues]
[QWENTHUR groaning]
[OHOHO] Ah, ha, ha!
Juliet handles the combat,
which means I've got
some time on my hands.
Why don't we take
this rare opportunity,
and get all close n'
cuddly n' smoochy?
[QWENTHUR]
Close and cuddly and smoochy?
[MILINDA gasps]
That voice.
Qwenthur...?
[OHOHO laughs] Unsophisticated
and out of the loop?
Maybe your blonde boy toy would
be happier here with me!
Qwenthur, I have no idea why
you're in there with that woman,
but you'd better escape
before I destroy that
Object with you in it.
[QWENTHUR screams]
[QWENTHUR groaning]
[MILINDA]
Qwenthur.
[gasps]
It doesn't matter if you escape.
I'm going to hit her with
everything I've got!
Stop! It's not--
[gasps]
[MILINDA] Yes. I'm sure it's
all so very complicated.
Just trust me.
I'll try to do something
about the Rush's movements.
[OHOHO]
Enough monkeying around.
[QWENTHUR yelps]
[QWENTHUR]
What should I do now?
[QWENTHUR gasps]
[QWENTHUR] This is Qwenthur
with an urgent message!
[MILINDA] Sorry. I'm a little
distracted right now.
[QWENTHUR]
Yeah? Well I'm at my wit's end.
Can I ask you for a favor in
case the worst should happen?
[MILINDA]
What's that?
[QWENTHUR] At the barracks
in the maintenance base,
I hid an engagement ring.
[MILINDA gasps]
[QWENTHUR] If something
should happen to me today,
please return it to my
sweet Angelina back home.
We've known each other
since we were little.
[MILINDA grunts]
[QWENTHUR yelps]
Sorry it has to end like this,
I forgot to ask you which
way you'd like to go out.
You get to choose between
the coil guns, laser turrets,
and the fixed base
plasma cannon.
[QWENTHUR] Isn't there an option
where I don't end up dead?
I don't think so.
Any other last wishes?
[QWENTHUR]
Now that you mention it,
things got pretty hot and
heavy with little Julia,
this foreign waitress in
one of the Safe Nations,
and she was as unflappable
as a computer program.
But not the night
we were together.
So, if you could send
her that necklace
I have stashed in the barra--
[QWENTHUR screaming]
[QWENTHUR screams]
[OHOHO laughs]
You know,
I'm also kinda curious
about these female friends
you've been hoarding rings
and necklaces for.
You were so distraught to not
find any G cups in here,
so tell me more about
this "hot and heavy" night
you spent with Julia!
[QWENTHUR]
Hurry! Baby Magnum!
You've gotta go wide right!
[MILINDA] Is that what you
told your little Julia?
[QWENTHUR]
This isn't the time!
Now I'm begging you,
listen to me!
There's a way to win!
To the right!
You've gotta trust me!
Now go left!
Turn a little at a time!
[QWENTHUR] Fire your main gun
at the Rush's front armor!
Follow up with a Killer Squall
from your secondaries!
You're aiming for the wreckage
of the Water Strider!
If you melt the snow behind
it with your lasers,
it'll roll into place
and make an obstacle!
[OHOHO laughing]
You're not quick enough!
Your cute companion can
relay tactics all he wants,
but with your speed, it won't
make any difference!
Now, for the finale,
a grand crescendo!
[OHOHO laughing]
[OHOHO]
Here comes the kill shot.
You'll regret not
choosing to surrender
when I gave you the chance.
Prepare to die!
[QWENTHUR] Never give up.
We can still win this!
[gasps]
[OHOHO groaning]
How strange. What happened?
The Gatling 033
just came to a stop.
Ha, ha, ha... Ha...
What did you do?
Is it over?
[OHOHO]
What did you do to my Object?!
Why isn't it responding?!
If you wanna make
this a quiz show,
we're gonna need some buzzers.
I've already determined
the nature of the problem.
For some reason,
Juliet is acting on her own
learning from variables
that shouldn't even be
factored in this battle!
She's spitting out
multiple bugs,
errors and conflicting
command priorities.
They're completely
locking the system.
There's too many
for me to keep up!
And that's why I'm asking you!
Not about the situation,
but the reason!
What did you do to make Juliet's
processors shut herself down?!
She must have bogged
herself down
recalculating the
risk assessment.
But why? What did you do?
[QWENTHUR] Juliet picked
up on subtle changes
in the situation
you didn't notice.
She's been steadily
calculating ever since.
Desperately trying
to avoid a checkmate.
The Rush stopped dead in its
tracks because so many variables
popped up that Juliet
had to shut down
to attempt to process them all.
But what put us at risk?
It's ludicrous!
My Gatling 033 had an
overwhelming advantage!
It was obvious I was
about to win that fight!
My little message about
rings and necklaces
was never meant
for the Princess.
[OHOHO]
Uh?
And just so you know,
I never had a childhood
friend named Angelina.
That was simply a veiled
reference to the
Legitimate Kingdom report on the
shortcomings of strategic AIs.
The Angelina List.
[QWENTHUR]
And what's another way
to name someone "little Julia"?
Using a diminutive?
[OHOHO]
Juli... et. You don't mean--!
[QWENTHUR]
You were so confident.
You wanted to make direct
contact with the Baby Magnum.
But in your arrogance, you sent
your message out unscrambled.
You broadcasted
that transmission
to every other
soldier in our army.
[HAVIA panting]
Qwenthur, you moron!
Relying way too heavily
on this ever handsome,
high-born, comrade-in-arms!
"I'm at my wit's end" signaled
the start of the secret message.
The "foreigner" bit has
to refer to the Rush.
He said "computer program,"
but also mentioned "Angelina,"
so it must be some kind
of automated Object.
A spare power drill battery
has still got enough juice
to get an infrared targeting
system up and running!
Heh.
[QWENTHUR] My partner's primary
vocation is as a radar analyst.
He sees the battlefield
as a game board,
and Objects as pieces.
He specializes in
watching their moves,
and figuring out
their weaknesses.
[HAVIA]
Qwenthur can guide the Princess,
while luring the Rush back
into the target area.
That's when I'll bring the
infrared targeting system
back to life.
Then, the Rush's strategic
AI will mistakenly believe
that the Water Strider's
main guns are aiming at it.
Making it think it's threatened
from both sides!
[QWENTHUR] The problem arose
from you removing
anything smaller than
50 meters from targeting.
Thus, Juliet can't target
the second threat,
and keeps spinning her wheels
trying to resolve the issue.
[OHOHO whimpers]
I never imagined
the Angelina List could be
put to such practical use!
[QWENTHUR]
Even as we speak,
she keeps diving through
countless errors.
Lost in an ocean of
conflicting subroutines.
Far too many to deal with, even
with an Elite's cognitive speed.
[OHOHO laughs nervously]
All right, I'll admit it, you've
completely deadlocked Juliet!
However...
Don't fool yourself into
thinking we're finished here.
Hard shutdown! Unlock full
keyboard entry mode!
[QWENTHUR yelps]
[OHOHO laughs] I might have to
give it my undivided attention,
but I'm perfectly
capable of piloting
this Object all on my own!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
But I do find myself
wanting to make you
mine even more now!
What is it about you
that makes my heart
feel like it's been set ablaze?
Sure, there's the quick wit, and
plethora of practical skills,
but I've never felt so
enthralled by anyone!
[QWENTHUR]
Don't do it.
You'd be fighting in vain.
You can't win against
our Princess
with the way things stand.
Oh, ha, ha! And how
do you figure--?
She'd... beat me...?
[OHOHO gasps]
[QWENTHUR] There's a bomb set
in this little alcove here
behind your seat.
Check for yourself.
[OHOHO]
No way.
Why?
What is something
like that doing here?
[QWENTHUR]
Objects are monstrous weapons
that can't even be
destroyed by nukes.
It's a backup plan for
an "emergency shutdown"
if an Elite turned traitor.
And it's recently
been activated.
[OHOHO]
But I'm not a filthy traitor!
[QWENTHUR]
The commander of the base zone
apparently thinks differently.
Must have seen your Object stop
on the verge of victory.
I'm the Elite pilot
of Gatling 033,
and not so expendable.
It doesn't make sense
for them to cast me aside
like I was nothing!
Normally, that would be true,
but there's something here
more important to them
than the Object or its Elite.
They can't afford to
give the enemy Juliet!
[QWENTHUR groans]
[OHOHO]
It's your fault!
This is all because of you!
I did nothing. Got it?
Nothing wrong!
It's not my fault!
You did this to me!
[QWENTHUR]
What're you gonna do?
You've only got
a couple minutes,
then they set the bomb off.
What's your ejection system?
It's...
my pilot's seat is rigged up
to eject when activated.
It figures.
The bomb was set to go off when
the ejection signal was sent.
But don't worry.
I should be able to sever
the connector pretty quickly.
But if the bomb's gonna
go off after I eject,
how are you planning to escape?!
[QWENTHUR]
I'll try to defuse it.
But--!
This is the truth of war.
There's no room for kindness.
Just go.
For me, this is an opportunity
to capture an enemy
Object intact.
A one-time deal.
Whenever we meet again,
we'll have to meet as enemies.
Got it?
But wait. Why risk
yourself to save me?
[QWENTHUR]
The song you sang.
It was really nice.
[OHOHO gasps]
[QWENTHUR] Do me a favor,
and keep this between us.
If they find out I let
an enemy Elite get away,
I'm definitely in
for a court-martial.
I won't say anything. [laughs]
Very well, I agree to
the terms of your deal.
[QWENTHUR]
I appreciate it.
It's a one-time deal.
Whenever you and I meet again,
we meet as enemies.
Right.
[OHOHO] And when that
time comes around again,
I shall sing a song
just for you.
[QWENTHUR gasps]
[radio static]
[HAVIA]
Yo, Sir knight!
Looks like your plan
worked after all.
[QWENTHUR]
Yeah, we pulled it off.
I showed her the self-destruct
device in the cockpit,
and she was good enough to
eject for me, just like that.
[HAVIA]
Heh.
And she didn't notice that
it was made of Hand-axe?
[QWENTHUR]
This is the truth of war.
There's no room for kindness.
But do me a favor. Don't tell
the Princess or Frolaytia, okay?
[HAVIA]
Sure thing,
but I'd start thinking
up excuses to make
to the Princess while you can.
I hear she's going ballistic
wanting to know who the
hell "sweet Angelina"
and "sweet little Julia" are.
[QWENTHUR] Huh? Why would what
I said have upset the Princess?
[HAVIA]
Never mind that,
just hurry it up...
so I can smack you upside
your oblivious head!
[LENDY]
We found you!
You weren't hurt, were you?
The loss of the Gatling
033 is truly upsetting,
but control systems
and strategic AIs
are more important
to our military.
It's all right. We have
a backup of Juliet.
[gasps]
[LENDY]
That means we can keep going.
We'll just change the layout
of the Object
currently being built,
and you'll be reinstated
in no time.
Plus, once we've completed
Juliet's counterpart, Romeo,
we'll never be fooled by
makeshift countermeasures again.
Even if Juliet was seized,
there are measures in place
to keep her sensitive
intel under wraps.
We don't have to worry
about our tech
falling into the wrong hands--
Uh!
If you ever do anything
like that again,
I'll turn my main guns
on your base zone
without a second thought.
[LENDY whimpers]
[OHOHO]
That boy...
I'm sick of these
professional soldiers
parroting out the
official position.
It might be safer to keep an
egghead engineer like him close.
He can be the Ace up my sleeve.
Ah, ha. That just makes
me want him even more!
See you again soon, Qwenthur.
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR] "The Coal Mine
Littered with Stacks of Money."
[MILINDA] "The Kamchatka
Peninsula Nighttime Blitz I."