[QWENTHUR]
Hey, Havia...
It's kind of weird, huh?
We were freezing in Alaska
just a few days ago.
[HAVIA] You do understand
the seasons are reversed
in the southern
hemisphere, right?
It does seem a bit ironic though
that this is the hemisphere
where we get to meet
Mini Skirt Santa.
Yeah? Is that some kinda
heat stroke-induced fantasy?
Huh?
[SOLDIERS chattering]
[SOLDIERS groan, laugh]
[HAVIA]
It's crazy.
Soldiers of rival
warring nations,
battling it out over a
game of cards and coins.
[QWENTHUR]
They sure look relaxed.
[HAVIA]
Why wouldn't they be?
The enemy's Object is a
freakin' old-school Half-Gen.
It's the musket of Objects.
It should be in a
museum, not at war.
It's a joke.
Doesn't stand a chance,
especially since
we're hunting it down
with over twenty First
and Second-Gen Objects.
What I don't get is why
the Oceanian Military State
wants to fight. They're
choosing to go up against
an allied force of
the Four Great Powers.
[HAVIA]
Pride, maybe?
It's a country.
Not an insecure human being.
Is their government that petty?
[HAVIA] Governments are just
collectives of humans, man.
Yeah, can't argue with that.
What're you working
on over there?
Mini Skirt Santa.
[QWENTHUR]
What? That's real?
[OHOHO] You lucky bastards
have made it through
--the Lottery from Hell!
--[QWENTHUR] Oh, ho, ho!
[OHOHO] And guess what?
I'll be the one to escort you
--directly to Heaven!
--[HAVIA] She's a pop star
from the Intelligence Union.
And she's here on
this base right now.
[QWENTHUR]
To entertain the troops?
[HAVIA] Believe it or not,
she's an Elite pilot
working for the
Intelligence Union.
[QWENTHUR]
Seriously? She's an Elite?
[gasps]
[BOTH]
Whoa!
Those are G cups, dude.
Gotta give it to the IU.
I would gladly lie down
and surrender to her.
[QWENTHUR]
Hey, c'mon, man.
I wouldn't call the Princess
a slouch or anything.
[sneezes]
[HAVIA] Sorry, but our armed
forces lose this battle.
[QWENTHUR]
Personally...
I prefer a size that
actually fits in my hands.
[BOTH]
Whoa!
[MILINDA] But wouldn't it
have been good for the region
to grow more forests?
[FROLAYTIA]
Undoubtedly.
If they'd fertilized the
desert region of Oceania,
it would've allowed for
wide-scale agriculture.
[FROLAYTIA] The profits from
that would've supported them
to expand their cities and
transportation network,
which would've allowed
them access to mining,
giving them more resources
to develop the nation.
But... not everyone was
on board with the plan.
The local tribes opposed
the fertilization.
They didn't want the
land to be blanketed by
genetically-modified vegetation.
And that's why the
Oceanian Military State
is persecuting them?
Precisely, which
is why we're here.
To protect the local
tribes from the state.
That's the pretext under which
the allied forces came together.
[QWENTHUR] Did you hear that
our commander this time around
isn't even military?
[HAVIA] Yup. He's about
the most powerful man
in the Legitimate
Kingdom though--
Councilor Flide, himself.
Is it parent observation day?
A bigwig bureaucrat
out here on the front?
What? No way.
The councilor would never take
the risk of coming out
to the battlefield.
--[phone beeps]
--[QWENTHUR gasps]
[HAVIA]
Princess mailing you?
Yeah.
She's bored with
being held on standby.
[HAVIA]
Huh...
[chuckles]
[grunts]
[QWENTHUR gasps]
What the hell, man?
You could always respond
in person, y'know?
We are on the same
base, after all.
[QWENTHUR]
Cut it out.
Quit acting like she's
just the cute girl
from the class down the hall.
She's a freakin' Elite, man.
--I can't simply--
--[GIRL] Hey!
Excuse me...
Is that what I think it is?
[HAVIA]
Huh?
Uh, that's...
It is, isn't it?
It's the giant Friendly
Rock Beast from my book!
Uh, yeah, exactly! That's right.
Whenever there's a scary storm,
he provides shelter for the
squirrels and the kangaroos.
You sure about this?
Lying to an innocent
little girl?
Then, you tell her
the truth, Havia.
Tell her it's a
giant death machine
here to crush the
Oceanian Military State.
[FROLAYTIA]
That's enough,
--you twits.
--[BOTH gasp]
Quit hiding behind
the barricade,
gossiping like old ladies.
--Get your act together!
--[GIRL gasps, yelps]
[QWENTHUR]
Talk about a waste.
That's how it is, dude.
She might be beautiful, but
she's a hard ass by nature.
Up against her, even
a heavyweight fighter
would be terrified
out of his damn mind.
--[groans] O-Ow...
--[FROLAYTIA] If it's tenderness
you're looking for,
I'll stomp it into you
with the heel of my boot.
Now look.
Stop hanging by the barricade,
making yourselves targets.
You understand this is
a battlefront, right?
C'mon, don't overreact.
I mean, we do have two Objects
stationed at this base.
No sniper's gonna
take that risk.
Not snipers.
It's cameras I don't
want you getting shot by.
Huh?
[FROLAYTIA] We've got a
swarm of photojournalists
eager to expose the Military
State's despotic ways--
A bunch of rich, Safe Nation
boys who've never known war.
Well, either that or
purported intellectuals.
[HAVIA
Oh, right, and don't forget
the mercenaries
with an axe to grind
after Objects put
them out of business.
[QWENTHUR] Can't you just
shoo them away from the base?
Blame it on military statutes?
[FROLAYTIA] That would go
against the PR strategy.
The higher-ups want
the world to see
a parade of righteous heroes.
So if I banned all
the media-types,
I would get royally chewed
out by the candidates
for ruining their
election campaigns.
[QWENTHUR]
Huh, there's an election?
Yeah, the council elections
are coming up soon back home.
Oh!
So that's why Councilor Flide is
our commander on this mission.
[FROLAYTIA]
Quick as ever, Qwenthur.
The guy's on the warpath
to make sure his image
remains respectable.
And he's going all out.
There might even
be a side-mission
to rescue an anti-war group.
Savvy as he is, it
could actually happen.
We're here to make a
politician look good?
All for something so childish
as maintaining his image!
--This is the freakin' worst.
--[sighs]
[CROWD chattering]
I'm guessin' you're
Legitimate Kingdom?
You angling to interview
your Object killing heroes?
That's right.
Guess they're famous in the
Intelligence Union too, huh?
Yeah, that's one word for it.
You interviewing them in person?
If I can get past the PR team.
They don't make it easy.
But then...
...I'm after a pop star.
I came all the way here for
a face-to-face interview.
[LK REPORTER]
Hell, it could be worse.
Can't say I'd mind doing
a face-to-face with her.
[BOTH laugh]
Enemies acting like
they're best friends.
[scoffs]
[music plays]
[AYAMI] Yes, there you go;
the calibration looks good.
I'll send you the next piece.
[monitor buzzes]
[music plays]
[SUBORDINATE DOCTOR]
Such precision.
She always delivers.
[AYAMI]
Indeed.
[music continues]
[monitor buzzes]
[COMPUTER (MILINDA)]
The performance
without the artistry is boring.
[AYAMI] But to be fully
enveloped by the sound?
That must feel nice, huh?
[COMPUTER (MILINDA)] How the
dome vibrates at every point
and dissolves into my notes?
To find this satisfying would
be an insult to orchestras.
[door opens]
[QWENTHUR]
Hey, wait!
--[QWENTHUR, HAVIA arguing]
--[COMPUTER (MILINDA) gibberish]
Well, there goes the test.
Let's just take a break.
[MILINDA]
What are you doing here?
Wow!
I've never seen a tuning
suit in person before.
It's really cool.
It's a new design.
It can actually make physical
adjustments to my body.
[QWENTHUR]
Yeah, I bet.
Just look at all the patches
wired up to your bare skin.
Lemme see! If the Princess
is putting on a fashion show,
I want-- Ugh! Ahh!
My eyes!
--[HAVIA groans]
--You showed up
--at the perfect time.
--[HAVIA] I'm blind!
--Y'musta known I needed help.
--I can't see!
Why just me?
Whoa, hey! Qwenthur!
I get it.
So the data is temporarily
collated through these.
[MILINDA]
Uh...
[QWENTHUR]
Is that also new?
It's what they call
a flute, right?
I remember seeing one
back in the Safe Nation.
[MILINDA]
Wanna take a look?
[QWENTHUR]
Sure!
Let's see...
You're supposed to hold
it sideways, right?
--[plays notes]
--[MILINDA gasps]
[playing contines]
[gasp]
[whimpers]
What's the deal?
Why doesn't it sound right?
[inhales]
[plays note]
[yelps]
[whimpers]
[pants]
[QWENTHUR]
What's up with this thing?
And which keys do I have to
press to produce a C note?
--[plays note]
--[gasps]
That's... not it..
[pants]
[QWENTHUR]
It's hopeless.
I can't get it to work.
Hey, Princess, how do you--
Uh...
[whimpering]
[pants]
Um, are you okay?
--Don't tell me.
--[gasps]
[QWENTHUR]
You've gotta pee, don't you?
[growls]
[QWENTHUR]
You don't need to wait for--
--[MILINDA grunts]
--[QWENTHUR screams]
Jeez.
"Do you need to pee?"
How old are you, man?
You say something?
[HAVIA]
Nothing.
Just saying this
should be an easy win.
Unleashing the power of
twenty-plus Objects on 'em?
And they've only got
one rust-bucket antique?
It's like a whole beach trying
to snag one babe's bikini.
[QWENTHUR]
Actually...
I don't think it's gonna
be as simple as it sounds.
Huh?
From what I heard, the enemy's
got their Object camouflaged
as one of their
water storage plants.
And they've got those
things set up everywhere.
[HAVIA] I guess it
wouldn't stand a chance
if it was out in the open.
But they've got their
girl locked in a box.
[QWENTHUR]
What if we opened up the box,
and there really
was a girl inside?
It may only be a  Half-Gen,
but it's still an Object.
If we don't respect that,
we'll get kicked in the nuts!
And did you hear who they've
got piloting their Object?
It's apparently none other
than the Oceanian dictator.
Well that explains why
they've taken such pains
to play hide and seek.
[QWENTHUR]
Our satellites haven't even
narrowed down
their location yet.
It's a little tedious,
but we have to take out
each plant one by one.
[HAVIA]
Sheesh...
It's like a giant
shooting gallery.
Ugh...
It'll be worth it if I can
see those G cups in pers--
[OHOHO]
Well, look what we have
--here.
--[gasps, screams]
If it isn't the
Legitimate Kingdom's
most famous and
cherished guard dogs.
I've been looking forward to
working with you on this
mission. Oh, ho, ho!
[QWENTHUR] That's the
Intelligence Union Object!
Which must mean--
[BOTH]
It's the G cup Mini Skirt Santa!
[QWENTHUR]
So that's the IU's Object?
[OHOHO] With twenty Objects
committed to this mission
and two of them
operating out of this base,
I can't imagine there'll
be much for you boys to do,
so you can just
kick back and relax.
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho, ho!
I'd love for that to be true.
This is great!
We're actually talking with
an Intelligence Union Elite!
Hey, uh... I hope you
don't mind me asking, but...
Is it true that the
Intelligence Union
is developing a humanoid Object?
[OHOHO]
Oh, ho, ho! That is nothing more
than a silly lie, of course.
Its center of gravity
would be too high,
making it fall over too easily.
[QWENTHUR]
Aw, that's no fun.
--How about this one?
--[rumbling]
--Rumor has it your Objects
--[HAVIA gasps]
have power plugs on them.
Is that one just another lie?
[OHOHO]
Oh no, that one is true.
It's all a matter of efficiency.
It actually conserves energy
to keep the power reactors
operating around the clock
rather than constantly
switching them on and off.
And for that reason, we
redirect the surplus power
to the base when
we're on standby.
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho!
Okay, but that's not
bidirectional, is it?
The power reactors are
fundamentally maintained
at a high temperature
and voltage, so--
Enough, Qwenthur.
Lay off.
How often do you get the chance
to talk shop with a rival?
I'm a little more worried about
the gloomy mood the
Princess is giving off.
Uh...
You're not getting hit with
some homesickness, are you?
Not really.
It's nothing.
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR scream]
[HAVIA gasps]
Saved. That was close.
[OHOHO] Oh, ho, ho!
It's simple acts of kindness
that win the trust and
hearts of soldiers.
But I guess that concept
might be too abstract
for a boorish
Legitimate Kingdom Elite.
[MILINDA grunts]
[QWENTHUR]
Stop! If we fall, we will die!
[HAVIA]
Just apologize, already!
For what?
How can you be so dense?
[BOTH groan]
Soldiers, I'm Flide.
And I have the honor of
telling you the King's Council
has entrusted me with the
security oversight of Oceania.
I may not be a soldier,
but I am no stranger to war.
My long involvement in
the defense industry
includes the development
of the Elites.
With the need for
the application of
Object-intensive warfare
and advanced diplomacy,
I believe I'm well-suited
for the matter at hand.
Who is the onsite CO?
[FROLAYTIA]
Major Frolaytia Capistrano, sir.
Well then, Major Capistrano,
consider this your first order.
You are to launch
an attack at once.
[FROLAYTIA] Attention,
6th Security Oversight Army
of the Legitimate Kingdom.
This is Major
Frolaytia Capistrano,
Security Oversight
Front-Line Commander.
[FROLAYTIA]
Stay sharp!
This operation is now under way!
Focus your firepower
on the locations
where their Object is
predicted to be hiding.
[HAVIA] Sure is nice to
be on this side of things
for a change, huh?
[QWENTHUR] I've had enough of
the other side for a lifetime.
[MILINDA]
All done. Targets destroyed.
[QWENTHUR] Looks like this
location was a bust after all.
[HAVIA]
Guess so.
Onto the next potential spot.
[OHOHO] Oh, but this is where
your expertise comes into play.
[HAVIA]
What?
[OHOHO] We need you to
survey the area on foot
and confirm there aren't
any communities in our path
before we head over to the
next point. Oh, ho, ho, ho!
[HAVIA gasps]
What?! It's not like we're
getting paid overtime here!
Can't you just search
from the Objects?
They might not be
able to mobilize.
Are you physically fatigued from
all of the inertial g-forces?
[OHOHO] Oh, ho, ho!
You really do know your stuff.
[HAVIA]
Huh?
From pushing all that mass
through such high
mobility maneuvers.
Their pressure-resistant
suits only do so much.
[OHOHO] Well, they
certainly do a bang-up job
of making my legs numb.
Yeah, that's right.
I heard they're designed to
restrict blood flow to the legs.
All to prevent loss of
circulation to the brain.
[OHOHO] Heat builds up in
our bodies during combat,
so we remove our suits afterward
and spray ourselves
down with a coolant.
[QWENTHUR]
You take 'em off?!
Does the Princess do that too?
[gasps]
That's none of your business.
And you don't need
to think about it!
--[HAVIA screams]
--[QWENTHUR] Okay, jeez!
Point made! Goin' a little
overboard, aren't cha?
[OHOHO] Oh, ho, ho! Time to peel
the top half of this suit down
to the high-cut legs so I can
cool off my voluptuous figure.
[BOTH]
For real?
[QWENTHUR] Did she just
actually say those things to us,
or am I freaking dreaming?
[MILINDA growls]
--[QWENTHUR screams]
--[HAVIA] Are you an idiot?!
I'm pretty sure she's
just trying to bait us
into getting ourselves killed!
--Think about it!
--[QWENTHUR] I don't understand!
If her suit had high cut legs,
it wouldn't have
anti-g functionality!
[OHOHO]
Oh... I admit it, you got me.
But the cut of the suit
is still rather risqué.
Much more so than
your average bikini.
Really? Oh man, Havia,
are you hearing this?
Pull it together, Qwenthur!
She's messing with your head,
man, and you're falling for it!
And you're sending the Princess
into an emotional
tailspin in the process!
[OHOHO]
Oh, ho, ho, ho, ho!
Excuse you! You bumped into me!
[MILINDA]
Must be a sensor malfunction.
[OHOHO]
Oh, it's like that?
[OHOHO giggles]
How strange, my control
system is malfunctioning!
[MILINDA growls]
Quit trying to pretend
you're not our enemy.
[OHOHO] Right now, we're
supposed to be allies.
For this battle, yes,
but once it's over we'll
be adversaries again.
[OHOHO]
And when that time comes,
Little Miss Loutish
Legitimate Kingdom First-Gen,
I shall render you into
nothing but a sticky puddle.
[QWENTHUR]
Both of you, stop it!
[HAVIA] Yeah, save the
catfight for the mudpit!
[QWENTHUR] Our only enemy is the
Oceanian Military State, okay?
[OHOHO]
You're right!
--Thank you for reminding me.
--[BOTH sigh]
[OHOHO] Now then, as
I explained earlier,
we really can't move
ahead without you.
--[HAVIA gasps]
--Without us?
[HAVIA] Man, this is
one hell of a forest.
All of this was
genetically modified, right?
[QWENTHUR] Yeah, it's crazy to
think this used to be a desert.
Well, here's my beef.
They're gonna raze this forest.
So what's the point in
sending us to scout?
They're playing it safe.
They're not gonna raze it
if there are any tribes
living out here.
[HAVIA]
Yeah, true.
I guess that would defeat
the purpose of the mission.
[HAVIA gasps]
Get down!
What's up?
[HAVIA] It looks like we've
found ourselves a winner here.
There's a village down there.
[QWENTHUR]
Wonderful.
The Oceanian military's
here, too. But...
It doesn't look like they're
about to start fighting.
They're probably settling up
next month's rent or something.
What now?
Hey, we're not the cavalry, man.
There's only two of us
and a squadron of them.
Exactly! And it looks
like everything's
getting handled
peacefully anyway.
Nothing to worry about.
--[gunshot]
--[BOTH gasp]
[QWENTHUR]
Hey, did you shoot him?
That's not a serious
question, is it?
Do you know of any
rifle that's so silent
you wouldn't have
noticed me firing it?
--[QWENTHUR] If you didn't--
--[static]
[HAVIA gasps]
Is that interference
from a sniper device?
Clearly. But no one in
our military is gonna
launch a silent
attack like that.
Who is this asshole?
Some freelance merc
with an antique rifle?
[gunshots]
[BOTH gasp]
Oh, man, I am not liking
what I'm hearing.
You wanna tell me
what's happening?
Explaining it would be
way too complicated,
so I'll just repeat
exactly what I heard.
"You bastard! You tricked us!"
"No, we would never do that."
"Shut up! We'll kill everyone
and burn your village
to the ground!"
Okay, that is really bad!
[HAVIA]
So what the hell
--do we do?!
--What can we do?
--[gunshots]
--[VILLAGERS screaming]
[QWENTHUR grunts]
We've got no choice.
Let's go!
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA] "The War of
the Ant and the Grasshopper."
[MILINDA] "The Invasion of the
Oceanian Military State II."