The CS Military Channel
welcomes you!
I'm your singing, dancing,
throat-shlashin'
battlefield reporter, Monica!
On today's episode,
we're with the
Legitimate Kingdom's
37th Mechanized
Maintenance Battalion!
Our theme for the show is:
Women makin' an impact
in the military!
I'll be getting up close and
personal with female commanders
and Elite pilots
on the front lines!
I hope theyre not sending
her out with us.
Magazine models don't
belong on the front.
[FROLAYTIA]
Are you serious, Havia?
I thought she'd be
the type of girl
to really get your
young blood pumping!
Sure, she's hot, but this
seems like a bad idea.
They're blazing those lights
during a nighttime operation.
[FROLAYTIA] It's not a problem
if they're on site.
And it's not like we'll let them
broadcast the invasion live.
And besides, this has full
approval from High Command.
[HAVIA]
Huh?
They understand now,
more than ever,
the power of the media
can't be underestimated.
If we can get the show
to feature us favorably,
it'll help the army achieve
its recruitment goals.
And make people less critical
of the blood tax,
and other defense spending.
Though, I relish the
thought of poor saps
who join because
of a magazine model
and the reality waiting for
them once they get to boot camp.
[HAVIA chuckles]
I figure hot babes are a
better reason to enlist
than an obsession with
cheesy action flicks.
[FROLAYTIA] I'm about to
do an interview with them,
so I'll keep that in mind.
Your service to our country
is much appreciated.
[FROLAYTIA]
Yours too.
[gasps] Y'mean it?
[FROLAYTIA]
In about two hours,
I'll lift the ration
limit on caffeine.
Brew a couple pots of coffee,
and let everyone in
the barracks know
they're gonna need all the
boost they can get tonight.
Knowing we have to get up
in the middle of the night
makes it that much harder
to fall asleep.
You learn to force
yourself to sleep.
Who knows when you'll
get the chance again?
An operation under
the cover of night,
it's not the kinda thing
you want to coast
through half-awake.
[MAINTENANCE MEN chatting]
Something's got them
all worked up.
[MILINDA] I heard from
Frolaytia there's a TV show
doing a shoot on base.
Oh, well that explains a lot.
I hope you hunks at home
are ready for the show!
Stay tuned!
[QWENTHUR]
This is kinda exciting!
I wonder what the Faith
Organization's Object
is gonna be like.
I've looked over the
data we have on it,
but it just isn't the same
as seeing it in person.
[MILINDA]
I doubt you will.
Uh? I guess you're right.
It'll be hard to see
much in the darkness.
But you're the backbone
of this operation,
so I shouldn't complain.
You gonna be okay
running on no sleep?
[MILINDA]
Yeah, I'll be fine.
I'm more relaxed in the cockpit
than I am in most other places.
[QWENTHUR]
Yeah, I get what you mean.
What about you, though?
Shouldn't you be
getting some sleep?
I'm still technically a student.
I've gotten good at
pulling all-nighters.
Since I'm not
officially a soldier,
I shouldn't get sent
to the front lines.
It could be the front lines,
or while you're asleep
in your bunk.
You never hear the one that
has your name on it comin'!
[QWENTHUR whimpers]
[AYAMI]
Remember that next time
you start to let
your guard down.
Uh. I can't always
be on guard.
Hell I could drop dead tomorrow
while spankin' it in the shower!
Doing what?
My point is, there
are too many things
to waste your time and
energy worrying about.
--[chirping]
--Uh?
An e-mail?
We're short all of these parts?
No. Are you sending me
to grab this crap now?!
[AYAMI]
You say somethin', little boy?!
[QWENTHUR whimpers]
Um, Qwenthur? Did you give her
your e-mail address, too?
It's just a work thing,
it means nothing.
You're the only
one I love, baby.
[gasps]
Get your tuchus in gear,
ya lazy long hair!
We haven't got all day!
[QWENTHUR]
Aye-aye!
[QWENTHUR growls]
How did this many things
get left until the last second?
By the time I'm done
unloading this,
I'll have graduated with honors.
[CHARLOTTE]
You, there.
"You, there"?
Her uniform's different.
I wonder who she is...
Oh, hi. Can I help
you, my lady?
You don't need to call me a
lady. I was born a commoner.
Though, you wouldn't be the
first to make the same mistake.
More importantly,
this is about you.
[QWENTHUR]
Uh...?
[CHARLOTTE]
Other than the Baby Magnum's
Elite and maintenance
crew, all personnel were ordered
to standby until further
instruction, no exceptions.
[QWENTHUR] Crap! She's the
straight laced brown nosey type!
I know, and I'm sorry,
but I have a request
from maintenance to bring these
materials for final repairs!
What is your affiliation
and rank?
[gasps]
[CHARLOTTE]
Affiliation and rank.
I need an answer.
Gun?! I'm a student!
I'm a designated engineer,
but as for where I belong
in the battalion,
that's kind of a gray area!
But basically,
if I'm not getting chewed
out with my buddy Havia,
then Granny's giving me a
lecture in the maintenance bay!
[CHARLOTTE]
A student, huh?
How disappointing.
That's not my jurisdiction.
[exhales]
Bang!
[yelps]
You're not official
military personnel.
My oversight duties
don't apply to you.
Please excuse me.
[QWENTHUR sighs]
[HAVIA] So tell me more about
this lady in the black uniform.
[QWENTHUR]
She pulled a revolver on me,
and asked "affiliation
and rank?"
The oversight.
What's it all about?
They're supervising the
battlefront. What a joke.
But they keep an
eye on us anyway.
Making sure we don't commit
any crimes or abuse POWs.
They're basically keeping
tabs on everything.
How novel.
This "oversight"
sounds more intrusive
than your average dorm
resident advisor.
That's why it's better
to stay on her good side.
Though honestly,
I don't think you have
too much to worry about.
Black uniforms deal with
official military personnel,
and non-regular combat personnel
that we hire on-site.
But as far as classifications
go, you're still a civilian.
[FROLAYTIA]
As you were.
I hope everyone had a nice nap
and a belly full of coffee,
because you'll wish you had
when you're out in the
middle of the night,
facing the biting cold.
Now then, eyes forward,
mouths shu--
Uh!
Someone's off her game.
Booberella's never acted so
nervous before a briefing.
Back of the room, right corner.
A CS TV camera is filming.
[HAVIA] This whole TV show
thing's a big pain in the butt.
It's bad enough they
keep getting in our way,
but they've got everybody
walking on eggshells.
[FROLAYTIA]
Let's start, shall we?
Our mission is to infiltrate
Faith Organization territory,
and proceed to capture and
destroy the military coal mine
on the eastern coast of
the Kamchatka peninsula.
According to Intelligence
Division analysis,
this military coal mine
is providing fuel
for JP-level MHD reactors
which are capable of
powering Objects.
With the coal mine's
destruction,
the Faith Organization's
military
will learn the limits
of their capabilities
as they struggle with
their impeded movement.
But that's not all.
[clears throat, coughs]
As I was saying, they've
deployed a second gen Object
to try and stymie our advance.
This photo was taken
three months ago,
over the Pacific Ocean.
Designated the "Wing Balancer".
It's disproportionate in size
to the large gun barrel,
with the main weapon being
a small caliber coil gun.
Though not very powerful, it's
capable of piling up damage
over time by scoring
long range hits.
This second gen unit relies
on air jets to get around,
and has full amphibious
functionality
without the need to
exchange parts.
I'll cut to the chase.
It's formidable.
It's not the sort of
opponent we can send
the Baby Magnum
against head-on.
[NUTSRAY] Heh. She's drop-dead
gorgeous, chesty,
and honest to boot! I could've
done a whole lot worse
with my officer assignment!
[clears throat]
I want you to check out our
upcoming field of battle,
the eastern coast of
the Kamchatka peninsula.
What the heck is that?
It's almost like
a spider's web!
[COOKMAN] That's the result
of the Bering Sea earthquake,
although the Faith
Organization's
submarine base project
takes some of the blame.
With that topography,
the amphibious Object
will have an
overwhelming advantage.
The Baby Magnum needs
to exchange parts
to operate on water.
The terrains not in her favor.
That's why I brought
the lot of you together
for this mission briefing.
Let me guess, you're leaving
things up to Havia and me?
You can relax. We have
a plan this time.
The enemy put these
radar dishes in place
with the intent of improving
the Wing Balancer's accuracy.
Instead, we'll put them
to work for us.
You'll head for the radar base,
then upload a program
we've prepared
to throw off their supplemental
targeting data.
A question! Once they notice
the targeting is off,
won't the Wing Balancer
move to act independently?
You've seen the size
of that thing.
Objects aren't as simple
as fluorescent lights,
where one switch can
turn it off or on.
Even if it only takes
a minute or two
to switch back over to manual,
that's all the time
the Princess will need.
So to boil it all down,
you're ordering us to go and
hack the radar facility.
[FROLAYTIA] The radar facility
and their UAVs to be precise.
[NUTSRAY] UAVs? Like, unmanned
aerial vehicles?
[FROLAYTIA]
Sounds like this student
has learned his
military acronyms.
[NUTSRAY]
Heh.
A student?
I wonder if he's
anything like you.
[FROLAYTIA] There's a
surveillance network of UAVs
covering all approaches
to the facility.
So your first job is to disable
these eyes in the sky.
Charles.
[CHARLES]
Uh! Right.
The UAVs fly with
complete autonomy,
but follow parameters set by
their navigation software.
There's a catch.
A course correction is
uploaded every half hour
to adjust their flight paths.
That's the exploit
we're looking for.
Well isn't that convenient?
The post-earthquake
geography is complicated.
If you don't send
frequent updates,
then you risk slamming 50,000
euros worth of technology
into the face of a cliff.
[CHARLES]
Yes.
We simply have to infect a
single UAV out on patrol.
From there, it should spread to
every other unit in the field.
And that's when we move in.
Now, I'll go over
the plan of attack
on our primary target,
the coal mine.
First, Unit A will go to
Point One on the coast,
and upload the virus
to the enemy UAV.
Next up, Unit B,
you'll head inland
to Point Two,
and patch into the
radar facility's cables
to upload the sabotage
program directly.
At that point, the
Princess will mobilize.
With the enemy's targeting
systems corrupted,
she'll proceed to Point Three,
and put the Wing Balancer
down with one shot.
With their Object
out of the picture,
we'll offer the coal mine
terms of surrender.
We'll give them a grace period
to evacuate their personnel,
and then the Baby Magnum will
turn her guns on the mine.
If we proceed
according to schedule,
then by daybreak we'll have
a base-wide champagne-filled
water gun fight
in celebration of our victory.
Uh! [coughs]
As of now, the Kamchatka
Peninsula Nighttime Blitz
has the green light!
I wish you all good luck.
[ALL]
Thank you, Major!
[HAVIA]
This is all wrong.
Screwed up beyond
all recognition.
What are you talking about?
It's simple, Myonri.
The fact that I, the great
and handsome Havia,
have been sent to the
dangers of the front line again.
While my buddy Qwenthur gets to
be on standby in the safer rear!
[COOKMAN] It seemed to me
like Major Capistrano
wanted to toss that Qwenthur
kid right in the warpath
with the rest of us.
But with the Black Uniforms
here asserting their authority,
sending a civilian student
off to the front line
was no longer
a viable option.
And besides, Qwenthur
and the rest of Unit A
are headed to Point One
to disable the UAVs.
It's not like he's curled
up snug in bed, y'know.
You have a lot to learn
about this world, Myonri.
Him getting it easier
than me, even by a little,
is absolutely criminal!
[WESTY] You're upset
because your boyfriend
isn't here to keep you
warm, just admit it.
Shut your trap, Westy!
And why would you want to pair
up two straight guys anyway?
He says, like he's never
fantasized about two girls
getting together for
his viewing pleasure.
You got the two girls right,
but in my dreams I
do more than watch!
Fair enough.
When dreams are all you have,
you might as well dream big.
I feel like a teacher
leading a field trip.
[QWENTHUR]
Wow, look at that aurora!
It's not entirely wasted on
a future Object designer.
But this kind of assignment
seems better for someone
in a different field.
Like environmental science.
[NUTSRAY] Quit griping and enjoy
it, you gargantuan gearhead.
If you study harsh
environments to operate in,
it can only help to
flesh out the margins
of your future designs.
If I'm learning to adapt my
designs to colder environments,
a walk-in freezer is more
than enough, Nutsray.
[NUTSRAY]
The trick to a happier life
is to pick up new ideas
in new places,
to find inspiration no
matter what situation
you may find yourself in.
Judging by your outlook
and lust for life,
I'd say you're a
tequila drinker.
Hey, Charles! I think the
charm of playing in the snow
has started to wear off,
wouldn't you agree?
Yo, Charles!
Once the homesickness sets
in, he gets all distant.
Or at least, gloomier.
Do you really think we can rely
on Mister Social Graces, here?
He helped develop
the sabotage program,
and he's in charge of hacking.
That's a lot for
such a timid guy.
[NUTSRAY] No better reason
for our current lineup!
Charles is such a
terribly gloomy,
shy-around-strangers-type.
Having our team with students
instead of soldiers
can help reduce tension,
which makes the mission
more likely to succeed.
Looks like one non-student
member of our team
is raising tensions
all by herself, though.
[NUTSRAY] Apparently, Miss Class
President's name is Charlotte.
She leaves as soon as her
oversight duties are over,
though. Gotta admit,
I'd love to seal the deal
with that one before
she leaves. [chuckles]
You realize we aren't going
to be students abroad
on deployment forever.
How many quote "practical
skills" can you acquire
with such a cavalier attitude?
I'll just repeat a year
and extend my time abroad,
if I have to.
The major premise here
is to be happy, okay?
If you're all doom and gloom,
you won't have any luck gettin'
things to stick upstairs!
[grunts] What're you
in such a hurry for?
You're studying to be
a designer, right?
You really want to
be rich that badly?
When I was little,
there was a noble family
that lived in our neighborhood.
A famous family name
and a sprawling mansion.
They looked so secure,
so unshakeable.
But one day, their
family fell to ruin,
and the neighborhood
turned on them.
The family decided to flee.
Even their former servants
were hunting them.
I remember they had
a spoiled daughter.
I'm talking annoying.
It makes me sick to think
of what the mob might have
done to her if my father
hadn't offered them shelter.
[NUTSRAY] Your dad must be
one hell of a courageous man.
I admire that.
One small ripple
can bring a noble family
tumbling down to nothing.
Even now, it's burned
into my eyes.
Mighty nobles so used to
getting their way all the time.
Huddled together, trembling in
a commoner's cramped storehouse.
To be rock-solid.
How much wealth does
it take to get there?
And if a commoner ever
wants that stability,
he can't afford to be
conventional, can he?
Guess not.
But I don't plan to risk
my life against Objects.
I can't work miracles
like you can,
Mister Qwenthur Barbotage
the Giant Slayer.
All right, Charles.
It's about time we got that
antenna set up, isn't it?
[CHARLOTTE]
You, there.
I apologize, but I couldn't help
but overhear your conversation.
Then you understand
why I wanna be rich.
Your desire for financial
security is only natural.
But if you want my opinion,
the character your father
showed when those people
needed help is the kind of
stability money can't buy.
That's only because you don't
know what he's really like.
My old man is a lowly,
non-descript office worker.
He's spent his career bowing
and scraping to let his future
be constricted by
modest pensions.
If the company ever
went bankrupt,
he'd be up a creek
without a paddle.
And that's a possible fate
for anyone, pedigree or not.
[CHARLOTTE] I still respect
a man with integrity.
Despite the danger, he reached
out to the family in need.
He sounds like an absolutely
wonderful father.
If he does lose his job,
I'd like to help.
Tell him to contact Charlotte
Zoom, should he find the need.
For a man of his caliber,
I know I could refer him to
a job that would be suitable.
Thank you, that's very kind.
[CHARLOTTE]
Out of curiosity,
what happened to the ruined
noble family after that?
They got their chance
at a fresh start in life
with new identities from
the Bureau of Ancestry.
And if I remember correctly,
that annoying,
spoiled daughter of theirs
became a starlet
somewhere, I think.
[MONICA]
Here we go! Ta-da!
It's time to check out
the 37th Mechanized
Maintenance Battalion's
totally awesome
command center!
That figure of feminine ferocity
is the commanding officer,
Major Frolaytia Capistrano!
Hey, this is a
restricted area!
[FROLAYTIA]
It's all right.
The higher-ups have ordered
us to fully cooperate.
And for that,
I'm super grateful!
However, since we currently
have an operation underway,
we'll have to check all
the footage your crew
has shot so far.
Fine!
Uh?
Uh... Ah!
Is that a diagram of
the Baby Magnum?!
[FROLAYTIA]
No. You're looking at
the 24th Mechanized
Maintenance Battalion's
new second gen Object.
Codename: Indigo Plasma.
Wow! What a cool name!
It's actually a decoy.
Because of its presence, the
Wing Balancer is staying put,
ready for a standoff.
While Indigo Plasma
is drawing focus,
Baby Magnum will proceed
to Operation Point Three.
We've got two Objects,
and the enemy only has one.
Couldn't we just beat
'em with brute force?
There's more than the enemy
Object's combat power.
Between the geography, and
the defense facilities,
a straight-forward path
would be advised against.
So the answer is 'no.'
[coughs]
[MONICA]
Ah... Sounds complicated!
[HAVIA]
That's a long way down.
You'd fall to your death.
So then, what're we
gonna do now, chief?
The mission requires us to be
on the other side, but first,
we've gotta figure out how
to get across this gorge.
According to the map,
we'll find a suspension
bridge three klicks north.
And I'll bet that bridge is
covered by surveillance devices,
with artillery zeroed
in for good measure.
In other words, if we
take a route that diverges
from what the enemy
expects from us,
we'll better our odds of
remaining undetected.
Myonri, please.
[MYONRI]
Mm.
Don't tell me. She's got
an inflatable boat!
We'll make our
descent right here,
cross the water, and
then climb back up.
It's the simplest, quickest
way to get to the other side
without exposing
ourselves on a bridge.
Of course, why not?
[QWENTHUR] So, the transmission
antenna is fully set up now?
[NUTSRAY]
Yeah!
Now we just have to track down
a target to relay the virus to.
So what?
Go and confirm the
location of a UAV.
But why me?
[NUTSRAY] Well, I'm the one
who set up the antenna.
Charles is in charge of
sending the data. So...
Which one of us hasn't
done anything yet?
[QWENTHUR]
All right, fine, I'll go dammit.
Totally figures I'd end up with
the riskiest job of them all.
I'll join you as well.
Since I haven't done
anything so far, either.
[QWENTHUR]
Uh, thanks, but--
You move like an amateur, and
forget to cover your tracks.
I can't allow you to
be spotted so easily.
[QWENTHUR]
Uh!
Hey Qwenthur, when you
guys go hide behind a rock
to get it on, be
sure to call me!
When it's this cold, the more
people there are, the merrier!
[CHARLOTTE]
You should watch your mouth.
if you were a regular soldier,
I would've blasted a
hole in you already.
Wow, good luck for me!
I'm not a regular soldier!
[chuckles]
[ANNOUNCER A] Upon completion
of the floating parts exchange,
transition to sequence Sexy.
Crew members are to take shelter
in the waterproofed sector.
Repeat.
Crew members take shelter...
[MILINDA]
Baby Magnum, booting up.
You heard the announcement!
[MILINDA]
I'll see you real soon!
I hope you're right, dear.
Ya ask me, this mission's
a damn circus act.
It'll be okay.
I know Qwenthur will create an
opening for me to hit 'em hard.
This is Baby Magnum.
I am mobilizing and headed
to Point Three now.
[AYAMI] It's not you that
concerns me, Princess.
I'm worried about
that foolish boy.
Infiltrating enemy territory?
If somethin' happens,
he'll be surrounded by
enemies on all sides.
[NUTSRAY] Charles! How's
the program coming along?
We good to go?
What's the matter, Chuck?
Didn't anyone tell you
when you were a kid?
When somebody's talkin' to you,
you should look 'em square in
the eye. Cause if you don't...
It can get dangerous.
[QWENTHUR grunts]
Relax. You don't want
to tense up like that.
They won't have an easy time
finding us in this blizzard,
so try to stay loose.
I'll try to keep that
in mind, thanks.
[CHARLOTTE]
Small speck, north-northwest.
[QWENTHUR]
I see an eagle, is that it?
[CHARLOTTE] Farther behind it.
There's something else.
It's strange that a bird
that isn't nocturnal
would be flying around
so late in this weather.
Did a noise startle it
into taking flight?
[QWENTHUR]
I found it!
Twenty-nine hundred meters
to the north-northwest.
[CHARLOTTE]
Just talk right into it.
[QWENTHUR] Charles!
The target is moving at 150KPH.
Going from BC-Nine to BF-Nine.
It's proceeding right
alongside the cliffs,
so check the geography
to make an estimate.
Charles? Are you there,
Charles? Come in!
[CHARLOTTE] That's odd,
his radio's connecting.
I get being homesick, but
this is just ridiculous.
[CHARLOTTE]
I'll go check in on him--
[gunshots]
[CHARLOTTE gasps]
Charlotte!
[gunshots]
[QWENTHUR gasping]
[QWENTHUR]
But... why...?
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA] "The Coal Mine
Littered with Stacks of Money."
[MILINDA] "The Kamchatka
Peninsula Nighttime Blitz II."