[HAVIA]
Hey.
Does this feel like an
enormous step down to you?
Where's the appreciation
for busting Flide?
Probably canceled out by all
the orders we've disobeyed.
[VANDERBILT]
Lovely.
I'm utterly pleased to hear Lord
Havia's doing so frickin' well.
[FROLAYTIA]
But of course.
He is the heir to the
illustrious Winchell family.
We wouldn't possibly
risk sending him
to any truly dangerous
front lines.
That is a relief.
I can scarcely find
the words to explain
how much it would frickin' suck
if he were to be killed
before our grand ceremony.
I don't mean to be rude,
but isn't it true that both the
Winchell and Vanderbilt families
are vehemently opposed
to your betrothal?
With matters of love,
the greater the obstacle,
the greater the passion.
You should try falling in love
yourself, Miss Soldier. So...
Is Lord Havia free to
speak with his fiancée?
[groans] I can't take anymore.
Objects do all of the
fighting in these days,
so what's the point
of sticking us
with the busy work
of loading shells?
[QWENTHUR]
Beats me.
But compared to our
last few missions,
don't you find it restful?
No, it's not restful!
Really. This is the
kind of tedious work
that should be reserved
for machines.
[HAVIA]
Huh?
Oh, crap, Qwenthur.
You won't believe what I found.
[QWENTHUR]
Hm?
Hidden treasure!
Ten-Hut!
I'm Mistress Jessica,
your brilliant and
experienced captain.
It's my job to whip you
soft, quivering recruits
into hardened soldiers!
Now come at me, all at once!
[AV ACTOR A]
Oh, Captain!
[AV ACTOR B]
No! You're too much, Captain!
[JESSICA]
Yes you can!
[QWENTHUR]
I'm starting to get the feeling
that you need a dominant
woman to submit to.
Hey, I just found the thing!
It's not like I bought it!
But, wait. What the...
My pace is increasing!
[JESSICA]
On your feet, you baby!
No one told you you
could take a break!
You don't stop until Mistress
Jessica gives you the order!
You're right!
The work goes faster when you
match the rhythm of her voice!
It's like my hands are
moving on their own!
I don't even feel the urge
to take a break anymore!
Quit your sniveling and begging
and move those fingers faster!
You better keep Mistress
Jessica from getting bored!
Yes, Mistress Jessica!
I won't let you down!
I'll do whatever you say!
Oh, yes, captain! My captain!
[JESSICA]
Yes, like that!
Just what the frickin' hell
do you think you're doing?
[HAVIA yelps]
Oh, Lord Havia.
A noble effort.
But you left some evidence
on the back shelf there.
[HAVIA screams]
Who's that girl?
Is she a friend of yours?
[HAVIA] She's the daughter
of the Vanderbilt family.
Long story, I'll tell you later.
What do you want?
I'm on duty here.
[VANDERBILT] Do we need a
reason to have a conversation?
Besides, it's perfectly frickin'
normal for a betrothed couple
to speak on a daily basis.
Whoa, betrothed?!
What in the world is that
grim and dingy room you're in?
Does the Winchell
family approve
of this moonlighting of yours?
Look, I've got a lot going on.
That might be tough for a
pampered girl sipping tea
in the Safe Nation.
[VANDERBILT]
Yes, the Safe Nation.
Aptly named, is it not?
I'm on vacation at the most
isolated and distant resort
from all of the conflicts
plaguing our planet.
National flags aren't
even recognized here.
[HAVIA]
Hm?
All right, you two noobs.
Come on, I've got
a new job for you.
I need to borrow him.
[VANDERBILT]
Of course.
[HAVIA]
Uh... Wait. Hey, hey, hey!
Put him through the frickin'
grinder, just don't kill him.
Hurry up and make the
poor boy a war hero.
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR screaming]
[HAVIA]
For real?
Antarctica?
Ant-freakin'-arctica?!
[QWENTHUR] It doesn't even
make sense to ship us here.
There aren't any Objects
on this continent.
[FROLAYTIA] One of our
Legitimate Kingdom survey planes
was doing a routine scan of
the coastline by the Ross Sea
when they were targeted by
a surface-to-air missile.
They marked it with
a lock-on laser
intending to hold the
passengers hostage.
Fortunately, the survey plane
was able to flee outside
the missile range.
[QWENTHUR] There's no
way it could've escaped
if it was targeted by an Object.
And I don't need to tell you
that Objects aren't even
equipped with S.A.Ms.
That's right.
Evidence suggests that the enemy
doesn't even have an Object.
[HAVIA]
In that case,
the outcome is pretty
much already determined.
The Princess aims
the Baby Magnum,
fires off a shot, and boom!
[FROLAYTIA]
Not quite.
For our time in Antarctica,
Objects are off the table.
[HAVIA]
Huh?
The monster does weigh well
over 200 thousand tons. So...
On the most rudimentary
strategic level,
it would be a dumb move
to drive it out onto a
continent made of ice.
Yeah, okay, um...
The both of us are members of
an Object maintenance unit.
So what exactly do you recommend
we do without an Object?
The same thing you always do.
We're sending you
ahead of the unit
to fight the terrorists for us.
It feels more like I'm getting
pummeled with fists than wind!
[QWENTHUR]
This is Antarctica.
It actually gets down
to 50 degrees below.
Uh. This sucks! It's a
frozen barren wasteland.
I mean, couldn't
there at least be
some cute penguins
or something?
Why would they bother
setting up S.A.Ms out here
in the middle of nowhere?
What the hell are these
terrorists up to?
[FROLAYTIA]
Well, it is your mission
to get to the bottom of it.
But there's still no need to
engage them once you find them.
We've got the
Princess on standby
in the Baby Magnum off
the coast of the Ross Sea.
All you need to do is relay
the terrorists' location
and the Princess will
blow them to hell
with long-range
artillery fire.
[HAVIA] So you didn't even
need to send us by foot?
Couldn't you have just done
a thorough scan of the area
with military satellites?
Not that I'd actually
expect you to understand
how much we're suffering in
the freezing cold out here,
not like where you are. Probably
bundled up and barking orders
from the bridge
while sipping cocoa.
The situation's a little
complicated in Antarctica.
The stationary satellites
close to the equator
don't have the
surveillance reach.
Polar-orbiting military
satellites run into sovereignty
issues, so the Legitimate
Kingdom can't use them.
Communication satellites
for scientific studies
are the only ones
that are authorized.
[slurping]
Did I just hear a slurping?!
I did!
You really are sipping cocoa!
[gun shot]
[BOTH grunt]
[QWENTHUR]
The terrorists?!
Does it really matter?
[HAVIA]
Distance, 200.
About 7 or 8 of them.
[QWENTHUR]
Can you get them?
Why are you asking like
you're just a spectator?
Get out your gun and take aim!
Uh, well, I don't
have a firearm.
I've only got explosives on me.
What the hell'd you come out
here without a gun for?!
[QWENTHUR]
Well...
I wanted to bring
one with me, but--
[FROLAYTIA] I can't issue
military firearms to a student.
I would like to, but not until
he's finished his training.
[HAVIA] Explosives are
way more dangerous!
[HAVIA] Wait, that was
definitely slurping I heard!
[HAVIA]
Why am I the only one
who has to risk his life
by returning fire?!
We could really use a little
help here, Princess!
At that location, the
shockwave from the cannon
would be massive.
And it would mow you both
down right along with them.
But it's your call. Over.
Damn it, damn it,
damn it, damn it!
Oh, no.
Yeah, it's safe to say
that we're screwed.
That's not what I meant.
There's penguins!
Huh? Penguins?
[HAVIA]
Baby penguins?!
--[penguins honking]
--[TERRORISTS] Uh...
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR]
Aww!
[TERRORISTS]
Aww.
[HAVIA gasps]
Don't do it, Havia.
Let Mother Nature have this
one. We can't interfere.
[HAVIA]
Huh...
[TERRORIST A]
Yes!
[TERRORISTS cheering]
Leave it to Mother Nature
to bring us together.
We're all on the same side
when it comes to penguins.
[BOTH gasping]
Well, damn, I guess our
penguin break is over!
[HAVIA] I don't see how
the map's gonna help us
not get shot! It's not
like the Princess
can give us any backup!
Never mind, just keep firing!
Try to keep them at bay.
Damn it!
[HAVIA] What, you
can't throw that far!
[HAVIA] Oh! I told you!
Way to waste a bomb!
It landed right where
I wanted it to.
Now, get down!
[TERRORISTS screaming]
[HAVIA]
How did you pull that one off?
It's pretty easy if you
just look at the map.
They were standing on
nothing but pure ice.
But it was basically
an ice bridge
covering a rocky V-shaped cliff.
So, I got rid of the bridge.
[HAVIA] I'm never gonna doubt
your skills with a map again.
I can't take all the credit,
the bomb helped a little.
[FROLAYTIA]
The Legitimate Kingdom's
unmanned observation
post is nearby.
We determined the
S.A.M.'s location
by reverse calculating
the targeting laser.
Man, I thought Alaska was bad,
but this cold is murder!
I'm starting to think
global warming is a lie.
I'm no climatologist, but
it's not like it's gonna turn
Antarctica into some
tropical paradise.
--[radio static]
--[BOTH] Uh?
[MILINDA] Can we hurry and
wrap this up, already?
The heat is making it
really stuffy in here.
Qwenthur.
You messed with the AC during
maintenance, didn't you?
Uh! Oh, well...
The Princess's castle sounds
more comfy than ever.
[MILINDA sighs]
It's so hot.
Not like anyone's watching,
so I might as well strip down.
Doesn't look like there's gonna
be any high-speed combat anyway.
Um, is that your way of kindly
trying to keep us warm
by firing up our imaginations?
[QWENTHUR]
Looks like the observation post.
[HAVIA] Actually, does it feel
like it's getting warmer?
Or is that just the effect of
picturing the Princess naked?
[QWENTHUR]
We're in a volcanic area.
So there's geothermal heat
rising from the ground.
[HAVIA gasps, laughs]
Check it out, Qwenthur!
That's a hot spring!
Wow.
Who would've thought you could
find a hot spring in Antarctica?
[FROLAYTIA]
Well?
Have you located the S.A.Ms yet?
Nope, but we found a hot spring.
So go on and grab your bikini.
[FROLAYTIA] Huh? You want
me to grab what now?
[HAVIA] Grab some new
pants for me instead.
Those are rail guns
meant for Objects!
[BOTH whimper]
[BOTH yelp]
Damn it! Why the hell do
they have those set up?
[HAVIA]
Qwenthur, this way!
[QWENTHUR grunts]
[BOTH scream]
[BOTH groan]
[HAVIA] Man, this is
not looking good!
It's even worse
than you realize.
The only way to operate those
things is with a reactor!
Hold on, are you saying...
Run of the mill
terrorists, my ass!
These guys have got
an Object somewhere!
Try to stay calm.
I'm not picking up any
signs of an Object.
Did you just tell
me to stay calm?!
C'mon, Qwenthur!
Can't you pull that same
move from earlier?
Blow up the ice and drag
them down into a canyon?
Yeah, I would if I could.
But the ground around
here is solid bedrock.
Uh! Come in, Baby Magnum!
Can your artillery
fire reach this far?!
[MILINDA]
There's a mountain between us
so I can't directly
target anything.
I could set the coil guns
to fire in a broad arc.
That's really the only way
to clear the obstacle.
There's no time to target
each one of them.
Here's the grid data!
Based on coordinates
zero zero two one two.
W11.
J18.
G26.
M19.
L27.
B20.
R12!
I'll try, but...
I don't know if I
can hit the targets
with those scattered
coordinates.
Just trust me and open
fire! That'll do it!
Bring a torrent of coil gun
fire and unleash hell!
[BOTH grunt]
Damn it, she didn't hit
a single one of them!
What do we do, man?
How do we get out of this?
It's okay.
It is not okay!
You wanna explain
what happened?
They were just too strong
for their own good.
In order to fire an Object
rail gun from the ground
they have to be fixed
in place with anchors.
So, I had the Baby Magnum
render those anchors useless.
[HAVIA]
Uh...
[QWENTHUR] Well technically,
it cracked open the ground
around the anchors and
rendered it useless.
[RADIO ANNOUNCER A]
Investigating the unmanned
observation post. We haven't
found any personnel or Object
that could've operated
the rail guns.
Continuing to search
the surrounding area.
Investigating the unmanned
observation post...
[QWENTHUR]
I'm still confused.
I don't get why the terrorists
threatened the plane
with surface to air missiles.
[HAVIA] I don't know and I
can't say I really care.
[yawns]
I'm too comfy and sleepy
to think about anything.
Hey.
Don't forget that you'll
die if you fall asleep.
There's something kinda
fun about sayin' that.
[HAVIA] I just spotted
something nasty, man.
[QWENTHUR]
Nasty like Mistress Jessica?
[HAVIA exhales]
Not funny!
[QWENTHUR]
Uh?
[HAVIA]
Is it a probe robot?
Yeah. I can't tell
if it's for civilian
or scientific use, though.
[HAVIA] Hey, it looks
like it's functioning!
Who's operating it,
the terrorists?!
[HAVIA]
Whoa, dude!
You think it's smart
to mess with that?!
It might suddenly blow
up on us or something.
That's the least
of our worries.
From what I can tell,
it's being controlled
by a remote lab somewhere
via communication satellite.
And that satellite?
That's what the
terrorists are after.
[HAVIA]
What do you mean?
[QWENTHUR]
The satellite is equipped with a
high-powered laser. They're
trying to hack its system
in order to gain
control of it.
Why would they even bother?
That laser's just for burning
the surface of asteroids
to collect data, right?
I mean, there's no way it could
reach the surface of Earth,
it's just not strong enough.
If their target is Earth, yeah.
But that's not what
they're shooting for.
They wanna destroy the vacation
resort for the rich on the moon.
[HAVIA]
On the moon?!
To be more specific, well,
they're aiming to take
out the Blind Net,
the source of the terraforming
project up there.
[HAVIA]
Hold on, the Blind Net?
That's what provides the optical
secondary atmosphere, right?
If that gets destroyed...
[QWENTHUR]
It'll be havoc from every angle.
The entire resort will be
fried by direct sunlight.
But before that can happen,
the vacuum will kill
everyone from asphyxiation.
Don't worry about it, boys.
It's not your concern.
According to the collated
data from the laser,
the terrorists' target is Rock
Castle's VIP, Buffa Planters.
The major general of the
Capital Enterprise Army.
The Legitimate Kingdom
has actually tried
to assassinate him a few times
in the past and failed.
If the terrorists wanna
do the dirty work for us,
we might as well
turn a blind eye.
[HAVIA groans] Man, my
exhaustion just quadrupled.
I mean, what the hell
have we been fighting for
this whole time?
[QWENTHUR gasps]
[HAVIA]
What's up?
Let's hurry and get back.
Hey, the girl you're engaged to?
[HAVIA]
Uh?
She, um...
Didn't she say that she's
at the most isolated resort
from all of the conflicts
on our planet?
[HAVIA]
Oh, no.
Lord Havia, what a surprise!
It's a rare treat when
you actually call me.
Where the hell are you?!
Where else would I be?
I'm at Rock Castle,
the illustrious vacation
resort on the moon.
[HAVIA]
No!
Uh. Well that was emphatic.
I didn't know the distance
would upset you.
But, if you wanna get closer,
you could always ask
me to frickin' visit.
Well there's some motivation.
Is this really happening?!
The military wants to waste
this major general guy so badly
that they're actually willing
to let the daughter of a
noble family get killed?
I'm betting that Frolaytia
doesn't know she's there.
There's no way she
would've given that order.
Not if she knew there
were civilians up there.
[VANDERBILT]
Okay, what are you two
frickin' whispering about?
[BOTH laugh nervously]
What is it?
Maybe just push it and say
"whoops, my hand slipped."
[HAVIA]
Are you serious?
Do you realize what
you're saying?!
[QWENTHUR] Just do it! It fires
in less than 30 seconds!
[HAVIA]
Fine, damn, I'll do it!
But don't complain if we
get court martialed!
Oh, whoops!
Uh... My hand slipped!
[QWENTHUR]
You idiot!
Wrong one, right there!
Wait, which one?
That one!
This one?
No, right there!
[HAVIA]
Oh, this one.
[QWENTHUR]
Hit it!
[HAVIA grunts]
[VANDERBILT]
You guys are frickin' weird.
Seriously, what are you
wigging out about down there?
[BOTH]
Oh, nothin', just bein' awesome.
We're just modestly
risking life and limb
like a couple of bad asses.
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR gasp]
You're lucky.
This whole looking-the-other-way
thing was off the record,
of course.
It's not like this was some
kind of official mission,
so I couldn't even hold you
responsible if I wanted to.
If it weren't for that, you'd
be behind bars right now.
Yeah, we get it.
Damn it all.
We saved the heroine
like we're supposed to,
and all we get for it
is this guilty lecture.
[laughs]
Well?
How'd the young lady feel
about you saving her?
I'd say she seemed pretty happy.
[FROLAYTIA]
Yeah?
Well, then.
There's no need for
any further questions.
[HAVIA] You feeling a bit
less worried at least?
Yes, although...
Why do you do it?
What do you mean?
[VANDERBILT] I understand
it's not a frickin' easy task
to prove yourself worthy
as the family heir,
but is this worth it?
[HAVIA] What, you're afraid that
the military's too dangerous?
What I saw today seemed
pretty frickin' unsafe.
[HAVIA] Our noble families, the
Winchells and the Vanderbilts,
they both hate each
other so much
that they actually wish
to destroy the other.
[VANDERBILT]
Yes.
[HAVIA] And yet, the two
of us refuse to be held
at the mercy of their
stupid altercation.
You do still feel
that way, don't you?
[VANDERBILT]
Yes, but I don't see wha--
[HAVIA] Well, that's what
I'm trying to explain.
No matter what it takes,
I will succeed as the
head of my family
and put an end to this stupid
bickering so we can be together.
So, I need you to wait for me.
[HAVIA]
With that at stake.
I'll take on every
massive Object
the world can throw at me.
Those are power supply cables.
How could we not have
detected it moving around?
Is it some kind of
submersible Object?
Don't tell me...
Not stealth?
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA]
"Three-Legged Mountain-Climbing
Is Life-and-Death".
[MILINDA] "The Artillery Battle
in the Iguazú Mountains I".