Damn it!
No, Havia!
Don't do it!
He's right!
We have to help him!
I know that! But what
the hell are we gonna do?
[NUTSRAY chuckles]
[ALL gasp]
[GIRL A gasps]
[QWENTHUR grunts]
[NUTSRAY] That girl knew
about the weak spot
on this thing's arm?
Annoying little gnat.
You're the girl from earlier.
No time! Run!
Look out!
Havia! Is she all right?
[HAVIA] I caught her.
She's gonna be just fine!
Okay good. Now back away.
Don't waste your time
trying to fight back!
Hey, get real, man.
We can't just keep running!
[QWENTHUR]
You know what'll happen
if you use that
rifle, don't you?
Fine, we'll do it your way...
[HAVIA] I'll make sure
she gets somewhere safe.
Now's the time to run.
[QWENTHUR]
I'm counting on you, Havia!
Don't you go kicking
the bucket on me!
You crazy, chivalrous idiot.
The Baby Magnum has been hit!
Main gun three knocked
out of commission!
We're having trouble
communicating
with unit Indigo Plasma!
[FROLAYTIA] And we still
haven't made contact
with the two infantry
units we sent in?
[OPERATOR B] It's been two hours
since they were scheduled
to check in, ma'am.
That's not a good sign.
[MONICA] I don't care if the TV
station is calling!
I'm already in full make-up
here, you clowns!
Now, now.
Doesn't matter. I can't
find what I came here for.
I don't care.
[FROLAYTIA groans]
We have an incoming signal!
Unit One or Unit Two?
It isn't one of ours, Major,
and it's not in our database of
previously registered codes.
So who's calling?
[QWENTHUR]
He isn't shooting.
It's a model made for mining.
I doubt it has any weapons.
[QWENTHUR] Just so I know
we're on the same page.
If you had to guess,
who would you say is in this
powered suit, chasing us?
Considering the timing
of the attack,
the most rational
line of thought
would lead us to
the infiltrator.
[QWENTHUR]
Right!
It's time to make
that traitor pay.
Let's give him everything
he deserves!
[NUTSRAY]
You're on foot.
And I'm in a machine.
Your stamina will run
out soon enough.
You really think
you can get away?
[CHARLOTTE] So, how far down
were you planning to run?
Far enough so that Havia and
the others won't get caught
in the blast when I blow
this bastard apart!
[CHARLOTTE] But these tunnels
will constrict the shockwave,
making it travel farther.
[QWENTHUR]
If we're clever,
we should be able to
mitigate the effect.
After all, I only
need a small amount.
[grunts]
[CHARLOTTE]
Well, that's one way to do it.
[QWENTHUR]
Get down!
[CHARLOTTE groans]
[QWENTHUR grunts]
[NUTSRAY]
What the--?
[QWENTHUR] Have a time-delayed
blast. My treat!
[QWENTHUR]
How's that?
That thing's tougher
than I thought.
Run now, ponder later.
[QWENTHUR]
Yes, ma'am!
[CHARLOTTE]
That level of explosives won't
get the job done.
Increase the amount next time!
No can do.
If we increase the amount,
the force of the blast
will bury us alive!
[NUTSRAY sighs] I'm losing
interest in our game of tag.
[NUTSRAY] Let's play a
little baseball next!
[gasps] Look out!
[QWENTHUR]
Charlotte!
[CHARLOTTE]
Damn it all.
[QWENTHUR] Are you okay?
Here, you can lean on me.
Just go on without me.
I'm holding you back, there's
a chance you can escape.
[QWENTHUR]
I would never.
[CHARLOTTE]
No! Just save yourself!
That's enough.
Now shut up and hear me out.
Do you know about
the first Object?
It was developed by a small
island nation in Far East Asia.
What're you talking about?
As an aspiring Object designer,
I respect what they did.
I even learned what I could
about their language
and culture,
but they have one expression
I never cared for.
Enlighten me.
I'm not well-versed
in East Asian idioms.
"Rare beauties die young."
[gasps] Bet ya say that to
all the girls you rescue.
[QWENTHUR]
No need to be like that.
Now let's get back
to the me-risking-my-life-
to-save-you thing.
[NUTSRAY]
Hm.
[QWENTHUR]
What's this place?
[CHARLOTTE]
Unless I'm mistaken,
this area is for sorting the
ore after it's been extracted.
[explosion]
I think we should hide.
Agreed.
It's only a matter of
time before he finds us.
Just stay out of sight.
[CHARLOTTE]
Come back!
[CHARLOTTE] I imagine he has
some kind of plan in mind,
but what?
[QWENTHUR] If this mine
is what we think it is,
there has to be one.
[CHARLOTTE] We're running
out of time, Qwenthur.
Here we go.
Yes! I've got you!
[QWENTHUR grunting]
It's been fun, but I'm tired
of this game of hide and seek.
They've been using
that powered suit model
to mine something very special.
But as a spy, I guess
you knew that already!
Ha, ha. Found you!
[QWENTHUR] This time,
it's no ordinary bomb.
It's more like a claymore with
the world's hardest ore!
You should see yourself.
Sparkling there like a
giant, evil disco ball.
[CHARLOTTE gasping]
And you're welcome.
I gave you the most extravagant
funeral make-up of all time.
[CHARLOTTE]
Look. It's the surface.
Once we're out, you think we
can signal them with this thing?
[CHARLOTTE]
No, it isn't a laser pointer.
It's an IR jamming device.
That's totally misleading.
You know, you can be
mistaken from time to time.
Believe it or not, I've
never thought of myself
as a know-it-all.
[CHARLOTTE gasping]
That light.
It's from a coil gun!
All right. We've gotta
contact Frolaytia.
But we're too far
away to transmit!
Not if we piggyback our signal
off an Object's antenna!
An outside source is
transmitting through my antenna.
[MILINDA]
Qwenthur!
[QWENTHUR]
It's getting to the point
where I'll have to say Object
designing's merely a hobby.
'Cause what I really do is
survive against all odds.
Gimme a sitrep.
[MILINDA] The enemy Object keeps
hopping all over the place.
I'm having a hard
time catching it.
[QWENTHUR]
Those air-cushion types
have a distinct
mobility advantage.
With your Object,
we have to switch out
parts every single time.
And that's a headache.
But its speed isn't much
of a selling point to me.
If we were to exchange fire
under normal circumstances,
my Object would have
defeated theirs already.
[QWENTHUR] The Intelligence
Union's Rush model
was also agile.
They utilized caterpillar
tracks in conjunction
with the Object's
main air cushions
for high-speed mobility.
[MILINDA]
The Rush?
[gasping]
Why did you have to bring
up that horrible woman?
[explosion]
Are you all right?
[MILINDA]
Just a scratch.
I want to help you,
but I need info!
Have you noticed any particular
quirks while fighting it?
Maybe some part it
tries to protect?
It does seem to have a more
delicate suspension system.
Whenever I aim for its feet
it always jumps out of
the way of the blast.
If that's the case,
we've gotta find
a way to make sure
our attacks on its legs
can get through.
It spotted me!
Hit the deck!
It missed me? Of course!
The sabotage program!
[QWENTHUR]
Must've been Havia!
You know I've got your back,
but you owe me big time.
I can't believe we did it!
You've been a big help
acting as our guide!
[MILINDA]
You can't hit me.
[MILINDA gasps]
It changed course,
now it's headed for...
A lens?
I can't miss!
[screaming]
You still alive, Galahad?
Surprisingly!
And I might've found
the Achilles' heel
we were looking for.
I've got an idea.
Dirty coward.
Why don't you pick on
someone your own size!
That's it.
[CHARLOTTE]
Be serious!
That rifle won't be any
good against an Object!
Air cushions work by compressing
the surrounding air.
That means having a greater
surface area is more efficient.
There's only one reason to
forego that kind of advantage.
[QWENTHUR] It has to do with
the terrain's ruggedness.
It has to distribute the
air output and suspension
to match the varying topography
or else it can't neutralize
its own weight!
Which means we simply have to
target the infrared sensor
that detects the evenness
of the terrain!
Give it a shot!
Roger that.
[CHARLOTTE sighs]
[QWENTHUR]
That worked!
It's all over now. We did it!
[radio static]
[FROLAYTIA] Point One.
Glad to see you're still alive.
But I'm afraid your lucky
streak might be at an end.
You need to get out
of there immediately!
There are those who'd
draw out the war
between the Faith
Organization and ourselves.
Forcing us to commit more assets
to this senseless conflict.
To achieve that,
they're planning
the wholesale massacre of the
civilians working in the mine!
Take a deep breath, Major.
It's gonna be fine.
The enemy Object has already
been rendered inoperative.
Now time to close up
shop and head home.
[FROLAYTIA] That Object you
rendered inoperative.
It was the Wing Balancer,
wasn't it?
Huh? Well, yeah.
[FROLAYTIA] Then we still have
one more Object to contend with.
[QWENTHUR]
One more?
But there's only one other
unit on the field of battle.
You mean it's ours?!
That's right.
Someone has an interest
in continuing this war.
The Wing Balancer was
just the beginning.
[QWENTHUR]
Stop it!
Stop firing! There are
still civilians that
need to be evacuated!
[QWENTHUR exhales]
[QWENTHUR] There are those who
profit from the horrors of war.
Friend and foe alike.
Nutsray wasn't an enemy spy.
He was one of our own.
An operative dispatched
by a hostile faction
within our kingdom.
[QWENTHUR]
All for greed.
There's no justice in war.
Only survival.
[FROLAYTIA]
Point One, do you copy?
Point One, if you hear me,
please report in.
[QWENTHUR]
We're still alive, somehow.
But...
the mine.
[FROLAYTIA]
Rest easy.
All the civilians were
evacuated from the mine.
[QWENTHUR]
What?
I thought you'd heard.
The Faith Organization
had originally intended
to build a submarine base.
There was a squadron
of subs left over
from that abandoned project.
The antiwar miners boarded
them and made their escape.
Wait. How'd you know?
[FROLAYTIA]
It was rather easy, actually.
The antiwar group got a
hold of one of our radios,
and established
communication.
Communication?
Even though our
countries are at war?
[FROLAYTIA]
It was all a gamble.
But they were willing
to at least listen
to what I had to say.
And they told us about
the extra facilities
at their disposal
within the mine.
That's great. So they're
all still alive?
Great news!
[FROLAYTIA]
We were able to contact
Havia and Myonri as well.
They reported that they had one
worker under their protection.
So that means there were
zero civilian casualties.
[QWENTHUR]
Then...
[FROLAYTIA]
We saved the day.
We found it in ourselves
to trust the word of others,
and emerged victorious.
[HAVIA]
Still alive and kicking, I see.
[QWENTHUR]
Somehow, yeah.
[HAVIA]
So, did you hear?
[QWENTHUR]
Huh?
The Indigo Plasma isn't alone.
The 24th Maintenance
Battalion is with him.
They made an official
statement on their position.
The Council and
the Royal Congress
are still bickering
over how to handle things.
But one thing's
absolutely certain.
Our next fight will be
against our countrymen.
It's sad, but it's true.
Reminds me of what happened
with Councilor Flide in Oceania.
Speak of the devil; I hear
that old creep escaped.
Though things are tough
when you've been frozen
out of all your assets.
That sounds pretty rough!
A cardboard house at his age.
How can the two of
you act so blasé
about everything
that's happening?
The old bastard
tried to kill us!
Yeah, screw that
wrinkled fartbag.
[MYONRI] I'm talking about
the Indigo Plasma!
This means we're headed for
civil war, doesn't it?
And what is it that we're
fighting for exactly?
One thing's for sure, we're not
fighting for peace or justice.
I'm the successor
to a noble house,
and you're studying to become
a licensed Object designer.
So nothing's really
changed for us.
We know our next fight is going
to be against the Indigo Plasma.
So what?
We'll just use it as another
stepping stone to the top.
[AYAMI]
Hey, you kids!
If you've got time to stand
around, we could use some help!
You think fighting in
one battle's enough
to earn paid time off?!
[QWENTHUR]
Uh.
Just my luck!
Wish I'd been the one to lend
the sexy class-president
chick a shoulder!
First come, first served, bud!
Laugh it up, big shot.
You're comin' with me.
If I'm going to have to do
a lot of manual labor,
I at least want a cute girl
to witness my masculine prowess
and muscular physique!
What?! Cute girl?! Me?!
[CHARLOTTE]
I swear.
I'm not cut out for
this kind of detail.
Being a Black Uniform
specializing in oversight
never prepared me for this.
[QWENTHUR]
You're tellin' me.
I'm just a poor student,
abroad on deployment.
But in the end, it
was all worth it.
Because I am now fully
confident you're not related
to that other matter.
[QWENTHUR]
The what...?
It's a need-to-know-basis thing.
I'm convinced that you two
aren't working for
someone else's agenda.
You're just doing
whatever you can
to save friendlies
in need of rescue.
Before, too.
"Before, too" what?
To tell you the truth,
I've been a big fan of
yours for some time.
There's a bar that
I'm a regular at,
and all of us are
so proud of you.
The bartender even
creates a new cocktail
each time you defeat an Object.
So, I've kept an eye on
what you've been doing.
I choose to be flattered
by your attention.
[QWENTHUR whimpers]
[CHARLOTTE]
What's that?!
[chuckles nervously]
[CHARLOTTE] You moron!
Did you know I've been trained
to strangle a full size man
with one arm around his neck?
I give! Stop it, please.
When you squeeze me
tight like this,
your boob pushes right into my
face not that I'm complaining,
you understand!
Also, I may or may not have
a slight "thing" for armpits
and sexy authoritative women.
I just thought you
might like to know,
since I'm cataloguing
this away for later.
After all the blood I lost,
struggling with you
isn't worth it.
We'll chalk it up
as a one-time pass.
[CHARLOTTE]
It can't be helped, right?
[QWENTHUR]
Uh?!
Officially, I don't
have the authority
to dole out punishment
to civilian personnel,
so this will stay
our little secret.
[MONICA] Why the hell are
we getting sent back now?!
We're a small
production company,
and we're short-handed.
Now rest. We have a couple hours
before we land and have to
start broadcasting again.
I went where I thought he'd
be, but he wasn't there.
Qwenthur, you thoughtless jerk!
You can't avoid me forever!
[CHARLOTTE]
Reporting in.
Qwenthur Barbotage
is in the clear.
[SUPERIOR OFFICER A]
So, we're back to square one.
And you sound excited,
if I'm not mistaken.
What?
No sir.
[coughs]
Anyway, their victories aren't
due to the List's scenarios,
as expected, but rather,
their own efforts.
[SUPERIOR OFFICER A]
I see. This new development
with the 24th Mechanized
Maintenance Battalion
has the Royal Congress
in an uproar.
He may only be a student,
but having someone
like him we can rely on
is joyous news indeed.
[CHARLOTTE]
Shall I continue to accompany
the 37th Mechanized Maintenance
Battalion for the time being?
[SUPERIOR OFFICER A]
No.
I need you to keep pursuing
leads from the List.
We have new intel related
to the fugitive Flide.
You're to look into it.
[CHARLOTTE]
You can count on me, sir.
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA] "You Can't
Put a Price on Honor".
[MILINDA] "The Critical Running
Battle on Victoria Island I".