[QWENTHUR] I can't believe you
found such a fine specimen.
Impressive.
I'm a nobleman, remember?
I have my secret sources.
What about you?
[QWENTHUR]
Here, take a look.
I think you'll find this
trade favorable.
[HAVIA gasps]
Wow, man.
How'd you ever track down
something this rare?
I've got my sources,
just like you.
Even so, it didn't come easy.
Sly dog. You're savvier
than I thought.
Can't wait to see what
future trades will bring.
Yeah. Me neither!
[door opens]
[OFFICER A]
Don't move!
[BOTH]
Uh!
Freeze right where you are!
Wait! What's going on?
This isn't what it looks like!
Ah... Ah!
I swear! I don't know anything!
Hands on the wall, creep!
This has gotta be a mistake!
You have the right
to remain silent!
Anything you say can and
will be used against you
in the court martial
proceedings.
Dude... Weak!
I'm innocent!
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA gasp]
Give it up! We've got
the dirt on your filth!
As suspected, their
hidden stash is huge.
We found some
more over here.
There's even more
in the lockers.
[FROLAYTIA]
Well, well. What have we here?
A mountain of dirty books.
[OFFICER A] The proclivities
they cater to are wide ranging,
but the majority seem
to involve large bosoms.
Perverts.
[OFFICER C] Then there's the
pantyhose and heel fetish mag.
Exclusively featuring
blonde models.
Disgusting.
We found some that
were cosplay themed,
and a large pile called
"Blondes in Bondage."
Scumbags.
[HAVIA, QWENTHUR]
Uh...
[FROLAYTIA]
Mm.
Ooh! Now that's titillating!
So, this is what gets your
horndog motors running?
That pose doesn't
look very comfortable.
What do you boys do
when you look at this?
I bet it's gross.
Speak up now!
[BOTH] Uh. Please.
Stop, we'll do anything!
Anything?
In that case,
it would be rude of me to deny
your generous offer of service!
And since you asked so nicely,
I've got a mission
that'll suit you.
[BOTH]
A mission?
In the perfect place for virile
young men like you to cool off!
[HAVIA]
Alaska.
[QWENTHUR]
Here we go again.
Great to see ya again, Alaska.
You shouldn'ta gone
to all the trouble
of getting colder just for us.
New plan, Qwenthur.
While we're here,
we might as well go looking
for Santa Claus's workshop.
[QWENTHUR] Dude, Santa
lives at the North Pole.
Or maybe Northern Europe.
[HAVIA]
Whatever.
Maybe we should ask
the know-it-alls
from the Faith Organization?
Man, it's like there's
nothing but rubble
as far as the eye can see.
I wonder how many klicks the
explosion scattered this junk?
[QWENTHUR]
Once upon a time,
there was an Object called
the Water Strider.
It was a cutting-edge, second
gen unit everyone thought
would be too much for a first
gen Object to overcome.
But it was miraculously
destroyed
by a student on
deployment abroad,
and a blue-blooded
radar analyst.
All that remained was
a mountain of treasure
too great to haul away.
Weighing roughly 200,000 tons.
The Intelligence Division
frantically combed
through the rubble
analyzing the surviving
enemy tech
and extracting whatever rare
metals they could find.
All done, that
big enough to fit?
Yeah, perfect.
Hand-axe is so powerful,
this'll be plenty.
Setting the detonator on
a timer, per instructions.
The enemy could've sent
Advance Recon to set up jammers.
But they can't jam us if
we don't send a signal.
All right. Let's bug out.
Our enemy this time is one
of the Intelligence Union's
top-tier Second-Gen Objects.
The whiz kids over in the
Intel Division have given it
the official designation
"Codename: Rush".
Please tell me it's not Ohoho.
Is it the same second
gen we saw in Oceania?
Yes, but I'd advise
you not mention it
in front of the Princess.
Knowing her, it'd make
her all flustered.
Ha, ha, ha. I can imagine.
Well, that sucks.
Oh, bummer.
Stick out your tush.
[HAVIA]
Uh!
All right, but what
the heck for?
[HAVIA screaming]
[HAVIA groans]
[HAVIA] Oh, that hurt!
What's the big idea?
Where I come from, we have
a little tradition
when some doofus not
only misses his shot,
but scratches the cue ball,
whoever's up next gives
a swift kick in the butt
to the fool who missed.
That's the rule.
[BOTH]
What kinda rule is that?
Lemme show ya how it's done.
[QWENTHUR gasps]
[FROLAYTIA] The wreckage
of the Water Strider
is scattered around
the Alaskan wilderness.
Technologies related to its
design, digital programs.
It's a veritable buffet
of military secrets.
[FROLAYTIA]
As the ones who are responsible
for blasting their
Object to scrap metal,
we in the Legitimate Kingdom
have the right to take it all.
But there are
scavengers out there
who'd also like a
piece of the pie.
We've known for a few weeks
now that the Intelligence Union
already has people lurking
around the wreckage,
trying to grab
anything they can.
But now they've gone too far.
They threw an antenna
relay together
and are continually transmitting
all analyzed data back
home to their bosses.
Our orders have come down.
The brass wants us to make sure
the facility is destroyed.
Which of course, they
won't take lying down.
The logical conclusion
is they'll dispatch
their Arctic Circle Object.
Codename: Rush,
piloted by Ohoho.
And bolstered by
its two trademark
serial swift beam-type
Gatling guns.
Hang on a sec.
That kind of firepower,
and you're sendin' us in
to knock it out of action?
After what we found,
I don't think you're in
any position to complain.
[QWENTHUR gasping]
It's no use, Qwenthur.
Hear it in the voice
straining to get out
from under those
ginormous ta-tas?
Her voice sounds the same way
every time she asks
us to achieve
the "impossible mission."
Don't talk about me like I'm
some bully on a power trip.
The Princess is the
star of the show.
You clowns are just
the supporting actors,
which I've already taken
into account, so shut up.
It's a cut-and-dry
blasting operation.
Uh!
Step on up then, Qwenthur.
Your turn.
[QWENTHUR]
Uh. It is...?
[FROLAYTIA]
Uh-huh.
You're in charge
of kicking my butt.
If you think you're man enough.
[QWENTHUR whimpers]
All right!
Consider that passage
blocked off.
[QWENTHUR] That makes five
spots. Our maze is complete.
Damn straight. That should
slow those suckers down.
Even if the Intelligence
Union found another path,
these valleys are loaded with
fragments of plate armor,
they're like freakin' caltrops!
It'll make short work of tires,
maybe even caterpillar treads!
But we know the right pathways.
Meaning we can move around
completely unimpeded!
Just so you know this doesn't
really qualify as an offensive.
Dude, the Rush's drive system
is a combination of air cushions
and caterpillar tracks.
Unlike the Baby Magnum which
floats electrostatically,
it touches the ground.
[HAVIA] So there's a distinct
possibility it could eat
some of those armor fragments
and become immobilized!
Bingo.
Things'll be different
this time around,
the battlefield
favors the Princess.
Seems Commander Cup-size
actually put some
thought into it.
[QWENTHUR]
Yeah. Guess she wasn't too busy
pulling spot checks for porn
with her elite girl-goon squad.
Ah, the Foxy Force.
Why would she put
together a squad
that's entirely made up of
cute ladies in their twenties?
Is that a fetish?
Beats me. But now that
I think about it,
this is the perfect time
to come to an arrangement.
How 'bout any time a porn
check might be coming,
we agree to hide each
other's collection,
till we know the coast is clear?
'Cept radio communications
are subject to oversight
by higher-ups. Make
an "emergency call,"
and Mount St. Mammaries
hears everything.
That's why we'll
use a code word.
We could say like, "I'm at
my wit's end" or something,
and that's when we'd know
the secret talk is starting!
Clever devil.
From that point on,
we'd speak in code
to better report the situation!
It's a plan.
[beeping]
The Princess and the Rush should
be bumping in to each other
at any moment.
[HAVIA]
Soon, we'll get to see
how effective our
sabotage efforts were.
It should be a hell of a show!
Radar just picked
up the enemy unit.
[beeping]
What's this?
That's not a military
frequency hailing.
They didn't even bother
with encryption.
[laughs] I haven't seen
you since Oceania.
Little Miss Loutish Legitimate
Kingdom First Gen.
Oh, you.
Who can blame you for trembling
in fear, petite princess?
But don't you worry
about a thing,
I won't be too hard on you.
You have my word!
[laughs] I'm not
completely heartless,
so wave the white flag,
and I'll graciously
accept your surrender.
As long as my
Object's standing,
I will never surrender to you.
I'm gonna turn you into
an Alaskan landmark,
just like the Water Strider!
[OHOHO]
Ah, that simply won't do at all!
I have a personal stake in
making you use the white flag.
If I can't force your surrender,
I won't get rewarded!
Ah, ha, ha!
Rewarded?
It's an old rule of war.
Any soldier who surrenders
can be taken prisoner,
and ransomed back to their side.
[laughs] But I honestly may keep
that blonde gentleman
in your unit for myself.
[MILINDA growls]
[OHOHO laughs]
I will kill you!
[laughs] Guess I struck a nerve!
Once I've made your cute friend
mine, I'll put a collar on him,
maybe some floppy puppy ears,
and give him the privilege
of serving at my feet!
He's bound to be happier with me
than stuck with a frigid
taskmaster like you!
[OHOHO laughing]
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA screaming]
Way too close!
That was almost
divine retribution
for watching from the sidelines,
like a couple idiots!
Divine retribution?
You sound like a Faith
Organization zealot!
Now let's go!
[sighs] Talk about pitiful.
Entrusting our lives to
a lump of wire and alloys
that nearly got us
killed once already?
It's like taking a bath in
a tub full of day old water.
[QWENTHUR]
Even worse.
Day old bathwater out here
would be frozen solid.
The Rush's primaries are swift
beam-type Gatling guns.
Seems each can only sustain
fire for 30 seconds.
To counteract overheating,
I'd guess.
If they could fire continuously,
the Princess would
never get away.
But if they pause long enough
for heat dissipation
she might have a chance
to get through.
By alternating between
the two main guns,
the Rush can fire
without interruption.
But the starboard
gun only covers
the 180 degrees to the right
while the port gun covers
the same on the left.
Ohoho is trying to
compensate by circling,
but she can't keep up with
the Princess's evasion speed.
Hey, Qwenthur. Listen to this!
[OHOHO laughing] Just hurry
up and admit defeat already!
Then your handsome friend
can rest his tired blonde head
on these heaving G cups.
[MILINDA]
His entire existence revolves
around keeping my
Object maintained;
which means he's not interested
in you, so beat it!
Or refuse, and die!
I bet a certain stacked
superior officer
is pulling her hair out by now!
And now Elites from both sides
are fighting each other over a
member of the maintenance crew?
That is absolutely
unprecedented!
Just how skilled
is this engineer?
Maybe he came up with
some exclusive patent.
[QWENTHUR yelps]
They're both hit!
Is the Princess okay?
She blasted the Rush's
port gatling gun!
She knocked the
main gun out first,
in anticipation of
a drawn-out battle!
No, this is bad!
The Baby Magnum's
connecting joint
to her main guns has been hit!
If that joint's compromised,
worst-case scenario,
she can't fire any
of the seven guns!
She put too much focus
on the Rush's main gun,
and left herself wide open!
Hang on. What the
heck just happened?
A pit stop.
Pit stop?
The only thing that can
penetrate the thick armor
of an Object is the main
weapon of another Object.
And that's precisely
where they were damaged.
Neither side will fight without
a way to secure a win.
Whoever gets their unit back
to the base zone quickest
has more time to get
their main gun repaired,
and will have a better shot
at ending up victorious.
[QWENTHUR] Wait, the Baby
Magnum only took out one
of the Rush's main guns.
But the remaining gun can
only cover its right side.
And for only 30 second
bursts, before overheating.
And while the Princess's
main guns aren't broken,
they'll be a lot harder to aim.
In theory, her guns are still
operational, just inaccurate,
so if there's time to repair
them, why wouldn't we withdraw?
Valid point.
Meanwhile, the enemy's
maintenance corps gets caught
in the maze of rubble we
created with demolitions.
Game, set n' match.
While they burn up time trying
to clear roadblocks,
the Baby Magnum
gets her repairs,
and shifts back into action.
Then we can chalk this up
as another win!
[FROLAYTIA]
Qwenthur, Havia, listen up.
Are you still at Point 199 ASD?
Yeah.
[FROLAYTIA] Then I'll get
right to the point.
The Rush didn't head for their
maintenance base as predicted.
It seems to be attempting
to rendezvous
with a convoy detachment.
If they start making
those repairs,
they'll have their
main gun replaced
faster than we can repair
the Baby Magnum's!
Whoa, back it up a second!
Whatever happened
to those obstacles we spent
the whole day preparing?
I thought the rubble was
supposed to block the roads!
[FROLAYTIA]
For large vehicles, yes.
[QWENTHUR] Hey, they're using
manual labor to get through!
[sighs]
How much does an Objects'
main gun freakin' weigh?
The Rush's gatling gun
incorporates a number of
lightweight alloys and polymers.
So I'd say only a
hundred tons or so.
It's basically five serial swift
beam guns bundled together.
And each gun should
be about 20 tons.
They break that down into
over a hundred parts
to more easily facilitate
transportation.
The per person load
averages... 200 kilos?
That ain't happenin'!
No one can trudge around
carrying something that heavy
in these snowfields!
Not with their bare hands,
but what if they were
all in power suits?
[HAVIA gasps]
[FROLAYTIA]
The mounds of rubble might stop
some of the larger vehicles,
but there might be gaps
big enough for a human
to get through.
They're trying to find
and exploit those gaps,
so they can link
up with the Rush.
That changes everything!
If they've already got
a head-start on repairs,
the Baby Magnum'll be toast
before it even gets a
chance to retaliate!
You have to find a way to
disrupt the Rush's repairs!
The rendezvous point is
two klicks north of you.
No one else is close
enough to help in time!
Small arms won't do
a whole helluva lot
against powered
suits, Major!
And the Rush still has a
hundred other working guns
that can cover all directions!
How do we even get close
enough to spot it?!
[FROLAYTIA]
If there were any other options,
I wouldn't leave the fate
of our entire battalion
in the hands of snot-nosed
degenerates like you!
I'll leave the specifics
to your discretion.
Good luck, gentlemen.
[click]
You are kidding me!
How many times is Major
Melons gonna give us
a one-way ticket to Hell?!
Well, she's got a ticket
booklet full of them.
Hold up. Where ya
think you're going?
[QWENTHUR]
Isn't it obvious?
I'm gonna figure out a way
to deal with this problem.
Cause if I don't,
the first person to
suffer'll be the Princess.
Easy, brave Sir Knight.
Is looting the most chivalrous
thing you can do right now?
This used to be a fixed
base plasma cannon.
In order to focus the plasma,
the interior of
the barrel is lined
with thousands of
electromagnets.
[HAVIA] How're electromagnets
supposed to help?
[QWENTHUR]
Object armor is just steel
mixed with a high-performance
anti-fire reactant.
Which means it's magnetic.
In other words,
you're going rock climbing
on that massive
metal monster's back.
[QWENTHUR]
Check it out.
Frolaytia sounded antsy, but
we've still got a little time.
The route two klicks north
has the densest rubble,
and nobody's getting through,
and that means they'll have to
double back and take a detour.
While they're busy
taking that detour,
there's a passage that'll bring
the Rush closer to our position.
That should provide us
with ample opportunity
to run some kind of
harassment op.
[HAVIA]
Are you serious?
Just give me a hand, Havia.
We're running out of time.
[OHOHO] It'll take more than
rough passages to stop us.
Objects can survive
a nuclear attack.
I'm not concerned
about a little debris.
But then again, why tempt fate?
The gods can be awfully fickle.
Adjusting scheduled rendezvous
time. Please keep working.
See if you can have the
main gun module assembled
by the time I arrive.
Yes ma'am!
Yes! Phase one is a success!
Lucky SOB.
I wonder if bein' stuck with
him will win me more medals,
or shave more years off my life?
Most likely both. Heh.
What silly bit of mischief did
the gods send my way, I wonder?
[laughing]
[QWENTHUR]
Just like you can't see
the smudge of dirt
on your own face.
At least not without
the help of a mirror.
Even the vast array of
sensors onboard the Rush
aren't calibrated
to scan this close.
[HAVIA] Everything you do is
spur-of-the-moment nonsense,
but you've got more confidence
than any noble I've met.
[QWENTHUR] When the Rush
hoisted us up in the car
back in Oceania,
I couldn't help but notice
that it didn't have
any magnetic sensors.
And also that the cameras
weren't angled
to notice targets this close.
Guess the hard part's over.
[grunts]
[HAVIA] Rock climbing is fun,
but you do have a plan, right?
Yeah, kinda. Might need
to break something
along the way to
extend repair time.
Better find it soon.
You'll rendezvous with the
maintenance crew any minute!
Oh, crap!
[HAVIA]
Qwenthur!
Ah crap, Qwenthur, come in!
[OHOHO laughs]
That was a simultaneous volley
of all secondary guns. I picked
up a rogue radio signal nearby,
but between the shockwave and
radiant heat from that barrage,
consider your bug
squashed! [laughs]
Juliet program
confirmed offline.
Seeing to the main gun
exchange as we speak.
[OHOHO] Be a dear, and make this
pit stop as quick as you can.
We've gone to all the
trouble to be wily,
but it'll all be for nothing
if we waste this
precious opportunity.
[MAINTENANCE CAPTAIN A]
All personnel! Double time!
[OHOHO]
Maintenance Captain?
Re-check Sensors
Alpha through Echo.
I'm finding discrepancies
between point five
and point seven.
[MAINTENANCE CAPTAIN A]
Apologies, Ma'am,
but if we add that
job to the docket,
it will add a delay to
our work timetable.
Sensors are within limits.
[OHOHO]
What did you say to me?!
I'm up against other
Objects out there!
Even the slightest discrepancy
is unacceptable!
Our mission parameters
didn't account for anything
more than swapping out
the damaged Gatling gun!
As long as we have our orders
from Lieutenant
Colonel Farolito,
contradicting them will
lead to a court-martial!
[OHOHO]
Stupid coward.
Doesn't matter, I'll just
recalibrate them myself!
I swear! You grunts are
flippin' useless! [laughs]
[QWENTHUR]
Pardon me, Mademoiselle.
Do forgive me for
rudely breaking into
a lovely lady's
private chambers.
Now quickly and quietly
do everything I tell you.
Don't worry about that, sir.
To be honest, I'd intended
to invite you here myself.
[laughs]
[gasps]
You have got to
be kidding me.
No, dear. Ah, ha.
Can't believe your
eyes, Blondie?
I am the Elite chosen by
the Intelligence Union
to pilot their finest Object!
[OHOHO laughs]
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA]
"The Graveyard of Junk
is a Mountain of Rare Metals".
[MILINDA] "Interception at the
Site of the Alaska Battle II".