[QWENTHUR]
When the attack came,
every second felt like
a waking nightmare.
[MALE OPERATOR 2A]
Enemy Object approaching fast!
[FROLAYTIA] Call all
Category 1 combat stations.
[QWENTHUR] Before the sun
could rise on a single day
after our barbeque,
we were cast into hell.
[FEMALE OPERATOR 2A] Baby Magnum
launch sequence activated.
[AYAMI]
This is the real deal!
Put it all together
and look alive, boys!
Five minutes until
maximum output!
[MILINDA]
System contact.
Starting boot-up sequence.
Running system check.
Stand by.
[MILINDA] Power reactor
has now reached rated output.
System, all green.
Milinda Brantini and
Baby Magnum moving out.
[QWENTHUR] The attacking
Object was given life
by the world power known
as the Faith Organization.
A unique model scarcely
resembling Baby Magnum.
It was named "Water Strider."
When it moved,
it was like an insect
skating on water.
[QWENTHUR] Since Heavy Objects
possess both massive firepower
and extremely thick armor,
victory often boils down
to who has the best position.
A deadly tug-of-war between
titans vying for advantage.
[FROLAYTIA] Sending data
on enemy position
and path projections.
You cannot let that thing
get behind you.
[QWENTHUR]
Because of these tactics,
Objects are endowed with
high-speed mobility,
which can be surprising,
given their enormous bulk.
[FROLAYTIA] Their speed
is just about equal.
It's like a race with
the mountain between them.
At this point,
it boils down to instincts.
[QWENTHUR]
And that's when I remembered
what the Princess had
been so worried about...
The harsh reality
of her situation.
[QWENTHUR] Her opponent
was a second-gen Object
optimized for combat
in a specific environment.
Its performance far
exceeded the multipurpose
first-gen model she piloted.
[MILINDA gasps]
[alarm sounding]
[QWENTHUR]
She was worried she might lose.
Which, honestly,
was a pretty valid fear.
[OPERATOR 2A]
Baby Magnum taking fire!
[OPERATOR 2C]
Propulsion unit damaged!
Mobility reduced to 12%!
[OPERATOR 2A]
Second wave, incoming!
[QWENTHUR] I thought it was
completely over at that point.
But it wasn't.
For us, that moment was just
the beginning of something else.
A true nightmare.
[HAVIA panting]
Hold on...
They aren't aiming those
cannons at us, are they?
You raise the white flag
when an Object loses, right?
So what gives?
Hurry up and
surrender already,
we're about to get
blown to pieces over here!
[beeping noise]
That's the signal.
The white flag.
Guess it just took a sec.
Either way, we're saved.
Didn't they hear?
What's wrong?!
[FROLAYTIA] I mean,
there's no formal treaty
stating anything to that effect.
[QWENTHUR]
They don't care.
They're gonna fire.
Go now.
Move! Get outta here!
Aw, hell,
so much for surrender!
Those freaks
really want us dead!
If we don't get outta here,
that thing's gonna vaporize us!
[SOLDIERS shouting]
[QWENTHUR]
There's...
There's nowhere to run.
[HAVIA growls]
[HAVIA]
The way that thing moves...
So creepy.
[QWENTHUR] The build's
different, but it probably uses
the same electrostatic
levitation drive as Baby Magnum.
It's just gliding now,
but I bet it can pull
300 klicks an hour, easy.
[QWENTHUR] That massive body
must put a lot of strain
on those legs,
but the design allows it
to maneuver in
pretty much any terrain.
[QWENTHUR] Point is, it can
chase us down wherever we go.
[HAVIA] So you just
wanna stand here and die?
Screw your science, let's run!
[BOTH panting]
[BOTH grunting]
Okay. Lucky break.
Seems we picked
the right way to go.
Aw crap. Our luck's up.
Now they're aiming for
the maintenance facility!
Everyone, get away
from the equipment!
They're about to fire!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[QWENTHUR]
We're done for!
Once they wipe out
the equipment,
they're gonna
pick off the scraps!
[QWENTHUR]
We're dead...
[QWENTHUR] I don't get
why it didn't attack us.
[HAVIA]
Me neither!
Worry about it later.
All I know is if
we don't move now,
it'll be the difference
between life and death.
[beeping noise]
It's an SOS signal.
[gasps] From the Princess,
it looks like.
I see.
The enemy got it, too.
[tires screeching]
[FROLAYTIA]
Blue Blood! Schoolboy!
Better run while you still can!
There's a ravine on the
other side of that mountain.
That giant can't chase us
across the suspension bridge.
In other words,
we're not dead yet!
[QWENTHUR]
But... what about the Princess?
[FROLAYTIA]
Are you an idiot?!
Why do you think she sent that
signal in the first place?
She let the enemy intercept it
so we could get away!
If she didn't draw
their attention,
every last one of us
would've been massacred!
You wanna let her
sacrifice go to waste?
[QWENTHUR]
No way.
She's what, like, 14 years old?
And she's throwing her entire
life away just to save us?
So that's it?
We just abandon her and run?
We can't do this!
[HAVIA]
Have some common sense!
I hate to say it,
but she's dead no matter what.
Get it?
Either we take off and save
ourselves, or everyone dies.
[QWENTHUR] You're trying to
justify this for your own sake.
But you know the situation
and you know these people
are monsters,
what do you think they'll do
to her once they've got her?
All right then. Fine!
You wanna fight
that monster on your own?
If think you can
waltz up to that thing,
save the princess and get
everyone else out of here alive,
then be my guest!
But I have a very strong
hunch that you can't!
The moment anyone pops up
on that thing's radar,
they're as good as dust.
I'm not justifying anything;
that's just how it is.
You're afraid, Havia, I get it.
But think about the Princess.
She has been fighting
those things all on her own!
Things that scare the
wits out of entire armies
of highly trained soldiers.
Things you wouldn't
dare to face,
even to save your own comrade!
She's ready to
face those monsters
without a second thought!
And I know damn well
she'd never leave us to die!
Screw it!
Hand over your rifle!
It's suicide.
[QWENTHUR] It's not like
we have a choice.
[QWENTHUR]
You gotta have faith...
That if we make it across
the ravine, we can escape!
The Princess is
obviously trying to buy us
the time to do that.
But without help,
she can only do so much.
And I'm sorry,
it's gotta be me.
I won't pass the buck
to someone else.
[QWENTHUR] I have no
intention of dying out here.
We are all gonna survive!
[QWENTHUR]
Well this sucks, I'm lost.
I get thrown into a war
and I can't even figure out
my position.
Shows how sheltered
I've really been.
[QWENTHUR] Duh.
Just remember your training.
[ENEMY SOLDIER 2A]
Found her!
Over here! Come on!
[QWENTHUR]
That-a-way.
[ENEMY SOLDIER 2B]
Yeah, right?
[ENEMY SOLDIER 2A]
Huh...
So this is one of
the mighty Elites
of the Legitimate Kingdom!
[QWENTHUR]
The Princess!
Captured.
Crap, just what I was afraid of.
[panting]
[QWENTHUR]
I don't see the Object, though.
Did it go back for
maintenance or something?
Okay.
If I can do something
about those four,
then I can save the Princess
and get out of here!
"Do something," huh?
Like, actually
use this on them...?
Oh, just stop!
This is a battlefield!
Get real!
What the hell did you think
was gonna happen?
She's been doing this
on her own for how long now?
It's time to take
some responsibility!
[growls]
[QWENTHUR] But that's
a human being down there,
not some paper target.
Probably a lot like me,
spoiled for so long
by the illusion of peace.
[ENEMY SOLDIER 2A]
Let's test the durability
of this fancy suit of hers.
Once the Object comes back,
let's tie up her wrists
and hook her up
to one of its legs.
If she ain't naked by the time
we drag her back to base,
we'll know it's
made of tough stuff.
[ENEMY SOLDIER 2B]
As for you, Elite witch,
we'll use hypnosis and
electrodes to interrogate you.
It won't take
more than 30 minutes
before you spill the contents
of that pretty
little head of yours.
You might as well say
goodbye to your mind
while you can still speak!
[ENEMY SOLDIER 2A]
Interrogation Room.
[ENEMY SOLDIER 2B]
So we test her suit,
then they test her body, huh?
[ENEMY SOLDIER 2C] Why don't
we run a preliminary test
of our own right now?
[ENEMY SOLDIER 2A]
It'd be irresponsible not to!
[SOLDIERS laughing]
[QWENTHUR]
"Human beings," huh?
Guess I was naïve. Not anymore.
[QWENTHUR]
Get down!
I did it!
[HAVIA]
Move, dumbass!
Princess. Hang on...
[HAVIA]
Hey. Hey, stupid! Qwenthur!
[HAVIA] I know you're not dead,
so quit napping!
Rise and shine.
Walk it off!
[QWENTHUR]
What are you doing here?
I thought you ran away.
Oh, shut up.
Don't make it a thing!
You saved my life.
I would've been blown to pieces
if you hadn't shown up.
[coughing]
What about the
Princess, is she okay?
After all that ass
you kicked back there?
Yeah, relax,
those SOBs are dead.
[HAVIA]
So what?
You think you're some kinda
knight in shining armor now?
[QWENTHUR]
You know it wasn't like that.
Someone had to do something
and it ended up being me.
But why?
You're not an Elite like me,
and you don't have
an Object to fight with.
You don't even have
armor to protect you,
so why'd you risk it?
Weren't you afraid
you'd die coming here?
Truth is,
even if I didn't say it,
I've always looked down
on you people.
On everyone who needs
my power to protect them.
Because without my Object,
you'd all be killed like ants.
I know that's a
horrible way to think,
and even though I never
said it to your face,
I couldn't erase
that feeling from my mind.
And even if
I did protect you,
if I'm filled with
so much contempt,
how am I worth
risking your life?
Sure, it sounds cruel.
But everything
you said is still true.
Huh?
Now that I've had one
turn its sights on me,
I understand.
Objects aren't just tools,
they're terrifying monsters.
But you never
said that yourself.
All this time, you just
toughed it out alone,
without a word of complaint.
[gasps]
It doesn't matter now.
Now we're all in this together.
Let's just say we saved you
'cause it was the
right thing to do.
[HAVIA]
This guy gets it.
All dramatics aside,
he had a practical reason
for coming here.
If it was as shallow as
just "save the Princess,"
I wouldn't have followed.
The reality is
we're gonna need to make
an even bigger
distraction if we want
the rest of the troops
to escape here alive.
So it's not like a favor.
We just didn't have a choice.
[chuckles]
All right.
We've got a princess and
her knight in shining armor.
But to survive, you're gonna
have to be soldiers again.
[gasps]
Let's move.
I've got a feeling all
that gunfire of yours
didn't go unnoticed.
Our big metal friend will
be here to inspect soon.
[QWENTHUR]
But where can we go?
[HAVIA]
I saw a cave up ahead.
That should be a
safe place to hide.
Hopefully, we'll keep it
distracted searching for us.
They've got their plasma
cannons locked on us!
[QWENTHUR]
They're not firing, though.
Maybe they're still deciding
if they want to take
the Princess alive or not.
Qwenthur!
You're with the
Engineering Corps, right?
Didja bring any explosives?
[QWENTHUR]
I've got about 5 kilos of C4,
but it's not like that's gonna
do anything against an Object.
[HAVIA]
I'll explain later!
[QWENTHUR]
Whoa!
Okay, I know it's not the
best time for this, but dang!
What an impressive rack!
Come on, we gotta
get to the back!
You two can make out later!
[QWENTHUR] What the hell
kinda plan is this?
Their plasma cannons
are gonna roast us alive
no matter how far
into the cave we go!
[HAVIA] Yeah, why do you think
I borrowed the C4?
It's a longshot, but so
is this whole operation.
[explosion, screaming]
[QWENTHUR sighs]
I thought I was dead for sure!
Hearing's still
messed up, though.
But at least it didn't
rupture my eardrums.
[HAVIA]
That should do it.
With any luck, they'll waste
some time looking for us
in the cave while we
get long gone.
[QWENTHUR]
Nice one.
[HAVIA]
Any news?
[QWENTHUR]
I'm not seeing any signs
that they picked up
our trail, but who knows?
[MILINDA] I can sort of
feel the ground rumbling,
so I think the Object
must still be pretty close.
At any rate, it seems
they've lost sight of us
for the moment.
So if we make
a break for it now,
we might actually survive.
[QWENTHUR]
Yeah, maybe.
But I'm still worried.
If we were less distracting
than we thought we were,
our entire unit could die.
[MILINDA]
That's true.
But how long can
we keep this plan up?
We can't buy time
for anyone if we're dead.
Yeah, no kidding, huh?
No offense and all,
but even in your Object,
you got your ass handed to you
by that thing real fast.
We got lucky,
but I don't have high hopes
for a second run-in.
I lost 'cause
the safeguard device
suddenly activated.
I had to disarm it,
so I was distracted.
If they hadn't attacked then,
I would've won.
Safeguard?
For classified materials?
[HAVIA]
Huh?
It's an auto
self-destruct function.
An Object is a
veritable treasure trove
of classified materials,
so when its various
sensors detect
that it's been compromised,
it protects those secrets
by destroying them.
Yeah, thanks for the lecture.
But that's all in the past.
Now let's focus on
how we're gonna get away.
Alive, if we can.
[QWENTHUR]
Havia!
We are not saving our own hides
just to leave our unit to die.
Or do you really wanna
live with that guilt
for the rest of your life?
Not to mention, as a noble,
you'd be branded a
disgrace to your family,
so you could say goodbye to that
precious inheritance of yours.
Then what're we
supposed to do, jackass?
Let's not think of
how to sacrifice ourselves.
Think of how to win.
Even if it's improbable,
there's gotta be some way
we can deal with the--
[gasps]
We've got someone
well-versed in Object design,
an analyst who's
already outsmarted one,
and an Elite pilot,
in case we really want
to get ambitious with this.
[gasps]
Wait, hold on just a second.
I mean, I get where
you're coming from,
but you're getting
way ahead of yourself.
It's not even possible, is it?
[QWENTHUR]
Guess we're about to find out.
Even an Object has
to have a weakness somewhere,
and mark my words,
we're gonna find it.
[QWENTHUR, HAVIA] "Rank and File
Soldiers Who Tie Down Gulliver."
[MILINDA] "The Snowy, Deep
Winter Battle of Alaska - III."