- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Rin: HEY, KAEDE. WE GOTTA GO.
- Kaede: JUST A MINUTE.
I'M ALMOST DONE.
- HERE, DON'T FORGET YOUR LUNCH.
- OH, THANK YOU!
OKAY. WE'D BETTER RUN.
- PRIMULA, CAN YOU PLEASE TAKE
CARE OF THINGS WHILE WE'RE GONE?
- SURE. I'LL BE WAITING
RIGHT HERE, OKAY?
- WELL, GOOD MORNING, YOU TWO.
GLAD I'M NOT
THE ONLY ONE BEHIND.
- HI. HOW'S IT GOING
THIS MORNING?
- HEY. WHERE'S SIA?
SHE RUNNING LATE TOO?
- ( yelling ) HOLD UP!
HI, EVERYONE! RIN, WAIT
FOR ME! I'M COMING TOO!
- GOOD MORNING, SIA. I...
- ( giggling ) GOTCHA!
- WHA? SIA...
HEY!
- ( both giggle )
- Sia: YEP, THESE DAYS, THERE
ARE TONS OF DIFFERENT
COLORS AND PATTERNS
TO CHOOSE FROM.
MY DAD GOT SO CARRIED AWAY, HE
VOLUNTEERED TO TRY THEM ON.
WE GO THROUGH A DOZEN PAIRS
BEFORE HE BLURTS OUT,
"RED, NOTHING BETTER THAN RED
WHEN IT COMES TO
CLASSIC UNDIES."
HILARIOUS!
- ( laughs )
THAT SOUNDS JUST LIKE
YOUR FATHER, ALL RIGHT.
BUT THE OLD MAN HAS
A GOOD POINT.
RED IS THE MOST SENSIBLE COLOR.
- WELL, UM...
I'M LOST.
WHAT PRECISELY DID YOUR DAD MEAN
BY THE TERM "CLASSIC" UNDERWEAR?
- YOU SERIOUSLY DON'T KNOW?
UH... RIGHT.
HOW DO I PUT THIS DELICATELY,
BUT IN A WAY THAT
YOU'LL UNDERSTAND?
- WELL, IT'S NO MYSTERY,
ANY GUY WILL TELL YOU
THAT NOTHING LOOKS QUITE AS HOT
ON A GIRL AS RED.
ESPECIALLY UNDERGARMENTS. HA!
SILKY, SMOOTH AND SO SEXY.
- ( gasps )
- WHOOPS. GUESS I SAID TOO MUCH.
- ACTUALLY, ITSUKI,
THAT'S AN INTERESTING INSIGHT.
- Mayumi: OH, SHOOT!
I FORGOT I'M SUPPOSED TO GET THE
MATERIALS FOR NEXT PERIOD.
- WOW, YOU'RE ON DUTY AGAIN
TODAY? YOU SEEM STRESSED OUT.
- I SURE AM.
BEING AN ASSISTANT TO A PHYSICS
TEACHER IS REALLY HARD WORK.
KANEDA USES MORE
PRINTOUTS THAN ANYONE.
- I'D BE HAPPY TO HELP YOU
IF YOU NEED ASSISTANCE.
- YOU WOULD?
- OF COURSE.
- YOU'RE AWESOME!
- GEE, YOU COULD
SHOW SOME ENTHUSIASM.
- COME ON!
YOU MIGHT WANT TO WEAR GLOVES.
THAT INK GETS EVERYWHERE.
- JUST AN OBSERVATION.
AND FEEL FREE TO CORRECT ME
IF I'M WRONG,
BUT, IT SEEMS THAT
NERINE'S ATTITUDE
HAS CHANGED EVER SO SLIGHTLY.
- WELL, SURE.
BUT NERINE ISN'T THE ONLY ONE.
AND, LATELY, OUR
PRIMULA HAS BECOME
QUITE THE
CHATTERBOX, TOO.
A NICE CHANGE.
DON'T YOU THINK, RIN?
- OH, YEAH. ABSOLUTELY.
- THAT MAY BE TRUE,
BUT ONE FACT IS GLARINGLY CLEAR.
SOMETHING WILDLY LIFE-CHANGING
HAPPENED TO THOSE GIRLS
DURING THEIR TRIP
TO THE DEMON WORLD.
- YEAH, THEY'RE MORE CHIPPER
AND FULL OF LIFE.
I DON'T SEE ANYTHING
WRONG WITH THAT.
WE COULD ALL USE MORE CHEER.
- YOU'RE RIGHT, OF COURSE.
YOU WANT TO KNOW THE
BEST PART THOUGH?
AS A RESULT, THE REST OF US
HAVE BEEN ABLE TO RETURN
TO OUR NORMAL LIVES.
- YUP. MOST DEFINITELY.
- AND, EVERYONE'S HAPPY.
- OH, YEAH. THAT REMINDS ME.
KAREHA!
- OH, RIN. HELLO.
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
- NO, UM, THERE'S SOMETHING
I WANTED TO ASK YOU.
BUT, IT'S...
IT'S ABOUT ASA THOUGH.
- WHAT'S WRONG? WHY DON'T
YOU TALK TO HER DIRECTLY?
- HEY! WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
OH, RIN.
- Itsuki: AND NOW, GIVE A
CHEER IN CELEBRATION
OF ASA SHIGURE'S FULL RECOVERY!
- All: CHEERS!
- I HAVE TO BE HONEST.
THIS EXTERIOR,
IS REALLY JUST A BIG OLD SHAM.
I WAS ACTUALLY GOING CRAZY
WORRYING ABOUT ASA'S HEALTH.
- YOU'RE LYING.
AND THAT'S THE TRUTH.
- EVERYONE HERE KNOWS
YOU'RE AN OPPORTUNIST.
- THE GOOD THING IS
WE'RE TOGETHER.
KAEDE, SIA, NERINE, PRIMULA
AND EVEN ASA, ARE ALL BACK NOW.
IT FINALLY FEELS LIKE THINGS
HAVE RETURNED TO NORMAL
AROUND HERE.
- I COULDN'T HAVE
SAID IT BETTER!
- ( groans )
- THAT'S GOING TO LEAVE A MARK.
BUT, THANK YOU, THOUGH.
- NOW THINGS HAVE REALLY
GONE BACK TO NORMAL.
I MEAN, WHAT'S A DAY WITHOUT A
GOOD SLAP ON THE BACK FROM ASA?
- AM I RIGHT?
- ABSOLUTELY!
AND I COULD NEVER
IMAGINE ABANDONING
ONE OF OUR MOST
BELOVED TRADITIONS.
- THANKS, ASA.
- SERIOUSLY, THOUGH,
I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT YOUR VISIT WAS AN
AWESOME SURPRISE
AND IT MEANT A LOT.
I NEVER IMAGINED YOU'D BE
THE ONE TO COME SEE ME.
- I'M GLAD THAT
YOU TAKE IT SERIOUSLY.
ORIGINALLY, YOU TOLD ME
YOU'D BE BACK IN SCHOOL
BY THE BEGINNING OF THE WEEK,
AND WHEN YOU DIDN'T SHOW UP,
I WASN'T SURE WHAT TO THINK.
- YOU WERE WORRIED
ABOUT ME, RIN?
- WELL, OF COURSE, I WAS.
- I DID TOY WITH THE IDEA OF
COMING BACK RIGHT AWAY THOUGH.
BUT MY MOTHER INSISTED
THAT I TAKE IT EASY
AND REST FOR JUST
A FEW MORE DAYS.
SORRY.
- IS THAT REALLY THE TRUTH?
- OH, SURE, YES!
- ( both laughing )
- ASA, IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
YOU DON'T SEEM
TO BE EATING MUCH.
- THAT'S BECAUSE I'M DIETING!
WELL, IT'S NOT SO MUCH A DIET.
I'M BEING RESPONSIBLE
WITH MY CALORIE INTAKE,
ESPECIALLY SINCE I'VE BEEN SICK.
I TEND TO GAIN WEIGHT
RIGHT AROUND HERE.
- ( gasps )
STOP. OKAY, WE GET THE IDEA.
- ( girls giggling )
- THIS MIGHT NOT BE THE BEST
TIME TO PRESENT THIS, BUT...
IT'S ONE OF
YOUR FAVORITE DISHES, SO...
- NO, IT'S PERFECT!
I CAN'T THINK OF A BETTER WAY TO
GET BACK TO OUR NORMAL ROUTINE.
THIS EGG OMELET IS
AN EXCELLENT TOUCH.
- I'M SO GLAD.
HEY, I HAVE ENOUGH
FOR EVERYONE, SO DIG IN.
- I'LL GIVE IT A TASTE TEST.
NOW, BE HONEST, NERINE.
YOU MADE THIS LOVELY DISH
JUST TO IMPRESS ME, DIDN'T YOU?
- THAT'S NOT WHAT SHE SAID,
YOU IDIOT.
SHE'S BEING REALLY POLITE
AND OFFERING SOME TO ALL OF US.
- IN THAT CASE, I'D LOVE A BITE.
- I LIKE THE CORNERS.
- ME, TOO!
- ( gulping )
DELICIOUS!
YOU'VE MANAGED TO CREATE
THE PERFECT BLEND OF SPICES
AND RAW FLAVOR.
IT'S EXQUISITE!
- WOW, I NEVER THOUGHT I'D
SAY THIS, BUT ITSUKI'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE CULINARY SKILLS
ARE OFF THE CHART.
- YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW MUCH IT
MEANS TO HEAR YOU SAY THAT.
THANK YOU, ASA.
- ( clock chiming )
- ALL RIGHT, CLASS DISMISSED!
SO, WHAT'RE YOU WAITING FOR?
BEAT IT.
- HEY, RIN!
WHY DON'T WE WALK HOME TOGETHER?
- SURE, SOUNDS GREAT.
WELL, HOW ABOUT YOU, KAEDE?
- ME? I GUESS I DON'T HAVE
ANY SHOPPING TO DO
THIS AFTERNOON, SO YEAH.
- OKAY THEN, LET'S GET GOING.
- IT'S THE GREATEST.
AND EVERYTHING THEY SELL THERE
IS REALLY SUPER COOL.
- WOW, CAN I THINK ABOUT IT?
- WHAT'S TO THINK ABOUT, NERINE?
COME WITH US.
- WELL, I GUESS I WILL. I COULD
USE A COUPLE OF NEW OUTFITS.
- THERE'S BEEN
A CHANGE IN PLANS.
SIA, YOU TWO GO ON
WITHOUT ME, OKAY?
- WHAT?
- OKAY.
YOU GIRLS GO HAVE FUN.
- I KNOW ONE OF THE GUYS WHO
WORKS THERE AND HE'S WAY SWEET.
- NERINE?
- SIA, ARE YOU COMING?
- UH-HUH.
- WE'D BETTER GET A MOVE ON
IF WE WANT TO GET IN ON
THE AWESOME SALES.
- SEE YA.
- REALLY? ARE YOU CERTAIN?
- POSITIVE.
WHEN WE VISITED THE LABORATORY
IN THE DEMON WORLD,
I DISCOVERED THAT
LYCORIS ONE TRUE WISH
HAD FINALLY BEEN FULFILLED.
- WOW, NERINE, I HAD NO IDEA.
- LOOK, I'M SORRY.
IT WASN'T MY INTENTION TO
KEEP IT A SECRET FROM YOU.
- FORGET IT.
THERE WASN'T A THING YOU
COULD DO ABOUT IT ANYWAY.
BUT, TELL ME STRAIGHT.
DOES THIS MEAN...
IT'S TRUE. MY FEELINGS
FOR RIN ARE MY OWN.
I LOVE HIM AS NERINE,
AND NERINE ALONE.
FROM HERE ON I'M LOOKING
AT RIN THROUGH MY OWN EYES.
AND I KNOW I'LL GROW
TO LOVE HIM EVEN MORE.
- I'M GLAD.
IF THAT'S WHERE YOUR HEAD'S AT,
THEN I FEEL A LITTLE RELIEVED.
- ( Nerine giggling )
THERE IS SOMETHING STRANGE.
NOW THAT I CAN FOCUS ON JUST ME,
I'M SEEING CLEARLY.
AS IF MY EYES HAVE BEEN OPENED
TO THE HUMAN WORLD
FOR THE VERY FIRST TIME.
EVERY ASPECT OF RIN'S WORLD
IS WASHING OVER ME.
THE SIGHTS, SOUNDS,
EVEN EMOTIONS
SEEM EASIER TO INTERPRET.
SO, I'VE DECIDED
TO START FROM ZERO
AND REBUILD MY RELATIONSHIP
WITH HIM FROM THE GROUND UP.
AND NOT JUST ONLY WITH RIN.
BUT WITH THE ENTIRE WORLD
IN WHICH HE LIVES.
IT'S MY OPPORTUNITY
TO REALLY START OVER.
- I SEE.
YOU SEEM QUITE HAPPY.
WELL, ARE YOU?
- OH, YES!
AND NOW, SIA,
IT'S YOUR TURN TO BE HAPPY.
- WAIT, NERINE? WHAT?
MY TURN?
WHY WOULD SHE SAY THAT?
NERINE DESERVES TO BE HAPPY.
HMM...
WHO AM I TO THINK MY HAPPINESS
IS MORE IMPORTANT THAN HERS?
- ( sighs )
- IT'S SO GORGEOUS.
I'VE NEVER SEEN A SHOP
LIKE THIS BEFORE.
ANY ITEM YOU COULD IMAGINE.
- Kaede: I HAD NO IDEA.
- Rin: YOU SHOULD GO WITH HER
NEXT TIME, KAEDE.
- Nerine: YES, I'D LIKE THAT.
- AND NOW, SIA,
IT'S YOUR TURN TO BE HAPPY.
- WAKE UP!
- ( Rin screaming )
- GOTCHA! MORNING.
- YEAH, YOU DID.
COULDN'T WE JUST SHAKE HANDS?
- ( laughing )
COME ON! YOU DON'T WANT TO
BE LATE FOR CLASS, DO YOU?
- ASA, WAIT!
- ( Mayumi laughing )
SMELLS GREAT. KAEDE SURE
MAKES A DELICIOUS LUNCH.
- DON'T MIND IF I DO.
- HEY! CUT IT OUT!
- PARDON THE OBSERVATION, BUT...
IT SEEMS TO ME THE COMFORTS
OF DAY-TO-DAY LIFE
OFTEN MANIFEST IN OUR ROUTINE
HABITS, MEALTIME FOR EXAMPLE.
AH! THE SPLENDOR
OF FAMILIAR CUISINE.
- I JUST DIDN'T HAVE TIME
TO MAKE IT TODAY.
- WHAT?
THERE'S NO EGG OMELET?
- I KNOW. I'M SORRY.
- THIS ISN'T HAPPENING.
EXCUSE ME,
I THINK MY STOMACH'S IN SHOCK.
- ( inaudible )
- THAT SMACK OF YOURS, IT'S
NEVER THE SAME TWICE, IS IT?
A WHOLE NEW PAIN EVERY TIME.
- IT HURTS ME
AS MUCH AS IT DOES YOU.
- I'M SURE.
- ( Asa giggling )
- WHAT THE?
- ( phone ringing )
- Kaede: YES? FUYOU RESIDENCE.
OH, HI, ASA!
YEP. OH.
- IT WHAT? ABOUT RIN?
- FOR ME?
HELLO?
YES.
WHEN? TOMORROW?
A SHOPPING SPREE, WOW.
SURE, THAT'S NO PROBLEM.
LISTEN, CAN YOU HOLD ON
FOR A MINUTE?
I'M GOING TO SWITCH TO THE
PHONE UPSTAIRS, OKAY? COOL.
- WHAT AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO ABOUT RIN?
THIS IS KILLING ME.
I CAN'T HIDE
MY FEELINGS FOR HIM.
NO MATTER HOW THIS PLAYS OUT,
I'LL ALWAYS LOVE RIN.
SOMETHING HAS TO CHANGE.
BECAUSE WITH THE WAY
THINGS ARE RIGHT NOW.
EVERYONE IS MISERABLE.
( gasps )
( crying )
- ( clock chiming )
- ( laughing ) COME ON,
SLOWPOKE, THERE'S TONS TO BUY.
AND THAT'S WHERE
YOU'LL BE STEPPING IN.
I NEED SOME STRONG MUSCLES
TO LIFT ALL OF THOSE BAGS.
- MA'AM, YOU PICKED THE PERFECT
GUY. MUSCLES AT YOUR DISPOSAL.
- LISTEN UP!
I DON'T EXPECT FREE HELP.
ONCE I HAVE PERFECTED
MY BEST AUTUMN-INSPIRED RECIPES,
I WILL SERVE THEM TO YOU
BEFORE ANYONE ELSE.
- SOUNDS FAIR TO ME.
- YOU'RE IN FOR A TREAT.
- I'LL BET.
- Man: ATTENTION SHOPPERS,
RIGHT NOW WE'RE OFFERING
A TWO FOR ONE SPECIAL ON ALL
YUM-TUM ROTISSERIE CHICKENS
AND GAME HENS.
SO, WADDLE ON OVER TO THE DELI
AND PICK UP A BIRD,
OR TRY ANY OF OUR
AWARD-WINNING DELUXE DINNERS
COMPLETE WITH ALL THE TRIMMINGS
YOUR FAMILY WILL LOVE,
LIKE SQUASH SURPRISE,
OR RED BEET CASSEROLE!
HURRY BEFORE
THEY'RE ALL GOBBLED UP!
- HE'S HERE.
- ( heartbeat )
- YOU SAID YOU'D BUY A LOT,
BUT I DIDN'T ANTICIPATE
THE ENTIRE STORE.
WE'RE GOING TO NEED
A BIGGER BASKET.
- GREAT DISHES TAKE
A GREAT MANY INGREDIENTS.
- COOL. THOUGH TELL ME,
SEEING AS YOU'RE GOING TO USE
THIS IN THE COOKING CLUB,
HOW DO YOU PLAN TO
TRANSPORT IT ALL
FROM YOUR HOUSE TO THE SCHOOL?
- IT'S A TWO-PARTER.
FIRST, I'LL HAVE YOU CARRY
EVERYTHING TO MY PLACE
WHERE I CAN PROPERLY
STORE IT ALL.
- UH-HUH.
- THEN, TOMORROW, WE'LL LUG IT
ALL FROM MY HOUSE TO THE SCHOOL.
SIMPLE!
- ( screams )
PIECE OF CAKE.
- ( stomach growling )
( sighs )
SHE'S LATE.
IT'S BEEN SO LONG. I'LL WASTE
AWAY BEFORE SHE GETS BACK.
( stomach growling )
SHE'S HOME!
OH, WELCOME HOME, SIA!
NOW THAT YOU'RE BACK, UM...
WHAT'S FOR DINNER?
( stomach growling )
- UNBELIEVABLE!
- ( gasps )
HUH? WHAT'S WRONG?
- AS IF YOU DON'T KNOW.
YOU WALKED RIGHT BY HIM AT THE
STORE WITHOUT EVEN SAYING HELLO.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW WEAK
YOU'VE BECOME. MAKES ME SICK.
- IT'S NOT MY FAULT. WHY ARE
YOU SAYING SUCH HURTFUL THINGS?
- IT'S THE TRUTH.
I'M ONLY LOOKING OUT FOR
YOUR BEST INTERESTS.
YOU NEED TO TRUST HIM
AND BE MORE ASSERTIVE.
- IF I'M HOLDING BACK,
IT'S FOR MY FRIENDS.
- FRIENDS? HOW NAIVE.
- NO, WHAT'S NAIVE IS THE BELIEF
THAT MY LOVE FOR RIN
WAS EVER TRULY ENOUGH.
WE ALL CARE ABOUT HIM,
JUST TAKE NERINE, FOR EXAMPLE.
HER HEART ACHES AS MUCH AS
MINE DOES. MAYBE EVEN MORE.
- YOU'VE LOST HIM!
DON'T WASTE MY TIME
IF YOU'RE NOT WILLING TO FIGHT
FOR WHAT YOU WANT.
YOU THINK NERINE OR ANY
OF THOSE TRAMPS
ARE CONCERNED ABOUT
YOUR FEELINGS?
LOVE IS UGLY!
- UGLY? WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- IT ISN'T A RIGHT, SIA.
TO CLAIM LOVE, YOU HAVE TO
GET YOUR HANDS BLOODY.
YOU MUST CLAW YOUR
WAY TO HIS HEART
AND BEAT DOWN ANY COMPETITION.
AND, IF NOT, MISERY'S ALL YOU'LL
EVER HAVE TO CURL UP NEXT TO.
- NO, YOU'RE WRONG!
LOVE REQUIRES HONESTY.
LOVE IS PATIENT AND... EITHER
HE'S MEANT FOR ME, OR HE ISN'T.
- LIAR!
- YOU'RE LYING!
- WHAT AN IDIOT.
IN CASE YOU'D FORGOTTEN,
I AM YOU.
I KNOW HOW YOU REALLY FEEL!
- IF THAT'S TRUE...
YOU'LL RESPECT MY CHOICE.
YOU CAN SAY WHATEVER YOU WANT,
BUT THAT DOESN'T CHANGE
WHAT'S RIGHT.
IT'D BE SELFISH OF ME TO
TRY TO GAIN HAPPINESS
AT THE EXPENSE OF
SOMEONE ELSE'S.
- CAN'T SAY I DIDN'T TRY. I'M
DONE REASONING WITH YOU, SIA.
YOU HAD PLENTY OF
CHANCES TO MAKE RIN OURS
AND YOU BLEW THEM ALL.
I THINK IT'S TIME
I TOOK CONTROL.
IF YOU WON'T CLAIM HIM, I WILL!
- NO, YOU CAN'T!
LET ME OUT!
- AW, MAN.
I SHOULD'VE THOUGHT THIS
THROUGH JUST A LITTLE BETTER.
AGREEING TO HELP ASA SOUNDED SO
MUCH EASIER WHEN I WAS AWAKE!
STILL, I PROMISED.
- Kikyou: HI, RIN! GREAT TIMING!
- WHERE ARE YOU?
- YOU'RE NO FUN! UP HERE!
- ( gasps )
- ( giggling )
HEY THERE, SWEETIE!
- ( gasps ) SIA.
WHY ARE YOU UP THERE?
- BECAUSE... I LIKE TO SIT
ON A COLD FENCE IN THE MORNING.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I SURPRISED YOU, HUH?
WHICH MEANS YOUR
REASON FOR BEING HERE
IS FAR MORE INTERESTING
THAN MY OWN.
- UH, WELL, I WAS JUST...
- ( giggling )
SINCE WE'RE BOTH JUST STANDING
HERE, WE SHOULD GO ON A DATE.
- HUH? WAIT. A DATE?
- WHY NOT?
- UH, HUH, UH...
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Rin: I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO SIA,
BUT, SHE'S DEFINITELY
NOT HERSELF LATELY.
I GUESS HER ASKING ME OUT ISN'T
CRAZY OR ANYTHING, IT'S JUST...
WAIT! HEY, WHAT DOES SHE
THINK WE CAN DO RIGHT NOW?
WE HAVE SCHOOL!
- Nerine: NEXT TIME ON SHUFFLE.
EPISODE 17, "HONEST FEELINGS."
- Kikyou: YOUR WISH
AND MINE ARE THE SAME.