- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( clock chiming )
- ( coughing )
- Rin: ARE YOU OKAY?
- UH-HUH.
( continues coughing )
- HERE, LET ME SHOW YOU.
SEE, IF YOU DO IT THIS WAY,
YOU WON'T BREATHE IT IN.
- YOU'RE SO CLEVER, RIN.
- UH... IT'S REALLY NOT
ALL THAT IMPRESSIVE.
- HERE, LET ME TRY IT.
( coughing )
- TRY HOLDING IT
DOWN HERE. LIKE THIS.
- THANK YOU, I...
- OH, UH,
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- Mayumi: HEY, YOU GUYS
KISSING OVER THERE?
WITH TONGUES?
- HEY, NO KISSING!
- THANK YOU FOR HELPING.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
SOMEBODY HAS TO DUMP
THE TRASH AFTER ALL.
- BUT, IT'S MY JOB.
- HEY, IT'S EVERYBODY'S JOB.
AND BESIDES, NO GIRL
SHOULD EVER HAVE TO
CARRY THE TRASH
ALL BY HERSELF.
- I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
ANYWAY, I'M REALLY HAPPY THAT
I'M GETTING A CHANCE TO SPEND
TIME WITH YOU LIKE THIS.
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN
A DREAM OF MINE.
NOW THAT I'M ACTUALLY HERE,
MY DREAM'S FINALLY COMING TRUE
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS.
- NERINE.
- Man: ( guffaws ) OH PLEASE!
- IT'S SHOCKING!
I'VE HEARD THAT BOY,
RIN TSUCHIMI,
IS QUITE THE WOMANIZER!
- YES! I'VE HEARD THAT EVEN
THOUGH HE'S LIVING WITH KAEDE,
THE BELOVED PRINCESS
OF OUR SCHOOL,
HE'S AFTER THE PRINCESSES OF
THE GOD AND DEMON WORLDS, TOO!
THIS GUY IS AN ANIMAL!
- WHAT'S UP WITH YOU TWO?
- OH, SO NOW YOU'RE HOOKING
UP WITH PRINCESSES
SO YOU CAN BECOME
KING OF THE WORLD.
AH, DISGUSTING!
- JERKS. JUST IGNORE THEM,
IT'S OKAY.
( exclaims )
- ( rumbling )
- ( inhales ) I WON'T LET ANYONE
GET AWAY WITH INSULTING RIN!
- ( both screaming )
- UH, UM, NERINE?
- HOLD ON A SECOND, RIN.
I'M NOT QUITE FINISHED
WITH THESE TWO JUST YET.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY "FINISHED?"
- ( glass shattering )
- ( both screaming )
- WHAT'D YOU DO THAT FOR?
- YOU TRYING TO KILL US?
- OH, DON'T WORRY.
YOUR SUFFERING
WON'T LAST TOO MUCH LONGER.
- NERINE! NO!
- NOW I'M GONNA SEND YOU
STRAIGHT INTO HELL!
- ( explosion )
- FORTUNATELY THERE WERE
NO CASUALTIES.
BUT, ONE MISSTEP AND
THIS COULD HAVE BEEN
A MAJOR CATASTROPHE!
- BE GLAD THE DAMAGE WAS MINOR.
IT LOOKS LIKE NERINE IS FINALLY
LEARNING TO CONTROL HER POWER .
- THAT'S YOUR IDEA
OF MINOR DAMAGE?
- OH, ABSOLUTELY! I MEAN,
IF NERINE HAD USED ALL HER POWER
SHE COULD HAVE BLOWN THIS ENTIRE
SCHOOL TO KINGDOM COME! TWICE!
- SORRY. THEY WERE INSULTING
RIN, SO I COULDN'T HELP IT.
- NERINE, YOU HAVE NOTHING
TO APOLOGIZE FOR.
IN FACT, I'M UNBELIEVABLY PROUD
THAT YOU WERE ABLE TO
CONTROL YOUR MAGIC SO WELL!
MAYBE, IT'S BECAUSE OF
YOUR LOVE FOR RIN!
( laughing )
- THIS IS FUNNY TO YOU?
- NO.
- ( door opening )
- Eustoma: YO! MABO!
I HEARD THAT NERINE'S
BEEN GETTING INTO SOME MISCHIEF.
- WELL, THERE WERE SOME
LITTLE DEVILS INSULTING RIN,
SO NERINE GAVE THEM
WHAT THEY DESERVED. THAT'S ALL.
- OH... I SEE.
IN THAT CASE,
I HOPE NERINE SENT THEM
ON A LITTLE TOUR
OF THE UNDERWORLD!
( laughing )
UGH! YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND THE
SERIOUSNESS OF THIS SITUATION.
- HEY! NO BIG DEAL.
MY BEST TEAM OF MAGICIANS
WILL FIX EVERYTHING,
SO DON'T GET YOUR
PANTIES IN A BUNCH!
- IT'S NOW TIME FOR
A FATHER - TEACHER CONFERENCE.
SO WE CAN DEAL WITH
THE ROOT OF THIS PROBLEM.
- Forbesii: NO, NO! WE'RE
GOING HOME TO CELEBRATE!
- YOU WILL STAY HERE!
- ( both exclaiming )
- YOU MEAN, YOU WERE
WAITING FOR US?
- OF COURSE. ARE YOU OKAY?
- WE HEARD YOU TRIED TO DO
DIRTY THINGS TO NERINE
AND SHE GOT MAD
AND USED HER MAGIC
TO BLOW YOU TO SMITHEREENS,
SO WE WERE WORRIED.
- IF YOU KEEP ON MAKING UP
WEIRD RUMORS LIKE THAT
YOU MIGHT JUST END UP SUFFERING
THE SAME FATE AS THAT GYM.
- NERINE, YOU'RE PRETTY
INCREDIBLE WHEN YOU GET MAD!
- I'M SORRY.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO
APOLOGIZE FOR THAT!
IF I WAS THERE, I WOULD HAVE
KNOCKED THEM DEAD WITH A CHAIR!
- PLEASE DON'T DO THAT.
- DOES THIS MEAN YOU TWO
ARE ALLOWED TO GO HOME NOW?
- YEAH. ACTUALLY,
FORBESII AND EUSTOMA
SEEM TO BE IN MORE TROUBLE
THAN EITHER OF US.
- Sia: MY DAD'S IN TROUBLE?
NO WAY!
ALTHOUGH, I'M NOT REALLY SURE
HOW THAT HAPPENED.
- I'M SO SORRY I'VE
MADE SUCH A MESS
AND CAUSED EVERYONE
TO WORRY SO MUCH.
- OH, RINA.
PLEASE DON'T BE UPSET!
- SO, YOU DID ALL OF THAT
FOR ME, RIGHT?
I'M SORRY FOR THE GYM,
BUT IT MADE ME FEEL GOOD.
- I'M SO GLAD!
- THANKS A LOT, RINA.
- UH! COME ON. THAT'S ENOUGH,
YOU TWO LOVEBIRDS.
WHY DON'T YOU GUYS GET A ROOM?
- WELL, I GUESS WE SHOULD
HEAD HOME, TOO.
- YEAH, SURE.
RIN? IS IT OKAY?
IF I FALL MORE IN LOVE WITH YOU?
- ( heart beats )
- ( door opens )
- GOOD MORNING. ( gasps )
PRIMULA?
- MORNING RIN.
- WHAT THE HECK IS SHE
DOING IN MY DRESS SHIRT?
- I'M SORRY.
I WASHED RIMU'S PAJAMAS
BUT THEY WEREN'T DRY IN TIME.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU
GIVE HER ONE OF YOURS?
- I TRIED TO GIVE HER MINE.
SHE INSISTED ON WEARING
ONE OF YOURS INSTEAD.
- NICE?
- ( groans )
OH, I NEED TO PAY
MORE ATTENTION TO PRIMULA
OR THERE'S NO TELLING WHAT
KINDS OF THINGS SHE MIGHT DO.
- ( doorbell ringing )
- MORNING, RIN!
- GOOD MORNING, RIN.
- ( sighs ) GOOD MORNING,
SIA, RINA.
- IT'S A BEAUTIFUL DAY
TODAY, ISN'T IT?
RIN, IS IT OKAY IF I FALL
EVEN MORE IN LOVE WITH YOU?
- HEY! WHERE'S KAEDE?
- SHE'S MAKING LUNCH.
- HERE, RIN! IT'S READY!
- THANK YOU.
BUT, WHERE'S YOURS?
- ( gasps ) I FORGOT!
- KAEDE WORKS REALLY HARD,
DOESN'T SHE?
- SHE DOES. PRIMULA'S HERE NOW,
SO SHE HAS TO MAKE
LUNCH FOR THREE OF US.
- I WANNA MAKE LUNCH
FOR YOU SOMETIME, RIN!
- OH! THAT WOULD BE NICE.
- YAY! WHY DON'T WE COOK
FOR HIM TOGETHER, RINA!
- ( hesitatingly ) YEAH.
- ( clock chiming )
- ( students chattering )
- ( Itsuki laughing )
HEY, YOU REMEMBER THE PROMISE
WE MADE BEFORE THE EXAM, RIGHT?
- YEAH, OF COURSE.
BUT ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
I'M FEELING REALLY GOOD
ABOUT MYSELF TODAY!
- HMMM. WE'RE VERY CONFIDENT,
AREN'T WE?
- AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I DON'T BELIEVE THERE'S ANY WAY
YOU COULD HAVE POSSIBLY GOTTEN
A BETTER GRADE THAN ME,
SO BRING IT ON!
- OH, I SEE.
WELL, SHOW ME THEN!
- HERE...
- WE GO!
- NO WAY!
- COME ON. DON'T BE
SO HARD ON YOURSELF.
I WOULD SAY I GOT LUCKY, EXCEPT
THAT I'M OBVIOUSLY SMARTER.
( laughing deviously )
- YOU ACTUALLY GOT A GOOD
ENOUGH GRADE TO BEAT ITSUKI?
- YEAH, I DID.
THAT'S GREAT. I DID PRETTY
WELL ON MINE, TOO.
- WELL, THAT'S GOOD NEWS.
WE SHOULD ALL BE ABLE TO
ENJOY OUR SUMMER BREAK...
- WORRY FREE.
- RINA! WE NEED A FAVOR!
- PLEASE BLOW UP THE SCHOOL!
- ( gasping )
- OHH! WHY WASN'T I BORN
A FULL - FLEDGED DEMON
INSTEAD OF A HALF - BLOOD?
- COME ON, RINA! PLEASE!
JUST BLOW THIS JOINT UP!
- LEMME GUESS. YOU GUYS
FAILED, DIDN'T YOU?
- ( both exclaiming )
- UM. WHY ARE YOU ASKING
ME TO BLOWUP THE SCHOOL
FOR SUCH A SILLY REASON?
- BECAUSE YOU
ALMOST DID IT YESTERDAY.
- OH, RIGHT, BUT I WAS ONLY
TRYING TO HELP RIN.
- SO YOU WOULD DO IT
IF I ASKED YOU TO?
- OF COURSE!
- ( groans )
- DO IT, RIN!
C'MON, WISH FOR IT!
WISH FOR THE SCHOOL TO BLOW UP!
- NO.
- ( sobbing ) THIS IS SO UNFAIR!
YOU CAN DO ANYTHING,
RINA! SCHOOL! MAGIC!
YOU'RE GOOD AT EVERYTHING
AND I'M NOT!
- YOU KNOW THAT'S NOT TRUE, SIA!
- THERE'S NO GOD
IN THIS CRUEL WORLD!
- Rin: I DON'T THINK
YOUR DAD WOULD LIKE IT
IF HE HEARD YOU SAY THAT.
- ( students chattering )
- Kaede: OH, COME ON,
YOU TWO! CHEER UP!
- ( both moaning )
- HEY, WAIT. I THINK
I KNOW OF A WAY
YOU CAN AVOID
SUMMER SCHOOL CLASSES
JUST DO A PAPER
ON LAPLACE'S THEORY.
- COME ON, LIKE
I CAN UNDERSTAND THAT.
- WHAT? RINA, YOU CAN WRITE
ABOUT THAT STUFF? NO WAY!
- YEAH. IT'S EASY
IF YOU PAY ATTENTION.
- ALL RIGHT! CAN I
HAVE YOUR NOTES?
- SURE, I GUESS YOU CAN.
- YOU'RE A LIFESAVER! IT'S
SO GREAT TO HAVE A FRIEND
WHO'S AS GOOD AT
EVERYTHING AS YOU!
- I THINK MY APPETITE IS FINALLY
STARTING TO COME BACK!
- OF COURSE, RIN'S LUNCH
LOOKS REALLY GOOD
BECAUSE KAEDE MADE IT,
BUT I DIDN'T EXPECT YOURS AND
NERINE'S LUNCH TO LOOK SO YUMMY!
- UM, WELL...
- DID YOU MAKE IT YOURSELF?
- UM-HM. WHILE I'M
EATING BREAKFAST
I TRY TO THINK ABOUT WHAT
I SHOULD PUT IN MY LUNCH.
THE MORNING GOES BY
A LOT QUICKER THAT WAY!
- HM. I DO THE SAME THING,
ONLY THE NIGHT BEFORE.
HOW 'BOUT YOU, RINA?
- UH, WELL, I...
- MAN!
WHEN IT COMES TO LUNCHES,
NOTHING CAN BEAT HOME - MADE!
( chomping )
- OH, SURE.
- YEAH, YOU ALWAYS HAVE
A HOME - MADE LUNCH, TOO,
DON'T YOU?
- 'COURSE I DO!
- SO, WHO IS IT FROM THIS TIME?
- A FRESHMAN.
THEY'RE STILL SO
INNOCENT AND TRUSTING
WHEN THEY'RE THAT
YOUNG. TURNS ME ON.
- YOU'RE SUCH A SLIME-BUCKET.
DIDN'T YOU GET YOUR LUNCH
FROM A JUNIOR YESTERDAY?
- YES, I DID. AND THERE'S
NOTHING WRONG WITH THAT.
- UGH! YOU SUCK!
- ( laughing )
HEY! SINCE THERE
ARE SO MANY OF US
WHO LIKE TO MAKE
HOME- MADE LUNCHES!
WHY DON'T WE PLAN
A BIG PICNIC FOR NEXT SUNDAY?
IT WOULD BE SO MUCH FUN!
- AGREED! WE COULD SAMPLE
EACH OTHER'S FOOD THAT WAY!
- I'M NOT TOUCHING YOURS.
BUT I CAN'T WAIT TO TRY WHATEVER
NERINE AND SIA BRING FOR LUNCH!
- I GET IT. SO MY
COOKING SUCKS. FINE.
- HUH?
SO RIN IS GOING TO BE
EATING MY LUNCH.
I WONDER WHAT I SHOULD MAKE!
RINA! DO YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE GONNA BRING?
- WELL, I, UH...
- I'M SURE IT'LL BE GREAT!
- Kaede: HEY, RIN, I HAVE
A QUESTION ABOUT SUNDAY.
- SURE, WHAT IS IT?
- ASA OVERHEARD US
TALKING ABOUT THE PICNIC,
AND SHE WANTS TO COME WITH US,
IS THAT OKAY WITH YOU?
- YEAH, OF COURSE IT IS.
- OH, GOOD. ITSUKI AND
MAYUMI DIDN'T MIND, EITHER.
- AND NERINE?
- I THINK SHE ALREADY LEFT.
- THAT'S UNUSUAL. BUT I'M SURE
SHE WON'T MIND IF ASA COMES.
- ALL RIGHT! THEN
WE'LL GO AND TELL ASA
THAT SHE'S MORE THAN
WELCOME TO COME!
- YEAH!
- ( Kaede giggles )
- ( sighs )
- Kaede: THAT'S IT.
CUT LITTLE CHUNKS.
NOW BE CAREFUL. IT'S OKAY
TO GO SLOW AT FIRST.
- HEY, WHATCHA DOIN' THERE?
- WHOA! WHAT'S THAT FOR?
- COOKING.
- YOU'RE COOKING?
- RIMU TOLD ME SHE REALLY
WANTED TO LEARN HOW TO.
SO I'M TEACHING HER THE BASICS.
- THAT'S GREAT!
I GUESS PRIMULA'S GOT
A DOMESTIC SIDE TO HER.
SO HOW'S IT GOING SO FAR,
IS SHE DOING WELL?
- GOOD.
- ( whimpers )
- SHE HAS A LOT OF POTENTIAL.
- WELL, SHE SHOULDN'T
HAVE ANY PROBLEMS
WITH YOU AS HER INSTRUCTOR.
- BUT I THINK SHE WOULD
LEARN A LOT FASTER
IF SHE COULD TAKE
LESSONS FROM ASA.
- ASA?
- SHE'S REALLY AMAZING.
SHE TAUGHT ME HOW TO COOK!
- IF SHE'S WILLING,
MAYBE WE COULD GET HER TO
COME AND TEACH A LITTLE BIT.
NO, YOU.
- ( Rin chuckles )
- OKAY THEN. LET'S REVIEW
HOW TO HOLD THE KNIFE.
THIS WAY, REMEMBER?
- THAT'S IT.
TAKE YOUR TIME.
- ( paper shuffling )
- ( tapping )
- Man: DON'T RELY
ON YOUR EYES! FEEL IT!
- Rin: SHE'S GONE AGAIN?
- I REALLY WANTED TO
MAKE PLANS WITH HER
FOR THE PICNIC, YOU KNOW?
- SHE WASN'T HERE FOR
LUNCH, EITHER, WAS SHE?
- NO. IT SEEMS LIKE SHE'S
BEEN LEAVING TO GO SOMEWHERE
AS SOON AS CLASS GETS OUT.
- I HOPE EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
- MAYUMI AND SIA WERE WORRIED
THAT SOMETHING MIGHT
BE GOING ON WITH HER.
- I SEE.
- ( door opens )
- NERINE!
- OH! ASA!
- ARE YOU OKAY?
LET ME SEE THAT.
IT'S NOT AS BAD AS IT LOOKS.
HOLD ON, GIMME A SECOND.
- WOW, THOSE ARE HANDY.
- YEAH, THEY'RE A NECESSITY
FOR COOKING CLUB.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH, ASA!
- WELL, YOU'RE VERY WELCOME.
BUT, WHAT'RE YOU DOING
HERE ALL ALONE?
YOU'RE COOKING?
- UM, ASA, WILL YOU...
- HMM?
- WILL YOU TEACH ME
HOW TO COOK?
- HEY! WELCOME HOME!
- WHAT ARE YOU
STANDING OUT HERE FOR?
- WELL, NERINE IS
LATER THAN USUAL
GETTING HOME FROM SCHOOL.
DO YOU HAPPEN TO
KNOW WHERE SHE IS?
- NO, I'M AFRAID SHE WAS
ALREADY GONE WHEN WE LEFT.
- HMM...
- DO YOU THINK SHE MIGHT
HAVE STOPPED SOMEWHERE
TO DO SOME SHOPPING?
IT'S STILL EARLY AFTER ALL.
- HUH. I GUESS
IT'S A POSSIBILITY.
BUT SHE USUALLY
COMES STRAIGHT HOME
SO FORGIVE ME IF I'M WORRIED.
- WE COULD GO LOOK
FOR HER IF YOU WANT.
- NO! THAT'S OKAY. I'LL JUST
WAIT HERE A LITTLE WHILE LONGER.
- I HOPE SHE COMES HOME SOON.
- ( chuckles )
- I WONDER WHERE SHE COULD BE?
- Asa: IT'S VERY SHARP, SO
KEEP YOUR FINGERS TUCKED IN.
- 'KAY.
- COME ON, YOU NEED TO
RELAX A LITTLE BIT.
- 'KAY.
- ( door closes )
- Rin: WHERE'S NERINE?
- I THINK THAT SHE LEFT
FOR SCHOOL ALREADY.
HMM?
- AS WE ALL KNOW, IT'S POSSIBLE
FOR HUMANS TO BE SPIRITED AWAY
FROM OUR WORLD TO OTHER REALMS.
IT'S ALSO POSSIBLE FOR
BEINGS FROM OTHER REALMS
TO APPEAR IN OUR WORLD.
- TSUCCHI.
YOU OWE ME A TEN PAGE REPORT
ON THIS BY TOMORROW!
- NO WAY!
- ( students laughing )
- NERINE!
- WHAT IS IT, RIN?
- DID SOMETHING HAPPEN RECENTLY?
I HEAR YOU'VE BEEN COMING
HOME FROM SCHOOL LATE.
AND NOW EVERYONE'S
WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
WHAT'S WRONG?
- COME ON. DON'T PRESSURE HER,
MAYBE SHE'S NOT READY TO
TALK TO YOU ABOUT IT YET.
- COME ON, ASA.
TELL ME WHAT'S GOING ON.
- NOW, RIN. A GIRL HAS EVERY
RIGHT TO KEEP A SECRET
FOR AS LONG AS SHE WANTS TO.
YOU BE PATIENT.
IT'S UP TO NERINE
TO TELL YOU WHAT'S GOING ON,
WHEN AND IF SHE
DECIDES SHE'S READY.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
DON'T YOU TRUST HER JUDGMENT?
CATCH YOU LATER!
RINA, DO YOU NEED TO
TAKE A LITTLE BREAK?
- I'M SORRY.
- SO WHY DID YOU WANT TO
KEEP THIS A SECRET FROM RIN?
WHAT'S WRONG, NERINE?
- UH, WELL, IT'S JUST...
RIN SAID THAT HE WAS
REALLY LOOKING FORWARD
TO EATING THE LUNCH
I WAS MAKING, SO...
I DIDN'T WANT HIM TO KNOW
THAT I COULDN'T COOK.
I REALLY DIDN'T MEAN
TO LIE TO HIM, BUT
WHEN I IMAGINED HOW DISAPPOINTED
IN ME HE WOULD BE,
I JUST COULDN'T
TELL HIM THE TRUTH.
- OH, I GET IT!
YOU MUST REALLY LIKE RIN
A WHOLE LOT, IS THAT IT?
- YEAH.
- THIS'LL BE EASY THEN!
A MEAL ALWAYS
TURNS OUT THE BEST
WHEN IT'S MADE FOR
SOMEONE SPECIAL.
JUST PUT YOUR HEART AND SOUL
INTO IT AND IT'LL BE DELICIOUS!
- HMM.
- YOU KNOW, I REALLY THINK
YOU SHOULD TELL RIN
THE TRUTH, THOUGH.
IT'S NOTHING TO BE ASHAMED OF.
DON'T LOOK SO WORRIED!
IT'LL BE FINE!
BEFORE SUNDAY, I'LL TEACH YOU
A VERY SPECIAL RECIPE!
IT'LL BE AN ABSOLUTE SUCCESS!
I PROMISE YOU!
- THANK YOU.
I'M VERY GRATEFUL.
- NOW GO FIND RIN. THE POOR
GUY'S WORRIED SICK!
- 'KAY. THANK YOU, ASA!
- OH, BY THE WAY, I
WAS KIND OF WONDERING
IF MAYBE YOU LIKED
RIN, TOO. DO YOU?
- ( gasps ) WHY DO YOU ASK?
- I HAD A FEELING.
- SILLY! HE AND I ARE
JUST FRIENDS, THAT'S ALL!
HURRY! YOU BETTER GO FIND HIM!
- RIGHT!
- ( sighs )
- ( footsteps approaching )
- ( door opens )
- ( panting )
- NERINE.
- HELLO.
- WHAT IS IT?
- I JUST... I WANTED
YOU TO KNOW THE TRUTH
BEFORE WE WENT ON
THE PICNIC TOGETHER.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO COOK.
MY DAD'S BEEN MAKING
MY LUNCHES FOR ME.
- NERINE...
- I DIDN'T MEAN TO HIDE IT,
BUT I WAS AFRAID I WOULD
DISAPPOINT YOU, SO...
- SO, ASA WAS GIVING YOU
COOKING LESSONS?
- I'M SORRY.
- HOW SILLY!
YOU DON'T NEED TO
APOLOGIZE FOR THAT!
- BUT...
- YOU SHOULD NEVER
EVER BE AFRAID
TO TELL ME THE TRUTH,
OKAY, NERINE?
I HAVE NO DOUBT THAT
WHATEVER YOU COOK FOR ME
WILL BE DELICIOUS.
IT'S SETTLED THEN.
I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO IT!
- SO AM I!
- WELL, I DON'T WANT TO
INTERRUPT YOUR LESSONS.
SO, I'LL LEAVE YOU TO IT.
IT WOULDN'T BE ANY FUN
IF I SAW WHAT YOU WERE MAKING.
IT WOULDN'T BE A SURPRISE.
- RIN, THANK YOU.
- WELL, RINA, I'LL
SEE YOU ON SUNDAY.
HAVE FUN COOKING!
I CAN'T WAIT TO TRY YOUR LUNCH!
- ( giggling )
- All: THAT'S BEAUTIFUL.
- HERE.
- IS IT OKAY TO OPEN IT?
- Both: HUH?
- UH, UM-HM.
- All: UHH...
- IT'S AN OMELET.
- I'M REALLY SORRY. YOU SEE,
SO FAR, IT'S ALL I CAN MAKE.
- THIS IS THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
OMELET I'VE EVER SEEN.
I CAN'T WAIT TO EAT IT!
WOW! IT'S SO GOOD!
IT'S ABSOLUTELY DELICIOUS.
YUM! NEED MORE!
- DON'T HOG IT ALL!
LET ME TRY!
- Itsuki: I CAN'T WAIT TO TEST
DRIVE SOME OF NERINE'S OMELET!
- NO! THIS IS MINE!
NERINE MADE IT FOR ME!
- HEY!
- NO FAIR!
- Rin: STOP IT! I'LL BITE YOU!
- Kaede: COME ON, SHARE!
- Rin: I'M SERIOUS!
THERE'S ONLY ENOUGH FOR ME!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Nerine: I HATE
WAKING UP EARLY!
- Kaede: TRY GOING TO
BED EARLIER, SILLY!
- I'LL DO MY BEST!
- Kaede: NEXT TIME ON SHUFFLE!
EPISODE 5. WHERE I BELONG.
- I'M GOING TO SLEEP NOW!
- ( yawns )
- SEE! IT'S NOT SO HARD!
- Rin: THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK.