- ( alarm ringing )
- HMM.
- GOOD MORNING, RIN.
- ( giggles ) COME ON,
IT'S TIME TO GET UP NOW.
- AW, GIVE ME A BREAK.
- IT'S EARLY STILL.
- JUST LET ME SLEEP A LITTLE
BIT LONGER, PLEASE?
- BUT RIN, YOU WANT TO
BE ABLE TO SIT DOWN
AND ENJOY YOUR FOOD, RIGHT?
THERE'S HOT MISO SOUP
WAITING FOR YOU,
WITH MUSHROOMS,
JUST LIKE YOU LIKE IT.
- SHIITAKE MUSHROOMS? BECAUSE
THOSE ARE THE ONES I LIKE.
- SILLY, WHICH OTHER ONES
ARE THERE?
- AND THOSE LITTLE GREEN ONIONS?
YOU KNOW I LIKE GREEN ONIONS.
- ( chuckles )
HOW COULD I FORGET?
- HMM.
- HOW DO YOU DO IT, KAEDE?
I MEAN, YOU NEVER FORGET
A THING, DO YOU?
- ( giggles )
NOT WHEN IT COMES TO YOU.
ANYWAY, BREAKFAST IS READY
AND WAITING FOR YOU, OKAY?
SO, COME DOWN
AS SOON AS YOU CAN.
- HARD TO BELIEVE
WE'RE THE SAME AGE.
SO, THIS IS ME.
I'M RIN TSUCHIMI.
I'VE BEEN LIVING WITH KAEDE
FUYOU FOR EIGHT YEARS NOW.
BOTH MY PARENTS PASSED
AWAY IN AN ACCIDENT,
ALONG WITH KAEDE'S MOTHER.
SINCE THEN, KAEDE HAS PRETTY
MUCH TAKEN CARE OF ME.
ALTHOUGH, SINCE I
STAY HERE RENT FREE,
I SHOULD REALLY BE
DOING ALL THE WORK.
- HERE YOU GO, RIN.
JUST LIKE I PROMISED.
- OH, THANKS.
- UH, HEY, KAEDE, I KNOW
I'VE SAID THIS BEFORE
BUT WE COULD JUST HAVE TOAST.
- OKAY. I'LL MAKE
TOAST TOMORROW.
LET'S SEE, WHAT'S
GOOD WITH TOAST.
- AH, WE CAN HAVE EGGS,
AND BACON, AND MAYBE...
- NO, NO. I MEAN...
- HMM?
- IT JUST SEEMS LIKE A LOT
OF WORK TO COOK ALL THIS
EVERY MORNING, THAT'S ALL.
- OH, NO, NOT AT ALL. I REALLY
LOVE TAKING CARE OF YOU, RIN.
IT'S WHAT I ENJOY
DOING THE MOST.
DOES THAT BOTHER YOU?
- OH, NO. I DIDN'T MEAN THAT.
- ( chuckles )
GOOD, WANT SOME TEA?
- HERE YOU GO. DON'T
FORGET ABOUT YOUR LUNCH.
- OH, THANKS.
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHERE'S YOUR LUNCH?
- ( gasps ) OH, NO,
I CAN'T BELIEVE I FORGOT.
- HUH, ALWAYS THINKING
ABOUT ME INSTEAD OF HERSELF.
- I FEEL SO STUPID.
THANKS FOR WAITING.
- NO PROB. HEY LOOK, I GUESS
THE SATOHS ARE MOVING OUT.
- YEAH, THE TANAKAS,
THE YAMAMOTOS,
AND THE UESUGIS MOVED OUT, TOO.
SO DID THE GOSHOGAWARAS.
- THAT'LL MAKE EIGHT NEIGHBORS
ON BOTH SIDES OF US, WON'T IT?
- YOU THINK MAYBE WE'VE DONE
SOMETHING TO PISS THEM ALL OFF?
- HUH?
- IS YOUR DAD GONNA BE GONE
FOR A VERY LONG THIS TIME?
- HIS BUSINESS TRIPS ARE
GETTING OUT OF HAND.
- YEAH, I KNOW, RIGHT.
- HE SAID HE COULD BE GONE
FOR AS LONG AS
THREE OR FOUR MONTHS.
- DON'T YOU THINK THAT'S WEIRD?
I MEAN LEAVING A YOUNG
MAN AND A YOUNG GIRL
IN A BIG HOUSE
ALONE ALL THAT TIME?
- I DON'T KNOW. MAYBE, IT JUST
SHOWS THAT HE TRUSTS YOU.
- ( chuckles ) YOU THINK?
- 'CAUSE YOU KNOW,
WHEN HE WAS LEAVING,
HE DID TELL ME I
OUGHT TO 'GO FOR IT',
SINCE I HAVE HIS APPROVAL.
- ( gasps )
- I THINK HE SHOULD BE
PUTTING MORE THOUGHT
INTO HIS DAUGHTER'S FUTURE.
ISN'T HE AFRAID GUYS
ARE GONNA BE INTIMIDATED
BY OUR RELATIONSHIP?
I MEAN, DOESN'T HE
WANT YOU TO BE HAPPY?
- I THINK MAYBE DADDY MIGHT
BE THINKING THE SAME THING
ABOUT MY FUTURE THAT I AM.
- HUH?
- OH, UH, NOTHING.
- I'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR YOU, RIN.
I'M MAGNUM SAKAI, OF
KAEDE'S PERSONAL GUARD,
THE KNIGHTS OF KISSY KAEDE
OTHERWISE KNOWN AS THE KKK.
UH, NOT THE MEAN GUYS
WITH THE SHEETS.
- ( whimpers )
- WAIT, YOU'RE IN HIGH SCHOOL?
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING.
- SHUT YOUR MOUTH, RIN TSUCHIMI.
I HEREBY CHALLENGE YOU
TO A DUEL FOR MISS FUYOU'S LOVE.
- WOW, WHAT A CHARMER.
SO, "MISS FUYOU," HOW DOES IT
FEEL BEING TURNED INTO A PRIZE?
- ( laughs awkwardly )
UH, I...
- NOW, YOU DIE!
- ( screams )
- YOU CAN'T, I'VE ALREADY GIVEN
MY WHOLE BODY AND SOUL TO RIN.
- ( cries )
- I'M SO SORRY, RIN.
I DIDN'T REALLY MEAN
THAT LIKE IT SOUNDED.
- UH, KAEDE, LET'S JUST GO.
- ( cries )
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- YEAH, I'M FINE.
- ( panting )
- I GUESS WE FINALLY LOST THEM.
- THANK GOODNESS.
I'M SO GLAD THERE WERE ONLY
A FEW GROUPIES OUT TODAY.
- THEY DO THIS EVERY
SINGLE MORNING.
WHEN ARE THEY GOING TO GET
THE HINT AND LEAVE US ALONE.
- HUH. OH MY GOSH, UH, RIN?
- HUH? OH, I'M SORRY.
- THAT'S OKAY.
- ( grunts )
- HELLO.
GOOD MORNING, RIN.
- SO, HOW ARE YOU DOING
THIS MORNING, ASA?
- YOU WALKED TO SCHOOL
TOGETHER AGAIN, HUH?
DOES THIS MEAN YOU TWO
ARE LOVEBIRDS, TELL ME.
- HUH? DID YOU JUST ATTACK ME
OUT OF A SUDDEN FIT OF JEALOUSY?
- YOU BETTER BE CAREFUL RIN.
US GIRLS HAVE FRAGILE HEARTS,
YOU WOULDN'T WANT
TO STRING HER ALONG.
UNLESS YOU REALLY
DO LIKE HER, WELL?
- DON'T BE SILLY ASA. BY THE
WAY, DO YOU THINK YOU COULD BE
A LITTLE MORE GENTLE WITH
ME FROM NOW ON, PLEASE.
- OKAY. IS THIS GENTLE
ENOUGH FOR YOU?
- AH. STOP IT, ASA.
- I BET YOU'LL BE DREAMING
ABOUT THIS TONIGHT, WON'T YOU?
- WOULD YOU KNOCK
IT OFF, PLEASE?
- ( laughs ) JUST KIDDING.
- MAN, I REALLY WISH
SHE'D STOP TEASING.
I MEAN, SHE'S EMBARRASSING ME.
- DO YOU REALLY
THINK I'M TEASING?
- HUH?
- DON'T MISS ME TOO MUCH.
- CRAZY GIRL. SHE REALLY KNOWS
HOW TO MESS WITH A GUY'S BRAIN.
- IT'S ALL THAT ENERGY SHE JUST
DOESN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH IT.
- SHE SURE WEARS ME OUT.
- ( students chattering )
- KAEDE.
- ( grunts )
- KAEDE! COME INTO MY BOSOM.
- ITSUKI, UM, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING TO RIN?
- WELCOME TO MY FISTS, ITSUKI.
- UH, I DON'T LIKE YOU
LIKE THAT, MAN.
- WHEN ARE YOU GONNA LEARN
TO LEAVE KAEDE ALONE.
- COME ON. I CAN'T HELP IT
I CAN'T DEPRIVE MYSELF
OF KAEDE'S LOVE, RIGHT?
- WHY ARE YOU SO STUCK ON KAEDE?
THERE ARE OTHER GIRLS, YOU KNOW.
TAKE MAYUMI FOR INSTANCE.
- AW, I GOTTA HAVE
SOMETHING TO GRAB ON TO,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- ( chuckles )
MAYUMI IS TOO FLAT CHESTED.
- UGH. WHATEVER.
- ( giggles ) IT'S NICE
TO SEE YOU, MAYUMI.
- HI, KAEDE.
- THERE IS NOTHING WRONG
WITH BEING FLAT CHESTED, OKAY?
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
THERE ARE LOTS OF GUYS
WHO ACTUALLY PREFER IT.
- YEAH, THAT'S ONLY A
TINY PERCENTAGE OF GUYS,
AND YOU KNOW IT.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
NO ONE WANTS D CUPS ANYMORE.
NOT D, NOT C, NOT B. IT'S
ABOUT WHAT FITS IN YOUR HAND.
- UM, THAT'S REALLY
EMBARRASSING.
- DOES IT FEEL LIKE
KIND OF LIKE A BOARD?
- UGH. YOU KNOW WHAT?
GUYS WHO CAN'T WAIT
TO HUG EACH OTHER,
FIRST THING IN THE MORNING
REALLY SHOULDN'T TALK.
- DON'T GET IDEAS. THAT WASN'T
WHAT IT LOOKED LIKE?
- NOW WAIT JUST A MINUTE
THERE, SUGAR LUMPS.
SEE, MY PRIORITY
IN LIFE IS GIRLS,
FOLLOWED BY FEMALES,
LADIES, WOMEN AND BABES.
THE GIRLS ARE WHAT
I ABSOLUTELY LIVE AND DIE FOR.
- LISTEN TO HIM, WE'RE
GONNA HAVE TO LOCK HIM UP
IF THIS TRANSFER
STUDENT IS A GIRL.
- OH. THAT'S RIGHT,
I THINK I'VE HEARD SOME
PEOPLE TALKING ABOUT THAT.
- IS THE STUDENT HERE ALREADY?
- NO. I'M NOT SURE OF
ALL THE DETAILS YET,
BUT IT LOOKS LIKE THEY'RE
GONNA BE HERE TOMORROW.
- I WONDER WHAT KIND
OF PERSON THEY'LL BE.
- CONSIDERING THE WAY
IT'S BEEN LATELY,
I'M GUESSING EITHER
A DEMON OR A GOD.
- THE TRANSFER STUDENT
WILL BE A VERY PRETTY GIRL.
- HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
- IT'S IN THE AIR. I CAN SMELL
"PRETTY" FROM A MILE AWAY.
MY NOSE HAS NEVER
BEEN WRONG BEFORE.
- YOU HAVE A VERY WEIRD NOSE
KIND OF LIKE THE REST OF YOU.
- YOU'D BE SURPRISED.
- ITSUKI'S SENSE OF
SMELL IS RIGHT ON TARGET
WHEN IT COMES TO GIRLS.
- WHAT DOES IT EVEN MATTER
WHETHER IT'S A GUY OR A GIRL?
- YOU'RE REALLY NOT INTERESTED?
OH, WELL YOU'VE
ALREADY GOT KAEDE
SO I GUESS IT'S NOT
ALL THAT SURPRISING.
- COME ON, THAT'S
NOT THE WAY IT IS.
- AW, RIN. IF YOU LOSE
YOUR INTEREST IN GIRLS,
YOU'RE GONNA LOSE
YOUR MAN CARD FOR EVER.
- AND THAT CAME FROM A GUY
WHO HUGGED ME EARLIER.
- YOU'RE JUST TOO SPOILED
FOR YOUR OWN GOOD.
YOU'VE GOT A GORGEOUS
GIRL NAMED KAEDE
TAKING CARE OF YOUR EVERY NEED,
SO, YOU'VE BEEN BLINDED.
AND YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
YOU'RE LIVING A MAN'S
DREAM COME TRUE.
- WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- AH, YOU'RE HOPELESS.
- RIN, DO YOU, DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE LIVING A FULFILLED LIFE
EVERY SINGLE DAY?
YEAH, I DIDN'T THINK SO.
WELL, I SAY AFTER SCHOOL,
WE ADD SOME FEMALE
FULFILLMENT TO YOUR LIFE.
- THAT'S WHAT
YOU WERE GOING FOR.
- ALL RIGHT CLASS,
BUTTS IN SEATS.
TEN YEARS AGO,
DUE TO THE INCIDENT
NOW KNOWN AS THE "GATE OPENING,"
THE GATEWAY TO THE
REALM OF THE GODS
AND THE REALM OF THE
DEMONS WAS OPENED.
SOON AFTERWARDS,
THE GODS AND THE DEMONS
BEGAN MIGRATING TO OUR WORLD.
NOW THERE ARE PLACES
WHERE DEMONS, GODS
AND HUMANS ALL STUDY TOGETHER.
SUCH AS OUR SCHOOL,
VERBENA ACADEMY.
JUST SO YOU KNOW, THE
HISTORY OF THE GATEWAY
WILL BE ON THE FINAL EXAM.
IF YOU GET IT WRONG,
I'LL MAKE YOU DO BUNNY
HOPS WITH DUMB BELLS.
- All: AW.
- Itsukido: YOU THINK YOU'RE
LIVING A FULFILLED LIFE
EVERY SINGLE DAY?
THE GIRLS ARE WHAT I
ABSOLUTELY LIVE AND DIE FOR.
- I REALLY LOVE TAKING
CARE OF YOU, RIN.
- MAYUMI LIVES FOR CHASING
THE NEWEST SCOOP.
ASA TRIES TO ENJOY LIFE
TO THE FULLEST EVERY DAY.
THEY ALL HAVE SOMETHING
THAT FULFILLS THEM.
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
- YOU SURE LOOK RELAXED
RIGHT NOW.
MY CLASS IS APPARENTLY
EXTREMELY BORING.
SORRY, I'M SUCH A BAD TEACHER.
- ME, TOO, I MEAN NO,
NOT THAT YOU'RE, THAT I'M...
- ( chuckles )
YOU LUCKED OUT, TSUCHIMI.
- ( sighs )
- COME WITH ME, WE NEED TO TALK.
RIN, DID YOU EVER BECOME
ACQUAINTED WITH GIRLS
FROM OTHER WORLDS
WHEN YOU WERE A KID?
- NO, NOT THAT CAN I REMEMBER.
ALTHOUGH I WASN'T REALLY
AWARE THAT PEOPLE
FROM OTHER WORLDS
EXISTED BACK THEN.
WHY DO YOU WANNA KNOW?
- OH, IT'S NOTHING
TO BE WORRIED ABOUT.
AT LEAST, I DON'T THINK IT IS.
- YOU'VE OBVIOUSLY GOT
SOMETHING ON YOUR MIND.
- HMM, THE ONLY ADVICE I CAN
GIVE YOU FOR NOW, IS THIS,
BE STRONG.
- OKAY.
- GOOD LUCK.
- I'LL HELP YOU
AS MUCH AS I CAN.
- WHA...
- REMEMBER, BE BRAVE.
STAY STRONG AND DON'T
GIVE UP NO MATTER WHAT.
- HUH? I DON'T GET IT.
BUT WHAT IS IT THAT I'M
SUPPOSED TO BE FIGHTING?
- READY TO GO HOME, KAEDE?
- I'M SORRY, BUT I CAN'T
GO HOME JUST YET.
- DO YOU NEED
TO STAY LATER TODAY?
- HEY, KAEDE, SORRY FOR
MAKING YOU WAIT SO LONG,
ARE YOU READY TO GO, SWEETIE?
- THAT'S A SURPRISE.
WHY ARE ASA AND KAREHA HERE?
DO YOU HAVE AFTER SCHOOL PLANS
WITH THEM OR SOMETHING?
- OH, HELLO, IT'S NICE
TO SEE YOU, RIN.
I HEARD SOMETHING
ABOUT YOU TODAY.
I HEARD YOU WERE GETTING
IT ON WITH ITSUKI.
- AH, WHAT KIND OF RUMORS
ARE THE UPPER CLASSMEN
SPREADING AROUND ABOUT ME NOW?
- OH, YOU KNOW, FORBIDDEN LOVE.
- ( laughing )
- WHATEVER IT IS YOU'RE
PICTURING IN YOUR HEAD
RIGHT NOW, JUST STOP IT, OKAY?
- OH, COME ON, GET OVER IT.
WE ALL KNOW YOU'RE KAEDE'S
"KNIGHT IN SHINING ARMOR."
- THE WAY YOU SAY
IT, I'M NOT SURE
HOW I SHOULD TAKE THAT.
- WELL, ANYWAY, MR. KNIGHT.
WE HAVE TO BORROW KAEDE
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
- HUH?
- I'M REALLY EXCITED, RIN.
I'M LEARNING HOW TO MAKE
A BRAND NEW RECIPE FOR YOU
TODAY IN COOKING CLUB.
IT'LL BE GREAT.
- ( giggles ) ISN'T IT NICE
TO KNOW A GIRL
WHO'S SO EAGER TO LEARN HOW TO
MAKE YOU GREAT FOOD? LUCKY.
- ( grunts ) DO YOU HAVE
TO BEAT THE STUFFING
OUT OF ME LIKE THAT?
- AH, LISTEN UP. THE NEW
TRANSFER STUDENT IS A GIRL.
ACTUALLY, THERE ARE TWO OF THEM.
- ( excited chatter )
- ONE OF THEM IS A GOD,
AND ONE OF THEM IS A DEMON,
AND THEY'RE BOTH
RIDICULOUSLY PRETTY.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU,
AREN'T YOU EVEN INTERESTED?
- HUH? WHAT DID YOU SAY?
- ( laughs ) YOU'RE CLUELESS.
I GUESS KAEDE STILL
DOESN'T HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT ROMANTIC
RIVALS FOR A WHILE.
- ROMANTIC RIVALS?
- ( laughs ) ANYWAY, YOU READY,
KAEDE? WE SHOULD GET GOING.
- LATER, RIN.
- I'M SO SORRY, RIN.
- I'LL MAKE A
GREAT DINNER FOR YOU
AS SOON AS I GET HOME,
OKAY? I PROMISE.
- OH, DON'T RUSH OR ANYTHING.
I THINK WE NEED SOME MILK.
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE
THAT WE'RE OUT OF?
HMM. I WISH I WOULD HAVE
THOUGHT OF ASKING KAEDE
BEFORE I LEFT THE SCHOOL.
- IF WE NEED ANYTHING ELSE,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I'LL GO SHOPPING LATER.
YOU JUST STAY HOME AND RELAX.
- I KNOW THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT SHE WOULD SAY.
I GUESS I'LL JUST HAVE TO DO
THE BEST THAT I CAN FOR NOW.
- THOSE EARS, SHE MUST BE A GOD.
I DON'T THINK I'VE SEEN
HER AROUND HERE BEFORE.
- SO, AS FAR AS COST GOES,
THIS ONE'S LESS EXPENSIVE,
BUT IF I GET MORE WITH THIS ONE,
IT MIGHT BE WORTH
PAYING A LITTLE EXTRA.
- AH, EXCUSE ME.
CAN YOU HELP ME DECIDE
WHICH ONE OF THESE I SHOULD GET?
- UH, SORRY?
- I'VE MANAGED TO NARROW
IT DOWN TO THESE TWO,
BUT I JUST CAN'T
MAKE UP MY MIND.
- OH.
- SEE, I'M COOKING FOR SOMEONE
WHO EATS A LOT,
SO, I DON'T KNOW IF I SHOULD BUY
TWO OF THESE MEDIUM PACKAGES,
OR JUST GET ONE OF THE BIG ONES.
SAVINGS OR QUANTITY?
- AH, MY HEAD HURTS
JUST THINKING ABOUT IT.
- OH, THAT'S ROUGH.
- SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK, HUH?
- UM, IF THEY HAVE THAT
BIG OF AN APPETITE,
THEN MAYBE YOU SHOULD
GET TWO PACKAGES.
- THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
THANKS, IT'S SETTLED.
I'M GOING TO BUY
TWO OF THESE PACKAGES.
- YOU'VE REALLY BEEN A BIG HELP.
- OH, NO PROBLEM.
- I'M SORRY I CAN'T
STAY AND TALK,
BUT THERE'S A TOILET PAPER
SALE AT THE DRUG STORE
AND I CAN'TMISS IT, YOU KNOW?
- OH, OF COURSE. I DON'T
WANT YOU TO MISS YOUR SALE.
I'M GLAD I COULD HELP.
- I GUESS I'LL SEE YOU
LATER THEN, RIN.
- I WONDER IF I GOT TOO MUCH?
WELL, AT LEAST KAEDE
WON'T HAVE TO GO SHOPPING
FOR A LITTLE WHILE. HUH?
♪ BECAUSE YOU'RE SO FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BUT I KNOW,
WE'LL BE TOGETHER SOON ♪
♪ SO I'M THINKING OF YOUR EYES ♪
♪ REMEMBERING YOUR
WARM EMBRACE ♪
♪ SUDDENLY BEFORE I KNOW IT,
THERE'S A SMILE ON MY FACE ♪
♪ AND WHEN ALL ♪
- OH, I, I'M SORRY,
I DIDN'T SCARE YOU DID I?
- UH, UH.
- YOU HAVEN'T BEEN
STANDING THERE
LISTENING TO ME SING THIS
WHOLE TIME, HAVE YOU?
- YEAH, I'M AFRAID SO.
YOU HAVE A BEAUTIFUL VOICE.
- OH, WELL I DON'T
KNOW ABOUT ALL THAT.
IT'S NICE OF YOU TO SAY,
BUT I KNOW LOTS OF PEOPLE
WHO SING MUCH BETTER THAN I CAN.
- OH, DON'T SAY THAT.
- ALTHOUGH I SUPPOSE
IF I AM BAD,
YOU COULD CALL THAT YOUR
PUNISHMENT FOR SPYING.
AH, SPEAKING OF PUNISHMENT,
IF I DON'T GET HOME PRETTY SOON,
I'M PROBABLY GONNA
BE IN TROUBLE
- WELL, I WOULDN'T WANT THAT.
SORRY IF I INTERRUPTED YOU.
- NOT AT ALL. I'M REALLY GLAD
WE HAD A CHANCE TO TALK.
- ME, TOO. I HOPE I GET
A CHANCE TO HEAR YOU SING AGAIN.
- WELL, WHO KNOWS.
IT'S A SMALL WORLD, RIN.
KEEP YOUR EARS OPEN,
AND YOU MIGHT HEAR MY VOICE
SOONER THAN YOU THINK YOU WILL.
- ( chuckles ) BYE THEN.
- A BEAUTIFUL GIRL
AND SHE SINGS, TOO.
I ACTUALLY MET TWO NEW GIRLS
FROM BOTH WORLDS TODAY.
HOW FUNNY.
- HUH? WAIT A SEC,
HOW'D THEY KNOW MY NAME?
WOW, THAT'S INTERESTING.
I WONDER IF I'VE MET THOSE
GIRLS SOMEWHERE BEFORE.
LET ME THINK, I DON'T REMEMBER
SEEING THEM AT SCHOOL.
- I GUESS I'LL SEE YOU
LATER THEN, RIN.
- IT'S A SMALL WORLD, RIN.
- KEEP YOUR EARS OPEN,
AND YOU MIGHT HEAR MY VOICE
SOONER THAN YOU THINK YOU WILL.
- OH, WELL, ANYWAY.
IF I DO KNOW THEM,
I'M SURE I'LL SEE THEM
AGAIN AT SOME POINT.
- YOU'RE CLUELESS. I GUESS,
KAEDE STILL DOESN'T
HAVE TO WORRY ABOUT
ROMANTIC RIVALS FOR A WHILE.
- NO WAY.
( chuckles )
- OKAY, TWO NEW PEOPLE
ARE GOING TO BE JOINING
OUR CLASS STARTING TODAY.
- GREAT, I GUESS I DON'T
REALLY NEED TO EXPLAIN.
- COME ON. WOULD YOU
GET A GRIP, PLEASE?
- NO, I CAN'T GET A GRIP.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
THE FIRST IMPRESSION
A GUY MAKES IS CRUCIAL.
- WHATEVER, BE A FREAK.
- HEY, YOU GUYS, ARE YOU READY?
- YEAH.
- BOYS WILL BE BOYS. YOU CAN
GO AHEAD AND COME IN NOW.
- ( cheering )
- ALL RIGHT NOW. HERE WE GO.
- NOW, THIS IS WHAT I CALL
A HAPPENING SCHOOL.
LOOKS LIKE IT MIGHT BE
A FUN PLACE AFTER ALL.
- WOW, I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT.
THERE'RE SO MANY PRETTY
YOUNG GIRLS AROUND,
I'M BEGINNING TO FEEL
LIKE A YOUNG STUD AGAIN.
- HEY LOOK, SOMETHING
IS WRONG WITH THESE GUYS.
- NO WAY.
- THOSE ARE THE PRETTY GIRLS
THAT ITSUKI SMELLED?
I THOUGHT HIS NOSE NEVER LIED.
- WELL, WHICH KID IS IT?
IS HE HERE RIGHT NOW?
- AH, LOOK, THERE HE IS.
- HMM, HE'S DEFINITELY NOT BAD
TO LOOK AT, IS HE?
HE'S GOING TO MAKE A VERY
FINE PROSPECT FOR MY SIA.
- HEY, NOT SO FAST THERE, SHIN.
RIN HERE HAPPENS TO BE
NERINE'S FIANCE, YOU REMEMBER?
- HEY, THAT'S NOT FAIR.
RIN, TAKE GOOD CARE OF
MY SIA FOR ME, OKAY?
- SURE.
- HEY. LISTEN UP,
PAL, GET WITH IT.
SIA'S GOT A CUTE BODY AND YOU
BETTER HAVE THE ENERGY...
- DAD, GROSS.
DON'T' SAY THINGS LIKE THAT.
- SIA, I'VE TOLD YOU BEFORE
THAT HITTING PEOPLE WITH CHAIRS
IS GOING A LITTLE TOO FAR.
- SIA, THAT WAS
A LITTLE BIT HARSH.
- WAIT, YOU TWO KNOW EACH OTHER?
- SO, LET'S LET THESE PEOPLE
INTRODUCE THEMSELVES.
- MY NAME'S LISIANTHUS. I COME
FROM THE WORLD OF THE GODS.
- MY NAME IS KIND OF LONG,
SO YOU CAN CALL ME SIA.
- UH, HI. MY NAME IS NERINE.
I COME FROM THE
REALM OF THE DEMONS.
I WOULD LOVE IT IF EVERYONE
WOULD JUST CALL ME RINA.
- MY NAME'S EUSTOMA.
I AM SIA'S FATHER, AND I'M
KING OF THE GODS AS WELL.
- AND MY NAME IS FORBESII.
I RULE AS KING OF THE DEMONS
AND I'M ALSO NERINE'S FATHER.
- I DIDN'T MEAN YOU PEOPLE.
- UH, UM, TEACHER?
DID I JUST HEAR THEM
SAY, THEY WERE, UM,
THE KING OF GODS AND DEMONS?
- YOU JUST HEARD RIGHT.
BEAR WITH ME HERE,
I KNOW IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE.
TRUST ME, I'VE HAD A HARD TIME
BELIEVING IT MYSELF.
BUT, THESE TWO MEN
REALLY ARE THE KINGS,
WHO RULE THE WORLDS
OF THE GODS AND THE DEMONS.
- UH, WE REALLY DON'T
WANT YOU TO WORRY
ABOUT THE FACT THAT
WE'RE PRINCESSES, OKAY?
- WE'RE SERIOUS, WE WANT
TO HAVE A NORMAL LIFE HERE,
SO TREAT US JUST LIKE
YOU TREAT EVERYONE ELSE.
- SO, THERE YOU HAVE IT.
TSUCHIMI, IT'S GONNA BE YOUR JOB
TO TAKE CARE OF THESE GIRLS.
- WHAT? WHY IS THAT UP TO ME?
WHAT THE?
- I'LL BE HAPPY TO EXPLAIN,
IF YOU'D LIKE.
YOU SEE, RIN, YOU'VE BEEN
CHOSEN AS A PRIME CANDIDATE
TO BE THE HUSBAND
OF EITHER NERINE OR SIA.
- HUH?
- ( all gasps )
- TO PUT IT PLAINLY,
YOU CAN CHOOSE TO BECOME KING OF
THE GODS OR KING OF THE DEMONS.
IF YOU PICK MY SIA,
YOU CAN USE THE POWER OF THE
GODS AS MUCH AS YOU WANT.
BUT CHOOSE NERINE,
AND ALL THE POWER OF THE
DEMONS WILL BE YOURS TO USE,
HOWEVER YOUR HEART DESIRES.
- ( giggles )
- ( laugh awkwardly )
- ALL OF A SUDDEN,
I COULD EITHER BECOME KING OF
THE GODS OR KING OF THE DEMONS.
UH, DO YOU GUYS
LIVE AROUND HERE, TOO?
- YOU BET. WE'RE
JUST ABOUT THERE.
- HMM.
- UH, WELL, THIS IS OUR HOUSE.
- OUR PLACE IS RIGHT OVER THERE.
- AH.
- AND OUR HOUSE
IS THAT BIG ONE THERE.
- HUH?
- I'M GLAD WE LIVE SO CLOSE.
- WE'LL HAVE LOTS OF FUN
BEING NEIGHBORS.
- UH, YEAH, SURE.
- IT'S A BIG PARTY.
I CAN'T WAIT.
- ( theme song playing )
- Nerine: SIA, LET'S ENJOY THE
HUMAN WORLD, AND GO OUT TO EAT.
- TEMPURA SUSHI.
- THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
- MOUNT FUJI.
- WELL, THAT'S...
- GEISHAS.
- THAT SOUNDS YUMMY.
- WHAT?
- NEXT TIME ON SHUFFLE,
EPISODE 2:
"I WANTED TO SEE YOU!"
- IS GEISHA REALLY A FOOD?
- MY FATHER SAID IT WAS.