- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( siren wailing )
- ( door opens )
- THANKS SO MUCH FOR YOUR HELP.
- HI, AMA.
- HELLO, RIN.
- IS SHE GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT?
- SHE'LL BE FINE.
- SHE JUST NEEDS TO REST FOR A
COUPLE OF DAYS, THAT'S ALL.
- SHE'LL BE AS GOOD AS NEW.
- THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR.
- SO. DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT HER.
- OKAY.
- UM, RIN, ARE YOU BUSY
RIGHT NOW?
COME WITH ME, LET'S HAVE A CHAT.
- ( crying )
- YOU OKAY?
- I'M SORRY. I'M SO SORRY.
- WHAT IS IT?
- RIMU, I HURT THEM.
LET GO. JUST DIE.
WHY? I DID IT AGAIN.
I HURT THEM.
I PROMISED MYSELF.
I PROMISED IT WOULD NEVER
HAPPEN AGAIN, AND IT DID.
I'M SORRY. I'M SO SORRY.
- WHAT DID YOU WANNA TALK ABOUT?
- TELL ME, YOUNG MAN,
DO YOU LOVE MY DAUGHTER? WELL?
- UH, THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION.
I DON'T REALLY HAVE
AN ANSWER YET.
- COME ON, YOU'RE A BOY, SHE'S
A GIRL. HOW HARD CAN IT BE?
- OW, OW, OW.
- SO, GOT AN ANSWER?
- NOT YET.
- ( sighs )
I GUESS IT'S ALL RIGHT. YOU'LL
FIGURE IT OUT SOONER OR LATER.
I JUST WANT ASA TO BE HAPPY.
EVEN THOUGH SOMETIMES I'M
NOT HER FAVORITE PERSON.
- HUH?
- I LOVE MY DAUGHTER,
AND SHE ALWAYS HAS A SMILE
FOR ME BUT I DO WONDER.
IS SHE STILL ANGRY WITH ME
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS? WELL.
- ( crying ) STOP IT. WHY DID
YOU GIVE ME A BODY LIKE THIS?
- ASA.
- WHY DOES IT
ALWAYS HURT SO MUCH?
I JUST WANT TO BE LIKE
EVERYONE ELSE.
- IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT
I'M SUFFERING.
YOU MADE ME THIS WAY.
I'M IN SO MUCH PAIN, I WISH
I'D NEVER EVEN BEEN BORN.
- I CAN'T BLAME HER FOR IT.
IT'S REALLY MY FAULT,
IT'S BECAUSE OF ME SHE HAS
TO FIGHT SO HARD RIGHT NOW.
- YOU MUST KNOW THAT'S NOT TRUE.
YOU'RE HER MOTHER
AND SHE WILL ALWAYS LOVE YOU.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT. NO MATTER
WHAT SHE THINKS OF ME,
I'LL NEVER STOP DOING EVERYTHING
I CAN TO KEEP HER HAPPY AND SAFE
AS LONG AS I'M ALIVE.
- IT, IT'S OKAY.
- I KNOW AND SHE'LL ALWAYS
HAVE YOU, WON'T SHE, RIN?
- ( phone ringing )
- Kaede: FUYOU RESIDENCE?
- OH, RIN.
- KAEDE?
I'M STILL AT THE HOSPITAL.
I'M GOING TO BE HOME LATE.
SO, GO AHEAD AND EAT
WITHOUT ME, ALL RIGHT?
- OF COURSE, I UNDERSTAND.
HOW'S ASA DOING?
I SEE. WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
TRY TO TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF,
TOO. GOODBYE.
- RIN?
- WELCOME BACK, ASA.
- GOOD MORNING.
- ARE YOU FEELING BETTER?
- WELL, MY HAND IS CERTAINLY
FEELING BETTER.
- OH, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- I COULD STAY
LIKE THIS FOREVER.
- YEAH, BUT THEN YOU'D
HAVE TO LIVE IN THE HOSPITAL.
- HAVEN'T YOU LEARNED
THAT SOMETIMES IT'S BETTER
JUST TO SHUT UP AND NOD?
RIN, DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT A WOMAN'S FEELINGS?
- FORGIVE ME, I'VE NEVER
BEEN A FAST LEARNER.
BESIDES, YOU'RE NOT
A TYPICAL GIRL.
- OH, HI.
- GO TO BED, KAEDE.
- WHY? I CAN'T SLEEP.
RIN WILL COME HOME
FROM THE HOSPITAL SOON.
I'M SURE HE'LL NEED ME.
- ( door opens )
- UH. YOU'RE BACK.
WELCOME HOME, RIN.
- GOOD TO SEE YOU.
- YOU TOO. IS ASA
FEELING BETTER?
- SHE'LL BE FINE.
THIS HAPPENS SOMETIMES.
SHE'S GOTTEN USED TO IT.
- WELL, THAT'S GOOD. UH, RIN.
- HMM?
- I'VE GOT YOUR BACKPACK
AND YOUR LUNCH READY FOR SCHOOL.
- OH, UH, SORRY,
I'M NOT GOING TODAY.
- HUH?
- I WAS UP REALLY LATE. I
THINK I'M JUST GONNA SLEEP.
- YOU MEAN YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO SCHOOL AT ALL?
- YEAH.
JUST GIVE MISS NA A REALLY GOOD
EXCUSE FOR ME, ALL RIGHT?
- ALL RIGHT.
- UH, RIN.
- HEY, KAEDE.
- I THOUGHT THAT YOU
WERE GOING TO SCHOOL.
- OH, WELL, I DID GO. BUT, BUT
I FORGOT SOMETHING AT HOME.
- OH, ALL RIGHT.
WELL, SEE YOU LATER.
- ARE YOU GOING TO
THE HOSPITAL AGAIN?
- HUH? YEAH.
- DO YOU HAVE TO?
- HUH?
- I MEAN, IS IT REALLY
NECESSARY FOR YOU
TO BE THERE EVERY SECOND?
- HEY, WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
- WHY DO YOU HAVE TO GO? WHY?
TO TAKE CARE OF HER?
YOU'RE NOT A DOCTOR.
I THINK SHE'LL BE
ALL RIGHT WITHOUT YOU.
- WHAT'S BOTHERING YOU, KAEDE?
WHAT IS IT?
- I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU HAVE TO GO.
- YOU'VE BEEN ACTING
REALLY STRANGE LATELY.
IT'S LIKE I DON'T EVEN KNOW YOU.
- ( gasps ) I'M SORRY.
- ( crying )
- Ama: LUNCH IS SERVED. I HOPE
YOU BROUGHT YOUR APPETITES.
- WOW, AMAZING.
- THANKS A LOT, MOM.
- BUT ARE YOU SURE IT'S OKAY
TO EAT IT?
- HMM? SURE, WHY NOT?
- BECAUSE AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED
TO EAT HOSPITAL FOOD
WHEN YOU'RE IN THE HOSPITAL?
- HOW IS SHE SUPPOSED TO
GET HER STRENGTH BACK
EATING THAT STUFF?
- ( both laugh )
- ( sighs )
- BESIDES, I'M GETTING
OUT OF HERE TOMORROW.
- YOU SURE IT'S OKAY TO LEAVE?
- YEAH, THE DOCTOR SAID SHE
WAS DOING BETTER.
- JUST ONE MORE DAY
OF TAKING IT EASY
AND I'LL BE BACK TO MY OLD SELF.
BESIDES, IF I STAY
IN THE HOSPITAL ANY LONGER,
I HAVE A FEELING
SOMEONE WILL USE IT
AS AN EXCUSE TO SKIP SCHOOL.
YOUR GRADES ARE BAD
ENOUGH WITHOUT MISSING
EVEN MORE CLASSES.
IF YOU GET HELD BACK,
IT'S GOING TO PUT
ANOTHER YEAR BETWEEN US.
- YOU SAY THAT, BUT WHETHER
I PASS OR NOT,
YOU'RE STILL GOING
OFF TO COLLEGE SOON.
- ( sighs ) I DON'T WANT
TO THINK ABOUT IT NOW.
- ISN'T THERE A COLLEGE
YOU'RE INTERESTED IN?
- OH, THANK YOU.
- I'M REALLY JUST GOING TO GO
ANYWHERE THAT'LL TAKE ME.
- WELL, IF YOU DON'T CARE
WHERE YOU GO,
THEN WOULDN'T YOU LIKE
TO GO TO THE SAME SCHOOL AS ME?
- HUH?
- WELL, IT WOULD BE FUN.
- LIKE HIGH SCHOOL,
BUT WITHOUT ALL THE RULES.
- I THINK WE'D HAVE A GREAT TIME
TOGETHER. BUT WITH YOUR GRADES,
THERE'S NO WAY YOU'LL
GET INTO THE UNIVERSITY
THAT I'VE GOT MY EYE ON.
- ( chuckles )
- YEAH, YEAH.
I THINK I CAN TAKE A HINT.
- WELL, I GUESS
I'D BETTER START STUDYING.
- OH, SILLY.
I DON'T THINK SHE MEANT YOU
HAD TO LEAVE RIGHT NOW.
- I THINK HE CAN STAY FOR A BIT.
ONE DAY IS NOT GONNA MAKE
HIM ANY SMARTER,
AND I'M ENJOYING HIS COMPANY.
TOMORROW THEN.
WE CAN STUDY TOGETHER, AND
I WON'T GO EASY ON YOU.
BUT AS FOR RIGHT NOW,
SAY "AH".
- AH.
- NOW CHEW. THAT'S A GOOD BOY.
- IT WAS NICE. BACK WHEN
THERE WAS ONLY RIN AND I.
- YOU KNOW, THIS IS KINDA NICE.
MAYBE I COULD GET USED TO IT.
- WHAT?
- JUST SITTING HERE, DOING
NOTHING, RELAXING.
- IT'S NOT REALLY A BAD WAY
TO PASS THE TIME, IS IT?
- DON'T YOU THINK
YOU'D GET BORED?
- NO, WAY. DON'T GET ME WRONG,
MOST OF THE TIME I LIKE TO KEEP
BUSY, I LIKE BEING ACTIVE.
I LIKE TO HAVE FUN.
BUT SOMETIMES IT FEELS GOOD
TO SLOW DOWN, YOU KNOW?
JUST STAND STILL AND BREATHE
WHILE THE WORLD KEEPS MOVING.
SOMETIMES DOING THAT CAN MAKE
YOU FEEL EVEN MORE ALIVE, RIGHT?
- WELL, YEAH, IT CAN. I GUESS.
- IT'S JUST WHEN I WAS A KID,
I WAS SO SICK THAT I WAS IN THE
HOSPITAL AS OFTEN AS AT HOME.
I GOT USED TO DOING NOTHING.
AND I HATED IT.
IT ALWAYS FELT LIKE I WAS JUST
WASTING AWAY MY LIFE.
- I'M SORRY, ASA.
- SO, WHENEVER I WAS FEELING
WELL, I WANTED TO DO SOMETHING.
- ANYTHING, JUST TO FEEL ALIVE.
THAT'S WHEN I STARTED LEARNING
HOW TO COOK SO MANY THINGS.
BUT NOW, I'M STARTING TO THINK
THAT LIVING FRANTICALLY
ISN'T THE ONLY WAY TO DO IT.
SITTING HERE LIKE THIS AND JUST
TAKING IT EASY WITH YOU
FOR A WHILE, IT'S REALLY
KIND OF NICE.
- YEAH, IT IS.
- I'LL HAVE TO THINK
OF SOME WAY TO THANK YOU.
LET'S SEE.
( chuckles )
- I'LL COME BACK SOON.
- OKAY. SOUNDS GOOD.
- THANKS FOR STOPPING BY, RIN.
- OF COURSE.
- TAKE CARE, RIN.
- ( crying )
- I'M HOME.
- I'M GLAD THAT YOU'RE
BACK. COME ON IN.
- I DON'T KNOW IF YOU'RE
HUNGRY YET,
BUT DINNER'S READY
WHENEVER YOU ARE.
- I'M FINE. I HAD A REALLY
BIG LUNCH,
BUT PLEASE GO AHEAD AND
EAT WITHOUT ME.
- OH, THAT'S OKAY.
THEN I'LL GO AND GET
A NICE BATH READY.
- ACTUALLY, I'M GONNA GO
LAY DOWN.
I REALLY HAVEN'T GOTTEN MUCH
SLEEP LATELY.
- HEY, SIA AND RINA BOTH
BROUGHT COPIES OF THEIR NOTES
FROM SCHOOL
FOR YOU EARLIER.
THEY'RE ALL ON YOUR DESK IF YOU
WANT TO TAKE A LOOK AT THEM.
- COOL. THANK YOU.
- ( knocks on door )
- YES?
- GOT A SEC?
- WHAT IS IT?
- UM, I JUST, I WAS WONDERING.
IS ASA FEELING BETTER NOW?
- YEAH, SHE'S DOING FINE. SHE'LL
BE OUT OF THE HOSPITAL TOMORROW.
- GOOD FOR HER.
- YOU KNOW, IT'S INTERESTING.
ASA SAYS THAT SHE AND HER MOTHER
DIDN'T USED TO GET
ALONG VERY WELL.
BUT NOW THEY SEEM SO HAPPY
AROUND EACH OTHER.
- ISN'T THAT NICE.
- YEAH, IT IS. BUT I THINK
THEY'RE BOTH STILL HURTING.
ASA FEELS BAD FOR BEING
MEAN TO THE PERSON
SHE LOVES MOST IN THE WORLD,
AND AMA STILL WORRIES
THAT HER DAUGHTER IS ANGRY.
- I'M SURE THEY'RE FINE.
- MAYBE THEY ARE.
I THINK THEY'D BE HAPPIER
IF THEY SAT DOWN, TALKED,
AND JUST CLEARED IT ALL UP.
- SOMETIMES THERE ARE THINGS
YOU JUST CAN'T TALK ABOUT.
SO, YOU KEEP THE PAIN QUIET.
- HMM?
- BUT THEN THERE'S YOU,
YOU'RE ALWAYS SO CONCERNED
FOR EVERYONE ELSE'S SUFFERING.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- SO, MAYBE IT IS BETTER
TO TALK ABOUT THE PAIN.
MAYBE THEN YOU'D LISTEN.
- KAEDE, WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
- NOTHING, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- ( gasps )
- ( moans )
- ( door opens )
- RIN.
- HEY, KAEDE.
- WHAT THE HECK DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
- PLEASE, RIN.
PLEASE DON'T GO ANYWHERE.
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- I JUST WANNA TAKE CARE OF YOU.
THAT'S ALL I WANT.
- PLEASE DON'T LEAVE, RIN.
PLEASE JUST STAY HERE WITH
ME IN THIS HOUSE FOREVER.
- YOU SEE, I WILL
GIVE YOU EVERYTHING.
- JUST STOP IT.
- DON'T GO. NO, STAY. I TAKE
IT BACK. I TAKE IT ALL BACK.
- THAT WAS CRAZY. I'M SORRY,
I DIDN'T MEAN IT THAT WAY.
JUST COME BACK. PLEASE, RIN.
- ( crying ) NO,
WHAT DID I DO? RIN.
- ( panting )
- Kaede: OH, NO. NOT AT ALL.
I REALLY LOVE TAKING
CARE OF YOU, RIN.
IT'S WHAT I ENJOY
DOING THE MOST.
- YOU'RE KIDDING,
YOU DON'T EVEN CARE?
YOU'RE JUST GOING TO LEAD ALL
THREE OF THEM ALONG,
UNTIL YOU BREAK THEIR POOR,
LITTLE HEARTS?
- BUT, IN THE END, ALL THAT
MATTERS IS WHAT YOU WANNA DO.
BE HONEST WITH ME, RIN. WERE
YOU FORCED TO GO ON THIS DATE?
- ( grunts )
I'M AN IDIOT. WHAT THE HELL
HAVE I BEEN DOING ALL THIS TIME?
I FAILED THEM. KAEDE?
I WAS SUPPOSED TO PROTECT HER.
AND WHAT ABOUT ASA?
I WANTED TO HELP HER, AND
SHE ENDED UP HURT AGAIN.
- ( whimpers )
- LIKE SIA AND NERINE
AND PRIMULA.
I THOUGHT THAT SOMEHOW
I COULD MAKE ALL OF THEM HAPPY.
OF COURSE I COULDN'T. WHAT
WAS I THINKING? WHAT AN IDIOT.
HOW DID I NOT NOTICE ANY OF IT?
I WAS COMPLETELY BLIND TO
EVERYTHING. DAMMIT, DAMMIT.
DAMN! DAMN, DAMN, DAMN.
- ( crying )
- WHERE DID I MESS UP? WHEN DID
ALL THIS START FALLING APART?
WHAT DID I DO?
WHAT DID I DO WRONG?
MAYBE RIN NEVER
FORGAVE ME AFTER ALL.
MAYBE HE'S REALLY HATED ME
THIS WHOLE TIME.
BUT AFTER ALL THOSE
HORRIBLE THINGS I SAID,
I REALLY CAN'T BLAME HIM, CAN I?
WHAT AM I GONNA DO
IF HE GOES AWAY?
HOW CAN I KEEP LIVING
IN THIS HOUSE WITHOUT HIM?
I WANTED TO SHOW HIM
HOW SORRY I AM.
THAT'S IT, THAT'S ALL IT WAS.
I JUST WANTED TO TAKE CARE
OF HIM TO MAKE UP FOR THE PAST.
- ARE YOU SURE? WAS IT
ALL FOR RIN? JUST FOR HIM?
- NO, YOU'RE RIGHT.
IT WAS FOR ME.
I JUST WANTED TO BE WITH HIM.
THAT'S WHAT I REALLY WANTED.
- TELL HIM, WHY DON'T
YOU TELL RIN THAT?
TELL HIM THAT YOU WANT
TO BE WITH HIM.
- I HAVE NO RIGHT TO TELL HIM
THAT. NOT AFTER WHAT I'VE DONE.
- BUT WHY NOT?
- BECAUSE HE WILL
NEVER LOVE ME BACK.
I HAVE NO RIGHT TO TELL
RIN HOW I FEEL,
BECAUSE I DON'T DESERVE
TO BE LOVED BY HIM.
- SO, THAT'S IT?
YOU'LL LET HIM GO?
- WHAT ABOUT ME?
I WANT HIM TO STAY, TOO.
- HE'LL BE BACK.
- OF COURSE.
COME TO THINK OF IT.
THIS RAIN IS VERY FAMILIAR.
WOW, THAT WAS SO LONG AGO.
- ( breathing heavily )
- THERE.
- ( door opens )
- I'LL JUST DO WHAT I'VE ALWAYS
DONE, LIKE NOTHING HAS CHANGED.
AND I'LL KEEP DOING IT FOREVER.
I'M FINE WITH THE WAY THINGS ARE
NOW. REALLY, I CAN HANDLE IT.
BECAUSE WHAT I WANT
IS FOR RIN TO BE HAPPY.
SO I CAN ACCEPT
WHATEVER HE WANTS TO DO.
AS LONG AS HE JUST STAYS
HERE WITH RIMU AND ME,
IT WILL BE FINE. I DON'T MIND
IF HE LOVES ASA.
HE CAN DATE WHOEVER
HE WANTS TO. I'LL BE FINE.
IF HE'LL ONLY STAY HERE.
- HI.
- I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE BACK.
I WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
- YOU'LL CATCH COLD
JUST STANDING THERE.
I'LL START RUNNING YOU
A NICE BATH.
- KAEDE, WAIT.
- OH, YEAH?
- I'VE, I'VE BEEN THINKING.
- WHAT HAVE YOU BEEN
THINKING ABOUT, RIN?
- WELL, I... I THINK IT'S TIME
FOR ME TO LEAVE THIS HOUSE.
- ( gasps )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )