- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( thunder rumbles )
- Kaede: I WISH YOU WERE DEAD.
I MEAN IT.
JUST DIE!
- OH, NO.
- HI, THERE! THERE'S SOME
FOOD FOR YOU ON THE TABLE.
- THANK YOU.
IT'S WEIRD YOU DIDN'T
WAKE ME UP THIS MORNING.
- IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S A
SCHOOL DAY OR ANYTHING.
I JUST THOUGHT I'D
LET YOU SLEEP IN.
NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
YOUR FOOD'S PROBABLY
GOTTEN PRETTY COLD.
- HEY, DON'T BOTHER.
I'M GOING TO HEAD OUT IN A SEC
AND MEET UP WITH ASA, ANYWAY.
- YOU'RE NOT HUNGRY?
- SORRY, WE'LL GET FOOD. BYE!
- SEE YOU LATER.
I GUESS WHILE HE'S OUT
WE SHOULD TRY TO FINISH
WITH THE DISHES AND GET
SOME OTHER CLEANING DONE.
YOU'LL HELP, RIGHT?
I'M SURE WE CAN KEEP BUSY.
- Woman: I HEARD SHE WAS ON
HER WAY BACK FROM A TRIP
WHEN SHE WAS IN THE ACCIDENT.
- Man: SHE'D GONE WITH
MR. AND MRS. TSUCHIMI.
- Woman: AND NOW, HE'S GOING
TO HAVE TO RAISE HIS DAUGHTER
ALL BY HIMSELF.
THAT'S ROUGH.
- NOT JUST HER.
HE'S GOING TO BE TAKING IN THE
TSUCHIMIS' ONLY CHILD, TOO.
- Woman: OH, WOW.
- RIN, WOULD YOU MIND
IF I ASKED YOU TO HELP
TAKE CARE OF KAEDE
WHILE I'M GONE?
- I'LL BE FINE! PROMISE! RIGHT?
- YEAH!
- Man: KAEDE? KAEDE!
- WHAT'S WRONG?
WAKE UP! WAKE UP!
- Doctor: YOUR DAUGHTER
WAS ADMITTED TO THE HOSPITAL
OVER TWO WEEKS AGO.
THE LOSS OF HER MOTHER WAS
OBVIOUSLY A TREMENDOUS SHOCK.
AS FOR HER CONDITION,
IT'S ALMOST AS THOUGH SHE'S
LOST THE WILL TO LIVE.
- DOCTOR.
- SHE NEEDS YOU TO GIVE HER
A REASON TO SNAP OUT OF THIS.
ANYTHING THAT MAKES
HER WANT TO LIVE AGAIN.
ANYTHING.
- HEY, KAEDE?
YOU CAN HEAR ME, CAN'T YOU?
I WANT YOU TO LISTEN.
IT'S ABOUT YOUR MOM.
IT'S JUST...
THERE'S SOMETHING I NEED TO TELL
YOU, BUT I'VE BEEN AFRAID TO.
I'M SORRY.
YOUR MOM DIED BECAUSE OF ME.
I GUESS I'M JUST SELFISH.
IT WAS REALLY
LONELY BEING AT HOME
WITHOUT MY MOM AND DAD AROUND.
SO, I ASKED THEM IF THERE
WAS ANY WAY THEY COULD
COME HOME EARLIER THAN
THEY WERE SUPPOSED TO.
AND THEN, THEY GOT IN THAT
ACCIDENT ON THE WAY BACK.
THAT'S WHY.
KAEDE?
- Kaede: REALLY?
- WHAT?
- THAT'S...
THE TRUTH?
- YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
- DAD, WHAT'S GOING ON?
- OH, MY LITTLE GIRL!
I'M SO HAPPY!
I HAVE MY LITTLE GIRL BACK!
OH, MY BABY GIRL!
EVERYTHING IS OKAY!
DADDY'S HERE.
( crying )
- STARTING TODAY, THIS ROOM
IS GOING TO BE YOURS.
ALL OF YOUR THINGS HAVE
ALREADY BEEN MOVED IN THERE.
GET YOURSELF SETTLED
AND THEN COME DOWN
FOR DINNER WITH KAEDE
WHEN YOU'RE READY.
- OKAY.
- Both: WE'RE LEAVING NOW!
- SEE YA LATER.
YOU TWO BE CAREFUL, OKAY?
- HEY, KAEDE! GOOD MORNING!
- GOOD MORNING!
HEY, DID YOU FINISH
ALL OF YOUR HOMEWORK?
- I ALWAYS DO!
- I'VE BEEN MEANING TO ASK.
HOW'S IT BEEN LIVING WITH US?
HAVE YOU GOTTEN
USED TO IT YET?
- YEAH.
- THAT'S GOOD.
AND WHAT ABOUT YOU, DEAR?
- ARE YOU HAPPY THAT RIN WILL BE
STAYING WITH US FROM NOW ON?
- MMM-HMM.
- ( laughing ) I'M GLAD.
- SO I WAS BUSY PRACTICING
ALL DAY YESTERDAY.
I THINK I'M GETTING
A LOT BETTER!
YOU SHOULD REALLY SPEND
MORE TIME WORKING ON IT.
IF YOU WANT, I CAN COME OVER
TO YOUR HOUSE AND HELP YOU.
I DROPPED IT.
PICK IT UP.
- ( gasping )
- ( bell rings )
- Kaede: I WISH YOU WERE DEAD.
TELL ME.
WHY DO YOU THINK MY
MOTHER HAD TO DIE?
BUT YOU STILL GET TO LIVE?
I DON'T THINK THAT'S FAIR.
I WISH YOU WERE DEAD.
I MEAN IT.
JUST DIE!
WHAT?
IT'S MY MOM?
IT'S ADDRESSED TO ME!
THE DATE IS,
THE SAME DAY SHE DIED!
"KAEDE, PLEASE TAKE CARE
AND GET BETTER SOON.
"I'D LIKE IT IF YOU COULD
COME WITH ME NEXT TIME."
I WAS SICK?
"TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
AND GET BETTER?"
- IT'S ME.
SHE'S BEEN GETTING WORSE.
YEAH. COUGHING AND A FEVER.
I FEEL BAD ASKING YOU
TO COME BACK EARLY.
- I WANT MOM TO COME HOME.
- DON'T WORRY. SHE'LL BE
BACK VERY SOON, SWEETHEART.
- ( coughing )
- YOU'RE REALLY WELL
ENOUGH FOR ME TO GO?
I'M STARTING TO
FEEL A BIT GUILTY.
RIN, WOULD YOU MIND
IF I ASKED YOU TO HELP
TAKE CARE OF KAEDE
WHILE I'M GONE?
- OH, I'LL BE FINE!
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME!
- DON'T READ THAT!
- YOU LIED TO ME THAT NIGHT.
HOW COME?
WAS IT MY FAULT?
- DON'T SAY THAT.
- THEN I'M THE ONE.
- I KILLED HER.
- NO YOU DIDN'T!
- I'M THE ONE.
IT WAS MY FAULT.
SHE DIED TRYING TO GET BACK.
( crying ) SHE'S DEAD
BECAUSE OF ME.
- Rin: KAEDE!
KAEDE!
- ( car honking )
- YOU OKAY?
- ( Kaede sobs )
- KAEDE?
- I'M SO SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY.
I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY!
I'M SORRY! I'M SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY!
I'M SO SORRY, RIN.
RIN HAS BEEN SO GOOD TO ME.
I REALLY DO OWE HIM.
THAT'S WHY, I'LL MAKE HIM
HAPPY ANY WAY I CAN.
I OWE HIM THAT MUCH.
- YOU GUYS SHOULD
TOTALLY DO IT!
GET THE "LOVEY DOVEY
TROPICAL JUICE" SPECIAL.
DRINKING IT TOGETHER WOULD
BE ALMOST LIKE KISSING!
- NO, THANKS.
- I THINK I'LL JUST
HAVE A MILKSHAKE.
- YOU TWO ARE NO FUN AT ALL.
FINE. I'LL GO GET YOUR ORDER.
- IS IT REALLY A GOOD
IDEA TO COME HERE
WHILE KAREHA'S WORKING?
I KNOW YOU'RE FRIENDS,
BUT YOU DON'T THINK SHE'LL
SPREAD RUMORS ABOUT US
AT SCHOOL, RIGHT?
- WELL, IT WOULDN'T
BOTHER ME. YOU?
( giggling )
( gasps )
- BESIDES, I'VE HAD A
CHANCE TO THINK ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENED THE
OTHER DAY, AND...
YOU OKAY?
EARTH TO ASA!
NOT LISTENING?
- THAT'S RIGHT. NOT A WORD.
- AM I THAT BORING?
- SORRY. I NEED TO MAKE A
QUICK RUN TO THE LADIES' ROOM.
( gasps )
- ASA!
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- MY GOODNESS!
- PLEASE SAY SOMETHING!
- OH, ASA!
- RIN...
SCOOP ME UP AND CARRY
ME LIKE A PRINCESS.
- THAT WAS SCARY.
- I GOT DIZZY WHEN I STOOD UP.
PROBABLY BECAUSE I
PULLED AN ALL-NIGHTER.
- ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY?
LET'S GET UP.
- I DON'T WANT TO.
I'M WAY TOO COMFORTABLE WITH YOU
HOLDING ME LIKE THIS TO GET UP.
- ASA...
- ( door opening )
- YOU'RE BACK ALREADY?
THAT DIDN'T TAKE VERY LONG.
- ASA WASN'T FEELING WELL,
SO I ENDED UP WALKING HER HOME.
- SHE GOT SICK AGAIN?
- SHE SAID SHE HADN'T
GOTTEN ANY SLEEP.
I HOPE SHE'S OKAY.
- ARE YOU HUNGRY? IT DOESN'T
SOUND LIKE YOU GOT TO EAT.
- NOPE.
THINGS WERE SO CRAZY THAT
I TOTALLY FORGOT ABOUT FOOD.
- I'LL WHIP UP
SOMETHING QUICK.
YOU GUYS GO HANG OUT
AND HAVE SOME FUN.
- HEY, YOU! WHAT'S GOING ON?
- WELL, UM, IT'S JUST...
- I KNOW! LET'S GO AND
PLAY A VIDEO GAME TOGETHER.
I'M GOING TO CHANGE FIRST.
IT'LL JUST TAKE A MINUTE.
- Primula: OKAY.
- ( breathing heavily )
- ( knock on door )
- Ama: CAN I COME IN?
- YEAH, MOM!
- YOU DOING ANY BETTER?
I BROUGHT YOU SOME
MORE MEDICINE.
- THANKS A LOT. YOU CAN PUT
IT DOWN RIGHT OVER THERE.
- DON'T PUSH TOO HARD.
DATING RIN'S FUN,
BUT HE'LL BE TURNED OFF IF HE
ALWAYS HAS TO CARRY YOU HOME.
- MOM! THAT WAS MEAN.
- HEY, WE'RE BOTH A
COUPLE OF TROUBLEMAKERS.
NOW YOU REST AND I'LL
WAKE YOU FOR DINNER. OKAY?
- I'LL TRY.
- YOUR COFFEE'S GOTTEN COLD.
CAN I DUMP IT?
- MMM-HMM.
- DO YOU HAVE ANY SOLID
PLANS TOMORROW,
OR ARE YOU FREE
TO DO SOMETHING?
- HMM.
- I WAS THINKING THAT WE
COULD TAKE RIMU SHOPPING
FOR SOME NEW OUTFITS.
- YOU PROBABLY NEED SOME,
TOO, DON'T YOU?
- HMM.
- AND WHEN WE'RE DONE WE COULD
GO OUT TO DINNER SOMEPLACE.
I CAN'T EVEN REMEMBER THE
LAST TIME WE DID THAT.
- ( phone rings )
- IT'S OKAY. I GOT IT!
- Rin: ASA?
- RIN!
YOU WERE WAITING
FOR ME TO CALL!
I'M TOTALLY FINE NOW.
SORRY ABOUT THAT!
YEAH. LISTEN,
IT'S NOT REALLY TO
MAKE UP FOR EARLIER, BUT,
HOW ABOUT WE TRY THAT
DATING THING AGAIN?
- YES! GREAT!
THAT SOUNDS AWESOME. AND,
IT'LL BE YOUR TREAT THIS TIME!
MONEY'S NO OBJECT, RIGHT?
( laughing ) OKAY, OKAY!
YOU'RE ON! SEE YA TOMORROW!
- WAS THAT ASA ON THE PHONE?
- MMM-HMM. WE'RE GOING TO SEE
A MOVIE TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
- OH, WHAT ABOUT ALL
OF US GOING SHOPPING?
- GOING SHOPPING?
- NEVER MIND.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- DON'T WORRY.
IT'S NOT THAT IMPORTANT.
- Rin: OKAY.
- AFTER YOU GUYS GO TO
THE MOVIE, YOU'LL HEAD HOME?
- MMM, I HAVE NO IDEA.
- I'LL HAVE YOUR DINNER
ALL READY AND WAITING
FOR YOU WHEN YOU COME BACK.
- NAH, GO AHEAD
AND EAT WITHOUT ME.
- ALL RIGHT, THEN.
- Rin: SEE YOU LATER!
I'M OUT OF HERE!
- UM, ARE WE STILL
GOING TO GO SHOPPING?
- FORGET IT, RIMU.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
- WHERE'S RIN?
IT'S DARK OUTSIDE.
- IT MUST MEAN HE'S
STILL OUT HAVING FUN.
HE WAS PRETTY JAZZED ABOUT
GOING OUT WITH ASA TODAY,
- DON'T YOU THINK?
- I GUESS SO.
- I DON'T THINK I'VE
EVER SEEN HIM LOOK
REALLY HAPPY LIKE THAT BEFORE.
- NOT EVEN ONCE.
- Primula: OH?
ARE YOU OKAY WITH THIS
AS LONG AS RIN'S HAPPY?
WILL YOU BE ALL RIGHT
WITH HIM SEEING HER?
CAN YOU STILL BE HAPPY?
- Kaede: OF COURSE I CAN.
CARING FOR RIN
IS MY WHOLE LIFE.
HE'S THAT IMPORTANT TO ME.
HIS HAPPINESS IS
ALL THAT MATTERS.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- ( phone rings )
- HI, THERE.
IS THAT YOU, RIN?
- IT'S ME. ASA'S MOM
INVITED ME TO STAY HERE
AND HAVE DINNER WITH
THEM TONIGHT, SO,
I DON'T REALLY NEED YOU
TO MAKE ANYTHING FOR ME.
IF I ATE ALL THAT, I'D EXPLODE!
- Ama: A BOY YOUR AGE SHOULD
BE ABLE TO EAT TWICE THIS MUCH!
I EXPECT YOU TO
CLEAN YOUR PLATE!
- Asa: SHE'LL MAKE
YOU DO IT, TOO.
YOU'RE NOT DONE UNTIL
SHE DECIDES YOU'RE FINISHED!
- ANYWAY, THAT'S THE DEAL. I'LL
BE BACK LATE. DON'T WAIT UP.
- SO THAT'S IT, THEN.
- ( Kaede sobs )
- KAEDE?
KAEDE? IT'S ME.
SORRY I UPSET YOU YESTERDAY.
HELLO?
KAEDE?
WHERE ARE YOU?
- ( doorbell rings )
- ( gasps )
OH, KAEDE, NO!
KAEDE!
- HI YA!
IT'S GOOD TO BE BACK!
- YEAH. IT'S LIKE A MILLION
YEARS SINCE YOU BEEN HERE.
COME ON IN!
- EVERYTHING IS EXACTLY
THE SAME AS I REMEMBER IT!
- GET OUT!
GET OUT OF THIS HOUSE!
GET OUT OF THIS HOUSE.
GET OUT. GET OUT.
GET OUT. GET OUT!
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- OUT!
GET OUT OF MY HOUSE! GO AWAY!
- STOP IT!
- GIVE HIM BACK.
HE'S MINE.
- WHAT?
- BACK OFF!
- NO!
LET GO OF ME!
- QUIT IT!
- WHY ARE YOU
FREAKING OUT? DAMN!
- CUT IT OUT!
- LET GO!
- ( panting )
- JUST DIE!
- THAT'S ENOUGH!
WHY WOULD YOU
SAY THAT TO HER?
- Kaede: OH, RIN. I...
- SHE FAINTED!
ASA!
ASA, WAKE UP!
COME ON, NOW.
PLEASE!
SPEAK TO ME! PLEASE!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Kaede: THERE'S NO WAY
THAT I'LL EVER BE FORGIVEN.
I'M STILL GOING TO TAKE CARE OF
RIN, NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS.
BECAUSE IT'S ALL I
HAVE LEFT.
AND IT'S THE ONLY
THING I CAN DO.
- Primula: WE'LL SEE YOU
HERE NEXT TIME ON SHUFFLE!
EPISODE 20, "INDELIBLE SIN."
- Kaede: RIN, DON'T GO!
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME!