- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( laughter )
- Eustoma: GIVE IT UP, MABOU!
- ( laughter continues )
- Eustoma: I'M GAINING
ON YOU, BUDDY!
- AT THAT PACE
YOU'LL NEVER GET ME!
CATCH ME IF YOU CAN.
MISSED ME AGAIN!
- OKAY. IF THAT'S WHAT
THEY WANT TO DO HERE.
- NEXT!
- Kaede: THERE YOU ARE!
I'M SORRY FOR MAKING YOU WAIT!
THERE WASN'T ANYTHING
WE COULD DO ABOUT IT.
THE CHANGING ROOM WAS FULL,
WE WERE HAVING TROUBLE
MOVING AROUND IN THERE.
- WHOA!
- ( exclaims )
- LOOKS LIKE YOU GUYS DID
A GOOD JOB OF FINDING A SPOT.
- YES, IT'S PERFECT!
BUT I'M SORRY I WASN'T
HERE IN TIME TO HELP
YOU BOYS SET THINGS UP.
- IT WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN
CHIVALROUS OF THEM
IF THEY'D MADE YOU HELP.
BESIDES, ISN'T THIS,
"A MAN'S JOB?"
- ( all groaning )
- WHAT? WHY'D YOU CREEPS
SUDDENLY HAVE TO BE SO
LET DOWN WHEN
I WALKED OUT HERE!
- Sia: I'M BACK! RIN, I'M
WEARING MY NEW BATHING SUIT!
CHECK ME OUT!
( giggles )
- WOW. SIA, IT LOOKS
AMAZING ON YOU!
IT'S GREAT.
- THANK YOU! I WAS REALLY HOPING
THAT YOU'D LIKE THIS ONE ON ME!
I HAD TROUBLE CHOOSING.
- THAT GIRL'S ON FIRE!
- YOU KNOW, I'M GETTING
SOME INTERESTING VIBES
OFF OF THOSE TWO.
- BUT HE'S NICE TO EVERYONE.
- WELL, I MEAN, HOW CAN
HE NOT DROOL AT THE SIGHT
OF THESE BEAUTIFUL WOMEN
RIGHT IN FRONT OF HIM?
IT'S INSULTING FOR HIM NOT
TO COMPLIMENT ALL OF US.
AM I RIGHT, KAEDE?
- WHAT? WELL,
IT'S JUST THAT...
- ACTUALLY, IT SEEMS THE
BIGGER PROBLEM'S RIGHT THERE.
- IT'S ME?
- LOOK, I DON'T WANT TO MAKE YOU
FEEL WEIRD ABOUT OR ANYTHING,
BUT YOUR BATHING SUIT...
- IT LOOKS PRETTY SWEET,
DOESN'T IT?
MY INSTINCTS WERE
DEAD-ON, AS USUAL.
- PLEASE! SCHOOL SWIMSUITS
ARE A FETISH FOR PERVERTS!
- NERINE'S STILL CHANGING?
- Girls: SHE SHOULD
BE DONE BY NOW.
- Nerine: HEY, I'M RIGHT HERE!
- COOL, NOW EVERYONE'S HERE.
- SORRY! I HOPE YOU WEREN'T
WAITING TOO LONG! HI, RIN!
( giggling )
- UM, NERINE, THAT'S AN
INTERESTING CHOICE.
I'M SURPRISED YOU DECIDED TO
WEAR YOUR SCHOOL SWIMSUIT.
- OH, UM, I THOUGHT YOU
MIGHT LIKE SEEING ME
IN SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
I KNOW IT SEEMS WEIRD, BUT
MY DAD TOLD ME I SHOULD
WEAR IT IF I WAS GOING TO THE
BEACH IN THE HUMAN WORLD.
HE SAID HE WAS SURE YOU'D
REALLY WANT TO SEE ME IN IT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
DOES IT LOOK FUNNY?
- OF COURSE IT
DOESN'T LOOK FUNNY!
I LIKE IT,
IT'S JUST A LITTLE BIT...
- Itsuki: SO NERINE'S DAD
THOUGHT THAT US
GOING TO THE BEACH
WOULD BE THE PERFECT CHANCE
FOR HIS DAUGHTER TO YANK BACK
THE LEAD THAT SIA'S GAINED.
MAN, IT LOOKS LIKE
THE KING OF DEVIL'S
REALLY UNDERSTANDS
THIS FETISH, TOO.
- Rin: YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I BET YOU, HE KNOWS EXACTLY
WHAT HE'S DOING.
- SERIOUSLY, WHY DO MEN HAVE
TO BE SUCH BONEHEADS, ANYWAY?
THERE ARE LOTS MORE IMPORTANT
THINGS TO LIKE ABOUT A GIRL
THAN HOW SHE LOOKS
IN HER BATHING SUIT!
- Itsuki: I HEAR WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING, AND YOU MIGHT BE RIGHT.
THE PROBLEM IS, IS THAT
YOU'RE REALLY NOT QUALIFIED
TO TALK ABOUT IT YET.
SO WE'LL PICK THIS UP ONE DAY
AFTER YOU GET A LITTLE
BIT BIGGER THAN PRIMULA.
THIS KID'S BOOBS ARE BIGGER
THAN YOURS. SAD, HUH?
- ( groans )
IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S
JUST YOU AND ME, KID.
SO MAYBE WE CAN FORM
A "FLAT-CHESTED"
ALLIANCE TOGETHER?
WE'LL FIND THE SMALL NUMBER
OF BOYS ON THE BEACH
WHO'RE INTO OUR TYPE
AND MAKE THEM DROOL!
- FLAT-CHESTED ALLIANCE.
- ( chuckles )
- Asa: AT ANY RATE,
NERINE'S SWIMSUIT
IS KIND OF PERVERT BAIT,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- RINA? DID YOU
BRING A BACKUP CHOICE?
- ACTUALLY, I DID.
JUST IN CASE THIS ONE
DIDN'T LOOK RIGHT.
IT'S THE ONE I PLANNED ON
WEARING FOR YOU ORIGINALLY.
- OKAY, THEN.
I THINK YOU SHOULD GO AND PUT
ON THE OTHER ONE INSTEAD.
ESPECIALLY BECAUSE
YOU PICKED IT OUT
JUST SO YOU COULD SHOW IT TO ME.
- I'D REALLY LIKE TO SEE IT.
- SURE! NO PROBLEM!
I'LL GO AND PUT IT
ON RIGHT NOW! OKAY?
- MY DAY'S ALREADY STARTING OUT
TO BE EMOTIONALLY EXHAUSTING.
- Itsuki: WELL, I THINK YOU
HANDLED THAT SITUATION
PRETTY TACTFULLY, BUT...
YOU ALSO MANAGED
TO MAKE SOME NEW ENEMIES
AT THE SAME TIME. WAY TO GO.
- ( grunting in anger )
- HEY, DON'T WORRY ABOUT THEM!
WE'RE HERE AT THE BEACH, RIN!
LET'S GO FOR A SWIM!
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT!
LET'S HAVE FUN.
- COME ON! LET'S PLAY!
- Rin: YOU GOT IT!
- Mayumi: HERE IT COMES!
- Nerine: RIN! I'M BACK!
SORRY YOU HAD TO WAIT AGAIN.
WHAT DO YOU THINK? DOES THIS
ONE LOOK ANY BETTER?
- Rin: IT'S REALLY NICE.
YOU LOOK GREAT IN IT.
- THANKS, I'M SO
GLAD YOU LIKE...
- HEY. WHAT'S UP?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- ( screams )
- OH, WOW, THAT WAS...
( yells )
- ARE YOU OKAY?
UH...
WHOA! I THINK IT'S SAFE
TO LET GO NOW.
- OH, I'M SO SORRY, RIN.
THAT WAVE CAME
CRASHING DOWN ON US,
AND I GUESS I WAS TOO
SCARED TO THINK CLEARLY.
- WHAT? I SEE.
YOU'RE AFRAID A WAVE
MIGHT PUSH YOU UNDER?
- THE OCEANS IN MY
WORLD DON'T HAVE ANY WAVES.
AND BESIDES THAT,
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO SWIM.
SO, BEING UNDERWATER
MAKES ME PANIC.
- REALLY? WELL, I'D BE WILLING
TO TEACH YOU, IF YOU'D LIKE.
- YOU'D DO THAT FOR ME?
THANK YOU SO MUCH,
I'D REALLY APPRECIATE THAT.
- ( laughs nervously )
- OKAY, WHO'S GOING TO
CATCH THIS BALL?
- Rin: ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S GOOD! KEEP IT UP!
NOW TRY PUTTING YOUR
FACE IN THE WATER!
- Nerine: OKAY.
- WHEN CAN WE PLAY?
MAN.
- YOU'RE DOING GOOD. KEEP IT UP.
NOW, KICK A LITTLE HARDER.
- Nerine: I'M TRYING.
LIKE THIS?
- WELL, WHAT CAN YOU DO?
- Waitress: GOOD
AFTERNOON, GIRLS!
YOU SHOULD COME IN! WE HAVE
SOME AMAZING SPECIALS TODAY!
- CUTE!
- ( both sigh )
- ( panting )
NEXT TARGET ACQUIRED.
HI YA!
( screams )
MY MISTAKE!
SORRY ABOUT THAT!
- FOR SOME REASON,
HE SEEMS KIND OF FAMILIAR.
- ( exclaims )
OH, MAN. THAT WASN'T COOL.
( gasps )
- IF HE SPENDS
ALL DAY WITH HER,
WHEN'S HE GOING TO
HAVE TIME FOR ME?
- THAT'S GOOD!
YOU'VE GOTTEN A LOT BETTER!
ALRIGHT. I THINK YOU'RE
READY TO USE THIS NOW.
- Sia: NO! SHE'LL NEVER
GET ANY BETTER
IF YOU KEEP DOING
THINGS THAT WAY!
THIS STUFF ISN'T
DOING YOU ANY GOOD!
- WHAT? IT'S NOT? YOU SURE?
- YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND, RIN!
WHEN YOU'RE A GIRL YOU CAN DO
IT ALL! JUST STAY FOCUSED!
ALL THESE TOYS ARE HOLDING YOU
BACK FROM ACTUALLY DOING IT!
YOU NEED TO TRUST YOUR
INSTINCTS! I'LL HELP YOU OUT,
SO LISTEN TO ME
AND FOLLOW MY LEAD.
- Nerine: ARE YOU SURE?
- Sia: YES, OF COURSE I AM!
- Nerine: OKAY. I TRUST YOU!
- ALL RIGHT!
NOW, KEEP YOUR LEGS STRAIGHT!
- Nerine: OKAY!
- YOU GOT IT! JUST LIKE THAT!
- WELL, GUESS
SHE WAS RIGHT.
THIS FEELS SO GOOD.
COMING TO THE BEACH TODAY
WAS A REALLY GREAT IDEA.
THIS IS WHAT
SUMMER IS ALL ABOUT.
- Asa: OH, YAY! JUST THE
PERSON I WANTED TO SEE!
- HUH?
- I NEED YOU TO HELP ME.
- WHY? WHAT'S GOING ON WITH YOU?
WHY ARE YOU STAYING
ALL CROUCHED DOWN,
WHEN IT'S SHALLOW
ENOUGH TO STAND?
- ACTUALLY, THERE IS A REASON.
- WHOA! WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR TOP?
- WELL, THERE WAS AN ACCIDENT
AND MY TOP GOT
WASHED OUT TO SEA.
- IF THAT'S THE CASE
COULDN'T YOU JUST HIDE THEM
WITH YOUR HANDS OR SOMETHING?
- I THOUGHT ABOUT DOING THAT,
BUT I CAN HIDE A LARGER
SURFACE AREA THIS WAY.
- YEAH, I GET IT,
BUT THIS CAN'T BE THE BEST...
( grunts )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
I GET THE FEELING
I MIGHT BE EMBARRASSING
YOU A LITTLE.
- LOOK, THE PROBLEM ISN'T
WHETHER OR NOT
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING.
- YOU KNOW YOU LIKE IT.
- WILL YOU STOP TEASING ME!
KNOWING YOU,
YOU'RE PROBABLY HAVING
SOME FUN AT MY EXPENSE.
- I WANTED TO MAKE
THE BEST OF IT.
AND YOU? YOU HAVING FUN?
- DAMMIT, ASA! COME ON, LET'S
GET YOU ONTO THE SHORE.
- Rin: JUMP UP,
I'LL CARRY YOU!
MAKE SURE YOU HOLD ON TIGHT!
- ( Asa laughs )
- Rin: YOU KNOW, SERIOUSLY,
YOU ALMOST GAVE
ME A HEART ATTACK.
- ( laughs )
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP.
- ( sighs ) IT'S BEEN SO CRAZY.
LIKE, I DON'T THINK
I COULD HANDLE
ANOTHER PAIR OF BREASTS TODAY.
- Sia: OH? "HANDLING BREASTS?"
IS THAT WHY YOU SNUCK
OFF HERE WITHOUT US?
ISN'T THAT WHAT YOU SAID?
I TOOK MY EYES OFF YOU FOR A
SECOND AND NOW!
I'D LIKE TO KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT YOU'VE BEEN DOING
SINCE YOU RAN AWAY.
- NO! NO WAIT!
IT'S NOT WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE!
JUST LISTEN... HELPING!
I WAS JUST HELPING
HER OUT OF THE WATER!
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG!
SHE WAS HAVING AN EMERGENCY!
- YOU WERE JUST
HELPING HER OUT?
IT LOOKS LIKE THAT'S NOT
ALL THAT WAS GOING ON HERE.
- NO, I SWEAR,
I'M TELLING YOU THE TRUTH!
- OH, YEAH?
- DON'T BE HARD ON HIM.
YOU'RE MISUNDERSTANDING.
HE REALLY DID SAVE ME.
NOTHING ELSE WAS GOING ON.
WHY DON'T I GO BUY EVERYONE
SOME COLD DRINKS AS AN APOLOGY?
JUST LET ME GET DRESSED,
AND WE'LL GO OUTSIDE...
- ( both gasp )
- HEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
- YEAH, I THINK I'M ALL RIGHT.
- YOU SURE?
- I'M A LITTLE WEAK FROM BEING
IN THE SUN SO MUCH TODAY.
I KNOW I'LL BE FINE
AFTER I DRINK SOMETHING.
- ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET GOING THEN.
- THANKS. I'LL FINISH
GETTING CHANGED.
- THAT WAS KINDA SCARY!
- DON'T PUSH YOURSELF.
IT'S NOT WORTH GETTING SICK.
- I PROMISE TO TAKE IT EASY.
- Kaede: GOOD, YOU'RE ALL IN
HERE! EVERYBODY'S HUNGRY,
SO I THOUGHT MAYBE WE'D
GO HAVE SOME LUNCH
WHEN YOU'RE ALL READY?
- Mayumi: THAT'S TOO FUNNY.
- Kaede: DOES ANYONE
WANT MORE OF THIS?
- HERE YOU GO! IT'S THE
EXTRA DISH YOU ORDERED!
JUST LET ME KNOW IF I CAN
GET YOU ANYTHING ELSE, OKAY!
- HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE DOING
BETTER NOW. ARE YOU?
- I'M SURE IT WAS JUST
SENSORY OVERLOAD
SO EARLY IN THE MORNING.
AND, NOW THAT I'VE EATEN,
I HAVE TONS OF ENERGY.
SO YOU CAN GO HAVE FUN WITH SIA
WITHOUT ME GETTING IN THE WAY.
- Sia: BOY, THAT WAS GOOD.
BUT I ATE WAY TOO MUCH!
I'M FEELING TOTALLY
STUFFED AND SLEEPY.
WHENEVER I FIND
I HAVE A FULL STOMACH,
I ALWAYS
GET SUPER TIRED.
- I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
- Sia: I GUESS WE
COULD BOTH USE A NAP.
LET'S GO BACK IN LATER, AND EVEN
FARTHER OUT THIS TIME, OKAY?
AND I'D LIKE IT IF IT COULD
JUST BE US FOR A WHILE.
- THAT SOUNDS
LIKE A GOOD PLAN.
WE CAN GO FARTHER OUT THEN.
IT'LL JUST BE THE TWO OF US.
- WE FELL ASLEEP.
I FEEL LIKE I MIGHT'VE BEEN
OUT IN THE SUN FOR TOO LONG.
HEY, YOU SHOULD
GET UP NOW, SIA.
YOU'LL GET SUNBURNED IF WE STAY
LIKE THIS FOR MUCH LONGER.
( gasps ) WHAT? HOW THE HELL
DID WE END UP HERE?
- WHY'D YOU SHOUT?
IT'S SO QUIET.
EVERYONE ELSE TAKE
OFF AND GO SOMEPLACE?
- NO, WE'RE THE ONES
WHO TOOK OFF.
I MEAN, TAKE A LOOK AROUND US.
YOU'LL GET THE PICTURE.
- ( gasps ) NO WAY!
- WE MUST'VE BEEN TOO
CLOSE TO THE WATER
WHEN THE TIDE GOT HIGH.
I DON'T KNOW HOW LONG
WE'VE BEEN FLOATING,
BUT WE MIGHT BE PRETTY
FAR AWAY BY NOW.
- WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
- THAT'S NOT AN EASY QUESTION.
- MY SKIN'S STARTING TO GET
ITCHY. I'M GETTING A SUNBURN.
- I THINK WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE TO GET OUT OF THE SUN
BEFORE WE BOTH FRY.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO PADDLE TO
SHORE. THERE'LL BE SHADE THERE.
- Sia: OKAY!
- Rin: IS ANYBODY HERE? KAEDE?
NERINE! MAYUMI!
- PRIMULA! DAD!
KAREHA! ASA!
WHERE ARE YOU?
NO ONE'S HERE. WHAT DO YOU
THINK WE SHOULD DO NOW?
- DAMN! I DON'T SEE HOW WE
COULD'VE GOTTEN SO FAR AWAY.
- CAN WE GO?
IT'S TOO HOT TO STAY HERE.
- RIGHT. LET'S TRY TO
FIND A NICE SHADY SPOT
WHERE WE CAN RELAX AND THINK.
- THAT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE IT'LL BE EASY.
- WE'VE GOTTA TRY.
THIS IS IT. SO COME ON.
- BUT WHERE? ARE WE JUST
GOING TO WANDER AROUND?
- THERE'S NO GOOD REASON
FOR US TO STAY HERE.
MAYBE WE CAN EVEN FIND SOMEPLACE
WHERE THERE ARE PEOPLE.
- OH, RIGHT!
- ( sighs )
OH MAN, IT'S JUST LIKE
THIS GRASS GOES ON FOREVER.
THE GROUND HERE'S SO HARD,
MY FEET ARE KILLING ME.
YOU DOING OKAY BACK THERE?
- UH-HUH. YEAH, I'M DOING FINE.
( screams )
- Rin: ( gasps ) SIA!
- Sia: OW! THAT REALLY HURTS!
- THINGS ARE GOING
FROM BAD TO WORSE.
DO YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU CAN STILL WALK?
- YOU KNOW WHAT
I'VE BEEN THINKING?
THAT MAYBE SOMEHOW WE'VE
CROSSED OVER INTO ANOTHER WORLD.
A PLACE WHERE THERE
ARE NO PEOPLE.
WHAT IF, AFTER ALL WE'VE BEEN
THROUGH, WE DON'T FIND ANYBODY?
- I CAN'T HELP FEELING
WE'RE ALL ALONE!
- THAT'S NOT TRUE!
THERE'S NO WAY WE'RE THE
ONLY ONES IN THIS WORLD!
- ( wind blowing )
- ( bird cawing )
- ( exclaims in fright )
- OH, NO BIG DEAL.
IT'S JUST A BIRD.
DON'T BE SCARED. THERE'S
NOTHING TO BE AFRAID OF.
IT'S ALL RIGHT NOW.
- I HATE THAT YOU'RE HAVING
TO LUG ME AROUND.
- DON'T WORRY, YOU'RE LIGHT.
THIS IS A PIECE OF CAKE.
- BUT, YOU MUST BE FEELING
EXHAUSTED BY NOW.
DO YOU THINK THIS IS MY FAULT?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- I REMEMBER WISHING I
COULD GO FAR AWAY WITH YOU,
JUST THE TWO OF US.
BEFORE WE FELL ASLEEP ON THE
BEACH. AND THEN THIS HAPPENED.
- Rin: LISTEN,
YOU DIDN'T DO ANYTHING WRONG.
INSTEAD OF WORRYING
ABOUT WHO'S TO BLAME,
WE SHOULD CONCENTRATE ON WHAT WE
NEED TO DO TO GET THROUGH THIS.
- WHAT IF WE NEVER GET
TO SEE RINA AND RIMU
OR MY FATHER AGAIN?
- IF WE CAN'T, I... DON'T KNOW.
- YOU CAN'T THINK LIKE THAT!
IF WE'RE NOT RESCUED,
I'LL MAKE SURE WE
MAKE IT HOME SAFELY.
BESIDES, IF THAT WISH DID
COME TRUE, WE'RE BOTH TO BLAME.
I'VE GOTTA ADMIT,
I WANTED THE SAME THING YOU DID.
- HUH?
- I WANTED TO BE ALONE
WITH YOU, SIA,
EVEN IF IT WAS JUST
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
MY WISHES WERE THE SAME AS
YOURS. AND IF THEY CAME TRUE,
IT'S BECAUSE WE BOTH HOPED
THAT IT WOULD HAPPEN. YOU KNOW?
- YEAH, OKAY.
- OKAY, NOW LET'S SAY
THE WORSE CASE SCENARIO
IS TRUE AND WE'RE THE ONLY
ONES LIVING ON THIS WORLD.
OF COURSE YOU'D
MISS YOUR FRIENDS,
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE
YOU'D BE ALL ALONE.
YOU'VE GOT ME HERE
TO PROTECT YOU.
AND I'LL BE BY YOUR SIDE,
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS.
RIGHT?
- THANK YOU, RIN.
- ( leaves rustling )
- ( animal growls )
- WHAT IS THAT THING?
- TRY TO STAY CALM.
HOLD STILL FOR NOW.
LOOK, EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE.
- BUT WE NEED A PLAN. ALRIGHT?
- ALRIGHT.
- IF THAT ATTACKS US,
LET ME HANDLE IT.
I WANT YOU TO LEAVE ME BEHIND
AND RUN AS FAST AS YOU CAN.
DON'T EVEN LOOK BACK UNTIL
YOU'RE SOMEPLACE YOU FEEL SAFE.
- NO WAY! I WOULD
NEVER RUN OFF AND
LEAVE YOU IF YOU WERE IN DANGER!
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME, GO.
- NO! YOU'D HAVE TO ESCAPE WITH
ME OR I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE!
- DON'T SAY THAT!
I'D WANT TO KNOW THAT
AT LEAST YOU'D BE ALL RIGHT!
- RIN, I DON'T CARE!
- Rin: HURRY! THIS WAY!
- Sia: WATCH WHERE
WE'RE RUNNING!
- ( both scream )
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- THINK SO.
IT'S LIGHT!
- SOMEONE'S OVER THERE!
- ANYBODY? WE NEED SOME HELP!
- WE'RE OVER HERE!
- ( both laugh )
- Rin: OH, MAN.
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES HERE,
AFTER ALL.
IT'S LIKE WE ACTUALLY
HAVE WANDERED
INTO SOME TERRIBLE,
LONELY PLACE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE TO DO.
IT'S LIKE, I WANTED TO SAVE YOU,
BUT WE'RE STILL IN THE
MIDDLE OF NOWHERE.
I FEEL LIKE I LET YOU DOWN.
- MMM-MMM.
OH, NO!
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU'VE DONE MORE THAN ENOUGH.
BESIDES THAT, YOU'VE MADE ME
REALIZE SOMETHING IMPORTANT.
YOU KNOW THE STUFF
YOU WERE SAYING BEFORE?
YOU MADE ME FEEL BETTER
KNOWING NO MATTER
WHAT KIND OF CRAZY PLACE
WE'RE IN, I HAVE YOU.
SO, AS LONG AS WE'RE
TOGETHER, I'LL BE FINE.
THERE'S NO ONE BUT US.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE WE'RE THE ADAM
AND EVE OF THIS WORLD, ISN'T IT?
- YEAH.
LET'S TRY TO MAKE OUR LIFE
TOGETHER A HAPPY ONE. EVEN HERE.
- YES, IT'LL BE OUR NEW HOME.
AND I'LL HAVE LOTS OF BABIES FOR
YOU TO LOVE, TOO.
- THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
- MY LOVE.
- Itsuki: HEY, CHECK IT OUT!
IT LOOKS LIKE THOSE TWO ARE
ABOUT TO START MAKING OUT!
- Mayumi: I DIDN'T THINK SIA
WAS SO FAR IN THE LEAD
AGAINST THE OTHER GIRLS.
- WOW! THIS IS A BIG SCOOP!
- Kareha: OOH LA LA!
- ( both gasp )
- KAEDE? NERINE?
ITSUKI, HOW... MAYUMI?
WHERE HAS EVERYONE BEEN
HIDING ALL OF THIS TIME?
- Mayumi: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THAT'S WHAT WE'VE BEEN
WANTING TO ASK YOU!
- YOU TWO JUST VANISHED
ALL OF A SUDDEN
AND WE COULDN'T FIGURE
OUT WHERE YOU'D GONE.
WE KEPT WAITING FOR YOU TO
COME BACK, BUT YOU NEVER DID.
- HOLD ON, DOES THIS MEAN?
WHAT I THINK IT MEANS?
- Both: SO THAT'S WHAT
HAPPENED TO US!
- BUT NOW, IT LOOKS LIKE WE'VE
INTERRUPTED SOMETHING.
MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST GO.
- NO. YOU WEREN'T
INTERRUPTING ANYTHING!
WE WERE JUST TALKING
ABOUT THE WEATHER.
- OH!
- ( laughs loudly )
- COME ON, NO LAME EXCUSES.
JUST LEVEL WITH US.
SO, WHAT WERE YOU DOING
TO KEEP YOURSELVES BUSY
ALL THOSE HOURS YOU WERE GONE?
- YOU WEREN'T DOING THAT,
WERE YOU?
- JUST TELL US.
- DAMN, YOU SURE ARE
ONE HEARTLESS GUY, RIN.
- ( laughs )
- YOU DON'T...
NOTHING LIKE THAT HAPPENED.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT'S OKAY.
THIS'LL BE A SECRET BETWEEN
THE TWO OF US. OKAY!
- Boys: LOOK AT THOSE WAVES!
THREE CHEERS FOR THE NIGHT SEA!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- MABOU, YOU BETTER WATCH OUT!
I'M GOING TO CATCH YOU!
- NOT IN A MILLION YEARS!
- I'LL NEVER GIVE UP!
- Nerine: WE'RE SO SORRY
YOU HAD TO HEAR THAT.
- Sia: SEE YOU NEXT TIME
ON SHUFFLE! EPISODE 10,
"MOONLIT CONFESSION."
- Forbesii: I'M BEGINNING TO
SUSPECT THAT OUR DAUGHTERS
AREN'T VERY IMPRESSED WITH US.
- Eustoma: SIA!
THAT'S NOT TRUE, IS IT?