- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( breathing deeply )
- WE'RE GOING TO NEED
AN OXYGEN MASK HERE, STAT!
- ON IT.
- SHE'S MUCH WEAKER THAN
I WOULD HAVE EXPECTED.
SHE WASN'T THIS BAD
WHEN SHE WAS IN LAST TIME.
- I AGREE. AND NOTHING'S
SHOWING UP IN HER BLOOD WORK.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THIS BEFORE.
- WE'RE JUST GOING TO
HAVE TO KEEP HER HERE
AND WATCH HER CLOSELY.
- EXCUSE ME?
- ARE YOU A MEMBER
OF HER FAMILY?
- WELL, NO.
DOCTORS?
CAN YOU JUST TELL ME HOW SHE IS?
SHE'S GOING TO BE OKAY,
RIGHT, DOCTORS?
- IT'S HARD TO SAY FOR SURE.
- WHAT NOW?
- ASA!
- I WAS THERE.
AND COULDN'T HELP.
- ( breathing deeply )
- Doctor 1: THE SYMPTOMS
YOUR DAUGHTER IS EXPERIENCING
ARE LIKE NOTHING
WE'VE EVER SEEN BEFORE.
ALL WE CAN DO NOW IS
KEEP HER ON THE IV
AND UNDER CLOSE OBSERVATION.
BUT I'M AFRAID, IF THINGS
CONTINUE LIKE THIS...
- YOU THINK SHE MIGHT
NOT SURVIVE?
- WE'LL KNOW MORE
AFTER WE GET HER TEST RESULTS.
UNTIL THEN, WE'LL JUST
HAVE TO WAIT.
- WHAT? IS THAT ALL YOU CAN SAY?
WE HAVE TO WAIT?
- PLEASE, CALM DOWN.
- YOU'RE A DOCTOR, AREN'T YOU?
SO WHY AREN'T YOU DOING
ANYTHING TO MAKE HER BETTER?
- Ama: RIN, PLEASE.
- I'M SORRY, DOCTOR.
- HEY, RIN, LET'S CHAT
FOR A FEW MINUTES.
I WANTED TO THANK YOU.
- FOR WHAT?
- FOR BRINGING HER
TO THE HOSPITAL, OF COURSE.
FOR BEING THERE, WHENEVER
SHE NEEDED YOUR HELP.
IT'S NOT EASY, IS IT?
- NO.
IT'S JUST, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING ON.
- TELL ME SOMETHING.
ARE YOU IN LOVE
WITH HER YET? WELL?
I KNOW THAT I'VE
ASKED YOU BEFORE...
BUT, WELL?
- I LOVE HER.
- WONDERFUL.
- NOW I CAN TELL YOU.
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF PROJECT YGGDRASIL?
- YEAH, I HAVE.
- THAT SHOULD MAKE THIS
EASIER THEN.
ARE YOU FAMILIAR WITH
THE SUBJECTS THEY USED
FOR THEIR EXPERIMENTS?
- YES.
- LOOK AT ME, RIN.
IT'S TIME YOU FINALLY
KNEW THE TRUTH.
- YOU'RE FROM THE WORLD
OF THE DEMONS!
- THIS NEEDS TO BE OUR SECRET.
YOU CAN'T TELL ANYONE, OKAY?
- WAIT, BUT THE KING
OF THE DEMONS SAID
THAT THE FIRST EXPERIMENTAL
SUBJECT DIDN'T SURVIVE.
- SO HE TOLD EVERYBODY THAT
I WAS DEAD ALL THIS TIME.
THAT REALLY DOESN'T SURPRISE ME.
AT THAT POINT IN MY LIFE, I
WOULDN'T HAVE MINDED IT REALLY,
IF I HAD DIED.
- WHAT? BUT WHY?
- BECAUSE I DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT ELSE TO DO.
I NEVER HAD A FAMILY
WHEN I LIVED IN THE WORLD
OF THE DEMONS.
AND EVERY DAY
I FELT TRULY ALONE.
SO I VOLUNTEERED
FOR THE EXPERIMENT.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD
GIVE ME SOME PURPOSE.
IT NEVER OCCURRED
TO ME TO WORRY
THAT THE EXPERIMENT MIGHT FAIL.
RISKING EVERYTHING SEEMED
BETTER THAN HAVING NOTHING.
I JUST NEEDED TO ESCAPE
FROM THE LIFE I HAD.
AND THEN, WHEN I CAME TO,
I FOUND MYSELF
IN THE HUMAN WORLD.
IT WAS BEFORE PEOPLE KNEW
THAT THE WORLD OF THE DEMONS
AND THE WORLD
OF THE GODS EXISTED.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I COULDN'T TELL ANYONE WHO I
WAS OR WHERE I CAME FROM.
- ( tires screeching )
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW IMPORTANT
THAT NIGHT WOULD BE.
THE NIGHT I MET HIM.
- THIS MAN, HE'S ASA'S FATHER?
- MM-HMM.
HE'S THE PERSON I ADMIRE
MORE THAN ANYONE IN THIS WORLD.
- I CAN SEE WHY HE WOULD MEAN
SO MUCH TO YOU.
- WHEN I NEEDED SOMEONE MORE
THAN ANYTHING ELSE,
HE WAS THERE.
I AM WHO I'VE BECOME TODAY
BECAUSE HE WAS THERE FOR ME
AT THAT MOMENT.
WITH HIM I FINALLY FOUND
SOMEWHERE TO BELONG.
THAT ALONE WOULD HAVE BEEN
ENOUGH TO MAKE ME HAPPY.
BUT IN THE END, HE GAVE ME
SOMETHING EVEN BETTER
THAN I'D EXPECTED.
HE GAVE ME MY ASA.
- ARE YOU SAYING
THAT ASA'S A DEMON?
- NO. ASA'S A HUMAN,
LIKE HER FATHER.
BUT IT ISN'T THAT SIMPLE.
SHE INHERITED HER HUMAN BODY
FROM HER FATHER.
AND HER MAGIC FROM ME.
DUE TO THE EXPERIMENT
I WAS PUT THROUGH,
THE MAGIC INSIDE ASA
WAS INTENSIFIED,
MAKING IT TOO STRONG
FOR HER HUMAN FORM TO CONTAIN.
- ( moans )
- YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY.
- HI, RIN.
- HEY, ASA. WELCOME BACK.
- WHERE AM I?
- THE HOSPITAL.
YOU COLLAPSED
AT THE APARTMENT.
- OH, RIGHT.
THANK YOU, RIN.
HAVE YOU BEEN WAITING HERE
WITH ME THE WHOLE TIME?
- I DIDN'T MIND WAITING.
- WELL, STOP IT.
I'M GONNA BE JUST FINE NOW.
- YOU'RE NOT READY
FOR THAT YET.
COME ON. STAY IN BED.
- I REALLY DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S WRONG.
I GUESS THE MOVE
MUST HAVE TIRED ME OUT.
- Ama: RIGHT NOW,
THE MAGIC LIVING INSIDE HER
IS GETTING READY TO OVERFLOW.
NOTHING ON THIS PLANET
CAN SAVE HER.
SHE HAS TO DO IT.
- RIGHT. BUT CAN'T WE
DO SOMETHING?
- THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
FOR HER TO SURVIVE THIS.
SHE HAS TO GET RID OF ALL
THE MAGIC THAT'S INSIDE HER.
- THE MAGIC.
SO THAT'S ALL SHE HAS TO DO?
- WELL, WAIT.
GETTING RID OF THE MAGIC
WON'T BE THAT EASY.
- ASA, PLEASE.
- WHAT IS IT, RIN?
- YOU HAVE TO USE
YOUR MAGIC, OKAY?
PLEASE JUST DO IT.
- SO YOU FOUND OUT.
- YOU ONLY HAVE TO USE IT ONCE.
AND THEN YOU'LL BE
TOTALLY CURED.
- THEN WE CAN JUST GO HOME!
- NO!
- BUT WHY NOT?
- I WON'T!
I WON'T EVER USE MY MAGIC.
BESIDES, IT WOULDN'T WORK
EVEN IF I DID TRY.
I'M A HUMAN, JUST A HUMAN!
- LISTEN, YOUR MOM SAID
THIS WAS THE ONLY WAY.
- I'M A HUMAN!
MAGIC IS JUST...
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- ( coughing )
- Nurse: NURSES' STATION.
- HURRY, PLEASE!
SOMETHING'S WRONG!
- YES, SIR!
- HANG ON, ALRIGHT?
YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY!
- Kaede: RIN!
KAEDE, PRIMULA.
WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
- WE CAME TO SEE ASA.
AMA CALLED.
- I HOPE YOU'RE ALRIGHT, RIN.
YOU LOOK REALLY TIRED.
SO, HOW'S ASA DOING?
RIN?
- SHE'S BETTER.
SHE'S SLEEPING RIGHT NOW.
DON'T WORRY.
SHE'LL BE UP ON HER FEET
IN NO TIME, REALLY.
- THAT'S GOOD.
PLEASE PROMISE ME
THAT YOU'LL BE CAREFUL.
AND DON'T LET THIS
WEAR YOU OUT, OKAY?
SORRY. I WANT TO MAKE SURE
YOU'LL BE OKAY, TOO.
- I'LL BE FINE.
- ALRIGHT. JUST
PROMISE TO TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF
WHILE YOU'RE LOOKING AFTER HER?
- SURE.
- THE HOSPITAL ISN'T LETTING
ANY MORE VISITORS IN TONIGHT.
WHY DON'T WE
COME BACK TOMORROW?
- KAEDE?
- YES.
- OF COURSE
WE'LL COME BACK TOMORROW.
AND THIS TIME WE'LL INVITE
SIA AND THE OTHERS AS WELL.
- 'KAY?
- OF COURSE.
- I'M SORRY.
I KNOW YOU GUYS CAME
A LONG WAY.
- BUT WE'LL COME BACK.
YES.
- PLEASE GIVE HER THESE.
- YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE WHO'LL
BE ABLE TO SAVE HER LIFE.
DON'T GIVE UP ON HER, RIN.
- WHY DOES EVERYONE
THINK THAT?
WHY ME?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I CAN DO
TO HELP HER.
SHE WON'T LISTEN TO ME.
- JUST THINK FOR A WHILE.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
THAT ONLY YOU CAN DO.
- IF THERE IS,
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT IT.
ASA.
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
THERE'S GOTTA BE SOMETHING
I CAN DO.
- THAT POOR GIRL IN 501, YOU
MEAN THEY STILL HAVEN'T
FIGURED OUT WHAT'S
WRONG WITH HER?
- NO, THEY STILL HAVE NO IDEA.
AND SHE'S HAVING ATTACKS
MORE FREQUENTLY, TOO.
I WISH THERE WAS SOMETHING
WE COULD DO FOR HER.
- THEY'LL RUN MORE TESTS
AND CONTINUE TO OBSERVE HER.
- I JUST HOPE
THAT WILL BE ENOUGH.
- OH, GOOD, YOU'RE BACK.
THANKS, RIN.
- DON'T YOU THINK YOU
SHOULD BE LYING DOWN?
- NO, I'M FEELING MUCH
BETTER NOW. I'M REALLY FINE.
SO CAN I HAVE MY JUICE NOW?
LET'S SEE. I THINK I'LL
TAKE THE APPLE.
WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU'RE NOT DRINKING YOURS.
- ASA, PLEASE.
JUST USE IT ONCE.
- NO WAY.
SAVE YOUR BREATH, RIN.
- JUST ONCE!
- I SAID NO, SO DROP IT, OKAY?
- NO, I WILL NOT.
I'M NOT GONNA LET YOU DIE
BECAUSE YOU'RE IRRATIONAL
AND STUBBORN.
- I'M NOT LISTENING
AND YOU CAN'T MAKE ME.
THANKS FOR THE JUICE.
- SHE WON'T USE HER MAGIC.
WHAT NOW?
WHAT CAN I DO?
HOW DO I CONVINCE HER?
HOW?
- Asa: I'M MISSING
SO MUCH SCHOOL.
I'M GONNA BE REALLY BEHIND
WHEN I GET BACK.
THEN YOU SHOULD HURRY UP
AND GET BETTER.
THE SOONER YOU DO,
THE SOONER YOU CAN GO BACK.
- YOU'VE ALREADY MISSED
THREE WHOLE DAYS.
AND YOU CAN'T AFFORD TO GET
ANY FURTHER BEHIND.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
AMA SPOKE WITH THE SCHOOL AND
EXPLAINED I'D BE ABSENT
FOR A WHILE.
- THEY UNDERSTAND.
- BUT STILL...
BESIDES, YOU KNOW I WAS
ALREADY PLANNING
TO MISS A FEW DAYS
BECAUSE OF THE MOVE.
- I ALMOST FORGOT.
I PROMISED TO COOK YOU
SOMETHING AT THE NEW APARTMENT
TO MAKE IT FEEL MORE LIKE HOME.
- YOU CAN DO THAT
WHEN YOU GET OUTTA HERE.
- ( chuckles )
AS SOON AS I GET OUT
I PROMISE I'LL COOK YOU
SOMETHING REALLY GOOD.
SO WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- I KNOW THAT ANYTHING YOU
MAKE WILL BE DELICIOUS, ASA.
- YOU KNOW, THAT DOESN'T
HELP ME VERY MUCH.
HMM, NOW LET ME THINK.
HAMBURGER STEAKS,
OR MAYBE A CASSEROLE!
SINCE IT'S GETTING
TO BE COLD SOON,
BEEF STEW WOULD BE GOOD, TOO.
OH, THAT REMINDS ME, WE NEED TO
GET OUT AND DO SOME STUFF,
BEFORE WINTER COMES.
WE SHOULD GO FOR WALKS TOGETHER,
MAYBE HANG OUT AT THE PARK.
JUST AS LONG AS
WE'RE TOGETHER, 'KAY?
WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE SHOULD DO FIRST, RIN?
WHAT IS IT?
NEVERMIND, I'M SORRY.
WHAT WERE YOU SAYING?
- HEY, WHAT WERE YOU
THINKING JUST NOW?
- IT WAS NOTHING.
- DON'T WORRY.
I'M NOT GONNA DIE,
I PROMISE.
- SO...
- BUT I'M NOT GONNA USE MAGIC.
I MIGHT DIE IF I DON'T USE IT.
BUT AS FAR AS ANYONE KNOWS,
THERE'S A CHANCE I
WON'T DIE, RIGHT?
- AND YOU'RE WILLING
TO BET YOUR LIFE ON THAT?
- IT'S MY LIFE TO BET,
NOT YOURS.
WHEN I START TO GET SCARED,
THERE'S THIS DREAM I REMEMBER.
- WHAT DREAM?
- A DREAM I HAD ABOUT THE TWO
OF US WHEN WE'RE BOTH VERY OLD.
IN THE DREAM YOU HAD TAKEN
ME BACK TO THAT OVERLOOK.
THAT PLACE WHERE YOU
FIRST TOLD ME YOU LOVED ME.
AND IN THE DREAM,
YOU WERE TELLING ME AGAIN.
AND IT STILL FELT LIKE
THE FIRST TIME.
WE HELD EACH OTHER AND WERE SO
THANKFUL WE HAD A LIFE TOGETHER.
AND SO GLAD WE STILL HAD MORE TO
LOOK FORWARD TO WITH EACH OTHER.
THAT'S WHY I'M NOT GOING TO DIE.
OH, YEAH!
CAN I OPEN THE GIFTS NOW?
I CAN'T GET IT OPEN.
WILL YOU SEE IF YOU CAN FIND
SOMETHING TO CUT THIS WITH?
- SURE.
EXCUSE ME. WE'RE TRYING
TO OPEN HER GIFTS.
DO YOU HAVE A PAIR OF SCISSORS
I COULD BORROW?
- UM, LET ME SEE IF
I HAVE SOMETHING
THAT YOU CAN USE IN HERE.
THERE, I THINK
I FOUND SOMETHING.
RIGHT. HERE YA GO.
- ( Asa coughs )
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- ( machine buzzing )
- DOCTOR!
- WE NEED A STABILIZER
AND OXYGEN! RIGHT NOW!
- WE'VE DONE EVERYTHING
THAT WE CAN FOR HER.
UNFORTUNATELY, AT THIS POINT,
IT'S OUT OF OUR HANDS.
I'M AFRAID HER BODY'S
DETERIORATING
AT AN ALARMING RATE.
YOU SHOULD PREPARE YOURSELVES.
- AMA, SHE...
SHE CAN'T HANDLE THIS
FOR MUCH LONGER.
- COME ON, LET'S GO, RIN.
- WHAT... WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
AMA, WAIT!
WHY ARE YOU LEAVING? SHE NEEDS
YOU NOW MORE THAN EVER.
AREN'T YOU WORRIED ABOUT HER?
- HOW DARE YOU...
- WELL, THEN?
- AM I WORRIED?
ANY MOTHER WOULD BE
SCARED TO DEATH RIGHT NOW, RIN!
SHE'S FRIGHTENED
AND IN SO MUCH PAIN.
OF COURSE I'M WORRIED ABOUT HER.
- AMA.
- IF I COULD TAKE HER PLACE,
I WOULD IN A HEARTBEAT.
IF DOING IT WOULD
MAKE HER BETTER,
BELIEVE ME, I'D DO IT,
AND NOT CARE FOR ONE
SECOND ABOUT MYSELF.
I'D GLADLY GIVE ASA MY LIFE!
I'VE ALWAYS TRIED TO BE THERE
FOR HER, LIKE ANY MOTHER WOULD.
BUT, I'M NOT THE ONE
WHO CAN HELP HER.
I'M SORRY. BUT, RIN,
ASA DOESN'T NEED HELP FROM ME.
THE PERSON SHE NEEDS IS YOU.
- WHAT?
- YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
THAT CAN SAVE HER!
- I'VE TRIED.
BUT ASA WON'T LISTEN.
- ASA'S STUBBORN,
BUT PLEASE DON'T GIVE UP.
SHE'LL COME AROUND,
JUST KEEP TRYING.
THE TWO OF YOU SHARE
A SPECIAL BOND OF LOVE.
THAT'S WHY SHE'LL LISTEN.
- YOU ALL KEEP SAYING THAT.
IT'S NOT TRUE.
I CAN'T DO ANY MORE FOR HER
THAN YOU CAN.
- YOU'RE WRONG ABOUT THAT.
I THINK PART OF YOU
KNOWS IT EVEN NOW.
ASA IS MORE IMPORTANT TO YOU
THAN ANYONE ELSE IN YOUR LIFE,
AND YOU'LL FIND A WAY
TO SAVE HER BECAUSE YOU HAVE TO.
- IF I CAN, I WILL.
- RIN, SAVE ASA.
I KNOW YOU CAN.
I LOVE HER SO MUCH.
BRING HER BACK.
- I'M SORRY, RIN.
I CAN'T GET RID OF THIS COUGH.
COME ON, CHEER UP.
I HATE TO SEE YOU
LOOKING SO SAD.
I'M GONNA BE FINE.
- JUST TELL ME.
WHY ARE YOU STILL
REFUSING TO USE MAGIC?
WHAT DO YOU HAVE AGAINST IT?
- I DON'T WANNA HURT HER,
MY MOTHER.
SHE ALWAYS HAS A SMILE
ON HER FACE.
BUT I'VE SEEN HER CRY ONCE.
- WHY IS MY BODY LIKE THIS?
WHY AM I DIFFERENT
THAN EVERYONE ELSE?
- AND SHE TOLD ME
SHE WAS A DEMON.
SHE ENDED UP HERE IN THE HUMAN
WORLD BECAUSE OF AN EXPERIMENT.
I FOUND OUT EVERYTHING THAT DAY.
- ( sobbing ) IT'S MY FAULT.
I'M SO SORRY, ASA,
IT'S MY FAULT.
IF I WEREN'T A DEMON,
THEN YOU WOULDN'T HAVE TO
SUFFER THE WAY YOU ARE.
I'M SORRY FOR BEING
SUCH A BAD MOTHER.
I'M SORRY, ASA. I'M SO SORRY.
- Asa: THAT WAS THE ONLY TIME
I'VE EVER SEEN MY MOTHER CRY.
THIS WOMAN
WHO HAD ALWAYS SMILED,
NO MATTER WHAT TERRIBLE THINGS
I SAID TO HER, WAS NOW CRYING.
I FINALLY REALIZED HOW MUCH
I WAS HURTING MY MOTHER,
WHO LOVED ME
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
I NEVER SHOULD HAVE
ASKED HER THAT QUESTION.
I CAUSED HER NOTHING BUT PAIN.
SHE DESERVES BETTER THAN THAT.
THAT'S WHY I WON'T USE MY MAGIC.
I'M ONLY A HUMAN
IN A HUMAN BODY.
I'M A NORMAL CHILD BORN TO
A NORMAL MOTHER AND FATHER.
I'M NOT A DEMON.
I'M JUST A REGULAR GIRL.
I WON'T HURT MY MOTHER LIKE
THAT AGAIN AS LONG AS I LIVE.
I WON'T DO IT!
- ( coughing )
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- I WON'T USE MAGIC.
DON'T ASK THAT OF ME, PLEASE.
( crying )
- ( grunts )
ASA.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO HELP.
I... I'M GOING TO FAIL YOU
WHEN YOU NEED ME MOST.
FORGIVE ME.
- STILL HERE.
- I HAVE TO SAVE HER.
HOW? HOW DO I SAVE HER
FROM THIS? WHAT DO I DO?
- ( coughs )
THIS IS IT. I THINK I'VE
REACHED MY LIMIT.
I'M SORRY, RIN. GOOD-BYE.
- DID YOU HEAR SOMETHING?
( gasps )
- ( breathing deeply )
- ASA!
WHERE ARE YOU?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Rin: I DON'T CARE IF I CAN
BECOME A GOD OR A DEMON.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT ANYTHING.
IF I CAN JUST SAVE HER,
THAT'S ALL I NEED!
- Primula: NEXT TIME
ON SHUFFLE...
THE FINAL EPISODE,
"AND... WHAT IS IMPORTANT."