- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Kaede: I'M SORRY, I KNOW
I'M RUNNING A LITTLE BEHIND.
- IT'S OKAY. WE'RE REALLY
NOT IN A HURRY.
- I'M JUST EXCITED ABOUT
STARTING THE SECOND TERM.
HEY, RIMU, WE'RE HEADED OFF
TO SCHOOL, OKAY?
- KAEDE, LET'S GO.
- ARE YOU OKAY?
- I'LL BE FINE.
WE BETTER GET TO SCHOOL.
- Primula: RIN, KAEDE?
- RIN. KAEDE.
- Nadeshiko: HUSTLE, MAYUMI,
YOU'VE GOT TWENTY MORE LAPS.
SIA, STOP YOUR WHINNING.
FIFTEEN TO GO.
- Mayumi: SOMEBODY KILL ME,
PLEASE. ANY TIME NOW.
- IT'S YOUR FAULT FOR
FORGETTING YOUR HOMEWORK.
YOU GET TO RUN ONE LAP
FOR EACH THING YOU FORGOT.
WAIT. STOP. TSUCCHI!
- HANG IN THERE, SIA,
I'LL RUN, TOO.
- WHAT? BUT...
BUT YOU'LL GET IN TROUBLE.
- I KIND OF FEEL BAD ABOUT
MAKING YOU WORRY SO MUCH.
BESIDES, I CAN'T LET YOU
RUN ALL THIS BY YOURSELF.
- OH, RIN.
- KAEDE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SPACE CADET,
YOUR POT IS BOILING.
- WHAT?
I'M SORRY.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU'RE COMPLETELY OUT OF IT.
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN,
TOTALLY OUT OF THE BLUE,
YOU'RE INTERESTED IN
LEARNING TO MAKE SWEETS?
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
- NO. IT'S NOTHING.
IT'S JUST THAT, I THOUGHT THAT
IF I MADE RIN SOMETHING NICE,
IT MIGHT CHEER HIM UP.
- JUST TELL ME WHAT HAPPENED.
- OH, RIN, I MADE YOU A YUMMY
BAVARIAN CREAM PIE FOR DESSERT.
DO YOU WANT ME
TO GO AND CUT YOU A SLICE?
- SURE.
- OH, I'M SORRY, KAEDE.
I WAS JUST THINKING
ABOUT PRIMULA, YOU KNOW?
THINKING ABOUT WHETHER OR NOT
SHE GETS TO EAT
AS WELL AS WE DO.
- I DON'T KNOW. I HOPE SO.
- SORRY ABOUT THAT.
OF COURSE,
SHE'S EATING WELL, RIGHT?
SHE WENT BACK TO THAT PLACE
SO SHE'D GET BETTER.
I BET SHE'S PROBABLY BACK
TO 100 PERCENT BY NOW
AND STUFFING HER FACE WITH
DELICIOUS DEMON
WORLD STYLE FOOD.
- SHE'S ONLY BEEN THERE A DAY.
- YEAH, I KNOW. IT ISN'T
GOING TO HAPPEN OVERNIGHT.
- WHAT ABOUT MAGIC?
WHAT IF SHE WAS
MIRACULOUSLY CURED
BY SOME POWERFUL MAGICAL SPELL?
- HEY, IT COULD HAPPEN.
( laughing )
- Forbesii: THE EXAMINATIONS
AREN'T HAPPENING AS
QUICKLY AS WE'D HOPED.
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE SHE'LL BE
ABLE TO COME BACK FOR A WHILE.
- FOR A WHILE?
AND HOW LONG IS A WHILE?
- AT THIS POINT, WE DON'T KNOW.
WE'LL CONTACT YOU AS SOON
AS WE HAVE MORE INFORMATION.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
PROMISE ME THAT YOU'LL
TAKE GOOD CARE OF PRIMULA
WHILE SHE'S AWAY.
- ( sighs )
- Nerine: FATHER.
- WHAT IS IT, NERINE?
- IS RIMU...
IS HER CONDITION AS BAD
AS I'VE BEEN TOLD?
- NO. IT'S JUST LIKE I TOLD RIN.
- DON'T YOU LIE!
I KNOW THAT SOMETHING'S
WRONG. RIMU'S IN TROUBLE.
I FEEL THIS PAINFUL ACHE IN MY
HEART AND IT HURTS FOR PRIMULA.
- I GUESS THERE'S NO WAY
TO KEEP IT FROM YOU. ALL RIGHT.
- Researcher: THE MAGIC
ACCUMULATED IN HER
IS FAR GREATER THAN WHAT
WE HAD ORIGINALLY PREDICTED.
- NOW STOP RIGHT THERE.
IF PRIMULA REGAINED
HER HUMANISTIC EMOTIONS,
WASN'T SHE SUPPOSED TO BE
ABLE TO CONTROL HER POWERS?
- WELL, IN THEORY.
- ARE YOU TELLING ME
THE HYPOTHESIS WAS WRONG?
- WE DON'T UNDERSTAND IT EITHER.
OUR PREDICTIONS INDICATED
THAT SHE WOULD GAIN A
DEGREE OF CONTROL, BUT...
- BUT SHE'S NOT DOING IT.
WHAT OPTIONS DO WE HAVE?
IF THINGS GET WORSE?
- THERE IS A HIGH PROBABILITY
THAT SHE WILL SUFFER
THE SAME FATE AS
THE PREVIOUS SUBJECTS.
- SHE'S THE THIRD ONE ALREADY.
ARE YOU SAYING
THERE'S NO WAY TO SAVE HER?
- THERE IS A WAY, BUT...
- NO THAT'S AWFUL.
- THAT'S OUR ONLY OPTION
RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE OBVIOUSLY LOOKING
FOR OTHER WAYS, BUT...
- NO, BUT... BUT THEN...
- NERINE, I UNDERSTAND HOW YOU
FEEL. I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT
I HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN
ABOUT LYCORIS EITHER.
REMEMBER, RIN CAN'T KNOW ABOUT
THIS. KEEP OUR SECRET SAFE.
- NERINE, IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
POOR RIN. HE SEEMS
SO DEPRESSED, ALONE.
I HOPE THAT PRIMULA
CAN COME BACK SOON.
- UM, YOU KNOW, SIA, I...
NOTHING. IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
- DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
IF YOU HAVE SOMETHING ON
YOUR MIND, DON'T BOTTLE IT UP.
WE'LL WORK TOGETHER, OKAY?
SINCE THERE'S TWO OF US,
WHO KNOWS WHAT IDEAS
WE'LL BE ABLE TO DISCOVER.
- SIA...
- I DON'T WANT TO SEE
RIN FEELING LIKE THAT
ANYMORE THAN YOU DO.
- LET'S GO SOMEWHERE
MORE PRIVATE.
- I HAD NO IDEA.
- I DON'T THINK THAT I CAN BRING
MYSELF TO TELL RIN THE TRUTH.
- YEAH, BUT, I DON'T THINK
THAT WE CAN STAY QUIET
AND KEEP THIS THING
TO OURSELVES EITHER.
- WELL, I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT
ABOUT THAT, SIA.
I JUST DON'T HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW TO TELL HIM.
- BUT, WHAT IF THERE WAS
A SPECIAL OCCASION?
HOW ABOUT THIS?
LISTEN, LET'S GET IN TOUCH
WITH BOTH RIN AND KAEDE
AND INVITE THEM OVER FOR DINNER?
WE'LL INVITE BOTH OF
OUR FATHERS AS WELL,
AND THEN WE'LL WAIT FOR
THE PERFECT TIME TO BRING IT UP.
- DO YOU REALLY THINK
IT'S A GOOD IDEA
THAT OUR FATHERS BE THE ONES
TO TALK TO RIN ABOUT RIMU?
- YEAH.
- THANK YOU.
LET'S FIND RIN AND KAEDE,
SO WE CAN INVITE THEM OVER.
- HEY, I THOUGHT YOU AND
I WERE HAVING DINNER
OVER AT NERINE'S PLACE TONIGHT.
- YEAH. I KNOW, I'M JUST WORRIED
IF WE DON'T BRING AT LEAST
ONE DISH TO THE PARTY,
THEY'LL THINK WE'RE RUDE.
- YOU'RE RIGHT. WE PROBABLY
SHOULDN'T SHOW UP TO THIS THING
COMPLETELY EMPTY HANDED, HUH?
- APPARENTLY, SIA AND HER FATHER
ARE COOKING UP A PRETTY
EXTRAVAGANT FEAST.
I WANNA MAKE SURE THAT
I DON'T BRING SOMETHING
THAT'S ALREADY ON
THE MENU, YOU KNOW?
- YOU OUGHT TO CALL THEM AND SEE
WHAT KINDA STUFF THEY'RE MAKING.
- NO! THERE'S NO WAY I COULD
EVER ASK THEM THAT, RIN.
THEN THEY'LL DEFINITELY THINK
WE'RE RUDE.
- I DON'T MIND.
I'LL GO ASK THEM.
- Eustoma: HOW ARE WE
GOING TO HANDLE THIS?
ARE WE REALLY GOING TO TELL RIN
AND KAEDE THE TRUTH ABOUT RIMU?
- WE HAVE NO CHOICE.
IT'S NOT SOMETHING
WE CAN HIDE FOREVER.
AND I THINK IT'S CRUEL TO FORCE
OUR DAUGHTERS TO BE QUIET
AND TO LIE TO THEIR FRIENDS.
- I COMPLETELY AGREE.
BUT IT'S AN IMPOSSIBLE THING
TO TELL THEM.
WE JUST SIMPLY CANNOT LET
PRIMULA COME BACK HERE AGAIN.
- WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
MAKE THEM UNDERSTAND.
THE WAY THINGS ARE,
PRIMULA WON'T LAST LONG.
- ( door creaking )
- WHO'S THERE?
OH, RIN.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- I KNOCKED ON THE DOOR
AND NOBODY CAME,
SO I LET MYSELF IN. SORRY.
IS THAT THE TRUTH?
WHAT YOU WERE JUST SAYING?
- WELL... NOW, RIN, LISTEN HERE.
- I WANT THE TRUTH NOW.
- YES, IT'S TRUE.
- BUT WHY?
DIDN'T SHE GO BACK TO
THE REALM OF THE DEMONS
SO THAT SHE COULD GET BETTER?
- YES, THAT WAS THE INTENT.
NO, NO, THAT IS THE INTENT
EVEN NOW AS WE SPEAK.
BUT, PRIMULA'S CONDITION HAS
WORSENED FAR BEYOND ANYTHING
THAT WE HAD EVER ANTICIPATED.
- NO, BUT...
BUT THAT MEANS PRIMULA IS...
- IT'S EXACTLY AS HE SAID.
AT THIS RATE
THERE'S NO WAY OF KNOWING
IF SHE'LL LIVE THROUGH THE DAY.
- IS THERE SOME KIND OF CURE?
THERE MUST BE SOME WAY
TO HELP HER.
TALK TO ME.
- THERE IS ONLY ONE CURE.
- OH, THANK GOODNESS.
SO SHE CAN BE SAVED, RIGHT?
- BY ALLOWING HER EMOTIONS
TO SHOW,
SHE WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
ABLE TO CONTROL HER MAGIC.
BUT, UNFORTUNATELY, IT APPEARS
THAT IT HAS SERVED TO HAVE
THE OPPOSITE EFFECT ON HER.
THUS RESETTING
PRIMULA'S EMOTIONS
BEFORE THEY GROW ANY STRONGER.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY.
PRIMULA WILL FORGET
WHAT IT IS TO FEEL.
AND SHE WILL LIKELY
NEVER RECALL IT AGAIN.
- OH. HEY, RIN,
I'M SORRY WE TOOK SO LONG.
WE'LL GET STARTED COOKING
RIGHT AWAY.
RIN?
- OH, NO. LISTEN, RIN.
- YOU KNEW.
YOU BOTH KNEW ABOUT PRIMULA?
WHY?
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
AS SOON AS YOU FOUND OUT?
TELL ME WHY?
- I'M SO SORRY, RIN.
- I APOLOGIZE.
WE REALLY NEVER MEANT
FOR IT TO BE THIS WAY.
- I'M SORRY. YOU GUYS ARE RIGHT.
HOW COULD YOU POSSIBLY TELL ME
ABOUT HER?
- OH, RIN.
- I UNDERSTAND
HOW YOU MUST'VE FELT.
SOMETHING LIKE THIS. HOW AM I
EVER GOING TO TELL KAEDE?
- HEY.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU, RIN?
HIDING AWAY IN PRIMULA'S ROOM
LIKE THIS?
- OH, UH...
YOU KNOW OUR DINNER PARTY THING?
IT GOT CANCELLED,
SO WE'RE NOT GONNA GO.
- OH, I HOPE EVERYTHING IS OKAY.
- YEAH. APPARENTLY, SOMETHING
JUST HAPPENED TO COME UP.
- WELL, THAT'S TOO BAD.
I WAS LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
- ME, TOO.
- WELL, I GUESS I'D BETTER GET
DINNER STARTED, OKAY?
- SURE THING, KAEDE.
- I SURE HOPE RIMU'S ABLE TO
COME HOME SOON, DON'T YOU?
- WHAT?
- 'CAUSE WHEN SHE
DOES COME BACK,
I'M GONNA MAKE HER THE
BEST MEAL SHE'S EVER HAD.
- YEAH, WELL, I'M SURE
SHE'LL BE HOME REAL SOON.
- I KNOW THAT YOU'RE LYING
TO ME, RIN.
( sobbing ) YOU'RE A WONDERFUL,
KIND PERSON.
BUT YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN
A HORRIBLE LIAR.
- ARE YOU GOING TO SIT THERE
AND DO NOTHING?
- ( Kaede sobbing )
- ( sobbing )
- I SURE AM SURPRISED
TO SEE YOU TWO HERE.
WHERE'S RIN AND KAEDE?
THEY'RE NOT WITH YOU?
HELLO, RIN.
- HEY THERE, ASA.
- WHAT'S GOING ON HERE? YOU TWO
ARE SITTING WAY TOO FAR APART.
NOW, YOU LISTEN UP, MISTER,
YOU BETTER NOT HAVE GONE
AND DONE SOMETHING
TO UPSET KAEDE AGAIN.
- NO, RIN HASN'T DONE ANYTHING.
- DON'T YOU LIE FOR HIM.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO PROTECT HIM.
COME ON, JERK FACE,
IT'S TIME TO FESS UP.
- EXCUSE ME,
BUT I'M JUST NOT IN THE MOOD.
- RIN, WAIT.
IT'S ABOUT RIMU, ISN'T IT?
TELL ME WHAT'S WRONG.
- ( students talking )
- Sia: RIN, DO YOU WANNA
WALK HOME TOGETHER?
- OH, I WOULD
BUT I'M JUST GONNA WALK AROUND
AND GET SOME AIR.
- HUH?
- SORRY.
- WHAT'S UP? SO, YOU'RE NOT
GOING HOME WITH RIN, HUH? KAEDE?
HELLO. UH... LADIES?
- ( upbeat music playing )
- OH, PRIMULA.
- MAYBE YOU SHOULD TAKE A BREAK
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
I HEARD ABOUT WHAT'S GOING ON
FROM KAEDE.
BUT STILL, RIN, WHAT WAS
ALL THAT ABOUT EARLIER?
IT'S REALLY NOT LIKE YOU.
- I JUST...
I DIDN'T WANNA GO HOME.
- HUH?
- IT DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT
WITHOUT PRIMULA THERE.
AND THEN, TO SEE
THAT LOOK ON KAEDE'S FACE.
THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO
TO HELP HER.
PLUS, IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
WHAT I DID WAS HORRIBLE.
SHE DEFINITELY DIDN'T WANT
TO GO BACK.
I FORCED HER.
I MADE HER GO BACK.
WHEN SHE WAS SO AGAINST IT.
I JUST DIDN'T KNOW.
I DIDN'T KNOW I WASN'T
EVER GOING TO SEE HER AGAIN.
- YEAH, BUT IF THINGS
HAD BEEN LEFT ALONE,
RIMU WOULDN'T HAVE GOTTEN
ANY BETTER, RIGHT?
- MAYBE SO. BUT THAT
DOESN'T CHANGE THE FACT
THAT I FORCED PRIMULA TO
GO BACK AGAINST HER WILL.
KAEDE WOULDN'T STOP CRYING.
BUT YOU KNOW, SHE HASN'T SAID
A BAD WORD ABOUT ME.
I THINK THAT I WOULD FEEL BETTER
IF SHE'D JUST BLAME ME.
LIKE SHE DID BEFORE.
IF SHE'D JUST SAY THAT
IT'S MY FAULT THAT RIMU'S GONE.
- THAT'S ENOUGH ALREADY.
CUT OUT THIS MOPING NONSENSE.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU TO FEEL
SORRY FOR YOURSELF, RIN.
- ASA. I...
- YOU'RE A GOOD PERSON AND
YOU'RE ALWAYS THERE
FOR A FRIEND WHEN
THEY NEED YOU.
YOU BUST YOUR BUTT TO HELP THEM
BECAUSE YOU GENUINELY CARE.
RIMU WAS ABLE TO SMILE AGAIN
BECAUSE OF YOU.
DID YOU FORGET THAT?
- YEAH BUT BECAUSE OF THAT
PRIMULA, SHE...
- OH, WOW, I CERTAINLY HOPE
YOU'RE NOT SAYING PRIMULA'S
SMILING AGAIN WAS A MISTAKE?
- THAT'S NOT.
- OF COURSE NOT.
SHE HAD THE MOST BEAUTIFUL SMILE
I'D EVER SEEN.
YOU KNOW SOMETHING? I KNOW
WHY SHE SMILED SO PRETTY.
SHE SMILED SO PRETTY BECAUSE OF
YOU, BECAUSE SHE'D MET YOU, RIN.
- YOU THINK SO, HUH?
- ARE YOU GONNA BE OKAY?
- WHAT THE HECK
HAVE I BEEN DOING?
I NEED TO BE THERE RIGHT NOW
FOR PRIMULA.
- YEAH.
- SITTING HERE ALL DEPRESSED
ISN'T DOING ANY GOOD.
WHAT THE HELL HAVE I BEEN DOING?
IF I WANNA SEE HER,
I CAN JUST DO THAT.
- THAT'S TRUE.
- I CAN'T SIT HERE.
I GOTTA GO AND SEE HER.
PRIMULA IS PART OF MY FAMILY.
- I BET SHE'S THERE WAITING.
- RIGHT. LISTEN, I KNOW
YOU WENT OUT OF YOUR WAY
TO COME AND FIND ME.
THANK YOU.
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING.
- WHAT'S A FRIEND FOR?
RIGHT?
- RIGHT.
- Sia: YOU'RE GONNA GO SEE RIMU?
- YES. THAT'S WHAT I'VE DECIDED.
- HOLD ON JUST A SECOND, RIN.
RIMU IS REALLY SICK
AND I THINK THAT...
- I KNOW THAT.
I ALSO KNOW WHAT CAUSED
THE SICKNESS TO HAPPEN
AND THAT THERE'S ONLY ONE CURE.
AND THAT'S WHY I HAVE TO BE
THERE FOR HER.
- BUT, IF SHE CONTINUES
HER TREATMENT
FOR JUST A LITTLE WHILE LONGER,
THEY SAY THAT
SHE MIGHT GET BETTER.
- THAT'S RIGHT. I
THINK THE BEST THING TO DO
IS TO WAIT A LITTLE
LONGER AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
- I'M NOT GOING TO ABANDON
A FAMILY MEMBER.
KAEDE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- I CAN REALLY UNDERSTAND
HOW YOU FEEL RIGHT NOW.
BUT SEEING PRIMULA
JUST WOULDN'T BE...
- KAEDE, TELL ME.
- JUST LISTEN, RIN.
I REALLY DON'T THINK THAT
RUSHING INTO THIS IS VERY SMART.
- SHE'S EXACTLY RIGHT,
LET'S NOT PUSH IT.
- AND YOU CALL YOURSELVES
POTENTIAL GIRLFRIENDS FOR RIN?
YOU'D HAVE TO BE
BLIND NOT TO NOTICE
HOW MUCH RIN'S BEEN SUFFERING.
THE WAY HE'S BEEN AGONIZING
AND HURTING OVER THIS.
BECAUSE HE WANTED TO PROTECT
SOMEONE PRECIOUS TO HIM
AND HE COULDN'T.
THINKING THERE WAS NOTHING
HE COULD DO.
HE WAS COMPLETELY
AND TOTALLY DESTROYED.
YOU DON'T GET IT. DON'T YOU SEE
THAT HE'S NOT HIMSELF.
HE'S NOT HIMSELF AT ALL.
- YOU SEE, ASA FINALLY
SLAPPED SOME SENSE INTO ME
AND MADE ME THINK.
WAITING ISN'T
GOING TO CHANGE ANYTHING.
IF I DON'T TAKE THE INITIATIVE,
I WON'T BE ABLE TO PROTECT
THE PEOPLE I CARE ABOUT.
I'M GOING.
I JUST DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
- THEN GO.
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU BELIEVE.
- WOW, SIA, THANKS.
- I'M COMING, TOO. I WANNA
GO WITH YOU TO SEE RIMU.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH, KAEDE.
- I...
I... NO.
I DON'T EVER WANNA LOSE A PERSON
I CARE ABOUT AGAIN. NOT EVER.
- NERINE.
- NO. WAIT.
- DO SOMETHING.
- RIGHT.
- Nerine: ♪ BUT I KNOW IT
IN MY HEART SOMEHOW ♪
♪ THAT YOU'LL
COME BACK SOMEDAY ♪
♪ AND THE TEARS
FALL DOWN LIKE RAIN ♪
♪ BECAUSE YOU'RE SO FAR AWAY ♪
- NERINE.
- I SING THESE WORDS ALTHOUGH
THE SONG ITSELF IS NOT MY OWN.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Rin: THAT BEAUTIFUL SMILE IS
ABOUT TO DISAPPEAR
FROM PRIMULA'S FACE.
BUT THERE'S NOTHING
THAT I CAN DO TO HELP HER.
- Nerine: I SING THESE WORDS
ALTHOUGH THE SONG
ITSELF IS NOT MY OWN.
IT BELONGS TO MY...
- Kaede: NEXT TIME ON SHUFFLE.
EPISODE 14 - "LYCORIS."
- Nerine: I ROBBED HER OF
EVERYTHING THAT SHE EVER WAS.