- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- THERE HE IS, YOU
GUYS! COME ON!
- Girl: WAIT UP!
- I SEE.
A NEW KIND OF COOKIE, HUH?
- YEP. IT'S CALLED
A TRICOLOR COOKIE.
WHEN IT'S FINISHED, I'LL
LET YOU HAVE THE PRIVILEGE
OF BEING THE FIRST
ONE TO TASTE IT!
- HOLD ON, DOESN'T THAT MAKE
ME SOME KINDA GUINEA PIG?
- WELL, IF THAT'S HOW
YOU'RE GONNA BE, RIN,
I'M NOT GONNA GIVE YOU ANY,
EVEN IF YOU TRY TO BEG ME.
- NO, I WAS JUST KIDDING.
NOTHING IN THE WORLD
WOULD MAKE ME HAPPIER
THAN EATING
YOUR COOKIES, ASA!
- ( grunting )
- I LOVE YOUR COOKIES,
IT WAS JUST A FIGURE OF SPEECH!
REALLY! I PROMISE!
- DO YOU THINK SHE MIGHT BE THE
GIRL THAT RIN IS IN LOVE WITH?
- I GUESS. MAYBE.
- MAYBE, HUH?
THOSE TWO MIGHT
BE A GOOD MATCH.
AND ASA IS A REALLY
GOOD PERSON, SO...
- WELL, YEAH, BUT. IT'S NOT LIKE
RIN HAS EXACTLY COME OUT
AND SAID IT TO
EITHER ONE OF US!
- DO YOU THINK THAT HE'S
SAID ANYTHING TO ASA?
- I'D BE WILLING TO
BET THAT HE HASN'T!
- SO, WHAT DO YOU
THINK WILL HAPPEN?
- I DON'T THINK WE CAN LET
THINGS STAY THIS WAY ANYMORE!
- MMM-HMM.
- WAIT, A DATE?
- YEP! WE THINK YOU SHOULD
GO ON A DATE WITH ASA!
- HOW COME YOU TWO ARE ASKING
ME TO DO THIS ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- ARE YOU SAYING IT'S
NOT SOMETHING
YOU ARE WILLING TO CONSIDER?
- NO, I'M WILLING
TO CONSIDER IT,
IT JUST SEEMS OUT OF THE BLUE.
- SO, YOU'RE OKAY WITH IT THEN?
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU TWO WOULD BRING
SOMETHING LIKE THIS
UP SO RANDOMLY?
- HONESTLY, ARE YOU
THAT CLUELESS?
- RIN, JUST LISTEN TO ME.
I THINK YOU NEED TO
TAKE THIS OPPORTUNITY
TO MAKE THINGS CLEAR!
- WHAT DO I NEED
TO MAKE CLEAR?
- YOU NEED TO MAKE A DECISION
ABOUT WHO IT IS THAT YOU LOVE.
- THE WAY THINGS ARE NOW,
IT IS REALLY DIFFICULT
FOR THE BOTH OF US.
SO, I GUESS THERE MUST
BE SOMEONE ELSE SPECIAL
IN YOUR LIFE, ISN'T THERE?
- Nerine: HEY, DON'T WORRY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GIVE
ME AN ANSWER RIGHT NOW.
FOR ALL I KNOW,
YOU MIGHT ALREADY HAVE A
SPECIAL GIRL IN YOUR LIFE.
- I'M SORRY.
- AND BESIDES,
IT'LL BE MUCH EASIER
FOR THE TWO OF US TO FIGHT OUR
COMPETITION IF OUR RIVAL KNOWS.
- ROMANTIC RIVALRY SHOULD
BE FAIR AND SQUARE.
PLUS, IN MY OPINION, COMPETITION
BRINGS OUT THE BEST IN EVERYONE!
- AND, IF ASA REALLY
IS OUR COMPETITION,
THEN WE'VE GOT A
WORTHY ADVERSARY.
- RIGHT?
- RIGHT.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THE BOTH OF YOU!
- LET'S GET RIGHT TO WORK!
- WAIT, HOLD ON
JUST ONE MINUTE.
YOU SAY I SHOULD MAKE IT CLEAR
BUT WHAT EXACTLY SHOULD I DO?
- I KNOW EXACTLY WHAT YOU...
- Itsuki: TELL HER HOW
YOU FEEL RIN, WHAT ELSE?
- HUH?
- SO, ARE YOU GOING TO TAKE
HER SOMEWHERE REALLY FUN RIN?
- WELL, YOU KNOW.
WE'LL GO WHEREVER!
- Nerine: DON'T BE LIKE THAT.
YOU'LL EARN A LOT OF POINTS
IF YOU TAKE HER SOME
PLACE SHE REALLY LIKES.
- WELL, WHAT KIND OF
PLACES DOES SHE LIKE?
- WELL, HOW ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO KNOW THAT?
- ( grunting in anger )
- Kaede: I WONDER WHAT
RIN IS DOING RIGHT NOW?
OH. HEY, TRY AND DO IT
SO IT WHIPS IN MORE AIR!
HE CAME HOME AND WENT
STRAIGHT OUT AGAIN.
I GUESS SIA AND THE OTHERS
WERE WITH HIM AS WELL.
- THEY SAID THEY WERE
TAKING RIN TO PLAN A DATE.
- WE ALL KNOW RIN'S
NOT QUALIFIED
TO MAKE THESE DECISIONS.
CONSIDERING THE GRAVITY
OF THE SITUATION,
IT IS UP TO ME TO CHOOSE
THE ULTIMATE DATE LOCATION!
BEHOLD! CUPID LAND!
- ( all exclaim )
- THE SEATS ON EVERY RIDE
ARE MADE FOR COUPLES!
IT'S MADE OF LOVERS,
BY LOVERS.
AND FOR LOVERS WHO ARE
LOOKING TO SHARE THEIR LOVE!
NO BETTER PLACE ON EARTH
TO CONFESS YOUR FEELINGS!
- ( girls exclaim )
- WOULDN'T SOMETHING
A LITTLE MORE
ON THE NORMAL SIDE BE BETTER?
- AND WHAT EXACTLY IS
"THE NORMAL SIDE" RIN?
- WELL, FOR EXAMPLE,
GO SEE A MOVIE OR SOMETHING.
- FOOL!
GO ON AN UTTERLY NORMAL DATE,
YOU'LL ONLY BE ABLE TO MAKE
AN UTTERLY NORMAL CONFESSION.
A CONFESSION OF LOVE SHOULD BE
A BEAUTIFUL AND DRAMATIC THING!
- I JUST THINK A NORMAL
DATE WOULD BE BEST!
- YOU JUST DON'T GET IT,
DO YOU?
THIS IS TRUE LOVE, BABY!
THERE'S NOTHING
NORMAL ABOUT IT!
- YES! I THINK THIS
IS A GREAT PLAN!
- NOW, LET'S MOVE ON TO
WORKING OUT THE DETAILS.
- ROGER THAT, CAPTAIN ITSUKI!
- I WILL DO EVERYTHING
THAT I CAN FOR YOU, SIR!
- HEY, HEY. HAVE YOU ALREADY
PICKED OUT THE SPOT WHERE
RIN SHOULD TELL
HER HE LOVES HER?
- ( girls chattering )
- Rin: WHAT ABOUT,
WHAT I WANNA DO?
- SO, YOU'RE FINALLY GOING
ON A DATE WITH RIN, HUH?
NOW YOU'LL BE...
- KAREHA! NOW DON'T START
IMAGINING WEIRD THINGS.
WE'RE JUST GOING OUT ON
A DATE TO HAVE A LITTLE FUN!
- GIVE IT UP, LET'S GO BACK
TO CLASS. COME ON!
- WELL, OKAY.
I'LL SEE YOU AT TEN IN FRONT
OF THE TRAIN STATION.
- ( sighs )
- SO, THE DATE IS
TOMORROW, RIGHT?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU THINK IT'LL BE ALRIGHT
IF I WEAR NORMAL CLOTHES?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
NO MATTER WHAT YOU WEAR,
FANCY OR NOT,
I'M SURE THAT ASA WILL BE
THRILLED JUST TO BE GOING
ON A DATE WITH YOU.
THIS IS THE FIRST DATE, RIGHT?
I GUESS NORMALLY, IT WOULD BE
ALL THREE OF US OUT AND ABOUT.
YOU, AND ASA, AND ME.
- SORRY ABOUT THAT.
THIS WASN'T MY IDEA.
- IT'S NO BIG DEAL,
I PROMISED RIMU THAT
I WOULD TAKE HER
SHOPPING FOR CLOTHES
ALL DAY ON SUNDAY.
SO, IT'S NOT LIKE
I WOULD'VE BEEN ABLE TO COME
ALONG ANYWAY. RIGHT, RIMU?
- MMM-HMM.
- I'LL BE BACK. I'M GONNA GO
MAKE A FRESH POT OF TEA.
- GOING "ALL OUT" AND FANCY
LIKE THAT WOULD BE WEIRDNESS.
BUT DRESSING TOO CASUAL
WOULD BE KINDA WEIRD TOO.
WHAT'S UP WITH ME?
I'M REALLY NOT THE KIND OF GIRL
WHO STRESSES OUT OVER
WHAT TO WEAR ON A DATE.
MAN, THIS IS HOPELESS.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT
MAKING ME DINNER TONIGHT.
- ALL RIGHT.
THAT WON'T BE A PROBLEM, RIN.
- WELL, WISH ME LUCK THEN!
- OH, KAEDE!
- HEY, DOESN'T A LITTLE
YARD WORK SOUND FUN?
- Nerine: THERE HE IS!
- Itsuki: AND EXACTLY
AS I PREDICTED,
RIN IS LATE JUST
LIKE HE ALWAYS IS!
- Mayumi: HEY,
SHE REALLY WENT ALL OUT!
WELL, HE IS LATE,
BUT HE'S HERE.
- Itsuki: THAT'S IT,
RIN, LAY ON THE CHARM!
- WOW, ASA LOOKS
ABSOLUTELY GORGEOUS!
- IT MUST BE SO NICE TO ACTUALLY
GET TO GO OUT ON A DATE!
- YEAH.
- SO, I GUESS WE SHOULD GO.
- UH...
- HE JUST MISSED THE PERFECT
OPPORTUNITY TO GRAB HER HAND!
- I HAVE A HORRIBLE FEELING THIS
DATE IS GOING TO BE A NIGHTMARE.
- HERE WE GO EVERYONE!
WE HAVE TO BE THERE TO GIVE
OUR COMPLETE SUPPORT TO RIN!
- THAT'S RIGHT,
SO THAT HE CAN CLEARLY
CONVEY HIS FEELINGS TO
THE GIRL HE LOVES THE MOST.
- AND FOR OUR OWN SAKES TOO!
- THAT LOOKS LIKE FUN.
YOU WANNA GO ON
THIS RIDE FIRST?
- WELL, MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T
GO ON THIS ONE AFTER ALL.
- MOVE IT! COME ON, NOW!
- EXCUSE ME! WHAT THE...
- MOVE IT OR LOSE IT,
MISTER MAN!
- WAIT FOR ME, RIN!
- WELCOME TO THE
MERRY-GO-ROUND OF LOVE!
- ( carousel music playing )
- LISTEN, YOU SURE
I'M NOT HEAVY?
- NO, I THINK I CAN HANDLE IT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- DON'T BE EMBARRASSED.
JUST HOLD ON TIGHT TO ME, OKAY?
- YES MA'AM!
- SIR, MA'AM, PLEASE DO NOT
BEHAVE RECKLESSLY ON THE RIDE!
- THESE COFFEE CUPS SURE ARE
SOMETHING ELSE, DON'T YOU THINK?
YOU KNOW, THE WAY THEY
SPIN AROUND REAL GENTLY
AND ARE NICE AND
RELAXING AND STUFF.
( laughs nervously )
- Nerine: WHY ARE THEY
SITTING SO FAR APART?
- OH, RIN.
YOU'VE LEFT US NO CHOICE.
I DIDN'T WANT TO DO THIS,
BUT I GUESS IT'S UP TO US NOW!
- YOU'RE RIGHT. LET'S DO IT!
- ( both scream )
- YOU DID IT, NERINE!
- I'LL BET YOU THAT RIN IS
HAVING THE TIME OF HIS LIFE NOW!
- SIR, MA'AM, PLEASE DO NOT
BEHAVE RECKLESSLY ON THE RIDE!
- Asa: HERE!
SO, ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY, RIN?
- I'LL BE ALL RIGHT. HOW ABOUT
YOU, YOU FEELING OKAY?
- RIDING ROLLER COASTERS DOESN'T
BOTHER ME, SO I'LL BE FINE.
- I CAN'T EVEN HANDLE THAT
COFFEE CUP RIDE. IT'S TOUGH.
- DO YOU WANNA TAKE A
BREAK FOR A LITTLE WHILE?
- I THINK I'D BETTER.
NO, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK I'LL BE OKAY!
ALL RIGHT.
I THINK WE'RE READY TO GO.
- SO, LET'S SEE.
- LET'S GO ON THAT ONE NEXT!
THIS IS A LITTLE MORE
RELAXING, DON'T YOU THINK?
- YOU KNOW, IT'S GETTING PRETTY
LATE, WE'D BETTER HURRY UP.
WE STILL NEED TO
HIT THE PIRATE SHIP.
AND WE CAN'T MISS
THE HAUNTED VILLAGE.
- YOU KNOW,
THERE'S NO NEED TO RUSH,
IT'S NOT LIKE THEY'RE
GOING ANYWHERE.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
- SINCE YOU DON'T LOOK LIKE
YOU'RE GONNA THROW UP ANYMORE,
YOU THINK YOU WANNA
GIVE IT ANOTHER GO?
- YOU BET I DO.
I SUPPOSE WE OUGHT TO TRY THE...
- LET'S GET ON THE GO CARTS!
BETTER GET DRIVING RIN
OR I'M GONNA HIT YOU!
- YOU'VE HIT ME ENOUGH ALREADY!
- ( laughs )
- ( both scream )
- RIN. SMILE! NOW, SAY CHEESE!
- ( camera clicks )
- SORRY FOR DRAGGING YOU
AROUND EVERYWHERE.
GUESS OUR LUNCH SORT OF TURNED
INTO A LATE AFTERNOON SNACK.
- OH, DON'T WORRY. IT'S
REALLY NOT A PROBLEM AT ALL.
- Itsuki: HAVE LUNCH
AT PASTA HOUSE!
- THIS IS SO NOT GOOD.
EVERYBODY WORKED SO HARD
TO COME UP WITH THIS PLAN.
AND NOW, EVERYTHING WE'RE
DOING IS COMPLETELY DIFFERENT.
- RIN, ARE YOU NOT HAVING
FUN HANGING OUT WITH ME?
- WHAT? NO, REALLY.
I'M HAVING A GREAT TIME.
- OKAY.
- IS IT JUST ME OR ARE
THEY ACTING STRANGE?
- WHAT DID I SAY, I TOLD
HIM TO TAKE HER
TO THE PASTA
HOUSE, DIDN'T I?
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
THAT FOOL DESERVES WHATEVER
HE GETS FOR IGNORING
MY FLAWLESS DATING PLAN!
- EVEN THOUGH EVERYTHING DIDN'T
GO EXACTLY AS WE PLANNED,
IT STILL LOOKED TO ME LIKE ASA
WAS HAVING FUN, DON'T YOU THINK?
- YEAH. I THOUGHT THAT THINGS
WERE LOOKING PRETTY DARN GOOD.
- I AM HAVING FUN. HONESTLY.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
SEE? DID YOU THINK I WAS
REALLY GONNA HIT YOU?
- NO, I...
- THAT WAS TASTY.
SLIGHTLY RIN-FLAVORED.
- Mayumi: I LIKE
WHAT I'M SEEING!
- THEY REALLY DO LOOK GOOD.
- YEAH. I'M GLAD FOR THEM.
- SO, TELL ME,
WHAT DO YOU WANNA DO NOW?
- UH...
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- HOW ABOUT GOING FOR A
RIDE ON THE FERRIS WHEEL?
- THIS IS FINALLY IT, BUDDY!
- I'M LOCKED AND LOADED
AND READY TO GO.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- I THINK WE SHOULD
ALL JUST WAIT HERE.
- WHY WOULD WE DO THAT?
WE'VE FINALLY GOTTEN...
- WELL, ALL RIGHT THEN.
- I GUESS YOU GUYS ARE RIGHT.
- I'M VERY SORRY.
BELIEVE ME, I AM.
- IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
- OH, NO. I'M OKAY. NOTHING'S
WRONG AT ALL, REALLY.
HEY, YOU KNOW.
I WAS KIND OF THINKING,
- WHAT?
- NOTHING.
IT WAS JUST SOMETHING
STUPID, FORGET IT.
- Asa: YOU KNOW, I HAD A WHOLE
LOT OF FUN WITH YOU TODAY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE,
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
YOU'VE EVER ASKED ME OUT ON
A REAL DATE. IT MADE ME HAPPY.
IT MADE ME REALLY HAPPY.
OH, AND I HAVE SOMETHING HERE
THAT I WANNA GIVE YOU,
IF IT'S OKAY.
THESE AREN'T THE TRI-COLOR
COOKIES I WAS TELLING YOU ABOUT.
BUT I THOUGHT YOU WOULDN'T
MIND REGULAR COOKIES.
- THEY LOOK JUST
ABOUT PERFECT TO ME!
- I BAKED THEM FOR YOU
TO SAY "THANKS" FOR TODAY.
- HUH? YOU REALLY DIDN'T
HAVE TO DO THAT!
- NOW OPEN UP AND SAY "AH"!
- Asa: HOW ABOUT WE
TRY IT LIKE THIS?
- ( gasps )
- WAIT, ASA, I...
- ( creaking )
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR RIDING WITH US TODAY!
- YOU HAD YOUR CHANCE!
DID YOU WANT TO TALK
TO ME ABOUT SOMETHING?
THERE WAS SOMETHING YOU WANTED
TO SAY TO ME WHILE WE'RE HERE,
WASN'T THERE RIN?
- WELL, IT'S JUST THAT I...
- BUT, YOU KNOW, I'M NOT SURE
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA RIGHT NOW,
IT'S KINDA WEIRD WITH
EVERYONE WATCHING.
I'M SO ON TO YOU PEOPLE.
YOU CAN ALL COME ON
OUT NOW, ALL RIGHT?
YEP, THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
- BUT, HOW DID YOU
KNOW THEY WERE HERE?
- I NOTICED WHAT
YOU WERE DOING.
YOU WERE TRYING TO
PLAN OUR DATE
ACCORDING TO WHAT THIS
THING SAYS, RIGHT?
- NO. IT'S NOTHING
BAD, IT'S JUST...
I DON'T REALLY HAVE A CLUE
WHAT TO DO ON A DATE,
SO I WAS...
WELL, I THOUGHT...
THIS WASN'T MY IDEA.
HONESTLY, I JUST WANTED
TO GO ON A NORMAL DATE,
BUT ITSUKI SAID THAT
WASN'T GOOD ENOUGH.
AND THEN, OF COURSE,
THAT LEAD...
- NO, I THINK I GET IT.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN REALLY
STRESSFUL FOR YOU WITH
ME TRYING TO DO
MY OWN THING, HUH?
- LISTEN, IT'S JUST...
I ONLY FELT BAD BECAUSE SIA
AND NERINE WENT TO A LOT
OF TROUBLE TO MAKE THE
DATE PLANS FOR ME.
I MEAN, THE ONLY REASON
I EVEN WENT ON THE DATE,
WAS BECAUSE THEY TOLD ME TO,
YOU KNOW?
AND I WANTED TO DO WHAT
I COULD FOR BOTH OF THEM!
- ( all gasp )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU, RIN.
YOUR FRIENDS TELL YOU WHAT TO DO
AND YOU JUST DO WHAT THEY SAY?
SO, WHERE WAS YOUR HEART
IN ALL OF THIS, HUH?
WAS THERE EVEN ONE TINY
THING IN THIS ENTIRE DAY
THAT WAS YOUR IDEA?
ONE MOMENT THAT YOU
WANTED TO SHARE WITH ME?
DID YOU EVEN WANT
TO GO OUT WITH ME?
- NO, WAIT. ASA, LISTEN!
- THIS IS OUR FAULT,
ALL THIS HAPPENED BECAUSE
WE FORCED RIN TO DO IT
AND HOPED THAT IT WOULD...
- I'M NOT TALKING
TO THE TWO OF YOU!
EVERYONE HERE HAS THEIR
OWN SELFISH REASONS
TO TRY AND GET YOU
TO DO THINGS, RIN.
BUT, IN THE END,
ALL THAT MATTERS IS
THAT YOU DO WHAT
YOU TRULY WANNA DO.
BE HONEST WITH ME, WERE YOU
FORCED TO GO ON THIS DATE?
- OF COURSE NOT, ASA.
I WANTED TO TAKE YOU OUT!
- NEXT TIME, RIN,
DO IT BECAUSE YOU WANT TO
AND NOT CAUSE THEY SAID TO.
- HEY, LISTEN.
I REALLY FEEL JUST HORRIBLE.
- I'M SO SORRY, RIN.
- NO, IT'S OKAY. I WAS WRONG.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- I'VE GOT TO TAKE MATTERS
INTO MY OWN HANDS
OR NOTHING WILL EVER CHANGE.
GUESS I LEARNED THE HARD WAY.
NEXT TIME, I'LL HAVE THE
COURAGE. TO TELL HER HOW I FEEL.
I'M BACK.
- HEY THERE,
WELCOME BACK HOME, RIN!
- OH. WHEN I LEFT,
DIDN'T I TELL YOU I WOULD NOT
BE NEEDING ANY DINNER?
- OH MY GOSH,
I COMPLETELY FORGOT,
I'M SORRY.
I'LL CLEAN IT UP RIGHT AWAY!
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Kaede: RIN. RIN. RIN...
NO MATTER HOW MANY TIMES
I CALL YOUR NAME,
I CAN'T PUT MY FEARS TO REST.
WHAT'S COME OVER ME?
- Primula: NEXT
TIME ON SHUFFLE,
EPISODE 19,
"UNFORGETTABLE SENTIMENTS."
- Rin: KAEDE, I...