- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Nerine: DO YOU REMEMBER
THE FIRST TIME WE MET?
I WAS SITTING ON
THIS SWING SINGING
AND YOU TOLD ME
I HAD A BEAUTIFUL VOICE.
- YEAH... I COULD NEVER FORGET
HOW PRETTY YOUR VOICE IS.
- THAT WASN'T MY VOICE
YOU HEARD.
IT ISN'T CAPABLE OF
CREATING SUCH BEAUTY.
THE REAL ME COULD NEVER SOUND
LIKE THAT.
- BUT I DID HEAR YOU.
- NO, THE SONG AND THE VOICE
YOU HEARD AREN'T MINE.
THEY BELONG TO SOMEONE
VERY CLOSE TO ME.
- I DON'T GET IT,
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- THEY'RE A PART OF
MY OTHER SELF.
LYCORIS.
- LYCORIS?
- SHE WAS A SEPARATE PART OF ME,
MY BETTER HALF.
I AM THE ONE WHO'S RESPONSIBLE
FOR ROBBING HER OF EVERYTHING
THAT SHE REALLY WAS.
- WAIT, JUST BACK UP A SECOND,
THIS DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE AT ALL.
- OF COURSE IT DOESN'T.
I'M SORRY, RIN.
- I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHO THIS LYCORIS IS.
- YOU KNOW THE STORY BEHIND RIMU
AND HOW SHE'S AN ARTIFICIAL
LIFE FORM CREATED
BY THE GODS AND DEMONS FOR
EXPERIMENTATION, RIGHT?
- YEAH, AND I DON'T CARE WHO'S
LIFE THE RESEARCH IS SAVING,
USING PRIMULA AS A GUINEA PIG
IS JUST WRONG TO ME.
- RIMU ISN'T THE FIRST.
IT TOOK THEM A FEW TIMES TO
GET EXACTLY WHAT THEY WANTED
AND THERE WERE TWO ARTIFICIAL
LIFE FORMS CREATED BEFORE HER.
- THEN YOU'RE TELLING ME
THEY ACTUALLY HAVE
THREE INNOCENT BEINGS
LOCKED UP FOR EXPERIMENTATION?
- NO.
THE FIRST WAS A GIRL
CHOSEN FROM AMONG THE DEMONS.
THEY PLANNED TO REINFORCE
HER BODY.
THIS WOULD ALLOW HER
TO CONTROL GREAT MAGIC.
HOWEVER...
HER BODY COULDN'T TOLERATE
THE INTENSIFIED MAGIC.
AND IT CONSUMED HER AND
EVERYONE IN THE LABORATORY.
OBVIOUSLY, THE RESEARCH TEAM
LEARNED THEIR LESSON.
THEY REALIZED THEY NEEDED
THE PARTICIPATION OF SOMEONE
WHO ALREADY POSSESSED
POWERFUL MAGIC.
THEY NEEDED A GIRL
ALMOST AS POWERFUL
AS THE RULER OF THE DEMONS.
- I'M NOT SURE
I WANNA HEAR THIS.
- THEY NEEDED ME.
OF COURSE MY FATHER
WOULD NEVER ALLOW THEM
TO RISK PUTTING
ME IN SUCH DANGER.
SO THE RESEARCH TEAM WAS
LEFT WITH NO ALTERNATIVE
BUT TO DUPLICATE MY CELLS
AND PRODUCE ANOTHER ME.
- YOU MEAN, THEY CLONED YOU?
- AND THEN CREATED LYCORIS.
SHE WAS A NICE GIRL.
SHE KNEW SHE WAS CREATED
TO BE AN EXPERIMENTAL SUBJECT.
BUT THAT NEVER STOPPED HER
FROM SMILING.
- OH, NERINE,
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- I'M OKAY.
- I HOPE THAT YOU
START FEELING BETTER SOON.
FATHER TOLD ME THE REASON
I'M ALWAYS GETTING SICK
IS BECAUSE MY MAGIC
IS TOO POWERFUL
AND MY BODY HASN'T GROWN
ENOUGH TO HANDLE IT YET.
- DON'T WORRY, NERINE,
I WON'T LET ANYTHING HAPPEN.
I'LL MAKE YOU BETTER,
I PROMISE.
- WHAT?
- IF THE EXPERIMENTS ON ME
GO AS PLANNED,
THEY SAY THEY'LL BE
ABLE TO CURE ANY ILLNESS,
NO MATTER WHAT.
SO I KNOW THEY'LL BE
ABLE TO MAKE YOU BETTER.
- I HOPE SO.
- I KNOW.
HOW ABOUT I SING YOU A SONG TO
TAKE YOUR MIND OFF HOW YOU FEEL?
♪ FROM THE FIRST TIME
THAT WE MET ♪
♪ I KNEW WE'D BE
THE BEST OF FRIENDS ♪
♪ I KNEW THAT YOU WERE SOMEONE ♪
♪ WHO WOULD BE THERE
TILL THE END ♪
- SOMEBODY ONCE TOLD ME THE
EXPERIMENTS WERE EXCRUCIATING.
IF THAT'S TRUE,
THEN SHE NEVER ONCE LET ON
THAT SHE WAS IN SUCH PAIN.
- SHE MUST HAVE BEEN STRONG.
- LYCORIS WAS VERY KIND, TOO.
THE EXPERIMENTS BEGAN
TO GROW MORE FREQUENT.
SHE RARELY LEFT THE LAB
AND I BEGAN TO SEE
LESS AND LESS OF HER.
SHE MUST HAVE BEEN
SO LONELY AT FIRST,
BUT THAT'S WHEN SHE MET RIMU.
- SO, PRIMULA KNEW LYCORIS?
- SHE WAS PRACTICALLY
RIMU'S SISTER
AND FOR A WHILE,
THEY WERE ALL THEY HAD.
- Eustoma: HAS HER CONDITION
IMPROVED AT ALL?
- Researcher: WE'RE TRYING
EVERYTHING WE CAN.
BUT THERE IS THE POSSIBILITY
THAT SHE'LL NEVER
REGAIN CONSCIOUSNESS.
- THEN WE'RE NEARING THE POINT
WHERE WE HAVE ONLY ONE
OPTION LEFT TO SAVE HER.
- YES, WE BELIEVE THAT
IF WE RESET HER EMOTIONS
THEN THE CHANGES WILL
POTENTIALLY REVIVE HER.
- AN UNFORTUNATE LOSS.
- BUT, SIRE, PRIMULA IS SIMPLY
AN INDEPENDENT LIFE FORM.
SHE HAS NEITHER SIBLINGS
NOR PARENTS
OR ANY EMOTIONAL ATTACHMENTS.
THERE'S NO ONE TO MOURN...
- YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
THAT'S NOT TRUE, NOW IS IT?
PRIMULA?
- HELLO.
MY NAME'S LYCORIS.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- PRIMULA.
- PRIMULA, HUH?
IT'S NICE TO MEET YOU.
♪ THOUGH WE MAY BE FAR APART ♪
♪ OUR PATHS WILL CROSS AGAIN
SOME SHINING DAY ♪
♪ WE'RE BENEATH
THE SAME BLUE SKY ♪
♪ AND THE WIND
CARRIES OUR LOVE ♪
- LYCORIS.
- I SEE. I LIKE KNOWING PRIMULA
HAD SOMEONE TO CARE FOR HER.
I HAD NO IDEA.
SO, WHAT HAPPENED TO LYCORIS?
IS SHE STILL WITH
PRIMULA IN THE LAB?
THEY'RE NOT STILL CONDUCTING
EXPERIMENTS ON HER, ARE THEY?
- LYCORIS NO LONGER EXISTS.
- HUH?
- RIGHT NOW, I'M ALL
THAT'S LEFT OF HER.
LYCORIS SHE...
SHE SACRIFICED HERSELF
IN ORDER TO SAVE MY LIFE, RIN.
- I HOPE NERINE'S ALL RIGHT.
- I'M SURE SHE'S OKAY,
SHE'S GOT RIN WITH HER.
- RIGHT, I'M SURE SHE'S FINE.
- I'M SORRY. I FEEL
LIKE THIS IS MY FAULT,
I SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN SO HARSH.
- OH, YOU WEREN'T.
- I'M ASHAMED, ASA.
YOU WERE BEING HONEST.
- SIA.
- I WAS TRYING TO BE CONSIDERATE
OF RIN'S FEELINGS TOWARDS RIMU.
BUT WHEN I HEARD WHAT YOU SAID,
I REALIZED I WAS FOOLING
MYSELF INTO THINKING THAT.
- I KNEW HE WAS PRETTY
BROKEN UP ABOUT RIMU,
BUT MAYBE WE SHOULD HAVE
BEEN A LITTLE MORE...
- NO WAY.
I THINK YOU TWO HAD EVERY RIGHT
TO SAY WHAT YOU DID.
YOU WERE JUST CONCERNED FOR HIM.
CONSIDERING THE CONDITION
RIMU'S IN,
GOING TO SEE HER COULD
POTENTIALLY BE VERY DANGEROUS.
TRUST ME, I AM AWARE OF THAT.
SO I CAN UNDERSTAND
YOUR RELUCTANCE,
YOU JUST CARE ABOUT HIM AND
YOU DIDN'T WANT HIM TO GET HURT.
BUT THERE ARE SOME THINGS THAT
ARE MORE IMPORTANT THAN THAT,
AND THERE ARE TIMES WHEN
A PERSON HAS TO TAKE A RISK.
ESPECIALLY FOR SOMEONE
YOU CARE ABOUT.
I'M BEING UNUSUALLY
SERIOUS TODAY, HUH?
HOW 'BOUT I MAKE US SOME TEA?
- THAT'S OKAY, I CAN GET IT.
- I GOT IT, I GOT IT.
I KNOW THIS HOUSE WELL EN...
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- ASA, WHAT'S WRONG?
- SHE SACRIFICED
HERSELF. REALLY?
- YES.
- BUT WHY?
- SINCE LYCORIS WAS MY CLONE,
HER LIFE WAS UNSTABLE.
THE TECHNOLOGY FOR CLONING
IN THE DEMON WORLD
ISN'T EXACTLY PERFECT.
IT'S NOT MUCH BETTER
THAN THE HUMAN TECHNOLOGY.
SO HER PHYSICAL STRUCTURE WAS
ALREADY SOMEWHAT VOLATILE
AND THE EXPERIMENTS ON HER
ONLY MADE IT WORSE.
- THEN WHY DIDN'T
ANYONE STOP THE EXPERIMENTS?
- SHE WAS BORN WITH A BODY
THAT WAS NEVER GOING
TO LIVE FOR VERY LONG.
AND EVEN THOUGH YOU'D NEVER
GUESS IT BY HOW HAPPY SHE WAS,
SHE MUST HAVE KNOWN.
AROUND THAT TIME, I CAME DOWN
WITH A SERIOUS ILLNESS.
- THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
YOU CAN DO.
- Doctor: NOT EVEN OUR HEALING
MAGIC IS WORKING FOR HER.
I'M SORRY, BUT THERE'S
NOTHING WE CAN DO.
- THAT CAN'T BE RIGHT.
- ( gasping )
- LYCORIS.
- I WANT YOU TO USE MY LIFE
TO SAVE HER.
IF YOU GIVE HER MY REMAINING
LIFE ENERGY,
THEN SHE'LL HAVE ENOUGH
STRENGTH TO RECOVER.
- YES, LYCORIS WAS CLONED BY
EXTRACTING VITALITY FROM NERINE.
IF WE RETURN THAT ORIGINAL
LIFE FORCE TAKEN FROM HER,
WE SHOULD BE ABLE TO SAVE HER.
- YES.
WAIT. IF WE DO THAT,
YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO...
- I KNOW WHAT'LL HAPPEN.
BUT ALL THAT MATTERS TO
ME IS SAVING THE LIFE
OF SOMEONE I CARE ABOUT.
- LYCORIS AND I BECAME ONE
AND BECAUSE SHE GAVE ME
HER LIFE, I AM ALL THAT'S LEFT.
MY LIFE IS WHAT
REMAINS OF LYCORIS.
- I SEE.
- AND IF THAT WASN'T ENOUGH,
I TOOK EVEN MORE FROM HER.
I TOOK WHO SHE WAS.
THERE WAS SOMETHING MY FATHER
AND THE DOCTORS DIDN'T REALIZE
ABOUT TRANSFERRING
HER LIFE TO ME.
- WHAT?
- WHEN OUR TWO LIVES
WERE MERGED,
I INHERITED ALL OF
LYCORIS' TRAITS,
EVERYTHING THAT MADE HER
WHO SHE WAS.
I ABSORBED HER MEMORIES AND HER
EMOTIONS, ALL OF HER TALENTS.
THE SINGING VOICE YOU SO GREATLY
PRAISED ISN'T EVEN MINE.
HER VOICE WAS KNOWN THROUGHOUT
THE ENTIRE WORLD OF THE DEMONS.
IT LEFT NO ONE UNMOVED.
I STOLE THE THING
THAT MADE HER BEAUTIFUL.
- NERINE, YOU CAN'T
BLAME YOURSELF.
- BUT I DID STEAL IT FROM HER,
I ROBBED HER OF HER LIFE.
AND I STOLE HER VOICE, THE ONE
THING SHE CHERISHED THE MOST.
NO. THERE'S SOMETHING
EVEN WORSE.
I TOOK SOMETHING
EVEN MORE PRECIOUS
THAN HER SINGING VOICE, RIN.
- WHAT WAS IT?
- I TOOK HER...
( sobs )
- TELL ME.
- I'M SORRY. I JUST
DON'T THINK I COULD HANDLE
LOSING SOMEBODY
CLOSE TO ME AGAIN.
- BUT, NERINE, I...
- I'VE ALREADY LET
ONE PERSON I LOVE TO DIE
AND I COULD NEVER
FORGIVE MYSELF,
IF I WERE TO LET THE SAME
HAPPEN TO RIMU,
BUT I DON'T KNOW
IF THERE'S ANYTHING I CAN...
I'M SORRY, RIN.
- NERINE.
- Rin: I'M HOME.
- RIN, SOMETHING TERRIBLE
HAPPENED. IT'S ASA.
- ( telephone ringing )
- Ama: YES? OH, HI, RIN.
- HOW'S ASA,
IS SHE FEELING BETTER?
- YEAH, SHE'S FEELING OKAY NOW.
I GUESS SHE MUST HAVE
FAINTED EARLIER
AND SCARED POOR KAEDE
HALF TO DEATH,
BUT THERE'S NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
YEAH, SHE'S SLEEPING SOUNDLY
RIGHT NOW.
MM-HMM, NO PROBLEM.
HER HEALTH HAS
ALWAYS BEEN FRAGILE,
SO STUFF LIKE THIS
USED TO HAPPEN A LOT
WHEN SHE WAS YOUNGER.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
HER HEALTH IS FRAGILE?
- ( chuckles ) NO, REALLY,
IT'S NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
I PROMISE YOU SHE'S FINE.
- WAIT, AMA, ARE YOU SURE?
- I'M SORRY, THE SOUP
I MADE FOR HER IS STILL
HEATING ON THE STOVE,
I REALLY NEED TO GO.
BYE, RIN.
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO THINK ABOUT THAT.
WELL, AMA SAID THAT
ASA'S DOING OKAY NOW.
- OH, THANK GOODNESS.
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- OH, NO,
I'M JUST REALLY EXHAUSTED.
- I DON'T EVER WANNA LOSE
A PERSON I CARE ABOUT AGAIN.
NOT EVER.
- WAS I WRONG?
THE ONLY THING I COULD THINK OF
WAS GOING TO SEE PRIMULA.
AND I IGNORED EVERYBODY ELSE.
I WAS ONLY TRYING TO HELP HER.
BUT I WAS SO FIXATED ON IT
THAT I COULDN'T SEE THAT I WAS
HURTING THE PEOPLE AROUND ME.
- ( knock at door )
- RIN? CAN I COME IN?
HEY, THERE, WANT COFFEE?
- SURE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- NOTHING.
- KAEDE?
- YEAH?
- THANKS FOR THE COFFEE.
- AND YOU CALL YOURSELVES
POTENTIAL GIRLFRIENDS FOR RIN?
- I MEAN, WHAT DO YOU
SAY TO THAT?
- POOR ASA.
I WISH YOU WERE HERE.
YOU'D KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- RIN, WHAT'S UP WITH NERINE,
I HAVEN'T SEEN HER.
- YEAH, IT'S KIND OF WEIRD. IT'S
NOT LIKE HER TO MISS SCHOOL.
DID SHE CATCH A COLD
OR SOMETHING?
- IF THAT'S THE CASE, I'LL DO
MY BEST TO RESTORE HER HEALTH.
I WON'T EVEN LEAVE HER BED
UNTIL SHE'S BETTER.
- DON'T YOU MEAN
"LEAVE HER BEDSIDE"?
- NO. I DON'T THINK IT'S A COLD
OR ANYTHING.
- WELL, HAS SHE
BEEN MOODY LATELY?
IT COULD BE HER TIME
OF THE... ( groans )
- RIN, IS THERE SOMETHING
YOU'RE NOT TELLING US?
- MAYBE.
- NO, ASA IS ABSENT TODAY.
- OH, SHE IS?
- YOU LOOK A LITTLE WORRIED
ABOUT HER.
- NO, I'M SURE SHE'S FINE.
I JUST KIND OF NEEDED HER ADVICE
ON SOMETHING.
IT'S NOTHING IMPORTANT,
I'LL JUST TALK TO HER TOMORROW.
- YOU COULD ALWAYS JUST GO
SEE HER INSTEAD OF WAITING.
- HUH?
- IF YOU NEED TO ASK HER
FOR SOME ADVICE,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST GO
VISIT HER, RIN?
- NO, IT'S NOTHING.
- I'M SURE ASA WANTS TO SEE YOU
AS MUCH AS YOU WANT TO SEE HER.
- YEAH, I SUPPOSE.
I GUESS I'LL GO SEE HER.
- Asa: THANKS FOR DROPPING IN
TO CHECK ON ME,
I'VE BEEN SO FREAKIN' BORED.
- HOW' ARE YOU FEELING?
- I THINK IT'S JUST
HEAT EXHAUSTION.
KIND OF SAD SINCE
BEING ENERGETIC
IS MY ONLY REDEEMING TRAIT.
- YEAH, IT'S A LITTLE WEIRD.
- COME ON. THAT'S WHEN
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO TELL ME
THAT I HAVE MORE THAN
ONE REDEEMING TRAIT.
- OH, I'M SORRY,
I DIDN'T REALIZE THAT YOU
WERE FISHING FOR COMPLIMENTS.
THERE'S ALSO
YOUR SENSE OF MODESTY.
- IF I WASN'T STUCK IN BED,
I'D KNOCK YOU TO THE FLOOR
WITH MY SENSE OF
MODESTY, YOU JERK.
- ( laughing )
- BUT REALLY. I AM RELIEVED
TO SEE YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
- YEAH. I'M FINE.
SORRY TO MAKE YOU WORRY.
SO, YOU GONNA TELL ME
WHAT HAPPENED?
THERE'S SOMETHING YOU WANT
TO TALK ABOUT, RIGHT?
- AM I THAT OBVIOUS?
- YOU DON'T KNOW
THE MEANING OF SUBTLETY.
WELL, COME ON AND
GET ON WITH IT.
LET'S HEAR WHAT IT IS ALREADY.
- Rin: THE TRUTH IS...
- ( knocking at door )
- NERINE, I'M LEAVING
FOR THE DEMON WORLD.
- IS RIMU...
- NO, NO, THERE STILL HAVEN'T
BEEN ANY NEW DEVELOPMENTS
WITH PRIMULA'S CONDITION.
SHIN HAS SOMETHING HE NEEDS TO
DISCUSS WITH ME THAT CAN'T WAIT.
WELL, IF ANYTHING HAPPENS,
I WILL CALL YOU.
TRY TO GET SOME REST NOW, OKAY?
- Asa: I SEE.
SO, NERINE SAID THAT?
- YEAH. AND IT'S NOT LIKE
I'VE CHANGED MY MIND
ABOUT WANTING TO SEE PRIMULA.
I MEAN, SHE'S PART OF MY FAMILY.
I FEEL LIKE I HAVE TO BE THERE
FOR HER, BUT...
- BUT WHAT?
- HONESTLY, I JUST DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO ANYMORE.
- RIN, LISTEN.
YOU DO REALIZE I'M NOT MAKING
SOME THOUGHTLESS DECISION
BY RECOMMENDING
YOU GO SEE RIMU, RIGHT?
- WELL, SURE.
- I UNDERSTAND HER PAIN.
I'VE BEEN THERE.
- WHAT'RE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- THERE WAS A TIME IN MY LIFE
WHEN I WAS BASICALLY A
PRISONER TO MY OWN BODY,
AND I HATED MY MOTHER FOR IT.
THIS WAS BEFORE
I MET YOU AND KAEDE.
I HAD SOME PRETTY SERIOUS HEALTH
PROBLEMS WHEN I WAS A KID.
I WAS SICK ALL THE TIME,
BUT EVEN WHEN I WASN'T,
MY BODY WAS IN SO MUCH PAIN,
I RARELY WENT TO SCHOOL.
- ( coughs )
- ( children laughing )
- ( sobbing )
- ( knock at the door )
- Ama: ASA? ARE YOU AWAKE?
HEY, SWEETIE.
HOPE YOU'RE HUNGRY,
I MADE YOU A DELICIOUS SOUP
AND IT'S CHOCK
FULL OF NUTRIENTS.
SO IT'LL HELP YOU GET
BACK ON YOUR FEET IN NO TIME.
WELL, IT'S A BEAUTIFUL DAY.
LET'S OPEN THESE CURTAINS.
GET SOME HEALTHY
SUNLIGHT IN HERE.
- DON'T OPEN THEM.
- BUT, ASA...
- I DON'T WANT THEM
OPEN, STUPID.
- OH, SORRY.
WELL...
I THINK YOU'LL LIKE THE SOUP.
I TRIED USING SOME APPLES AND
HONEY TO SWEETEN IT UP FOR YOU
AND IT TURNED OUT
PRETTY DELICIOUS.
YOU MUST BE HUNGRY, TRY SOME.
HERE, I'LL BLOW ON IT, SO IT'S
NOT TOO HOT FOR YOU. OKAY?
THERE.
- I DON'T WANT IT!
STOP IT! WHY DID YOU
GIVE ME A BODY LIKE THIS?
- ASA!
- WHY DOES IT
ALWAYS HURT SO MUCH,
I JUST WANNA BE LIKE
EVERYONE ELSE?
IT'S ALL YOUR FAULT
I'M SUFFERING.
YOU MADE ME THIS WAY.
I'M IN SO MUCH PAIN.
I WISH I'D NEVER EVEN BEEN BORN.
I WISH YOU'D NEVER HAD ME.
- SORRY, ASA.
- ( coughing )
- WHAT'S WRONG?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- ALL THE OTHER KIDS HAVE
HEALTHY BODIES, EXCEPT FOR ME.
BECAUSE OF YOU,
I'M GOING TO DIE.
PRETTY AWFUL, ISN'T IT?
JUST THINKING ABOUT IT
MAKES ME WANT TO SLAP MYSELF.
- ASA'S ONE OF THE MOST CHEERFUL
AND ENERGETIC PEOPLE I KNOW.
I NEVER WOULD HAVE IMAGINE
THAT SHE'D GONE THROUGH
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- SORRY TO UNLOAD THAT ON YOU.
- NO. I... I HAD NO IDEA, ASA.
- WELL, OF COURSE YOU DIDN'T.
YOU'RE THE FIRST PERSON I'VE
FELT COMFORTABLE ENOUGH
TO SHARE THAT WITH.
REALLY. I WAS AWFUL.
BUT NO MATTER WHAT,
MY MOTHER NEVER GOT MAD.
NO. ALL SHE EVER DID WAS SIT
BY MY SIDE AND COMFORT ME.
AND EVEN WHEN THINGS
GOT THEIR WORST,
SHE NEVER STOPPED
SMILING FOR ME.
SEEING HOW STRONG SHE WAS,
AND HOW MUCH SHE CARED FOR ME,
I PROMISED MYSELF THAT
I WOULD BECOME AS STRONG
AS MY MOTHER AND
NEVER LOSE MY SMILE.
SHE'S THE REASON I GOT BETTER.
IT WASN'T MEDICINE OR DOCTORS.
IT WAS BECAUSE I HAD SOMEBODY
THAT WOULD DO EVERYTHING
THEY COULD TO SHOW ME
HOW MUCH THEY LOVED ME.
BECAUSE I HAD SOMEBODY
THAT WOULD STICK BY MY
SIDE NO MATTER WHAT.
I BECAME THE PERSON
THAT I AM TODAY.
RIN?
- I'M AN IDIOT, AREN'T I?
PRIMULA, SHE NEEDS ME
AND I'M NOT THERE,
I CAN'T BELIEVE I EVEN HESITATED
ABOUT GOING TO SEE HER.
I'VE JUST ACTED SO SELFISHLY.
- YEAH.
- I COULDN'T HAVE SEEN THAT
WITHOUT YOU. THANK YOU, ASA.
- OH!
HERE, TAKE THIS WITH YOU.
- WHAT?
- I WANT YOU TO TAKE THIS
SINCE I'M STUCK IN BED
AND I CAN'T GO WITH YOU.
MY MOTHER GAVE IT TO ME
AND I'VE ALWAYS WORN IT
TO REMIND ME OF HER
LOVE AND HER STRENGTH.
IT'S ALWAYS GIVEN ME COURAGE
AND I THINK IT'LL HELP YOU
GET THROUGH THIS, TOO.
- COURAGE.
I KNOW THIS IS TOUGH FOR YOU.
BUT I NEED YOU TO
LET ME GO SEE PRIMULA.
I'VE MADE UP MY MIND.
AND NO MATTER WHAT
RISKS MIGHT BE INVOLVED,
I HAVE TO GO SEE HER.
- BUT...
- LISTEN, EVEN IF YOU'RE SCARED,
YOU HAVE TO ALLOW HIM TO DO THIS
OR YOU'RE GONNA REGRET IT.
- NERINE.
- RIMU IS WAITING.
- OKAY.
I UNDERSTAND.
IT WOULD BE WRONG OF ME
NOT TO TAKE YOU.
- NERINE, THANK YOU.
SO, THIS IS THE GATE, HUH?
HANG ON, WE'RE COMING FOR YOU,
PRIMULA.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Nerine: I NEVER
THOUGHT I'D RETURN
TO THE DEMON REALM LIKE THIS,
BUT I KNOW HOW
IMPORTANT THIS IS.
I CAN'T LOSE ANOTHER PERSON
CLOSE TO ME AGAIN.
- Rin: WAIT FOR US, PRIMULA.
WE'RE COMING FOR YOU.
- Kaede: ON THE NEXT EPISODE OF
SHUFFLE, "WHAT WAS REGAINED."
- Primula: JUST NOW, I THOUGHT
I HEARD MY BIG SIS SINGING.