- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- THE EDGES ARE A
LITTLE CRUNCHY,
BUT I THINK THEY'LL STILL TASTE
DECENT, I HOPE.
HERE ALL THESE YEARS, I THOUGHT
COOKING WAS PRETTY EASY.
BUT THAT'S PROBABLY 'CAUSE
I NEVER ACTUALLY HAD TO DO IT.
- WHERE'S KAEDE?
- UM, STILL IN BED. SHE'S
RESTING UNTIL SHE FEELS BETTER.
SHE'LL BE OKAY.
EAT UP BEFORE THEY GET COLD.
- RIN? IF YOU DON'T MIND,
I'LL EAT LATER WITH KAEDE.
- OKAY, GOOD IDEA.
- THANK YOU. SORRY.
- DON'T BE.
KAEDE?
KAEDE. COME ON, GET UP.
WE CAN WALK TO CLASS
TOGETHER, IF YOU WANT.
OKAY, MAYBE NEXT TIME.
- GOOD MORNING, RIN.
- OH, GOOD MORNING, RIN.
YOU LOOK HANDSOME.
- IS KAEDE NOT COMING?
- AFRAID NOT. SHE'S STILL
NOT QUITE FEELING HER BEST.
- IT MUST BE SERIOUS
TO KEEP HER DOWN THIS LONG.
- IS SHE GONNA BE ALL RIGHT?
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
- WOULD IT BE OKAY IF WE
MAYBE TALK ABOUT THIS LATER?
RIGHT NOW IS JUST
NOT A GOOD TIME.
SORRY, I DON'T MEAN
TO WORRY YOU.
- NOT AT ALL. YOU'LL TELL US
WHEN YOU FEEL READY.
- TILL THEN, IF THERE'S ANYTHING
WE CAN POSSIBLY DO TO HELP,
PLEASE DON'T THINK TWICE
ABOUT ASKING.
- YOU TWO ARE THE GREATEST,
SERIOUSLY
- OCCASIONALLY, BETWEEN
HUMAN AND DEMON WORLDS,
A PHENOMENON TAKES PLACE THAT
TRANSCENDS BOTH SPACE AND TIME.
- IS IT BECAUSE YOU HATE ME
FOR WHAT I'VE DONE?
- I DON'T HATE YOU.
- GIVE ME A CHANCE TO MAKE THIS
UP TO YOU, I CAN GET BETTER.
PLEASE, RIN. I'LL
EVEN LEARN TO COOK
MORE THINGS
YOU LIKE TO EAT.
PLEASE, JUST GIVE ME ANOTHER
CHANCE. PLEASE DON'T LEAVE.
- JUST TELL ME WHAT I'M
DOING WRONG...
- IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
- THEN IS IT ABOUT ASA?
- BECAUSE SHE'S
WELCOME, ANYTIME.
- NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
- DON'T YOU GET IT?
THE ONLY THING I CARE ABOUT IS
TAKING CARE OF YOU, RIN.
COOKING MEALS FOR YOU
AND DOING YOUR LAUNDRY.
IT'S WHAT GIVES MY LIFE
A SENSE OF PURPOSE.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE. THIS ISN'T
REALLY THE LIFE YOU WANT.
WE'VE LIVED TOGETHER FOR
A LONG TIME. I KNOW YOU.
KAEDE, BE HONEST WITH YOURSELF.
- I HAVE DEVOTED MY ENTIRE LIFE
TO TAKING CARE OF YOU, RIN.
IT'S THE ONLY THING I LIVE FOR.
- I KNOW IT IS.
THAT'S THE REASON.
THAT'S WHY I'VE DECIDED
TO LEAVE, UNDERSTAND?
IT'S WHY I HAVE TO LEAVE, KAEDE.
- ( crying ) NO. BUT IT DOESN'T
HAVE TO BE LIKE THAT.
I'M BEGGING YOU.
DON'T LEAVE ME LIKE THIS.
I WON'T SURVIVE IF YOU
DISAPPEAR FROM MY LIFE.
- Nadashiko: HENCE THE ISSUE
OF A TIME PARADOX.
HOWEVER, WE'VE NO
CITABLE CASES TO DATE.
CURRENTLY, FURTHER RESEARCH
IS BEING CONDUCTED.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
DOES IT TASTE THAT BAD?
- NO, IT'S OKAY.
- WHY DON'T YOU TRY THIS ONE?
ALL THOSE STARCHES ARE JUST
GONNA SLOW YOU DOWN.
- THANKS, I APPRECIATE IT.
- HOW'S KAEDE DOING?
IS SHE FEELING BETTER?
- SHE'S NOT.
- HMM. I THINK YOU MIGHT
HAVE OUTDONE YOURSELF.
THIS TASTES AMAZING!
- WELL, THANK YOU.
- NOW, TELL ME
WHAT'S REALLY HAPPENING.
- "WHAT'S REALLY HAPPENING?"
- WITH YOU AND KAEDE.
NERINE AND SIA TOLD ME THAT
SHE WON'T SEE EITHER OF THEM
OR COME OUT OF THE HOUSE.
- IS IT MY FAULT?
- NO, I THINK IT'S MINE.
I HAVEN'T BEEN FAIR TO KAEDE.
STAYING WITH HER ALL THESE
YEARS MADE HER BELIEVE
THAT THERE WAS SOMETHING
BETWEEN US WHEN THERE WASN'T.
IT'S LIKE, SHE'S WASTED
HER ENTIRE LIFE ON ME.
- THAT'S NOT TRUE.
- I REALIZED HOW
SELFISH I'VE BEEN
AND I JUST CAN'T KEEP
DOING THAT TO HER.
AND SO, THE BEST THING
THAT I CAN DO IS TO LEAVE.
THE SOONER THE BETTER.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
TO GET THROUGH TO HER.
OTHERWISE, KAEDE WILL NEVER
BE ABLE TO LET GO.
AND AS MUCH AS I HATE
TO HURT HER,
AS MUCH AS IT SEEMS LIKE
I'M PUSHING HER AWAY,
THIS IS, THIS IS THE ONLY THING
I CAN DO TO HELP HER MOVE ON.
I ONLY WISH...
- NO, THERE'S NO OTHER OPTION.
- I'M SO SORRY.
- AT BEST, I COULD EARN ABOUT
SEVENTY A MONTH WORKING
PART TIME, OR
CLOSER TO SIXTY.
IT'S GONNA BE TIGHT REGARDLESS.
- WELL, HELLO, RIN.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
PEEKING IN A REAL ESTATE OFFICE?
- ( chuckles awkwardly )
I'M JUST LOOKING.
- "FOR LEASE?" JUST LOOKING?
FOR WHO?
KAEDE KICKING YOU OUT AND
MAKING YOU FEND FOR YOURSELF?
- AH. WAIT A MINUTE.
- IS SHE RIGHT?
- OKAY, GIRLS, I GUESS, IT'S
TIME TO EXPLAIN.
- HUH?
- KAEDE?
I'M COMING IN.
- ( gasps ) WHERE ARE YOU?
- YOU'RE SERIOUS ABOUT THIS?
- BUT, WHAT'S YOUR
REASON FOR MOVING?
- BECAUSE IT'S THE RIGHT THING
TO DO FOR BOTH OF US.
- BUT YOU DO LIKE LIVING THERE.
AND YOU'RE NOT TIRED OF LIVING
WITH KAEDE, RIGHT?
- ABSOLUTELY NOT.
I THINK LIVING WITH KAEDE HAS
BEEN A GOOD THING FOR ME.
- BUT RIN, IF THAT'S
REALLY HOW YOU FEEL,
THEN ISN'T THAT REASON
ENOUGH TO KEEP LIVING THERE?
- LIVING BY YOURSELF
IS A LOT HARDER THAN IT SOUNDS.
COOKING, CLEANING, LAUNDRY.
IT'S PRETTY HARD LABOR WHEN
YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
- HARD LABOR IS RIGHT, AND
ALL THIS TIME SHE'S BEEN
DOING EVERY BIT OF IT
BY HERSELF. AND ALL FOR ME.
ALL THAT FOR ME.
- GOOD MORNING, RIN.
HERE YOU GO, DON'T FORGET
ABOUT YOUR LUNCH.
HERE YOU GO. TAKE THIS.
IT'S MEDICINE.
- ( chuckles ) WELL,
ONLY WHEN IT COMES TO RIN.
- I DIDN'T REALIZE,
I WAS TAKING HER FOR GRANTED.
BOTH KAEDE AND I,
GENUINELY THOUGHT
WE WERE MAKING
EACH OTHER HAPPY.
- WE WERE FOOLING OURSELVES.
MISTAKING COMFORT FOR HAPPINESS.
- I SHOULD HAVE SEEN IT. WE
WERE BOTH LIVING IN THE PAST.
STUCK THERE BY SOMETHING
THAT HAPPENED TO US
WHEN WE WERE JUST KIDS.
- I REALLY LOVE TAKING
CARE OF YOU, RIN.
IT'S WHAT I ENJOY
DOING THE MOST.
- BUT THE TRUTH WAS SHE
WAS ONLY FEELING GUILTY.
SHE FELT HORRIBLE FOR THE
WAY SHE'D TREATED ME
AND WAS STILL TRYING TO
MAKE UP FOR IT.
- AND I WAS AFRAID THAT
IF I TRIED TO STOP HER, WELL,
I FELT LIKE IT WOULD CRUSH
HER SPIRIT.
IF HER DEVOTION TO ME
WAS ALL SHE LIVED FOR
THEN WHO WAS I TO TAKE
THAT AWAY FROM HER?
BUT THEN, YOU TWO
HELPED ME REALIZE
THAT I HAD BEEN FOOLING MYSELF.
SEEING IT ALL WRONG.
ONE THING I'M SURE OF
IS THAT IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO TAKE A NEW STEP FORWARD.
- YOU AND NERINE TAUGHT ME THAT.
- WE DID THAT?
- NOT JUST FOR ME,
BUT KAEDE AS WELL.
IT'S IMPORTANT THAT BOTH OF US
LEARN TO TAKE CARE OF OURSELVES.
THANK YOU FOR HELPING ME
SEE THAT.
- YOU'RE WELCOME.
- THAT'S WHY I'VE DECIDED
TO FIND ANOTHER PLACE TO LIVE.
THAT WAY, JUST LIKE
YOU TWO HAVE DONE,
KAEDE AND I CAN EVENTUALLY
FIND HAPPINESS ON OUR OWN.
- ( chuckles )
- I BET YOU'LL FIND IT.
- WE'LL HELP IN ANY WAY WE CAN.
- THANKS.
JUDGING BY THOSE NUMBERS
AT THE LEASING OFFICE,
LIVING ALONE IS GONNA BE
TOUGHER THAN I THOUGHT.
RENTING A TEENY APARTMENT
IS GONNA BE EXPENSIVE.
- I'M CERTAIN
YOU CAN HANDLE IT, RIN.
- I DON'T WANNA SEEM PUSHY,
SHOULDN'T I AT LEAST FIGURE
OUT WHAT I'M GONNA SAY TO HER
BEFORE I SEE HER?
- NO!
- THIS IS PROBABLY A BAD IDEA.
- DO YOU NEED A GIFT
FOR SOMEONE?
- AH, I WAS JUST LOOKING.
THANKS.
WELL, I AM GOING
TO VISIT SOMEONE.
- RIN.
- WHAT'S GOING ON? WHAT ARE
YOU DOING HERE, PRIMULA?
- ( panting )
- ARE YOU OKAY?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- I CAN'T FIND KAEDE.
- KAEDE'S GONE?
- ( crying ) I MEAN IT.
JUST DIE!
I'M SORRY.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- KAEDE?
- HELLO, ASA.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- IT'S ABOUT TO POUR.
- I CAME HERE TO GIVE YOU THESE.
YOU SHOULD GET INSIDE
BEFORE THE RAIN STARTS.
YOU'RE GONNA CATCH A COLD
IF YOU'RE NOT CAREFUL.
- I GUESS YOU KNOW WHY
I'VE BEEN MISSING SCHOOL.
- I'VE JUST BEEN HIDING
IN MY ROOM.
- RIN TOLD ME ABOUT IT.
- BUT, I KINDA KNEW
BEFORE HE TOLD ME.
- I SEE.
- THEN, YOU ALSO KNOW
THAT RIN DECIDED TO MOVE OUT.
- YEAH.
- I WASN'T GOOD ENOUGH
TO MAKE HIM LOVE ME.
- KAEDE.
- IT'S NOT THAT SURPRISING.
SOME OF THE AWFUL THINGS I DID
SHOULDN'T BE FORGIVEN.
NONETHELESS, I TOOK CARE
OF HIS EVERY NEED.
IT WAS ALL I CARED ABOUT.
EVERYTHING I DID WAS FOR RIN.
IT WAS THE ONE THING I COULD
DO TO TRY AND MAKE UP
FOR WHAT I'D DONE.
BUT THEN, AFTER A WHILE,
I REALIZED THAT
WHAT I REALLY WANTED WAS FOR
HIM TO FALL IN LOVE WITH ME.
I WASN'T HONEST WITH MYSELF.
EVERYTHING I DID WAS BECAUSE
I WANTED TO BE WITH RIN.
I HAVEN'T BEEN FAIR TO HIM.
THE TRUTH IS I TOOK CARE OF HIM
OUT OF LOVE, NOT DEBT.
DESPITE WHAT WE'VE BEEN THROUGH,
I THINK I WILL ALWAYS LOVE HIM.
I WASN'T BEING HONEST.
I WAS AFRAID OF THE TRUTH,
BECAUSE I KNEW HE WOULDN'T
LOVE ME THE SAME WAY BACK.
- BUT HE KNEW, HE KNEW
THAT YOU CARED.
- I CAN NEVER FORGIVE MYSELF
FOR WHAT I DID, NEVER.
IT MAKES SENSE, THOUGH.
I CAN'T BLAME RIN FOR
CHOOSING SOMEONE LIKE YOU
OVER SOMEONE LIKE ME.
- I'M SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY, KAEDE.
- YOU SHOULDN'T BE.
RIN IS A BIG BOY AND IT WAS
HIS CHOICE TO MAKE.
I DECIDED A LONG TIME AGO,
THAT I WOULD CONTINUE TO LOVE
RIN NO MATTER WHO HE CHOSE.
- SO, I GUESS, IT'S YOUR JOB
TO MAKE HIM HAPPY NOW.
- KAEDE.
- YOU WILL MAKE HIM HAPPY, WON'T
YOU? BECAUSE RIN DESERVES IT.
- I CERTAINLY PLAN TO,
BUT SO FAR,
HE'S BEEN THE ONE
MAKING ME HAPPY.
- I CAN SEE IT IN YOUR EYES.
YOU REALLY HAVE FALLEN FOR HIM,
HAVEN'T YOU, ASA?
- HE CAUGHT ME OFF GUARD.
- GOOD FOR YOU.
- I HATE TO THINK ABOUT ALL THE
SUFFERING HE WENT THROUGH
BECAUSE OF ME.
BUT IF YOU MAKE HIM HAPPY,
I THINK IN SOME WAY IT'LL
SORT OF MAKE UP FOR IT.
- KAEDE.
- ASA, I NEED YOU TO LET ME
MAKE ONE SELFISH REQUEST.
- I WANT TO SEE HIM.
IF I'M ABLE TO JUST SEE HIM.
I CAN KEEP ON LOVING HIM.
I KNOW HE'S NOT MINE,
HE'S NEVER BEEN MINE,
BUT I NEED TO KEEP LOVING HIM.
( crying )
- KAEDE.
- I'M SO SORRY, ASA.
I KNOW IT'S SELFISH.
I JUST... I KNOW HOW RIN FEELS.
AND ASA, I KNOW
THAT YOU LOVE HIM.
BUT I STILL... I'M SO SORRY.
- STOP THAT. IF ANYBODY
IS SELFISH, IT'S ME.
I SHOULD HAVE SEEN IT
FROM THE BEGINNING.
YOU'VE BEEN IN LOVE WITH RIN
FOR AS LONG AS I'VE KNOWN YOU.
I'M SORRY. FORGIVE ME.
- KAEDE?
- KAEDE? KAEDE!
- HI, RIN.
- WHAT HAPPENED? I'VE BEEN
WORRIED SICK.
- I'M SORRY YOU WERE WORRIED.
- TELL ME WHERE YOU'VE BEEN.
YOU'RE SOAKING WET.
- ASA AND I GOT CAUGHT
IN THE RAIN.
- I ASKED HER IF SHE WOULD
TAKE GOOD CARE OF YOU.
- HUH?
- I NEEDED TO MAKE SURE.
SINCE, I'M NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO DO IT ANY LONGER.
- KAEDE. JUST LISTEN.
- I THINK I'M FALLING
IN LOVE WITH...
- DON'T SAY ANOTHER WORD!
- PLEASE, RIN. I CAN'T HEAR IT
FROM YOU. I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
I DON'T NEED TO HEAR IT.
NOT FROM YOU.
- NOW HOLD ON, THAT ISN'T FAIR.
YOU NEED TO HEAR THIS. RIGHT
NOW, FROM ME, AND NO ONE ELSE.
- ( crying )
- I'M IN LOVE WITH ASA, KAEDE.
I'VE BEEN DOING A LOT OF
THINKING,
ABOUT US, THE OTHER GIRLS,
AND ABOUT DECISIONS I'VE
BEEN NEEDING TO MAKE.
I ASKED MYSELF, WHO IS IT THAT I
WANT TO BE CLOSEST TO RIGHT NOW.
AND WHO IS IT THAT
I REALLY LOVE THE MOST?
- AND YOU REALIZED
THAT SOMEONE WASN'T ME.
- PLEASE UNDERSTAND.
YOU MEAN THE WORLD TO ME, KAEDE.
WE'VE SPENT MOST OF
OUR LIVES TOGETHER.
YOU KNOW ME BETTER THAN ANYONE.
YOU'VE ALWAYS BEEN THERE FOR ME.
- ( camera clicks )
- YOU'RE ONE OF MY
CLOSEST FRIENDS.
I COULD NEVER HATE YOU,
EVEN FOR A MINUTE.
AND I HOPE YOU'LL NEVER HATE ME.
EVEN THOUGH I DON'T LOVE
YOU ROMANTICALLY,
I WILL ALWAYS LOVE YOU, KAEDE.
- PLEASE, DON'T SAY YOU LOVE ME.
PLEASE DON'T, RIN.
DON'T YOU DARE LOVE ME.
NOT LIKE THAT.
NOT THAT WAY.
- DON'T.
- KAEDE.
- PLEASE DON'T LOVE ME.
- I'M SO SORRY.
- PLEASE DON'T LOVE ME. I DON'T
KNOW HOW I'M SUPPOSED TO...
( sighs )
( crying ) I LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
I'M BACK.
- WELCOME HOME, KAEDE.
- HMM? WHAT HAPPENED?
YOU'RE ALL MESSY.
- YEAH, I MADE DINNER.
YOU'RE ALL WET. YOU MUST BE
FREEZING. I'LL GET YOU A TOWEL.
I MADE STEW BECAUSE I FIGURED
YOU'D PROBABLY BE
COLD AND HUNGRY, AND STEW'S
GOOD FOR THAT.
OKAY, YOU MAKE IT BETTER,
BUT I WANT YOU TO HAVE SOME.
- THANK YOU.
- Asa: I SEE. I NEVER REALIZED
THERE WAS SO MUCH HISTORY
BETWEEN THE TWO OF YOU.
I PROBABLY SHOULDN'T HAVE ASKED
YOU ABOUT IT SO CASUALLY. SORRY.
- IT'S OKAY. AT THE TIME,
THE ONLY THING I CARED ABOUT
WAS MAKING SURE
KAEDE DIDN'T HURT
HERSELF, YOU KNOW?
- TYPICAL RIN BEHAVIOR.
- WHAT CAN I SAY? I FOLLOW
MY INSTINCTS.
- I KNOW HOW SHE FELT.
I'VE BEEN THERE.
I KNEW SOMETHING WAS UP.
THERE WAS NO WAY KAEDE
COULD "HATE" ANYONE,
ESPECIALLY YOU.
I REMEMBER BACK IN
MIDDLE SCHOOL,
WHEN SHE AND I WERE IN
THE COOKING CLUB TOGETHER,
ONE DAY I ASKED HER
WHY SHE JOINED THE CLUB.
SHE SAID THERE WAS SOMEONE
WHO HAD BEEN VERY GOOD TO HER.
AND SHE WANTED A WAY
TO SAY THANK YOU.
SHE TOLD ME THAT SHE HAD SAID
AND DONE HORRIBLE THINGS
TO THAT PERSON.
BUT SHE ALSO SAID
THAT SAME PERSON
MADE HER WHO SHE IS TODAY.
SO, I KNEW YOU WERE THE
ONE SHE WAS TALKING ABOUT
ALL THOSE YEARS.
BUT I DIDN'T KNOW AT THE TIME
WAS WHAT ACTUALLY HAPPENED
BETWEEN THE TWO OF YOU.
SO, I DECIDED TO ASK,
BUT IT WASN'T MY PLACE.
- YES, IT WAS. I'M GLAD
THAT YOU ASKED ABOUT IT.
I WANTED YOU TO KNOW, ASA.
- YOU DID? HOW COME?
- BECAUSE IT WAS IMPORTANT.
AND I GUESS IT'S PROBABLY
FOR SOME OF THE SAME REASON
YOU WANTED ME TO TELL YOU.
- WOW, I THINK YOU'RE BLUSHING.
- NO, IT'S JUST HOT TODAY.
- QUIT TRYING TO EMBARRASS ME
AND JUST TELL ME WHY YOU
ASKED ME TO MEET YOU HERE.
DID YOU WANT TO TALK
ABOUT SOMETHING?
- WELL, YES, I DID. I TOLD KAEDE
ABOUT MY FEELINGS FOR YOU.
I MADE SURE SHE HEARD IT
STRAIGHT FROM ME.
THEN, I REALIZED, I HADN'T
TALKED TO YOU EITHER.
ASA SHIGURE.
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT I LOVE YOU.
THAT'S WHY I'M ASKING YOU,
TO BE MY GIRLFRIEND.
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- WHAT YOU SAID BEFORE,
ABOUT BEING HATED BY KAEDE.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN
INCREDIBLY PAINFUL,
TO ENDURE SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- I'D BE LYING IF I TRIED
TO TELL YOU IT WASN'T PAINFUL.
BUT AT THE TIME, I JUST WANTED
TO PROTECT KAEDE.
- EVEN THOUGH SHE WAS BEING
SO MEAN TO YOU?
- YOU'D BE SURPRISED.
WHEN YOU CARE FOR SOMEONE,
YOU PUT UP WITH A LOT.
- YOU'RE STRONG.
YOU KNOW THAT, RIN?
- WELL, I DON'T REALLY
SEE IT THAT WAY.
- OH, COME ON.
YOU'RE VERY STRONG.
ALMOST AS STRONG AS SHE IS.
- AS WHO?
- IS IT REALLY THAT
BIG A MYSTERY?
I OWE HER EVERYTHING.
SHE PUT UP WITH ALL THE PAIN,
ALL OF THOSE TERRIBLE THINGS
I SAID AND SHE NEVER COMPLAINED.
ALL SHE CARED ABOUT WAS
PROTECTING HER LITTLE GIRL.
SO, DO YOU PROMISE THAT
YOU'LL TRY TO PROTECT ME, RIN?
JUST LIKE SHE HAS, THE
PERSON I ADMIRE MORE
THAN ANYONE
ELSE IN THIS WORLD?
- I PROMISE. I'LL PROTECT YOU.
- WELL, THAT WAS QUITE
AN IMPRESSIVE DELIVERY.
NOW, I AM DEFINITELY BLUSHING,
AND I THINK MY HEART MAY HAVE
JUST SKIPPED A BEAT OR TWO.
OKAY. WELL, RIN,
HERE'S YOUR ANSWER.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Sia: WE ALL GOT TO MEET RIN.
- Nerine: AND WE TOLD
HIM HOW WE FELT.
- Primula: AND NOW, ALL OF US.
- Kaede: WILL WALK TOGETHER.
- Asa: NEXT TIME ON SHUFFLE,
EPISODE 22,
"TOWARDS A NEW TOMORROW."