- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( thunder rumbling )
- ( sniffling )
- I... I HATE YOU!
( screaming )
- Rin: KAEDE!
- YES? WHAT IS IT, RIN?
WHAT'S WRONG?
WELL, ANYWAY, IT'S TIME
TO WAKE UP NOW, SLEEPY HEAD.
- Woman: THIS MORNING
WILL BE CLEAR,
EXCEPT FOR A FEW LIGHT
SHOWERS IN THE AFTERNOON.
IT WOULD PROBABLY BE A GOOD
IDEA TO HAVE YOUR...
- HEY, RIN? UM, WHAT WERE YOU
DREAMING ABOUT? WHEN I WOKE YOU?
- 'CUSE ME? THAT'S AN
INTERESTING QUESTION. WHY?
- DON'T YOU REMEMBER, SILLY?
YOU CALLED OUT MY NAME.
- ( exclaiming )
- COME ON, TELL ME.
WHAT WAS IT ABOUT?
- WELL, I... I JUST
DON'T KNOW IF I REMEMBER.
OH, WAIT! I REMEMBER NOW!
YOU WERE ALMOST ABDUCTED
BY ALIENS THAT MUTILATED COWS!
THEY HAD BIG SCARY BROWN EYES
THAT COULD SEE
RIGHT THROUGH YOU!
- YOU JUST MADE THAT WHOLE
ENTIRE THING UP, DIDN'T YOU?
- MAYBE.
ANYWAY, ENOUGH ABOUT THAT.
HOW ARE YOU DOING LATELY?
YOU KNOW, YOU DO
ALL THE HOUSEWORK,
YOU MAKE HUGE
BREAKFASTS EVERY DAY,
PLUS ALL OF OUR LUNCHES,
AND THEN YOU STILL FIND
TIME TO DO YOUR HOMEWORK.
HOW DO YOU DO IT? DO YOU SLEEP?
- OF COURSE I DO!
AND I WAKE UP FEELING
VERY WELL RESTED!
- REALLY? WELL, SINCE YOUR
FATHER'S AWAY ON BUSINESS
YOU CAN MAKE SMALLER MEALS
IF YOU WANT.
JUST TAKE IT EASY AND
DON'T WORK SO HARD.
- DON'T SAY THAT.
I ENJOY TAKING CARE OF YOU, RIN.
IT MAKES ME SO HAPPY AND
IF YOU TOOK THAT AWAY...
( crying ) I DON'T' KNOW
WHAT I'D DO. SORRY.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
- ALL RIGHT! I'M SORRY!
DO WHATEVER MAKES YOU HAPPY!
- ( cheerfully ) OKAY!
SO, FOR LUNCH TODAY
I MADE BROILED BLACK COD
WITH SAIKYO MISO SAUCE!
AND DINNER TONIGHT
IS GOING TO BE GREAT!
IN HONOR OF THE SPECIAL THING
THAT HAPPENED TO ME TODAY.
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- YOU HAD A DREAM ABOUT
ME THIS MORNING.
THAT'S SPECIAL TO ME!
- IT'S GONNA SHAKE.
- ( both exclaim )
- ( rumbling )
- AN EARTHQUAKE!
- WHERE'S MY PURSE?
RIN! GRAB YOUR WALLET!
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT RIGHT
NOW! GET UNDER THE TABLE,
OR OUT OF THE HOUSE!
- YOU WANT ME TO TAKE
THE TABLE OUT OF THE HOUSE?
- NO, UNDER THE...
NEVER MIND, JUST COVER YOUR
MOUTH WITH A WET HANDKERCHIEF!
- BUT ALL OF THE HANDKERCHIEFS
ARE DIRTY AND NEED TO BE WASHED!
- ( Rin screams )
- Both: UH, IT'S OVER.
- ARE YOU OKAY? PRIMULA?
- MORE PLEASE.
- ( sighs )
- ( frightened cry )
- ( screeching )
- YOU BETTER RUN,
I'M A MEMBER OF THE KNIGHTS
OF KISSY KAEDE, OR THE KKK!
NOT THE BAD GUYS WITH SHEETS.
AND BROTHER NUMBER ONE!
- I BELONG TO THE
SEXY SIA SOLDIERS! OR SSS!
SCIENCE CLUB VICE PRESIDENT!
AND BROTHER NUMBER TWO!
- I'M A MEMBER OF
RINA'S RANDY RAIDERS, THE RRR!
SCIENCE CLUB TREASURER!
AND BROTHER NUMBER THREE!
- ( together ) TOGETHER
THE THREE OF US...
- HM.
- HA HA.
- HA.
- ARE THE NAKABAYASHI BROTHERS
PERSONAL GUARD UNIT!
- OH, NO!
- PREPARE TO MEET YOUR FATE,
RIN TSUCHIMI!
- WE'VE COLLECTED THE
ATHLETIC TEAM'S SMELLIEST SOCKS!
AND WE'RE GOING TO
SHOWER YOU WITH THEIR STENCH!
- NO WOMAN ON THIS EARTH
WILL EVER COME NEAR YOU AGAIN!
- DIVINE PUNISHMENT!
- WE'LL PUNISH ANYONE WHO
CAUSES TROUBLE FOR RIN!
NOW YOU LEAVE HIM ALONE!
- YOU'RE LUCKY. NEXT TIME
IT'LL BE A BENCH!
- STUPID BROTHERS!
- I'M SO SORRY, RIN!
THIS IS ALL BECAUSE OF US!
- PLEASE FORGIVE US.
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE,
PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE, PLEASE.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT. BELIEVE
ME, I'M USED TO IT BY NOW.
- YOU TWO SAVED MY LIFE. THANKS.
- HUH?
- ( giggles ) NO PROBLEM!
- ( metal clanking )
- ( clock chiming )
- THAT'S THE BELL!
- WE'RE GONNA BE LATE!
- LET'S GO! KAEDE!
- 'KAY, I'M COMING.
( whimpers )
- ( footsteps retreating )
- ALRIGHT. I'M PUTTING ALL THIS
ON YOUR NEXT EXAM.
AND SINCE I'M TELLING YOU
EXACTLY WHAT WILL BE ON IT,
YOU SHOULDN'T GET IT WRONG,
UNLESS YOU'RE AN IDIOT.
- ( whimpers )
GREAT! RIN, WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
I'M GONNA GET IT WRONG
ANYWAY, I KNOW IT.
- IT'S OKAY, WE'RE BOTH
IN THE SAME BOAT. DON'T WORRY.
- TSUCHI! THAT'S NOT SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD BE PROUD OF!
- ( giggling )
- RIN!
- Nerine: RIN...
I WROTE DOWN ALL THE NOTES,
AND I'LL LET YOU COPY THEM LATER
IF YOU WANT TO USE THEM
TO STUDY WITH TONIGHT.
- RINA! CAN I
USE THEM TOO, PLEASE?
- ( clock chiming )
- I'M SO HUNGRY!
- GIVE IT TO HIM! THIS IS WHAT
YOU MADE IT FOR, ISN'T IT?
- UH-HUH.
- UH. WHAT IS IT?
- HERE'S YOUR LUNCH, RIN.
I MADE THIS FOR YOU, SO ...
- GOOD JOB, I'M IMPRESSED!
ALL OF THAT AFTER ONLY A
FEW LESSONS? WAY TO GO!
- ( laughing sheepishly )
- BUT, WHY DID YOU MAKE SO MUCH?
- WELL, I KIND OF GOT A LITTLE
CARRIED AWAY. BUT, HERE.
- IS THAT AN OMELET?
- THINK SO.
- THAT'S NOT ALL. LOOK.
- OH, IT'S...
IT'S ANOTHER OMELET.
- NOT THAT.
THERE'S SOY SAUCE!
- SO IT'S LIKE QUANTITY
OVER VARIETY.
- YES! WHEN I SEE THAT BOWL
OF SLIMY MIXED YELLOW EGGS
TURN INTO SUCH A
BEAUTIFUL FLUFFY LIGHT OMELET
I SOMEHOW FEEL LIKE
THEY'RE SHOWING ME
THE FEELINGS IN MY HEART
CAN TURN INTO SOMETHING
BEAUTIFUL, TOO,
AND THAT MAKES ME SO HAPPY!
- THANKS. UH, I DON'T KNOW IF I
CAN EAT THE WHOLE THING, THOUGH.
- ( moans )
- ON SECOND THOUGHT,
I'M SO HUNGRY,
I COULD EAT ABOUT NINE OF THESE!
- ( laughs ) DO YOU
MEAN THAT, RIN? REALLY?
- OH, YEAH, I DO, EVERY WORD!
IT SMELLS DELICIOUS!
( munching )
IT'S SO GOOD, I LOVE IT!
- ( thunder rumbling )
- Itsuki: WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
- ATE TOO MUCH.
- RIN, YOU'RE TRAGIC.
IT'S HARD ENOUGH TO GET A
WOMAN TO KNOW HER PLACE
AND ACTUALLY COOK SOMETHING.
SO WHEN SHE DOES, YOU HAVE
TO REWARD HER BY EATING IT.
EVEN IF IT'S GROSS.
- ( clattering )
- WHAT'S TRAGIC IS THAT OUTDATED
MISOGYNIST VIEWPOINT, YOU PIG.
- WHATEVER. I'M JUST SAYIN'
YOU SHOULD NEVER REJECT
A GOOD WOMAN'S LOVE LIKE THAT.
I KNOW I WON'T.
POOR RIN, HE'S STILL GOT A LOT
TO LEARN ABOUT THE LADIES,
DON'TCHA BIG GUY?
- Kaede: THAT'S NOT TRUE.
HERE YOU GO.
TAKE THIS. IT'S MEDICINE.
- OH. THANKS, KAEDE.
THAT HELPS.
- RIN ALWAYS TREATS
EVERYONE RIGHT.
THAT'S WHY WE LIKE HIM SO MUCH.
ANYWAY. I'M GONNA GO GET SOME
WATER. I'LL BE RIGHT BACK, OKAY?
- HE DOESN'T NEED
ANY WATER, DOES HE?
- ( grunting )
- HE NEEDS A TASTE OF REAL LIFE.
IT'S TIME FOR YOU
TO BECOME A MAN!
- GET OFF ME!
- OW!
- ( Rin and Mayumi sneeze )
- WOW. IT'S REALLY RAINING HARD.
- AND I FORGOT MY UMBRELLA.
NOW WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO?
- MAYBE WE SHOULD JUST
GIVE UP AND GET WET.
- THAT'S RIGHT. YOU SHOULD
GIVE UP, RIN TSUCHIMI!
- ( together ) BUT
WE NEVER WILL!
WE ARE THE NAKABAYASHI BROTHERS
PERSONAL GUARD UNIT!
TURBO ONE!
- ( explosion )
- Asa: WHOA!
THERE THEY GO AGAIN.
- IT LOOKS BAD OUT THERE.
I HOPE RIN IS OKAY.
- WAIT A MINUTE. DON'T YOU
USUALLY WALK HOME TOGETHER?
- I, UH, REALLY NEED TO
LEARN THIS NEW RECIPE.
- AWW! I HOPE RIN KNOWS
HOW LUCKY HE IS!
- WELL, IT'S, UM... IT'S ALL
I CAN DO TO SHOW HIM I CARE.
- HUH?
- NOTHING.
- ( door opens )
- THANK YOU, ASA!
- ( door closes )
- NO PROBLEM.
GOOD LUCK!
- OH, NO.
I'LL NEVER FORGIVE YOU!
- ( gasping )
YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING ME.
- ( grinding )
- WHAT'S THAT NOISE?
UH, PRIMULA?
- WHAT, RIN?
- NEVER MIND.
I DON'T WANT TO KNOW.
WHERE'S KAEDE?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I HAVEN'T SEEN HER YET.
- UH, KAEDE?
- ( clanking )
- KAEDE!
OH, MY GOSH, WHAT HAPPENED?
ARE YOU OKAY?
SHE'S GOT A FEVER! KAEDE!
WAKE UP! KAEDE!
- Doctor: IT'S JUST A COMMON
COLD THAT GOT OUT OF HAND
DUE TO OVEREXERTION.
SEE THAT SHE GETS
AS MUCH REST AS POSSIBLE.
- THANK YOU, DOCTOR.
KAEDE.
I'M GONNA GO AHEAD AND
FINISH MAKING BREAKFAST MYSELF.
KAEDE'S GONNA NEED SOMETHING
TO REPLENISH HER STRENGTH
WHEN SHE WAKES UP.
- SO CAN YOU GIVE
ME A HAND HERE?
- UM-HMM.
- UGH!
I DON'T GET IT. WHY DOESN'T
MINE LOOK LIKE THAT?
- BECAUSE YOU SUCK, RIN.
- KAEDE'S GONNA BE PISSED.
I GIVE UP.
NO! THIS IS STUPID! I'M A
MAN, DAMMIT, I CAN DO THIS!
WHAT THE CRAP? FIRE!
PRIMULA, GET ME SOME WATER!
HURRY, I NEED WATER!
- ( sizzling )
- THAT'S REALLY DANGEROUS.
YOU SHOULD NEVER EVER USE
WATER ON A GREASE FIRE.
- I KNEW THAT.
- I'M SORRY. THIS IS
ALL MY FAULT.
I'LL DO THE REST. DON'T
WORRY ABOUT A THING, OKAY?
- PLEASE, GO BACK TO BED,
YOU NEED YOUR...
- SHOULDN'T YOU BE AT SCHOOL?
- UH, ACTUALLY, NO,
I ALREADY CALLED IN.
- OH, NO! YOU STAYED HOME FROM
SCHOOL TODAY BECAUSE OF ME?
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE DONE THAT.
I'M SORRY. I'VE CAUSED YOU
SO MUCH TROUBLE.
- HEY, DON'T YOU
WORRY ABOUT THAT.
YOU GET BACK TO YOUR ROOM
AND LET ME TAKE CARE OF THIS.
- OH, I'M FINE, REALLY!
I'LL FINISH COOKING THE...
- KAEDE!
THIS IS WHY WE SAID
NOT TO PUSH YOURSELF.
- YEAH, I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
- ( doorbell ringing )
- HEY, GUYS, WE BROUGHT
YOU SOMETHIN'!
DELICIOUS PASTRIES
FROM THE CAFETERIA
WITH YOUR HOMEWORK
ON THE SIDE! YUMMY!
- WHAT ARE YOU-
- KAEDE! ARE YOU OKAY IN THERE?
- ASA, WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
- WE KNEW YOU WOULD BE TOO SICK
TO COOK FOR EVERYONE,
SO WE THOUGHT WE WOULD
COME AND HELP OUT.
- LOOK AT ALL THIS
FOOD WE BROUGHT.
I'M SURE WE CAN MAKE
SOMETHING YOU LIKE.
- I APPRECIATE THAT.
BUT TAKING CARE OF EVERYONE
HERE IS MY JOB, SO I'D RATHER...
- NOT TODAY. YOU REST
AND GET BETTER.
- THANK YOU.
THAT MEANS A LOT.
I KNOW KAEDE APPRECIATES IT.
- ( girls giggling )
- EXCUSE US!
- MOVE IT.
OKAY! WE NEED TO
MAKE HER SOMETHING
THAT'LL HELP HER FEEL BETTER
AND GIVE HER ENERGY AS WELL!
- ( cracking )
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
I THINK I'VE GOT THIS,
SO WHY DON'T YOU GO ASK
SIA IF SHE NEEDS SOME HELP
WITH THE CLEANING,
'KAY? BYE BYE NOW!
- OHHHHH!
- ( vacuum cleaner whirring )
- WHAT'S GOING ON IN HERE?
- ( screaming )
HELP ME, SIA!
COME ON, THIS IS STUCK!
IT HURTS! STOP SUCKING SO HARD!
IS THERE ANYTHING
I CAN HELP YOU WITH, RIMU?
- LATELY, I'M SPENDING
LESS TIME WITH RIN.
I HATE BEING SICK SO MUCH.
BEFORE THEY CAME...
I WAS THE ONLY ONE
WHO TOOK CARE OF HIM.
I WONDER IF...
HE LIKES THE OTHER GIRLS BETTER.
- ( knock on door )
- KAEDE?
- ( giggling )
WOW, ASA! NO WONDER YOU'RE
CALLED "THE SHOCKING SHIGURE!"
- "THE SHOCKING SHIGURE?"
WHAT? WHAT'S THAT?
- IT'S BECAUSE YOU DON'T
REALLY COME OFF AS SOMEONE
WHO'D BE SUCH AN AMAZING COOK,
BUT YOU ARE, SO YOU'VE BEEN THE
"SHOCKING SHIGURE" EVER SINCE!
- THAT'S SHOCKING.
WHY WOULD ANYONE WANT
ME TO HAVE AN UGLY NAME?
- ( screams ) WHAT IS THAT?
- HMM, LOOKS LIKE OKRA NATTO.
- I'VE NEVER IMAGINED
ANYTHING SO HORRIBLE!
THE OKRA'S RUINED BY THE NATTO!
IT'S TOO CRUEL!
WHO KNEW THAT PEOPLE COULD
DO SUCH TERRIBLE THINGS
TO INNOCENT FOOD IN
THIS WORLD! IT'S AWFUL!
- SOMETHING WITH A REALLY WEIRD
TEXTURE IS INSIDE THIS OMELET.
WHAT IS THAT?
IT TASTES FUNNY.
- WELL, IT'S NOT JUST AN OMELET.
THOSE ARE EGG DUMPLINGS
WITH DICED OCTOPUS.
- ( crying )
- I GUESS YOU
DON'T LIKE OCTOPUS.
- "THE SHOCKING SHIGURE?"
- NATTO IS SO HATEFUL! WHY?
- OCTOPUS?
( crying )
- WHERE'S KAEDE?
HAVE YOU SEEN HER?
- SHE SAID SHE WASN'T HUNGRY.
SHE'S SLEEPING.
- ( girls giggling )
- HE DOESN'T NEED ME ANYMORE.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR YOUR HELP.
- ( giggling ) OH, RIN,
THERE'S NO NEED TO THANK US!
- YEAH, IT WAS NOTHING.
- I TRIED REALLY HARD, BUT I
WASN'T ABLE TO DO ANYTHING.
I'M SORRY.
- COME ON, DON'T SAY THAT.
YOU MADE THINGS A LOT
EASIER, TRUST ME.
- I MADE THINGS EASIER?
- UH, OF COURSE.
- ( giggling ) WE SHOULD
BE GOING, YOU GUYS.
- WE'LL SEE YOU
AT SCHOOL TOMORROW!
- MAKE SURE YOU
TAKE CARE OF KAEDE, 'KAY?
ANYONE CAN TAKE
MEDICINE TO HEAL THEIR BODY.
BUT I THINK YOU MAY
BE THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN CURE HER BROKEN HEART.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
SEE YOU LATER, 'KAY!
- THANKS FOR MAKING THIS.
BUT I THINK WE SHOULD
HAVE DINNER TOGETHER.
JUST YOU AND I,
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- REALLY?
SORRY ABOUT THE
TROUBLE TODAY, RIN.
- LISTEN, THE ONLY
TROUBLE YOU'RE CAUSING
IS NOT GETTING ENOUGH REST.
- RIN? DO YOU LIKE
HAVING ME AROUND?
I MEAN, OR DO I JUST
GET IN YOUR WAY?
- KAEDE.
- I THINK...
YOU DON'T NEED ME ANYMORE.
- ( rumbling )
- ( exclaiming )
- ANOTHER EARTHQUAKE!
- RIN! I, UH...
I NEED TO...
- KAEDE, LISTEN.
THANK YOU.
I REALLY...
I APPRECIATE YOU.
- ARE YOU SURE?
I'M NOT A BURDEN TO YOU?
- NO WAY!
I'M A COMPLETE WRECK WITHOUT
YOU. ARE YOU KIDDING?
- IF THAT'S TRUE,
IS IT OKAY IF I KEEP TAKING
CARE OF YOU FROM NOW ON?
- ALRIGHT, ON ONE CONDITION.
- SLACK OFF EVERY ONCE
AND AWHILE, YOU KNOW?
GET SOME SLEEP.
OTHERWISE YOU'RE JUST
GONNA GET SICK AGAIN
AND I'LL END UP BURNING
THE HOUSE DOWN, OKAY?
- 'KAY!
TIME TO WAKE UP, RIN!
- ( curtains shuffling )
- MORNING.
- THERE'S A NICE HOT BREAKFAST
ALL READY FOR YOU.
- 'KAY, ARE YOU FEELING BETTER?
YEAH! I TOOK THE MEDICINE
RIMU MADE FOR ME
AND BEFORE I KNEW IT,
I WAS COMPLETELY WELL!
- SHE MADE YOU MEDICINE?
ALRIGHT, THAT MUST HAVE BEEN
WHAT SHE WAS GRINDING IN THERE.
- HERE ARE YOUR CLOTHES, OKAY?
HURRY UP AND COME DOWN.
IF YOU WAIT TOO LONG,
YOUR BREAKFAST'LL GET COLD.
- WHAT HAPPENED TO LAST NIGHT?
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
TO GO EASY ON YOURSELF.
- I DID! I SLEPT IN TODAY!
I USUALLY GET UP
AT AROUND 4:30 OR SO.
BUT INSTEAD I SLEPT IN
UNTIL FIVE O'CLOCK!
- OH.
- ( giggles ) FOR SOME REASON,
WHEN I SLEEP MORE,
IT MAKES ME MORE TIRED.
ISN'T THAT FUNNY?
SO, DO YOU THINK IT
WOULD BE ALL RIGHT
IF I GOT UP AT 4:30
AGAIN TOMORROW?
- I GUESS.
- I'LL BE WAITING FOR
YOU DOWNSTAIRS, OKAY?
- ( sneezing )
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Sia: I CAN'T DECIDE
WHICH CHAIR IS BEST.
- Rin: HOW 'BOUT THIS ONE?
- THAT'S NOT QUITE
STRONG ENOUGH.
- STRONG ENOUGH?
- I'LL HAVE TO TEST IT OUT!
- ( Sia grunts )
- WHAT THE HECK ARE YOU DOING?
- NEXT TIME ON SHUFFLE!
EPISODE 6. SMILE!
I THINK I LIKE THIS ONE.
- YEAH, IT'S GREAT.
GOOD CHOICE.