- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Sia: IS IT STILL
OFFICIALLY SUMMER, RIN?
- IT IS SUMMERTIME. YEP.
- THEN WE STILL HAVE
TIME TO GO TO THE BEACH.
- THAT'S TRUE.
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING CAN BEAT
THE BEACH IN THE SUMMER TIME.
- JUST THINK OF ALL
THE WONDERFUL MEMORIES
WE'LL HAVE CREATED
BY THE TIME IT'S OVER.
- YEAH. GOOD TIMES AND GREAT
FRIENDS TO SHARE THEM WITH.
- UH-HUH.
- Nerine: UH, GUYS?
- ( both gasping )
- THIS IS NO TIME FOR DAYDREAMS.
THERE'S A LOT TO DO.
LIKE FINISHING OUR SUMMER
HOMEWORK BEFORE THE DAY IS DONE.
- OKAY.
- ALWAYS HOMEWORK.
- ( Rin grunts )
I DON'T UNDERSTAND THIS AT ALL.
- WHICH PART?
MAYBE I CAN HELP YOU.
- HERE, THIS EQUATION
MAKES NO SENSE.
- OH, SILLY. ALL YOU NEED TO DO
IS USE THIS FORMULA RIGHT HERE.
SUBSTITUTE THIS NUMBER FOR X
AND CARRY THE REMAINDER.
YOU SEEM A LITTLE DISTRACTED.
- NO. I'M ALL RIGHT.
- REMEMBER TO APPLY THE SAME
RULES TO THESE OTHER EQUATIONS,
AND YOU'LL GET THE
RIGHT ANSWER EVERY TIME.
- OH, I GET IT. YOU KNOW,
THIS REALLY IS SIMPLE.
- YOU SURE ARE A QUICK STUDY.
- OH, BECAUSE YOU'RE A
GOOD TEACHER, NERINE.
THANK YOU FOR TAKING
THE TIME TO HELP ME.
- THAT'S AMAZING. MAYBE YOU
COULD GIVE ME A FEW POINTERS.
- CERTAINLY. WHERE ARE
YOU HAVING TROUBLE?
- ON PROBLEM SEVEN, RIGHT HERE.
- ( chuckling nervously )
- FOR A SECOND THERE, I THOUGHT
NERINE HAD LOST TO YOUR SIA.
- HAD MY DAUGHTER SEIZED THE
MOMENT SHE WOULD'VE WON.
- BUT NERINE'S ABOUT TO
RALLY BACK. YOU WATCH!
- HMM.
IT'S ANYONE'S GAME.
- NOT ANYMORE.
I WIN.
- ( grunts )
( yells )
- Rin: HEY, MAYUMI.
HOW'RE THINGS GOING?
- JUST STOP BOTHERING ME.
I'M BUSY!
- OKAY, OKAY.
I'M JUST RELIEVED TO HEAR THE
SOUND OF YOUR WONDERFUL VOICE.
- THAT'S GREAT.
BUT, RIN, I DON'T HAVE
TIME TO CHAT RIGHT NOW.
JEEZ! I'VE WASTED 5
SECONDS OF MY TIME
TELLING YOU I DON'T HAVE TIME.
GOODBYE.
- PERFECT. WE'RE NOT THE ONLY
ONES SCRAMBLING TO FINISH.
- THAT'S FABULOUS. AND IT
MAKES ME FEEL BETTER SOMEHOW.
- YEAH, BUT WE'RE STILL BEHIND.
SO BACK TO WORK.
- ( groaning )
- Crowd: WHOA!
- ( grunts )
( breathing heavily )
- YES. I'M DONE.
- I'M JEALOUS, RIN.
WE'RE STILL WORKING.
- CONGRATULATIONS ON
ALL YOUR HARD WORK.
- THANKS, NERINE.
IT WASN'T EASY.
- HUH. I SUPPOSE
NOW YOU'RE GONNA GO
HAVE FUN ON YOUR
OWN, AREN'T YOU?
- I DON'T HAVE TIME FOR ANY FUN.
I HAVE TO START WORKING
ON MY ART ASSIGNMENT NEXT.
- OH, RIGHT. A SKETCH THAT
REFLECTS YOUR SUMMER.
BUT HOW WILL YOU CHOOSE?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DRAW?
- I DON'T HAVE TIME TO GO TO
THE BEACH LIKE I HAD PLANNED,
SO I GUESS I'LL
HEAD ON TO THE RIVER.
- I DON'T THINK WE'LL
EVER FINISH AT THIS RATE.
I'M DONE FOR!
- KAEDE, ARE YOU
GOING SOMEWHERE?
- NOT AT THE MOMENT.
I'M PREPARING A
SANDWICH FOR RIN'S LUNCH.
IF I REMEMBER HIS ITINERARY,
AFTER HE FINISHES HIS MATH
AND LANGUAGE ASSIGNMENTS,
HE'LL BE HEADING OUT TO
DO SKETCH WORK FOR ART.
- RIN CAN DRAW?
- YES.
THAT'S WHY I DECIDED
TO MAKE HIM SOMETHING
HE COULD EAT ON THE RUN.
- HOW COME YOU'RE SO MUCH
SMARTER THAN EVERYONE ELSE?
- WELL, ONLY WHEN
IT COMES TO RIN.
- Rin: KAEDE.
MAKE MY LUNCH TO GO.
- SURE, NO PROBLEM.
RIMU, IF YOU'RE NOT DOING
ANYTHING, I COULD USE YOUR HELP.
WOULD YOU MIND
FILLING THE THERMOS
THAT'S ON THE TABLE
WITH ICE TEA?
- SURE.
HMM?
OH.
- THIS LANDSCAPE NEEDS
A LITTLE SOMETHING ELSE.
GUESS I COULD PUT IN A
FEW RANDOM PEOPLE FISHING.
- HEY, NO CHEATING.
- ( groans )
HONESTLY, ASA,
STOP HITTING ME ALL THE TIME.
SINCE YOU'RE HERE, I'M ASSUMING
YOU FINISHED YOUR HOMEWORK.
- OF COURSE.
I THOUGHT I'D MARK THE
END OF OUR SUMMER BREAK
BY SIMPLY RELAXING.
SO I SET OUT FOR A WALK.
- MUST BE GREAT TO
FEEL SO CAREFREE.
- BY THE LOOKS OF IT YOU KNOW
A THING OR TWO ABOUT UNWINDING.
THE PICNIC LUNCH
IS A SMART TOUCH.
OH, IS THAT A BOLOGNA SANDWICH?
DELICIOUS! KAEDE'S NUMBER ONE
IN THE KITCHEN.
NOBODY ELSE CAN COME CLOSE.
- THAT'S QUITE A COMPLIMENT
CONSIDERING YOU TRAINED HER.
- AT THE RATE SHE'S PROGRESSING,
SHE'LL BE READY TO BECOME
YOUR WIFE IN NO TIME, RIN.
- MY WIFE?
- THERE YOU ARE.
IS SOMETHING THE MATTER?
ARE YOU NOT FEELING OKAY?
- IT'S NOTHING.
( sighs )
- ASA, PLEASE.
WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT?
- IF NOT KAEDE,
THEN SIA PERHAPS?
YOU HAVE TO ADMIT, THINGS GOT
PRETTY EXCITING THIS SUMMER.
- BUT, THAT WAS A...
- Sia: RIN.
- IT WASN'T LIKE THAT.
- OKEE DOKE, I BELIEVE YOU.
IF SIA'S NOT YOUR CHOICE,
IT MUST BE NERINE.
- HERE.
- NERINE'S NO STRANGER
TO THE KITCHEN EITHER.
SHE HAS THE CUTS AND
BLISTERS TO PROVE IT.
SHE'S MORE DETERMINED
THAN EVER TO IMPRESS YOU
WITH HER CULINARY SKILLS.
- YOU'RE JUMPING TO CONCLUSIONS
THAT AREN'T TRUE.
- IF I'M WRONG ABOUT
THOSE THREE, THEN WHO?
MAYBE YOU FAVOR PRIMULA?
- ( sighs )
YOU CAN'T BELIEVE THAT.
PLEASE TELL ME YOU'RE KIDDING.
- UH-HUH. OF COURSE.
- I GUESS THIS
MOUNTAIN OF HOMEWORK
HAS RUINED MY SENSE OF HUMOR.
THIS ISN'T EXACTLY HOW I PLANNED
TO BURN MY LAST DAY OF SUMMER.
- REMEMBER, LOVE WON'T
WAIT ON YOU FOREVER.
- THAT MIGHT BE TRUE.
BUT, I CAN'T THINK ABOUT
WHO I'M SUPPOSED TO SPEND
THE REST OF MY
LIFE WITH RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE TO PASS ART FIRST.
- MOST BOYS WOULD DISAGREE.
- I'M NOT SAYING
I'M NOT FLATTERED.
IT'S JUST THIS FRIENDSHIP WE
ALL HAVE IS MORE IMPORTANT.
- ( Asa sighs )
- WHAT ABOUT YOU? EVER SINCE
THAT INCIDENT WITH TAKIZAWA,
I'VE HEARD A FLOOD OF GUYS
HAVE CONFESSED THEIR
UNDYING DEVOTION FOR YOU.
- YEAH, MAYBE THERE'S A SMIDGE
OF TRUTH IN ALL THE RUMORS.
BUT, PICKING A BEAU IS
A LONG WAY OFF FOR ME.
I'M ALL ABOUT HAVING
FUN WITH MY FRIENDS.
- THEN YOU UNDERSTAND EXACTLY
WHERE I'M COMING FROM.
- YEAH. I GUESS SO.
- ( both laugh )
- THE POT IS BOILING OVER.
- I FORGOT.
HOW COULD I HAVE
BEEN THIS CARELESS?
- I THINK WE PASSED ONE A WHILE
BACK, BUT I'M STILL FULL.
- AH-HA. DID I CATCH YOU TWO
ON A SECRET RENDEZVOUS?
- NOPE. WE JUST CAME
BACK FROM THE RIVERBED.
- OH, REALLY? THE RIVERBED?
OH! PERFECT!
- KAREHA, GET A GRIP.
- OH-LA-LA-LA.
- I DON'T THINK A THING
YOU OR I CAN SAY
WILL MAKE A BIT OF DIFFERENCE.
SHE'S MADE UP HER MIND.
- Itsuki: RELAX, RIN!
NOTHING TO BE EMBARRASSED ABOUT.
YOU'RE A YOUNG MAN,
SHE A VOLUPTUOUS WOMAN.
CERTAIN URGES CREEP UP.
WHY, IT'S NOTHING UNUSUAL.
- Both: SHUT UP!
- HUH?
( gasps )
( breathing heavily )
- HOW DID SHE GET LIKE THIS?
- I DON'T HAVE A CLUE.
IT'S THE WEIRDEST THING.
I FOUND HER LAYING
UNCONSCIOUS IN THE BACKYARD.
- WHAT'S SHE HAVE? A FEVER?
- THAT'S THE THING.
THE THERMOMETER MUST BE BROKEN.
- BROKEN? WHAT MAKES
YOU THINK THAT?
- I TOOK HER TEMPERATURE AND
IT WAS 50 DEGREES CELSIUS.
- FIFTY? THAT'S JUST CRAZY.
- THE NORMAL TEMPERATURE
FOR A HUMAN IS 37.
- OF COURSE, RIMU IS NOT FROM
THIS WORLD, SO WHAT'S NORMAL?
- GOOD POINT.
SHE'S OUT OF HER ELEMENT HERE.
HEY, NERINE, TELL US
WHAT WE'RE DEALING WITH?
HAS THIS HAPPENED BEFORE?
NERINE?
I DON'T KNOW ENOUGH ABOUT
YOUR KIND TO MAKE A GUESS.
WOULD IT DO ANY GOOD TO
TAKE RIMU TO A DOCTOR?
- MMM-MMM.
- TELL ME WHAT TO DO.
- ( sighs )
- WHAT DO YOU THINK, SIA?
YOU AND NERINE ARE THE EXPERTS.
WE CAN'T HELP HER
IF YOU WON'T HELP US.
- ( sighs )
- WHY ARE YOU TWO SO
RELUCTANT TO HELP ME?
SPEAK UP! SAY SOMETHING!
- STOP IT, RIN.
- I'M SORRY.
- PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
- I APOLOGIZE.
- ( breathing heavily )
- YOU REST AND GET
WELL SOON, 'KAY?
- WAIT UP.
- WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH THIS GARDEN?
IS PRIMULA RESPONSIBLE
FOR ALL THIS?
WHY WOULD SHE TAKE THE TIME?
- Forbesii: SPEAKING OF TIME,
MAY WE HAVE A MINUTE?
I REGRET THE TROUBLE
PRIMULA'S CAUSED YOU.
- THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
I WANT AN EXPLANATION
FOR HER CONDITION.
YOU KNOW, DON'T YOU?
- NOW CALM DOWN,
YOU MUST EXERCISE PATIENCE.
- THAT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN.
I WANT ANSWERS.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT, SHIN.
AM I TO UNDERSTAND
PRIMULA IS SUFFERING
FROM A HIGH FEVER AT THE MOMENT?
- YES.
- DEMONS AND GODS RARELY
SUFFER SUCH MALADIES.
IT'S PRACTICALLY UNHEARD OF.
- WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
- PLEASE UNDERSTAND,
PRIMULA IS UNIQUE.
SHE IS NEITHER GOD NOR DEMON.
AND, MOST CERTAINLY,
SHE ISN'T A HUMAN EITHER.
- WELL, THEN. WHAT IS SHE?
- SHE'S SPECIAL.
NO, THAT'S AN UNDERSTATEMENT.
ACTUALLY, PRIMULA IS WHAT YOU
HUMANS WOULD CLASSIFY AS A.I.,
AN ARTIFICIAL LIFE FORM.
- YOU'RE JOKING!
YOU'RE SERIOUS, THEN?
BUT...
- Eustoma: PRIMULA IS
A TOP SECRET ENDEAVOR
BETWEEN SCIENTISTS
ON BOTH OUR WORLDS.
- Forbesii: PROJECT YGGDRASIL.
PRIMULA REPRESENTS AN
EVOLUTIONARY TRIUMPH.
THE MOST OUTSTANDING
SENTIENT LIFE FORM
MAGICAL SCIENCE HAS TO OFFER.
- PRIMULA IS NOT
JUST SOME LAB RAT.
WHAT EXACTLY IS THE PURPOSE
OF PROJECT YGGDRASIL?
- LIFE.
THE STUDY OF CREATION.
- CREATION?
- YOU SEE, MAGIC IS
THE POWER OF MIRACLES.
- ( gasps )
- WITH IT, EVEN THE
MOST OUTRAGEOUS DESIRE
CAN BE MADE REALITY.
BUT EVEN THE POWER OF
MAGIC CANNOT HOLD SWAY
OVER THE MOST POWERFUL
FORCE IN THE UNIVERSE.
- HE MEANS, THE GIFT OF LIFE.
- Forbesii: SINCE THE DAWN
OF CREATION,
IT WAS BELIEVED THE DEAD COULD
NOT BE BROUGHT BACK TO LIFE.
AFTER ALL, EVEN THE
RESTORATIVE POWER
OF HEALING MAGIC HAS ITS LIMITS.
BUT WHAT IF WE COULD
ERASE THOSE LIMITATIONS?
WHAT IF WE COULD SAVE
LIVES OF THE TERMINALLY ILL?
OR, INDEED, RETRIEVE PRECIOUS
LIVES THAT WERE ONCE LOST?
THE A.I. PROGRAM WAS
ESTABLISHED TO MAKE THESE
AND OTHER FANTASTIC
ADVANCEMENTS A REALITY.
- YOU MEAN, PRIMULA...
- OH YES, AND SHE IS
AN EXCELLENT SPECIMEN.
- BUT, BECAUSE OF
HER PERFECTION,
SHE'S BEEN FORCED TO SHOULDER
A TERRIBLE RESPONSIBILITY.
- WHAT ARE YOU TELLING ME?
- HER CURRENT STATE IS
AN UNFORTUNATE NECESSITY.
- YOU'RE BACK.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
- OUT WALKING.
WELL, HOW'S SHE DOING?
- SLEEPING. KAEDE'S KEEPING
AN EYE ON HER RIGHT NOW.
- WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
- YOU SEEM SO UPSET.
- OH, IT'S NOTHING.
I'LL GO CHECK ON HER.
- ( door opens )
- HEY.
- NO CHANGE.
HER FEVER HASN'T GONE DOWN.
- ( breathing heavily )
- Eustoma: THERE'S A TREMENDOUS
AMOUNT OF MAGICAL POWER
PENT UP INSIDE THAT TINY BODY.
SO MUCH THAT SHE CAN
WORK MIRACLES BEYOND THAT
WHICH NORMAL MAGIC
IS CAPABLE OF.
- Forbesii: SHIN AND I
WOULD HAVE DIFFICULTY
CONTROLLING SUCH POWER.
FOR PRIMULA, THIS ABILITY
IS A DOUBLE EDGED SWORD.
A BLESSING AND A CURSE.
- YOU'RE AWFULLY QUIET.
WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
- KAEDE, I'VE JUST LEARNED
SOMETHING TERRIBLE.
WE REALLY DON'T
KNOW PRIMULA AT ALL.
- Sia: RIN, ARE YOU POSITIVE?
- YEAH. DON'T WORRY.
BESIDES, IT'S GETTING LATE.
KAEDE AND I CAN MANAGE
THINGS FROM HERE.
- IF YOU'RE CERTAIN.
BUT, IF ANYTHING HAPPENS, YOU
BE SURE TO CALL US RIGHT AWAY.
- I WILL.
PLEASE GO REST, YOU TWO.
- RIN, YOU'RE NOT GONNA
BELIEVE IT. RIMU'S AWAKE.
- HUH?
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
- NOT SO GOOD, RIN.
- I FEEL TERRIBLE THAT
I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO
DO ANYTHING FOR YOU.
- IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
I KNOW YOU TRIED.
- LISTEN, RIMU.
I HAVE A FAVOR I WANNA ASK YOU.
- OKAY?
- I WANT YOU TO GO BACK
TO THE DEMON WORLD.
- RIN, WHAT ARE YOU ASKING?
- I KNOW IT SOUNDS LIKE
A BIZARRE THING TO ASK.
BUT PRIMULA'S ILLNESS
CAN'T BE CURED IN OUR WORLD,
ONLY IN HER OWN.
THAT INFORMATION COMES STRAIGHT
FROM THE KING OF DEMONS HIMSELF.
IF YOU JUST RETURN HOME.
IF YOU WILLINGLY GO
BACK TO THE DEMON REALM.
HE SAYS THEY'LL CURE YOU.
- NO.
- BUT, YOU MUST!
- I WANNA STAY WITH YOU.
- YOU CAN'T GET HEALTHY
IF YOU STAY IN THIS WORLD.
GO HOME FOR NOW
AND WHEN YOU'RE BETTER,
YOU CAN COME BACK HERE.
- I'M NOT LEAVING.
- RIMU, PLEASE.
- Forbesii: THE REASON WE
ALLOWED PRIMULA TO LIVE WITH YOU
WAS BECAUSE THERE WAS A CHANCE
SHE MIGHT LEARN TO CONTROL
HER SPECIAL ABILITIES.
THAT WAS THE THOUGHT
BEHIND BRINGING HER HERE.
- I'M NOT SURE
I'M FOLLOWING YOU.
- THROUGH OUR RESEARCH,
ONE FACT BECAME CRYSTAL CLEAR,
EMOTIONS HAVE A HUGE IMPACT
ON HER MAGIC.
- YOU'LL RECALL THAT WHEN
YOU FIRST MET PRIMULA,
IT WAS RARE FOR HER
TO EXPRESS EMOTION.
- THAT'S RIGHT, BUT THEN AS SHE
GOT USED TO US SHE OPENED UP.
- Forbesii: YES, AND YET,
EVERYTHING THAT LITTLE GIRL
HAS GONE THROUGH
HAS TAKEN ITS TOLL,
ROBBING HER OF HER EMOTIONS.
- Rin: GO ON.
- ONE SOLUTION THE RESEARCH
LAB CAME UP WITH WAS THIS.
IF PRIMULA WERE ABLE TO
REGAIN HER HUMANISTIC EMOTIONS,
THEN SHE MIGHT BE ABLE TO
CONTROL THE MAGIC INSIDE OF HER.
- SO, WE BROUGHT HER HERE,
HOPING SHE TOO WOULD
FIND YOU COMPELLING
THEREBY RESTORING HER
DORMANT EMOTIONS. IT WORKED.
- IT WORKED, HUH?
THEN HOW COME PRIMULA IS
LYING IN BED WITH A FEVER?
- THE RESEARCH WAS
FLAWED, CLEARLY.
- THE FUTURE IS IMPOSSIBLE
TO KNOW, EVEN FOR THE TWO OF US.
OUR ONLY CHOICE IS TO RETURN
HER TO THE WORLD OF DEMONS
AND PERFORM MORE TESTS.
- Forbesii: RIN, IT'S IMPERATIVE
YOU CONVINCE PRIMULA
TO RETURN TO HER WORLD.
- Primula: I'M NOT LEAVING.
- ( knocking on door )
- HMM?
- TELL ME WHAT'S GOING ON?
DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING TO SAY?
( sighs )
YOU KNEW... YOU KNEW PRIMULA
IS AN ARTIFICIAL LIFE FORM.
AND YOU MUST'VE ALSO KNOWN
THAT NOTHING CAN BE DONE
UNLESS SHE GOES BACK
TO THE DEMON WORLD.
- SHE'LL ONLY
LISTEN TO YOU, RIN.
TELL RIMU TO GO HOME
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
- I TRIED THAT,
BUT SHE DOESN'T WANT TO.
- SHE'LL DIE IF SHE STAYS.
- YES, SHE WILL. I KNOW.
BUT THE CHOICE TO STAY
OR GO IS HERS TO MAKE.
- YOU'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING.
- AW, NERINE.
- I KNOW MY HOME WORLD
CAN SAVE HER.
I COULDN'T BEAR IT IF
ANYTHING HAPPENED TO HER.
NOT NOW.
I CAN'T LOSE ANYONE ELSE.
- YOU WON'T.
- PROMISE ME,
YOU'LL HELP HER, RIN.
- ( giggling )
( gasps )
( sighs )
- ( door opens )
- UH, RIN.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- PLEASE LISTEN.
PRIMULA, YOU MUST GO BACK HOME.
- NO, I CAN'T.
- RIN, DON'T.
- PLEASE, DO IT FOR MY SAKE.
- RIN?
- I BEG YOU.
- FOR YOU.
- BE GOOD,
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF.
- I WILL.
- THANK YOU. BE STRONG.
- RIN, I...
GOODBYE.
- PLEASE COME BACK SOON.
( crying )
- GOODBYE.
HOPE I DID THE RIGHT THING.
- Man: SIR, I'M AFRAID WE WILL
NOT BE ABLE TO LET HER RETURN
TO THE HUMAN WORLD EVER AGAIN.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Kaede: I GOT UP THIS MORNING
AND PREPARED
BREAKFAST FOR THREE.
LATER, AS I WAS ABOUT
TO LEAVE THE HOUSE,
I CALLED OUT FOR
RIMU TO JOIN ME,
EVEN THOUGH I KNEW
SHE WASN'T THERE.
- Rin: NEXT TIME ON SHUFFLE,
EPISODE 13, HOUSE OF TWILIGHT.
- Kaede: RIN, YOU DO BELIEVE