- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- LISTEN UP, EVERYONE.
TAKE YOUR SEATS. QUICKLY!
WHERE ARE RIN AND SIA?
- ( Asa whining )
OH, JEEZ! RIN, WHERE ARE YOU?
- ( giggling ) COME ON! SILLY.
- HEY, HOLD ON A SECOND!
- COME ON. HURRY!
- SIA, STOP IT!
THAT'S ENOUGH, OKAY?
MAN, I BET CLASS HAS ALREADY
STARTED BY NOW.
- OH, WHO CARES?
FORGET ABOUT SCHOOL.
WHY DON'T WE JUST SKIP IT TODAY?
- HUH?
SKIP SCHOOL? THAT'S REALLY
EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
BUT JUST THINK WHAT WILL HAPPEN
TO US IF MISS NA FINDS OUT.
IT WON'T BE PRETTY,
YOU CAN BE SURE OF THAT.
- RIN, ARE YOU JUST
SAYING ALL THAT
BECAUSE YOU DON'T WANT TO
GO ON A DATE WITH ME?
- NO, NOT AT ALL! UH, WELL,
YOU SEE, IT'S JUST THAT...
IF YOU WANT TO GO OUT,
IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE TODAY.
- LIAR!
YOU'RE MAKING EXCUSES!
AND I HAVE NOTICED THAT
YOU HAVEN'T SPENT
ANY TIME WITH ME LATELY.
- WHAT ARE YOU...
MAYBE YOU'RE A LITTLE RIGHT.
- I AM RIGHT!
AND THAT'S WHY I DECIDED...
THAT YOU AND I ARE GOING
ON A DATE TODAY, ALL DAY.
AND YOU'RE ONLY GOING TO
PAY ATTENTION TO ME!
YOU'RE NOT GETTING AWAY FROM ME.
- SIA, I REALLY THINK WE
SHOULD BE HEADING TO SCHOOL.
- WELL, IF THAT'S THE WAY
YOU'RE GOING TO BE,
YOU LEAVE ME WITH NO CHOICE.
- ( screaming )
- ( Kikyou shrieking )
THAT MONSTER! YOU PERVERT!
HE PULLED UP MY SKIRT!
- NO! WAIT A SECOND! SIA?
- HE TRIED TO MOLEST ME!
- Woman: HOW DISGUSTING!
- NO, REALLY, IT'S NOT WHAT...
- Man: SCUMBAG!
- HEY! HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
- I PROMISE, I DIDN'T.
I THINK WE FINALLY LOST THEM.
NO THANKS TO YOU, SIA.
- ( giggles )
- WELL, READY TO GO?
- YEAH.
WE'RE REALLY LATE
FOR SCHOOL NOW.
SIA?
- SO, I GUESS, SCHOOL'S MORE
IMPORTANT TO YOU THAN ME, HUH?
- SIA, STOP IT! THAT'S
NOT IT AT ALL.
- BUT THAT IS IT!
THERE REALLY IS A REASON I
ASKED YOU OUT TODAY BUT...
I DON'T KNOW.
I DO HAVE SOMETHING
IMPORTANT TO TELL YOU,
BUT I CAN'T DO IT AT SCHOOL.
- IT'S SOMETHING IMPORTANT?
- OH, I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHY I'M TRYING.
YOU'LL JUST
END UP SAYING "NO".
- SIA...
( sighs ) WELL, OKAY THEN.
- DOCTOR? MY WIFE? HOW IS SHE?
- THERE REALLY IS
NO EASY WAY TO SAY THIS...
BUT YOUR WIFE ONLY HAS
ONE MORE WEEK TO LIVE.
- WHAT? NO! OH, GOD!
- Rin: OKAY...
SO WHY ARE WE WATCHING A MOVIE?
- HEY, SIA?
WHAT WAS THAT IMPORTANT THING
YOU WANTED TO TELL ME?
- HMM?
- COME ON, WHAT'S GOTTEN
INTO YOU TODAY?
YOU'RE ACTING KINDA WEIRD
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
- ( shrieking ) HOLD ME, RIN,
I'M SO SCARED!
- SIA! HEY!
- ( crying ) NO!
- ARE YOU GOING
TO GET WELL, MOM?
- ( Asa groaning )
MY ARMS ARE SO SORE.
- YOU CARRIED IT
ALL BY YOURSELF?
- UM, EXCUSE ME. ASA?
- HMM?
- Kareha: OH.
WHAT BRINGS YOU HERE, KAEDE?
- KAEDE? ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I'M SURE I'M WORRYING ABOUT
NOTHING, BUT HAVE YOU SEEN RIN?
HE LEFT THE HOUSE
EARLY THIS MORNING
AND HE SAID HE WAS STOPPING BY
YOUR PLACE, BUT...
- WAIT. HE'S NOT HERE?
- NO.
- WELL, THAT'S WEIRD.
HE TOLD ME HE'D MEET ME
AT MY PLACE BEFORE SCHOOL,
BUT, HE STOOD ME UP
THIS MORNING.
- OOH LA LA.
I DON'T MEAN TO SOUND MORBID,
BUT, YOU DON'T THINK HE
WAS IN AN ACCIDENT, DO YOU?
- OR MAYBE ON HIS WAY TO
MY HOUSE THIS MORNING,
HE GOT KIDNAPPED.
- KIDNAPPED?
( exclaims )
- KAEDE!
- KAEDE'S GONE, TOO?
- ( Kikyou humming )
- I HOPE ASA WILL
STILL TALK TO ME AFTER THIS.
- HEY, RIN.
TELL ME, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- ABOUT THE DRESS? IT'S REALLY
NICE. BUT, I DON'T KNOW...
I DON'T THINK IT'S YOUR STYLE.
- OH. WELL. AND THIS ONE?
- THAT'S, UM...
THAT ONE'S MUCH BETTER.
( groans )
I REALLY DON'T KNOW
IF I SHOULD BE DOING THIS, SIA.
- THEN HOW ABOUT THIS?
- ( screams )
- EXCUSE, ME? MA'AM? IS
EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT IN THERE?
HUH. I COULD'VE SWORN...
- OH, IT'S OKAY, SWEETIE.
THERE'S NO REASON FOR YOU
TO BE EMBARRASSED WITH ME.
- THAT'S EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
YOU DIDN'T GET FLASHED.
- DON'T WORRY. I'M JUST FINE
WITH YOU SEEING MY BODY.
IN FACT, IF YOU'D LIKE,
I'D BE MORE THAN HAPPY TO
SHOW YOU THE REST OF IT.
- SIA...
- ( giggling )
- WELL, THAT WAS FUN.
WHAT SHOULD WE DO NEXT?
- HAVEN'T WE DONE
ENOUGH ALREADY?
LOOK, WHY DON'T WE BUY SOMETHING
FOR DINNER AND HEAD HOME?
- DINNER?
HEY, DON'T WORRY ABOUT DINNER.
THE ONLY THING YOU NEED
TO CONCERN YOURSELF WITH
RIGHT NOW IS, ME. OKAY?
- UH... YOU'RE...
YOU ARE REALLY SIA, RIGHT?
- WELL, OF COURSE I AM, RIN.
I MEAN, COME ON, IF I'M NOT SIA,
WHO THE HECK ELSE WOULD I BE?
HEY, RIN.
LET'S GO SIT OVER THERE!
HEY. COME ON, RIN!
SITTING HERE ALONE LIKE THIS...
IT FEELS ALMOST LIKE YOU AND I
ARE THE ONLY TWO PEOPLE
IN THE WHOLE WORLD RIGHT NOW.
EARLIER...
I MEANT IT.
I AM SERIOUS, RIN.
YOU CAN SEE ALL OF ME.
- SIA!
- IF YOU WANT.
- ( heart beating )
- WHY, RIN?
WHY NOT?
DON'T YOU...
THIS WAS WRONG.
( crying )
- SIA!
NO! SIA, DON'T!
I'M BACK, KAE...
- OH. WELCOME HOME, RIN.
- ( all gasping )
- OH, RIN!
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
- ( stomach grumbling )
( sighs )
SIA. WHERE ARE YOU? WE SHOULD
HAVE HAD DINNER HOURS AGO.
- ( door opening )
- SHE'S BACK!
OH, SWEETHEART! I WAS WONDERING
WHEN YOU'D GET HOME.
GUESS YOU'RE GOING
TO COOK DINNER NOW, RIGHT?
- ( stomach grumbling )
- ( crying ) RIN.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU.
YOU'RE TERRIBLE!
WHY? WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
- BECAUSE SOMETHING
HAD TO BE DONE
SINCE YOU WERE TAKING FOREVER
TO MAKE A MOVE.
I DID YOU A FAVOR
AND JUST MADE IT FOR YOU.
- BUT I NEVER ASKED YOU TO.
YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE DONE THAT!
- SORRY, I DIDN'T
KNOW YOU WERE OKAY
WITH THE WAY THINGS WERE GOING.
ARE YOU TELLING ME THAT YOU
PREFERRED IT THAT WAY?
NOT BEING ABLE TO TELL RIN
HOW YOU FEEL?
- AT LEAST I WAS HAPPIER THEN!
I WOULD HAVE BEEN FINE
KEEPING THINGS THE SAME
IF I KNEW HOW TODAY
WAS GOING TO TURN OUT.
BUT NOW, HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO FACE RIN AFTER ALL THIS?
- THERE'S SOMETHING
WRONG WITH RIN.
YOU THREW YOURSELF AT HIM
AND HE WOULDN'T EVEN KISS YOU.
YOU KNOW, I TOTALLY THOUGHT
THINGS WOULD GO WELL
FOR YOU TODAY, SIA.
I KEPT TELLING MYSELF,
"SIA DESERVES THIS.
SHE DESERVES TO FALL IN LOVE!"
"SHE DESERVES HAPPINESS!"
GUESS I WAS WRONG.
- HAPPINESS?
- OF COURSE!
I MEAN, YOU REALLY ARE IN
LOVE WITH RIN, AREN'T YOU?
SO THEN IF YOU TOLD HIM THAT,
MAYBE IT WOULD LEAD
TO HIM LOVING YOU!
- YEAH, BUT...
- SIA, DON'T YOU WANT TO
FIND HAPPINESS?
- YES, BUT...
IT'S OKAY. REALLY.
BECAUSE...
I DON'T WANT ANY HAPPINESS IF IT
MEANS I HAVE TO BE SELFISH.
- SIA!
JUST SAY IT.
IS IT BECAUSE OF ME?
- NO! IT'S NOT. NOT AT ALL.
PLEASE DON'T THINK THAT!
- DON'T LIE!
YOU CAN'T HIDE ANYTHING
FROM ME. YOU NEVER COULD.
DON'T FORGET THAT I AM INSIDE
YOU, I KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
HOW DO YOU THINK THAT
MAKES ME FEEL?
KNOWING THAT YOU CAN'T
EVER BE HAPPY PERSONALLY
BECAUSE YOU'RE TOO CONCERNED
ABOUT MY HAPPINESS?
MAYBE IT'S TIME
I FOUND HAPPINESS ON MY OWN.
LOOK, IF YOU REALLY CARE
ABOUT ME, SIA,
THEN YOU'LL GO FIND
HAPPINESS FOR YOURSELF.
- DOES THAT MEAN YOU'RE...
- I'M AFRAID SO. YEAH.
I'VE GOT TO. EVERY
TIME I COME OUT,
I'VE CAUSED SO MUCH
TROUBLE FOR YOU, SIA,
SO...
SO, I'LL JUST...
I'LL GO AWAY.
AND NEVER BOTHER YOU AGAIN.
- KIKYOU! PLEASE, DON'T!
- GO FIND YOUR HAPPINESS.
- WAIT! DON'T GO. STAY HERE.
DON'T LEAVE.
DON'T GO AWAY.
PLEASE, JUST STAY WITH ME.
- I'LL ALWAYS LOVE YOU, SIA.
- ( crying )
- Mayumi: WELL, GOOD MORNING,
RIN. KAEDE. NERINE.
- Rin: MORNING.
- Kaede: AND A GOOD MORNING
TO YOU, MAYUMI.
- Nerine: HOW ARE YOU TODAY?
- Sia: RIN...
- Mayumi: KAEDE CALLED
AND TOLD ME EVERYTHING.
SO, YOU FINALLY HAD A RUN-IN
WITH SOME COPPERS, HUH?
- "FINALLY?" HEY, WHAT DO
YOU MEAN BY THAT EXACTLY?
- OH, I DON'T KNOW.
I JUST ALWAYS THOUGHT YOU'D
EVENTUALLY BE WANTED
BY THE POLICE FOR
SOMETHING OR THE OTHER.
- Kaede: MAYUMI, STOP!
- WAIT, YOU DIDN'T TELL ANYONE
ELSE ABOUT THIS, DID YOU?
PLEASE, TELL ME YOU DIDN'T.
- UH, TELL EVERYONE ELSE
ABOUT WHAT, RIN?
- Mayumi: OH, YOU'VE GOT TO
HEAR THIS. IT'S A RIOT!
- Rin: COME ON, MAYUMI!
- Mayumi: OW! HEY,
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
- Rin: YOU SURE DO
HAVE A BIG MOUTH.
- NO, I HAVEN'T.
- Rin: SOMEBODY BACK ME UP HERE.
- Mayumi: WELL, DON'T
LOOK AT ME, MISTER.
- HEY! GOOD MORNING, RIN!
- OH. HELLO, ASA. GOOD MORNING.
- OH, YES. GOOD MORNING.
- NICE ONE, ASA.
- WHAT GIVES, ASA? THAT WAS
A LITTLE HARDER THAN USUAL.
- HUH? I WONDER WHY?
IT COULDN'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO
WITH YOU STANDING ME UP
YESTERDAY, COULD IT?
- UH... YEAH. YOU SEE...
ABOUT THAT, I CAN EXPLAIN...
- REALLY?
WHY DON'T YOU START THEN?
- WELL, IT'S LIKE THIS, I...
- WHATEVER.
I WAS SURPRISED THAT KAEDE
THOUGHT I WAS BEING SERIOUS
ABOUT THE KIDNAPPING THING.
I NEVER THOUGHT
SHE'D ACTUALLY CALL THE POLICE.
- Kaede: BUT I THOUGHT...
- SO YOU'RE THE GUILTY ONE
WHO PUT THAT CRAZY IDEA
IN HER HEAD, WEREN'T YOU?
IT TOOK ME HOURS TO STRAIGHTEN
THINGS OUT WITH THE COPS.
- SERVES YOU RIGHT,
BUT DON'T YOU DARE TRY
AND BLAME ME FOR THAT.
BLAME THE GUY WHO BROKE HIS
PROMISE AND STOOD ME UP INSTEAD.
- BUT, ASA, THAT HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH THIS! HEY!
- WOULD YOU JUST WAIT A MINUTE?
- Sia: OF COURSE.
- THAT MIGHT EXPLAIN
SOME THINGS.
ASA, PLEASE. I CAN EXPLAIN
EVERYTHING! IT'S LIKE THIS...
- ( clock chiming )
- Nadeshiko: OKAY!
THAT'S ALL FOR TODAY.
- WELL, ALL RIGHT.
THANKS TO KAEDE
SMOOTHING THINGS OVER,
MISS NA DOESN'T WANT
TO KILL US NOW.
- HELLO.
HEY, RIN. DO YOU THINK WE
COULD TALK AFTER CLASS?
SEE YOU THEN.
I LOVE THIS!
IT REALLY IS A PERFECT
AUTUMN DAY, ISN'T IT?
- OH. UH, YEAH.
- WOW!
LOOK AT ALL THIS!
THERE ARE SO MANY FLOWERS!
I WONDER WHAT
THIS KIND IS CALLED?
- WELL, SIA, YOU'RE BACK
TO YOUR OLD SELF TODAY.
- HOW DID YOU FEEL ABOUT THE
SIA FROM YESTERDAY, RIN?
I'M SORRY FOR ALL THE TROUBLE
THAT I CAUSED YOU.
THAT WAS A SIDE OF ME
YOU HAD NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
WELL, THE TRUTH IS, THERE'S
ANOTHER SIA INSIDE OF ME.
- HUH?
- I KNOW THIS MIGHT BE
HARD TO BELIEVE.
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN HONEST
AND TOLD YOU THIS BEFORE.
BUT I DIDN'T KNOW HOW. I WAS
SCARED OF WHAT YOU'D THINK.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO
HAVE A TWIN SISTER.
- "SUPPOSED TO HAVE"?
DOES THAT MEAN? YOU LOST?
- YEAH.
THERE WERE SOME
COMPLICATIONS WITH MY SISTER
WHEN WE WERE STILL IN THE WOMB.
AND SO...
I WAS BORN AN ONLY CHILD.
- SIA, I'M SORRY.
- IT'S REALLY SAD, ISN'T IT?
IT BREAKS MY HEART.
SO, IN THE WOMB, RIGHT BEFORE
MY SISTER FADED AWAY,
I ABSORBED ALL OF
HER THOUGHTS AND FEELINGS.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
DISAPPEAR COMPLETELY.
YOU'RE A SPECIAL PART OF ME.
I DON'T WANT TO LOSE YOU.
SO, LET'S STAY TOGETHER.
YOU'LL ALWAYS BE WITH ME.
WE'LL BE SISTERS FOREVER, OKAY?
AND SINCE THAT DAY, THERE HAVE
BEEN TWO VERSIONS OF ME.
ONE IS THE NORMAL ME
WHO'S STANDING IN FRONT
OF YOU RIGHT NOW.
AND THE OTHER,
YOU MET YESTERDAY.
I GUESS YOU COULD SAY THERE ARE
TWO VERY DIFFERENT PEOPLE
LIVING INSIDE OF ME.
I EXPERIENCE SO MANY DIFFERENT
EMOTIONS LIKE EVERYBODY ELSE.
WHETHER I'M LAUGHING, CRYING,
OR FALLING IN LOVE,
YOU'RE STILL SEEING
THE NORMAL SIA.
BUT, SOMETIMES,
THE OTHER ME COMES OUT
CAUSING THOSE SAME EMOTIONS
TO BE MUCH MORE INTENSE.
SO THEN, SHE HAS TO GO BACK
INSIDE MY SUBCONSCIOUS,
ALL ALONE.
THAT'S WHY I DECIDED THAT
I CAN'T BE HAPPY ON THE OUTSIDE
IF SHE'S UNHAPPY ON THE INSIDE.
BECAUSE THAT JUST WOULDN'T
BE FAIR TO HER, WOULD IT?
- I SEE.
- HOWEVER, THANKS TO YOU, RIN,
I REALIZED SOMETHING.
ALL THIS TIME, SHE COULDN'T
STAND THAT WAY OF THINKING.
- HUH?
- I REALLY BELIEVED THAT
HAPPINESS FOR MYSELF
WAS IMPOSSIBLE.
MY SISTER NEVER WANTED ME
TO GO THROUGH LIFE LIKE THAT,
SHE DIDN'T WANT ME TO BE ALONE.
SO EVEN THOUGH SHE CAUSED
A LOT OF TROUBLE,
SHE WAS JUST TRYING TO HELP.
SHE DIDN'T MEAN TO
INTERFERE AT ALL.
SHE ONLY WANTED WHAT SHE
THOUGHT WAS BEST FOR MY LIFE.
SHE COULDN'T EXPERIENCE
IT FOR HERSELF,
BUT SHE WANTED ME TO BE HAPPY.
- REALLY?
- MY SISTER FINALLY GAVE ME
THE COURAGE I NEEDED.
THE COURAGE TO LOVE,
AND TO BE OKAY WITH WANTING
THAT FOR MYSELF.
I NEED TO SAY SOMETHING
AGAIN TO YOU.
I LOVE YOU. REALLY.
FROM THE BOTTOM OF MY HEART.
- SIA.
I'M SORRY.
- YOU KNOW, I HAD A FEELING
YOU'D SAY THAT, RIN.
SO, I GUESS THERE MUST BE
SOMEONE ELSE SPECIAL
IN YOUR LIFE, ISN'T THERE?
- SIA.
- HEY, I AM REALLY SORRY
I'VE BEEN KEEPING
SOMETHING THIS
IMPORTANT FROM YOU.
I EVEN SAID I WANTED YOU
TO GET TO KNOW ME BETTER.
IT FEELS SO GOOD TO FINALLY
GET THIS OFF MY CHEST!
WELL, COME ON, RIN.
LET'S GET GOING.
- OH, THERE'S ONE THING
YOU MIGHT WANT TO KNOW.
- HMM?
- IN THE REALM OF THE GODS,
IT'S COMMON FOR A MAN TO
HAVE MANY WIVES.
- HUH?
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Nerine: WE'VE REALIZED
SOMETHING IN SPITE OF OURSELVES.
- Sia: BECAUSE ALL
OF US LOVE RIN.
- Nerine: THEN, FOR RIN'S SAKE,
AS WELL AS OUR OWN.
- Primula: NEXT TIME ON SHUFFLE.
EPISODE 18, "THE ONE RIN LOVES"
- Rin: I SHOULDN'T LET THINGS
DRAG ON LIKE THIS, SHOULD I?