- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- WATCH THE HOUSE FOR US
WHILE WE'RE OUT!
- I HOPE YOU LIKE WHAT
I MADE FOR LUNCH TODAY.
IT'S PROBABLY ON THE COUNTER.
WELL, YOU KNOW,
WHERE IT USUALLY IS.
- YES, I KNOW.
- COME ON, RIN!
TIME TO GO!
- HELLO, THERE. IT'S NICE
TO SEE YOU THIS MORNING.
- MORNING, YOU TWO. WE'LL
SEE YOU LATER, PRIMULA!
- TAKE CARE, RIMU.
- HAVE A NICE DAY.
- ( clock ticking )
- I WAS WONDERING...
DOESN'T RIMU GET LONELY AT HOME
BY HERSELF? I KNOW I WOULD.
- YEAH, I FEEL KIND OF BAD
FOR LEAVING HER, BUT...
- THERE ISN'T ANYTHING
WE CAN DO ABOUT IT.
- SINCE WE'RE ON THE SUBJECT,
THERE'S SOMETHING THAT
I'VE NOTICED RECENTLY.
SHE NEVER SMILES.
I DON'T THINK SHE'S SMILED
ONCE SINCE SHE'S BEEN HERE.
- Kaede: ( gasps ) YOU'RE RIGHT!
- I MEAN, KIDS HERE AGE
ARE USUALLY MORE CHEERFUL
AND DOING ANYTHING
THEY CAN TO HAVE FUN.
THEY LAUGH, THEY GET IN TROUBLE.
I CAN'T HELP FEELING
LIKE SHE'S UNHAPPY.
- I KNOW.
DO YOU THINK MAYBE
IT'S OUR FAULT
FOR LEAVING HER
ALONE ALL THE TIME?
- OH, NO!
NO, IT ISN'T YOU. SHE WAS LIKE
THAT EVEN WHEN SHE WAS BACK
IN THE REALM OF THE DEMONS.
- SHE'S ALWAYS LIKE THIS?
- WELL, SHE DOESN'T REALLY
SHOW ANY OF HER EMOTIONS,
SO SHE'S HARD TO READ.
- WE JUST NEED TO BE
A LITTLE MORE PATIENT
AND GIVE HER SOME TIME
TO GET USED TO
LIVING IN THIS WORLD
SHE'LL COME AROUND
AND LOVE BEING HERE, YOU'LL SEE!
- LEMME THINK.
MAYBE WE COULD COME UP
WITH SOME SORT OF EXCUSE.
- AN EXCUSE? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- YOU KNOW, TO TAKE
HER SOMEWHERE FUN.
WHAT DO KIDS LIKE?
IT SHOULD BE SOMEWHERE
WE CAN ALL GO.
I DON'T KNOW, WE'LL
FIGURE IT OUT.
- YEAH, THAT'S A GOOD IDEA!
- ( both giggling )
- ( clattering )
- ALRIGHT! WOULD YOU JUST
LISTEN FOR A SECOND?
- ( beeping )
- SINCE ANCIENT TIMES MANY HAVE
TRIED TO FIND THE SECRETS
TO ETERNAL YOUTH AND LONG LIFE.
MANY PEOPLE THROUGHOUT THE AGES
HAVE BELIEVED MAGIC TO
BE THE OBVIOUS SOLUTION.
ALTHOUGH WE UNDERSTAND THAT
MAGIC CAN DO MANY THINGS,
IT CANNOT REVIVE THE DEAD.
EVEN NOW, THE MYSTERIES
OF LIFE AND DEATH
ARE ACTIVELY BEING RESEARCHED
ON ALL THREE WORLDS.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- ( gasping )
- Lycoris: PRIMULA.
- ( giggles )
A CAT.
- THIS IS SOMETHING THAT'S
VERY SPECIAL TO ME.
WHAT THIS TOY
MEANS TO ME IS LOVE.
- LOVE?
- Itsuki: HEYA, RIN!
SO I HEAR YOU'VE
HAD SOME PROBLEMS
WITH YOUR LITTLE GIRLFRIEND.
- SHE'S NOT A GIRLFRIEND.
- COME ON NOW, MAN!
I CAN UNDERSTAND WHY YOU
DON'T WANT ANYONE TO KNOW
ABOUT THE CRADLE-ROBBIN' THING,
BUT I ACCEPT YA JUST THE WAY
THAT YOU ARE, SO WHAT'S UP? HUH?
- DUDE, I'M NOT A PEDOPHILE.
CUT IT OUT AND WHERE IS
ALL THIS COMING FROM?
- Sia: I AM SO SORRY!
WE DECIDED TO TELL HIM ABOUT
OUR TALK THIS MORNING.
- YEAH, HE SEEMED
LIKE THE KIND OF GUY
WHO WOULD KNOW HOW
TO CHEER SOMEONE UP,
SO WE THOUGHT WE'D ASK
HIS ADVICE. IS THAT BAD?
- IT'S A COMPLETE WASTE.
WHAT WERE YOU GUYS
THINKING ANYWAY?
- ( laughing nervously )
- JUST LISTEN, ALL
YOU EVER HAVE TO DO
TO GET ON A GIRL'S GOOD SIDE
IS BUY HER A GIFT. IT'S EASY.
- SO I BUY HER A DOLL
AND IT'S ALL OVER, HUH?
- TSK, TSK. RIN, RIN, RIN,
SO MUCH TO LEARN!
OKAY, YOUNG GIRLS
ONLY WANT ONE THING,
AND THAT IS TO FEEL
MORE LIKE GROWN-UPS.
- AND WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- IT MEANS LINGERIE!
THAT'S RIGHT,
BUY HER LINGERIE AND THEN
YOU GET TO PICK OUT EXACTLY
WHAT YOU WANT HER TO WEAR!
- ( sighing ) SOMEHOW I DON'T
THINK THAT'S THE ANSWER,
BUT THANKS.
- OH, THOUGH I BET THAT LITTLE
GIRL WOULD ALSO LOOK GOOD
IN A SCHOOL SWIMSUIT.
- NOT THAT AGAIN.
SOMEONE PLEASE RID HIM
OF THAT STUPID SWIMSUIT FETISH?
- ( together ) COUNT US OUT!
- HEY, ROMEO. IT LOOKS LIKE
YET ANOTHER GIRLFRIEND
HAS APPEARED ON THE SCENE!
- PLEASE DON'T STOOP TO ITSUKI'S
LEVEL WITH THOSE KINDS OF JOKES.
- YOU FLATTER ME.
- DOES SHE LOOK LIKE
A JOKE TO YOU?
- Rin: PRIMULA?
- Kaede: ARE YOU OKAY?
- Boy: ( whispering )
WHO'S THAT GIRL?
- WHAT'S SHE DOING HERE?
- ( whispering ) ANOTHER GIRL
HERE FOR RIN?
- Girl: OH MY GOSH!
SHE'S SO ADORABLE!
- Boy: ( whispering ) THIS
ONE CAN'T BE A GOOD IDEA,
EVEN FOR HIM!
- HI, RIN.
- IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
- WHAT HAPPENED? WAS THERE
A PROBLEM AT HOME?
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
THAT'S BOTHERING HER.
- SO I GUESS THIS MUST BE
THE NEW ONE, RIGHT?
DO YOUR OTHER GIRLFRIENDS
APPROVE OF THIS?
- GIRLFRIENDS? WHERE DO YOU COME
UP WITH THIS STUFF, MAYUMI?
- WELL, THEY ARE YOUR
GIRLFRIENDS, AREN'T THEY?
COME ON, THE TRUTH
NEVER HURT ANYONE.
- THERE IS NOTHING TRUTHFUL
ABOUT THAT STATEMENT!
- RINA! ( screams )
RINA, DID YOU HEAR THAT?
SHE CALLED US RIN'S GIRLFRIENDS!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
IT'S JUST LIKE A DREAM!
- I KNOW IT'S KIND
OF EMBARRASSING,
BUT THE THOUGHT OF BEING
WITH HIM LIKE THAT
JUST MADE MY HEART BEAT
A LITTLE FASTER!
- RIN'S GIRLFRIEND?
- ( students muttering )
- ( clock chiming )
- LOOK WHAT YOU'VE DONE, MAYUMI.
WHAT'S THE POINT
OF THIS, REALLY?
- WHATEVER, STOP TRYING TO
COVER IT UP AND INTRODUCE HER.
COME ON! WE WANT TO MEET
GIRL NUMBER FOUR, BE POLITE!
- YOU MAKE IT SOUND LIKE
SOME KIND OF FAN CLUB.
THIS IS PRIMULA. SHE'S LIKE
NERINE'S LITTLE SISTER
WHO FOLLOWED HER
FROM THE WORLD OF DEMONS.
- ( gasping ) IS THAT TRUE?
- UH, WELL, YES.
- NERINE'S FATHER ASKED
IF SHE COULD STAY WITH US,
SO WE'RE TAKING CARE OF HER NOW!
- SO WHAT YOU'RE SAYING
IS YOU'RE LIVING WITH
THE HOT LITTLE SISTER
WHO ISN'T ACTUALLY
RELATED TO YOU,
SO IF YOU LOOK, IT'S OKAY. NICE!
- YOUR ABILITY TO TURN
AN INNOCENT SITUATION
INTO SOMETHING
OBSCENE AMAZES ME.
OH, HEY, SORRY ABOUT THAT!
SO DID SOMETHING BAD HAPPEN
AT HOME? WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- BECAUSE I WANTED TO SEE YOU.
- OH.
- ( students muttering )
- ER...
LOOK, IT'S JUST...
WHY NOW?
- LOOK.
- IS THIS ABOUT THE TOY?
- HM.
- OH, YEAH.
THE ARM'S RIPPED.
- IT'S NOT BAD!
IT'S JUST THE SEAM.
I CAN FIX IT WHEN I GET HOME
FROM SCHOOL TODAY.
- DID YOU HEAR THAT?
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
NEXT TIME IT'S OKAY FOR YOU
TO WAIT FOR US AT HOME
IF IT'S NOT AN EMERGENCY.
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- WHAT'S GOING ON? THE BELL
STOPPED RINGING A LONG TIME AGO.
- TSUCCHI, ARE YOU CAUSING
A DISTURBANCE AGAIN?
- I'M SORRY, BUT SHE JUST
SORT OF SHOWED UP.
- I HATE TO TELL YOU THIS,
BUT YOUR CLASS IS ABOUT TO START
AND YOUR LITTLE FRIEND
NEEDS TO GO HOME, NOW.
- IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO
GO BACK TO THE HOUSE.
- OKAY, RIN.
- I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
BE CAREFUL.
WHAT'S WRONG?
- Nadeshiko: OKAY!
LET'S GET STARTED!
- ( thunder rumbling )
- PLACES SUCH AS THE PYRAMIDS
IN EGYPT, STONEHENGE IN BRITAIN,
MACHU PICCHU IN PERU,
MOHENJO-DARO...
WHY WERE THESE ANCIENT PLACES
BUILT AND HOW WERE THEY MADE?
IN ALL MANKIND'S LONG HISTORY,
THERE HAVE BEEN...
- EXCUSE ME.
- YES?
- GOTTA USE THE RESTROOM.
- TOO WET.
- HEY.
- ( gasping )
RIN!
- IT STARTED POURING RAIN
OUT OF NOWHERE AGAIN.
WHAT A PAIN, HUH?
- SURE IS.
- CLEAR SKIES DON'T
MEAN ANYTHING
THIS TIME OF YEAR, YOU KNOW?
- I'M SORRY.
GUESS YOU'RE MAD AT ME.
- UM-UM.
- LISTEN, WHEN YOU GET HOME
MAKE SURE YOU TAKE
A NICE HOT BATH.
THE LAST THING WE NEED
IS FOR YOU TO CA...
( exclaims )
- WHAT'S WRONG, RIN?
- YOU DON'T... YOU DON'T
HAVE A BRA UNDER YOUR SHIRT?
- WHAT'S A BRA?
- THAT'S RIGHT. YOU
PROBABLY DIDN'T NEED ONE
OF THOSE WHERE YOU CAME FROM.
FIGURES.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE'LL BE
GOING ON A SHOPPING TRIP SOON.
WHY ME?
- RIN?
- HM?
- FORGOT YOUR UMBRELLA...
- UM-HM.
- I DIDN'T THINK ABOUT THAT!
- ME, EITHER.
ALTHOUGH IN MY DEFENSE,
I AM A GUY.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE TO KNOW
ABOUT THOSE THINGS.
- AW, POOR THING.
SHE MUST BE CONFUSED.
I WISH I COULD HAVE DONE
SOMETHING FOR HER SOONER.
- LIKE WHAT? I MEAN, IT'S NOT
LIKE YOU COULD HAVE JUST
GIVEN HER ONE OF YOUR OLD ONES.
MAYBE WE COULD GO
SHOPPING ON SUNDAY?
- YEAH, SOUNDS GOOD.
- WHAT HAPPENED WITH THE CAT?
- I FIXED IT, BUT IT'S PRETTY
WORN OUT IN SOME PLACES.
IT'LL PROBABLY RIP AGAIN.
- THAT STUFFED ANIMAL
DOES LOOK PRETTY OLD.
IT MAKES ME WONDER
IF IT HAS SENTIMENTAL VALUE.
- MAYBE. BUT HOW WOULD WE KNOW?
SHE HASN'T TOLD US
ANYTHING ABOUT HERSELF.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
SHE'S SO QUIET.
- ( door opening )
- ( giggling )
- HELLO, HOW'S IT GOIN'?
LEMME GUESS?
YOU WANT TO GO SHOPPING.
- WHA... HOW DID YOU KNOW?
WHY IS EVERYONE OUT
HERE WAITING FOR US?
- KAEDE TOLD US YOU WERE
SHOPPING FOR CUTE LINGERIE,
SO WE THOUGHT
WE'D COME HELP OUT.
- YEAH, I MEAN THE THOUGHT OF
YOU PICKING OUT UNDERWEAR ALONE
IS PRETTY SCARY
TO SAY THE LEAST,
AND IF YOU WANT TO FIND
THE BEST GIFT POSSIBLE
THREE RINGS ARE BETTER THAN ONE!
- ( sighing ) YOU WANT
TO HELP US? RIGHT.
WHY DOES IT SOUND LIKE
YOU'RE JUST USING THIS
AS AN EXCUSE TO GO SHOPPING?
- ( laughs ) OH, RIN! YOU WORRY
TOO MUCH, YOU KNOW THAT?
- THANKS. THAT'S COMFORTING.
- SO, IS THERE ANY KIND
OF STYLE IN PARTICULAR
WE SHOULD BE LOOKING FOR?
ANY COLORS OR PATTERNS YOU LIKE?
- DON'T KNOW.
- OKAY!
THEN YOU LEAVE
EVERYTHING TO US!
- YAY, I'M EXCITED! THIS
IS GONNA BE SO MUCH FUN!
- OH, MY GOSH, THESE ONES
ARE SO CUTE! RIN, LOOK AT THIS!
- ( exclaims )
- ORANGE STRIPES.
YOU KNOW, WITH THE RED HAIR?
- YEAH, UM, IT'S GREAT
BUT I THINK WE'RE SUPPOSED TO
BE LOOKING FOR SOMETHING...
( groans )
WHAT DO YOU THINK? DOES
THIS MAKE ME LOOK SEXY?
- AWW, THAT'S SO SWEET!
ASKING HIS APPROVAL SHOWS
HOW MUCH YOU TWO
RESPECT EACH OTHER.
DO YOU LIKE IT, RIN?
IT'S SO CUTE!
- UH, LISTEN. THAT'S NOT
WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
- COME ON, DON'T BE SHY!
YOU LIKE IT, DON'T YOU?
YOU CAN SAY IT.
- WOULD THIS ONE
LOOK PRETTY ON ME?
- OKAY, SO WHICH DO
YOU LIKE BETTER,
THIS ONE OR THE
ONE I HAD BEFORE?
- Asa: RIN!
LET'S TRY THIS AGAIN.
DOES THIS MAKE YOU WANT ME?
TELL THE TRUTH.
- I GOTTA GO!
I'LL WAIT OUTSIDE!
( panting )
OKAY, THAT WAS AWKWARD.
- Boy: LET'S GO TO THE ARCADE!
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA
BEAT ME TODAY!
- RIGHT, THE ARCADE. THAT'LL BE
A GOOD PLACE TO KILL SOME TIME.
- ( Japanese song playing )
- TOO BAD. IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE
THEY HAVE ANYTHING NEW.
WAIT JUST A MINUTE.
THIS IS WHERE I
FIRST SAW PRIMULA.
SHE WAS STANDING RIGHT THERE...
STARING AT ONE OF THOSE
CRANE GAMES SO INTENSELY.
THERE WAS SOMETHING I WAS
TRYING TO WIN FOR HER THAT TIME.
SOMETHING IT SEEMED LIKE
SHE REALLY WANTED.
WHY CAN'T I REMEMBER
WHAT IT WAS?
RIGHT!
A CAT!
- UM.
- UM-UM.
IT'S MAY BE TOO CONSERVATIVE.
- WHAT ABOUT SOMETHING
MORE LIKE THIS?
- IT'S KIND OF SEE-THROUGH.
- ( giggles ) MORE THAN KIND OF.
YOU KNOW THAT SET
OVER THERE MIGHT BE BETTER.
OR YOU LOOKING FOR SOMETHING
MORE ON THE MATURE SIDE, RIGHT?
RIMU?
YEAH, SHE AGREES.
- I THINK SHE'D LIKE SOMETHING
A LITTLE LESS FLASHY.
- Kareha: OH, MY GOSH! LOOK!
CHECK THIS OUT!
ISN'T IT PERFECT FOR HER?
- ( giggling and squealing )
- IT'S BOLD!
A NICE CHOICE!
- YOU REALLY HAVE
AN EYE FOR COLORS!
- SO THAT'S THE KIND OF
STYLE YOU'RE INTO?
- IT IS SEXY.
YOU!
- YOU GUYS? CAN YOU COME
OVER HERE FOR A SEC?
I HAVE SOMETHING TO SHOW YOU!
- AGH. WHAT IS IT THIS TIME?
- WE'RE COMING!
- YES?
- IS SOMETHING WRONG?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I CALLED YOU HERE BECAUSE
THERE IS SOMETHING
PRETTY AMAZING
BEHIND THIS CURTAIN!
DUH-DUH-DUH-DUH!
- ( drum roll )
- ( laughing )
- OH, MY GOSH!
- WHERE'D RIN GO?
DO YOU THINK HE LEFT?
- WE WERE IN THERE FOR A WHILE.
MAYBE HE GOT TIRED OF WAITING
AND DECIDED TO GO HOME?
- NO WAY. HE WOULDN'T
LEAVE HER HERE LIKE THAT.
I HOPE HE'S OKAY.
- I'M HERE! SORRY!
- PLEASE DON'T APOLOGIZE!
WE'RE SORRY WE MADE YOU
WAIT SO LONG.
- WE GOT A LITTLE CARRIED AWAY.
THERE WAS SO MUCH FUN
LINGERIE TO PLAY WITH
AND WE COMPLETELY
LOST TRACK OF TIME.
- YOU PLAYED WITH
"FUN LINGERIE."
OH, GREAT, I'M AFRAID TO ASK.
DID YOU BUY HER SOMETHING LACY,
STRINGY, INAPPROPRIATE
AND SEE-THROUGH?
- ( laughing sheepishly )
THEY DID TRY TO TAKE
SOME OF THAT UP TO THE CASHIER,
BUT I CONVINCED THEM
TO PUT IT BACK.
- YEAH, I THOUGHT SO.
AH, WELL. I HOPE
YOU WERE AT LEAST
ABLE TO GET WHAT YOU NEEDED.
- IT TOOK A REALLY LONG TIME.
- ( chuckles )
- IT LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE BEEN
DOING SOME SHOPPING YOURSELF.
- YEAH, I DID. I WANTED
TO GET SOMETHING FOR PRIMULA.
- CAN YOU TELL US WHAT IT IS?
- WELL, IT'S A SOUVENIR.
YOU SHOULD OPEN IT.
- A SOUVENIR?
- I SUPPOSE IT'S A LITTLE BIT
MORE LIKE A PRESENT, THOUGH.
- I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE
SOMETHING YOU WOULD LIKE.
- A CAT.
- YOU WANTED ONE WHEN WE
FIRST MET. DO YOU REMEMBER?
- THANK YOU.
- I HOPE IT'S OKAY,
SINCE IT'S NOT THE SAME ONE
YOU WERE LOOKING AT BEFORE.
- NICE KITTY.
MY CAT.
- YOU LIKE IT?
- HOW SWEET. AWW.
- AND SHE'S SMILING. IT'S THE
FIRST TIME SHE'S DONE THAT.
- NICE GOING, YOU STUD!
- YOU THINK OF EVERYTHING!
- THANK YOU.
THAT WAS SO NICE.
- HOW DO YOU COME UP
WITH THINGS LIKE THAT?
- OO LA LA-HAH!
- NOW, LOOK. WE ALL
WANTED TO CHEER HER UP!
I'M JUST GLAD SHE SEEMS TO
LIKE HER PRESENT, RIGHT?
- WHAT THIS TOY
MEANS TO ME IS LOVE.
- MY LOVE.
THANK YOU, RIN.
( giggles )
- WAY TO GO, RIN! WAY TO MAKE
HER FALL IN LOVE WITH YOU!
- THAT'S NOT FUNNY, ASA.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Kaede: SO, I'M TEACHING
PRIMULA HOW TO COOK.
- Asa: USE THE TRADITIONAL
COOKING CLUB PRACTICE DRILL
OF A THOUSAND KNIFE SWINGS!
- OH, OF COURSE I WILL!
- AND THE SLICING
AND DICING RACE?
- WE'RE COVERING
ALL THE BASICS!
- Rin: IS ALL THAT
REALLY NECESSARY?
- Asa: NEXT TIME ON SHUFFLE
EPISODE 7, ROMANTIC SCRAMBLE!
- Kaede: NOW ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS FIND A SECLUDED MOUNTAIN
WHERE WE CAN TRAIN!
- Rin: WHAT?