Rise, Hibiki.
Who are you?
My name is Oboro.
[HIBIKI gasps]
What? Oboro?
That was my mother's name.
This can't be.
[OBORO]
Hibiki.
You've grown into quite
a lovely young woman.
You're really her?
[HIBIKI gasps]
[OBORO sobs]
[HIBIKI]
Are you all right?
Mother, what's happening?
[OBORO]
Several years ago.
I was forced into making
the most difficult decision
of my life.
That was when I fell in love.
I met a man, and yearned
for him, and thus lost my path.
And in so doing,
lost many friends along the way.
It still pains me, even now.
That man was Kouga Gennosuke.
I don't care how many
lifetimes it takes for me
to have my vengeance.
I can never forgive him
for what he's done!
[gasps]
[OBORO]
Never!
Mother, hold on!
[RUI gasps]
You might want to clean some
of the blood off yourself.
Right, my kunai
started slipping.
[HADAEBOU]
Right on schedule.
[UTSUTSU]
What's wrong?
[RUI sighs]
You're scared, aren't you?
[RUI]
Are you?
Ah. Yes, they scare me as well.
They'll gladly throw their
lives away for nothing.
[RUI]
Unsettling, but that's not it.
[gasps]
What frightens
me more than that,
is dying without
having said anything.
Said anything about what?
[RUI]
I've always loved you, Utsutsu.
[gasps]
With every fiber of my being.
What're you saying?
We can't afford for you
to lose your nerve!
I know this battle's
enough to shake anyone,
but this isn't the
first war you've fought in!
I am perfectly sane,
so I wanted to say
it while there's time.
This war's different from
any others we've fought.
One of us
might actually die today.
[gasps]
[MAGOROKU]
We have Iga Hibiki, but then,
you already knew that,
did you not?
You can't stop us
from doing whatever we want
with her, as things stand.
Surely, you wish to
rescue the woman you love.
Again, we extend
the invitation to you
to visit our castle.
Rinne Magoroku.
Do you think you've made
a prisoner of me, as well?
Nonsense.
And Yasha Itaru.
Not using Destiny's passage
could be a huge mistake.
One you may not live to regret.
[ITARU]
Hmph. Still stalling?
Your bluffing
is utterly pathetic.
No, it's not a bluff.
It's possible that very
technique could be
affecting me right now.
I certainly feel strange.
Perhaps the desire to take my
own life is overwhelming me.
[ITARU, MAGOROKU gasp]
What would
happen if I turned
my skill against myself?
By using your mirror.
[ITARU]
You wouldn't dare.
This is not the time
for games, Kouga Hachirou.
Now. Adamantite Tower
and Destiny's Passage,
mixed with my
Spearing Eye technique.
What will transpire once all
of these abilities converge?
Well, why don't we find out?
Just keep holding that
mirror in front of your face.
You'll both find yourselves
in Hell, in due time.
Rinne, what is this?
[MAGOROKU] It seems
your Destiny's Passage
may be working, whether
or not that's your intention.
[ITARU]
No, it's just an illusion.
He's bluffing, I know it!
[MAGOROKU]
For now, I shall take my leave.
[ITARU gasps]
Listen, Kouga Hachirou.
You need only ask
and we'll oblige.
We will take you into Murakumo.
You have my word.
[ITARU growls]
Also, don't forget
to take your medicine
while I'm gone.
You play the part of
the doting wife rather well.
It might be the part
I was meant to play,
but that's a discussion
for a different time.
[RUI giggles]
[NUN A]
Welcome, Otoshi.
Senhime told us what a dear
friend of hers you were,
and asked that we take
very special care of you.
You're more than welcome
to stay as long as you need,
it's no bother at all.
[NAMENBA]
Thank you for your generosity.
By the way, who is that girl?
Which girl?
Oh. She's been with us for
going on six months now.
All the girls in our care have
their reasons for being here.
But I worry about her.
I think she has something
particularly awful in her past.
Is that why she
wears the eyepatch?
[NUN A] It seems her
left eye is perfectly fine,
but she always
leaves it covered.
I've never seen her
take the eyepatch off.
[Why the poor dear
insists on wearing it is
a mystery, but it's her choice,
so we thought it would be
best not to force
the issue any further.
That's good of you.
And by the way...
Go on?
[NAMENBA]
It's just, I've changed my name.
Please call me
Namenba from now on.
Sure.
[gasps]
It's a secret.
Have some.
[gasps]
[RUI]
Huh...?
[giggles]
[NUN A]
So it's time, then.
You must take your leave?
That's right.
It's been so nice here.
I do hate to go.
But I'm afraid I'll wear
out my welcome.
[NUN A]
Tell the truth.
It's time for you to return
to the battlefield, is it not?
[NAMENBA gasps]
[NUN A] I do know of things
beyond the convent's walls.
Yes, of course you do.
I've no intention of
asking you about matters
you'd rather not discuss.
Just know...
If ever you should wish it,
you may return to us.
You'll always have a home here,
and will be welcomed
back warmly.
We shall all pray
for your safety
until that day comes.
[NAMENBA]
I'll miss this place, Rui.
I'd love it if I could just stay
here with you and the others.
Wouldn't it be nice
if we could be here forever?
[RUI]
No. That would be impossible.
[NAMENBA]
Huh?
We're all going to die someday.
Nobody can live forever.
So it doesn't matter
where you are.
You could die out there,
and it would all be over.
[hawk screeches]
Stop this violence at once!
--[NUN A gasps]
--[RAIDER A grunts]
[RAIDER A gasps]
[NAMENBA gasps]
[NAMENBA]
Those tears of yours.
I would imagine that they
must've put you through a lot.
What will you do?
Would you like to come with me?
It won't be an easy path.
Or will you give up
because you're tired
of the whole world? Decide now.
Whatever you choose,
I'll make it happen.
[gasps]
[RAIDER B grunts, groans]
[RUI]
Namenba.
I'll follow you.
Wherever you go.
[SHICHIGEN]
I saw what happened back there.
Heard what was said.
If you'd allowed
them to take you
inside Murakumo, then both
of our clans' leaders
would be under the
enemy's control right now.
[SHICHIGEN]
Hachirou, what you said.
You were bluffing, weren't you?
Or was it the truth?
[HACHIROU] Shichigen,
was there ever a time
you sought out death?
[SHICHIGEN gasps]
[HACHIROU]
I know you.
You can't say that there wasn't.
I'll tell you once more.
We can't lose the heads of
both the Iga and Kouga.
We've spent our whole lives
training to protect you.
--[SAIZOU] Shikibu!
--[grunts]
[SAIZOU] What in the
hell is going on here?
[SHIKIBU] I don't know, and I
can't find Gorone anywhere.
[SAIZOU] You're saying a man in
his condition just up and left?
[SHIKIBU]
I think so.
At least, that's what
the signs point to.
[gasps]
Tadanaga- sama .
If you're truly him,
then you've made your choice.
Which means
you're useless to us.
A double, of course.
The real one may be alive
somewhere inside this place.
So as it stands,
this is still a rescue mission.
Yet another double?
Why am I not
the least bit surprised?
[TADANAGA] Stubborn fool,
will you never learn?
[NAMENBA] Wasting ammunition
will do nothing
but shorten your own life.
We'll fly.
Let's bet on that.
I have a feeling it was
a present left behind
by a certain someone.
Here we go!
[TADANAGA]
A rescue? That's unlikely.
You've come here to kill me
since I've shown that
I cannot be controlled.
[TADANAGA] My fate was decided
when I was still but a child
by a battle between ninjas.
If such insanity
can be allowed in this world,
then I shall change
the course of my fate
with an insanity of my own.
Why would I hesitate when
given such an opportunity?
I have the chance to
claim what I was unfairly denied
all those years ago.
You expect me to believe
the shogun would forgive
his brother's treason against
the Tokugawa legacy?
Iemitsu- sama
asked me himself to tell you.
He's eagerly awaiting
the return of his dear brother,
with open arms.
[TADANAGA]
Hmph. That's a fine speech
Tenkai gave you, assassin.
[HADAEBOU] I've heard that
the shogun has always felt
somewhat guilty about
being given his position
in such a cavalier manner.
How can one truly earn what the
whims of fate have handed them?
He understands how
you feel, and if you return now,
is willing to forget
the whole thing.
That's enough!
[HADAEBOU]
You don't believe me, my lord?
It's true.
Your brother shared with me,
a man of low station,
his happy memories
from childhood,
of spending time with you,
his beloved younger brother.
He spoke of a time
at a court banquet,
when you were five years old,
and he was seven.
You both argued over
who would take the red
or the white sweets.
[HADAEBOU]
He eventually gave in,
and handed over
all the red candies,
because he knew how
much you loved them.
It made the whole room smile.
[HADAEBOU] He also told me
of a time several years later.
It was summer.
And together you went on your
very first hunt with hawks.
The two of you
drank boiled water,
and he still remembers
the metallic taste of it
to this day.
He recounted all this
with tears in his eyes.
[TADANAGA whimpers]
[NARRATOR]
My name is Tokugawa Tadanaga.
Prepare to die, Joujin.
New flowers can
never bloom without
the old ones dying first.
Will Asura fall
with the demon gods?