It was uncouth, I know.
Please forgive my rude behavior,
but it was necessary
to put your skills to the test.
I come with a request.
The Suruga Dainagon himself
wishes to have a word with you.
[NAMENBA] Suruga- sama
was sent to Kouzuke?
Are you certain?
[GORONE]
That's the story going around.
Forced exile at Kofu
apparently wasn't harsh enough
for the shogun.
Iemitsu said that?
The rumors of their
animosity are widespread.
So it all sounds
perfectly believable.
Stop that.
Yawns are contagious,
and I'm trying to think
things through here.
Two brothers
who hate each other.
It's such a tragic story.
[GORONE] The destiny tying
them together is powerful.
It's possible what happened
to us was linked to them.
[gasps]
Or rather, likely.
I've been dwelling
on the implications
for some time myself.
When Gei'in sent
that final message.
He warned us that four of the
Five Treasures had been attacked
by the Kurokuwa
and the Joujinshuu.
The Kurokuwa are
servants of the shogun himself.
They attacked Suruga- sama
without provocation.
Which means...
No. That can't be!
The Kurokuwa
must've acted under
the shogun's direct orders.
Which is a rational
conclusion that Suruga- sama
might have come to.
No, he almost certainly
has arrived at that conclusion.
[NAMENBA sighs]
Yes.
The fact that it's so obvious
has me worried as well.
Perhaps that was the intention,
to make him believe he was
targeted, thus forcing his
hand to move for evil, right?
[NAMENBA]
"Evil"? What do you mean?
Treason, for example.
If he entertained even the
slightest idea of fomenting
a rebellion, that would provide
the shogun an excuse
to crush his rival
without mercy.
And so...
He'd have him killed?
[GORONE chuckles] I'd like to
think the man in charge
would never go that far.
However, if it was actually
Joujin behind everything...
[gasps]
[GORONE] It wouldn't be
a difficult task for a man
of his abilities to gain
control of the Kurokuwa.
And so I wonder...
Did he and the shogun
have a connection
that we haven't yet discovered?
If we figured out that link,
we could narrow down
the possible moves the
Joujinshuu might make next.
[NAMENBA]
Then we should ask the shogun.
[GORONE]
It isn't quite that easy.
If you want
to get into Edo castle,
I have a plan that
just might work.
[GORONE gasps]
[KUROKUWA A] Intruder. We, the
Kurokuwa of Iga will defeat you.
[KUROKUWA A] Were you trying
to sever some invisible threads?
[NAMENBA pants]
Your lordship, a message.
The Kurokuwa have returned
to serve you once again.
You mean the ninjas?
What do they have
to do with anything?
Have you forgotten, my lord?
You ordered them to delay
your brother's travels.
A mission your loyal
servants deftly performed.
My brother? Tadanaga?
Why delay him? How strange.
It's a mistake.
[NAMENBA] And do you have
any messages to relay
to Joujin- dono , my lord?
Who is that? I don't know him.
Farewell, your lordship.
Now close your eyes, and forget
about this conversation,
and descend into
a peaceful slumber.
Intruder! My lord!
Are you all right?!
[snarls]
[BOTH growl]
[FEMALE GUARD A]
Intruder! Everyone, after them!
[FEMALE GUARD B]
My lord, please wake up!
[gasps]
[HADAEBOU] It seems
you've wasted your time.
I think it's in both
our best interests to keep
the noise to a minimum.
Was that your handiwork
back there, as well?
It's a true pleasure
to meet you.
Greetings,
Namenba- dono , of the Iga.
[HIBIKI]
Houren?
[RUI] Gorone said there
was something about it
that reminded him of one.
What is it, this "houren"?
It's a special carriage that
the emperor rides in.
But... that thing looks
more like a castle.
I wonder if
it's Portuguese? Huh.
You think so?
It doesn't look it.
But it's been great for
bringing the customers in.
Since it appeared three
days ago, our sales numbers
have been higher than normal!
[HACHISU]
But who's in there?
That's my question.
It's the Joujinshuu.
[GIRLS gasp]
Impossible. You think
they made that thing?
I can't be certain. But still...
I feel something
dark emanating from it.
Something "dark"?
[HIBIKI] It's the same feeling I
had when they last appeared.
If that's the case,
we should probably do
something other
than just stare at it.
If things are really this bad,
shouldn't we go and inform
the boys of what's happening?
No. There's no point.
They're gone. All of them.
Really?
They're gone? Where to?
How am I s'posed to know?
Fine, we'll do it alone--
[HIBIKI] Not yet. It may
all be in my imagination.
Perhaps so.
If it is an enemy castle,
we should wait
for Namenba before we rush in.
But she isn't here now. So...
So we wait.
She'll be back before the
cherry blossoms bloom.
Yes, but--
That wasn't a wish,
it was an order
from me, your leader.
[HIBIKI sighs]
[TADANAGA] Excellent. I see
you received my message.
[HACHIROU]
Yes.
[TADANAGA] Please,
make yourself comfortable.
I no longer hold any territory,
nor do I have any
title to my name.
Do you know why
I've summoned you here?
Did Hadaebou tell you anything?
No.
I come as the former leader
of the Five Treasures.
I'm here to uphold my duty.
"Former leader."
I'm sorry about what
happened to them.
[HACHIROU] Is that not
the function of the ninja?
[TADANAGA]
Indeed.
You've heard of the one called
"Joujin," have you not?
I know of him.
He orchestrated the strike
against our clans.
When it happened--
when Joujin defeated
the Five Treasures--
I was there to bear witness.
Yes. I am aware of that.
As I'd expect,
they came and the Five Treasures
were slaughtered before me.
They brought the
Five Flowers' heads.
They wanted to show me the true
extent of their capabilities.
Do you understand?
I cannot imagine a better way
to demonstrate our power.
Joujin had me at his mercy,
and through coercion,
he pushed me to do something
I never wanted to do.
Have you heard
the troubling stories?
What?
[TADANAGA] The rumors that
this monstrosity was recently
sighted near Kinokawa?
Joujin has dubbed
this abomination "Murakumo."
You going?
Hush. Maybe try not
to say it so loud.
I hate not knowing about it.
Don't you?
What's in there?
You, too.
We should definitely go and do
a little on-site investigating,
and if we learn it has nothing
to do with the Joujinshuu,
then that's the end of it.
Hibiki specifically said not to!
So we make sure
we aren't gone too long.
Besides, it'll be better
for Hibiki if we do it.
We can get rid of
the uncertainty,
and she won't have to
take the risk herself.
[TADANAGA] Why not offer an
imperial carriage to Mount Kouya
in loving memory of my mother?
That was Joujin's suggestion,
and I gave him a great sum
of money to see it done.
I wanted to do
something to honor her.
This was several years ago.
I'd lost track of
the project, in all honesty.
But...
But now this shows up.
Does that thing look
like a damned imperial
carriage to you?
It's not an homage,
it's a castle!
And what's worse,
they constructed this eye-sore
during my father's
mourning period!
That's like rubbing salt
in an open wound!
[HACHIROU] What could possess
Joujin to build such a thing?
[TADANAGA] I wondered
the same. I've no idea.
But a full-fledged
castle was constructed
without the knowledge
of the shogunate.
And I, I footed the bill to pay
for it without ever realizing.
If word of this gets out,
what am I to do?
Joujin slaughtered
the warriors of the Five Flowers
and the Five Treasures,
all to raise money for
an imperial carriage?
They died... for that?
Wait. What're you trying to say?
[gasps]
I almost forgot.
Looking upon you as an enemy,
is to commit suicide.
[HACHIROU] I wouldn't dare use
my technique against my lord.
I should've known.
I guess there's
no hiding it from you.
I'll just say it.
You and I are alone here.
So please be discreet.
Because everything
I'm going to pass along to you
cannot leave this room.
Understood?
[HACHIROU]
As you wish, my lord.
[SAIZOU]
You two are all alone, huh?
This lord's a liar.
[TADANAGA] It's true.
Joujin wanted something more.
He encouraged me
to rebel against
my brother Iemitsu, the shogun.
[SAIZOU gasps]
He promised me that
he would keep my mother alive
if I complied with his wishes.
[JOUJIN]
Listen.
Unless the forest
itself is moved,
then failure is
impossible, Suruga- sama .
But he'd been
deceiving me all along!
My ailing mother's health
improved for a time thereafter.
[TADANAGA] But less than
six months later, she...
And then... the forest!
The forest?
The accursed
forest began to move!
[TADANAGA]
Two years ago,
I went to inspect my territory,
and was resting from
my travels at Sengen Shrine.
[TADANAGA] I was exhausted
from my time on the road,
and lost in a dream-like haze.
[TADANAGA gasps]
[TADANAGA] The forest
surrounding the shrine.
[gasps]
[HACHIROU]
It moved?
[TADANAGA]
Indeed!
It not only moved,
it lunged right at me!
[TADANAGA] Impossible.
The forest can't be moving!
[SOLDIER A]
My lord!
[MONKEYS screeching]
[SOLDIER A]
Monkeys! They're monkeys!
Monkeys? But why?
[SOLDIERS screaming]
We have to get you to safety!
Damn you, monkeys!
Lord...
[TADANAGA] You think some
lice-eating, screeching beasts
like you can mock the
Dainagon of Suruga?
My lord?
Kill them all! Open volley!
Suruga- sama , don't be hasty!
The legends say these
monkeys are holy creatures!
They're messengers
straight from the gods!
[TADANAGA]
I don't care! It must not move.
I can't afford to let it move!
[SOLDIER A]
My lord!
[TADANAGA snarls]
[TADANAGA] I wouldn't fault you,
if you were to laugh at me.
Joujin told me that
victory was certain,
unless the forest
itself were to move.
But that night, it started
moving all on its own!
Surely this must be
Heaven's punishment!
And he...
The monk, Joujin...
The man is a demon, more likely.
I was a fool to listen to him,
and on my honor,
I can never be
such a fool again!
Hachirou... will you help?
Go, destroy the castle Murakumo!
Bring death down
upon the Joujinshuu!
And after, burn their
fortress to the ground!
You wouldn't just
be doing it for me,
but for the Tokugawa!
And for the safety of Japan!
I refuse your task.
You... do?
[HACHIROU] My lord,
you will not be able to take
advantage of us any further.
I won't.
The cheek!
What did you just say?
[HACHIROU]
Do you remember?
When you were still a child,
many of the finest ninjas
from both clans--
They died for no better reason
than to determine
the next heir of
the Tokugawa line
And yet, that is not all.
The Five Treasures
and the Five Flowers--
Every one of them slain,
because of you.
A fool who thought
only of treason.
And then there were
the young ninjas in training,
who were nearly killed as well.
We refuse to sacrifice
ourselves anymore,
especially when it means dying
for the likes of the Tokugawa!
"For The likes of
the Tokugawa"? Bastard!
How dare you say that!
And after I've deigned to share
my deepest thoughts with you?
Inexcusable! You dog!
You dare refuse me?!
[SAIZOU chuckles]
Now I can't allow you
to leave this place alive!
Connect with my eyes,
let them help!
[SOLDIER D gasps]
[SOLDIER E gasps]
[SOLDIER F gasps]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[SOLDIER F groans]
[SOLDIER D rasps]
[SOLDIER G, H groaning]
[HACHIROU]
Saizou?
Were you surprised, Hachirou?
I've been refining my
techniques over the years.
I like to call this
one "Hundred Eyes."
[MEN wail]
You useless fool!
He's right over there!
[HACHIROU]
Will you still fight?
[TADANAGA gasps]
Stop, or you will suffer.
My lord, if we
allow him to leave,
then the shogunate
may discover everything
you discussed with him!
That's true,
and we cannot allow that!
Bring him down. Kill him.
Kill him!
[NARRATOR] The evil castle
spoken of in rumors
called "Murakumo."
It stands in the forest,
tall and dark.
As the women seek
to reveal its mysteries,
the men go into action
for the sake of their master.
And now, everything
is beginning to move.