[UTSUTSU pants]
[RANDOM MAN A] We still have
no idea who's behind it.
[RANDOM MAN B] What the
hell is that monstrosity?
It's impossible to believe
that such a castle
could simply appear
out of nowhere!
[RANDOM MAN A] This isn't merely
Kishuu's problem anymore.
[RANDOM WOMAN A] I've even heard
rumors that the former retainers
of the Toyotomi in the
west might be stirred
into full-scale rebellion.
[RANDOM WOMAN B]
Is that truly what they say?
I pray it isn't so.
[IEMITSU]
That's impossible.
I endeavor to learn
the truth behind the matter,
whether or not
it is as impossible
as it may first appear.
[ROYAL AIDE A]
Lift your gaze.
[gasps]
His lordship has
been feeling ill, of late.
Thankfully, today has found
his lordship in good health.
You are fortunate for the
chance to see him at all.
Yes, sir!
I am quite grateful
for the honor.
[SHICHIGEN]
Hachirou, wait.
Where are you going?
I told you not
to concern yourself.
Come now. How can you say that
after what just happened?
You cared enough about us
to step in and lend us aid.
That's correct.
Although I've heard,
only a coward fails to strike
when it is right to do so.
That is a teaching
of bushido, is it not?
We don't have the time
to argue with Hachirou.
You and I
still have a job to do.
[HACHIROU]
This is farewell.
I'm sorry.
I'm slowing you down again.
[RUI] If you were slowing me
down, I wouldn't take you.
I'm saving you because
I want you to be useful.
[SHICHIGEN]
Fair enough.
I'll try not to disappoint you.
They're here.
So it would seem.
[SAIZOU] I guess planning
for the diversion to draw
all the Rain away was
asking for the impossible.
[UTSUTSU] Too many
for that to be the case.
There must've been another unit.
[SAIZOU] Assuming
Shichigen checked properly
before setting off
the signal flare.
[UTSUTSU] Would you be
a man and stop whining?
Now, hold on to this.
It's more valuable than
your life, so look after it.
Your cheery disposition
really does wonders.
My morale soars.
I didn't exaggerate.
We can't complete
the mission without that.
[UTSUTSU grunts]
Damn it!
[UTSUTSU whimpers]
Saizou! Where's the cannon?
Your life's more important.
If it's lost,
we can't find a new one.
[UTSUTSU grunts]
Now then.
I want you to show me
one of your illusions.
Then I can reflect the visions
my eyes see and use
them against the enemy forces.
[SAIZOU]
Even through this smoke,
I can spread them everywhere.
But if you see
one of my illusions,
you'll be drawn inside it,
just like the others!
I'm not going to see it,
my eyes will do it for me.
[UTSUTSU growls]
How is that different?
Because mine are like
a doorway to my mind
that I can open and close.
[UTSUTSU grunts]
[SAIZOU]
There's no other way.
So be it.
[SAIZOU] Even if I start
burning, you can't stop.
You have my word!
[SAIZOU gasps]
[SOLDIERS A, B scream]
[SOLDIER C yells]
I can't believe that worked!
Saizou? Saizou!
[UTSUTSU gasps]
[SAIZOU whimpers]
[gasps]
[SAIZOU]
How long was I out?
Only for a few minutes.
There's still plenty
of time for the mission.
[SAIZOU]
Good.
[retches]
[SAIZOU]
I already see too much.
That's the downside to my power.
As a rule, I don't look at
things unnecessarily.
I don't even dream anymore.
I have the opposite
issue. It seems that I can
never see what I want to see.
[UTSUTSU]
So I have dreams.
But they're always horrifying.
I'll go and grab the cannon.
Hold the area while I'm gone.
That illusion of yours
was some nasty business,
but I'm sure you know that.
I can't imagine what
the hell happened in your life
to make you want to
show that kind of thing
to another person.
--[door clatters]
--[gasps] Father!
[UTSUTSU]
Father!
Father...
[gasps]
[UTSUTSU]
All the jet-black night.
He comes to me in my dreams.
[UTSUTSU]
Ever since I was very young,
I'd spend half the month in the
darkness of that storehouse,
staring endlessly
at the mandala.
Unsure if what I was enduring
was training or punishment.
What's wrong?
Ah... I want to see
something prettier, father.
Even if it's just in my dreams.
You dream? Truly?
Yes! I do!
But they're... always so scary,
and that place...
[UTSUTSU'S FATHER]
Hell.
[gasps]
[UTSUTSU'S FATHER]
Do you know the whole poem?
"It seems that my heart,
wants me to die of longing.
All the jet-black night.
He comes to me in my dreams.
My hopeless
passion burns bright."
I don't understand.
What's it mean?
[UTSUTSU'S FATHER] The speaker
falls in love with someone
from their dreams, and dies.
It may only be a love poem,
but I think there's an
aspect of truth inside it.
One's dreams
have the power to kill.
The same is true
for our emotions.
And when taken to their
extremes, a technique forms.
A powerful ability that
can only be learned
during one's youth.
The time grows near.
By the blooming of the cherry
blossoms, you must master it.
What happens when the
cherry blossoms begin to bloom?
The destined hour arrives.
With the blooming of the sakura,
you'll have grown too old
to learn the technique.
When that day comes,
if you've failed
to master the jutsu,
all of this will have
been for nothing.
[UTSUTSU'S FATHER]
And then, you will have to die.
[gasps]
[UTSUTSU'S FATHER] This skill,
called Dreaming Reality,
incurs a cost, Utsutsu.
It doesn't matter how tough
it's supposed to be,
I'm not afraid!
[UTSUTSU'S FATHER]
I see. So you aren't frightened?
[UTSUTSU yelps]
[UTSUTSU groans]
[UTSUTSU'S FATHER] You think
I'm trying to scare you?
Foolish girl...
[UTSUTSU whimpers]
[UTSUTSU]
Hmph.
[UTSUTSU'S FATHER]
Is that all the progress
you've made with this skill?
Yes...?
[UTSUTSU'S FATHER]
You would dare call
such a worthless technique
"Dreaming Reality"?
[gasps]
It seems we've come to an end.
[UTSUTSU whimpers]
[UTSUTSU gasps]
[UTSUTSU]
Is he going to kill me...?
[UTSUTSU gasps]
Father, no!
[UTSUTSU'S FATHER]
I soaked my kimono in oil,
in preparation for your failure.
These flames will rage on until
everything has burned to ashes.
[UTSUTSU]
Ah! Father!
[UTSUTSU'S FATHER] I cannot kill
my own daughter, but then...
...perhaps that would
have been more merciful.
You must live on,
custodian of the knowledge
that you killed your father,
rather than yourself!
This hell will remain
forever branded on
the innermost passages
of your mind.
[UTSUTSU'S FATHER] Fuel your
technique with that emotion.
[UTSUTSU whimpers]
[SOLDIERS screaming]
It is done. Dreaming Reality.
--[SAIZOU] Hey, let's go.
--[UTSUTSU gasps]
[NAMENBA] I still find it hard
to believe that this thing
uses whale whiskers.
[GORONE]
So that Hadaebou fellow,
how far do you think
we can trust him?
[NAMENBA] He's a highly
skilled ninja in the service
of High Priest Tenkai.
With a pedigree of that sort,
what is there to trust?
Indeed.
What's that?
Nothing.
I was just noticing the
similarities between us.
Ah, yes.
Both parties are trying to see
how much the other side
can do for them, and
what kind of advantage
such work affords us.
Well, we'll be the ones
to ultimately win.
I hope you're right
about that, but nevertheless,
when he's around,
keep your guard up.
[HACHIROU gasps]
[HACHIROU] So your plan
was to gain entrance,
by taking advantage
of the ensuing chaos
of the ninja raid.
That's the real
reason you recruited
my friends, correct?
[HADAEBOU]
Uh... Heh...
[SAIZOU]
Here goes.
You missed it.
You really thought we'd
hit our target the first time?
[UTSUTSU]
We still have three bombs left.
But that first shot had to
have notified the enemy
of our exact location.
As we speak, the Rain could
be heading right this way.
And when they get here,
you can take care of them.
[HACHISU]
What do you think you're doing?
I can barely keep watching.
[UTSUTSU]
You brought Hibiki with you?
That's right.
If we hope to win,
we'll need her power.
So we're headed
for an all-out brawl?
While you work the
cannon, we'll cover you.
--[UTSUTSU] Hmm?
--What's that?
[HACHISU]
I fire this into that embrasure.
And then, your bomb will
follow along behind it.
[SAIZOU]
Is that even possible?
If you're good enough.
[SAIZOU]
Hmm...
[BOTH]
Hmph.
--[HACHISU gasps]
--Watch out!
[gasping]
[HIBIKI groans]
Looks like I was mistaken.
I'd assumed the Rain would
be sufficient to handle
the likes of you.
[KUJAKU] I compliment you
for actually making me
have to work, if nothing else.
[HACHISU]
What just happened?
[SAIZOU] It's what that damned
monk was telling us about.
The technique to
reverse time's flow.
The Inverted Halberd of Time.
[HACHISU] Is a technique
such as that even possible?
It must be.
Though I'm having serious
doubts whether I can
trust my eyes on this one.
It's unbelievable.
But time really did
flow backwards, somehow.
Yeah. Then, that's...
Kujaku Tsuibamu.
That is him.
So he's one of the ones
we'll have to fight.
And he's dangerous.
Remember, these people
defeated the Five Treasures
and the Five Flowers.
[HIBIKI growls]
Hachisu, where's the cannon?
I've got it right here.
[SAIZOU]
Your Gorouza.
You can still use it, can't you?
Of course,
but what good will it be?
I can't be certain. Who knows?
But for the time being,
that's all we've got.
We have to do something with it!
[HACHIROU]
I'll say this, Hadaebou.
Your unending deviousness
is almost impressive.
[HADAEBOU]
Thank you for the compliment.
And?
What'll you do when you've
made it inside Murakumo?
Slaughter Joujin?
Be honest with me.
There are very few
excuses I could make
that would allow me to pass.
That's true.
But if it's adequately
entertaining,
I might grant you passage.
[HADAEBOU] We have reason to
believe that Tadanaga- sama
was kidnapped by Joujin.
[HACHIROU] Lord Tadanaga
was taken by Joujin?
But why?
[HADAEBOU] Well. That's
what I've come to learn.
Yet, what power
does Tadanaga hold now?
He has no title,
no courtiers, no soldiers.
[HACHIROU] What could Tenkai
possibly fear from such a man?
And if Joujin did indeed
take Tadanaga- sama ,
what concern is it of
High Priest Tenkai's?
It may not be
the most flattering thing
to say about the man.
But for better, or for worse.
Suruga- sama is
still Suruga- sama .
Nothing will change that.
[HACHIROU]
I understand.
Tadanaga is the grandson of the
late Shogun, Tokugawa Ieyasu.
[HACHIROU] He would
make the perfect puppet.
[HACHIROU] And because that
cannot be allowed to happen,
you have to rescue him
from Joujin's clutches.
I assume that's why you're here.
Well...
Best hurry, before the people
in power are agitated.
Right.
We can't hope to keep
using a double indefinitely.
[JOUJIN] But if he cannot be
saved, he is to be slaughtered.
That is precisely what
your master instructed you
to do, if I'm not mistaken.
[NARRATOR]
He opened his eyes,
and his glance fell
upon a sword.
Above it, he saw
swirling clouds,
thus he named the sword
Ama no Murakumo.
Murakumo, meaning
"a gathering of clouds".