Keep heading up?
I think so.
Let's move.
Not yet, look up there.
[JOUJIN]
Now, lie together.
Take her as your own.
Let me see you
fornicate like beasts,
and set the prophecy in motion!
[UTSUTSU]
It's the old man?
This doesn't make any sense.
Gorone- san took his arm!
We knew from the beginning
that they wouldn't be
just ordinary adversaries,
they're unique.
But I think I might
know what to do.
Gorone, you're
still playing a part in this.
I need one last favor.
[NEIRICHIOU]
Huh?
Ha!
You think you can blind me,
after you've seen my power?
It's becoming tiresome.
This is no different
than the technique
you tried to use against me
when you were but a child.
[growls]
This game has come to its end.
The time is nigh for you to
descend into your own
personal Hell
with my assistance,
[NEIRICHIOU gasps]
[NEIRICHIOU]
What? No!
[NEIRICHIOU yells]
[NEIRICHIOU groans]
I'd say my butterflies worked.
I wasn't sure they would.
Quite Impressive, old man.
Even at your age, you're
spry enough to still manage
to get it up!
You tricked me. How?
[RUI] Now that I've matured,
you understand my appeal!
He's done for
All right, let's go.
[NEIRICHIOU] You'll pay for
this, you filthy little brats.
[JOUJIN]
What will you do, Hachirou?
Why not grant the wish that
she's been longing for?
Either make love
to her, or slay her.
I care not, as either
way fulfills my needs.
Where am I?
Who are these people?
Have you forgotten?
We found you lost, and
having taken pity on you,
brought you to this place
so you may at long last
be reunited with your beloved.
He lies! These men
kidnapped you.
[JOUJIN] Whatever the case,
our goal was to bring
the two of you together.
We had to sneak you
past those who would
stand in the way of your love.
But still, he refuses
to pledge himself to you.
Even after all
that has transpired.
[BOTH gasp]
[RAIJIN growls]
[NEIRICHIOU] You caught me
off guard back there, girls.
I'm man enough to admit.
Look!
The demon god's
missing his right arm!
That slippery old bastard!
He made it so the monster
lost the arm, not him!
Then, when we stabbed
him in the stomach.
To your credit,
your trickery led to me
suffering quite the
grievous injury indeed.
Undoing your harm has made
my Raijin friend agitated.
Ugh! Why won't you just die?
Come down from there!
I'll make sure you stay
dead this time around!
Try not to get
ahead of yourself.
For your next opponent
approaches you from behind.
Behold!
Shichigen...
Rui, be careful.
Something's wrong.
Yes.
And that statue must have
something to do with it.
[NEIRICHIOU cackles]
You again?
If you plan to
destroy this place
with those bombs.
I'll guide you through to
the belly of the beast.
Are you injured?
Carelessness on my part.
I was stabbed by the man
I came here to save.
By Suruga- sama ?
[HADAEBOU]
Quite unfortunate.
Were you able to save him?
I see then.
Well, what are you
still doing here?
Shouldn't you be reporting
back to your master?
If he's dead, your job's
finished, is it not?
I guess I've stayed
due to curiosity.
[gasps]
It's not so strange.
I, too, am a ninja that
was sent on a mission.
So I have an interest
in seeing how this ends.
[NAMENBA]
How it ends?
--[HADAEBOU] Let's go.
--[NAMENBA] Hold on!
[NAMENBA] Use it.
It'll help dull the pain.
Thank you.
[HADAEBOU] If you can
actually pull this off,
and save the heirs
to both ninja clans,
you'll remember me, I hope.
[NAMENBA] To be honest,
if you die, I might forget,
[HADAEBOU] Then I suppose
I shall have to endeavor
to remain amongst the living.
[NAMENBA] People like you never
seem to die like you'd expect.
It doesn't make me happy, but
it doesn't make me sad, either.
What have you done to Shichigen?
His heart.
It cried out, saying he
wanted to see his mother,
so I helped him, and
made his wish come true.
[RUI]
His mother?
[NEIRICHIOU]
Fascinating is it not?
With just the slightest
push from me,
that which he most desired
to see appeared before him.
[NEIRICHIOU] It seems a
conflicted remembrance of
his mother is a core
aspect of your friend.
His mother, however,
was a lustful woman
who would sell her own body.
And he sees her in
the goddess Kanzeon?
Absolute nonsense!
You mock his mother,
on top of everything else?
How dare you?
Ooh! Did I upset you? So scary!
But I'm afraid
now is not the time
for such displays, young one.
Rui!
[NAMENBA growls]
[NEIRICHIOU] I'm going
to enjoy this a great deal.
The Koga and Iga clans
were historically enemies.
It's more natural
for you to kill each other,
than it is to continue the
pretense of being friends.
Stay back.
Shichigen, stop it!
[RUI gasps]
What happened?
I thought you used your
technique on him!
I did, but it
won't work anymore!
[HACHIROU]
I've come to a realization
about Hibiki and myself.
I know why we were
granted our power.
[JOUJIN]
And why is that?
[HACHIROU]
To defeat the wicked schemers,
the vile people, who
only see the blood
flowing through our
veins as a tool!
I take it that statement
is in reference to us.
Although your friends
in the Five Treasures
were no different.
You're wrong!
Gei'in and the others
understood the burden.
The toll that carrying the
memory in your blood
of lives lost can take!
It shook you down
to your very core.
You could not bear
such a heavy burden.
And so you ran.
[HACHIROU]
That's correct.
Which is why...
...I'm willing to use Ouka
right here, without hesitation,
to defeat you!
Oh?
As fascinating as that would be,
remember--the Ouka belongs
to both you and Hibiki.
Can you summon that power?
After all, that is
Oboro before you.
If that truly is the case,
if Oboro's mind is
in Hibiki's body.
I'll bet my life on Oboro's
feelings for her beloved!
Hmph!
We'll find out her
true feelings for Gennosuke.
[HACHIROU]
Oboro.
[gasps]
Gennosuke- sama , you
finally called me by my name.
[KUJAKU]
Heh
[HACHIROU]
Oboro.
Gennosuke, my love.
Look in my eyes, my darling.
Stare deep, into my very soul.
With every fiber of my being.
I'll return the emotions that
your eyes communicate.
And you, you must try to do
the very same thing for me.
The time has come, my love, for
our energies to unite as one.
[HIBIKI sighs]
[HACHIROU]
Oboro!
[gasps]
[HACHIROU]
Hibiki.
Oboro.
[HACHIROU]
Hibiki.
[HIBIKI]
Yes. That's me.
Utsutsu! That statue of Kanzeon.
Why is it there?
[RUI] I wonder if they're
connected to each other,
just like the red monster is
connected to the old man?
[UTSUTSU]
Watch out!
Mother.
[RUI gasps]
Rui! What are you doing?
Shichigen.
[NEIRICHIOU]
Hnn? You can't be that foolish.
Please.
Do you seriously intend to
impersonate the boy's mother?
And then what will you do?
Wake him?
What utter nonsense.
[RUI]
Here I am, Shichigen.
Now, come cling unto
your mother's breast.
[laughs]
Don't you see?
Your little techniques won't
work on your friend now.
What's this?
What the devil is happening?
[gasps]
Come to me.
Stop it, Shichigen!
That woman calling
to you isn't your mother!
She's an impostor!
Unless...
It looks like that is your
mother, Shichigen!
That indecent woman
you see before you
is undoubtedly your mother.
Kill her. Kill her now!
[UTSUTSU growls]
Yes, good.
Bring your sword down
upon the mother you hate.
Now kill her!
Kill off the very remembrance of
your mother who betrayed you!
[RUI whimpers]
[gasps]
[NEIRICHIOU yells]
[UTSUTSU snarls]
[yells]
Shichigen.
After all this time,
can't you forgive her?
[SHICHIGEN]
I never...
[gasps]
What he said... He was wrong...
I could never hate her...
I loved her, and she...
She never would have done
anything to betray her son.
[SHICHIGEN]
But...
I was just... so young...
I couldn't forgive her...
[SHICHIGEN] I couldn't forgive
myself for not forgiving her...
...and for what
happened that day...
That's why... That's why
you stabbed yourself?
In penance for that?
[grpw;s]
[gasping]
[HADAEBOU snarls]
You again?
[MAGOROKU groans]
No way.
[gasps]
[NEIRICHIOU chuckles]
[NEIRICHIOU gasps]
Wait. Have my wounds
become too much for you to bear,
great demon god?
[NEIRICHIOU] Thank you
for everything you've done,
my friend...
Farewell... Raijin- sama .
[NARRATOR]
To see the ending.
[NARRATOR] To witness the
answer the young ninjas
and their young leaders give.
To see it all end.