[NARRATOR] On the outside,
we look the same.
And yet, men call us monsters.
We are naught but
shadows lurking in between eras,
but if we are
destined to perish,
then I shall fall with
the cherry blossoms.
Yes.
I shall fall with
the cherry blossoms.
[HACHIROU]
I can't be certain,
but I think we might have
arrived at a different "now,"
altered from the "now" where
we faced the Joujinshuu,
and lost our companions.
No matter what world
we find ourselves in,
we can't stand by
as Joujin destroys it!
Not while we're
still able to fight!
You would interfere
in our affairs?
[laughs]
It'd be rude of us to
turn down free entertainment.
[KUJAKU] I don't know who you
people are, other than fools.
Ready?
We'll start with the one
that's the biggest threat.
[yells]
[KUJAKU]
Impossible.
[ITARU gasps]
My Destiny's Passage
will make short work of you!
You knew?
Damn you.
Your attack was a feint--
you used me to distract them!
[NEIRICHIOU growls]
Neirichiou!
You...
[NEIRICHIOU growl]
[NEIRICHIOU grunts]
[NEIRICHIOU screams]
Who are you? Tell me your names!
Kouga Hachirou.
Iga Hibiki.
[JOUJIN] Well, they
proved to be worthless.
Killed so easily.
[JOUJIN]
What's wrong?
I stand before you now.
Won't you use your
"eye magic" on me?
Hachirou.
I can't.
My Spearing Eye
won't work against him.
Well then, I'll try.
No, that last time.
Your technique only worked
because he was caught off guard.
[HIBIKI growls]
Joujin.
No matter what world you're in,
we won't allow
your wicked desires to
ever come to fruition!
Oh?
No matter what world I'm in?
So, what happened
to me in this "other world"
to which you refer?
You met with a gruesome death.
[JOUJIN]
I died, and then what happened?
Nothing.
You died, and all your
scheming lead to failure.
Then that possibility
is the only one you have seen?
It was.
I see.
[chuckles]
[HACHIROU]
Why do you laugh?
[laughs]
That's enough!
Begone!
[gasps]
You know nothing.
No matter the fate that
bound us in another world,
we are but strangers
in this one.
I will achieve my
ambitions with Murakumo!
I cannot be stopped!
Perhaps, or perhaps not.
Because in this world, you know
nothing of our final technique!
Your what?
[gasps]
I've never seen
a power like this before!
I'll handle the rest of it.
Thank you.
So, try to tell me
what it's like, best you can.
[HIBIKI sighs]
There's love, caring.
Plus pain and sorrow.
All those feelings combined.
Perhaps it's connected
to the contradictory powers
you originally possessed.
Something that channeled
those diverse feelings,
and distilled them into
a strength unmatched.
But...
If that's how it works,
why aren't we able
to control the power ourselves?
Because of those emotions.
They're rooted in
violence and passion,
and can't be controlled.
It's a power
that's fueled by joy,
melancholy, and madness.
[GORONE]
I find it hard to comprehend.
Why would the technique you
both created be so powerful,
yet unable to bring
you happiness?
The entire equation is unfair.
[gasps]
Ouka can evolve,
this is the first stage.
[GORONE]
Yes.
What we've seen of the technique
could easily be eclipsed
by the intense brilliance
of its true form.
[HIBIKI]
The brilliance of its true form.
[JOUJIN]
This is your ultimate technique?
[HIBIKI gasps]
[JOUJIN]
Behold.
Look upon the destruction
your ability has wrought.
[HACHIROU gasps]
[HIBIKI growls]
In the end, my weakness
brings me shame.
I'll never get over the pain of
being unable to defeat you
without using the Ouka.
So now... you will kill me?
I will put you down
without mercy.
Die, Joujin.
[HACHIROU] It doesn't
matter what the Ouka is,
we must abstain from
ever using it again.
Yes.
[HACHIROU]
But as long as we're together,
we cannot escape its grasp!
I've chosen.
I know what I'm
willing to forfeit.
[HIBIKI gasps]
No, don't leave again!
[gasps]
[HIBIKI]
No! Give me another chance!
You have to!
[HACHIROU grunts]
Wait. Your Shielding Eye.
Yes, Hachirou.
It's finally time to do what I
should have done long ago.
[HACHIROU]
Hibiki!
No...
[HIBIKI] Now, you'll never
forget about Ouka.
Or leave me behind.
[HACHIROU whimpers]
Hibiki..
I'll never stray
from your side again.
I'll be with you, eternally.
[JOUJIN]
Pathetic fools.
[HACHIROU]
Joujin!
Tell me, was that display
the best you could muster?
Impossible.
I killed you, I'm sure of it.
That can't be. Tenzen?
I'm impressed
that you know of him.
[HACHIROU]
The Tenzen cherry tree blooms
above Jison'in Village.
They say an immortal ninja
gave the tree its name.
Tenzen.
[HACHIROU]
You mean to tell me he was real?
[JOUJIN]
So it would appear.
Now, he lives on within me.
[gasps]
[JOUJIN] I never thought she
would destroy her own eyes.
How very dull.
All right.
She's no threat,
just forget about us.
[JOUJIN]
I will, I assure you.
Of course, if I let you live,
you'll only get in my way.
What?
[JOUJIN] Even a single pebble
in the road could cause
a man to stumble.
That is why you must be removed.
[yells]
[JOUJIN] The eye magic you
used to defeat Magoroku.
it seems to reflect an enemy's
desire to kill you back on them.
An interesting technique,
to say the very least.
[HACHIROU grunts]
[JOUJIN] And still,
you will not use it on me,
now that all other options
have failed you?
I assume you used it
against me in that other world
you spoke of, and it
failed to affect me.
[HACHIROU growls]
[JOUJIN]
I have seen your weakness,
and know precisely
how to exploit it.
[HACHIROU growls]
[HIBIKI]
Hachirou!
Hibiki.
[HIBIKI]
Hachirou.
Where are you?
[HIBIKI whines]
[JOUJIN yells]
[JOUJIN]
Too easy.
Stupid boy.
[HACHIROU] Joujin, aren't
you ashamed of yourself?
[JOUJIN]
Hmm?
Keeping yourself alive.
Having to rely on
the power of Tenzen.
The power of a mere ninja?
That's your plan?
To draw out my desire to
kill you with your insults?
A feeble attempt at best.
Didn't you know?
Tenzen lusted after Oboro,
leader of the Iga clan.
He tried to rape the woman
he was honor-bound to serve,
a despicable monster.
If you realize your ambitions,
but only through the help of a
worthless excuse for a ninja.
Can you honestly take pride in
what you've accomplished?
You're a tenacious one,
I'll give you that much.
Hachirou, was it?
It won't work on me.
[gasps]
What?
Stop it!
[coughs]
You used... Tenzen's
desire... to kill you?
[JOUJIN groans]
Tenzen. Stop it!
What are you doing?
Hachirou!
Where are you?
[JOUJIN groans]
[TENZEN screeches]
Slow down, Chou!
Wait up!
[IEMITSU]
In truth.
I don't like my brother,
Tadanaga.
Neither do I believe his story.
He tried to plot rebellion.
He not only betrayed me,
but our legacy.
I will not abide this treason.
However.
I wonder who
stoked this fire within him.
Our stations were
determined by the outcome
of a ninja battle.
Such an embarrassing
fact about us both,
and one only a handful
of people could have known.
He still could not
forgive me, after so long.
[TENKAI]
Your Majesty.
In the end, it was all for the
glory of the Tokugawa Clan.
[NARRATOR] Some say Tenkai lived
on for another decade,
eventually surpassing
the century mark,
until he had fulfilled all
of his earthly desires.
Wait! I'm not ready yet.
I...
[NARRATOR] The tenth
year of the Kan'ei Era.
In December of that year.
Tokugawa Tadanaga commits
seppuku by the order
of the Shogun.
A fact that few people
were aware of,
due to the machinations
of the Joujinshuu
was that the true Tadanaga
had died long ago.
[NARRATOR]
And the cherry blossoms,
bloomed and fell several times,
as the seasons rolled on.
[CHILDREN laughing, yelling]
[SAIZOU]
Go for it, Shichigen!
Watch close, Utsutsu!
I won't lose today!
Rui! You should come
and watch with me!
[SHICHIGEN]
Go ahead and make your move!
Looks like we've got
a real match on our hands.
[RUI] I bet Hachisu wins, cause
she's the toughest girl I know!
[SHIKIBU]
C'mon!
[gasps]
Shikibu, wait!
[SAIZOU grunts]
[HACHISU] Saizou,
what do you think you're doing?
[SAIZOU]
I'm helping.
[SHICHIGEN]
I don't need any help from you.
I'm a samurai, remember?
[SAIZOU] Fine. Then I'm
on Hachisu's side.
[WOMAN B]
Food's ready, everyone!
Come and get it!
[CHILDREN cheering]
[WOMAN B]
Hibiki, stay.
We'll come get you once the kids
have all been taken care of.
Sure. The weather's
so nice today,
I don't mind staying out
a little while longer.
[JOUJIN]
Well, well.
[HIBIKI gasps]
[JOUJIN] You cannot see,
and Hachirou isn't here
to watch over you.
Joujin?
No. Joujin died long ago.
How can you be so certain?
In truth, I did perish
when last we met.
But then...
Tenzen.
[JOUJIN] I'd expect no less
from the leader of the Iga.
[HIBIKI whimpers]
[JOUJIN] Nobunaga- sama 's
soul has returned to Hell.
Hachirou is gone.
Since you rendered
your eyes completely useless.
I can no longer
harness the Ouka.
However, there
is one course of action
still available.
[HIBIKI whimpers]
[JOUJIN]
That's right.
I shall fill your womb
with the seed of life.
And you will be with child,
and bear forth my heir.
No one will come to save you.
Give up, and submit
yourself to my will!
[HIBIKI grunts]
Your blood is strong.
If my essence were to
combine with your bloodline.
We would create a technique
that would surpass Ouka.
[JOUJIN]
With our two bloodlines mixed,
we shall truly make
this world a living Hell!
[gasps]
[yells]
[TENZEN screeches]
Hachirou...
[HADAEBOU sighs]
Bright, with a healthy breeze.
Couldn't ask for a
finer day to travel.