Where are we?
[gasps]
[NAMENBA gasps]
What's wrong with you?!
Very funny!
Stupid Kouga brats!
[SHICHIGEN]
Heh!
[SHIKIBU grunts]
[SHIKIBU groans]
No fair!
He's the one not being
fair, he's got armor!
[SHICHIGEN grunts, groans]
You little--
No kunai allowed.
We don't want
to kill each other.
This is sparring.
You're only allowed
to fight here for
the purpose of training.
And we aren't doing this
for the glory of the Kouga,
nor for the Iga.
But rather, we do this
all for the sake of our leaders.
[RUI]
Is that her?
That girl's going
to be our leader?
So let's test her.
Hold on. Are you sure?
I won't hit her.
I want to see her get scared.
[HIBIKI gasps]
[gasps]
[HIBIKI giggles]
She can detect any
antagonistic thought.
and subdue it.
The secret
technique of Iga Hibiki,
leader of the
Five Flowers of Iga:
Eye Shield Magic.
That's their leader?
Then... that must be...
[SAIZOU]
Hachirou?
Wait, Saizou!
[SHICHIGEN gasps]
He okay?
[GORONE]
You almost died, boy.
Even if you were
planning to miss him,
with the slightest
whiff of malice...
...Hachirou's Eye magic sends
that energy back to its source.
Oh...
[HACHIROU]
Calm down, Hibiki.
It's all right.
[HIBIKI]
You're being selfish, Hachirou!
Utsutsu, Hachisu, Rui...
Why do you think
they're all here?
Saizou, Shikibu,
and Shichigen, too.
I realize that.
But I still must do what's right
for me at this point in my life.
[HIBIKI]
Then let's try it.
Try it?
That's right.
If this is to be the end
of all we know,
let's put our Eye Magic
to the test, and see
what awful things
our powers can do.
Kazuma! Kazuma, where are you?
Answer us, damn it!
[single lyre note plays]
[GEI'IN gasps]
Did you hear that?
Sounds like he caught something.
If that's the tone of his
Heaven's Lyre ringing out,
then his opponent must be dead.
He's there...
[GEI'IN gasps]
[KASOU]
Hold on, Kazuma!
[KAZUMA]
Kasou...
[KASOU]
Right. I'll come untie you!
[KAZUMA]
Did you hear it sing, Kasou?
The ringing of my ultimate
technique, the Heaven's Lyre.
I'm ready to play it
and hear its true melody.
[KAZUMA]
Now... listen with me...
Listen to the haunting melody of
the completed Heaven's Lyre!
No, Kazuma, don't do it!
No, wait!
[KUJAKU] This is the inevitable
destiny of the ninja.
To offer up
their lives to devils.
Ever chasing their
technique's perfection.
Until they are consumed wholly
by their unbound desires.
[KASOU]
You killed Tenshin and Kazuma?
[KUJAKU] But even if one
were to spend their lifetime
mastering such skills,
it would be nothing more
than a parlor trick.
Only fit for subtracting oneself
from the greater equation.
It seems rather
poignant, in a way.
Kusanagi Kazuma.
Though his life came to
a close somewhat abruptly,
I think he saw he was
a big fish in a small pond.
--What--?
--Hold on!
Now who're you?
Etiquette isn't
your strong point?
One typically introduces
themselves before asking
the name of the second party.
Alas, it's truly no matter,
because I already
know who you are.
The famous Five
Treasure of Kouga.
Both living and dead.
[growls]
[KUJAKU]
The Five Treasures.
Strange, it seems that one of
your number is currently absent.
As I recall, your leader
is Kouga Hachirou?
But he's still
just a child, is he not?
Perhaps something frightened
him, and he ran home weeping?
[KASOU]
Die!
Kasou! Stop!
[KUJAKU]
Hmph.
[GEI'IN gasps]
[KASOU gasps]
[KASOU screams]
Kasou...
[GEI'IN]
No, this is impossible!
[KUJAKU]
Well?
Your name.
I demand you tell me
who you are!
[KUJAKU]
The Joujinshuu.
Not that you would know it,
even with me telling you
to your face.
But I am one of their agents.
Kujaku Tsuibamu is my name.
But why?
I don't understand why the
Joujinshuu would choose
to rise up against
the Kouga like you claim!
Perhaps telling you
this will help you come
to grips with reality,
but things are exponentially
more complicated than us merely
being enemies of
the Five Treasures of Kouga,
I can assure you.
What?
[KUJAKU] We plan to see to it
that the Five Flowers of Iga
also perish tonight.
Utter nonsense.
[KUJAKU] Do you
honestly believe that claim
is outside our abilities?
Or have you at last
come to the realization
that your death is
fast approaching
and any shred of reason is gone?
Ripped away from you in a
maelstrom of mortal terror.
No, not quite.
I've grown far too old
to be afraid of death.
Getting old is such a
terribly depressing proposition.
You can go on acting as tough
as you'd like, but you can't
hide the beads of sweat
rolling off your forehead.
[GEI'IN] Then I suppose
we can dispense
with the pleasantries, can't we?
There's nothing left to say.
Yes. Let's.
[GEI'IN]
Very well, then!
[GEI'IN] Let's see if
you have what it takes
to finish me off, too!
If you can survive
my first attack!
[gasps]
You're a damned fool.
Your ignorance will cost you.
Light isn't the only
thing released by
my secret ninja technique,
Firefly Squid!
It seems you've
failed to realize
it contains a deadly
poison as well!
Hah! Oh, my!
[laughs]
[GEI'IN]
What?
[KUJAKU] I wonder, which one of
us is the real fool, old man?
[GEI'IN]
But... Why didn't it work?
It wouldn't matter
if it was a Firefly Squid
or just a regular one,
because no poison can work
without the victim coming
into contact with it.
There's no need
to act so surprised.
Even the Kurokuwa you
encountered earlier
have harnessed the
ability of levitation.
Another power in
their bag of tricks.
[GEI'IN] I see, and which
of the ninja lines did
the Joujinshuu come from?
[KUJAKU]
Ninja?
We aren't peons who
can only serve their lord
and live out their
lives in secret.
Not like you
unfortunate creatures.
[GEI'IN]
What?
[KUJAKU] The longer
the Tokugawas flourish
and the peace they
established continues unabated,
the less need they
will have for ninja.
Perhaps this is
a mercy of sorts for you.
To be killed before you see the
end of the ninja way of life!
I've had enough
of your proud posturing!
Oh, my!
[KUJAKU giggles]
[GEI'IN]
A strange sight, is it not?
The light that emanates from my
sweat derives from the fact
that since childhood,
I have ingested a litany
of virulent, toxic elements.
This is the power
of a ninja's technique!
A light gained after
total dedication.
All paid for with unyielding
focus and intense suffering!
[GEI'IN groans]
[GEI'IN yells]
[GEI'IN gasps]
So I...
I wasn't simply
imagining things...?
I take it you've
already figured out
what just happened.
Indeed.
Something altered
the very flow of time
and sent it backwards.
[GEI'IN] You made the passing
of time reverse itself?
No, that sort of technique
should be completely impossible!
[KUJAKU]
How interesting!
You noticed for yourself,
yet refuse to admit it?
That stubbornness
will be the end of you.
I can promise you that.
[GEI'IN]
The end...
This must certainly be
an exhilarating
experience for you.
Death by the coursing
of your own poison.
[giggles] Well, die slowly,
then, you pickled old squid.
[GEI'IN groans]
[GEI'IN]
I shall meet my demise
with my task
unfulfilled, my lord.
I beg your forgiveness.
[HIBIKI]
Hachirou, what's wrong?
[HACHIROU]
I heard Gei'in's voice just now.
And he... No, the
Five Treasures are dead!
[HIBIKI gasps]
I could hear his voice as if
he were standing here.
They've all been defeated!
I'll go on ahead!
[NAMENBA]
The Five Treasures are dead?
[HACHIROU] I hope with all my
heart that I'm wrong.
No, if that was
how it seemed to you,
then that must be what happened.
The rest of the
Five Treasures are lost.
Yes, but who's responsible?
If all four of them
were defeated in combat,
the enemy was
either very skilled,
or used overwhelming numbers.
Whatever the case,
they were strong ninjas.
It would have taken a great deal
of preparation to defeat them.
So Gei'in and
the others were targeted
from the start?
Then that means--
[HIBIKI whimpers]
Definitely.
Hachirou.
I can no longer allow you
to leave the village,
as we'd discussed.
With the
Five Treasures now gone,
I don't dare go
against their will.
[GORONE]
Wait.
Wait!
First thing's first--
We must tell the
Five Flowers of Iga.
I don't want to let
the damned Iga avenge
our fallen comrades!
Then who shall we
send to avenge you?
[NAMENBA]
Let's leave this to Rui.
She is the fastest.
Hold on.
If we're informing
the Five Flowers,
as their leader, I should go!
[HACHISU]
You have to stay behind, safe.
Can't risk you getting killed.
[HIBIKI sighs]
[UTSUTSU]
Besides,
whether the Five treasures
were actually killed or not,
do we Iga need to
meddle in Kouga affiars?
You're really
still talking like that?
Remember, our two clans
now share the same fate.
What I remember
is Kazuma tried to kill me
during yesterday's
training mission!
--He got what he deserved.
--Be quiet!
He only did that
because you threw a kunai
at him during his training!
[UTSUTSU] But did he
have to take things so far?
[RUI]
Give them a break.
The Kouga aren't
really all that bad.
[UTSUTSU] You mean
you never noticed it, Rui?
[RUI gasps]
That Shichigen guy
looks nice, and, who knows?
Maybe he is mostly harmless.
But whenever he thinks
that no one is looking,
he stares at your breasts.
[RUI whimpers]
He wants to get
his hands on them so bad.
No way...
[UTSUTSU growls] Why do
we have to keep company
--with these fools?
--That's enough, Utsutsu!
Even though we may be
called on to avenge the Kouga,
we have to do as we're asked.
Situations like this
are the reason we were
brought here in the first place.
[UTSUTSU]
Hmph.
[RUI sighs]
It's up to you.
Shichigen, you
volunteered for this assignment,
so don't let us down.
[UTSUTSU]
Hmph.
You might want to
stay close to me.
We don't know when the enemy
will choose to appear.
[RUI sighs]
Hey, you can hear me, can't you?
Of course I can.
Well then, don't
let your guard down.
[RUI] My guard's been
up this whole time.
The enemy may be even
closer than I expected.
[SAIZOU]
I'll send my eyes up to spy.
You can, I don't know,
watch the north?
I don't take orders from you.
I'll decide which direction
I'm going to check.
[SAIZOU groans]
[UTSUTSU]
Hmm?
[SAIZOU groaning]
That disgusts me
every time I see it.
And it can't be convenient.
Sure, it lets you see farther
away, but it also leaves
your eyes and your body wide
open to an enemy's attack.
I mean, what would
you do if you lost your eyes?
[SAIZOU]
I wouldn't care.
If it means protecting Hachirou,
I'd gladly give up
an eyeball or two.
[UTSUTSU]
What is wrong with everyone?
In any case...
...you wanted me to watch north?
Consider the north
under observation.
[HACHISU] So, the Treasures of
Kouga--are they really dead?
[SHIKIBU] Well, it's
definitely not something
that I want to believe.
But Hachirou would never lie.
It's true.
Huh.
It makes you itch?
[HACHISU] Hey. If it
itches, just take it off.
I can help, you know?
[gasps]
Cut it out!
[HACHISU gasps]
Don't touch me.
[HACHISU whimpers]
[gasps]
Sorry. No offense.
None taken.
[HACHIROU]
This is your plan?
You're going to keep us
cooped in here all night?
[GORONE]
That's precisely the plan.
There's also a place to
hide underneath the floor.
[HACHIROU]
Is that so?
[GORONE] And you'll only
come out when we're sure
that it's over.
Your safety is our priority.
They're late.
[TADANAGA]
Is that you, Gei'in?
Answer me, now!
[JOUJIN]
Forgive my impudence,
but may I ask you for
your name, my lord?
I'm searching for the one
known as Suruga Dainagon.
Is that you?
[TADANAGA gasps]
[JOUJIN] Are you Suruga
Dainagon, my lord?
I must know.
Indeed, I am.
[JOUJIN]
The ruler of the rich fiefdoms
of Suruga and To-otoumi.
As well as Dainagon of
the Imperial Court.
In other words,
after the former shogun,
Lord Hidetada and the current
shogun, Iemitsu- sama ,
you are the third most
important man in the country.
However, you are
also the most unfortunate soul
in the entire Land
of the Rising Sun.
[TADANAGA]
What? How dare you say that!
I refuse to forgive
such disrespect!
[TADANAGA gasps]
[JOUJIN]
I am afraid that someday soon,
your own neck, Suruga- sama ,
will be exposed to the blade
in order to maintain
the peace, as it were.
[TADANAGA]
What? Hold your tongue!
Kneel before me, that I might
bring about your execution
here and now!
[JOUJIN]
Execute me?
It is you who will be executed,
Suruga- sama .
This much I promise you.
Quiet, you bastard!
No more talk!
Impudent scum!
[JOUJIN] And, the one
who will bring death down
upon your noble head?
[gasps]
[JOUJIN] Your execution will be
brought about by your brother.
Shogun Iemitsu
will be your demise!
What utter nonsense.
[JOUJIN] You call it nonsense,
and perhaps you're right
in that regard, but you've also
noticed the sinister feelings
your brother thinks
he's hidden away
in the depths of his heart.
[TADANAGA]
Who the hell are you?
Tell me!
[JOUJIN] My lord Dainagon,
you may call me Joujin.
[NARRATOR]
Tokugawa Tadanaga.
Grandson of the shogun Ieyasu,
who began the
Tokugawa's 300 year reign.
He never ascended
to the role of shogun,
and was forced to
commit seppuku.
Or, so the history books say.