[HACHIROU] Joujin!
Open the doors to Murakumo!
[HACHIROU] Kouga Hachirou,
has at last arrived!
Kujaku Tsuibamu.
Gorone has fallen.
I want Namenba to
conduct funerary rites.
[SAIZOU]
We'll find a way in, too.
I'll set up, see if
I can get a clear line of fire.
Saizou.
We need you to keep
an eye out from above.
[RUI]
We'll go right, you go left.
[SHIKIBU]
Got it.
Hachirou and Hibiki,
we're coming to save you.
Then, I suppose it's
time for me to head to the back.
[SAIZOU groans]
[SAIZOU]
I need all of you.
Too narrow.
That slippery
monk could probably
slither in, but I can't.
[ITARU giggles]
[ITARU]
Your guts will burst out,
and fall to the ground, and
your soul sent straight to Hell.
[groans]
[HADAEBOU groans]
[gasps]
Yasha Itaru.
[HADAEBOU] Wait, has he fallen
victim to Destiny's Passage?
[GORONE] It's time you tell
us everything you know.
What are the
Joujinshuu's techniques?
[HADAEBOU] Yasha Itaru
has the power of what
one might call
"extreme suggestion."
Her technique
presents the victim a vision,
making their entire life
seem a burden to others.
An existence plagued
by evil and misfortune,
and ending violently.
[ITARU] One's whole world is not
but the tumbling of the dice.
They roll and scatter.
One stirs in slumber.
We dub this fitful dream
life, but death wakes us all.
Now listen, to learn
to play Oicho-Kabu.
You have to add up the two
cards, and whoever has
the highest first digit
is the winner.
[SAIZOU'S DAD]
Okay, how many points is that?
[SAIZOU]
Ah... [laughs]
I guess it's still
too early to try out.
[SAIZOU]
Six.
Five.
Eight.
[SAIZOU]
Two sevens.
Well, Dad?
How long are
we going to do this?
Tell me.
[MAN A]
Never seen you before.
[SAIZOU'S DAD]
Yeah. I'm not from here.
[MAN B]
Got any money?
[SAIZOU'S DAD]
Sure.
Just a little, to pay for
traveling expenses.
[MAN B]
Well, ante up then.
[MAN B] All right,
let's go another round!
[MAN B]
I'm staying in.
[MAN A]
Damn it!
[MAN C]
I'm in.
[MAN D]
It's your turn, stranger.
Ah-- Sorry about
that. I need a moment.
Just make a decision.
We don't have all
damn night, you know.
[SAIZOU]
Six.
Five.
Two sevens.
Here we go,
man's got to take a risk!
[MAN C]
Six!
[MAN B]
Five.
[SAIZOU'S DAD]
Two sevens.
[MAN C groans]
I thought I had that!
[SAIZOU] You're letting
him play you for fools.
Poor saps.
[SAIZOU] Of course,
the same could be said of me.
[SAIZOU]
But...
I suspect he was
being played, too.
[HACHIROU]
Tadanaga- sama ?
You've come to us
at last, Kouga Hachirou.
Joujin. Where is she?
I'm taking Hibiki back home.
We won't work with you.
We'll never give you control
of our Ouka technique.
Enough.
As impressive as your skill
may be, it was never our goal.
Tell me--and be honest--
do you really see the world
that we live in today as
one filled with peace?
[JOUJIN]
Hmph. Nothing to say?
Of course not.
Why did your mother and
father have to die so horribly
if our nation was truly
a land at peace?
[HACHIROU]
The Tokugawas are to blame!
[JOUJIN]
The Tokugawas!
Precisely as
I'd hoped you'd say.
[JOUJIN] The temporary
peace their dynasty boasts
is an illusion.
You of all people should know,
the age of civil wars
never truly came to an end!
They aren't over, there
hasn't been enough killing!
[HACHIROU]
What are you saying?
[JOUJIN] Should that
glorious Hell on Earth
really be allowed to
conclude so neatly?
Don't you understand?
Joujin shows this
world compassion.
An altruistic nature equaled
only by the Buddha.
That's nonsense!
The Buddha wishes only
to save the world from itself!
You are evil passions
in the flesh!
The total opposite!
[JOUJIN]
But that's where you're wrong.
I intend to bring true
salvation unto the masses.
And in order to do that,
the people of this world
must experience the hell that
comes with it along the way.
The sinners, the innocent,
the flames will
consume them all.
And when there
are none who long for war--
even the slightest--
left standing,
only then, will we know
real salvation.
True peace.
That is my one desire.
[HACHIROU]
You're mad.
[JOUJIN] The Tokugawas created
a temporary peace and engaged in
a capricious game to
determine their next heir
at the cost of your clan.
Do you think that
should be allowed?
Thus, my desire
to end such behavior.
[HACHIROU grunts]
By installing
a great demon king,
who can wield the sword that
will summon forth devils!
[SAIZOU'S DAD]
Five. Tough luck.
[MAN C]
You rat bastard!
You're cheating, I know it!
[SAIZOU'S DAD]
Hey, now.
just because you keep losing,
there's no need for you
to take it out on me.
[MAN A]
can't really blame him for that.
After all the money we've lost
to an outsider tonight,
I'm sure you can
understand how he feels.
[SAIZOU'S DAD]
Fair.
Now can we all get back
to having some fun?
Whaddaya say?
[SAIZOU'S DAD]
Well. I'll have fun at least.
Cause as long as Saizou's eye is
up there, watching out for me.
You idiots don't
stand a chance in hell.
[SAIZOU huffs]
[SAIZOU]
Dad, it's so cold.
[SAIZOU'S DAD]
Oh, my! I win again?
Can't believe my luck!
[SAIZOU'S DAD] Saizou,
this will be the final round
for the night.
Don't screw it up.
I'll get you something warm
to eat when we're done.
[MAN C]
Heh.
[
Give me another card.
[MAN C]
I won't lose this time!
[MAN B]
I'm in.
All right, I guess I'll
get in on this hand, too.
[SAIZOU'S DAD]
A three and a six, huh?
Good hand.
[SAIZOU'S DAD]
Hmm?
Where the hell is he?
[MAN D]
So? Are you in, or are you out?
Add up your cards, and the
first digit closest to nine
is the winner.
But ya know, matching
cards can beat that.
[MAN C]
Hmph.
[MAN C] I'm not letting some
outsider take me for everything!
[gasps]
[SAIZOU'S DAD]
Look at this beauty of a hand.
The gods of fortune are
smiling on me tonight.
I can win this on my own!
[MAN C] It's the last round,
so I'll bet everything
I've got left!
There's my stake.
[MAN B]
Too rich for my blood.
[MAN A]
I'm out.
[MAN D]
Okay, then, winner takes all.
[SAIZOU'S DAD] Show 'em.
I've got a three and a six!
[MAN C]
Doubles!
[MAN B] And he got matching
tens, the strongest hand!
You win double!
[MAN A]
Damn.
[MAN D] So, he took
everything you had, huh?
[MAN C laughs]
[blow lands]
[SAIZOU'S DAD]
What were you doing?!
I saw the moon...
What's that?
The moon made you fail me?
You worthless little bastard.
I didn't mean to...
I'm sorry, Papa...
[SAIZOU]
I did it deliberately.
[SAIZOU] To finish off your
sorry little enterprise.
It was all supposed to come to
an end there, under that moon.
[SAIZOU]
It was supposed to end there.
But instead the
Kouga took me in.
[ITARU chuckles]
[HADAEBOU] After gazing into
the abyss of your own despair.
Yasha's words take
root inside your soul,
and bring you to your doom.
[SAIZOU]
My so-called leader.
You didn't need us
until the very end, huh?
Well, I never needed
to be lead, anyway.
[HACHIROU]
Their destiny is to fall,
but the sakura blossoms
will always return.
So, my friends.
Join me.
The time has come
for us to fall!
[ITARU]
It's time to go to Hell!
[SAIZOU laughs]
That's been the plan all along.
[SAIZOU]
What have we here?
A perfect way to scatter
my guts on the ground.
[SAIZOU]
Heh.
It's funny.
I've always been a contrarian,
and the last thing that I want
is to do something just because
somebody ordered me to!
[UTSUTSU]
Saizou!
What are you doing? Stop!
[SAIZOU]
I already see too much.
That's the downside to my power.
As a rule, I don't look at
things unnecessarily.
[UTSUTSU] It seems I can never
see what I want to see.
So I have dreams.
But they're always horrifying.
[SAIZOU] This is the most
beautiful thing I've ever seen
in this unforgiving world.
[gasps]
[UTSUTSU]
Saizou!
We've stopped.
It matters not if you
stop Murakumo in its path.
Tell me, did you think this
was nothing more than
a palankeen to carry us to Edo?
There's more to the
Murakumo than meets the eye.
If you thinks it's simply a
moving castle, you're mistaken.
It serves as a barrier,
which will at last enable
the secret ritual
to be conducted
to revive Lord Nobunaga.
That is not all.
For when he revives,
reborn as a child, no--
reborn into this world
as a savage beast,
the Murakumo is the womb which
shall awaken the memories
lying dormant within him,
as well as his thirst for glory!
[HACHIROU] That's quite
an impressive speech
you've made to
justify your actions.
You should share this
with a playwright.
Your dream would make
fascinating Noh theatre.
But I have
no intention of performing
as a character in your playlet.
But you must,
for no one else can play
your part quite so capably.
We must have you.
And Hibiki!
[HACHIROU]
And Hibiki?
Indeed.
She's a necessary
aspect of the revival ritual
we've been planning.
Why is Hibiki needed,
or I, for that matter?
You're pieces
to the great puzzle.
We must have a young man
and young woman in love
with each other to continue.
Of course, not just
any man or woman will suffice.
For they must be
of a worthy bloodline.
Masters of an art, with perfect
bodies and powerful souls!
[HACHIROU]
To what end?
For this plan
to work the two of you
must lie together.
[HACHIROU gasps]
[JOUJIN] The fluids generated
by your coupling will flow,
and pour down into the skull,
becoming the blood
that will connect it to a body.
For only then, will the great
demon king be reborn unto us.
[HACHIROU] And you think we'll
agree to be a part of this?
[JOUJIN]
Will you not?
[HACHIROU]
You know the answer!
[JOUJIN] Should you refuse, then
I'm afraid that you and Hibiki
will be forced to
slay one another instead.
If you and
she kill each other,
the rite can still be completed.
[HACHIROU]
What?
[JOUJIN] You may not
know this, but the fluids
born of love-making can contain
the same potent magical energy
as the blood that is spilled
during deadly combat!
If you'll not willingly
generate those fluids,
then I shall require
your blood instead!
You sound like a madman.
We will never lie
together for you.
Let alone kill each other!
[JOUJIN] I fear you will find
that you have no choice
in the matter, boy.
[gasps]
Hibiki!
[HACHIROU gasps]
What's wrong? Hibiki?
I'm not her.
I am Oboro of Iga,
or have you forgotten?
Kouga Gennosuke- sama .
[HACHIROU gasps]
You are an inhuman monster.
I wish I'd never made
the mistake of falling in love
with you all those years ago.
Because if I hadn't,
then those in my clan
wouldn't have been slaughtered
like animals.
[HIBIKI] I regret everything,
but it's too late.
To atone, I must offer my
head before their graves!
No, that's no good,
it isn't enough!
First, Gennosuke,
I must offer them your head!
[NARRATOR]
No. You're the monster.
I shall permanently alter
that disgusting fate of yours.
Just wait and see.