[TADANAGA] At last,
we're finally going to Edo.
To Chiyoda Castle.
That's strange.
Why would it stop?
[gasps]
[HACHISU]
Namenba, look!
[NAMENBA]
Yes. I see her.
What are you doing, Hibiki?
Stay down.
[HACHISU]
I count three of them.
[NAMENBA]
Three more over there.
We can't let them call
for reinforcements.
Yeah. I'll fan out right.
[NAMENBA growls]
What is it you want now?
A colder greeting
than I'd hoped.
My assistance garners no thanks?
As always,
you only helped us because
you stand to benefit somehow.
That said, you saved us.
Let's go.
Before you take your leave.
[NAMENBA]
Hm?
Know this.
More of the Rain
are lying in wait.
Enough men to cover all of
the approaches to the castle.
Will you still
charge in blindly?
Two against an unknown
number of enemies?
That's our choice to make.
No, we should retreat.
[gasps]
Well, Namenba- dono .
It seems we are
of the same mind.
Let's ready our
weapons and return.
We'll need to discuss
this with Gorone.
How splendid!
May I go with you
to talk to him?
Totally out of the question.
We don't trust you,
quite frankly. It's uncanny.
How do you always show up
at the perfect moment?
It was the same back
at Chiyoda Castle.
Doesn't every
man like to flaunt his prowess
in front of the woman
whom he fancies?
[NAMENBA]
Hmph. Let's go, Hachisu.
[HACHISU gasps]
I see.
Hibiki followed them
into the new Murakumo.
There's nothing we could do.
We had been
keeping watch on her.
But we let our guard down.
Come now,
you mustn't blame yourselves.
If she attacked us while under
the influence of some kind of
mind control, no one
could defeat her.
No one but Hachirou that is.
And you say this castle
is currently on the
move, correct?
Last we saw.
But it was moving slow
enough to keep up with on foot.
We'll have no problem
catching up to it.
Then wait here for now.
What?
Don't try to go
after it on your own.
I know you're right,
but it's our leader
who was kidnapped by the enemy.
[UTSUTSU]
So are we going?
[NAMENBA]
We are.
Are you feeling
well enough to run?
I'm perfectly fine,
just some residual numbness.
It's my pride that hurts most.
Protecting her is our duty.
And yet... She was able to
slip away under our watch.
[UTSUTSU] And you want
us to wait for the rest?
Don't be ridiculous!
With this humiliation
hanging over our heads,
how could we face them?
It's dangerous
to make such a decision
based solely on
fleeting emotions.
[GIRLS sigh]
[NAMENBA] Give them
a chance, that's all I ask.
Besides...
I'm beginning to feel
the same way that they do.
Don't you understand?
These girls have
a lifelong bond.
Since they first lived together,
they've never been
separated from her.
Not even once.
[GORONE sighs]
Please say yes.
Fine, you win.
[GIRLS]
Hm!
[GORONE] But you'll need more
firepower than you've got now.
I'll have something
ready for you by dawn.
[MALE ROYAL A]
What do you mean,
the castle has
appeared once again?
[MALE ROYAL B] That's what
the Kurokuwa messenger
reported to us.
Also that it's moving.
[MALE ROYAL C]
Impossible.
[MALE ROYAL A] How much
can we believe in the word
of this "messenger"?
It sounds highly suspect.
[MALE ROYAL B]
All I'm sure of is what he said.
It's heading east, towards Edo.
[IEMITSU] Tenkai, were you
lying when you told me
Murakumo had disappeared?
[TENKAI]
I was not, mighty shogun.
But in all fairness,
I said nothing about
the Joujinshuu
themselves disappearing,
only that their
castle had done so.
Don't be so pedantic--
remember who I am.
I mean you no
disrespect, your lordship.
We should try to remain calm.
Even if the enemy
castle truly is moving,
we have a great deal
of time to prepare for it
as it slowly makes its way
toward Edo, your Excellency.
Before it arrives,
it will be dealt with.
So can I take you at your word?
You swear it?
That this time,
you'll defeat these
enemies of the state?
Answer!
[TENKAI chuckles] What an
utterly fascinating situation.
Explain.
[TENKAI] I never expected
the seeds of fate to change
the course of my life, but its
roots have grown far and deep,
interweaving with mine.
Nevertheless.
I will not allow
this threat to further
encroach upon Chiyoda castle.
You will be safe, my lord.
I swear upon the
peace that your ancestor,
Ieyasu- sama , brought
to this great nation,
and the prosperity
that followed.
[IEMITSU growls]
These are all we've got.
We're taking everything.
We can't carry this much stuff.
It's too heavy.
[UTSUTSU]
So we'll grab what ever we can.
Even with all of this,
we may not have enough.
It's been a while
since I went on a mission.
What?
[laughs]
It was just a silly joke.
Of course I can't go,
and wouldn't want to.
[NAMENBA]
Hmm...
[gasps]
[GORONE]
Care for a persimmon?
Sure.
[GORONE] You'll have to help
yourself, Namenba- dono .
Perhaps someday,
we'll have known
each other for a long time.
How did you know it was me?
Your face looks tired,
you must've traveled far,
but there are no droplets of
sweat beading up on your brow.
[GORONE] You're trying
to pass as a girl from
the nearby village, but you
aren't quite pulling it off.
Well then. I take it you're him?
Apologies, but could
you help me stand?
[gasps]
[GORONE] I could see
it etched in your face.
"I have to work
with a total weakling
who can't even walk on his own?
How'd I get stuck with
such a terrible assignment?"
I wasn't thinking that.
[GORONE]
Okay, that's the last of them.
Let's be honest.
If things were different, and
I was just a girl from town,
I would've had to spend the rest
of my life taking care of you.
And that wouldn't have
worked out for you, huh?
[NAMENBA]
You're right.
[NAMENBA] I would have
been sick of it soon enough.
We really have known each
other for quite a long time,
haven't we?
I can't believe how slow it is.
It's moving,
but it can't be crawling
any faster than a turtle.
That's true.
Why aren't we using your
robe to get inside from above?
That seems quickest.
Because we'd be far too visible.
We'll have to enter from below,
and start climbing up the walls.
It's the only way.
Hachisu, you'll cut across
with me to the front.
And I'll take care of
any Rain that try to stop us.
Right.
[explosions]
[NAMENBA]
It's begun.
Nothing.
We should head back!
[HACHISU grunts]
You again?
It didn't stop!
No, of course
it wouldn't be so easy.
And the Rain keep coming,
with no end in sight, as usual.
That explosive of yours.
I'm impressed by its firepower.
Is it your creation?
Or perhaps Gorone- dono 's.
What does it matter?
We really don't have the time to
waste talking to you right now!
But still, these
special bombs weren't enough.
Murakumo trudges onward.
So did you just
come here to mock us?
Now, now,
nothing like that at all.
Listen please, it's possible
we could help each other.
They've taken Iga Hibiki,
so naturally,
you're thinking of rescuing her.
[BOTH growl]
I am doing the same,
staging a rescue.
Trying to get Lord Tadanaga
out of there.
If our desires
converge at this point,
there no reason
not to work together.
Shall we?
To start things off,
I'll scale up the
fortress walls.
From there,
I'll work my way inside.
[HACHISU growls]
[HADAEBOU]
As for the two of you,
follow close behind,
and watch my back.
[NAMENBA]
So what?
We're supposed to assist
you until you've wormed
your way inside the castle?
That's right.
Listen, if we help you
get inside for your job,
then you're going to help us
search the whole fortress
for our leader.
Seems like a fair trade to me.
But still. If I may be so bold
as to ask for something more.
I can help. If you would
consider being my woman.
[gasps]
So you've ensnared
an eccentric spy monk.
Good for you.
Hachisu, we're going to help
that smug pervert right now!
Let's go!
[shamisen plays]
[ITARU] ♪ The dice
keeps tumbling 'round, ♪
♪ you live for one more day. ♪
♪ And dream, this fitful dream
but hear me when I say: ♪
♪ The time will come. ♪
♪ When your frail
body rots away. ♪
[shamisen plays]
That's too sad a song
to earn you any coin.
[ITARU] I am not at all
interested in your money.
[HACHIROU] You're with
the Joujinshuu, I take it.
So you cannot remember
my name, young ninja master?
It's Yasha Itaru, don't forget.
Someday soon,
I will have to end your life.
If I don't know your name,
I won't regret it.
My, how very violent.
You seem to be in quite
a hurry to head to the east.
So, you've already
heard the news, have you not?
About the new Murakumo.
Yes.
I shall take you there,
young master.
You have but to
make the request.
And in the blink of an eye.
I can take you into the
Murakumo, should you desire.
I have heard that same
manner of nonsense before.
I refuse.
[ITARU]
You think it's a trap?
Or are you too afraid?
How pathetic.
Since when have you placed your
own survival first, Hachirou?
You refuse to help
your beloved Iga Hibiki?
What did you just say?
[gasps]
This must be the
first you've heard of it!
Hibiki has already fallen into
the hands of the Joujinshuu!
You can't look
away from my mirror.
You want to, but you can't stop
staring at its shiny center.
[ITARU] Your technique
is useless against mine.
It would only
reflect back upon you.
And unless your
intention is to kill yourself,
I wouldn't recommend
using it right now.
But there's no need
for you to worry.
I'll refrain from using
my Destiny's Passage.
I'm under direct orders
from Joujin- sama not to.
However.
I can always change your desire
to refuse me, you know.
Make you easier to work with.
Now, come, Hachirou.
Do you not wish to
save Iga Hibiki from
the dark and dreadful castle?
[OBORO]
Hibiki.
Hibiki!
[OBORO]
Hibiki.
[NARRATOR] The world of man,
is a world of noise and warfare.
But, that young girl, with the
deep sadness that cannot be
concealed by her eyepatch...
You find she almost
never makes a sound.