Come on out!
I know you're here,
so there's no use hiding.
[ITARU]
One's whole world is naught
but the tumbling of the dice.
[ITARU]
They roll and scatter.
A woman?
[ITARU]
One stirs in slumber.
We dub this fitful dream "life."
But death wakes us all.
Well, miss, that was
quite an interesting poem.
Oh, my!
Why give so... generously?
It's only enough
to cover your fare across
the Sanzu River.
Well now,
what an odd thing to say.
Why would I need
to cross the Sanzu River?
[HOUETSU] Your pretty
face doesn't fool me.
I know right away when someone
breaks my root barrier.
It's the impregnable
defense system
of the Five Flowers of Iga.
There's no escape once crossed,
no matter who you are.
So you have
power over the roots?
Then you are the one called
Tsuta Houestsu- sama .
And you're just
a sneaky little fox
looking for the lay of the land.
Your name?
I shall share
my name with you
as a gift before your death.
I am Yasha Itaru.
Stop, you're making me laugh!
I'm not the one who'll be
needing the funerary gift,
thanks, because you're
already as good as dead
and don't even realize it!
Enough talking!
Feel my ninja technique,
Root Lasso!
You're unable to move now.
How unfortunate for you!
I wonder, what are
we going to do with
an interloper like yourself?
Hmm...?
[HOUETSU] After all, killing
someone so pretty too quickly.
[HOUETSU]
That would be a real shame.
[HOUETSU chuckles]
[HOUETSU]
Heh.
[ITARU]
How disgusting.
As a member of
the Five Flowers of Iga,
are you not ashamed
to behave in such a way?
Can you bear to see your
true reflection in the mirror?
The mirror?
[HOUETSU gasps]
[ITARU]
What's wrong?
Did you see your own
pathetic excuse for a life
reflected back into your face?
A meaningless, shallow
existence, devoid of any joy.
And self-loathing
masquerading as pride.
--[HOUETSU whimpers]
--I understand that.
The despair that
makes you long for death.
[HOUETSU whimpers]
[ITARU]
If that's the case...
[HOUETSU whimpers]
[ITARU chuckles]
[HOUETSU wails]
[ITARU] ...fall from this cliff,
and meet your end!
[ITARU] Once you've
stared into my mirror,
you will have borne witness to
the absolute futility of life.
No one can escape the gasp of
my Destiny's Passage technique.
[JOUJIN]
Suruga- sama .
Do you really not
remember me, my lord?
[TADANAGA whimpers]
[JOUJIN] Of course, it has been
many years since we first met.
When you were still but a child,
as was your elder brother,
Lord Iemitsu, who was
stricken down with
a debilitating case of the pox.
When your father
summoned the great priest
Tenkai to say prayers
for your brother,
I accompanied him,
as part of his retinue.
[TADANAGA]
That's right.
I remember being there.
Watching him.
I was just a boy back then.
Why would you seek me out now
with these wild allegations?
[JOUJIN]
You misunderstand, my lord.
Those word are my regurgitation
of what I heard you say yourself
on that occaision.
Is that so?
What did you hear me say?
[JOUJIN] "Someday, my brother
will see me as a threat
to his reign, and will use
his power to slay me,"
my lord.
[TADANAGA]
Stop! That's enough!
You're speaking utter nonsense!
You lie...
I would never say such things!
[JOUJIN]
Magoroku.
[MAGOROKU]
Sir.
[TADANAGA gasps]
I am Kujaku Tsuibamu,
Your Highness.
And I am Rinne
Magoroku, Suruga- sama .
[JOUJIN]
We've no choice.
Begin your technique, Magoroku.
[MAGOROKU] Are you certain
of that, Joujin- sama ?
[JOUJIN]
You heard me.
The past is cloudy,
and Suruga- sama needs
our help remembering it.
[MAGOROKU]
As you wish.
[TADANAGA whimpers]
Nobo akyasha kyarabaya.
Nobo akyasha kyarabaya
On arikya mari bori sowaka.
What is this place?
[JOUJIN] What Rinne Magoroku
has manifested here for us
is known as Akyashagaruba.
We're in the ethereal realm
of Kokuzo Bosatsu.
[KUJAKU] The original meaning
of the word "akyasha"
was translated as "void",
and "garuba" meant "womb."
To describe it other words,
the source from which
everything is born.
One could even say that
Kokuzo Bosatsu himself, is as
infinite as the ever yawning
expanse of the great void.
This is his own universe.
This is his own spacetime.
His universe?
Behold the raw scope of
Rinne Magoroku's finest talent.
His manifestation
of Kokuzo Bosatsu.
He calls it the
Adamantite Tower.
[RUI]
A question for me?
[SHICHIGEN]
Yes.
I was wondering...
How much do you know about men?
[RUI]
What do I know?
Men are brutish,
selfish, and they stink.
No, that isn't what I meant.
I want you to tell me how much
you know about men's bodies.
[growls]
What're you asking me?
[SHICHIGEN]
It's about our skills.
Your talents and mine
are very similar.
I heard your technique
involves summoning insects.
[SHICHIGEN]
That's one element.
You've heard that this power
goes well beyond that.
Haven't you?
This same power, when honed,
lets me seduce women
to do my will.
And your skill means
that you could...
[RUI] Well, you don't know
anything about women.
So keep practicing.
[SHICHIGEN]
No.
I'm not really that interested
in girls, frankly.
[KAREHA]
Houetsu!
Shuugetsu. Izuma.
Have you found him?
I haven't, but I know
I heard him scream.
[KAREHA]
No, that's impossible!
He couldn't have been
defeated so quickly.
Find him!
[gasps]
[NEIRICHIOU] Perhaps
I could be of assistance.
Is this the man you
gentlemen are looking for?
[NEIRICHIOU]
Am I mistaken?
Or can you not tell?
I can understand why.
Everyone's face contorts
in horror, after being
struck by Yasha Itaru's
Destiny Passage Technique.
[KAREHA]
Houetsu!
[SHUUGETSU gasps]
The hell are you?
I demand your name!
[NEIRICHIOU]
You wish to know my name?
It's a difficult one for
some to remember.
I'm Neirichiou.
[SHUUGETSU]
Neirichiou? I won't forget that.
But, I only need to hold
onto it for a short while.
Actually, just long
enough for me
to etch it into your gravestone.
What a compassionate
thing to do!
Offering to dig a grave
for an old man,
and etch a gravestone
in his memory.
But before we get to that,
you'll have to defeat
my associate here.
[GROUP gasps]
[TADANAGA whimpers]
[KUJAKU] I do hope
you're not feeling poorly.
Suruga Dainagon- sama .
I've just become
dizzy all of a sudden.
Try to bear it
for a bit longer, my lord.
You'll get used to it soon.
Get used to what?
What's happening here?
You're sensing us
traveling through
the flow of time.
[gasps]
[KUJAKU] You are moving now,
though not from one space
to another,
but through time itself.
You are walking backwards,
retracing the
pathways of the past.
The past?
What are you talking about?
For many years now,
you have envisioned
your demise by your
brother's hand.
We are revisiting
the moment this thought
first occurred to you.
The first time you
sensed his malice,
and realized the threat
to your own future.
[KUJAKU] My personal skill,
the Inverted Halberd of Time,
allows me to turn the gears
of time backwards at a whim.
If the sands of time
in my hourglass were scattered,
there's no telling
how far we'd be able to go.
[gasps]
[JOUJIN]
Don't worry.
As long as the sands of time
are contained within,
he can only travel back
a short distance.
Moreover, the focused
power of this place is acting
as a magnifier, taking us
further back in the timeline
than we could outside of it.
Pure madness.
[KUJAKU] Ah, it appears that
we have journeyed back
to the correct point in time.
[TADANAGA]
Brother!
This is from when
we were children.
Are you trying to
trick me with illusions?
[JOUJIN]
It is no illusion, my lord.
This is your memory.
You remember it
because you were there.
You're witnessing the time when
your brother, the future shogun,
was a young boy
afflicted with the pox.
[TADANAGA]
Wait, is that me?
[JOUJIN]
Suruga- sama .
[TADANAGA gasps]
[KUNICHIYO gasps]
[TADANAGA]
Yes. I remember this.
I thought it was strange, that
there were no attendants around.
It was just me there,
alone with him.
[TAKECHIYO rasps]
[KUNICHIYO]
Brother, it's me.
How are you feeling?
Does it hurt?
Takechiyo, are you all right?
I wish I could help.
Just bear with it for a moment.
I'm going to find the doctor.
[TAKECHIYO rasps]
[KUNICHIYO whimpers]
[TADANAGA breathes shakily]
[TADANAGA]
We're back...
Then that was all just a dream?
[JOUJIN]
No. It was no dream, my lord.
[TADANAGA gasps]
[JOUJIN] Indeed. Everything
that just happened was real.
You witnessed it all
with your own two eyes.
The child Takechiyo,
now Iemitsu- sama ,
has never forgotten that moment.
When he, the child
destined to be the next leader
was lying helpless
at death's door,
you were at his bedside.
The very picture of vitality.
[TADANAGA whimpers]
[JOUJIN] The harsh feelings
your older brother began
harboring toward you,
they were rooted in
the same bitter jealousy
the sick and infirm have
for the wealth and insouciance
of the able-bodied.
[JOUJIN]
That is impossible to change.
I was... just a boy.
The only thing I cared about
back then was praying for
the swiftness of
my brother's recovery.
[JOUJIN] I'm afraid
your personal thoughts
on the matter are irrelevant.
What's of most consequence,
was the look on your
face at the time.
In your healthy visage,
your brother saw in you
the joy and ambition of the
one who would replace him as
the next shogun of the
Tokugawa line.
[TADANAGA]
That's not true!
[JOUJIN]
You just witnessed it yourself,
did you not, Suruga- sama ?
[TADANAGA whimpers]
[rasps]
[TADANAGA]
No. Even if that were true,
if my brother
really thought that,
even for the briefest moment...
...that should all
be far behind us now!
It's crazy!
There's no need for him to
be jealous of me now--
He's the shogun!
[JOUJIN] Then can you think
of a more plausible reason
for the Kurokuwa to have
hunted you down like that?
[TADANAGA gasps]
[JOUJIN] The Kurokuwa of Iga
aren't some roving bandits.
Rather, they work directly for
the will of the Shogunate.
So the question
then becomes "why did they
act against the will of
the Suruga Dainagon?"
[TADANAGA]
Against me...
[JOUJIN]
Yes!
You yourself had serious doubts
about what this would mean
for you in the end, and
you choked back the words
that began to surface from
the depths of your heart.
That dark thought:
"Has my own brother
sent them here to kill me?"
[TADANAGA gasps]
Tha-That's enough! Silence!
[JOUJIN]
One need only to listen.
Your tone of voice
tells me I'm right.
[TADANAGA whimpers]
[JOUJIN] But then, you've come
to realize this yourself,
haven't you, my lord?
You brother's jealousy
still resides within him!
And he will do what
he must to be rid of it!
He can't.
No, he wouldn't dare!
[JOUJIN] Resolve yourself
instead to rebellion!
[TADANAGA]
What?
[JOUJIN]
Rebellion, my lord!
[JOUJIN] There is no
other option available if you
wish to survive your
brother's petulant wrath.
This I swear to you.
[HACHIROU]
Joujinshuu...
Is this the name of
the group Gei'in and the others
lost their lives
fighting against?
We're starting to get
close to the Iga village.
[RUI gasps]
What's wrong?
[RUI]
Blood?
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
Rui!
I see. It's over here, too.
[RUI whimpers]
Are these remains
the Five Flowers of Iga?
Let us pray dearly
that it not be the case.
[JOUJIN]
Suruga- sama .
Unless the forest
itself is moved,
then failure is impossible.
[TADANAGA]
What's that?
[JOUJIN] I once heard
a similar story from
the barbarians
several years ago.
And so, in accordance
with the story,
I shall make your lordship
the same promise.
[TADANAGA]
Oh? Really?
What nonsense
are you spewing now?
Who can make the trees
unfix their buried roots?
[JOUJIN]
Indeed. It is impossible.
And that is why I say that
this rebellion cannot fail.
As long as the forest doesn't
suddenly decide to migrate,
then you have nothing to fear...
...Suruga- sama .
[TADANAGA gasps]
[JOUJIN] Become the god
you were destined to be!
[JOUJIN] Ah, yes. It would
seem they have returned.
[TADANAGA gasps]
Who are these men?
[JOUJIN]
Shogyou Kareha.
Tsuta Houetsu.
Irootoroe Izuma.
And lastly, Suiren Shuugetsu.
With these four trophies,
we have eliminated the bulk
of the Five Flowers of Iga!
Is that so? Who's responsible?
[ITARU]
My name is Yasha Itaru, my lord.
[gasps]
[JOUJIN]
Now, only two remain.
Which two? What do you mean?
The leader of the
Five Treasures of Kouga
who is Kouga Hachirou,
and the leader of the
Five Flowers of Iga
called Iga Hibiki.
But why would you
want to assassinate them?
I cannot imagine a
better way to demonstrate
the magnitude of our
power, Suruga- sama .
One more thing.
[JOUJIN] We acted out of the
desire to help your mother
survive however we could.
She deserves as much.
You would even save my mother?
What are you suggesting?
[SHIKIBU]
I don't like pain.
I wonder if it hurts
when you die...
I hate it. All the aching.
[SHIKIBU]
Death scares me.
Just don't think about it.
[SHIKIBU]
But...
If it was for Hachirou...
Then you would die?
Yeah...
What if you had
to do it for her?
You willing to die for Hibiki?
Would I die for her sake?
No way in hell,
but I would do it for us.
Because we need
Hachirou and Hibiki,
and we will need their
magic to survive.
Without their blood,
our clans are through.
[gasps]
Utsutsu.
Utsutsu!
[grunts]
[UTSUTSU]
What are you hollering about?
[SAIZOU]
Look up. Look at the sky.
What? The sky?
What exactly am I looking for?
[SAIZOU]
You mean you can't see it?
Are your eye sockets empty?
No need to be rude!
Besides, you're one to talk!
[SAIZOU]
They're here.
No...! It can't be...
What is that...?
[NARRATOR]
Here comes Neirichiou,
one of the Joujinshuu.
His skill overwhelms the
young ninjas-in-training.
Adding insult to injury.
And in the face of Joujin,
will the well of power
within Hachirou begin
to lose its meaning?