[BOTH gasp]
[HADAEBOU]
You don't believe me, my lord?
It's true.
Your brother shared with me,
a man of low station,
his happy memories
from childhood,
of spending time with you,
his beloved younger brother.
[JOUJIN]
Enough, deceiver.
You should know
better than to lie
in the presence of nobility.
It's just preposterous.
The shogun would
never be so sentimental.
What's this?
[JOUJIN] It's entirely likely
that this snake in the grass
is simply repeating
the stories his Master
told him to memorize.
[TADANAGA] But the things
he said, they were all true.
And Tenkai wasn't
there to witness.
It was only my brother and I.
When were you and
your brother truly left alone
during your childhood?
Were there no
courtesans, or servants?
Men of your station are rarely,
if ever, by themselves.
So you've come, then.
Hachirou.
Shichigen!
Joujin.
I request you give me
some more time.
I'd like an opportunity to think
about the matter in full.
[JOUJIN] Hmph. Even now,
you would reconsider,
after all that's transpired?
Yes.
Let's go, Hadaebou.
Lord.
[MAGOROKU]
It won't be that simple.
I shall take your life
before you leave here.
What?
What did you just say?
Is this some joke in poor taste?
Didn't you give me your
word you'd take me to Edo
as the master of this castle?
[JOUJIN]
I did promise to take you.
But you, your lordship,
were never the master
we had planned for Murakumo.
But if you never wanted me,
then who was this for?
[HADAEBOU sighs]
I knew it.
His name is known to us all.
Oda Kazusanosuke
Nobunaga- sama ,
the Demon King.
[TADANAGA]
It can't be!
[NEIRICHIOU]
Kouga Hachirou.
I heard that Yasha Itaru
made you an offer
and you refused her.
Now. There's no need
to be so stubborn, boy.
It's clear who the victor
would be in this battle.
Come to Murakumo and
hear Joujin out instead,
I'd be glad to take you there.
I don't need you to take me!
I'll come save Hibiki myself!
[JOUJIN]
Hmph.
Wait, what're you planning?
This country needs
leadership, and you, my lord,
will act as our vessel
for this purpose.
--[gasps]
--You must be joking.
The matter is far too
serious for me to jest about.
As I said, we need
you to serve as our vessel.
To revive Nobunaga,
we must provide him
with an adequate body.
[MAGOROKU yells]
[HADAEBOU grunts]
[TADANAGA yells]
We cannot use
the body of a normal man,
it would not suffice for the
task of his reincarnation.
We require
the bloodline of a ruler,
the only ones able to
hold the magnitude of
the Demon King's spirit.
You carry the blood
of a great ruler in your veins.
You are of slightly
poorer quality, but alas,
that can't be helped.
We tried to find other
suitable host bodies,
but none of the other candidates
were so easily deceived.
You...
You bastard.
Then, I don't need
to ask for your permission.
I shall leave of
my own free will!
I'll have my revenge.
I shall return home
to my brother,
and together we'll come
back and finish you!
A wise choice, Tadanaga- sama .
I will hold them off. Now go!
[JOUJIN chuckles]
[HADAEBOU grunts]
No. You won't take him.
--[slashing]
--[groans]
[HADAEBOU gasps]
[HADAEBOU whimpers]
What?
[NEIRICHIOU] Now,
your Spearing Eye technique
will have no effect whatsoever.
Hachirou, what now?
[growls]
[laughs] I'll keep my
eyes closed, and you assume
that means I won't be
able to see anything?
But that is not the case.
[NEIRICHIOU] This Lightning
Deity lives within the space
between the real and the unreal,
bridging both worlds.
[NEIRICHIOU]
And by fusing with it,
I have developed
the same ability.
I need not use my
real eyes to see you,
when I can watch your every
move from the realm of spirits.
[HADAEBOU]
Tadanaga- sama ...
Why...?
[HADAEBOU groans]
Wait, what happened?
Hadaebou. I'm sorry.
[TADANAGA]
Prepare to die!
[TADANAGA grunts]
[TADANAGA gasps]
What is that?
[JOUJIN]
It is a fan, your lordship.
For you to use
to commit seppuku.
[JOUJIN] Simply beheading
you is unacceptable,
especially for a man
of your position.
Nor would it be fitting
to cause bodily harm to
the Dainagon of Suruga.
Thus, the least we can
do is offer you one last chance
to reclaim your lost honor
by using this fan,
and dying as a samurai.
Tadanaga- sama , die a man.
[TADANAGA]
I've been such a naïve fool!
[JOUJIN] Suruga- sama , unless
the forest itself is moved,
then failure
is impossible:
[TADANAGA]
What's that?
Oh? Really?
What nonsense are
you spewing now?
Who can make the trees
unfix their buried roots?
Indeed, it's impossible.
And that is why I say that
this rebellion cannot fail.
As long as the forest doesn't
suddenly decide to migrate,
then you have nothing to fear.
[JOUJIN]
Suruga- sama .
[gasps]
[JOUJIN] Become the god
you were destined to be!
[TADANAGA] At last,
we're finally going to Edo.
To Chiyoda Castle.
[TADANAGA]
Damn you, Joujin!
Even in death,
I will not forget this hatred!
You may take my head,
but my soul will remain
within my flesh and bones,
cursing your treachery forever!
[TADANAGA] One day,
you'll discover that
I'm no mere puppet.
I'm a direct descendent
of the Divine Lord Ieyasu!
[TADANAGA]
Though you may kill me,
your plan shall fall to ruin!
I will make you fail!
I will have my vengeance!
[TADANAGA]
Prepare to die, Joujin!
My name is Tokugawa Tadanaga!
I will make sure
you never forget it!
I know that autumn,
can be a painful season.
I shall not tire of the
sound of the bell crickets.
[gasps]
[HADAEBOU grunts]
What would you have me do?
Ignore him.
[HADAEBOU]
Suruga- sama .
Lord...
[NEIRICHIOU screams]
Vile pests!
[NEIRICHIOU groans]
Shichigen. You did it!
[SHICHIGEN grunts]
Not quite.
[NEIRICHIOU giggles] It seems
I underestimated you,
but that was very impressive.
You had best
prepare yourselves though.
That little stunt of yours has
awoken the wrath of the Raijin.
[SHICHIGEN gasps]
[NEIRICHIOU]
Hmm. Now, what do we have here?
It's Gorone!
Idiot!
[grunts]
[growls, yells]
[GORONE]
Well?
I've fought with the tenacity
of ten men, haven't I?
[NAMENBA]
Why?
Why do something so reckless?
I thought you hated bravado.
[GORONE] Hachirou, always
be true to your feelings.
[GORONE]
All men die, one day.
That's the order of nature.
The budding flowers
can bloom only after
the old ones have fallen.
[GORONE]
As it was meant to be.
[NEIRICHIOU screams]
[RAIJIN roars]
[NEIRICHIOU]
I've failed.
Everyone, please listen.
What I want is to save Hibiki.
[HACHIROU]
It might be a trap.
No, I'm sure it will be.
But I shall enter that castle
one way or another!
[SAIZOU] So you've finally
admitted the truth.
Though, if we're to continue,
there's one more thing
you have to say.
Right, we've all
been waiting to hear it
directly from our leader.
What do you command?
[HACHIROU]
Their destiny is to fall,
but the sakura blossoms
will always return.
So, my friends. Join me.
The time has come
for us to fall!
[HACHIROU] Joujin!
Open the doors to Murakumo!
[HACHIROU] Kouga Hachirou,
has at last arrived!
[NARRATOR] As long as Saizou's
eyeball hovers near the ceiling,
you can't hope to best me,
no matter how hard you try.
Well, everyone?
Let's have some fun.
What do you say?