[NARRATOR] On the outside,
we look the same,
and yet, men call us monsters.
We are naught but shadows
lurking in between eras,
but if we are
destined to perish,
then I shall fall with the
cherry blossoms.
Yes. I shall fall with
the cherry blossoms.
[NOBUNAGA, chanting] Fifty years
of a mortal man's life...
...pass by in the breadth
of a vivid dream.
When held 'gainst
the scope of heaven's history.
For once a man is born...
...as with all things
in this world...
...mustn't he one day die?
[KAZUSANOSUKE]
Indeed, he must.
[MAN A]
Kazusanosuke- sama .
Nobunaga- sama .
[KAZUSANOSUKE]
Who goes there?
Have you come
to take me to Hell?
[NOBUNAGA]
There's no hurry.
[MAN A]
Does it not frustrate you, then?
Frustrate...
[MAN A] Does dying here,
with your greatest desire
yet unfulfilled
not tear at your very soul?
That is my destiny.
[MAN A] And if it were possible
to change your destiny
from this, would you do it?
[KAZUSANOSUKE]
What do you mean?
[MAN A] You need only ask, and
I will insure that this is not
where your glorious fate
comes to an end.
[gasps]
[NARRATOR] Iemitsu, the third
shogun of the Tokugawa.
He and his brother, Tadanaga,
shared a rivalry still
spoken of to this day.
But behind the curtain
of the struggle
for succession that
began their feud,
the Iga and Kouga ninja clans
were forced to fight,
and death swept
through like the wind.
However, what occurred has been
shrouded in darkness.
Some dismiss this
clash as mere legend.
But in their wake,
they left animosity and
bloodshed as their legacy.
[SOLDIER B]
Open the gate!
Close the gate!
Shut it tight!
[MAN B]
Godspeed, Tadanaga- sama .
The journey will be perilous,
and I pray for a safe return.
[MAN C] But still, even if
the wife of the last shogun
is dying, the way
our lord panicked...
[OLD MAN A]
I understand his concern.
Not only is she the mother
of our lord and the wife
of the last shogun, but also
the only remaining ally
Tadanaga- sama
has left at Edo Castle.
Please, Mother!
Try to hang on just
a little while longer!
Your beloved son,
Tadanaga, is on the way!
[HIBIKI gasps]
[RUI gasps]
[RUI grunts, rasps]
[gasps]
[SHICHIGEN gasps]
[RUI grunts]
[SHIKIBU pants]
[SHIKIBU grunts]
[SHIKIBU]
Hmph.
[SHIKIBU yells]
[SHIKIBU rasps]
[gasps]
[HACHISU gasps]
[HACHISU grunts]
[gasps]
[UTSUSU grunts]
[SAIZOU]
No use trying that.
You may fool the others with
your illusions, but not me.
That's because my eyes...
watch us from above.
[gasps]
I'll go easy on you.
Give up right now
and you won't get hurt.
[UTSUSU gasps]
[SAIZOU]
Otherwise...
...I'll snap your arm.
[UTSUSU]
You can go to Hell.
An Iga ninja would rather
rip her tongue out
than concede to a filthy Kouga!
That sounds like a great idea
to me, if it shuts up you Iga.
You know what they say, though.
It was actually the Kouga who
won the war between the clans.
But then, the Iga told
lies to try to save face!
You're the only person
dumb enough to believe that.
You Kouga are pathetic
excuses for ninjas.
[UTSUSU] Refusing to
admit when you've failed
means you can't learn.
[SAIZOU rasps]
[UTSUSU] That's what
you get for gloating.
[SAIZOU growls]
You're gonna pay
for that, Iga bitch!
[NAMENBA]
Will I?
[SAIZOU gasps]
Or were you talking to
a different "Iga bitch"?
Namenba...
--[bone cracks]
--[SAIZOU groans]
Let this pain
serve as a reminder.
You shouldn't push your luck
going on about the clans.
Heh. I win yet again.
But it's getting so boring.
Way too easy for me.
[KAZUMA]
No.
[KAZUMA] This is not
the sound I wanted to hear.
Kazuma- sama ?
He's always so damn serious
about everything he does.
Maybe I can have
a little fun with him!
[KAZUMA grunts]
--[UTSUSU screams]
--No!
--[UTSUSU rasps]
--[KAZUMA] Don't struggle.
If you do, your head
might pop right off.
Or is that your wish?
Do you long to hear
the dulcet tones
of Heaven's lyre when you die?
[UTSUSU rasps]
[NAMENBA]
Kazuma- sama , please stop!
I don't know what
she's done to offend,
but I beg you to forgive her!
I can't.
This one underestimates what
it truly means to be a ninja.
They all make a mockery of it.
Have some mercy,
they're only children.
[KAZUMA] Which is why
she must be punished.
Unless they get a lesson in
true suffering at least once,
they'll never change their ways.
Let them see the blood
of their companion and learn.
[HACHIROU]
Knock it off, Kazuma.
Hachirou...
That's quite enough.
[KAZUMA growls]
[gasps]
Please, no.
[GEI'IN] What has you
so unsettled, Kazuma?
A man as knowledgeable
as yourself wouldn't be
so foolish as to confront
our clan's leader.
You jest, Gei'in- dono .
Why would I choose to fight him?
Could it be possible
that you've forgotten
how powerful and terrifying
Hachirou's eye magic can be?
Please be lenient
with him, Hachirou- dono .
He may be bull-headed,
but means no disrespect.
Strengthening his
abilities is the only thing
that drives him, but that
single-minded nature
is his greatest flaw.
You speak the truth, Gei'in.
[TENSHIN] Our young leader is
quite a handful, is he not?
He does nothing but
play with those whose skills
are not yet fully developed.
Don't say such things,
Tenshin and Kasou.
We must exercise patience,
for Lord Hachirou
is still but a child.
Those two are crucial to us.
For our future.
[KAZUMA]
Those two?
[GEI'IN] The blood that flows
within Hachirou and Hibiki
are from lineages that
must not come to an end.
They must continue
those bloodlines,
whether they like it or not.
[KASOU] Even when that requires
a brother to bed his sister?
You should know
better than to ask.
[GEI'IN]
To keep the line alive,
we would force
a parent to bed their child.
Without a new generation
of superior ninja,
both the Kouga and Iga clans
would be finished.
This is Hachirou
and Hibiki's birthright.
They should both be
well aware of this by now.
[KASOU]
A message?
[TENSHIN]
The wife of the last shogun--
her health is failing.
[KAZUMA]
Suruga- sama 's mother?
[TENSHIN] It says he left
by horseback last night.
[TADANAGA pants]
[SOLDIER C] My lord!
It's getting too dangerous!
We need to seek out shelter!
[TADANAGA pants]
I told you, I don't care!
Even if I risk being
struck by lightning.
I must go!
I will be by my mother's side!
[HIBIKI giggles]
[gasps]
Hachirou!
[HACHIROU]
Your sandals.
Aren't you cold?
[HIBIKI]
I'm fine!
A cherry blossom?
[HACHIROU] Hmm? Well,
I did just cut a branch off
of the Tenzen cherry tree.
[HIBIKI]
Mm! That's awful!
It was a branch,
trees lose them all the time.
Plus, the Tenzen tree is
immortal, so it's gonna be fine.
That's just a silly old legend!
They say that one
of those dirt mounds next
to the tree belongs to the great
Yakushiji Tenzen- sama .
but an "immortal" ninja wouldn't
have a grave, would he?
Maybe not.
[NAMENBA]
Are you in there, Gorone?
I'm coming in.
Is that Shikibu's?
[GORONE]
It is.
I'm tinkering with his Saibougu.
[NAMENBA] Hachisu wanted
to know if it was possible
to fire off multiple
rounds at once.
Multiple rounds?
It takes too long
between firing a round,
and following it up
with another shot.
Now that's an interesting idea.
Have you seen
what's going on
between Hachirou and Hibiki?
Sparks are flying.
I can hear excitement
in your voice.
Uh. [chuckles] Well, of course,
because it's wonderful news!
And besides,
I'm not the only one.
The whole village wants those
two to love each other.
[GORONE]
I suppose you're right.
What? That doesn't
make you happy, Gorone?
[GORONE] Could you fetch
the helmet back there for me?
[GORONE] Trying to improve
the head's field of motion
makes the neck more vulnerable.
This one right over here?
[GORONE]
Hmm. That's it.
--Tell me.
--[GORONE] Hmm?
Aren't you happy?
I haven't forgotten our duty,
and I know that you haven't.
After all, you and I--
[GORONE]
We're the ones responsible
for watching over
them as they grow.
Right.
It all sounds fine in theory,
but you're also trying
to justify bringing
those two together,
no matter what the cost.
[sighs] Why do you insist on
being so dramatic all the time?
What's wrong, you don't approve?
[GORONE gasps]
Let me.
Thank you.
[NAMENBA sighs]
[TADANAGA]
Where are the carriers?!
We need them to take
us across the river!
[SOLDIER E] My lord. I think
they've already gone home.
Then call them back!
I don't care how much
we have to pay!
[SOLDIER E]
Even with their assistance,
we would be ill-advised to
attempt crossing the river
in such a heavy
downpour, my lord.
[TADANAGA] You are not in any
position to refuse my command!
Have you forgotten that
I'm the Dainagon of Suruga?
[TADANAGA]
Do something other than snivel!
I know! A ship.
Is there a ship?
[SOLDIER F]
My lord!
[SOLDIER E]
Lord Tadanaga, wait!
[TADANAGA]
Halt!
I found one.
Praise be unto mighty Hachiman!
At last I have the chance to
make it to my ailing mother
without any further delay!
[SOLDIER F]
My lord.
You don't actually plan to
cross in this boat, do you?
[TADANAGA]
Of course!
We haven't another moment
to lose, so make haste.
Which of you can pilot a boat?
Since all of you have
become such pathetic cowards.
I shall take it across myself!
[TADANAGA] Now, men,
push the boat into the river!
[SOLDIER D] My lord,
we don't know what's waiting
--on the other side--
--[blade slashes]
[SOLDIER E]
What the hell?
[gasps]
Attackers!
Draw your swords!
[SOLDIERS groan]
[SOLDIER G rasps]
[TADANAGA whimpers]
[MAN D] With all due respect,
I'd like to ask a question.
[TADANAGA grunts]
[MAN D]
Forgive my boldness,
but you are the Dainagon
of Suruga, are you not?
Bastard! You slaughter my men
and beg for my title?
Who are you?
I demand to know your name!
[MAN D] Apologies,
but we men of low birth
haven't a name worthy of
sharing with our betters.
Especially the sons of
powerful men, like shoguns.
What's that?
Please allow me
to share a little advice.
Simply put, Suruga- sama ,
a man like you trying to take
that boat across the river
goes against the natural order.
What I mean is,
you're out of place,
like a dog trying to replace a
cat as a catcher of rats.
You would dare to call me a dog?
[MAN D]
No, sire.
It was just an example
to help illustrate my point.
Hold your tongue!
[yells]
[MAN D]
"My blade...
That strike should have
sliced right through
the overly-familiar bastard."
[TADANAGA growls]
[MAN D] That is what
you thought, is it not?
Indeed, under
most circumstances,
I would have been
slain just now.
Heh.
[TADANAGA yells]
How did I miss you?
[MAN D]
I sense your disappointment,
but this is not due
to any lack of mastery
you have with the blade.
It wouldn't matter
if your lordship were
the greatest swordsman
currently living.
You could not hope to
touch your steel to my skin,
no matter how you try.
[MAN D]
It's true.
Due to my unique
physical abilities,
the blade naturally avoids
making any sort of contact
with me, therefore, it is truly
not your shortcoming, sire.
This is the ninja
technique "Ukigumo,"
also known as
the Floating Cloud.
So then...
...you are a ninja.
[KAZUMA]
Indeed.
However, not an
impressive one, I assure you.
[KAZUMA]
If I were being charitable,
I'd say he was... below average.
It's you, Kazuma!
Worry not, my lord.
The Five Treasures of
Kouga are here to serve.
[NARRATOR] The leader of
the Five Treasures of Kouga--
Kouga Hachirou.
The leader of
the Five Flowers of Iga--
Iga Hibiki.
An innocent
brother and sister,
lighting the way forward for
those who lurk in the shadows.