[GORONE] The fortress of
Murakumo is surrounded
on every side by ninja
soldiers called the Rain.
[GORONE]
And here's the plan.
Shichigen and Rui will go
around to the opposite side,
and draw them away.
The guards distracted,
Saizou, Utsutsu,
and Shikibu will move in
and take out the
Murakumo's cannons.
They'll throw explosives
into the cannon ports.
So if it works...
[NAMENBA]
Hachirou is here?
Yes. He rescued
me in the forest.
Well, I didn't run
into him, but if you say so.
I believe she did.
Hibiki, do you want
to go along with them?
[HIBIKI exhales]
They've already come here once.
So if you want my opinion,
the mission would be safer.
Hachisu, be sure
to bring Gorouza.
Are you certain of that?
[GORONE]
She raises a valid point.
We can't afford to make the
assumption that it's safe here.
We'll use everything
we have at our disposal.
[GORONE] Once the new
Saibougu is tuned up, we leave.
--[BOYS laughing]
--[BOY C] Wait!
[BOY A gasps]
Time for us to
move on, Shichigen.
We have to make
our way there soon.
[SHICHIGEN'S MOTHER]
Before autumn comes to an end.
How many?
Seven... Eight... Nine...
There's ten of them,
at the very least.
Let's go.
Just as planned.
We'll draw the Rain
around to the back.
If it works,
I'll give the signal.
Until then...
[SAIZOU]
I understand.
Shikibu, that sutra
about the rhinoceros
continues beyond what
I've heard you quoting.
[GORONE] "For a sociable person,
there comes affection.
Following on the heels of
this affection, comes pain.
Seeing the perils such
affections hold over oneself,
instead, wander
alone, like a rhinoceros.
Does that mean...?
[GORONE]
Hmph. The note rings true.
Do you hear it?
It's almost as if
it's referring to the Ouka.
[GORONE]
That technique.
If the two of you were
able to create it,
considering how far
you've both advanced,
you and Hachirou could
change its very nature.
[GORONE] If loving each other,
and caring for one another
were the basis for a powerful
new ninja technique,
then perhaps the Ouka
will bring more
than misery into the world.
[SHICHIGEN]
Can we reach them at this range?
[RUI] Fortunately, we're upwind
of their position.
Should be fine.
[SHICHIGEN] Use your technique
and fall back immediately.
Then I'll take over.
[RUI]
Right.
[SHICHIGEN pants]
[gasps]
[SHICHIGEN]
Gunfire...?
The Rain have riflemen?
The ones who attacked us,
they must have been decoys.
The plan was for
us to lure them out.
Instead, they lured us in.
But the gunpowder...
I couldn't smell it.
[SHICHIGEN] That's why they
were waiting for us downwind.
We can't count
on Saizou's eyes either.
I had no idea the Rain
were even there.
Your leg!
[SHICHIGEN] Yes, they got
me in the left thigh.
Though I know...
I know that autumn
can be a painful season.
[SHICHIGEN] I shall not tire of
the sound--of the bell crickets.
[SHICHIGEN]
I'll need your help to walk.
Hurry.
[SHICHIGEN]
Did they leave?
[RUI]
I think.
[SHICHIGEN groans]
You okay?
[SHICHIGEN]
The bullet went clean through.
Missed the bone.
[SHICHIGEN'S MOTHER]
Namu Kanzeon bosatsu .
I hear you praying to Kanzeon.
How will she help us?
[SHICHIGEN'S MOTHER]
I asked her to watch over us
on our journey, and more.
Like what?
[SHICHIGEN'S MOTHER]
I prayed that autumn
would never come to an end.
[SHICHIGEN gasps]
[SHICHIGEN'S MOTHER]
Are you cold, my darling?
[SHICHIGEN]
No.
[SHICHIGEN'S MOTHER]
Oh, really?
I can feel you shivering.
[SHICHIGEN]
I'm fine.
I'm Shichigen, son of a samurai.
[SHICHIGEN'S MOTHER chuckles]
Of course.
[SHICHIGEN'S MOTHER] I know that
autumn can be a painful season.
I shall not tire of the sound
of the bell crickets.
[SHICHIGEN] You really love
that poem, don't you, mother?
[SHICHIGEN'S MOTHER]
I suppose I do.
We're traveling to the lands
of the Kouga.
A friend of your father's
is staying with them
through the season.
This man has connections within
the Daimyo's court in Kishuu.
And if we can meet with him
before he leaves,
you could be an officer someday.
[SHICHIGEN laughs]
[insects chirping]
Look what I can do!
Just listen. Shhh...
[chirping grows quiet]
[silence]
They've all fallen silent.
Very impressive.
[chirping resumes]
No. I failed...
I was trying to keep them quiet
for a lot longer than that.
It seems like it worked to me.
To be able to do something
like that, even for a second.
Perhaps it comes from
your father's bloodline.
You're so much like him,
in many ways.
How do you mean?
Can he control bugs?
[gasps]
It's fallen quiet again.
Now what?
No one ever said anything
about them having firepower.
[HIBIKI]
Let's hurry, Shikibu.
[SHIKIBU]
Of course.
Well? You see anything?
[SAIZOU]
Nothing's moving anywhere.
So what could those
fires we saw have been?
Are Rui and Shichigen all right?
[SAIZOU]
Would you calm down?
Wait for the signal.
[UTSUTSU growls]
--[SHICHIGEN'S MOTHER grunts]
--[MAN A growls]
[SHICHIGEN gasps]
[yells]
[MAN A gasps]
[MAN A growls]
[SHICHIGEN yelps, grunts]
That oughta teach you.
[SHICHIGEN'S MOTHER]
Shichigen!
[MAN A yells]
Stupid kid!
I'm through holding back!
[growls]
[SHICHIGEN'S MOTHER] You should
be more lenient with children,
you know.
Please, forgive his behavior.
Forgive? The hell are you?
Merely a mother traveling
the countryside with
her little boy.
Very well.
[yells]
[gasps]
[SHICHIGEN]
I know the truth now.
My father was a ninja.
What? Did you just
have a dream or something?
You were unconscious.
I guess so.
Besides.
I heard you were from
a samurai family.
That was what my mother told me.
Let's go.
Right.
[SHICHIGEN] The way she fought,
those were ninja techniques.
She used them fighting
for me that day.
[SHICHIGEN] But in the end, all
I could do was get in her way.
[SHICHIGEN]
Get down!
[RUI]
An ambush?
[SHICHIGEN] So it would seem,
but that's perfect.
Because that means
they're focusing
all of their attention on us,
and so Saizou's group
has gone unnoticed.
We've done
what we set out to do.
How can you act
so calm right now?
They remain upwind,
even though they know we
can smell their gunpowder,
but they won't charge us.
They're too worried
about your technique to try it.
So they'll keep their distance.
We can't rely on
your butterflies.
But I can buy
you some time, at least.
While I do, run!
[RUI gasps]
Shichigen!
[SHICHIGEN] I refuse to let
anyone else pay for my failure!
It won't happen again!
[RUI]
Who's there?
You shouldn't
be so hasty, my friend.
Hachirou?
You came just
in time to rescue us!
Does this mean you've decided
to give us a hand?
I have come to
avenge the Five Treasures.
Nothing more than that.
You haven't changed a bit.
Well, whatever the case,
we have to get
through this first.
[HACHIROU] Shichigen,
use your technique to help me.
[SHICHIGEN gasps]
[HACHIROU]
At this range, in the darkness.
I can't use my eye magic.
I would need to move in closer.
[HACHIROU]
And so...
...I'll use the distraction of
the insects you summon
to get near them.
Your eye magic is as
powerful as I remember.
Perhaps even stronger.
As is Shichigen's technique.
His level of mastery
summoning the insects,
few ninja in history
have been so skilled.
I named that technique
"Wind through the Pines."
[SHICHIGEN] The wind that
blows through the pines.
[SHICHIGEN] I know that autumn
can be a painful season.
I shall not tire of the sound
of the bell crickets.
[SHICHIGEN]
Though I know.
I know that autumn can
be a painful season.
I shall not tire of the
sound of the bell crickets.
[SHICHIGEN]
Can you hear it, Mother?
Their song? The bell
crickets are still crying.
Now come. We can go together,
[SHICHIGEN]
Because autumn, isn't yet over.
[NARRATOR]
A father risked his very life,
praying his daughter would
master her technique.
But the young girl has no way
to ever understand
just how he felt.
You would name
this useless technique,
"Dreaming Reality"?