[JOUJIN]
Quite the predicament
[BUNNOSHIN gasps]
Who's there?!
[JOUJIN] Perhaps, your treason
will be brought out
into the light of day.
Damn you! Where--
[TADANAGA gasps]
[JOUJIN] So there are
no further interruptions.
Greetings, my lord.
[TADANAGA]
Who are you?
[JOUJIN] Could it truly be the
case, you've forgotten me?
[TADANAGA whimpers]
Your eyes tell me
you remember who I am.
That desperate look of fear.
You're-- You're Joujin.
Intruder! Men!
Come to my aid!
[grunts]
I won't be fooled twice
by a madman like you.
I know better now.
First, my lord, you should
sheathe your sword
so we may have
a civilized conversation.
Now, please be seated.
You and I have much
to discuss before I leave.
[TADANAGA whimpers]
I let myself get carried away.
If only for a moment.
I was deceived by
your honeyed words.
I imagined being the ruler.
How different life could be
if I took my brother's place.
[JOUJIN]
I fear you misunderstood
what we talked about, my lord.
I never meant to insinuate
anything so simple
as becoming the ruler of Japan.
What?
You think too small.
I told you to embrace the
destiny I had foreseen in you.
As an actual god
who rules over all.
[TADANAGA whimpers]
The forest...
The forest moved,
while I was there!
Misled, by your prophecy.
You told me my wish
would come true,
unless the forest began to move.
Well, that's precisely
what I saw!
Those were mere monkeys
and nothing more, my lord.
Not messengers from
gods or ill omens.
Just groups of monkeys
seeking out a new habitat
in which to live.
You know this
by now, I'm certain.
You slew so many of them,
you had to have eventually
realized as much.
[JOUJIN] The moving forest was,
quite simply put,
a fantasy of your own making.
Perhaps the result
of a fevered brain.
[TADANAGA gasps]
[JOUJIN] A sickness,
that's the best way to explain
your irrational behavior.
However, any future displays of
such weakness will only serve
to put you in further danger.
A man who is destined
to be a god cannot be a slave
to his own emotions.
A god commands,
and all the laws of this world
would change to suit his whims.
That is what you
must learn, my lord,
if you are to ascend
into godhood!
I can't. How can any man
hope to become a god?
[JOUJIN] But in fact, it has
happened once before.
[gasps]
[JOUJIN] A man who became as
close to a god as one could be.
I speak, of course,
of Oda Nobunaga- sama .
[RUI snarls]
[yells]
[UTSUTSU]
When I see you in my dreams...
...it seems it is because...
[UTSUTSU] ...you are
telling me to die for love.
The hellscape
of skeletons and fire,
is no mere illusion.
Though seemingly impossible,
I assure you it's real.
This is the
true hell that awaits us.
[UTSUTSU grunts]
[UTSUTSU]
There are too many.
[gasps]
Rui ran in
this direction, didn't she?
I think so.
[NAMENBA growls]
--[NAMENBA] We should go.
--Yes.
[GORONE]
These are fascinating.
Do you think you can
learn anything from them?
Well, it'll take me a bit
of time to understand them.
This structure is like
nothing that I've ever seen.
[NAMENBA] Those crazy girls are
going to give me grey hairs.
They almost got
themselves into real trouble
on their little mission.
[GORONE] Then it seems you
came back at the perfect time.
You know...
...I was afraid we'd
never get the chance
to bathe together again.
Me, too. That was close.
Those men...
They referred to themselves
as the Rain, didn't they?
But who are they really?
The Rain?
The group of brigands
that attacked us
as we were scouting
out Murakumo.
Well, one thing's for certain.
If you and Namenba
hadn't saved us,
things would have ended poorly.
Then I guess you owe us one.
Yes, and I promise
that I'll repay you.
[UTSUTSU sighs] It's starting
to get cold, let's go.
[RUI]
Hey.
[UTSUTSU]
Hmm?
[HACHISU]
All right. I'm headed back.
About your illusions.
[UTSUTSU gasps]
[RUI] I wanted you
to show me one of them.
[RUI]
Something so rare and beautiful,
that no one has ever seen it.
[UTSUTSU]
I'm sorry...
The only illusions I can
show anyone are of Hell.
The endless realm of fire
that will come after
the end of the world.
It's an awful technique.
And then?
[NAMENBA]
Hmm.
[HADAEBOU]
Head straight back.
[GORONE]
You met with High Priest Tenkai?
[HADAEBOU] This is Namenba,
she is a ninja of the Iga clan.
During the Osaka
Summer Campaign,
after Osaka Castle
had been set alight,
she rushed inside and
rescued Senhime- sama .
Granddaughter of
His Divine Lordship, Ieyasu.
[TENKAI]
I welcome you, Namenba.
I assume that you're
aware of who I am?
[NAMENBA]
Yes.
To speak in the same
manner as your servant
hiding up in the rafters,
His Holiness, Nankoubou Tenkai.
Lord Ieyasu's
most trusted councilor.
You were heavily involved in
the Houkouji bell's inscription,
and the subsequent
interpretation of its meaning,
that led directly to
the Siege of Osaka.
So Tenkai asked for our help?
If crushing the Joujinshuu
is now beyond the scope
of his reach, will our
assistance be enough?
[NAMENBA]
He thinks so.
You're asking for
help defeating the Joujinshuu?
From the Iga?
Joujin wants to bring
an end to Tokugawa rule.
And if he does, that means an
end to the peaceful era
we've come to know and a
return to the chaotic civil wars
that once raged across Japan.
[TENKAI] After all that was
sacrificed during unification,
this cannot be.
However, as I'm sure
you are aware,
Joujin and his men will
not be easy to deal with.
Otherwise, I would
not request your help.
We're aware.
[TENKAI] Will you
put aside our differences?
To fight, side by side, for the
sake of the entire country?
The Divine Lord Ieyasu
did not struggle in
the unification of Japan
merely for the sake
of his own ambition,
nor the establishment of
the Tokugawa shogunate.
It was for the sake of
all people, across our nation.
[NAMENBA] Hmph. Really,
like I'd believe the crap
that bastard was spewing.
[GORONE]
High Priest Tenkai sounds like
quite an interesting old man.
I would even venture
to say, "crafty."
[RUI]
Thanks, come again!
[SHICHIGEN] I'll take a tea
and an order of dumplings.
Sure, coming up-- Ah!
Shichigen!
And you know I like 'em hot.
We tracked him
all the way to Kouzuke,
to the estate of
Tadanaga- sama .
What was Hachirou
doing there, of all places?
Tadanaga
had requested an audience.
He told Hachirou
to crush the Joujinshuu.
[GORONE]
And what was Hachirou's reply?
"Hell no," was the sentiment.
[SHIKIBU] And so, they tried
to ambush him with rifles.
[HIBIKI gasps]
[SHICHIGEN] Mere samurai
couldn't hope to best
our ninja techniques,
much less the power
of Hachirou's eye magic.
We had to kill so many...
And Hachirou?
He said he wasn't coming back.
[SAIZOU]
He plans to finish this himself.
If that's the way
Hachirou feels,
then there's no point in us
worrying about him any longer.
Let's just be glad
we found out where he is,
and that he's in good health.
So. Just forget him, Hibiki.
[HACHISU grunts]
Hey! Who the hell
do you think you are?
I'm one of the
Five Treasures of Kouga.
That's who I think I am.
Have you got
a problem with that?
[UTSUTSU]
What?!
--[HIBIKI] Enough.
--[UTSUTSU gasps]
The castle's been spotted here.
He's bound to come.
Right.
Our current focus should be
on gathering intelligence.
It's time to recon
the castle in force,
and learn what we can about
it before Hachirou's return.
Don't you think?
Indeed.
But what about
the Rain patrolling?
Do we take them out?
[HIBIKI]
This time, I will go.
[SAIZOU]
Hatching up a crazy plan, huh?
That's what you have me for.
[HIBIKI sighs]
Good work, Hibiki.
That was amazing!
[HACHISU]
Don't worry.
[HACHISU] I'll watch over
you the entire time.
I promise to keep you safe.
[SAIZOU]
Who is that man?
I feel like I've seen him
somewhere before.
But for the life of me
can't remember where.
[NEIRICHIOU]
Greetings, Sire.
Lord Nobunaga,
are you feeling stronger today?
[gasps]
That's Oda Nobunaga?
But he... He was burned
to death at Honnouji.
[gasps]
[SAIZOU]
That was too close.
We need to get outta here.
[UTSUTSU]
Hmph.
They sure are persistent.
Time to paddle harder, big guy.
Otherwise, you boys
will be affected by it, too.
Now.
Leaving her to do it by
herself, it seems pretty risky.
That's why she isn't alone.
Oh, yeah. I love this thing!
Seems the young
caterpillars have begun
to emerge from
their cocoons at last.
They must have
become quite agitated
by the sudden appearance of
Murakumo on the horizon.
And there are still so many
surprises yet in store.
[KUJAKU, NEICHIROU laugh]
[HACHIROU]
Who's that?
Those men?
They look to be
soldiers out of Kishuu.
Then it'd be best
to hurry along.
[NARRATOR]
The 20th year of Keichou.
The Iga ninja,
Namenba of Otoshi,
saved Oichi no Kata from Osaka
Castle, just before it fell.
The war led to the
Siege of Osaka,
and ended in what
would come to be known
as the Osaka Summer Campaign.