[ROYAL A] The shogun
has made his decision.
Listen, and learn his desires.
[ROYAL A]
Takechiyo.
[TAKECHIYO]
Yes, sir.
[ROYAL A]
Kunichiyo.
[KUNICHIYO]
Yes, sir.
No matter which way
the judgement may go,
do not forget that this was
your father's decision.
It would be most unseemly
to complain about the results.
Rather, when the decree
has been announced,
both the one who was chosen,
and the one who was not,
should not waste
time with jealousy.
Instead, work together
for a better future,
and for the glory of the
Tokugawa shogunate!
Understood?
[BOTH]
Sir!
[MAN A] "The last one to
write on this scroll was
the Iga clan ninja, Oboro."
Thus, Iga is the winner.
[MEN gasping, murmuring]
[MAN A] Which means that
Takechiyo- sama will
ascend to the
position of shogun.
[ROYAL A]
And thus it shall be done.
Now get that blood-covered
thing out of my sight!
[gasps]
[KUNICHIYO growls]
[GEI'IN]
Worry not, my lord.
The Five Treasures of Kouga
are here to serve.
[TADANAGA]
Who are these men?
[KASOU]
Iga vermin.
These ones here are also
known as the Kurokuwa,
and they're not worthy
of being called ninjas.
Essentially, they're
nothing more than farmhands
with a few tricks
up their sleeves.
I hear you
"Five Treasures of Kouga"
are supposed to be tough.
[GEI'IN] What reason could you
Iga have to try and stop
Suruga- sama from
arriving at his destination?
[TADANAGA gasps]
[KASOU]
Ninja Technique:
Grass Fire!
[TADANAGA whimpers]
[KAZUMA] My whips slice through
flesh like ripe pomegranates,
and snap bones in
twain like icicles.
[KAZUMA] Let the melody of
Heaven send your soul to Hell!
[TADANAGA]
He's attacking!
Ninja Technique: Darkness Web.
[TADANAGA]
I can't see what's happening!
There's no light!
Gei'in!
[GEI'IN] So they
intend to strike at us
while hidden in the darkness?
Laughable.
Now have a dose of my technique!
Try as you might,
you have no hope of escaping
the luminescence of
my special ability, which
is known as Firefly Squid.
It's my perspiration.
The sweat of Shichito Gei'in
that marks you.
Tenshin--now!
[TENSHIN] Gei'in- sama 's
Firefly Squid skill is a light
that shines on the path to Hell.
My caltrops,
the Thousand-Handed Kannon,
are the lights of virtue
that lead to Heaven.
[TENSHIN]
Now they've learned this lesson.
Thanks again for bringing these.
It's very kind of you to make
the trip so late in the day.
I'm glad to help, really.
Now, hurry on your
way back home.
They say that tengu stalk across
the mountainside at night.
--[HIBIKI] Mm-hmm.
--[WOMAN B panting]
My child! Please!
Help me find my child!
My boy!
I lost sight of him up
on the mountain!
[WOMAN A]
Just hold on!
I'll go alert the others!
You know I can see you.
Come out, Hachirou.
What's the matter?
I wasn't planning
to say anything,
but I decided at the very least
I needed to run things by you.
[TADANAGA]
Don't try to keep me from going.
I don't have time
to argue with you.
We wouldn't dare stand
in your way, Suruga- sama .
We shall prepare a vessel for
your lordship immediately.
Make haste, Tenshin and Kazuma.
We will travel
with you, milord,
and we shall ensure you reach
your destination by morning.
I pray that you will.
It's imperative.
[TADANAGA]
Eye magic, isn't that right?
[GEI'IN]
Yes.
[TADANAGA] The special
ability possessed by
your leader, Hachirou.
During the decisive battle,
wasn't the Kouga leader
at the time rumored to have
used the same technique?
[TADANAGA]
Kouga Gennosuke.
That was his name.
[TADANAGA] This power
gave him a great advantage.
Those who intended
to injure or slay him,
or to use magic against him,
were the only ones affected
[TADANAGA]
It's a type of illusion spell.
That causes the attackers
to destroy themselves.
[SOLDIER A yells]
[SOLDIER B groans]
--[SOLDIER C rasps]
--[SOLDIER D groans]
[TADANAGA] That was
the terror of Gennosuke.
His fearsome Eye Magic.
Correct?
[GEI'IN] I have only heard
of this ability second-hand
like yourself, my lord.
I was hoping
you could fill in
some of the details.
[IEYASU] Both sides are to
place the names of ten ninja
upon these two scrolls.
This will entrust
the third shogun's fate
to the feud between the
Iga and Kouga clans.
[IEYASU] The Kouga will
represent the second son,
Kunichiyo, and the
Iga will stand for
the first son, Takechiyo.
This fight will
last to the bitter end,
and the clan whose proponents
avoid the clutches of death,
bearing the Secret Scroll,
shall inherit the spoils.
You have my word
that the victor will bear
favored status for
a thousand years.
[VILLAGER A]
Can you hear us? Chou?
[VILLAGERS]
Chou! Where are you?
Mama wants you back home safe!
Please come out, Chou!
[HIBIKI gasps]
--Over here!
--What?
I heard a voice.
We may have found where he is!
Follow me!
[VILLAGER B]
There he is!
[VILLAGER C]
We found him!
[WOMAN B]
Chou!
Chou...
[CHOU sobs]
--[VILLAGER B] Are you okay?
--[VILLAGER C] Are you hurt?
What's wrong?
[WOMAN B]
I was so worried...
You gave my pistol
to Gorone, right?
Did he work something out?
He told me that
he'd take a look at it for you,
but you need to show him
a little respect.
Asking him yourself next time
would be a nice start.
This is me being respectful.
I gave him something
to do, didn't I?
[NAMENBA] There's a lesson
to be learned here.
If you're going
to choose to always leave
the upkeep of your
tools to other people,
you'll never fulfill
your duty, young lady.
I know that...
[UTSUSU]
Again?
[HACHISU]
Hmm?
[UTSUSU] Is this the
only stuff you ever buy?
Utsutsu, those are to be sold.
If only you
children could survive
on sunlight and morning dew.
--Huh?
--Hmm?
[HIBIKI]
Hachirou!
Tell me why.
What is it now?
[NAMENBA]
It's odd for her to be late.
If she isn't here,
where could she be?
She's just running
a little behind, Namenba.
You don't need to be so worried.
I suppose you're right
[sighs]
What is it?
I wonder if she bumped
into Hachirou on his way out?
What do you
mean, "on his way out"?
Is something going on with him?
[GORONE] He told me he
intended to leave the village.
What? Hachirou's leaving?
You should have
stopped him, Gorone!
[GORONE]
No.
Please, just stay out of it!
[NAMENBA gasps]
Why should I?
Because if Hibiki
really did meet up with him,
then I think it may be better to
leave things to them, for now.
So you believe
that she'll stop him, then?
I don't know,
but perhaps the whim of fate
dictates that they'll
never be together.
[HIBIKI]
What's going on?
Why are you leaving
without telling me?
Is it my powers
that you're worried about?
Or yours?
Are you afraid of
what might happen?
[HIBIKI]
You don't have to be.
I'm not scared of your power.
Know why?
Because unless I hate you,
or wanted to hurt you
for some reason,
you can't use it on me, right?
[HIBIKI] I'd never feel
that way about you.
[HACHIROU]
I know, but...
[HIBIKI] And when you compare it
to a technique like yours,
mine can do even less.
All I can do is disable
an opponent's power.
So then, why is it
that you seem so scared?
[GORONE] The first pair
to fight 12 years ago,
were Ogen- sama
and Danjou- sama .
They had been in love with
each other in their youth.
Gennosuke- sama
and Oboro- sama were
deeply in love as well.
But that's over.
The Kouga and the Iga will
never fight each other again.
Even if that is the truth.
I fear they were always
destined to be separated.
Perhaps that fate has been
inherited some other way.
Some other way?
[GORONE] As long as
those two bear the blood
of Gennosuke- sama
and Oboro- sama .
Gorone, how much do you know?
You just said that the children
carry the blood of
the two that fell in battle.
And I've often heard
others speak of
such an impossible thing.
But when I've asked about it,
no one can explain it to me.
Why?
Ninja are quite fascinating.
I daresay beyond
human understanding.
[GEI'IN]
Huh?
[TADANAGA] You challenge
our laws of nature,
with powers like turning
sweat into light.
[GEI'IN] There's no need to
flatter me, Suruga- sama .
[TADANAGA] I've even heard there
was a ninja who wouldn't die.
[GEI'IN]
That so?
[KASOU] You're referring to
Yakushiji Tenzen, most likely.
A powerful foe,
who was an integral part
of the war of the scrolls.
[TADANAGA]
Do you think it was true?
That he learned how
to defeat death?
[GEI'IN]
My deepest apologies, my lord,
but Tenzen was of the Iga.
I was never privy
to that information.
Well, I'm sure it's a
bunch of mystical nonsense.
[TADANAGA] And yet
Kouga Gennosuke was
still able to defeat
a creature such as that!
[BOTH gasp]
[TADANAGA] So how was he beaten
by this Iga Oboro woman?
He was so powerful,
it doesn't make any sense!
[HACHIROU]
You've noticed it, haven't you?
What?
I know you remember
what happened that last time,
when the cherry
blossoms bloomed.
[HACHIROU yelps]
[HIBIKI grunts]
[HIBIKI]
I finally won!
It's the first time
I've beaten you!
[gasps]
That was deliberate.
Hachirou...
Did you let me win?
Are you taking pity on me?
[HACHIROU grunts]
I don't think
that's very nice at all.
No, Hachirou.
Don't look away.
[HACHIROU gasps]
[HIBIKI gasps]
That was just a gust of wind,
it happens all the time
Nothing more than that.
[TADANAGA]
Tell me, Gei'in.
[GEI'IN]
Hmm?
[TADANAGA] Naturally,
I assume you know the man
named Hattori Kyouhachirou?
Of course I've heard
about him, my lord.
Kyouhachirou is the son of the
second Hattori Hanzo- sama .
[TADANAGA]
Indeed.
And in the final battle,
when Oboro and Gennosuke
faced each other to end the war.
Both he and his father,
the second Hanzo,
were present to witness.
[GORONE]
Using their powers,
they both overextended
themselves, and perished.
But Oboro- sama stayed
alive slightly longer.
Long enough to mark
the Iga victory on the scroll.
That is how it was
relayed back to the court
of the Shogun,
and is now history.
But here, in this village,
the story, when told,
differs slightly.
[GORONE] Before the
last battle even began.
Gennosuke- sama
was already injured.
He couldn't open his eyes
to use his Eye Magic.
Gennosuke- sama ,
you know I love you.
[GORONE] And so, Gennosuke- sama
embraced the lifeless body
of his beloved Oboro- sama ,
and wrote the Iga victory
onto the scroll with
his own hands.
And then...
[NAMENBA]
But that would mean...
[GORONE] Yes,
in the end, it isn't clear
how much of this
tale is even true.
[TADANAGA] There's a story
that involves Kyouhachirou.
The morning when Gennosuke and
Oboro were to end the war,
Kyouhachirou had a private
meeting with Oboro.
[TADANAGA]
Have you ever heard that?
[GEI'IN]
I've not.
This is news to me, my lord.
Could there have
been some secret agreement
between those two?
The Hattori clan
was originally part of the Iga.
Perhaps he gave
Oboro some sort of plan,
so that the Iga would
be the victors.
Couldn't that be
possible at least?
When I was a boy,
no more than
eight or nine years of age,
somebody came to the Kouga
village to visit Gei'in- sama .
[NAMENBA]
Then, that was...
[GORONE]
Yes.
Kyouhachirou- sama .
[NAMENBA]
So...
If Kyouhachirou- sama
actually did save
the two children back then,
what was his goal?
I can't be certain.
As the acting head of espionage
for the Tokugawa clan,
he tried to ensure
the bloodlines of such
powerful ninjas continued.
That seems the
most obvious explanation.
But maybe...
I'd like to think that he
might've been moved
by their selflesness.
By how, despite their being
destiny to be torn apart,
they willingly sacrificed
their own lives
for the sake of one other.
Otherwise, it would
be far too sad
for Hachirou and Hibiki.
I don't care what happens,
as long as we can be together!
[TADANAGA]
They say it's folly.
[BOTH gasp]
[TADANAGA] And I understand
those who laugh,
and say I should give in.
But that isn't something
I'm prepared to do, just yet.
Because I still don't
believe that the decision
they handed down
was the right one!
[BOTH grunt]
[TADANAGA gasps]
Tenshin!
Hurry up and close
the door, you fool!
The cold wind
is hitting my lord,
and the rain is getting in!
[TENSHIN]
I fear I cannot...
Grant me forgiveness...
Why is that?
Speak up!
Why can you not shut the door
to keep the cold weather
from coming inside?
I cannot because...
It's because...
Look at him--his neck.
I can't, because I'm--
It's because I'm...
...already... dead...
[NARRATOR] A ninja spends
his life in training.
Refining his technique
to perfection,
so he may do what is necessary,
and honorably fulfill
his duty to his lord.
Ah. Poor old Gei'in...