[WOMEN screaming]
[SENHIME]
Otoshi! Otoshi, where are you?!
Answer. Can you not hear me?
[MAN] A woman! I found
another one up here!
[MEN growling]
Stay back! Do you have
any idea who I am?
[MEN grunt]
[SENHIME gasps]
Otoshi...?
Senhime- sama , are you hurt?
No, I'm quite all right.
How did you learn to do that?
Otoshi. I've never seen you
wear such clothes before.
Who are you, truly?
[NAMENBA]
I am Namenba of Otoshi.
A ninja in service
of the Iga Clan.
[MAN A] We've searched the
mansion and the grounds,
but Lord Tadanaga
has not been spotted yet.
My men are scanning
the perimeter
around Takasaki
Castle as we speak.
[TENKAI]
It's useless!
The most likely scenario
is that Suruga- sama
has gone inside.
Take your leave at once,
and tell Hadaebou everything.
[SAIZOU] Those soldiers
from Kishuu brought along
dozens of cannons.
[SHICHIGEN] I doubt even
Joujin could withstand a barrage
from that kind of firepower.
Right. Perhaps there will
be nothing left for us to do.
Perhaps, but I
wouldn't get my hopes up.
[HADAEBOU]
Please, put your weapons away.
Who goes there?
[HADAEBOU]
Namenba- dono .
Could you intervene
for me, please?
What, you again?
Such rotten luck.
Someone you know?
We've just recently
formed a close friendship.
Isn't that right,
Namenba- dono ?
Sure, fine, that's
a creative way of looking at it.
So? What do you want?
I have come to ask you
if you'll help us capture
the fortress Murakumo.
Murakumo?
That castle on
the other side of the river.
I believe you know
of which I speak.
Well. You seem to be aware
of everything that's been
happening, but who are you,
and why should we care?
If you've come here
to ask us for a favor,
you can start off by
telling us who you really are,
and then ask politely.
I apologize for
being so bullheaded,
Gorone- dono . My name is--
This monk is called Hadaebou.
One of Tenkai's dogs.
Tenkai?
You've come
because you're trying
to use us again, aren't you?
I fear you
misunderstand, my lady.
You wish to defeat the
Joujinshuu, in that endeavor,
our goals are aligned.
[HIBIKI sighs]
It's true.
And if someone doesn't
step up to stop Joujin,
a terrifying demon king
will be revived,
and the nation will be
plunged into civil war.
This demon is Nobunaga?
That is quite a plan.
[HADAEBOU] And if this fiendish
scheme is successful.
They'll use him to turn
our world into a living hell.
To put it simply,
this plan must never
come to fruition.
If you really want
something done about it,
then why don't you try getting
your own hands dirty?
[HADAEBOU]
We work from behind the scenes,
and have no real
power of our own.
Frankly, we're far better
suited to espionage.
We'd, of course,
be willing to share
all the information
we've collected with
the Iga and the Kouga.
You'd prefer to
have others shed blood
for your cause.
While you hide in the shadows
protecting your own skin.
That's what you're
really saying, is it not?
[SHICHIGEN]
She's right.
Listen, Hadaebou, it doesn't
matter what you say,
we will never be
your pawns again.
Namenba- dono ?
Do you share in their feelings?
Very well, then. It seems
giving you time to think
it over would be in
everyone's best interest.
I shall return to you later,
and I hope to receive a
favorable answer when I do.
Now.
I shall take my leave.
[RUI sighs]
It's like he vanished.
I don't much care for that guy.
Namenba,
could you come help me
with repairs to the Ashura?
So I have to ask where
did you find the inspiration
for a name like "Ashura"?
[GORONE] That's the name of the
god who fought Taishakuten.
[NAMENBA]
I see.
So about what Hadaebou
was alluding to.
[GORONE]
That the civil wars would return
if we didn't help him?
I wouldn't mind so much.
At least then, the ninja would
be given a purpose again.
Are you serious?
[GORONE] It's what you
wanted, too, remember?
And besides, those of our number
who perished must be avenged.
[sighs]
You're right, but still...
They're planning
to bring back Nobunaga.
Do you really
think it's possible?
The man died ages ago.
So how could he come back?
Honestly, I don't have a clue.
Anyway. There's no use in
us staring at each other here.
[SHICHIGEN] Hold on. Where
do you think you're going?
The battle between
the Kishuu army and Murakumo
is starting soon.
I want to watch, and see
who comes out the victor.
I'll be going with you.
[RUI]
Me, too.
Rui, you should
stay here with Hibiki.
Just in case Hadaebou
makes another visit.
That monk is not to be trusted.
Fine. I'll stay.
I'll have you know,
my thoughts haven't changed.
If their intention is to drag
you into an insane battle,
I'll drive them off
with my power.
[SHIKIBU]
Hey, is it okay if I eat this?
[HACHISU]
Hmm? Sure, why not.
Idiot.
If you hang around the
shop in armor like that,
customers will be too
scared to come by!
Everybody's too busy
watching the battle.
No one's coming in today.
[MEN murmuring]
Excuse me, samurai!
Care to make a wager?
Who do you think
will be the victor?
[MAN C]
I'll bet one isshuban on Kishuu!
[MAN D]
Same, but I'll double that bet!
[MAN E] I'll put a nishuban
on Kishuu, too!
[gasps]
Hey, Samurai?
[TADANAGA whimpers]
Look! We're done for!
They've brought a battery
of cannons imported from
the Western barbarians!
[JOUJIN] You'll soon see there's
no need to be worried, my lord.
The cannons fielded
by the forces of Kishuu,
are little more than toys,
and no cause for concern.
How so?
[JOUJIN]
Simple.
They are nothing when
compared to the cannons
built into this castle.
[gulps]
Are you saying...
...that these cannons are
a part of the castle's design?
[TADANAGA whimpers]
Joujin...
Wait, isn't that enough
to prove our point?
So, why...?
[NAMENBA] For generations,
my family has had a task
to save the nobility from
castles that have fallen.
It was my duty
to wait here to save you,
Senhime- sama ,
should the need ever arise.
[SENHIME] But I married
into the Toyotomi clan.
I am Hideyori- sama 's wife!
I will not simply run away
and abandon my husband!
Hideyori- sama and
his mother, Ochacha,
have both committed seppuku.
[gasps]
Look below, my lady.
The battle is over,
the grounds aflame.
Anything further,
would be senseless slaughter.
And only you
can bring it to an end.
Senhime- sama , granddaughter
of Tokugawa Ieyasu.
You must use your kinship
to stop the carnage.
[NAMENBA]
Come.
Let us depart.
[SENHIME yelps]
[NAMENBA] Senhime- sama ,
hold tight, and don't let go.
[SOLDIER A rasps]
[SOLDIER A]
I-Is that...?
[MAN F]
Who goes there? A girl?
[SAKAZAKI gasps]
Is that...?
[SAKAZAKI]
Senhime- sama !
There's no mistake!
It's Senhime- sama !
Someone!
Bring a litter, quickly!
Senhime- sama is here!
Hello? Is anyone still alive?
[SOLDIER A whimpers]
A celestial maiden...
[gasps]
She was so beautiful...
Soaring through
the sky so high above...
Her white robe,
bright as the sun...
I hope... I can go, too...
That she'll carry me...
somewhere far beyond
that pale blue sky...
Yes. I will take you there.
To the place far beyond
the pale blue sky.
The army of Kishuu is gone.
What do you think, my lord?
It was absolutely astonishing.
With command of
such mighty cannons,
all of Japan could be mine.
What exactly's
happening in here?
What does it look
like's happening?
They're forcing the rest of us
to wait while they play Go.
Ugh. Seriously?
Shouldn't the two of
you be getting ready
to go to war instead?
I was waiting on you, Namenba.
[NAMENBA]
Uh.
[GORONE] I made this based
on Utsutsu's drawings.
Now. The fortress of Murakumo
is surrounded on every side by
ninja soldiers called the Rain.
[GORONE]
And here's the plan:
Shichigen and Rui will go around
to the opposite side,
and draw them away.
Why is my paper figure naked?
You know,
the resemblance
is really quite remarkable.
The guards distracted,
Saizou, Utsutsu,
and Shikibu will move in,
and take out Murakumo's cannons.
They'll throw explosives
into the cannon ports.
The fortress' structure
suggests that they keep
their gunpowder stores
directly behind the cannons.
So if it works...
[GORONE]
Ka-boom.
What'll I do?
You'll stay here with me.
I'll need some help protecting
Hibiki and the village.
Namenba will
go with the strike team
to supervise the mission.
That way, if any
problems crop up,
you can give everyone
the signal to retreat.
Right. Got it.
I suppose it's settled.
--Is that so?
--[SAIZOU] Hmm?
Let's say the plan's successful
and the Rain do get drawn away.
If the Joujinshuu
inside survive our attack,
surely, they'll
try to retaliate.
We have no idea
what kind of techniques
they have at their disposal.
That's a valid point.
Our last run in nearly
ended with none of you
reaching adulthood.
The answers
that we're looking for
can probably be given by
the man hiding outside.
[NAMENBA sighs]
[HADAEBOU]
Oh, dear.
I thought I'd gone unnoticed.
Reveal yourself!
It's all right, Hachisu.
Put the gun down.
[HADAEBOU] I couldn't help but
overhear that you've decided
to lend us your assistance.
That is most pleasing.
And now for my part of the deal.
Where I tell you everything
I know about the forces
of the Joujinshuu.
[GORONE] I actually
planned this out as well.
Where you tell us of the
techniques used by our enemies.
[HADAEBOU]
Is that supposed to be me?
I don't look anything like that.
[MALE ROYAL A] We've received a
report that the Kishuu forces
were completely wiped out.
But their army was said to be
among the nation's largest!
They say the enemy
repelled them with
the sheer power
of their cannons.
Now all of the western
daimyos still loyal to
the Toyotomi clan are conspiring
to rise up against us.
[MALE ROYAL C]
And if the rumors are true,
the Sakai merchants are
gathering huge amounts
of money to lend them.
[MALE ROYAL A]
What? I hadn't heard.
[TENKAI]
All of you calm down!
[IEMITSU gasps]
Tenkai!
You must not let
yourself be deceived
by mere rumors, mighty shogun.
That is precisely what
your enemies desire.
Master Tenkai,
what are we to do?
Have you any plan?
I've sent a
team of peerless ninjas
to deal with this threat.
Just ninjas?
They are more than capable,
and I am certain they will
succeed in their given task.
Simply await the arrival of
good news, your lordship.
[GORONE]
Why did you change your mind?
I couldn't stop it
back then, but I can this time.
[MAN A]
Hadaebou- dono .
How is everything proceeding?
Inform His Holiness,
the ninja have agreed
to help us fulfill our task.
Tomorrow,
they'll strike at dusk.
[MAN A]
Good. And one final thing--
[HADAEBOU]
I know, and I completely agree.
[MAN A]
Yes, sir.
[HADAEBOU] If Tadanaga- sama
cannot be saved,
we'll have no other choice.
His life is to be taken,
should it come to that.
[HADAEBOU]
The old man is a harsh master.
[JOUJIN] You, rejected by
the leader of the Kurokuwa,
and driven out
to fend for yourself.
The time has come for you
to find your purpose.
[UNKNOWN MAN]
Who's there?
[JOUJIN]
Fulfill the task I assign you,
and as a reward
for your service,
you will be granted
your freedom.
[UNKNOWN MAN snarls]
[NARRATOR] Renouncing violence
against all living things.
Harming not a single one.
With no wish for offspring.
How then, can you wish
for a companion?
It is your destiny to wander
alone, like a rhinoceros.