[IEYASU]
Ninjas?
You would suggest leaving the
future of the Tokugawa shogunate
to be chosen by the victor
of a ninja contest?
[TENKAI]
I would.
The growing power struggle
between the factions
of your eldest
grandson, Takechiyo.
and those of his
younger brother, Kunichiyo,
have reached the point
of becoming a threat to
the stability of
the entire nation.
Normally, as would be
befitting of a samurai family,
it would be perfectly acceptable
to settle the matter through
ten rounds of mortal combat.
But it would be a
tragedy to lose so many
Tokugawa samurai for
a cause that yielded
neither territory nor gold.
And therefore, use ninjas.
If we were to use the ninja
instead of your samurai,
who would care if they all
perished in a sea of blood?
We're already on the boat,
against orders.
Better to accept it.
Yes, I know.
Lord, there's no need
for you to feel dismayed.
I, Bunnoshin, have set up
both a second and third layer
of traps in which
to ensnare him.
And you're sure
that will be enough
to bring him down?
Yes, the next he'll face--
I call "the ears."
The ears?
[BUNNOSHIN] I have
personally selected a man
with exceptional hearing to
be our archery commander.
With his highly
perceptive ears,
he can locate a foe using naught
but the sound of his footsteps.
And thus, his own attempt
to flee will be his undoing.
Very good.
If they don't look at him,
then Hachirou's eye magic
can't affect them.
How many bowmen are there?
[BUNNOSHIN]
Twenty, in total.
And when a volley of 20
arrows comes flying in
unannounced over the wall,
even a ninja as monstrous
as this one, would find it
hard to survive.
[SHICHIGEN] I know that
autumn can be a painful season.
I shall not tire of the sound
of the bell crickets.
[cricket chirping]
[COMMANDER A gasps]
[SOLDIERS gasping, yelling]
[SOLDIERS murmuring]
[gasps]
[SOLDIER C whimpers]
[SOLDIER D wails]
[SOLDIER E grunts]
[SOLDIER F groans]
[SOLDIER G yells]
[SOLDIER H groans]
[SOLDIER I grunts]
[SOLDIER J whimpers]
[SOLDIER K gasps]
[SOLDIER K rasps]
[HACHIROU]
Shichigen...
[gasps] The archers have
all been wiped out?
[SOLDIER L]
Yes! They failed to strike him!
Not a single arrow
found its mark, my lord!
Bunnoshin!
Lord, don't panic,
there's still the third layer.
Your riflemen are
waiting to greet him.
But still...
Don't despair, sire.
Your riflemen
do not stand alone.
Gorouza the Hawk
is out there with them.
[gasps]
And is he with them now?
That's correct.
The man who shot Oda Nobunaga,
in the woods near Aekuni Shrine,
was named Otowanokido.
Gorouza the Hawk
was his finest student.
I've heard it
said that he surpasses
even his master.
[TADANAGA]
Hmm!
[BUNNOSHIN] I once had
the opportunity to see
his skill in action,
and that was all I needed.
He downed a rainbird,
flying faster than the eye
could see, with one shot.
I've heard many rumors
of his great talent.
Surely... Gorouza will prevail!
I have faith in the man.
It would be impossible for such
a marksman to miss his target!
Come now, my lord!
You should relax and await
the good news!
Yes, I shall indeed!
I'm feeling thirsty,
bring me tea!
No, wait, saké!
Have some saké prepared!
[BUNNOSHIN] Lord!
I'll see it done right away.
He's far. Aim high.
[SHIKIBU]
Or just stop.
I don't wanna
have to kill any of you.
So you're with him?
Open fire!
[SHIKIBU] I told you
I didn't want to kill you.
[SOLDIER N growls]
[SHIKIBU growls]
[SOLDIER O grunts]
[SOLDIER Q gasps, groans]
[SOLDIERS whimper]
[SHIKIBU snarls]
[SOLDIERS screaming]
--[SOLDIER U yells]
--[SOLDIER V grunts]
[SOLDIER W groans]
[SOLDIERS screaming]
Hachirou...
Shikibu.
[GOROUZA] Wind. Southeast
to northwest, but mild.
Adjustment, one and a half,
mixed, to the west.
[gunshot]
The evil intent is gone.
We're safe.
[SHIKIBU sighs]
I would bet that
he didn't see that coming.
Hold on! Don't just leave.
[SHICHIGEN] Hachirou,
why do you keep ignoring us?
We could help.
Why do you insist on
sneaking around by yourself?
It's unkind!
I hope you realize we've
been worried sick about you!
Have you nothing to say?
I do. So listen.
I will have vengeance for the
slaughter of the Five Treasures,
and the others.
That's my duty, alone.
Hachirou, you're heir
to the Kouga clan
and our leader!
Don't you understand?
Protecting you and your
bloodline is our duty!
[SAIZOU] It'll be fine.
If he wants to go, let him.
[SHICHIGEN]
Saizou.
Doing what he tells us
to is also our duty.
Hachirou is the leader,
just like you said.
Utsutsu and Rui are gone?
Yeah. I can't
find them anywhere.
It'll be time
to open up shop soon.
[HACHISU sighs ]
[gasps]
Of course.
They must've gone to scout out
that mysterious castle.
Even Rui?
I told both of them to wait here
until Namenba came back.
[NAMENBA] Wait until
I came back to do what?
[BOTH gasp]
[HACHISU, HIBIKI]
Namenba!
What's the paper for?
[UTSUTSU]
Making a sketch.
Something Gorone can look
at to learn about the structure
and any weaknesses
it might have.
[RUI]
Someone's coming!
[UTSUTSU]
It's only a couple of farmers.
Just wait.
--[splattering]
--[UTSUTSU gasps]
[UTSUTSU groans]
[RUI groans]
I'll take a bowl, please.
[WAITRESS A]
Coming up!
[HADAEBOU] The soba here
is of the finest quality--
you picked the right shop.
[gasps]
It seems we
meet again, Hadaebou.
I had quite a mess to deal with.
I suppose I have you
to thank for that.
Nonsense.
Suruga- sama 's forces couldn't
have been that dangerous.
I never had
an inkling of concern
about how things
would turn out for you.
I knew a man of your talents
wouldn't even break a sweat
defeating that rabble.
[HADAEBOU]
Apologies.
I failed to mention this
earlier, but I am a ninja monk
in the service of
High Priest Tenkai.
It was he that
ordered me to head to
the court of Suruga- sama ,
and work my way closer
to him however I could.
[HACHIROU]
High Priest Tenkai?
Here you go sir--
He left?
[HADAEBOU slurps]
[WAITRESS A sighs]
[WAITRESS A] The rain
didn't last very long at all.
[HADAEBOU]
Thank you. It was delicious.
[WAITRESS A]
Uh... You're welcome.
So tell me.
Why did you let Hachirou
just walk away?
I thought we came here
to bring him back!
Hey, Saizou! Are you listening?
[SAIZOU]
Hmm...
[growls]
[SAIZOU]
What was that for?!
Answer me!
We've come so far.
We were supposed to help
Hachirou so he'd come home!
You and I have
very different approaches
to playing the game.
Say what?!
You think this is
all just a game?!
We can't fight each other!
It's his choice.
He wants to make sure that
if any blood has to be shed,
it's his own.
[SHIKIBU] He's always
cared so much about us,
ever since we
were all just kids.
An average ninja leader
would send his men to die,
but Hachirou's never
been satisfied with being
anything less than exceptional.
Hah. Spoken like
a true eccentric.
I'm so lucky to have
gotten stuck with you.
[SAIZOU] Don't you find
it interesting, at least?
Eccentric ninjas protecting
their "abnormal" leader?
You can't use
an established playbook with
that formula, because
the game has no chance
of going the way it should.
I can see your point.
But I hate your metaphors.
Thank you.
Now, let's head back home.
There's something
that's bothering me.
[HADAEBOU] You didn't
stick around long enough
to eat your soba noodles.
Now that I know
you work for Tenkai,
we no longer have
anything to discuss.
He was the one who
instigated the battle between
the Kouga and the Iga.
Are you saying
he's your mortal enemy?
I would have never expected
such a short-sighted
approach from you.
How so?
Simple.
Who is the adversary
that you currently face?
You should consider
that very carefully.
If you intend to
defeat the Joujinshuu,
what need could you have
for grudges long forgotten?
Besides, at this point,
it can't be more than
an old story to you.
So you expect me
to forget everything?
Throw it all away
and offer you my help?
[HADAEBOU]
We have a common enemy.
Let's focus on that
for the time being.
The Joujinshuu are
a legitimate threat to us all.
[HADAEBOU] If you were
to promise us your aid,
we could begin to repay you by
sharing some of Joujin's secrets
we've been able to uncover.
[HACHIROU]
Joujin's secrets?
[HADAEBOU]
Indeed.
[HACHIROU]
Hmph. I'm not interested.
You're intending to lie to us,
and use us again, aren't you?
[HACHIROU]
We refuse to be anyone's pawns.
How awful. It's terrible...
[GEI'IN]
Yes, it is brutal.
However, that has always
been the destiny of the ninja.
And one day, Hachirou,
you will be the leader
of the Kouga forces.
You will have to be ready
to send your comrades off
to their deaths, should
the situation call for it.
I won't do it.
Hachirou...
[HACHIROU]
I refuse!
[HACHIROU] I wish to be
left alone, but if you insist.
[HADAEBOU] It was
my understanding that
your eye magic would be
totally useless against
someone who didn't consider
you to be an enemy.
Several centuries ago,
a monk traveled to Song,
where he performed a
prayer for rain to fall
upon the parched land.
The name of
that monk was Joujin.
That's right.
It was said that Heaven's favor
granted him the power
to make the rains fall.
Now, the name was
probably nothing more
than a coincidence.
But I can't be the
only one who thinks
the whole thing is
somewhat eerie.
[HADAEBOU] I've heard
it said that Joujin has
a large number of soldiers
at his disposal
beyond his lieutenants.
They are known as, "The Rain."
This is starting to look bad.
More of them keep showing up.
It's time to head back.
Rui. I'm charging straight in.
So follow my lead!
I'm right behind you.
Utsutsu, wait!
Keep going!
[RUI]
How far are we running?
[UTSUTSU]
How far do you think?
Back to the boat at the pier--
[UTSUTSU gasps]
[FAKE RUI]
Wait, Utsutsu!
[garbled]
Utsutsu, wait!
[more garbled]
Don't leave me behind!
Utsutsu, where are you?
[UTSUTSU]
Over here, Rui!
[RUI gasps]
[FAKE UTSUTSU]
Over here, Rui.
[garbled]
The Rain descends upon you.
[RUI gasps]
[RUI grunts]
[RUI snarls, yells]
All the riflemen...?
Not a single one
of them survived?
[BUNNOSHIN]
Yes, my lord!
And what of Gorouza the Hawk?
[BUNNOSHIN]
Dead as well!
[JOUJIN]
Quite the predicament.
[BUNNOSHIN gasps]
Who's there?
[JOUJIN] Perhaps, your treason
will be brought out
into the light of day.
Damn you!
Where--
[JOUJIN] So there are
no further interruptions.
Greetings, my lord.
[TADANAGA]
Who are you?
[JOUJIN] Could it truly be the
case, you've forgotten me?
[TADANAGA whimpers]
Your eyes tell me
you remember who I am.
That desperate look of fear.
[TADANAGA]
Joujin...
[NARRATOR] A failed young man,
who once aspired to rule,
finds his heart in distress.
The Kouga and Iga gather once
again, and make their way
to Murakumo Castle.
Oh, how they dance.