[HADAEBOU growls]
You again?
[MAGOROKU groans]
No way!
[gasps]
[NEIRICHIOU groans]
What's happening?
Have my wounds become
too much for you to bear,
great demon god?
[NEIRICHIOU] Thank you
for everything you've done,
my friend...
Farewell, Raijin- sama ...
I came here to help.
We could have
done this peacefully,
but now the only option is to
force them to shed their blood.
Either way, we still win.
I know who you are.
Then you've
come to your senses?
So be it.
[HIBIKI gasps]
[HIBIKI growls]
[KUJAKU]
Let me handle them.
It would be an honor,
Joujin- sama !
Not today!
We must be mindful
of your wounds.
[KUJAKU gasps]
You're weak from your injury.
[KUJAKU growls]
[JOUJIN]
Hachirou. Hibiki.
I am afraid that you've
left me with no other choice,
but to spill your blood
upon the skull of
the great demon
king, Oda Nobunaga!
Hurts too much to move...
But... we've done enough,
haven't we...?
[UTSUTSU]
It's so cold... Of course...
I must've lost too much blood...
It was cold back then,
bathing at the stream...
So crisp...
[UTSUTSU]
That picture is fantastic.
It makes me feel
like I can tap into more types
of hallucinations to project.
I've felt that since
you gave it to me.
That makes me feel good.
I'm so happy you like it!
All I can think about...
are those cold baths
we shared together...
[RUI gasps]
Perfect...
[UTSUTSU]
Just like lipstick...
Hadaebou, why are
you here, helping us?
Need a good story
to tell the shogun?
I had to be here
to see the ending.
There's been a burning
question in my mind
for quite some time now.
And I wanted to know the
answer that the young ninjas,
and you, their leaders, give.
[gasps]
What'll happen to us ninjas?
I couldn't resist finding out.
[HADAEBOU grunts]
Come and get me, Hachirou.
Aren't you filled with shame,
having no other power to
rely on but your eye magic?
There's no reason
to be ashamed
of what I've inherited.
[JOUJIN] But you've refused to
learn from our encounters.
My heart is like a placid sea.
Rendering your cursed
gift completely useless.
A placid sea?
Then I am the storm,
to make those waters rage!
[HADAEBOU grunts]
Now die!
[HADAEBOU groans]
[KUJAKU growls]
[HADAEBOU grunts]
[HADAEBOU groans]
[KUJAKU giggles]
Hadaebou!
[HIBIKI whimpers]
Hachirou!
[HIBIKI grunts]
Kouga Hachirou.
This is the end.
[JOUJIN]
Huh? What is this?
[RUI]
Ninja Technique...
...Butterfly!
[JOUJIN]
This won't stop me!
[JOUJIN whimpers]
Ninja Technique...
...Dreaming Reality...
[JOUJIN] You think
I'll fall for your illusions?!
Nonsense!
[yells]
How dare you?
You'll pay for the
ways you shamed me!
[groans]
This is a fraction of
the power you sought out,
so how does it suit you?
Joujin- sama ...
Joujin- sama !
[UTSUTSU]
Maybe now...
...I can show you
the vision I wanted...
[HACHIROU gasps]
[HIBIKI gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Joujin- sama , please
let me handle them!
I told you, you're too weak.
Know your master and obey!
Stand back, Kujaku!
[whimpers]
[gasps
[gasps]
Hachirou. Move aside.
Hibiki must pay for
her transgression.
And I guarantee her technique
won't work a second time.
[KUJAKU]
He honored me.
[gasps]
Far too highly.
Giving me a new name.
Calling me Kujaku
was his last gift.
So... I do this for you, Master!
[BOTH gasp]
[JOUJIN groans]
What are you doing?
You traitor!
Shut your mouth
and bleed out already!
[JOUJIN groans]
What is this?
Kujaku, why?
[KUJAKU]
Kujaku?
Each time you
call me by that name,
it sickens me to my stomach!
[JOUJIN grunts]
"Know your master and obey."
Those were your words,
weren't they, Joujin?
And so I shall!
I do this now, for the
glory of my master.
His Majesty,
who dubbed me "Kujaku."
My lord.
Ranmaru.
Lord?
[NOBUNAGA] That demonic
voice we just heard.
What are your thoughts
on its message?
[KUJAKU] I'm sorry to
tell you this, Master.
But your endless pursuit
of conquest is difficult
for the more simple-minded
to understand.
And so, my lord,
they've given you an epithet.
[NOBUNAGA]
Demon King of the Sixth Heaven?
[KUJAKU]
Yes, my lord.
[NOBUNAGA]
Hmm. Go on.
Lord.
Commoners and noblemen alike
are saying you're spreading
the flames of war across
this country like a demon.
That's why it
seems entirely possible,
that an actual demon has taken
an interest in your endeavors.
No.
I fear there's no other
possibility at all!
[NOBUNAGA]
You were always clever.
Come then, Ranmaru.
Help me commit seppuku.
[KUJAKU] I'll follow you
into death, my lord.
Do not.
But master, why hesitate?
[NOBUNAGA] Remember what
I've said in the past.
That I can take pride
in three things.
First, my white-spotted hawk.
Second, my pale songbird.
And third, my dear Ranmaru.
You honor your humble
servant too much, my lord.
[NOBUNAGA] My friend,
I have not a sliver of doubt
that if you were a bird,
you would be a peacock.
My very own "kujaku."
I know not when I shall return.
But while you yet live,
I'll ask this--
Will you keep your
brilliant wings spread?
Fanning the embers
of my conquest,
that the fire of my dream
will never die out.
Lord!
[yells]
[screams]
Well done, young warrior.
You fought valiantly.
Your voice is that of the demon.
[JOUJIN]
Hmm?
[KUJAKU]
If your words rang true,
then there's more
to my lord's fate.
But if you lied.
I'll become a devil
worse than you,
and plunge your rotten soul
to the depths of Hell.
I pledge myself,
to continue in the service
of the Demon King.
You'll become a devil.
--Why wait?
--[KUJAKU gasps]
[JOUJIN]
Your name, what is it?
Kujaku. That's my name.
Yes. I am Kujaku.
[KUJAKU]
I no longer need that name!
My true name is Ranmaru,
and the master I have
always served faithfully,
mighty Lord Nobunaga.
The one who called me by
that name will at last return!
So that's why.
[NOBUNAGA] Fifty years
of a mortal man's life.
Pass by in the breadth
of a vivid dream.
When held against the
scope of Heaven's history.
For once a man is born.
As with all things
in this world.
Mustn't he one day die?
[KUJAKU] I would expect nothing
less from you, Joujin- sama .
[KUJAKU] To think that
the blood of Kouga Hachirou
and Iga Hibiki was never needed.
That your blood alone
was more than enough!
[KUJAKU] Devouring a demon
shall open the path to conquest.
[KUJAKU] My master will
devour the blood of a demon,
and with it, return to life!
But why?
[KUJAKU laughs]
[heart beating]
[gasps]
So you've come...
At last, we meet in
person, Lord Nobunaga.
Welcome, Demon King.
With you made flesh,
you can finally bring
about a Hell on Earth.
Only then can true salvation
be brought unto the masses.
Let us bring my--
No, I mean our
desire to fruition
after such interminable waiting!
[JOUJIN grunts]
--[groans]
--[crackling]
[NOBUNAGA]
Silence.
--[skull shatters]
--[JOUJIN groans]
[JOUJIN] With true salvation
at hand after so long,
there is no further need for me.
[KUJAKU]
My master, welcome back.
It's me, my lord.
Your ever-faithful
servant, Ranmaru.
[gasps]
A repulsive sight.
[KUJAKU gasps]
Hachirou! Hibiki! We're leaving!
Namenba?
I'm ending this, right now!
What have you done?
[NAMENBA]
Hmph. Is that Nobunaga?
Well, isn't he a looker!
[BOTH grunt]
[NAMENBA] Maybe I'll see if he
wants to have some fun in Hell!
[MAGOROKU groans]
[MAGOROKU grunts]
[KUJAKU grunts]
[HACHIROU grunts]
[gasps]
The Halberd of Time?
[MAGOROKU grunts]
I will protect him!
You won't take my Master!
--[slashing]
--[KUJAKU grunts]
[NOBUNAGA]
Disgusting monster.
You would try to trick
the Demon King?
And to pick such
a hideous form to do so.
Claiming to be
the beauteous Ranmaru?
You fool.
A poor effort.
You are nothing at all
like my Ranmaru,
who was truly exquisite.
Like the peacock,
for which I named him.
[NARRATOR]
Let us stop this,
there's nothing else
to be done, Kujaku.
And as for your backward-flowing
corridor of time.
I must seal it within my
Adamantite Tower,
while I still can.