[MARIA] That was a close call.
Thanks for helping!
Anyway, my name's Maria.
And this is...
Call me Sizilien.
Heh. Nice to meet you,
my name's Shin.
Dirty scumbags like those guys
are just one more reason
I need to learn
some attack spells.
[SHIN] Spells? Are you a
student at the Magic Academy?
I will be if I pass the
entrance exam next month.
Sizilien's taking it too.
Gotcha, maybe I'll
see you two there.
[MARIA]
Huh?
I'm taking it as well.
Wait. What? As good
as you are at fighting,
you're training
to be a magician?
Both of us assumed that you must
be studying to become a knight.
[SHIN] Nope, I'm on
the same path as you.
Let's all do our best.
Dunno about you, but I'm
plannin' to take the top score,
so don't be a sore loser.
Best of luck. I guess I'm just
gonna take things slow.
Yeah, you don't seem like
the competitive type.
[SIZILIEN gasps]
Oh, uh. Your hand.
[SHIN]
Am I being too familiar?
I guess... I should shake it.
You seem a little
stressed out, Sizilien.
Nuh-uh. I don't know
what you mean.
Ahem. Um, let's do our best.
Yeah. Sure.
[MARIA] So what middle school
did you go to, Shin?
[SHIN] Nowhere you'd know.
I just moved to the capital.
Yeah? That reminds me!
Rumor has it that the Wise Man
Merlin and the Guru Melida
have come to stay
in the capital.
Oh yeah, I think I
might've heard something
about that as well.
What's with the tone,
don't you think they're cool?
Of course you do,
how could you not!
They're national heroes,
everyone loves them!
I get shivers when I
think of Merlin the Wise
using his great magic to
strike down the demonoid!
And Melida the Guru
is every girl's hero...
[SHIN] This is gonna
be the death of me.
Um. Are you all right, Shin?
[SHIN]
Yeah, I'm fine. Anyway, Maria.
You sure like Gran--
uh, the Wise Man and
the Guru, don't you?
Like is too weak a word!
I'm completely obsessed
with them actually.
Oh, and I hear their grandson's
taking the entrance exam, too!
[SHIN whimpers]
[MARIA sighs] I bet he's
as amazing as his grandpa!
And I'm so glad that
we're the same age!
[SHIN]
Well, I should get going.
[MARIA gasps]
You don't need to do that,
we can pay for ourselves.
[SHIN]
Nah, that's okay.
I'd be grateful if you
let me have this one.
[MARIA] I have to admit,
that guy's kinda cool.
[SIZILIEN]
Yeah.
He's good in a fight,
supposedly a magician,
and pretty unassuming to boot.
Yeah.
It's fine if I kiss him, right?
Oh good. Guess I'll take
him as my own, then.
Huh? Wait, no!
You can't do that!
[MARIA laughs]
[SIZILIEN gasps]
Maria!
Don't think I've ever seen you
act like this before, Sizilien.
[SIZILIEN groans]
What is it about him?
Don't give me that damsel
in distress nonsense.
"He saved me, it was
love at first sight!"
I wouldn't quite call it love
at first sight, but, I guess...
...I feel nervous,
which I normally hate.
My heart's pounding,
but I don't mind right now.
Also, my body feels really warm.
[MARIA] Good grief.
It's even worse than I thought.
[SHIN] Are they all here to
take the exam? I hope I pass.
It might mean getting to see
that girl Sizilien again.
Sweet! I'm gonna give
this all I've got!
[KURT] You're in
my way. Step aside.
[SHIN] Which room do I
report to? Ah, there it is.
I told you to step aside, twerp!
Out of my way!
[SHIN grunts]
Wh-What do you
think you're doing?
Release me at once, or else!
You're kidding me, right?
First, you grab my shoulder
without warning.
And then, you ask what
I think I'm doing?
Insolent fool!
I'll have you know that
I'm Kurt von Reitsburg!
Huh. I just go by Shin.
[STUDENTS laugh]
My point is that I
am the son and heir
of Count Rietsburg himself!
Good for you, I guess?
If you think you can defy me and
get away with it, you're wrong!
[AUGUST]
That's quite enough.
Your noble status is of
no value at this academy.
Should you attempt to leverage
it here, you will be punished.
That's not a school rule,
it's a royal decree.
Right. I know,
but this commoner...
[SHIN]
Who's this guy?
If you knew of this law
and ignored it,
you've defied the
royal family itself.
Wait. No. I-
Tensions are high all around.
Stop bothering people
and prepare for the test.
[KURT]
Yes, sir.
[AUGUST chuckles]
I like how you turned his
introduction around on him.
[SHIN]
Hm?
[AUGUST] Hm. You seem to be
as unworldly as I'd heard.
Huh?
My name's August.
August von Earlsheid,
to be more precise.
But all my friends
call me "Aug."
So your last name is Earlsheid?
Wait a sec! Ya mean
you're Uncle Dis's son?
[ALL gasp]
[AUGUST laughs]
"Uncle Dis's son," huh?
That's something I've
never been called before.
When people realize
that I'm the prince,
They usually start trying
to ingratiate themselves
in a hurry.
I don't care that you're
a prince, but if you're
Uncle's son, then in a way,
that makes us cousins.
[AUGUST laughs]
Know what? You're right,
let's call ourselves cousins.
I'm kinda confused,
but I'm glad something
about that made you happy.
All right, Shin. Let's watch
each other's backs in there.
[AUGUST laughs]
Is it just me,
or is Shin acting awfully
casual with Prince August?
I'm starting to wonder
who he really is.
Forget about Shin. It's Kurt
that I'm concerned with.
Why'd he have to go for
the same school as us?
[FEMALE EXAMINER A]
Pick your favorite target.
Once each of you has decided,
cast your best
magic spell at it.
You should use all
your strength.
Right!
[SHIN] I've never seen anyone
my age use magic before!
Wonder what he'll do.
All-consuming fire.
I call upon you!
[SHIN]
Huh?
[MALE EXAMINEE A]
Gather in my hands. Burn bright!
Fire ball!
[MALE EXAMINEE A]
Heh!
[EXAMINEES gasp]
[SHIN] I'm embarrassed
just from watching that!
[FEMALE EXAMINER A]
Okay, that'll do. Next!
Water. Flow! Whirl...
[SHIN] He's even goofier
than the last guy!
What's wrong with these people?
[MALE EXAMINEE C]
Dancing breeze. Come!
I call upon thee to raise up
a gust. To dance unrestrained!
Wind Storm!
[SHIN] After that much build-up,
that was all he could muster?
[FEMALE EXAMINEE A] Terra Firma,
great mother of all.
I beseech thee! Please lend me
your strength! Earth Blast!
[FEMALE EXAMINEE A exhales]
[SHIN]
Why does she look proud?
Ugh, what kind of self-deluded
magic recital is this?
Is something the matter? Because
if not, then you're up next.
Oh, uh. I'm good.
Good. His Majesty told me
about you in advance.
Please keep your
power under control.
It's imperative that you avoid
destroying the training room.
[SHIN]
C'mon, Uncle Dis.
What exactly did
you say about me?
[FEMALE EXAMINER A]
Use just enough power
to destroy the target,
understand?
[SHIN] Kinda hard to guess,
but here goes.
[EXAMINEES]
Huh?
Wait a second.
He didn't use a chant!
[ALL scream]
[FEMALE EXAMINER A]
I asked you to keep your power
under control, remember?
[SHIN] Well believe it or not,
I was holding back quite a bit.
That wasn't your full power?
Kay, in that case,
that was a fine showing.
[SHIN] Thank goodness.
She didn't get mad at me.
[MALE TEACHER A]
Is the Wise Man's grandson
actually that strong?
[FEMALE EXAMINER A]
Yes.
That settles who got the best
score on the entrance exam.
[STUDENTS chatter]
[AUGUST, SHIN chuckle]
[SHIN]
Here ya go.
[FEMALE RECEPTIONIST A]
Thank you. Let's see here.
Ah, so then you're
the Shin Wolford
I've heard so much about.
Sure am.
[FEMALE RECEPTIONIST A] Here's
your uniform and textbooks.
You'll notice that your
uniform's been enchanted
with defensive magic.
We ask that you students
refrain from attempting to add
to the enchantments on your own.
Would it be all right to modify
them if my granny helped out?
When you say "granny",
you mean...
Yeah. Melida the Guru, right?
I think we can
trust her judgment.
[SHIN] I'm'a give these
clothes a magic makeover!
Oh. By the way, Mr. Wolford,
you had the exam's
highest score this year.
So please write a speech to
give on your class's behalf
at the entrance ceremony.
[SHIN] Huh? Wait, you want me
to come up with a... speech?
Yes!
I am so not your man. Just think
about it, we've got Aug!
I mean, Prince August.
He should give the speech!
[AUGUST] Your words honor me,
but I couldn't possibly.
Earlsheid Magic Academy
is a place of rich,
time-honored traditions!
Whoever scores best has
to give that speech.
It's been that way since
the school opened!
Skill and knowledge are
what count at this academy.
Social rank is nothing.
I may be royalty, but here at
this school, I bow to you.
Break a leg.
[SHIN] This guy is
totally getting a kick
out of my suffering.
Aww, Looks like I fell
a bit short of getting
that top score I wanted.
Not bad, Shin.
He's not only a skilled fighter,
his magic's amazing too.
Are you sure that you don't
wanna go talk to him?
Um, for now, I think
I'd better wait.
I mean, I don't even know
what I'd say to him yet.
]You just need to get
out of your head.
You both did well at the exams,
that's something you
could talk about.
[SIZILIEN gasps]
[SHIN, SIZILIEN sigh]
[crashing]
[KURT] How dare they put me
in A. I should be S-Class.
It's insulting!
And what's worse,
that arrogant nobody
who insulted me
got the top score!
No way is he that good.
He cheated somehow,
he must have!
I'd be S-Class if not
for him, I'm sure of it.
He made me look bad.
He has to pay. He has to pay.
He has to pay!
[SHIN]
Hm. Its current enchantments
include Magic Defense,
Shock Suppression,
and Antifouling.
This is pretty
high-quality magic gear...
...but I'm still overwriting it.
[SHIN]
First, I'll need to nullify
the current enchantments.
My replacement needs
to be concise.
There's only room
for 20 characters.
I know I want to use
Antifouling, Auto-Healing,
and Magic Defense,
but the barriers I've pictured
up to now won't cut it.
I want this to be the
best gear I've made yet.
I need to change my mindset.
Blocking an attack takes
a lot energy, but what if
I dispersed it instead?
Now convert the magic
into kinetic energy...
I have done it!
Why are you shouting in
the middle of the night?!
[SHIN] Granny! Check out what
I just did to my uniform!
Can't this wait until morning?
[GASPS]
Wait... This is!
[horse neighs]
Be sure you tell no one
about the uniform you made,
all right Shin?
[SHIN]
Right. I get it.
[ALL gasp]
[MALE EXAMINEE A]
Look at those capes.
[FEMALE EXAMINEE A]
They're of the highest order.
[MALE EXAMINEE A'S MOTHER] Are
those two who I think they are?
[MERLIN grunts]
[STREET shouting]
It never gets old
for these people.
It's like they think
we're here on exhibition.
[SHIN grunts, yelps]
[sighs]
[AUGUST] Hey, Shin.
Nervous about your speech?
Nah. I should be okay.
Good, because my father,
the king, will be watching.
As will the rest of
the country's nobility
and leading figures.
We're all looking forward
to a great speech
from our new top student.
I see you.
You're tryin' to get back at me
for taking the top spot, right?
[ALL gasp]
[FEMALE EXAMINER A] Please
welcome our newest class.
[SHIN] Makes sense that
Sizilien's nobility, but Maria?
Who'd've seen that coming?
Keep your opinions to yourself.
[SIZILIEN giggles]
Without ado, A speech from
the new class's finest.
The top scorer on this
year's entrance exam.
Shin Wolford, welcome!
Thanks.
[gasps]
Did I hear that right?
That you did.
His last name's "Wolford."
He's the hero's grandson.
[BOTH]
Huh?!
[STUDENTS chatter]
My name is Shin Wolford.
Thank you for coming today.
I think I speak for
everyone in this class
when I say it's an
honor and a joy
to be welcomed into
this great institution
as our parents, guardians,
and friends look on with pride.
I'd also like to
thank the teachers
and current students
of this academy...
[ALFRED]
You made it. Well done.
I'm the S-Class's homeroom
teacher, Alfred Marcus.
I used to be a magician with
the court magic division.
Which means I'll also be
your Practical Arts teacher.
As for today, I'll lay out
the upcoming schedule,
and we'll call it good.
Hey. Do you have a minute, Shin?
[SHIN]
Hm? Uh?
[SIZILIEN whimpers]
[SHIN] Wait, some dude's
hounding you, Sizilien?
You're kidding me!
Shut up! You're being too loud!
Sizilien kept trying to
let him down nicely,
but now he's taking advantage
of his family's influence
to threaten her.
The guy sounds disgusting.
So who is he, anyway?
[MARIA]
He's a student at this school.
Seriously?
Sorry to spring this on you.
Thanks a lot for hearing me out.
Well yeah. Of course. And don't
be sorry. I'm glad you told me.
--[SIZILIEN exhales]
--[footsteps]
[SHIN]
Huh?
[KURT]
Hey, Sizilien!
How dare you talk with
another man in public!
Turn around at once,
you will look at me when
I'm speaking to you!
Wait, Kurt?
He's the guy.
[KURT]
Get over here!
[gasps] What do you
think you're doing?
I'll ask you the same question.
Sizilien is my betrothed, fool!
Stay away!
[SIZILIEN gasps]
He's lying, right?
Um. Well, he, uh...
You'll be okay.
Whatever happens,
I'll protect you.
[SIZILIEN]
Shin...
I have declined your proposal
multiple times now!
But you won't accept that!
You keep harassing me and
claiming we're engaged!
What? How dare you
talk to me like that?
If you don't like how I talk,
talk to someone else!
[growls, chuckles]
So it's gonna be like that.
If memory serves,
then your father's
a manager at the finance bureau.
Well, my father's the
undersecretary above him.
Maybe daddy and I
should have a word.
[KURT giggles]
[SHIN]
What a creep!
I've heard enough from you.
[KURT gasps]
Oh, Prince August!
[AUGUST] It seems you have
a terribly short memory.
[KURT]
Well, uh...
Frankly, That kind of threat
would be inexcusable
even if you weren't warned.
This is an affront
to the royal family.
Perhaps I should speak with
the finance bureau chief.
No... You wouldn't.
[AUGUST]
Walk away.
[KURT grunts]
All right, fine.
Thanks so much for helping,
Your Highness.
I was about to lose
my cool on that guy.
Yes. It sounded like things
were heading down an ugly path.
I would've cut in sooner,
but I just had to see
what you would do.
I'm glad you enjoyed the show.
"Whatever happens,
I will protect you."
[SHIN gasps]
Heroic is a good look for you.
Don't you think, Klode?
Oh, uh, if I had to answer,
then yes, he did look good.
Well there ya have it.
[SHIN] Damn. She is
still so friggin' cute!
[MARIA] So, do you think
Kurt'll leave her alone now?
[SHIN] Hm. Judging from
the look in his eyes,
I'd say you still
need to be careful.
[SIZILIEN exhales]
I know. You guys
wanna come over?
You mean to the home of
the Wise Man and the Guru?
I understand if
you're busy to--
[MARIA] No, no, no!
I'd love to come!
I have nothing going on tonight!
Just gimme some time to let my
parents know. Okay, Sizilien?
Yeah. Sure.
[SHIN, SIZILIEN chuckle]
I'll come as well. Think my
father's there right now.
[AUGUST grons]
It's nice to meet you.
We're his Highness' escorts.
[MERLIN]
You're running awfully late.
[MELIDA]
What have you been up to?
[SHIN] Sorry. There was
a bit of a situation.
Oh! Let me introduce
my new classmates.
As you might know, this is Aug,
Maria and Sizilien.
Those two are Thor and Julius.
It's a pleasure to make
your acquaintance.
Yup, I am very pleased to
meet you both! I'm Maria!
[SIZILIEN]
Um. Hello, I'm Sizilien.
--[MELIDA] Huh?
--[THOR] I'm Thor.
[JULIUS]
And my name's Julius.
[MERLIN]
Goodness. That's quite the tale.
[SHIN] So anyway, Granny.
For the sake of her safety,
I'd like to overwrite
the enchantment
on Sizilien's uniform.
[SIZILIEN gasps]
You wanna do what?
I'm confused.
Welcome to the club. You said
your name was Sizilien?
[SIZILIEN]
Uh, yes ma'am!
The enchantment Shin
wishes to give you
is exceptionally powerful.
It seems my grandson is quite
intent on keeping you safe.
Do you think yourself
worthy of his protection?
I hadn't really
considered that.
[SHIN] I think you're
making too much of this.
You be quiet.
Do you have any clue what's
become of your uniform, Shin?
Care to guess what
it's worth now?
I know that I improved it.
I would class it as national
treasure grade protective gear.
[ALL]
National treasure grade?!
[MELIDA] I can't even guess what
kind of price protective gear
of such enormous
power would fetch.
And Shin is offering to provide
you with your own free set.
So tell me, what makes you
worthy to receive such a gift?
I'm sorry. I'm kind of
nervous about responding.
But, I don't think I am worthy.
Huh?
I've taken advantage of
Shin's kindness. I see that now.
I told him about this because
I knew he'd try to help.
I preyed on his sympathy.
[ALL sigh]
[MELIDA]
Considering how strong he is,
I can understand why you'd
think to turn to him.
This doesn't involve Shin, but
he was still willing to help.
He said he would protect me.
I shouldn't have dragged him
into this, but it made me happy.
That's not fair! I was the
one who put you up to it--
I'm sorry for
the trouble, Shin!
I'll find a way to take
care of this myself.
I apologize to you
as well, Lady Melida.
--[MARIA] Sizilien!
--[MELIDA] Hold on.
Had you eagerly accepted the
gift without a second thought...
...mm, I think I would've
thrown you out of here.
[gasps]
[MELIDA] But you were honest.
With yourself, and with us.
Renouncing the chance to obtain
your very own national treasure.
That isn't something most
people could walk away from.
But, I tried to manipulate Shin!
[MELIDA] Oh honey.
You did more than try.
I think it's quite cute,
the way you turned to him.
And as for Shin's part, he
doesn't know what you've done.
Just look at him.
You've got the boy all
worked up on your behalf.
[SHIN gasps]
Yeah! I am worked up.
Sizilien, I don't feel like
you played me at all.
I offered to help you
of my own initiative.
[SHIN] So don't doubt
my intentions, okay?
You're welcome to use me
just as often as you want.
Do you mean that?
[MELIDA] I'm sorry for putting
you through that test,
but it was necessary.
I had to be completely sure
of your good intentions.
[SIZILIEN gasps, sobs]
[door clatters]
[MERLIN]
So, Shin.
[SHIN]
Yeah?
I just want it on
record that personally,
I had no idea the young
lady was trying to use you.
[SHIN]
Neither did I.
[MERLIN] But Melida saw right
through her. Good thing too.
If you'd gone ahead and
enchanted her uniform,
the poor girl's heart might've
been crushed by guilt.
I still don't feel
like my enchantments
are that big a deal.
They could change
the world, in my opinion.
But never mind that.
[SHIN]
Hm?
Seems like your grandma carries
the weight around here.
It's like I was
thin air just now.
Just try to stay strong, okay?
[MELIDA] I have to say. I really
am impressed by your honesty.
I don't think I was nearly
that honest at your age.
[SIZILIEN] When Shin stepped in
to save me, I was really happy.
But, even then, I felt guilty.
I don't wanna be
someone's burden.
[MELIDA] Shin doesn't have
a chance against this girl.
The letters are disappearing!
He's deleting them somehow?
It makes my head spin,
no matter how often I see it.
Yes, our Shin has
certainly grown, hasn't he?
[SHIN]
All done.
Is there anything
that you can't do?
This magic gear isn't
all that impressive.
First off, it needs at least
some magic input to activate.
Which means it can't protect
anyone against sneak attacks.
And the enchantment's
protection doesn't extend
past the uniform,
so your arms,
legs and head will
still be vulnerable.
[AUGUST]
Father. This is--
Yes, I'm well aware, son.
Forgive me, Shin, but listen.
This magic gear is outstanding.
No, it's far more than that.
If the world were to
find out about it,
there'd be hell to pay.
I ask that you tell no
one else about this.
[SHIN]
It matters that much?
If the military were to
find out it existed,
there could be those who
would wish to declare war.
You think this
could cause a war?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
It was reckless of me
to make these things.
[MERLIN gasps]
Wow! This is the first time
that Shin's had a regret!
That's true!
I just wanted you to
know what's at stake.
I was planning to perform
the same enchantments
on Aug's uniform.
But I should just stop.
I'm sorry, Aug.
[AUGUST]
Mm.
[DISEUM gasps] Well, hold on,
let's not be hasty.
A few more won't hurt, as long
as no one misuses them.
[SHIN]
I've enchanted everyone else's.
Are you sure you don't want one?
Yeah, the idea of wearing
a big mass of state secrets
kinda weirds me out.
[SIZILIEN] Thanks a lot, Shin.
When I wear this,
it almost feels as though
you're protecting me in person.
That thought makes me happy.
Y'know, that gives me an idea.
Starting tomorrow, how about I
take you home from school?
No. I wouldn't want to
trouble you more than I have.
[SHIN] It's all right.
We'll use a gate.
What's a gate?
[SHIN]
It's a little spell of mine.
[ALL gasp]
Step through and see.
[MARIA]
Where are we?
[SHIN] This is the house where
me and Grandpa used to live.
You're kidding.
I thought you told us that you
used to live deep in the forest.
Yeah, and that's where we are.
So we teleported?
I wouldn't exactly
call it teleportation.
I just bent space to
connect these two places.
I have no idea what
you're getting at.
[SHIN] I can only make gates
to places I've been before,
so we'd need to take a carriage
to your home at least once.
[SIZILIEN]
Oh. Okay.
All this craziness is starting
to give me a headache!
I'd heard you were
out of the loop,
but your nonchalance about
these things is boggling.
Maybe think before you
show us these spells.
Seems our top scorer flunks
when it comes to common sense.
Come on, is it really that bad?
[ALL]
Yes!
[SHIN]
Oh.
[SHIN chuckles]
I see.