[OFFICE WORKER A grunts]
All done.
[OFFICE WORKER B]
How's it comin' for you?
If you're finished,
you should join us for a beer.
[SHIN]
Sorry, I'm not even close yet.
You guys better go
on without me.
Good luck, man.
We'll see ya tomorrow.
Don't work all night, okay?
[OFFICE WORKER B]
So where should we go?
[OFFICE WORKER A]
I know a good dive bar.
[SHIN] This is taking ages.
Ehh, what do I care?
No one's waiting up for me.
After this, I can
either watch TV,
or try and finish up a game.
[SHIN grunts]
It's good to be out of there.
[OFFICE WORKER B]
You're all right. Just need to
flush out the system.
[SHIN] There sure are lots
of people in this world,
and they're all just like me.
[horn honking]
[MALE CITIZEN A]
Uh, s'cuse me.
Hey, Watch out!
[PEOPLE screaming, chattering]
[MALE CITIZEN B]
Call an ambulance!
[SHIN gasps]
[SHIN crying]
[CHICKENS clucking]
[SHIN chuckles]
[SHIN grunts]
[CHICKENS screech]
Oh yeah!
Caught myself some food!
[SHIN] My name's Shin Wolford.
And I just learned to hunt.
I live in this forest
along with my grandpa.
Have my whole life.
[SHIN pants]
[SHIN]
But I remember my last life.
I have memories of growing up
on a planet called Earth,
in a country called Japan.
I'm pretty sure I died there,
but I can't quite remember how.
[SHIN]
I'm home!
[MERLIN] Ah. So you are.
How was your hunt.
I'm eager to see the spoils.
[SHIN] This old man is
named Merlin Wolford.
Years ago, he found me in a
wrecked carriage in the woods
that had been
attacked by a demon.
I was just a baby,
and no one else survived,
so he took me in.
[MERLIN]
Ah! Three chickens and a boar.
[SHIN] Could'a got more but
you said not to overhunt.
[MERLIN]
Wind blade slashes.
That's an excellent
choice, my boy.
I feel like they're what's
best suited for hunting.
[SHIN] The biggest difference
between this world and Earth,
is that in this world,
magic's real.
My Grandpa's extremely
well‐versed in magic.
He's taught me a lot.
Good, now let's see how
your flames are coming.
Shin. Set that wood alight.
[SHIN]
Sure!
[SHIN] The magic in this world
works without any chanting,
you just have to visualize
what you want to create.
Whoa!
[SHIN] And honestly,
I'm pretty relieved about that.
From what I remember
of my past life,
chanting incantations and
calling out spell names
would have been a
little embarrassing.
[SHIN gasps] Granny Melida's
coming, and Michel's with her!
They're here for you.
My magic is a good start,
but you should study
swordsmanship
and magical gear, too.
Right!
[MELIDA]
You're hunting boar now?
Merlin! That's far
too dangerous, even for him!
[SHIN]
This is Melida Bowen.
She's a friend of Grandpa's,
and she comes to visit
us pretty often.
It's not really that dangerous.
Especially since I still have
the magic gear we made together.
There shouldn't be an
eight‐year old in this world
that can hunt down
a wild boar by itself.
But there is.
Oh, shut up!
Shin's exceptionally skilled
with magic, you know that.
Not to mention this forest has
practically been his backyard.
Sounds like your magic's gettin'
ahead of your combat skills.
That means it's time I
took off the kid gloves
for your training.
Uh, you don't have to do that!
[MERLIN, MELIDA, MICHEL laugh]
We're hunting a demon?
Well, I plan to do the fighting,
but now that you're ten I
think you should at least
see what they're like.
What are they like?
[MERLIN] Magic permeates
this whole world,
and all living creatures
can reap its benefits,
But some are unable
to keep the magic
they would use under control.
The powerful and
wildly violent being
this creates is
known as a demon.
Even a human being
can become one.
[SHIN] A person turned into
a demon a long time ago
and almost destroyed a
whole country, right?
Didn't you have to go
and save them, Grandpa?
So you're a big
hero there, even now.
[laughs] That was a
long time back, but yes.
Now let's start by
finding the demon.
How do we do that?
If you thinly spread your
magic power around yourself,
you can sense when
it comes into contact
with anything else's magic.
And since all living
creatures have magic,
you'll know what is
where right away.
This is known as search magic.
It's quite useful too.
Although, I should mention...
...t requires more finesse
than most of the spells
I've shown you.
[gasps]
[SHIN]
Wow, I can feel the magic
in all the creatures
of the forest.
I can even sense Granny
Melida back in her house!
[MERLIN] Hm. I knew
he could work it out,
but on his first try?
[SHIN gasps]
That sinister feeling.
What's it coming from?
Ah. Must be the demon.
You're sensing the magic
power that corrupted it.
We need to destroy it right now!
Won't something bad happen
if we just let it roam around?
Yes, but this is dangerous,
so I want you to be careful.
[SHIN pants]
[DEMON BEAR A growls]
[MERLIN, SHIN grunt]
That's what demons look like.
You're not going
one step further!
Shin, no!
[SHIN grunts]
[shouts]
[DEMON BEAR A growls]
[SHIN gasps]
[SHIN grunting]
[MERLIN gasps]
[SHIN]
Grandpa...? Grandpa?
[MERLIN]
Hm?
Did I do an okay job?
Hope I didn't mess things up.
[MERLIN] No, you did great.
Left me speechless for a moment.
That was a sight to behold.
I couldn't have
done better myself.
You mean it? So our demon
hunt was successful?
[MERLIN]
It certainly was!
Oh yeah!
Exactly what kind of enchantment
did you put on your
sword and boots?
Uh. Just the usual stuff.
You know...
[MICHEL] Shin took down
a demonized red grizzly?
Yes. He moved so fast
that I couldn't even help.
Shin's a prodigy. I've never
seen someone learn so fast.
He's already better with
magic than most adults.
He's keeping up with
Michel's combat training.
And he's memorized
countless enchantments
in the original tongue.
It's not inconceivable
that the boy really did
come from another world.
Shin's origins couldn't
mean less to me.
All that matters is that when he
looks up and calls me "Grandpa,"
I can't help but adore him.
Blood or no, he is
still my grandson.
I can't believe I'm hearing
this from the man once known as
the Lord of Destruction.
[MERLIN]
Why must you dredge up the past?
Is my embarrassment
that amusing?
Let's just say the
title of wise man
seems to suit you better.
[MELIDA] I adore that boy every
bit as much as you do, Merlin.
I'm not able to visit
as much as I'd like,
but I think of him as if
he were my grandson too.
[MERLIN gasps]
[swords clanging]
[MICHEL]
That's enough for today.
How's your training
coming along?
[SHIN] Michel's been going
really hard on me lately.
[MERLIN] Yet it looks to me
like you're keeping up with him.
Anyway, Shin.
[SHIN]
Huh?
I have something
I need to tell you.
Wait a sec, you're saying
I'm not really your Grandson?
[MERLIN]
Hm. My apologies, Shin.
I should've told
you much sooner.
[SHIN] Thing is,
I already know that.
This must've been
the work of a demon.
There's no saving them, but I
can give them a decent burial.
‐‐[SHIN cries]
‐‐[MERLIN gasps]
What is that, a crying infant?
[MERLIN]
How'd you survive?
[MERLIN gasps] Could this
be providence at work?
Your temperature had
dropped from the rain,
maybe that's why the
demon missed you.
But frankly, I wonder
if it wasn't the same‐‐
No.
[SHIN] Could it have
been that red grizzly?
Shin.
I was just thinking
it's possible, ya know?
If it was...
...well, it's nice
to think that maybe
I got to avenge my parents.
There's a chance
you did just that.
So uh, do you have any
idea who my parents were?
Their possessions
were nondescript,
and their bodies were both
ravaged beyond
recognition, so no.
Oh well.
[MERLIN] You're taking
this news rather well.
[SHIN] Hm. Well, I know
they were my parents,
but I don't remember them.
Also, I've always had
a great Grandpa.
[MERLIN]
Oh, uh...!
[SHIN]
And on top of that,
I've got Granny Melida,
and Michel too.
I've just never felt like
I was missing anything.
[MERLIN]
Shin...
[SHIN]
Listen, Grandpa.
I wanna tell you
how grateful I am.
Thanks for taking me in.
I'm really glad you did.
Oh, Shin, I...
Come on, stop crying Grandpa,
it's embarrassing!
I'm... just so happy!
[SHIN] But really though.
Thanks, Grandpa.
[DISEUM] Ahem.
Shin, the grandson of our hero,
Master Merlin,
has just turned 15,
and is to be regarded as a
man from this day forward.
[SHIN]
Hm.
A toast to the
young man's 15 years,
and to the many years
ahead of him. To Shin!
[ALL]
To Shin!
It's hard to accept that
the little baby I once knew
has grown into a man.
It happened much faster
than we thought.
I was meaning to ask. Where do
you plan to go from here?
I dunno.
You're free to pursue
your dreams now.
The first step is deciding
what you wish to do.
Well. For one thing,
I've never actually gone
beyond the forest.
So to start off, I might
go visit a nearby town.
[DISEUM]
I see. And then what?
Should there be more?
What do you wanna become?
Since you learned how to fight
from Sir Michel himself,
I'd imagine you could
join the royal order.
You could also do well
as a demon hunter.
[MICHEL]
Mm‐hmm.
[SHIN] I didn't know demon
hunting was a profession.
Yes, there's actually
a group called
the Demon Hunter's Society.
They have a system through
which hunters get rewards
for their victories.
[SIEGFRIED] Wow. You haven't
even heard about them?
No. I haven't thought
about jobs much.
You could also do pretty well
enchanting and
selling magic gear.
Or if the working life isn't
your style, you could always
use those looks to get a
girlfriend to support you.
Luckily he isn't sick
enough in the head
to think in those terms.
‐‐Say what?
‐‐Did I stutter?
Oh. Yeah.
Now that I'm an adult, I guess I
need to start making money,
not to mention, I need
to learn how to use it.
Hold on a moment.
You mean, you've never
gone shopping before?
Nope, can't say I have.
[ALL gasp]
You're kidding. Merlin!
I may have forgotten to teach
him some common practices.
[ALL]
What?
Come to think of it, I don't
really know much of
anything aside from how
to fight and use magic.
Eh. I'm sure it'll all work out.
[DISEUM gasps]
Amazing.
How'd we come so far
in the blink of an eye?
[SIEGFRIED]
Did we teleport?
[MERLIN] Yes, Shin made
the spell himself.
A spell like that
could transform
the world's supply chains,
communication,
even the way people think.
As if it wasn't amazing
enough that he mastered
all the magic Merlin
and I taught him.
I'm enjoying the walk and all,
but is there some reason
you brought us out here?
Yes, to ensure our safety,
I thought it best that we
do this in a place
without much around.
Safety?
[MERLIN laughs]
I've already seen this myself.
I'd advise all of you
to brace yourselves.
[ALL]
Huh?
[MERLIN] Shin. Show them
an attack spell.
Treat this like it's
one of your tests.
Yeah, sure.
How about a fire spell?
[ALL]
Huh?
[MERLIN chuckles]
[SHIN] First, visualize the
flames, then create a spark.
As long as there's oxygen,
this creates a small flame.
I've never seen such a pale
blue flame in my whole life!
[SHIN] Isolate more
oxygen and hydrogen.
Encase the mixture, sealing it
from surrounding air,
and ignite it from the
flashpoint on impact!
[ALL shout]
That's all I got right now.
[ALL gasp]
[SHIN]
Are... you guys okay?
[MELIDA]
What's wrong with you, Merlin?
You taught the boy
all manner of magic
but not an ounce of prudence!
[MERLIN] If he didn't
have any prudence,
he'd be making explosions
like that at the house!
I just wanted to see what
my grandson could do.
Is that so wrong?
Why don't you ask the crater
he left in the country‐side?!
[SHIN]
Please calm down, Granny.
It's not good for your heart
to get this worked up.
And whose fault is it
that I'm this worked up?!
[DISEUM] Between that fire spell
and his teleportation magic,
I'm concerned about setting
Shin loose on the world.
And don't forget that Michel
trained him in close combat.
Neighboring lands
would do anything
to get him on their side.
[MICHEL] Hm. This is
bound to spark conflict.
[SHIN]
So it's bad that I'm strong?
Master Merlin. Your grandson's
abilities could be enough
to upset the balance of
power in the whole region.
And on top of that,
he's utterly ignorant as
to how this world works.
[DISEUM] If we send him
into the world as is,
it'll spell disaster. Imagine if
an expansionist nation
like the empire learned of him.
Yes, I see your point.
[DISEUM]
But there is an alternative.
Enroll Shin in
the magic academy,
as a starting point to
learn of the world.
Huh?
It almost sounds as if you
wish to use Shin's power
for your own
country's purposes.
[DISEUM] I would never exploit
Shin for military use.
I've always thought
of him as my nephew.
I've no wish to involve him
in our nation's disputes.
Hold on, what's the
magic academy?
It's a school of magic
in the royal capital.
Those students who prove to
be exceptional at magic
in middle school, are invited
to continue their studies there.
If you were to attend yourself,
you would discover just how far
off the scale you are.
[SHIN]
Wait. Am I really off the scale?
[DISEUM] Not to mention,
you haven't had the chance
to be around people
your own age before.
This could be a good opportunity
for you to make some friends.
That is persuasive, but what
are your thoughts, Shin?
Sounds good. I think I might
enjoy going to school.
Then I'll make arrangements
back at the academy.
Your classes are determined
based on how you perform
at the entrance exams,
naturally.
My nation's magic academy
is under absolutely
no influence
from the nobility,
and it operates on an
extremely strict merit system,
so I can't show
you any favoritism.
Not that you would need it.
I'm kind of confused here.
What do you mean when
you say "my nation?"
[DISEUM] Oh. I guess I never
mentioned that, did I?
I'll start with my name.
In full, it's Diseum
von Earlsheid.
And I'm the monarch of
the Kingdom of Earlsheid.
[SHIN]
My Uncle Dis is a king?
So then what about my big
sis Chris and big bro Sieg?
I'm a member of the
Order of the Royal Guard.
And I'm here now as
His Majesty's escort.
And I'm a veteran magician with
the Court Magic Division.
Also here as an escort.
Huh? Big sis Chris I can
understand, but big bro Sieg?
There's no way!
[SIEGFRIED]
What does that mean?
Guess we can add a keen eye
to Shin's list of traits.
Just keep on
runnin' your mouth.
Don't worry,
I fully intend to!
[SHIN]
What about you, Michel?
Huh? Oh, I'm retired actually.
But I used to be Knight
Commander of the Order.
[SHIN]
Why didn't anybody tell me this
when I met them the first time?
You really haven't told him
a thing about this world,
have you?
My mistake.
I still don't get why a
king would be a houseguest
of my Grandpa's.
I'm sure you've heard the tale.
Of Master Merlin's fight?
When he defeated
the demonoid man.
Yeah, Grandpa told
me about it himself.
It was Earlsheid
the fiend attacked.
This was the first demonoid
that we'd ever seen.
And everywhere it went,
it left death.
Two subjugation
squads had fallen.
What's more, a whole city
had been wiped off the map.
In the midst of the crisis,
the nation had to
draft its students.
And I, then the Crown Prince,
and a student of
the magic academy,
ignored all objections
and volunteered to join
a subjugation squad. But then...
[CHIEF A]
Your Highness! Run!
[DISEUM gasps]
[DISEUM] Just as the demonoid
was about to take my life...
[DISEUM yells]
[gasps]
I'd step back, kid,
it's rather dangerous here.
[DISEUM]
...I was saved.
By Merlin and Melida,
in the nick of time.
Melida fought beautifully:
graceful and bewitching
with her magical gear.
And Merlin was a
force of nature,
ferocious and unrelenting.
What a sight they were.
I can't express how great
my admiration for them was.
[SHIN]
Bewitching and ferocious?
We were full of
youthful excess.
I can still do a little
bewitching when I feel like it.
[DISEUM] After these two
put down the demonoid,
they were named
heroes for delivering
our nation from crisis.
And since that day,
we've shared a friendship
that went beyond
our stations.
Mostly I like coming here so
I can belly‐ache about work.
[SHIN]
I see. Wait, belly‐ache?!
[DISEUM laughs]
You've learned that I'm a king,
yet you aren't treating
me any differently.
Thing is, proper royal
etiquette is another thing
Grandpa forgot
to teach me.
Not to worry! You're one
of the only people
I can have a conversation
this relaxed with,
so make sure you
never change, Shin!
Yeah, well anyway.
The real surprise here is
that Grandpa and Granny
formed a party once.
Those two did a lot more
than form a party.
They used to be
husband and wife.
[SHIN]
Huh? Huh? Huh?! For real?!
We're almost to the capital.
[MERLIN, MELIDA grunt]
[SHIN]
So hey, Grandpa.
What's your house at the
capital like, is it big?
[MERLIN]
I don't quite remember.
It was bestowed upon
me by the country,
so I think it was large.
[SHIN] At least we've got
other‐dimensional storage space
for the move‐in, right?
And listen, Granny, I know
you weren't all that keen on
coming to live with us,
but I'm really glad you
decided to do it anyway.
I had no choice, I mean
it's not like I could
leave everything up to
this doddering old man.
[gasps] Look! The capital walls!
[MALE GUARD A]
Do you have identification?
[MERLIN]
Certainly, will this do?
[MELIDA]
Right here.
[yelps] Merlin the Wise man
and Melida the Guru?
I can't believe it!
Wait, the wise man's here?
And the Guru?
No way!
Where are they,
let's find them!
[MERLIN] Pardon, but could I ask
that you finish this up quickly?
[MALE GUARD A]
Y‐Yes sir. I'm terribly sorry!
Um, who might the
young master, be?
Master?
You may call him Shin Wolford.
He's my and Melida's grandson.
[MALE GUARD A]
Master Shin!
[TOWN]
It's huge.
‐‐[gasps]
‐‐[door creaks]
[STAFF]
We bid you all welcome home.
Masters Merlin and Shin,
Mistress Melida.
Uh, hi there.
My name is Steve.
I'm your head butler.
My name is Marika.
I'll be your head maid.
And I'm Koller,
your head chef.
[STEVE]
If you require something,
you need but ask and
we'll make it yours.
What gives with the
sudden VIP treatment?
I would imagine Diseum
sent them here
once he knew we were coming.
I'm starting to remember
why we don't like to visit.
[SHIN]
Huh?
Melida and I can
handle things here,
why don't you go
explore the town a bit?
Okay, will do.
[SHIN]
Um, is this enough?
[SHIN] That was my first
time buying something.
I might be lost.
[SIZILIEN]
Please let us go!
[SHIN gasps]
[MARIA] Seriously, get away
from us, you creeps!
Ooh, scary. Stop with
the harsh words.
The boys and I just wanna
have a little fun with ya.
[MALE HUNTER B] This could be
fun for you too if you let it.
Hell, it might even feel good.
[SHIN]
These guys are walking clichés.
[SHIN] Uh, excuse me.
Are these guys bothering you?
They are! We're extremely
frickin' bothered!
Are you tryin' to
start something' kid?
I bet he thinks he's
some kinda hero.
We risk our lives every day
to protect these ladies
by hunting demons,
so we're the real heroes.
So you guys hunt demons.
While I have to admit, that does
sound like a noble line of work,
If you hunt girls too,
then you're just a
bunch of scum‐bags.
What did you just
call us, punk?!
Die!
[SHIN]
So slow.
[MALE HUNTER A]
You little‐‐!
[MARIA, SIZILIEN gasp]
You all right? Hope they
didn't hurt you.
We're fine, but what about you?
That guy pulled a dagger!
Yeah, but luckily for me,
he didn't know how to use it.
[SIZILIEN] Um. Thank you
so much for helping us.
I'm really grateful.
[gasps]
[SIZILIEN]
Huh?
Are you sure you're okay?
How? How are you so cute?
♪