[yawns]
[SHIN] What happened last night
was burned into my retinas,
so I barely slept at all.
[gasps]
[BOTH whimper]
Oh. Hi, Shin, I didn't see you!
Good morning, Sizilien!
Um, anyway, we should get
to the dining hall now.
If we don't hurry,
our breakfast'll get cold.
[SIZILIEN]
Right, that's a good idea!
Oh, and by the way, Shin.
Um, do you have some time?
You see, I need to
ask you for a favor.
[SIZILIEN] I apologize
for asking something
this important of you so
early in the morning, Shin.
But if we'd waited too long,
then my father would
have been at work.
That's fine. If I'm coming
to meet your folks,
then they should
both be here, right?
[SIZILIEN sighs]
Yes!
[SHIN] But despite what we said,
when it came down to it...
Alright. So, what were
you wanting to tell us?
If you interrupted
your training camp
to make the trip all
the way back to us,
it must be something
terribly important.
[gulps]
Well, um...
Sizilien has given me the
great honor of dating her.
So, now that you know,
I ask for your blessing,
if you wouldn't mind.
[BOTH gasp]
Young man.
[SHIN]
Yessir?
[CECIL] Thank you!
From the bottom of my heart,
I'm so grateful that you would
choose my dear Sizilien!
[SHIN]
Huh?
[SIZILIEN gasps]
Oh my! This is a wonderful day,
and it's just morning!
Who could've guessed we'd
receive such great news?
Please, darling!
[CECIL]
Hm? Yes? What's wrong?
Sit down. You're too eager.
Oh. Right.
[EILEEN] Before I accept your
relationship with my daughter,
there's one question I'd like
to ask you. Do you mind?
[SHIN]
Sure. Ask away.
[EILEEN] This family is a
noble one, a viscountcy.
Sizilien may be our
third daughter,
but still, the next step
is extremely imperative.
What do you mean when
you say "next step"?
I mean marriage.
[SIZILIEN gasps]
[EILEEN] I'm not talking
about right away.
But, the daughter of a viscount
should not be permitted
to date without being
formally engaged, you see.
[chuckles] Luckily, it looks as
though you're prepared for that.
Yes.
Do you mean it?
[EILEEN]
Congratulations, dear.
[gasps]
It appears that your longtime
wish has been granted.
[SIZILIEN gaps]
Thank you, Mother! I'm so glad!
But wait a minute!
Don't say those things
in front of Shin!
[grunts]
[shouts]
Not too shabby, Thor.
Same goes for you.
What's that magic?
Everyone is so powerful!
A nice effort, you guys.
Guess that's enough warmup.
Warmup?!
[MERLIN chuckles] Well, ladies?
How is the observation going?
You're welcome to try
for yourselves, if you'd like.
[BOTH gasp]
I do appreciate the kind offer,
but I'll have to decline.
I'm afraid I haven't the
slightest aptitude
for magic technique.
Please, sir! Can I try?
Of course. Why don't we
start off by teaching you
to master basic magic control?
[MAY]
Oh wow, this is so incredible!
Just look at all that power!
[MERLIN] Ah, that's quite
an impressive skill
you've got there!
Indeed, especially for
someone of your age.
You know, May, I think
you have some real
potential as a magician.
[MAY chuckles]
Princess May's really
good at magic, huh?
I wonder if she'll turn out
to be better than us?
I won't be outdone! Watch me!
[laughs]
Well, I'm glad her natural
talent inspires you
to work hard! Whoa! Easy, Lyn!
I think you're working
a little too hard there.
[LYN yelps]
[MELIDA laughs]
It's not my fault.
I tried to warn you.
See? Keep at it, you two.
If you don't apply yourselves,
I guarantee you little May is
going to surpass you someday,
in more ways than one.
[BOTH] When you say "more ways
than one," is that...?
[MAY giggles]
[LYN, ALICE]
You're dead!
[MAY whimpers]
What makes you want to
take cover behind Shin?
Your own big brother's
right here, you know.
[SHIN, MAY]
Hm?
It appears, some punishment
might be in order.
Uh-oh! Please protect me,
big brother Shin.
He looks really scary!
How did I get wrapped up
in this weird family drama?
I'm just kidding.
Are you, though?
[SCHTROM]
Miria.
I trust everything is
progressing smoothly?
Because of the many caravan
attacks along the roads,
cities throughout the empire
are facing food shortages.
Discontent is
increasing each day.
Well, then I would say the
ideal time is finally upon us.
[SHIN grunts] So, why are you
guys being extra cautious?
[YURI]
Because of you, Wolford!
You're experimenting with
new magic, aren't you?
Yeah, and the last thing
that I wanna do
is get blown away by
some crazy spell!
Better safe than sorry.
May. I want you to stay behind
me this time, understand?
Okay...
[SHIN chuckles]
[SHIN] This one isn't going
to be that dangerous, guys.
[AUGUST]
Define "Dangerous".
[SHIN] It's not even attack
magic. I promise, it's fine.
[AUGUST]
Oh, okay then.
[ALL gasp]
[THOR] He's collecting so
much power. It's extraordinary.
Uh... And you're positive
this isn't dangerous, correct?
[SHIN] Oh! That's great!
It actually worked!
[ALL gasping]
Excuse me, but exactly what
kind of technique is that?
It's floating magic.
Anti-gravity, or, I guess,
to use simpler terms,
it's like falling,
but the opposite way.
As per usual, I have no idea
what you're going on about,
but it's safe to assume you're
doing something amazing,
because that's kinda your thing.
[SHIN] No, this is the
truly amazing part.
[ALL]
Huh?
[SHIN] Casting floating magic
on myself to move upward.
While using wind magic to
travel from side-to-side.
[SHIN laughs] Hey, this is
kind of fun! Check it out!
[SHIN] There, another
successful experiment!
Of course. You're always
so over-the-top.
Nuh-uh! Schtrom used
the same trick.
I'm only doing it so
that I can counter him.
Oh, Shin! You're great!
Big brother Shin! I want to
fly around like that, too!
Teach me how, pretty please!
Uh. I don't think that's
such a good idea!
What do you mean?
Don't do it right now,
at least.
Why not?
Because if you do, then
everyone'll see your panties!
[MAY shouts]
[groans]
[MERLIN] What? You've already
gotten engaged?
[SHIN]
Yeah, we have.
I'm sorry I didn't tell
you about it sooner!
It was all my fault, sir!
It's just that...
...I couldn't wait to tell my
parents we were together.
Oh, no. It's nothing you
need to apologize for.
Well, that's that. Though it
was only a matter of time,
so I can't say that
I'm surprised.
[BOTH gasp]
However, before you go public
with your engagement,
there is one matter you'll
have to settle first.
[BOTH]
Hm.
My dear. I know it's late,
but I must pay a visit
to your parents.
Whoa, Granny! You're gonna--?
[MELIDA]
Mm.
My! The Wise Man and the
Guru right in my own parlor!
To what do I owe such
an unexpected honor?
Normally, we wouldn't
visit at this late an hour,
but time is of the
essence here.
There's something we must
discuss with the two of you.
[MELIDA] Now then. I believe
that sums it all up.
I see. So Shin here...
Right, he's not my actual
grandson by blood.
[gasps]
[SHIN grunts]
With all due respect,
we're glad to hear you
approve of their union.
And forgive me if I'm wrong,
but I assume that was because
you thought that we
were his grandparents.
Though, now you know that
there's no biological relation.
Regardless of that, they're
quite fond of each other.
Will you still allow it?
[sighs]
Milady. Master Merlin.
I have to say I'm upset...
[grunts]
I thought so. Very well.
There's nothing
we can do now.
...that you would
view us this way.
That is what upsets me!
[BOTH gasp]
We accept Shin,
not because we believed
he was your grandson,
but because of something far
more important than that.
He values Sizilien
more than anything
and does his best
to protect her.
It's because of the kind of man
he is that we approve of him
as a husband for our daughter.
I believe he's
what's best for her.
Yes, and I wholeheartedly agree.
[BOTH gasp]
I apologize for making
assumptions about you.
I hope you'll forgive me.
It's alright!
Please don't give it
another thought, Lady Melida!
Oh, and Shin.
I feel the same way.
I like you for you!
After all, when we were
first getting acquainted,
I had no idea you were
the Wise Man's Grandson!
[SHIN sighs]
Thank you, all of you.
I'm so happy.
And I promise you this.
I'll always protect Sizilien!
Right. I trust you.
Keep her safe... for life.
Grandpa. Thanks a lot
for taking me in.
I've said it before,
but I'm serious.
I'm so glad we're family.
You're the best.
Shin...
Granny. I'm really
grateful to you, too.
You may get mad at me a lot,
but I'm happy to have you,
you know that?
Oh, Shin, you're making
me so emotional!
[BOTH chuckle nervously]
[SHIN]
Wow. You guys look great!
So, the defensive magic you used
to enhance all of these garments
is supposed to make them
more protective, right?
[SHIN] Yep! Plus I added
"optical camouflage"
to help you blend in,
and "cozy temperature"
to make it so they'll never
be too hot or too cold.
Let me get this straight.
They're national treasure grade,
but you made all
these improvements?
[SHIN]
Right!
[MARIA groans]
So despite everything,
I'm still walking around wearing
a bunch of state secrets.
[SHIN] Oh, and I didn't end up
doing anything to the footwear.
At first I thought about making
them into jet boots like I did
with mine, but those
tend to be a little bit
difficult to operate.
[AUGUST] So, with these
clothes and the accessories
we received before, our defenses
are essentially perfect.
Which means whatever's
in store today,
it must be incredibly dangerous.
[SHIN chuckles]
You guessed it!
[ALL gasp]
[SHIN] I've been thinking
it's time we did some
combat training.
[ALL]
Huh?
We'll be taking down a
Catastrophic-class demon.
What? Catastrophic-class?
There's no way we'll survive!
I promise you,
everything'll be fine!
You've all gotten strong enough
to hold your own out there.
And besides, you're wearing
maxed-out protective gear.
It'll be pretty hard for
anything to hurt you in those.
[GIRLS groan]
It's so mean of you guys
to leave us behind!
Why don't you just let
us tag along with you?
Today is real combat training.
I refuse to expose you to the
slightest bit of danger.
[MARIA]
Sorry, Princess.
But you'll have to wait
in your room, okay?
[MAY whines]
Stop throwing a tantrum.
Hey, I know!
[SHIN]
Here, May. Take this.
What is it? Food?
[SHIN]
A magical communication item.
It's enchanted with
"transmit-and-receive sound"
magic.
When you talk, you hold
it like this. See?
Why don't you give it a try?
Hello? May? What's up? Hear me?
Yes, I do! Loud and clear!
[SHIN]
See? Told you.
Look at that.
Another cool gadget.
Yeah. It'll help us
with gathering intel.
Nice, huh?
You should hang onto this so you
can talk to us while we're away.
It's magical gear, so it'll
be good practice for you!
You're right!
Oh, come on.
[MAY]
Look, Lady Melida!
Shin made something
really neat for me!
Uh-oh.
I see you've made another
unprecedented magic item!
A device that remotely
transmits a person's voice
is something that's barely
been dreamt about!
And now you go and whip
one up like it's nothing!
Why, if enough people got word
that such a thing had been
conjured, disputes about the
right to its usage would break
out all over the land!
Don't be so irresponsible!
Hello? You'd better not be
ignoring me, young man!
Wait! What is that?
I'm guessing you feel it too?
Yes. Some large presence.
[SHIN] Hm. We're picking
up a Catastrophic-class.
Unlike the tiger,
which is pretty swift,
the lion is stronger,
but slower-moving.
Which means?
Um, that we should
attack it from a distance?
[SHIN] Correct! You sure
know your stuff!
[ALL groan]
[SIZILIEN, SHIN yelp]
[SHIN] Anyway. Julius.
Yuri. Mark. Sizilien. Olivia.
You five will go first.
But they're all more suited
to supportive positions.
Are you sure that's wise?
Yeah, I think they'll be more
than a match for this thing.
[OLIVIA whimpers]
Don't worry. Just have
faith in Wolford.
[OLIVIA sighs]
[LION roars]
Alright! Ready?
[SHIN]
Fire!
[OLIVIA]
[roars]
[All exhale]
[chuckles]
Oops. Guess we overdid it.
Um, but Shin. I'm lost.
What happened to the lion?
You defeated it. Wiped the
thing clean off the map.
Wait, so we just took down
a Catastrophic-class?
[SHIN] The support magicians
managed this as a team.
But since the rest of you
specialize in attack spells,
I'm sure any one of
you could do it.
[BIG CAT roars]
[shouts]
See? You did it!
Yeah, guess we did!
The question is, though,
should we have done it?
I think you did the best
out of all of us, Tony!
That vibration sword was
all like, "whoosh, gotcha"!
Hold on. When did you
acquire that thing anyway?
Oh, it's from Shin.
He thought that I might get
some good use out of it,
so he lent it to me.
I want to use it!
That's not fair!
Okay, well take
it up with him!
Good. It looks like
everybody in the group
has advanced to the next level.
Uh?
That's right, and now
it's your turn.
[SHIN]
Huh? Oh, yeah.
It's almost time for your
big engagement party.
Can't wait to see you there.
[SHIN grunts] I have no
idea what this thing
is even supposed to look like.
--[knocking]
--Uh, it's open!
[gasps]
Wow.
Um. Hi, Shin. Something wrong?
[SHIN]
Oh, no! I'm fine.
You look really
cute, that's all.
Oh. Well, thanks so
much for saying that.
And you! So handsome!
[SHIN]
Yeah? You think?
Definitely! And do you really
think that I look that cute?
Yeah. You're beautiful.
My heart's pounding!
[SIZILIEN sighs]
Oh, Shin.
Sizilien.
[EILEEN]
Ahem. That's enough, you two.
It's clear that
you like each other.
Now, hurry and make your
way over to the dining room,
if you please.
[SIZILIEN, SHIN giggle]
[ALL clapping]
[DISEUM] Now. Does everyone
have a glass for the toast?
My dear nephew, Shin Wolford,
and Sizilien von Klode.
I am here this evening, to bear
witness to your engagement
and to celebrate
your joyous union.
As ruler of the proud
Kingdom of Earlsheid,
I hereby deliver
this declaration.
I wish you both great happiness!
Now, let us raise our glasses,
and toast the couple!
[ALL]
Cheers!
[SHIN]
Whew. That's over.
You made it through, Shin!
I'm glad!
And now, things are going
to settle down, aren't they?
No. I have one more thing
that I need to do.
[SIZILIEN]
Hm?
Sizilien?
[SIZILIEN]
Yes? What is it?
[SHIN] I'm sorry for doing
this in the wrong order.
[gasps]
[SHIN] And I know our engagement
party is already over...
...but, hey, here goes.
Will you please marry me?
[SIZILIEN sighs]
Yes. Of course!
I would be honored
to be your bride.
[SIZILIEN sisgh] Oh, goodness.
This is... wonderful!
Sizilien...