[HERALD]
No. What's the meaning of this?
According to Zest's intel,
earlsheid had its hands full
putting down a massive
outbreak of demons!
If that were true,
the kingdom would've been
in no position to oppose us!
So why did we find what looked
like the entire royal army
waiting for us at the border?
Our troops suffered extensive
casualties in the ambush,
Your Majesty.
I think our best course of
action would be to pull back
and regroup for now.
[HERALD growls]
[MALE STAFF MEMBER A gasps]
Never mind that.
What became of Zest?
I've words for him.
Bring him to me!
[MALE STAFF MEMBER A] Apologies.
But he left at the head
of a scouting party
yesterday evening.
There's been no
sign of them since.
[HERALD gasps]
That settles it,
he must've betrayed
me and then fled!
The audacity. I didn't
think the commoner would
dare pull his grimy
wool over my eyes!
When next we cross paths,
I swear by my own throne,
I'll order that traitor
drawn and quartered!
[MALE MESSENGER A]
I bring a message!
Huh? Then spit it out.
Um, as you say!
It's from home.
A swarm of demons have
appeared in the capital!
Impossible! Our reports said
there were far too few demons
in the Empire to be a threat.
Please, hear me. This is much
more important than the war.
We must hurry back to the
capital with all haste!
[HERALD] Right! Relay this
to all our forces!
We shall return to the
capital immediately,
and drive out the
demonic intruders!
[ALL STAFF]
Yes, Majesty!
[RUPERT] The imperial forces
have begun to fall back.
[DOMINIC] Makes sense, with the
number of men they've lost.
Though I half-expected yet
another foolhardy attack.
So what now?
Should we pursue them all the
way back to their homeland?
Why not? We owe them no mercy,
considering how they
attacked us unprovoked.
[footsteps]
[MALE MESSENGER B]
I have a report, sir!
It's about the advance guard.
They were chasing the foe
and got ambushed by demons!
[DOMINIC]
What?!
The demons are blocking
our path forward.
We can't continue our
pursuit while they live.
Strange. What could it mean?
Are the demons deliberately
assisting the Imperial retreat?
--[LION ROARS]
--[MALE CITIZEN A gasps]
[FEMALE CITIZEN A screams]
[SCHTROM]
How does it feel, Miria?
Are you taking to
life as a demonoid?
Yes. I'm filled with an
incredible amount of power.
Far more than I've
ever felt before.
[SCHTROM]
It pleases me to hear that.
Listen. The Imperial army
should make it back soon.
Two to three days from now.
Luckily, Zest and the others
should return ahead of them.
Why don't we start
making preparations
to welcome everyone home?
Yes. All will be ready.
Damn those demons.
Look at what they've
done to my capital,
it's practically a ruin now!
Most of our remaining
troops have returned
and are beginning to put down
the demons, Your Majesty.
It's my belief that the
city will soon be secure.
[HERALD]
Soon isn't enough!
I want it dealt with today,
before sundown.
[MALE STAFF MEMBER A]
Um. As you command!
--[growls]
--[footsteps]
[SCHTROM]
I've been waiting for you...
...your Imperial Majesty.
Oliveira, is that you?
What are you doing here?
[HERALD gasps]
[SCHTROM]
No matter what else happened,
I wanted to be
absolutely certain
that I'd get to end
your life myself.
[HERALD gasps, groans]
[yells]
[exhales]
[RUPERT] The city's in shambles.
What happened here?
[DOMINIC] According to
our scouting parties,
the city was attacked by a
veritable horde of demons.
The Imperial army
received word
and hurried back
to assist, but well...
[SCHTROM]
Welcome!
[DOMINIC, RUPERT]
Huh?
[SCHTROM]
I've been expecting you,
gentlemen of the kingdom's army.
What's going on here?
And who would you be?
Tell us your name!
[SCHTROM]
Oliver Schtrom.
[DOMINIC]
You mean you're the demonoid
who disrupted the capital?
[SCHTROM] You certainly took
your time getting here.
What kept you?
I get it now. So you
brought the demons here!
[SCHTROM]
Thanks to your assistance
in thinning their numbers,
I was able to finish off the
Imperial army with ease.
[DOMINIC] Hold on.
Did you plan that as well?
Don't tell me you're the one
who instigated this whole war!
[SCHTROM] Yes. Leave it to
the Order's Knight Commander
and Bureau of Military affair's
chief to be so perceptive.
[BOTH gasp]
[DOMINIC] Those people.
Who are they?
They look like... Demonoids.
[DISEUM]
Unbelievable.
You're saying that
Schtrom is still alive?
There was no chance
we'd prevail on our own,
so we had no
choice but to run.
True. You made a
wise decision, Dominic.
None could blame you.
But to think, they have
over a dozen demonoids.
[MALE STATESMAN B] Your Majesty.
What course should we take next?
[DISEUM]
Hm...
[ALFRED] I'm sure you've
heard the announcement.
Schtrom has taken over
the imperial capital.
His objectives are
as of yet unclear,
so we can't form any
specific strategies.
But we will need to bolster
our fighting strength.
[ALFRED]
An edict has been issued.
We're to hone the
skills of our soldiers,
and in case of dire need,
our students as well.
So we're changing pace.
We're about to start doing
joint training sessions.
You'll work alongside
students from the
Knight Military Institute.
[SHIN] What's the matter?
Why all the weird looks?
Oh yes. Guess this
is new to you.
Huh?
Basically, we don't do a lot
of physical training here
because we're focused
on improving our magic.
[SHIN]
I knew that much.
But students at the
Knight Military Institute
work out all day.
They're fighters, right?
They need to.
Well, they're also bullies
who mock us every time
they see us. They call
us little bean sprouts.
Yeah. It stings worse
than you'd think.
Though I should admit,
we sometimes get back at them
by calling them muscle-heads.
Wait a sec. There are bean
sprouts in this world?
I love those.
We need to put aside
that rivalry though.
These are extreme circumstances.
We know, but where do they
get off calling us sprouts?
It's such a dumb name.
The blandness of the insult only
makes it sting that much worse!
It's so stupid! And all of
them think they're so clever!
Yeah. It gets under my skin too.
Especially since I grew up
as one of their peers.
Yeah, same here.
[SHIN]
I forgot.
Tony and Julius both come
from families of knights.
If you were to make
a good magician
fight a tough knight in
a battlefield scenario,
it's obvious the
magician would win!
And yet those knights have it
in their meaty little heads
that they're the
stronger ones!
[SHIN]
Whoa there.
Everyone has their strengths
and weaknesses, right?
We have the brains, they have
the brawn. That's okay.
Yeah, except for
maybe you, that is.
You can use both
magic and a sword.
[SHIN] I guess I
mostly meant you guys.
I was wondering. How'd you
get your combat skills.
Were you trained by a knight?
Yeah. It was
Grandpa's friend, Michel,
and he was a pretty strict
instructor to be honest.
Uh. What's the deal?
I don't understand, did I
say something weird again?
When you say Michel,
would you be talking
about Michel Colling?
Yeah, I guess you've
heard of him?
Of course we've heard
of Sir Colling!
He's the former Knight
Commander of the Order!
Right, I remember him mentioning
something along those lines.
So not only were you taught
magic by the Wise Man,
you were taught how to enchant
magic gear by the Guru!
And on top of that...
...ou were taught combat
by the Swordsaint?
[squeals]
He's called the swordsaint?
[THOR] You didn't know?
Michel Colling's a legend.
He wasn't Knight
Commander for nothing.
He's the greatest swordsman
in the kingdom.
So yeah, people call
him the Swordsaint.
[SHIN] To me, he was just
a harsh drill instructor.
Wow. So if you were taught
how to fight by the Swordsaint,
then the students from
the Knight Institute
can't talk crap about you,
now can they!
Oh, sure they can,
were they so inclined.
"What right has a bean sprout
to study under the swordsaint?"
They might say
if they're jealous.
[SHIN]
Then don't tell them!
Well anyway, I for one
think both of our schools
could really benefit from
a little joint training.
We have the same
objective here, don't we?
That's what matters!
Forget the sprout thing!
[MARIA, ALICE]
Hmph! We'll never forget!
[SHIN] Okay... This is
definitely gonna be a problem.
[SHIN] So they're putting
us in teams of eight,
with four students
from each school.
And we'll be
slaying demons, right?
It'll serve as combat
training for us,
and it culls the demons.
I'm a little bit apprehensive
about taking on demons,
but it's reassuring to know
that I'll be with you.
[SHIN]
Don't rest too easy.
This is training,
so you need to step up.
Oh! I'll do my best.
[KREIS] So that's the
hero's grandson, eh?
He's still just
another magician.
Looks like a sprout
to me. A bean sprout.
I'm just hoping that he won't
slow us down too much.
[MARIA groans]
See?
They're clearly a
bunch of jerks.
[SHIN chuckles]
We're all first-years
at the Knight Institute.
The name's Kreis Lloyd.
I'm top seat.
I'm second seat,
Miranda Wallace.
My name is Neun Curtis.
Kent McGregor. Don't forget it.
[SHIN] Of course we got paired
with the group from before.
Hey, before we start,
can I ask you something?
[KREIS]
What?
Tell me. Have any of
you fought a demon?
I see. You're just asking
that so you can brag about
the demonoid
you defeated, right?
That's not it, I promise!
Look, we might be in for
some serious combat.
We need to forget our
prejudices against knights,
and you need to do the
same thing with magicians.
Oh yeah, and what if we don't?
[SHIN]
You'll die.
[KNIGHTS gasp]
Hey! Shut up, Sprout!
The fact is that us knights
in training can put these
demons down without your help!
Miranda's right,
you aren't needed here.
Just stay out of our way and do
your best not to slow us down,
all right?
[AUGUST]
You're joking.
Is that truly how you view
this training exercise?
[KREIS] Oh, no! Forgive me,
Your Highness. I misspoke.
I didn't mean that you
would slow us down.
I don't care what
you think of me.
What matters is that you
learn to work with my peers.
It's the whole purpose
of this exercise.
Yeah. I know that, but...
You understand the goal
but don't think it has merit.
There's no choice then.
Shin. Let them fight
on their own.
Don't step in until
things get dire.
[SHIN]
Huh?
It's settled.
Try to defeat a demon
without a magician's backup.
You'll learn this
training's value.
[KREIS grunts]
We'll do as you say,
Your Highness.
[KNIGHTS exhale]
[MARIA]
Hmph!
[SHIN] They've taken us
pretty deep into the forest.
We're S-class students, so I
think the teachers sent us
somewhere more dangerous
because of it.
So there's a decent chance
that we'll run into
some powerful demons,
is that right?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but I thought that every team
was to be escorted
by an advisor.
[SIEG]
Yo, Shin!
Wait, is that Sieg and Chris?
[CHRISTINA]
Hey little brother,
we look forward to
working with you.
Are the two of you gonna
be our advisors today?
[SIEG, CHRISTINA]
Hm.
[SHIN]
It's really good to see you,
but could you do me a favor
and not fight for once?
[CHRISTINA] He's the one
to ask, he always starts it.
I literally just asked
you guys not to do this!
Excuse me, but my name's Maria
and I'm one of
Shin's classmates.
I'm really sorry
for interrupting,
but could I please shake
your hand, Lord Siegfried?
Well. If you're doing it--
Hi. Could we shake hands too?
Hi! My name's Kreis Lloyd!
Would you grace me
with a handshake?
It's an honor to meet you!
My name is Neun, and I hope
I can impress you today!
[KENT]
Hey! I'm Kent!
What is this?
It's normal. The two
of them are quite
popular at both our
school and the knights'.
[SHIN]
Huh?
Makes sense. They are
the knight and magician
entrusted with my
father's safety, after all.
[SHIN]
You have a point.
Big brother Sieg has always
been the debonair type,
so I get that he's popular.
But big sister Chris?
That's a surprise.
And why's it a surprise
that I'm popular?
Wait. You want us to let
the knights in training
fight the demons by
themselves at first?
Yes. By their request.
They won't understand the
importance of this training
through words alone.
[CHRISTINA] It's not rare.
Lots of newly enlisted knights
and magicians take
that attitude.
[SIEG] They learn how
to fight on their own
and take that to mean
they don't need help.
[CHRISTINA] Once they've
seen real combat,
they'll realize their mistake.
I think it might work.
It was smart of you to agree to
their request, Your Highness.
So now let's see how
it all plays out.
If they get knocked down a peg
while they're still in school,
it could save their comrades
a lot of trouble down the road.
I'm glad the four of you
are above that stuff.
Though some of us
are a little more
partisan about it than others.
[MARIA] Huh? Wait.
What're you getting at?
Oh. Just that you're not
fond of their school.
Not that you don't understand
the point of the exercise.
Good, because I really do.
I've watched Shin face off
against a demonoid
two times now.
I can't fight anywhere
near the level he did.
So unless I get way stronger,
I've got no chance of defeating
a powerful opponent without a
knight or swordsman helping me.
It was Maria. That right?
Um... yes.
It's admirable that you're able
to recognize your current
capabilities and limitations.
I'm certain that
you'll get stronger.
[gasps]
[ALL groan]
[MIRANDA] Why's Lord Siegfried
talking to her like that?
Why isn't is me?
[SHIN] Why are those four
so on their guard right now?
My Search Magic isn't
picking up anything nearby.
It isn't that they
sense something,
they're just feeling tense.
I can't really
fault them, though.
It's their first time
hunting demons, after all.
[SHIN gasps]
Something's coming.
I feel it. Kay.
Knights in training!
A demon's heading our way fast,
so prepare for battle!
[KNIGHTS grunt]
Whoa, it's a boar.
[SHIN grunts]
It would've been delicious
if it weren't demonized!
Come on.
[growls]
Keep it together guys!
Let's show these magicians
what the top performers at
the Knight Institute can do!
[KNIGHTS]
Right!
[ALL shout]
It's fast!
[KNIGHTS grunt]
So this is it. A real demon.
[KNIGHTS gasp]
[KENT]
With... a single blow?
He's incredible.
[CHRISTINA]
That was a poor showing.
This demon was a weaker one,
even by the standard of
others around its size.
Yet it had you soundly beat.
You boast that you're
the best of the
Knight Military Institute,
but you're still students.
You know nothing of battle.
All four of you are weak.
You must take that fact to heart
and try to learn
from this exercise.
Right.
Oh. You're hurt. I'll perform
a restoration spell.
Just hold still for a moment.
[KREIS gasps]
I'm grateful.
To think that you'd
show us such kindness
after we looked down on you.
Don't worry about it,
that's in the past.
Plus, we're in the
same party right now.
So it's a given
that I'd do this.
[ALL gasp]
[SHIN growls]
[AUGUST]
There, there.
I'll clear a path
for you, Sizilien!
Take my hand, Sizilien. Here.
Sizilien. Would you
like a drink?
No thank you. I'm just fine.
[SHIN grunting]
Do try not to get too upset.
I'm not upset in the slightest.
Yes you are. If you really
want them to stop.
Then step up and say,
"Sizilien's my woman."
That would work.
[SHIN] Whoa! What?
Have you lost your mind?
[MARIA]
Just let it go, Shin.
Stupid, shallow men
like that'll always
fall for the first pretty girl
who's nice to them.
Even when there are other
lovely magical girls
who could use a
gallant knight's aid.
[SHIN]
Uh...
[MIRANDA grunts] Those jerks
never once treated me
the way they're treating her and
it's completely infuriating!
Yo. Heads up.
Another demon's coming.
So stop messing around, will ya?
[SHIN] Uh? Actually. Aren't
there a whole bunch coming?
Yeah. There are quite a few.
[SHIN] Plus, one of them
feels pretty powerful.
[FEMALE MAGIC ACADEMY TEACHER A]
Listen Sieg!
You have to run!
[MALE MAGIC ACADEMY TEACHER A]
There's a huge pack
of demons coming!
[SIEG]
How many?
[FEMALE MAGIC ACADEMY TEACHER A]
At least a hundred of them.
A hundred?
You're kidding me!
Hey, Sieg.
[SIEG gasps]
What's up?
[SHIN] This "pack."
Can I take care of it?
It's fine by me. You don't mind?
[TEACHERS gasp]
[SIZILIEN] Wait, you're gonna
send Shin by himself?
There's no doubt in my mind
that he can handle it.
Okay everyone. Let's make sure
we're all out of Shin's way.
[WOLFS snarl]
[SHIN] It's been a while since
I've made a good explosion.
[SHIN] First, generate
hydrogen and compress it.
Once it's highly concentrated,
you can add some oxygen.
[WOLFS snarl]
[TIGER roars]
Oh, no. It's a tiger!
That's one of the strongest
demons out there.
I see now. The other demons
must be running away from it!
[SHIN] This might be too much,
but I'm a little upset
right now, so I need to
blow off some steam!
You damn monsters!
[WOLFS groan]
[ALL gasp]
[SHIN]
Phew. That is better!
That was crazy.
There's no way. What is he?
The Wise Man's grandchild.
He's even stronger
than they say.
Good job!
You're not injured, are you?
I'm perfectly fine.
[MIRANDA]
Hey, uh, excuse me. Wolford?
I just wanted to apologize
for all the rude things
I said before.
[SHIN]
Uh...
I was jealous of you.
Of the amazing environment
you grew up in.
And because of that...
I spitefully wanted to best you.
[SHIN]
She was jealous of me?
[MIRANDA]
But, seeing what you just did,
I finally realize how
behind you I am.
Miranda.
[MIRANDA]
And also, Sizilien?
Yes?
Um. I shouldn't have talked
to your boyfriend like that.
Sorry.
What was that? Did you just
call him my boyfriend?
Well yeah, it seemed
pretty obvious to me.
[SHIN] No, no, no, no, no!
We're just... Uh...
[SIZILIEN]
Right! Yes! What he said.
W-We haven't yet.
Yet?
[SIZILIEN, SHIN gasp]
[BOTH chuckle]
Judging by their reaction...
Yeah. It's true!
[SIEG] Shin was trying to
expose the knights' foolishness.
But it seems he ended up
exposing something else too.
[SHIN, SIZILIEN sigh]