We promise, we're gonna
take care of those demonoids!
We're the Ultimate Magicians!
[CROWD cheers]
[ALL]
What? The Ultimate Magicians?
[AUGUST giggles]
[SHIN] Let me guess,
you guys hate it.
I like that name, actually.
Well, I say we go
out with a bang.
We need to make sure
they have plenty of hope.
[SHIN]
Yeah. You're right.
And I know just what to do.
Here goes nothing!
[CROWD gasps]
[SHIN]
Ultimate Magicians, move out!
[ALL]
Right!
[SOLDIER A] Look, it's a red
signal flare from the border!
[SOLDIER B] So there's
a demonoid attack!
[COMMANDER A]
Send word to the castle!
Evacuate all the civilians!
[SOLDIERS]
Sir!
[SOLDIER A] I see them! It's a
massive group of demonoids!
I'd say... roughly a
hundred of them!
[COMMANDER A] Did you
say a hundred demonoids?
Oh, no. All hands
to stations, now!
Deploy the defensive magic gear!
[SOLDIERS]
Sir!
[COMMANDER A] Send Earlsheid
a request for aid, immediately!
[SOLDIER C]
Right!
[COMMANDER A] There's no
telling how many days it'll take
for them to receive word and
for reinforcements to arrive.
[COMMANDER A]
All units, quick!
Defend these walls
with your lives!
Don't let any harm
come to the civilians!
[chuckles]
Let's hurry up and break
through that wall of theirs!
[COMMANDER A]
Activate the magic gear!
[FABRO shouts]
[FABRO] Heh. They think a magic
barrier can keep us out?
Nice try.
I gotta say, I'm not too
proud of calling us the
"Ultimate Magicians."
How come? I think it suits
a tough group like us.
It was your fault for
putting me on the spot!
And you're a member
of this team,
so you're only making
fun of yourself here!
What's so bad about it?
I think it's a good name.
Well, I'm pretty sure
everyone in the entire kingdom's
heard it by now, so I guess
we're just stuck with it.
[THOR] Hey Shin,
the border's just ahead!
[SHIN]
Huh? That was fast.
It would have taken us days
to get here in a carriage!
It's a good thing we
traveled so quickly.
Shin's defensive magic gear is
good, but not indestructible.
I made so many of those, and you
decided to lend them to Sweed
without even giving
me a heads-up?
Wow, this is real.
We're gonna fight demonoids.
Makes me nervous.
You'll be fine, Maria.
You're stronger than
the demonoids now.
It'll all work out.
Yeah, that's easy for
you to say, Mr. Perfect!
[SHIN] Sizilien, I'd rather
you take care of anyone
who gets hurt.
I can do that!
Now, everyone else,
pair up and attack!
[ALL]
Roger!
Mark, sweetie.
I'll back you up, so please
don't throw any surprises at me.
Okay. I'll count on you.
If the rest of this
squad doesn't learn
to get a freakin' room,
I'm gonna scream!
It's the boys' fault.
They're all so busy living
the lovey-dovey life.
You've got a point.
Are Thor and Julius
the only guys here
who aren't seeing someone?
Actually, I have a fiancée.
Yeah, I don't think I mentioned
it, but I'm engaged too.
Seriously? Just you wait,
you stupid demonoids!
I'll take all my anger and
jealousy out on you!
Well, at least she's got
her mind off of how nervous
she was, I guess.
We should probably
stop joking around now.
The Kingdom of Sweed
is in sight.
[MOTHER A pants]
[laughs]
You better not slow down!
Yeah, keep running or
you're gonna get burned!
[MOTHER, DAUGHTER A scream]
[DAUGHTER A]
Mama!
Stop it! Please don't do this!
Aw man! No more playin'
follow the leader?
Then I'm thinkin' it's
time for us to kill y--
What was that?
[DEMONOID A groans]
[gasps]
[THOR] Shin! Please don't
barrel straight in like that!
Sorry. I couldn't
stand to watch.
[DEMONOID B growls]
How dare you?
Do you even understand
what you've just done?
I could ask you
the same question.
Ha! You look like you
can handle yourself, kid,
but you're out of your mind if
you believe that a mere human
could ever stand a
chance of surviving a fight
against a demonoid like me!
[DEMONOID B yells, gasps]
Huh? What the...? It can't be!
I'd ask you how it feels
to be beaten by a human,
but you wouldn't hear me.
Thor!
[DEMONOID A groans]
[THOR]
All done!
[SHIN]
Good job.
Are you okay?
Yes. Thanks!
Who are you guys? You're strong!
Reinforcements. We came here
from the Kingdom of Earlsheid.
Now, you should go.
[MOTHER A]
Right!
[DAUGHTER A giggles]
[SHIN chuckles]
[SHIN grunts]
[SOLDIERS chattering]
[inhales]
Attention, people of Sweed!
We were sent here from your
neighboring kingdom.
I'm Prince August von Earlsheid!
We have acquired the necessary
power to save your nation
and drive out the demonoids!
Please rest assured that we will
work closely with your royal
guards to eliminate this
threat once and for all!
As for you demonoids,
abandon hope at once!
We have Shin Wolford
on our side,
who's already defeated
some of your kind!
Mark my words,
you're certain to fail!
[FABRO]
Tsk!
[CROWD cheers]
So, his Highness
Prince August
and that famous hero
have come to help us?
Sizilien, go help the
wounded at the aid station.
Right. I'll save as
many lives as I can!
Do your best.
[SHIN]
Hm?
Oh and, Shin. You be
careful out there, okay?
[SHIN]
Yeah. You too.
You're here, Shin Wolford.
Rumor has it that
you're pretty strong.
Let's see how strong.
[ALICE, LYN pant]
Search magic... Extend!
There! You ready, Lyn?
[LYN]
Mm.
[DEMONOID B chuckles]
That was pathetic,
even for a bunch
of lousy humans!
[DEMONOID B]
Huh? What the hell? You're kids!
Kids? Call us that again!
Ah! I get it now,
you must be the ones the prince
was talkin' about earlier.
But powderpuffs like you
are a waste of my time.
I mean, what am I s'posed
to do, play house with ya?
[ALICE] Really? Is that
what you think of us?
In that case, I've got a real
fun game for us to play togeth--
[ALICE]
Watch where you're aiming!
This isn't the time
to get heated.
You fight sloppy when
you get too emotional.
This is serious!
Oh. Yeah, you're right.
I guess I lost my cool.
'Kay. I'll try to be more calm!
He's dead now.
[ALICE gasps]
[LYN] I mixed sand into
some high-pressure water.
I know he was a demonoid,
but that's hardcore!
I'm okay with that though.
He might've been human once, but
that part of him was long-gone.
I hear what you're saying,
and I understand, but...
Let me put it this way.
See, they're completely
aware of what they're doing.
And killing for the fun of it
makes them even nastier.
Because of them,
countless people could die.
Alice, get your
head on straight.
[ALICE]
Mm!
--[SOLDIER D yells]
--[LYN, ALICE gasp]
There ya go. How's that feel?
[SOLDIER D] I won't.
I won't let you--
[DEMONOID C] You won't let me
do what? Well, spit it out!
[SOLDIER D grunts]
[DEMONOID C laughs]
With this much power,
I've got nothing to fear!
If you won't get
up and fight me,
then I'll just bring
the fight to you!
[gasps]
You monster! You're gonna
pay for that one!
Two little girls? What the hell?
Why do all of you call me that?
I'm not just some kid!
How is she so powerful?
[screams]
[pants]
Wow, you really
snapped big-time.
[ALICE]
Hang in there!
Our friend at the aid station is
gonna fix you right up, okay?
[SOLDIER D] I feel weak for
having to be saved like this,
but I'm grateful.
I owe you my life.
That said, I think I can
get there on my own.
Thank you ladies
for all your help.
He seems like he's embarrassed.
At least we helped him.
Anyway, we have lots
more enemies to beat.
Heck yeah, we do!
Let's go kick some demonoid
butt and save the kingdom!
We'll see who can take out
the most. I'll race you!
[gasps]
No fair! Wait for me!
[SOLDIER E screams]
[FABRO chuckles]
Ah, what do we have here?
Those are some nifty little
magic items you've brought me.
[THOR grunts]
[DEMONOID D shouts]
[THOR gasps]
[JULIUS]
That's not gonna happen!
[DEMONOID D growls]
[DEMONOID E]
Ha! You're outta here!
[THOR shouts]
[groans]
I'm sure you won't tell
me anything helpful,
but here we go.
Are you acting on
orders from Schtrom?
[DEMONOID E] Forget it, boy.
I'm not interested in chit-chat!
Don't tell me this is the best
you weak demonoids can do!
[DEMONOID D growls]
You bastard!
[DEMONOID E groans]
[DEMONOID E chuckles]
I may be a demonoid,
but that doesn't mean
that I can't be killed.
And I was so sure that a hundred
of us would be more than enough
to take control of the country.
I could be wrong,
but aren't you former
commoners from the empire?
If so, how could you do
something so horrible?
[DEMONOID E]
Stupid question.
We're capable of all of this
because we're demonoids.
[THOR]
That's not what I asked you!
[DEMONOID E] Enduring
oppression from the nobility,
and having everything
we owned systematically
taken from us, all that
was left was our hate.
Burning, raging hate!
And after we turned into
demonoids, that hate erupted!
We're disgusted by those who
live in peace and comfort
within the walls of this empire!
[JULIUS shouts]
Be that as it may.
It still doesn't give you
the right to murder
innocent civilians!
We're not going to let
you hurt anyone else!
[chuckles]
Go ahead and stop me.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[DEMONOID F]
Aw, too bad for you, fellas!
Looks like there's
nowhere left to hide!
These are the brave
protectors of the kingdom?
Huh? Wait a minute,
what's happening?
[DEMONOID F gasps]
Why you little!
Oh, goodness. I guess
I've been found out.
You're the one who did that?!
[shouts]
This shouldn't be possible.
Man, this thing
cuts like a dream!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[DEMONOID H chuckles]
Lucky us.
We're the first ones
to their aid station.
This place'll be
full of weak humans.
[DEMONOID I]
Hey!
Stop! I won't let you past me!
[DEMONOID H laughs]
That boy's shakin' in his shoes!
I call dibs on his head!
[DEMONOID H]
Uh, wait!
[MARK gasps]
Olivia!
Let me protect you, Mark!
I'll get you!
[DEMONOID H laughs]
Only if I can
protect you, too!
[DEMONOID H groans] I thought
you were a swordsman!
What, just because I was
holding a sword?
[DEMONOID H yells]
[JULIUS, THOR grunt]
[MOTHER B] Lady Sizilien,
please help my child!
[SIZILIEN]
Right!
We need to give first priority
to the worst injuries!
[DEMONOIDS yell]
[DEMONOID L]
You brat!
[DEMONOIDS shouting]
You demonoids are really
starting to disappoint me,
you know that? I came
here for a battle!
[DEMONOID P]
What's this guy's deal?
[DEMONOID Q] Yeah, we can't
be defeated by a human!
[DEMONOID P]
We're demonoids, aren't we?
We're gonna take over this
nation and eventually the world!
[DEMONOIDS scream]
You've sure got some lofty goals
for someone of
your weight class.
So this guy is Shin Wolford.
How'd he learn to use
those amazing moves,
and where does he get
all that raw power?
I'll tell you one thing,
Shin Wolford gave me a
beating I didn't expect.
[LAWRENCE]
What is this guy's weakness?
I mean, does he even have one?
It looks like we're just about
finished clearing this area,
Your Highness.
Yes, but keep your guard up.
[BOTH gasp]
You've really done
a number on us, huh?
[AUGUST]
You don't know when to quit.
Wait, that voice. I knew
you seemed familiar.
You must be the famous
Prince of Earlsheid!
Yes. And I've come to put every
last one of you monsters down.
Someone's a confident leader.
I hate to break it to ya,
but once I claim your head,
all your little minions are
gonna turn tail and run away.
And I hate to break it to you...
[chuckles]
...but if you want the leader
of the Ultimate Magicians,
then you've got the wrong guy.
What are you cracking up about?
[AUGUST] And you? Are you
the demonoids' leader?
Huh? So what if I am?
[AUGUST]
Well, once I bash your head in,
the others won't have
as much will to fight.
[FABRO]
Go ahead and try it!
It'll take a whole lot more
than crushin' the empire
to satisfy my anger! I'm gonna
massacre every human here!
I assume anger is the
source of your power, then?
Either way, I'll still stop you.
Attack me as hard as you like!
I'll tear you twerps apart!
[MARIA]
You shouldn't talk a big game
when you're backed
into a corner, prince!
You're as bad as Shin is!
[FABRO grunts]
[gasp]
You fight dirty, girl, tryin'
to sneak in a surprise attack.
Name's Fabro, and I'm thinkin'a
makin' you my new woman.
Sound good?
I may be in the market
for a boyfriend,
but I'll never be desperate
enough to say yes to that.
Aw, look.
Somebody does like you.
Hey, that was uncalled for!
That's a damn shame. After all,
I can think of so many fun
things you and I
could do together!
[AUGUST, MARIA shout]
[FABRO grunts]
[MARIA groans]
[FABRO]
Somethin's not right.
A woman turns you down,
and you just punch her?
[MARIA] If it weren't
for this battle uniform,
that blow would have
shattered my bones!
--[MARIA gasps, yells]
--[FABRO laughs]
Messina!
[MARIA]
Don't worry! I'll be okay.
[FABRO] Huh... Your outfit's
protectin' you somehow.
But look. There's a nice
bruise on your cheek.
So I'll just hit you places
your clothes don't cover!
[MARIA]
You're welcome to try it.
That is, if you're able
to get close enough!
[FABRO gasps]
[MARIA grunts]
[AUGUST grunts]
[gasps]
He's not hurt!
[FABRO chuckles]
No way. Is that...?
This magic gear looked
like it would come in handy,
so I decided I'd borrow it.
Can't return it though, since I
killed the guy who had it.
[MARIA]
Is that what I think it is?
Yeah, no doubt.
How'd he get Shin's
magic-powered barrier?
[FABRO]
Well?
What happened to the guts
you had just a minute ago?
Now hit me with
that magic of yours!
Unless you're too scared to!
[AUGUST, MARIA grunting]
[FABRO]
That ain't gonna hurt me!
[ALL grunting]
[FABRO]
They're not givin' up!
They just keep launchin'
more magic blasts!
I don't know how much
this thing can take.
No! They broke through it!
Oh, you didn't know? If you
don't focus hard enough
when you use it, your magic
gear stops working!
This is unbelievable!
[FABRO]
How could I lose?
[AUGUST] You managed to figure
out what I was planning to do.
Smart, Messina.
Well, what else do you expect?
Shin and Merlin
trained me, remember?
[AUGUST]
This is tragic.
If only they had been
born in Earlsheid.
Anyway, there's nothing
more we can do.
[KING SWEED sighs] The fighting
appears to be reaching its end.
Then I take it our assistance
won't be needed.
I'll be sure to congratulate
those kids on a job well done.
[LAWRENCE]
What the hell's going on?
And it's not just Shin Wolford.
It's that entire group!
He'll destroy us
all before long.
No. There's still time.
I know what to do.
Well, I certainly
wasn't prepared
for this new development.
The plan was to lure
Wolford out into the open,
so as to obtain an accurate
assessment of his ability.
But if he's this overwhelmingly
mighty, that tells me that I'll
need to reevaluate my
previous appraisal.
They may be disposable pawns,
but it's still a shame
to let all of those
demonoids go to waste.
And it would be asking
too much of Lawrence
to organize their
retreat all on his own.
Which means I'll have to ask
this favor of you, Miria.
[COMMANDER A]
The demonoid attack has been
brought to a halt, but do
not lower your guard yet!
[SOLDIERS]
Sir!
[SOLDIERS yell]
[COMMANDER A gasps]
What was that?
Well, humans.
Show me what you've got.
[SCHTROM] Oh dear. I thought I
told you not to get involved.
This is quite an unfortunate
turn of events, Zest.
How could you start
something so fun,
and not even have the
courtesy to tell me about it?