Well, then.
I guess I will consider the
experiment a success for now.
More importantly...
[sighs]
[AUGUST]
What's wrong?
Don't tell me the
sudden hero status
is wearing you out already.
Yeah, maybe a little.
But something's bothering me.
Is it that easy to
become a demonoid?
You're right.
Huh? Huh? What's easy?
You know the previous demonoid?
He was a strong magician.
They say he messed up while
casting advanced magic.
And apparently that's
how he demonized.
But Rietsburg... He had just
barely enrolled in the academy.
At worst, if he lost
control of his spell,
he would over-throttle.
But to go full demonoid?
Well he did, and the whole
thing was pretty crazy.
Do you think... maybe this
was artificially induced?
You mean, like,
someone did this to him?
According to grandpa, demonoids
lose all sense of reason.
They can't communicate,
they can only howl.
But when Kurt turned demonoid,
he could still talk.
And when it came to actual
combat, he was pretty weak.
[ALL]
Something about this
doesn't add up.
Hey. What if Kurt was used in
some kind of human experiment?
[ALL gasp]
Huh? Uncle Dis?
Oh, this is good timing,
welcome home, Shin.
[SHIN]
Hm?
Sir.
Our noble majesty values heroism
in the kingdom of Earls-hide's
time of need. In a
selfless act of bravery,
you successfully
slayed a demonoid.
Therefore, we would be
honored to present you,
the First Order of Merit.
The... First Order of--
Hold on. Are you
giving me a medal?
[BOTH gasp, chuckle]
Diseum, did you not say you
weren't going to use Shin
for political gain?
What's all this fanfare about?
You know the danger.
The last time this happened,
the demonoid's attack left
the Kingdom of Earlsheid
on the verge of extermination.
That threat looms
over us yet again.
As you can imagine, news has
spread quickly among the people
about both the appearance of the
demonoid and its suppression.
For the sake of the kingdom,
we must address these
matters by going public.
Yes, I understand that much.
But what is the meaning of
awarding the young lad?
[DISEUM] How would it look
if we denied him an award
for a feat you two have
also accomplished?
[MERLIN]
Mm?
I suppose you do
make a good point.
Of course, there are
those who wish to profit
by exploiting him,
but I'll do all that I
can to prevent that.
So, please, I implore you
to allow this to happen.
Not for my sake,
but for the people.
[ALL gasp]
[sighs] Very well,
Diseum, you win.
We'll take you at
your word in this.
But if you break your word, we
will leave this kingdom at once.
Is that understood?
Absolutely. You can trust me.
You know, a nation's king really
shouldn't bow to someone else
so readily.
[MELIDA sighs] Honestly,
you seem to go from one spot
of trouble to another.
Uh, wait, this is my fault?
[ADMIRER A]
Everyone, look! It's Shin!
That's the new hero who
defeated a demonoid.
Wow, he's so cool!
Yeah! He's cute, too!
My uncle, Dis, said he
issued a gag order,
but that hasn't seemed to stop
anyone from gossiping about it.
Well, what'd you expect?
His Majesty specifically said
we couldn't keep you defeating
the demonoid a secret.
But he also said we weren't
allowed to reveal any
additional details about the
attack to the people, remember?
Who're those two girls
walking with him?
Come on, there's no way someone
who's as amazing as Shin
hasn't already been spoken for.
Yeah. One of them
could be his fiancée.
[SIZILIEN gasps]
[MARIA chuckles]
[SHIN]
Sizilien?
I'm sorry... for this.
[SIZILIEN]
Oh, no, it's fine. Really.
You sure?
I'm here walking by your
side of my own initiative.
So please don't doubt
my intentions, okay?
[gasps]
[SHIN] Sizilien, I offered to
help you of my own initiative.
So, don't doubt
my intentions, okay?
[giggles]
[STUDENT A]
We're begging you, sir!
Please let us in!
We wanna study with
the Wise Man's grandson!
[ALFRED] This is a nightmare.
I can't let all of them into
the study group,
but they're relentless.
All right, then.
Who can use other-dimensional
storage space?
[STUDENTS gasp]
That's the minimum standard.
If you can do that,
then stick around.
And I'll conduct
an entrance exam.
[DOMINIC]
What did you say?!
You really think there's a
chance the demonoid
was artificially created?
[DISEUM] Yes. Shin himself
came up with this theory
after fighting him personally.
Then that means...
...the recent increase in
demons may be linked.
[DISEUM]
Hm.
Yes. This could be a
very serious situation.
Dominic, Dennis,
investigate this.
Work together to find
out whatever you can.
Do not overlook anything!
[DENNIS, DOMINIC]
As you wish.
[MARK]
Pardon the interruption.
Hello, there.
Are you the students
who passed Mr. Marcus's
entrance exam?
Yes and it's an honor to be
joining you all, I'm Mark Bean!
My family runs a smithy
that's called Bean Works.
Oh, yeah? I've definitely
heard of that.
It's a well-known outfit.
Well known? They're good?
The weapons at Bean Works
are nice and sharp.
I've always wanted one.
Nice. And you are?
Oh, right. I'm Olivia Stone.
I've known Mark since
we were just kids.
You might have heard of
my family's restaurant
called the Brick Oven.
Are you kidding?
That place is awesome!
I dream about their brick
oven gratin. It's perfection!
Oh, man...
I actually celebrated passing
my academy entrance exams
by eating there,
and it was amazing.
I'm jealous,
you really lucked out.
It was so busy that we
couldn't get a reservation.
I'm flattered. If you want,
you should all come by again.
I'll serve you personally!
I'm so in! Shin, these guys get
my official seal of approval!
That is no way to welcome them!
So Mark, since you're
the son of a blacksmith,
does that mean you
can make blades?
[MARK gasps] Uh, sorta.
But I'm not exactly an expert.
At this point I've only been
able to manage crafting
a few knives.
Too bad. If you had the skill,
I would've asked you to
make me a new weapon.
I don't even know
if that's possible!
I mean, you slayed a
demonoid with that sword!
I doubt you'd have any luck
finding a replacement for that.
Nah, it was just a sword,
nothing' special.
Huh?
But it is enchanted,
so the blade vibrates
at ultrasonic speed.
Thanks to that,
I can cut through almost
anything without much force.
I like blades to be a
bit on the thin side,
but as a result,
they can break easily.
I was hoping I could make
some improvements to it.
If that's all you need,
I think I can do it.
But I'll be asking for your
input in the process.
Seriously? I've had a hard
time with the finer details.
Thanks a lot!
Is there anything that brain of
yours can't come up with, Shin?
That's incredible.
I used to think that my
enchanting skills were decent,
but now I'm not so sure.
Hey, don't be so down
on yourself, Yuri.
I can ask Granny to show you
how to improve your technique
if you want!
[gasps] You mean it?
Thank you! I'm so happy!
[SIZILIEN grunts]
[MARIA giggles]
Seems Kurt was visited by
a middle-school teacher.
The day he demonized. Huh.
Sounds like something
we should investigate.
I am Security Bureau
Investigator Ault Lieckermann.
And I'm Investigator
Carlos Bale.
Oliver Schtrom at your service.
Would that be sensory magic?
Forgive me. You have a patch
covering both of your eyes,
but you move naturally.
I thought you might be using
magic to replace your sight.
Ah, well. Something like that.
I mean no offense by asking,
but what happened?
[SCHTROM]
It may surprise you,
but I was born to a
noble family in the empire.
[AULT gasps]
Years later, there was
a power struggle,
and I was exiled
to the kingdom.
The fight for leadership
was violent,
and a family member attempted
to fatally wound me.
I survived--my eyes did not.
That's terrible.
I shouldn't have asked
such a personal question.
No, I get asked about
it all the time.
Anyhow, what brings
you men here today?
Surely you didn't come here
just to ask me questions
about my eyes.
No. Mr. Schtrom, sir, we are
aware that you have formed
a study group for students
with magical aptitude,
and that you have fostered
some exceptionally
talented magicians.
That's right. What about it?
We've heard that you
are quite enthusiastic,
inviting many students
to join the study group.
Well, I am a one-time
noble of the Empire.
I'm accustomed to facing
opposition in the kingdom.
In order to establish
myself at this school,
I needed to show
tangible results.
So that's why. Go on.
All of the students who
participated in my study group,
well, they improved their
abilities dramatically.
And as a result,
they're starting to acknowledge
me little by little.
Well then. This incident
must be quite a blow.
Indeed, it is. It pains me to
know this happened to Kurt.
Mr. Schtrom,
If it isn't a bother,
may I ask a favor of you?
[SCHTROM]
What is it?
Currently, we're
assembling specialists.
We plan to examine the
victim's demonized corpse.
Your insight would be
truly invaluable.
Why would you ask me?
In addition to your work
with the study group,
I've heard you are a fairly
high-level magician,
Mr. Schtrom. Any help you can
lend would be most appreciated.
[SCHTROM] In that case,
I'd be pleased to assist.
[SIZILIEN]
What's on your mind, Shin?
[SHIN gasps]
I'm sorry.
I was just thinking of ways
to customize my sword.
Do you have any idea what
kind you're looking for yet?
What's most important
to me is a thin blade.
But like I said, that's going
to make it easier to break.
[MARK] A sword that
combines both a thin blade
and increased durability, huh?
That's gonna be tricky.
Yeah, but if you do break it,
can't you just replace
it with another one?
I mean, come on, you are
the Wise Man's grandson.
I betcha can afford
a whole armory!
That's... not an option.
I don't get very much
of an allowance.
What? That's surprising.
But it's true. Granny told
Grandpa not to spoil me
so I'll learn the value
of money... Or something.
That sounds like the Guru.
Moderation can be just as much
of an asset as a suit of armor!
That's one way to
look at it, I guess.
[TONY] If breakage is the issue,
maybe it would be a good idea
to make the blades
easily replaceable.
[MARK, SHIN]
Huh?
Think about it. You could
hang on to the same hilt.
So that's one less
expense to deal with.
[MARK, SHIN gasp]
[TONY] The hilt and
blade are always firmly
attached for typical use.
But since you don't need
to use much force at all,
that feature wouldn't be as
important in its construction.
[MARK]
Huh! That might work!
Ya think you could come
by my place right now?
[SHIN]
Uh...
I wanna try that out
while I'm inspired!
Hey, can I come, too?
Yes. Me, as well.
Sizilien, Maria, do you mind
if we stop by Mark's place?
Sure, no problem!
Oh yeah. Go on ahead.
While you boys're
over at the workshop,
I think we'll pay a little
visit to Olivia's place.
[SHIN]
Hm?
I still have so many
questions to ask you.
Menu. How do you feel about
adding a few more items to it?
As long as you agree
to go easy on me.
[door clatters]
[SCHTROM gasps]
Pardon me, may I ask
why the examination
is taking place here?
I know it isn't ideal,
but it's our best option.
[SCHTROM] It's empty.
Where's Kurt's body?
[SCHTROM]
So you didn't bring me here
to examine a body after all.
[AULT] Oh, we'll be
examining a body. Your body.
Indeed?
See, Mr. Schtrom, you made
a critical miss-step.
[gasps]
After the boy had demonized,
his Majesty issued a gag order.
We were specifically asked that
we do not reveal his name
to the public.
[SCHTROM gasps]
To protect his family from
being unjustly treated,
it was imperative that
we kept a tight lid on it.
But somehow, you knew that it
was Kurt who had been demonized.
How could you have known?
[laughs]
[AULT gasps]
Well, that's rich!
I didn't have a clue that
his name was private.
It's had the kingdom
in such an uproar.
With all the gossip
going around,
I just assumed everyone
would know who the demonoid
was by now.
Are you the one whose
responsible for this?
What exactly was your objective?
Just an experiment.
What? You were conducting
experiments on humans?!
Yes, that's right.
[chuckles] And now, since I've
completed all my experiments
here in the capital,
I think it's a good time
for me to excuse myself.
Seize him! Right now!
Don't let him get away!
[SOLDIERS]
Yes, sir!
[SCHTROM chuckles]
No way! You and Mark
are really a couple?
We basically grew up together,
so it just happened.
I want to know
every single detail!
[OLIVIA]
Every detail?
[MARIA] Of course we
wanna know, are you kidding--
[ALL shout]
What in the world?
[SHIN pants]
That thing covering his eyes.
Aug, is that the guy?
Yes. Our middle-school teacher,
Oliver Schtrom.
Oh, look. If it isn't
Prince August
and his trusty companion:
the hero Shin Wolford.
He's dangerous, please run away!
This man is the culprit behind
the demonoid incident!
He is?
[SHIN] You're the one who
turned Kurt into a demonoid?
That's right!
A fascinating specimen
who danced to my tune
quite brilliantly.
I've heard enough.
[SHIN] I knew there was
something weird going on!
[SCHTROM]
Heh!
[SCHTROM gasps]
[SHIN shouts]
Your sword. It's enchanted, yes?
Maybe!
[SCHTROM, SHIN grunting]
[SCHTROM] You've got spunk.
I'll give you that much!
[SHIN grunts]
Playin' dirty? Take this!
Had to go up there, huh?
Well, you can't dodge this!
[gasps]
[SHIN] Isn't hovering in midair
is going against the rules?
[SCHTROM chuckles] Don't tell
me the grandson of the great
Wise Man can't use
floating magic.
[SHIN]
No. But guess what?
I can fly for a moment!
[SCHTROM groans]
[SHIN]
Incoming!
[SCHTROM grunts]
[SCHTROM]
A little advice, boy.
Don't press your luck!
[ALL grunting]
[SHIN gasps]
[SCHTROM growls]
Red eyes? No...
Now you've done it, Wolford.
How annoying.
I would have preferred
to leave the capital
with my true identity
still hidden.
How can you be a demonoid with
your sense of reason... intact?
[SCHTROM]
My sense of reason?
If you're under the assumption
that reason is what separates
demons from humans,
then I suppose you could say
I'm an exception to the rule.
[SHIN]
What do you mean?
[SCHTROM]
Now that I've been demonized,
humans have been reduced
to little more than
insignificant creatures
for me to experiment on!
I can kill them or
exploit them at will!
You creatures mean
nothing to me anymore!
[SHIN]
That bastard.
[SHIN] This is bad.
I have to... Stop you!
What's the matter with you?
Is your terror of me
making you clumsy?
This is why I can't
abide humans.
Stay where you are
just a little longer.
Another moment and you'll
see what my magic can do!
The Wise Man's grandson,
and you're a helpless fool.
[gasps]
You're in for it now!
[SCHTROM grunts]
[SCHTROM grunts, yells]
[SHIN grunts]
[ALL grunting]
[AUGUST]
Argh. You got him, right?
[SHIN]
Don't jinx it like that, Aug!
[AUGUST]
Huh?
[THOR] The high temperature
turned the ground to glass.
How did he create a
heat ray that intense?
[AUGUST]
Mm-mm...
[SHIN] My search magic
hasn't picked anything up.
Does that mean I really got him?
[RUPERT]
Cheer up! Why the long face?
He was a demonoid. You don't
regret killing him, do you?
No, it's not that.
You should hold your
head high, then.
Take pride in the fact that
you saved all our lives.
Thank you, Shin Wolford.
Oh, you don't
have to thank me.
We came as quickly as
we could when we heard
that another
demonoid appeared.
But much to our surprise,
you'd already taken him down!
[SHIN grunts]
Pleased to meet you,
I'm Dominic Gastor.
I'm Michel's successor as the
knight commander of the order.
Oh, dear. I haven't introduced
myself either, have I?
The name is Rupert Olgran,
captain of the court
magic division.
Michel told me all about his
immensely talented pupil.
He also expressed how much he
enjoyed training you, young man.
[SHIN]
Mm...
[RUPERT] Wolford, if you
wouldn't mind humoring
my curiosity, what exactly
did you do, and how?
Let's see. I converged
the light from the sun
and blasted it down
as a heat ray.
From the sun? And you got
that much force out of it?
Well, you see, the sun puts out
more than one kind of light.
So I just visualized collecting
the light that emits heat,
and from there it was
relatively straightforward.
[SHIN]
They have no idea what I mean.
Still, was it just a heat ray
that created the explosion?
[SCHTROM grunts]
[You beat me this time, Wolford.
Luckily I was able
to get out of there.
But the only way was to
release explosive magic.
But if I'd endured even a
fraction more of his magic,
it could have very well
have annihilated me.
That boy. He's more formidable
than I first thought.
I'll have to take every
precaution to ensure
that he won't interfere
with my plans.