Aha! Wow, this feels awesome!
[YURI]
Who could have ever imagined
we would get a chance to fly?
Well, Shin was the one who
cast floating magic on us,
so I guess we have him to thank
for all of this fun, Huh?
[THOR] Right. All we have
to do is keep controlling
our wind magic to make
sure we're traveling
in the right direction!
[SHIN] Wow, they're really
starting to improve.
Guess what, Shin?
I'm ready to go flying, also!
[MAY]
And this time, I came prepared!
[BOYS]
Huh?
[ALL gasp]
May! No! Stop that!
Huh? But... it's okay if I
have this underneath, right?
Um, it isn't as bad as nothing,
but it's still not good!
Okay! It's time
to come back down!
Aww... But we were just
getting the hang of it!
[SHIN]
We need to switch people out.
That magic gear.
Looks like it's pretty useful.
It'd be handy for
lots of things.
Maybe your investiture ceremony.
[MARIA] Oh yeah, that's coming
up pretty soon, huh?
Yes.
[MAY] Hey, you guys! Hurry up
and trade off so I can go next!
[SCHTROM] I see. So the final
town has fallen at last.
Yes. Which means that every town
and village within the empire's
territory has been wiped out.
[MIRIA] The demonoid squad
led by Zest launched attacks
on caravans traveling
on the roads,
stopping the food supply.
As the nobility continued
their lives of luxury,
resentment grew
among the commoners,
causing them to demonize.
And so, as the commoners
gradually transform
into demonoids, they begin
to slaughter the feudal lords
in an effort to
settle the score.
Laying waste to
village after village.
Master Schtrom despises
the imperial nobility,
but this strategy is
victimizing the innocent
townspeople as well.
My Lord, why go
to such extremes?
[SCHTROM] Thanks to
all of your efforts,
we have successfully driven
this empire to absolute ruin.
This day marks an
auspicious occasion.
[DEMONOIDS cheer]
Since that's done, I wonder
what I'd like to tackle next?
[DEMONOIDS grunt]
Crushing the empire
was my one goal.
There's nothing
left to accomplish.
Huh. I've achieved
everything I wanted.
What the hell are
you talking about?
That's crazy!
We need to keep taking
over the neighboring lands
until we gain control
of the whole world‐‐
And why, pray tell,
should we trouble ourselves
with something
so tiresome?
[DEMONOID A] Well, with this
many demonoids...
[DEMONOID B] ...we could
form a nation of our own!
All of you are more
than welcome to pursue
any ambitions you possess.
I only ask that you don't
impose them on me.
I'm not interested.
Is that right? In that case,
I'm gonna make my own decisions.
Go ahead.
In fact, you could have done
that from the beginning.
[DEMONOID A]
Tsk!
[SCHTROM] I imagine
there are more of you here
who share his feelings.
If so, you're free to go.
Please don't hesitate.
Pardon me, Master,
but are you sure it's
alright to let them do this?
It makes no difference.
As I said, I've already
accomplished my goal
of overthrowing the empire.
We might as well let
them do as they please.
Sir, if I may be so bold.
Why do you have such
hate for the empire?
I heard you were a
formerly a duke,
and that you were once in
line to become the emperor.
Oh, that's right. I suppose
I never told you the story.
Well, then. Why don't
I tell you right now?
Two years ago, when I was
still known as Oliveira...
[FARMER A gasps]
Lord Oliveira!
[FARMER B] Please don't concern
yourself with our labor, sir!
No. It's quite alright.
I see the soil's
maintaining its richness.
And the crops
continue to flourish!
Judging by that, I'd say
we can look forward to a
successful harvest this year!
[FARMER A] Yes! There's a
bumper crop in every field.
The population appears
to be growing swiftly.
[BODYGUARD A] Thanks to
your agricultural reforms,
we've been able to
increase our crop acreage.
There wasn't enough manpower,
so we started welcoming
workers from other territories.
Oh? And will that
trend continue?
[BODYGUARD A] Well, there are
other industries in town
that are also struggling
with labor shortages.
Right, it seems like everywhere
you go, we're shorthanded.
[BODYGUARD A]
By the way,
I've been meaning to ask you
this question for a long time,
Lord Oliveira, but why do you
always treat the commoners
so favorably?
Back when I was a little boy,
I never questioned the idea
of nobility receiving
special treatment.
But during a trip to
another country,
I received quite the
unexpected shock.
Unlike the empire, this society
had no system of slavery.
and even average people
were able to enjoy
a vibrant lifestyle.
[SCHTROM] Seeing how
different it was for the
commoners exploited here,
I decided to change our future,
and that's just what I did.
[BODYGUARD A]
What country was it?
The proud Kingdom of Earlsheid.
[door creaks]
[ARIA] Darling? Why don't
you come to bed now?
Well. I would, but this
district's yield is lower
than all the others. I'm trying
to find a solution to that.
It's kind of you to work
so hard to help your people,
but I'm starting to worry
about your health.
[SCHTROM]
Oh, Aria.
I'd much rather you concern
yourself with your own health.
Our treasure's on the way.
So let's take good care of it.
[HERALD]
I have a favor to ask of you.
Please summon Oliveira
to the imperial capital
as soon as possible.
Wait, are you referring
to Stradius? The duke?
That's the one. Do you not all
find him to be a nuisance?
Why yes, of course, we do!
He's causing problems!
More and more of our commoners
are moving into his territory!
We're positively furious over
the effect this is having!
And if he continues
to contribute money
to the empire and thus becomes
its greatest underwriter,
then, as I'm sure
you're all aware,
he will eventually ascend
to the emperor's throne.
We can't allow him
to be the emperor!
He's going to implement
policies that favor commoners!
[HERALD] Hm. True. Which is
why I urge you gentlemen
to call Stradius
to the capital.
While he's there, I plan to do
everything in my power to make
sure he won't bother us again.
Are you serious?
That'd be wonderful!
Yes, and it doesn't matter
to me what imaginary reason
you give him for the visit.
You just have to make
sure he stays there.
We'll say it's a reception!
Make him think we want
to have a talk about the
treatment of commoners!
And we can keep adding
sessions indefinitely!
[HERALD chuckles]
Your days are officially
numbered now, Oliveira.
[footsteps]
[SCHTROM]
Aria! Excellent news!
The other nobles,
they sent me this letter.
It says they want to go
along with my ideas!
Congratulations, dear!
But, why now of all times?
Lately, tax revenues
haven't increased as much
as they'd like.
Which means it's harder to
contribute funds to the empire.
If they're late with that,
they risk losing their titles.
They're concerned about
protecting their privilege,
so they're doing
whatever they have to.
It says they'll be holding
a meeting in the capital soon.
They're inviting me to go
teach them some things
about territorial management.
The capital? I don't know.
Are you sure that'd be safe?
[SCHTROM gasps]
[ARIA]
After all, I know some noblemen
see you as having
the upper hand.
What if they're planning on
doing something terrible to you?
[SCHTROM scoffs]
It's fine.
You know how handy
I am at using magic.
That's true.
You are very strong.
People say you're one of the
most prominent magicians
in the empire.
[SCHTROM chuckles]
See, there's no need to worry.
There was a time in my
youth when I worked
as a demon hunter, remember?
So it'd be hard for someone
to assassinate me.
You say that, darling,
but it's not much consolation
since you only did
it for a month.
[SCHTROM gasps] Well,
that's rather harsh of you.
[BOTH laugh]
[ARIA]
Please bring him back safely.
Don't let anything
happen to him.
[TOWNSWOMAN A]
Gone missing?
[TOWNSWOMAN B] That's three.
All women and children!
This is terrible!
And rumor has it,
the same thing's been
happening in other places, too.
[MILITARY POLICE A]
Please excuse me.
Yes sir, how can we help you?
Well, madam. I work for the
capital's military police force.
We've heard there's been
a rash of kidnappings.
‐‐[TOWNSWOMEN gasp]
‐‐[TOWNSWOMAN B] Oh no!
Sh! Keep your voice down.
We've also received
information saying the people
they've abducted have
been sold into slavery.
[TOWNSWOMAN C]
What?
[MILITARY POLICE A]
Yes, it's awful.
Do you know anything?
[FARMER A gasps]
The feudal lord's responsible?
But there's no way
that can be true.
He's always been so kind
to all of us commoners!
[FARMER C] Not according
to what my wife heard.
Turns out, the whole reason he
gathers people like us into his
territory is so he can turn
around and sell them off
as slaves!
Lord Oliveira really does that?
[FARMER C]
Think about it.
Why else would an imperial
feudal lord be so interested in
giving commoners
special treatment?
[FARMER A]
Good point.
[MILITARY POLICE B] Looks like
it's all going as planned.
They're so busy eating
up this fake story,
they haven't figured out
we're not really the police!
[MILITARY POLICE B] Well, we are
dealing with stupid commoners,
after all.
Oliveira's going home, you say?
[NOBLEMAN A] We tried keeping
him busy with everything
from receptions to
management training,
but he wouldn't have it.
He says his wife'll
be delivering soon.
Huh. It's been nearly two
months since we convinced him
to come visit the capital.
Heh! Perhaps it's time we
brought down the curtain.
[MILITARY POLICE A] At long
last, we've been able to pick
up the trail of the
serial kidnapper.
[FARMERS gasp]
But we're going to need
your cooperation
to get our hands on him.
[MILITARY POLICE A]
You! Stop there!
[MILITARY POLICE A] We'll have
to inspect your cargo.
[DRIVER A] But this vehicle
belongs to the duke.
I can't allow you to‐‐
Actually, I'm holding
a writ of examination
from the emperor himself.
Enough of your backtalk!
[FARMERS gasp]
[FARMER H]
It's the abducted women!
[TOWNSWOMAN B]
In the duke's wagon?
[FARMER A] Guess that means the
feudal lord was the kidnapper.
Hard to believe.
Can't the police do
anything about all this?
He's a nobleman!
They can't arrest him
without solid evidence!
[FARMER G] We can't wait
around for the police
to deal with this!
We'll just have to bring
down Oliveira ourselves!
[FARMERS shouting]
Goodness. Why's there
a commotion outside?
[gasps]
[FARMER G growls]
[SCHTROM]
Aria.
I'm sorry for leaving you alone
during such a critical time.
[SCHTROM]
I'll be with you soon.
[gasps]
What's wrong?
Sir! Your home!
[SCHTROM]
Huh?
[gasps]
As soon as I noticed that flames
were rising out of the roof,
I hurried to the mansion.
But the angry masses
had already laid
waste to everything.
By the time I got to the room
my wife was in, it was too late.
[SCHTROM gasps]
[SCHTROM]
Aria! My wife. She's gone.
Why'd you do this?
Don't play dumb!
We know all about
what you did!
You're the one who abducted
those innocent commoner women
and sold them into slavery!
[SCHTROM]
How could you possibly believe
I would do something
so horrible?
[FARMER A]
Don't lie to us!
[FARMER B]
We saw it with our own eyes!
[FARMER C] The wagon
with your crest on it,
the military police!
[SCHTROM]
The military police
would never let civilians
accompany them.
[FARMERS gasp]
Besides, carrying kidnapped
people inside a wagon
that prominently
displays my crest?
You think I would
transport illegal slaves
in such a foolhardy manner?
[FARMERS gasp]
Naturally, I figured it out.
While they used the noblemen
to make me stay in the capital,
they were spreading
harmful rumors about me.
Who was capable of pulling off
such a large‐scale endeavor?
And who had the most
to gain by putting me
in this kind of situation?
[SCHTROM chuckles]
Um... Lord Oliveira, are you?
[SCHTROM] Ah, what a fool
I've been up until now.
[SCHTROM] To have worked so hard
for the good of these cretins,
only to receive evil in return.
And for the empire, which has
always favored the comfort
of the nobility above the
wellbeing of its common people.
All so I could be
stabbed in the back.
Please forgive us, my lord.
We were mistaken!
[SCHTROM]
Forgive you?
After you so rashly
destroyed my entire life?
Do you hear the
nonsensical drivel
spewing out of your
disgusting mouth?
How could I ever forgive
what you've done?
[SCHTROM]
All of you...
That mob...
The noblemen who
put you up to it.
And the fowl empire that allows
such atrocities to occur.
You'll pay! Yes! Everyone!
I swear, you will pay!
[SCHTROM yells]
[FARMERS scream]
[screaming continues]
[SCHTROM laughs]
[SCHTROM]
Mark my words, Blusfia Empire.
I am going to
obliterate everything.
The emperor and every last
member of the nobility.
Not to mention the
lowly commoners I once
strove to protect.
[ZEST]
So, Lawrence.
What are your thoughts after
hearing Master Schtrom's story?
What are my thoughts?
After everything
that he went through,
I kinda understand it.
I mean, the whole empire
turned their backs on him.
Even the commoners
he'd befriended.
[ZEST]
Yes, but at this point,
he's already accomplished
the thing he set out to do.
It's probably for the
best if Master Schtrom
has a new objective
going forward.
You agree with me, don't you?
I guess so, sure.
Better than not, right?
Yes, Lawrence.
Which is why I'd like you to
mix in with those demonoids
who parted ways with our cause
earlier and convince them
to launch an attack on
the Kingdom of Sweed.
[LAWRENCE]
Hm?
Not only is Sweed a smaller
and less powerful nation,
but it also happens
to share a border
with the Kingdom of Earlsheid.
So, it's safe to assume
if a band of demonoids
were to show up there,
he would come running as
fast as he possibly could.
Wait, who is "he"?
[ZEST]
The famous Shin Wolford.
The person who drove
Master Schtrom away? Really?
Indeed, which is precisely what
makes him the perfect target
for our leader to set
his sights on crushing.
Understood. When
the day arrives,
you want to know exactly what
kind of power you're up against.
My! You learn quickly.
I'm entrusting this important
task to you, Lawrence,
so be certain you do
not disappoint me.
[SHIN gasps] Aug really
looks like a prince!
Well, he is a prince.
I ask you, noble August
von Earlsheid.
Do you swear to become the
crown prince, and to endeavor
with all of your
strength and honor
to serve this
magnificent kingdom?
Upon my very life, Sir.
I promise to protect this
nation and its people.
Eloquently spoken.
In that case, I now recognize
you as crown prince.
I expect you to devote
everything you have
in service to our people.
Yes, Your Majesty.
[footsteps]
[MESSENGER A]
I have urgent news!
[gasps]
A large group of demonoids
has just appeared
in the Kingdom of Sweed!
And they're already attacking!
[KNIGHT A] You fool!
How dare you barge in
and report something like that
during this important event!
No. Leave him alone.
[KNIGHTS]
But, sir!
Thank you for the news.
If demonoids attack,
then that takes priority.
Wait a minute,
did that guy just say there
was a demonoid attack?
That's terrible. I sure hope
those people are alright!
Please. Let's not panic.
It's true.
According to the report.
there are demonoids in
the Kingdom of Sweed.
But do not be alarmed.
We have a group to fight them.
We'll resist the demonoids!
You ready?
[gasps]
[AUGUST]
This is Shin Wolford,
grandson of the renowned
Wise Man, Merlin Wolford.
He's also the one who
defeated the demonoid
that appeared recently.
And, I‐‐No.
We have been continually
improving ourselves
under Shin's leadership!
We've gained the strength
we need to stop this!
We'll go to Sweed at once,
and eradicate those demonoids!
[SHIN]
They took them off?
Shin, it's your
turn to speak now.
Wait. My turn?
Yes, this is basically
a performance
to put the people's
minds at ease.
So make it good.
Another thing, think up
a cool name for our team.
Calling us a study group makes
us sound like a bunch of nerds.
[SHIN]
What? Like, right now?
[SHIN] Ladies and gentlemen,
there's nothing to fear.
Everyone here has more than
enough courage and ability
to combat the enemy.
We're...
[SHIN]
Come on, Shin, think fast!
We're the Ultimate
Magic Study Group, so...
The Ultimate, uh...
We promise, we're gonna
take care of those demonoids!
We're the Ultimate Magicians!
[CROWD cheers]
[ALL]
What? The Ultimate Magicians?
[AUGUST chuckles]
[SHIN] Let me guess,
you guys hate it.
I like that name, actually.
Well, I say we go
out with a bang.
We need to make sure
they have plenty of hope.
[SHIN]
Yeah. You're right.
And I know just what to do.
Here goes nothing!
[CROWD gasps]
[SHIN]
Ultimate Magicians, move out!
[ALL]
Right!