[SHIN]
Okay. I'm heading out.
[MERLIN] Alright, best of
luck on your first day.
[MELIDA]
And Shin.
Whatever happens,
think before you act.
[SHIN] Hm. There's no need to
worry about me. I'll be fine.
[SHIN] Well, I haven't picked
up anything abnormal
with my search magic yet.
[SIZILIEN]
Thanks, Shin. And sorry.
[SHIN]
Huh?
For making you come all the way
to my house just to make sure
I get to school safely.
I was happy to do it. And with
a gate, it took next to no time.
I refuse to stand by
when there's a chance
you're in danger. That isn't me.
[gasps] That's so sweet of you.
Ugh. I'm pretty sure I just
threw up in my
mouth a little bit.
[bells ring]
Good morning, Shin.
Already coming to school
with girls in tow, I see.
And so soon after enrolling.
Oh, give it a rest,
will you, Aug?
You know why I'm doing this.
Yeah. But that doesn't make
it any less fun to mock you.
Uh-huh.
It's a pleasure
to see you, Shin.
We wish you a fine morning.
[SHIN]
Right back at'cha.
[ALICE yelps]
I actually made it!
I'm not late, am I?
I'm okay, right?
Um. Yeah.
You made it, but what
gives with you barely
managing to show up on time
on the first day of school?
Oh, I was so excited
about our first day,
I had the hardest time
falling asleep last night.
And then, of course,
I overslept.
What, are you a child?
[SHIN]
I mean, officially,
you're an adult at 15
in this world, so...
[door clatters]
[ALFRED]
I assume everyone's here?
I think that's right.
How are you today, Teach? Good?
I'm all right.
Now take your seats.
We're about to start homeroom.
Once we finish in here,
I'll show you around the school.
[ALFRED]
Here's the basic breakdown.
The school is broadly
divided into two buildings.
One of them holds
all the classrooms.
And the other one has
the faculty offices
and the student council room.
As well as the rooms used
for labs and study groups.
[SHIN] Study groups?
Are those like clubs?
[ALFRED] There's the Attack
Magic Study Group...
[ALFRED] The Quality
of Life Study Group...
They come up with Magic Gear.
And the Body Language
Study Group.
They use magic to increase
their physical strength.
[SHIN]
What was that last one?
That seems like a pretty
weird way to use magic.
The Body Language Study
Group sounds great.
If I weren't dutybound
to guard His Highness,
I would apply to join that
study group in a heartbeat!
Look Julius, you don't
have to worry about me.
If you want to join
the group, go for it.
[JULIUS gasps] No. I wouldn't
even dream of it, Your Highness.
[AUGUST sighs]
This is the magic academy.
As long as we're
on these grounds,
my royal blood is
completely irrelevant.
There's no reason you
should have to guard me
the whole time we're here.
Your Highness! I'll never forget
the kindness you've shown me.
[SHIN] He's saying it's
because of that school rule,
but it's clear he just
doesn't want to be escorted.
Is there a particular study
group you wanna join, Shin?
[SHIN]
No, not really.
Guess that makes sense.
I doubt they would be
able to teach you much.
That's not what I
was trying to say.
Here's a thought. You should
start your own study group.
[SHIN]
Huh?
Oho. A study group
created by Wolford?
That may well be interesting.
I thought the same thing.
So, hypothetically, if you
were to start a study group,
what kind of magic do you
think you'd focus on?
Regardless, I'm quite intrigued.
I would join whatever
the subject is!
I think I'd look
into it as well.
Same here. What better
way to stay in S-Class
than to study with you, Shin.
[AUGUST]
All right.
So what does it take to
start a study group, anyway?
Five or more members
and a faculty adviser.
Once you've lined all that up,
you just need to submit a
request form and you're set.
If you kids ask nicely,
I'm willing to be your advisor.
[ALL cheer]
[SHIN] Can we slow this
bandwagon down, please?
It's fine if you don't want
to start a study group,
but if you did then I
would definitely join it.
Huh?
Well, it only makes sense.
If you're gonna be taking
her home, then you may as well
do extra-curriculars together.
[SHIN]
Huh. I guess you're right.
So once you're president
of your own study group,
what will you name it,
and what will we do?
[SHIN] I haven't even
agreed to this yet!
I know, let's make it
a hero study group!
Wait. What does that mean?
I kinda figured you'd spend
the whole time telling us
stories about Merlin and Melida!
[yelps]
That isn't a bad idea,
but unfortunately,
there's already a study
group that follows
the heroes' exploits.
[SHIN]
There is?
[LYN] In that case, why don't
we all just focus on mastering
different kinds of magic,
using Shin as a tutor.
[SHIN]
Huh?
I can see it now, we'll call it
the Ultimate Magic Study Group!
[SHIN] You're killing me, Lyn.
I'm actually gonna die.
Yeah, I like it.
"The Ultimate Magic
Study Group" sounds great.
And with Shin here,
it's quite fitting.
[SHIN]
Huh?
That settles it,
we'll be known as the
Ultimate Magic Study Group.
It'll be awesome!
Aren't we getting ahead
of ourselves here?
Shin's right, you can work
that out after class.
[SHIN groans]
[ALFRED] Everyone who
wants to join, sound off.
[ALL]
I do!
[SHIN] Can we please take
out the "ultimate" part?
So just in the last year,
the number of demon sightings
has gone up by this
large an amount?
But how? If demons
are proliferating as this
would imply, the whole kingdom
should be in a state of chaos
[OFFICIAL A]
That's true.
But the people seem to be
calm for the most part.
What do you make of
this puzzle, Dominic?
If you look closely
at the daily reports,
I'm sure it will be clear.
The day by day growth
in their numbers would
seem quite negligible.
No single increase went
outside the margin of error.
Hence why we didn't
notice this before.
[DISEUM]
Hm...
[DOMINIC] We had to look at
the data over the course
of this whole year to
see what was happening.
It's almost as though it
were planned that way.
One might even think this
was artificially induced.
That's ridiculous!
There's no way these
demons were made by men!
My King. It's a
strange situation.
We should launch an
investigation at once.
[DISEUM]
Very well.
Enlist the aid of the
Demon Hunters' Society
and investigate this
matter thoroughly.
[DOMINIC]
As you wish.
[RUSSELL]
Kurt...! Kurt! Come here!
What do you want now, Daddy?
Drop that defiant
tone at once.
I've received a
summons from the king.
And I'm sure you know why.
[growls]
[RUSSELL] Idiot! The hell
were you thinking?
We nobles are forbidden from
throwing around our influence
at the Magic Academy.
I've told you that!
With respect, Father,
it's a fact that no
commoner is my equal.
I refuse to pretend
that's not the case.
Not for you or anyone else!
Kurt. What is this? Where did
this ignorance come from?
[KURT] I'm chosen!
Destined to be special!
It's obvious that I'm
better than the rest!
And yet everyone I meet
disrespects and defies me!
[KURT growls] It isn't right!
I won't stand for it, I won't!
[gasps]
[KURT]
It's Wolford's fault.
Everything would have been
just fine if he hadn't shown up.
I can't even do as I
please with my girl now.
And what's more,
he went and turned His Highness
against me too. They'll pay.
You fool!
[KURT yelps]
I cannot turn a blind eye
to a statement like that!
I'll inform you of your
punishment shortly!
[RUSSELL] You! Take my son to
his room and lock the door.
[KURT grunts]
When did it come
to this, Kurt? And how?
Kurt's dad grounded
him from school?
Yes.
If I heard right, the Rietsburgs
told the school this morning.
[SHIN] So, if it's
all right to ask,
why does Kurt have such
an attitude, anyway?
No one else throws their
name around. What's his problem?
[THOR, JULIUS grunt]
Frankly, we've been
wondering that too.
Julius and I attended
middle school with Kurt,
as did His Highness
and he didn't act anything
like this in those days.
I suppose he could be a
little cocky at times.
But aside from that,
he was normal.
I think I know when
the change began.
It was right after
he started visiting
Mr. Schtrom's laboratory.
Come to think of it,
you're right.
Who's Mr. Schtrom?
[THOR] In our third
year of middle school,
he transferred in
as a magic teacher.
He said he was exiled from
the Empire. I'm not sure why.
[AUGUST] He ended up gathering
every student who was
half-decent with magic and
inviting the lot of us to come
and visit his laboratory.
Though it sounded shady to us,
so we turned him down.
Plus, he covers his eyes,
which originally made me
think that he was blind.
Although he never
seemed to show it.
Most search magic spells
only detect living things,
but I guess he might've used
a different version of one.
A magician who keeps
his eyes covered,
and who claims to be in
exile from the empire.
[door clatters]
[MRS. RIETSBURG gasps]
Mr. Schtrom!
Thank you so much for coming!
[SCHTROM] It's been far
too long, Mrs. Rietsburg.
How's your son doing?
Any changes?
Not yet. He's been the
same since we called you.
I don't understand
what happened.
Why would my sweet boy
start acting so horrible?
My husband's attempts
to discipline him
haven't helped at all.
The way things seem to
be going, I fear the worst!
Don't be afraid.
Your son looks up to me as his
teacher, you were right to call.
Take me to him,
he'll listen to me.
[MRS. RIETSBURG]
Thank you, Mr. Schtrom!
You're the only
person I can turn to.
Please, bring my son
back to his senses!
[door clutters]
[SCHTROM]
Hello, Kurt.
[KURT]
Mr. Schtrom?
I don't believe I've ever seen
you in such a pathetic state,
my boy.
[SCHTROM]
I told you that you're special.
You remember, right?
[KURT]
Yes.
Everything that you see in
this world is yours to take.
Your breeding and your
power give you that right.
I tried. I told the girl
that she was mine.
But then this guy came
and got in my way!
Did he, now? Sounds to me
like he's an obstacle.
A nuisance to be dealt with.
[KURT gasps]
[SCHTROM]
So deal with it.
Crush him underfoot, and sweep
him aside. You are special.
He is nothing.
[KURT groans]
[chuckles]
[SCHTROM]
Go forth.
Dance as best for me
as you can, my puppet.
[STUDENTS chatter]
[AUGUST] So, Shin, do you
plan to keep taking
Sizilien to school?
Well, why wouldn't I?
Kurt isn't allowed to leave
his house anymore.
So there's not too much chance
of him attacking her now,
is there?
[SHIN] Oh. You're right. So she
has no need for an escort.
[SIZILIEN gasps]
Yeah. So it goes.
Shin was just an escort.
Still, I don't think
there's any harm
in walking her to school anyway.
[SIZILIEN]
Huh?
Our houses are in
the same direction.
[SIZILIEN]
Yes! We should do that!
Like you said,
it's the same direction!
So why not walk to
school together?
It's a perfectly
natural thing to do,
there's nothing weird
about it at all!
[ALL]
Uh-huh...
[SIZILIEN gasps]
I'm so sorry.
Ya have a little
trouble containing
your excitement there?
No, I'm just fine.
That was an impressive play.
[SHIN]
Huh?
You're so direct. You wish
to never leave her side?
I don't think I could
ever be so bold.
[SHIN gasps] I didn't
say it like that, did I?
[AUGUST]
I was just teasing.
But all jokes aside, it's good
that you'll be walking together.
Even without Kurt around,
Klode and Messina
are pretty girls.
They may well attract
more unsavory characters.
Well, If that happens,
my Search Magic'll find them
before they do anything.
How does that work?
The normal way.
Don't you pick it up
when someone's directing
ill will at you?
[THOR]
I can use Search Magic,
but I can't sense
malice with it.
Oh. Huh. So then, have you
ever hunted a demon?
No way, I've never done
anything like that.
I thought that was a given,
since I only just got
out of middle school.
They have a distinctive aura.
Demon magic feels sinister.
You can sense its aggression.
Feels kind of gross.
Using that for reference,
I can tell if a human wants
to hurt someone too.
What are you saying right now?
Are you implying that you
have hunted demons before?
Yup.
[THOR, LYN, AUGUST gasp]
If you don't mind my asking,
how old were you the first time?
I was ten.
[ALL]
You were just ten?
It was a demon bear,
as I recall.
[ALL]
A bear?
Yeah, it was about
three meters tall.
Had to cut the thing's head off.
[ALL gasp]
Uh, what's wrong?
[SHIN] Uh-oh. Think I
went and did it again.
[SHIN] So. Which part of
this weirded you out?
[ALL]
All of it, Shin.
[MARIA] Now we've gotta do
Study Group Orientation.
Seems a bit pointless,
I mean we've already decided
that we're gonna start the
Ultimate Magic Study Group.
It does feel like a waste of
time to have them tell us
about study groups that we
have no intention of joining.
We should play along anyway.
If we refuse to participate,
some of our classmates
might feel insulted.
[SHIN gasps]
[SHIN]
Such tremendous malice.
And it's aimed at us.
[KURT laughs]
It's Kurt!
[ALL gasp]
[SHIN]
Damn it!
[SHIN grunts]
Sizilien, Aug! Your uniforms!
Channel magic energy into them!
[BOTH gasp]
[KURT yells]
[TONY grunts]
He made a magic barrier.
[SHIN pants]
Oh, no. You're hurt!
I should be all right.
My auto healing is kicking in.
I can feel it.
[SIZILIEN, AUGUST sigh]
[SHIN]
His attack was so sudden.
I didn't have time to completely
visualize my barrier.
[AUGUST] What does he
think he's doing here?
[MARIA] Isn't he supposed
to be grounded right now?
That spell was powerful.
I think he wanted to kill us.
Yeah. That was attempted murder.
There's no way we
can let this slide.
[KURT growls]
Damn you, damn you, damn you,
damn you, damn you, damn you!
[KURT gasps]
Damn you...! Damn you!
So what do you think, Aug?
Is Kurt in control of himself?
[AUGUST]
There's no way.
It's bad, right?
Bad as it gets.
Damn you, damn you, damn you,
damn you, damn you!
[ALL gasp]
[KURT screams]
Is this for real?
[groans]
[SHIN]
He's turned into a demonoid.
Aug, you take the
others and run.
[AUGUST gasps]
Wait, you're not going--
One way or another,
I'll stop him.
That's crazy! Come with us!
[SHIN] I won't let him
rampage through the capital.
Then I'll help.
You've never fought a
demon before. Don't be stupid.
[AUGUST grunts] So we would
only get in the way?
[ALL gasp]
[SHIN]
Yes. You're in my way.
I see.
[KURT screams]
Let's get out of here, now!
No! I won't leave Shin
to fight by himself!
We would only slow him down!
[SIZILIEN]
I don't care!
Messina! Drag Klode
out if you have to!
[MARIA]
Um, right! We're leaving!
[SIZILIEN shouts]
[AUGUST]
You need to go with them.
You two find the
nearest teachers
and tell them what's happening!
[THOR, JULIUS]
Right!
I'm ready when you are.
Come at me.
[screams]
[shouts]
[SHIN, KURT grunting]
[SHIN gasps]
Did that actually do damage?
I only hoped it
would slow him down.
[KURT grunts]
I hate you, Wolford. Just die!
[SHIN]
A demonoid that can still speak?
This isn't like what
Grandpa told me.
He said demonoids were supposed
to lose all sense of reason.
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
Wolford!
[SHIN, KURT shout]
[SHIN]
That really is hurting him.
I think this means he hasn't
completely turned yet.
Then maybe there's a
way to turn him back.
[KURT yells]
[SHIN] If I can find a way to
control the magic that's
demonizing Kurt, I can save him!
Die! Wolford!
[SHIN gasps]
It can't be.
He's condensing magic within
himself to make an explosion!
No way!
Damn it! With that
much magic power,
he could destroy
the entire academy!
It's over, Wolford!
[SHIN] What do I do?
What can I do?
[KURT yells]
[SHIN] I'm out of time.
There's no choice.
[KURT screams]
[SHIN]
Kurt... I'm sorry!
--[SHIN gasps]
--[thudding]
[SHIN] I've never killed
a person before.
[SHIN] Damn it. What's going on?
How'd this happen?
[ALL pant]
[AUGUST]
Are you all right? Shin!
[ALL]
Uh?
[SIZILIEN] Oh Shin.
You're okay, aren't you?
Tell me you're not hurt!
No. I'm all right.
I can't believe you actually
took down a demonoid
in a one on one fight.
[SHIN]
You saw the whole thing?
Yeah.
[ALL]
Mm-hm.
Was there another way?
Could I have saved him?
[SIZILIEN]
Huh?
[SHIN]
He was stalking you, Sizilien.
And if I hadn't stopped him, he
would've killed everyone here.
But even so...
Oh, Shin.
[AUGUST] Things are going
to be rough for you
from here on out, Shin.
Yeah.
In our whole history,
two demonoids have attacked us.
And you bested one of
them just like that.
This'll be a huge story.
[JULIUS]
Your Highness!
[THOR gasps]
Are you alright?
[MALE CAPTAIN A] We were told
there'd been a demonoid attack!
Did you see where
the fiend went?
His corpse is
lying right there.
[ALL gasp]
[MALE CAPTAIN A]
Hold on.
Are you saying that you brought
it down, Your Highness?
No, it wasn't me.
All of you! Bear witness!
The demonoid was slain by him!
Shin Wolford!
Grandson of the Wise Man!
[MALE CAPTAIN A gasps]
[SOLDIERS shout]
He took down a
demonoid by himself?
[MALE SOLDIER B] He really
is the Wise Man's Grandson!
Our country has a new hero!
Yeah, and his name's
Shin Wolford!
[SOLDIERS chanting] Shi-in!
Shi-in! Shi-in! Shi-in...!
Thanks guys,
but I really don't--
[AUGUST chuckles]
[SHIN gasps]
[SHIN] Well, he did say things
would get rough for me.