[KNIGHTS gasp]
[BEAR growls]
[MIRANDA]
A demon bear.
[KREIS]
It's fine. Stand firm.
Let's do this. You ready?
[MARIA, SIZILIEN]
Yeah.
[ALL grunt]
[roars]
Wolford saved him!
Now, finish it!
[ALL grunt]
[SIZILIEN] Well done, everyone!
Was anyone injured at all?
Just a few scratches.
Yeah, nothing bad.
[SIZILIEN] Then it's nothing
my spells can't heal.
The kids are starting
to shape up.
I agree. Now that the knights
get how useful magic is,
we're actually seeing teamwork.
Your team is strong.
Much like you.
What's the secret to
their improvement?
They're already at the
same level as some of our
best court magicians.
Maybe even better than that.
My classmates and I formed a
new study group at the academy,
and the three of them
are all members.
Are you doing some kind
of special training?
[SHIN] No, not really.
We've just been practicing magic
in the same way I
learned from Grandpa.
Is there really nothing else?
You're sure?
Well, uh. I did teach them how
I visualize magic as I use it.
[SIEGFRIED] That's it,
the way you visualize magic!
So, they're basically
learning magic
in the same way
you did, right?
You've taught them the basics of
Merlin's teachings. Amazing!
[SHIN]
I don't know.
Grandpa taught me
how to use magic,
but I don't visualize it
quite it like he does.
That's meant to be
unique for everyone.
Could you tell me what
you told your classmates?
I have room for improvement.
Yeah. I don't see why not.
[SIEGFRIED]
Hm!
[AUGUST]
Hold on, Shin.
Sorry Siegfried, but my
father made a promise.
The Kingdom isn't to
militarize Shin's power.
And you're a soldier, so that
may well cross the line.
[SIEGFRIED]
You're right.
We're pushing it
as things are now.
If this kind of power
spreads to more countries,
forget about demons.
Humans'll destroy the
world themselves.
The stakes are
actually that high?
[AUGUST groans] How have
you not realized that yet?
[SHIN] I dunno. Is what
I'm doing really a problem?
No. I wouldn't say that.
With the massive
outbreak of demonoids,
we're in a state of emergency.
I've told the members
of our study group
to keep the secret of their
new powers to themselves.
I don't care if we're
monopolizing it.
So, if you don't mind, I'd like
you to keep it a secret too.
Fine. I get it.
Fair enough, but could you just
tell me how you practice?
To be honest,
it's terribly ordinary.
You sure you're interested?
Of course. For power like that?
Go ahead. What's the secret?
Just practice your
magic control.
It's like exercise.
Every day you do it,
you'll be able to manage a
little bit more. That's it.
Is that actually
all I have to do?
Course it is.
Do you think I'd lie?
Klode, would you and
Messina come here?
[GIRLS]
Hm?
[MARIA]
What do you need?
So Sieg can see, would you mind
making some magic barriers?
Like Shin had you do when
the study group started.
[SIZILIEN]
Sure.
[MARIA]
Yeah, why not?
[MARIA, SIZILIEN grunt]
Whoa. No way. How can
those barriers be so thick?
[KNIGHTS]
Hm?
Strange, right?
We never knew that basic
spells could be this strong.
But once Shin trained
us in magic control,
they got like this.
Our barriers are
still pretty thin.
Compared to one
of Shin's, at least.
Wait, do you really
call that thin?
We still have a
whole lot to learn,
my technique's
pretty shoddy.
[SIEGFRIED]
No.
You should have more
faith in yourself.
In my eyes your magic technique
is incredible, Maria.
Anyway, I'll try your
training method too.
The exercise is over.
Head for the rendezvous point.
[ALL]
Right!
Thanks, Shin.
It's because of you that
we beat that demon bear.
[SHIN chuckles]
I see why magicians and fighters
should work together now.
Good. I'm glad to hear it.
That makes me wonder.
How'd the other teams do?
[JULIO growls]
[JULIUS] That guy seems a
little mad at you, Tony.
[TONY chuckles nervously]
So do you two have history?
Oh yeah.
Me and Julio have known each
other since middle school.
[ALL]
Mm?
Gah. Tony Freyd.
How dare you give
up knighthood, you weakling!
Well, there ya have it.
I'm from a knightly
family line too,
but no one got that mad at me.
[WOLF A growls]
A demon!
Don't go in until
we've weakened it!
As if you could!
No, hold on!
In an honest battle, magic is
nothing against steel!
You fool! This is
called joint training!
[MALE KNIGHT STUDENT A]
We're going in too!
[MALE KNIGHT STUDENTS]
Yeah!
Come back!
[MALE KNIGHT STUDENTS yell]
[JULIO grunts]
Damn. It got me!
[WOLF A yelps]
[WOLFS yelping]
[gasps]
[JULIO growls]
Hey, you all right?
Mind your own business, Tony.
He just saved you,
don't be such a jerk!
It seems to me he's upset
he was outdone by you.
We've always gotten
along really well.
But lately, he seems to
flare up at every little thing.
You must've done something.
[TONY] Hm... Huh. I guess
that could be it...
He had a crush on this girl who
randomly declared her love
for me, and I
dated her a bit.
[ALL]
Yeah, that would do it.
But we broke up so quickly.
I barely kissed her.
[ALL gasp]
[MARK]
Wow, the resentment runs deep.
[THOR groan]
If ya get scared, then you
can stand behind me.
Sorry they're makin' ya
come out here, tootz.
I'm sure you'd prefer deskwork.
You truly are a beautiful girl,
but wouldn't you be better off
learning how to keep
a house maintained?
Don't get any stupid
ideas and try to show off
to your lady friends, Sprout.
You'll just get hurt.
We're here to train.
Only speak when you have to.
--[MALE INSTRUCTOR B] Hear that?
--[WOLVES howl]
[MALE KNIGHT STUDENT D]
They're comin' toward us.
You sprouts watch and learn.
[MALE KNIGHT STUDENTS laugh]
Ya know what? I say we let
the demons eat them.
Yeah, these guys are
pretty worthless.
They're so disgusting.
[MALE KNIGHT STUDENT D]
Stupid mutt!
[ALICE growls]
What do you take me for?!
[GIRLS groan]
[MALE KNIGHT STUDENTS shouting]
[MALE KNIGHT STUDENTS gasp]
[ALICE]
That's it!
Just get out of
our way, you jerks!
[YURI] I think you boys
need to cool down.
[LYN gasps] I don't think
I can control all of this.
[THOR]
Get back! Run!
[ALL yell]
[SHIN] It looks like
the rest of our class
managed to get some
teamwork going.
So what exactly happened
with your team?
Well, we flexed our powers a
little more than we meant to
and there were side-effects.
The guys from the
Knight Military Institute
started it, okay?
Although we did
get carried away.
What's that guy's deal?
[MARK]
Just your typical teenage drama.
[SHIN]
Huh?
So uh, we beat our demons,
but it wasn't really
through teamwork.
Did the demon hunt go
well for your team, Wolford?
Yeah, it went okay.
Shin and Sizilien
spent the whole time
cozying up to each other.
Huh?
I don't know what you mean,
we didn't cozy up at all!
If you didn't think
that was cozying up,
then I can't imagine what
would actually count to you.
It must be steamy.
[SHIN]
Dude, shut up!
Putting all jokes aside though,
I'd say that our joint
training went pretty well.
The Knights in training
certainly learned a lot.
And on top of that, Shin gave
us time to help for once.
[SHIN]
Wait. "For once"?
Huh. I guess he's right.
[ALICE]
Hey. You doin' okay, Shin?
[MARIA] I think he feels
responsible for what's
happened to everyone
in the study group.
[YURI]
Responsible?
[TONY]
How so?
Well, here goes...
You should know something.
Once we graduate
from the academy,
all of us in the Ultimate Magic
Study group, aside from Shin,
will be placed under the
Kingdom's supervision.
Chances are, we'll be
turned into a special unit,
led by me personally.
[SHIN]
I'm really sorry.
I didn't realize I'd be
upending all of your lives.
But it isn't like that, Shin!
Huh?
All our futures
are secure now!
[LYN]
Agreed!
[MARK] We're gonna be
the best of the best!
[YURI] My parents'll be
so proud when they hear!
Hold on. You're all
happy about this?
[AUGUST chuckles] Provided that
none of us abuse it,
this power you taught us may
well end up saving the world.
Right.
If you ask me, Shin, you're the
brightest hope this world has.
If we're gonna fight demonoids,
it would be nice if you
could teach us more.
[SHIN]
Yeah, I guess they're right.
For us to protect the
world from this crisis,
I'll need them all to
get even stronger.
[AUGUST]
Hey. We should be alright,
since I'll be here to keep
things under control.
But keep in mind
that we have limits.
Y'know, it's funny you
should say that.
I'm starting to think
you're a mind-reader, Aug.
[AUGUST]
Hm.
Oh, no. Not when
it comes to you.
You pretty much write your
thoughts all over your face.
[SHIN chuckles]
Am I that easy to read?
[OLIVIA shouts]
[ALICE shouts]
[YURI]
Lyn!
[LYN]
Got it!
[AUGUST] It's like a live-fire
Magic Division exercise.
We can't let anyone see this.
I've used this location to
practice for a long time.
It's far from any people.
[YURI]
You okay?
[AUGUST]
Hey, All of us need to talk.
[AUGUST] We have new
intel on the demonoids.
Earlsheid's civilians
aren't being told yet.
So you're just gonna
tell us a state secret?
Yeah, um, maybe you'd be better
off telling Shin in private,
Your Highness.
[AUGUST] I'm telling you all.
And for good reason.
You aren't just
civilians anymore.
When war breaks out
with the demons,
we'll be a key part of
Earlsheid's army.
Demons?
When you start
talking like that,
it really hits home that we're
different from most people now.
I guess you weren't kidding
about the special unit.
We need to learn a lot
more magic, and quickly.
[SHIN] So, what's this
new information?
It's the Empire. Demonoids are
rampaging across it unchecked.
The damage done to their towns
and cities has been disastrous.
Every last member of their
nobility has been killed.
As have most of their commoners.
We're talking about
demonoids here.
So stepping in is a huge risk.
If we're to stand
against them,
we'll need to form a
coalition of nations.
[BOYS grunt]
Countless people are suffering,
yet we have no choice
but to watch and wait?
That's right. And worse,
the demonoids' numbers
increase with each attack.
[ALL gasp]
[AUGUST]
It's crazy,
but they must be turning
civilians somehow.
Like what happened to Kurt.
[AUGUST]
Probably.
[SHIN]
Schtrom. What are you thinking?
Even a single demonoid
is enough of a threat
to rock a whole nation.
This calls for one thing.
[ALL]
A training camp?
Sounds great! I'm in! Let's go!
[SHIN] Summer break is
coming up soon, right?
[AUGUST] That's true.
We'll have lots of spare time.
Yeah. Right. But if we're
gonna take on demonoids,
we need to get stronger
as fast as we can.
We'll study spells from
dawn to dusk! I can't wait!
So, where should we
hold this camp?
[SHIN] Hm. I'd like to do the
magic exercises right here,
but we could sleep
somewhere else and come here
in the mornings by Gate.
[AUGUST] Let's stay on the
family land of someone here.
[SHIN]
Say what?
[AUGUST] Nobles tend to be
landowners, as a general rule.
My family owns a city
district full of craftsmen.
My family has a seaport.
But there aren't any good
places to stay there.
My family owns a nice
little resort town.
[SHIN]
Never would've guessed that one.
Sounds nice. Why don't
we stay out there?
Sounds too luxurious.
We would risk looking apathetic
about the demon scare.
Yes, I think His
Highness is right.
[MARIA] Ah! Sizilien's place
might be a nice compromise.
[SIZILIEN]
Hm?
Ya see, her family owns a
town with a hot spring.
[SHIN]
Can we use it?
Yeah. If that's okay
with everyone.
Sounds perfect to me.
Great!
[MELIDA]
A summer training camp?
Oh ho. Well with recent events,
I can see why you'd want
to train your classmates
all that you can.
So tell me, have you
found a supervisor yet?
[SHIN]
Supervisor?
As I expected.
You're planning to have boys and
girls who think they're adults
sleeping under the same
roof in this place!
I will not permit you
students to romp about
there unsupervised!
Kay. I get it.
Especially since Aug's royalty.
[MELIDA]
Yes indeed.
And I have to imagine that the
parents of the other study group
members will be
busy working.
I suppose I can make some time,
as a special favor to you.
[SHIN gasps]
You sure?
I can come too,
if you want me there.
[MELIDA]
Huh?
That would be great!
[MELIDA] Nothing good ever comes
from us taking our eyes off you.
Huh? C'mon, I've been way
more careful lately, at least.
[MELIDA]
Is that a fact?
Not even I can back you
up on that point, Shin.
Don't talk as though he didn't
learn his recklessness from you.
[MERLIN gasps, sobs]
[SHIN]
Hang in there, Grandpa.
[ROOSTER crows]
[ALL]
Good morning!
Hi, Master Wise Man!
And Mistress Guru!
Ah. Hello to you as well.
How's everyone doing?
[ALL] Great! Thanks a lot
for coming out with us.
[SHIN] We won't reach
the spring for two days.
Will the horses be
okay in this heat?
[AUGUST]
Of course.
They have enchanted harnesses,
they'll be fine.
[MARIA]
Those harnesses are great.
They're enchanted with
fatigue restoration,
physical enhancement,
and a few other things, too.
[SHIN]
Huh?
Please tell me that
you at least know
who it was that
first developed them.
Who?
Oh boy.
It was your Grandmother,
Lady Melida.
[SHIN]
Huh?
Back in the day,
enchantments were mostly
just used for combat gear.
But Lady Melida saw their
potential in everyday living.
She made all kinds
of great things.
[AUGUST] The enchanted
items she came up with
improved countless lives.
And because of the
breadth of her influence,
we show our respect by
calling her the "Guru."
Huh...
Stop eying me like
some kind of freak show.
What? I was just thinking
of how amazing you are.
Eh, all that was
a long time ago.
And she didn't know how
to politely take a compliment
back then either.
[MELIDA grunts]
[SHIN]
It stands to reason.
[MELIDA] That's enough!
Leave me alone, both of you!
[gasps]
Hey. You sense that?
Yeah. It's a pack of demons.
They aren't that large,
but there're lots of them.
[WOLVES growling]
[COACHMEN gasp]
So, who should take them?
I can beat them easily!
You're not the only one.
I'd like to take
a crack at this.
[SHIN]
Guess we'd better draw straws.
Y'know, those are kind of
weird things to keep in your
other-dimensional storage.
I like to be prepared.
Eh...
[ALICE]
Ready, set...
[ALL]
Go!
Oh, cool. I won.
Aw... I wanted to fight them.
[ALICE sneezes]
Piece of cake.
[SHIN] If you rein in your magic
power just a little more,
you'll be able to engage
it quicker next time.
Good to know.
I'll keep working at it.
The girl defeated
that many demons?
With a single spell.
Who are we driving?
Seems Shin's quite the teacher,
seeing how they've improved.
I can't believe we're doing
this to other people's children.
[LYN] You wouldn't say that if
you'd just went!
[MERLIN laughs]
[SIZILIEN] Ah! Welcome to
the city of Klode!
[SHIN] Whoa. It's like the
whole town's a hot spring.
[SIZILIEN] Everyone,
this is it. Hope you like it.
[SERVANTS]
Welcome back, Miss Sizilien.
It's wonderful to see you.
[SIZILIEN]
Likewise, it's been too long!
Good evening, Prince August.
Master Wise Man.
Mistress Guru. You do us a great
honor by visiting this place.
As for Miss Sizilien's peers,
all of you are most welcome.
That goes especially for
our new hero, Shin Wolford.
[SERVANTS] It's our hope
that you and Miss Sizilien
will enjoy a long and
fruitful life together.
[SIZILIEN] Wha--?
Wh-Why would you say that?
What's gotten into you?
We haven't even broached
that subject yet!
What do you guys want?
[AUGUST]
Nothing.
I'm sure we're all tired after
the long journey today.
Let's unwind for a bit.
[SHIN]
Ah... This is amazing. Wow.
Y'can't beat a soak
in a hot spring.
This water's given me new life.
I'd like to thank
all of you boys
for befriending my grandson.
Wait. What?
[MERLIN] For 15 years, he never
once had a friend his own age.
I wasn't sure he had the right
experience to fit in at school.
But, my fears were
proved unfounded.
Shin quickly found his way
into the hearts of many
fine young friends.
I thank each of you for
giving him that chance.
[AUGUST] With respect, Merlin,
you have it backwards.
I should be thanking you.
I'm the First Prince
of this kingdom.
No friend ever looked
at me as an equal.
They'd all pander to
my every stupid whim.
But Shin? He doesn't care
what I can do for him
once I become king.
In his eyes,
I'm nothing but a cousin.
Wow. Aug.
[MARK] We, like, just met.
But I'm glad we did.
You've done a lot
for me and Dad.
When we hang out, there's never
have a dull moment.
Thanks for the good times.
To be honest, A lot of
my peers in the nobility
tend to treat me
like I don't belong,
but Shin just treats me
like I'm one of the guys.
There's no trace of
judgement in his eyes.
I may prefer female company, but
as guys go, I like this group.
It is a good group. Grandpa?
Huh?
[SHIN]
I'm still grateful to you.
For raising me, and training me.
If it weren't for you, I don't
think I'd be who I am right now.
[SHIN] Because of who
you helped me to become,
I've made so many great friends.
So thanks again, Grandpa.
[MERLIN sobs]
[SHIN] Crap. I was trying
to make him happy.
[OLIVIA]
Amazing! This bath is huge!
[ALICE]
I'm so excited to jump in!
It feels so nice.
I can feel the day's
fatigue melting away.
[MELIDA sighs] It warms me
right down to my bones.
I'm so glad to hear
you're enjoying it!
Is something wrong?
Oh! Sorry.
To be honest, I was just
thinking you have a nice figure.
[MELIDA]
Hm?
What's your secret?
There must be something!
[MELIDA] Well, I do exercise
using the equipment
Shin made for me.
[MARIA]
Equipment?
It's a wide belt that
can move itself.
I've been making
an effort to run,
or at least walk on it every
single day of the week.
That sounds awesome, would you
mind letting me use it sometime?
I'd like to try it as well!
[MELIDA]
I don't mind if you don't.
But I feel compelled
to warn you.
There's a chance it'll
make your breasts shrink.
[ALICE, LYN gasp]
If you want to increase
your size,
then take it up with
your classmates.
She must know something.
Same goes for her.
Wow! These are really something!
That settles it. I want
a pair just like 'em!
They're firm and sensitive.
[GIRLS shouting]
[MARIA chuckles]
[MARIA] Thought'cha
could slip by, did you?
[BOTH groan]
[OLIVIA gasps]
[MARIA]
So why does exercising
too much make your
breasts smaller?
Let me remember
how Shin put it.
When you move around a lot,
you burn through fat.
And if you should run
low on fat to burn,
your body will resort to
using the fat in your breasts.
[ALICE sighs]
[MARIA] That's crazy. How did
Shin know something like that?
That boy's been going off to
do experiments on his own
since he was a child.
My best guess is that he found
out through one of those.
[MARIA]
I see.
Say. It dawned on me quite
recently that Shin grew up
with no one he could
call his friend.
So I wanted to tell you
girls how grateful I am
that he has all of you
to call his friends now.
Lady Melida, you're more
than welcome.
I don't think anybody could
be more grateful that Shin's
in my life than I am.
And the same more or less
goes for the rest of us.
Shin's an incredible guy!
Shin teaches us lots
of amazing magic!
We really have gained a
lot from his friendship.
We're super lucky.
Sure are!
You girls are so sweet.
Okay.
I'm sure Shin does what he can,
but if you're to learn quickly,
you'll need teachers
with experience!
[ALL]
Huh?
You're not talking about
you and Merlin, are you?
[YURI]
You're gonna teach us?
Yes. And in return, you'll work
harder than you ever have!
So get ready!
[GIRLS]
Right!
[GIRLS chatter]
[MELIDA chuckles]
This ought to be enjoyable.