[♪]
ASTRO:
Look! A Komodo dragon!
ZORAN:
I've never seen animals
like this before.
It's amazing!
I know!
That's 'cause this is
a game preserve.
Check out that herd
of wildebeests.
Wow, they're fast.
Can I ride one?
DR. O'SHAY:
No, and you can't play
with the cheetahs either.
The game preserve
is here to protect
the animals.
All these animals
are in danger, right?
That's why they
need protection?
Exactly. Some selfish
people hunt them
for ivory or fur.
And others
cut down forests
so there's
no place left
for them to live.
That's awful!
How can they be so cruel?
I wish I knew,
Zoran,
but some people
just don't respect
the world around them.
That's why we have to
step in and help.
Then let's stop
all the people
who hunt them.
It's not that easy,
Zoran.
There's lots of them,
and they're hard to catch.
Really?
He's right.
We can't go out and catch
all the bad guys,
so we have to guard
the animals.
That's why this game preserve
is so important.
We can bring the animals here
and protect them from anyone
that might harm them.
[MONKEYS CALLING]
[SCREECHING]
[SQUAWKS]
[GROWLS]
[ROARS]
[MONKEYS SCREECH]
TIME HUNTER:
We're not here
to waste time.
Now, let's start collecting
their treasures.
[LAUGHS]
What a hairy elephant.
DR. O'SHAY:
That's a mammoth.
They became extinct
about 12,000 years ago.
ZORAN:
With teeth like that, they must
have used lots of toothpaste.
TIME HUNTER:
I told you, the beasts
from this time period
have great
genetic traits.
We can take his DNA
and give Web here a new coat.
How do you think he'd look
all covered with spots?
[ANIMALS LAUGH]
[GROWLING]
Ooh.
Mean, are you?
Like to fight, huh?
Well, let's see
how tough you are.
[ROARS]
Ha!
TIME HUNTER:
Get him!
This thing is really fast!
Slime him!
Good job, Web.
And as a reward,
I'm gonna use his DNA
to make you twice as fast.
Traveling through time
has certain advantages.
[LAUGHS]
All right now.
Let's see what other beasts
we can find.
[WEB SCREECHES]
ASTRO:
Mammoths weighed several tons.
Believe it or not,
they walked on their tiptoes.
This rock painting
was done by humans
who lived at the same
time as the mammoths.
Uh, er,
according to this,
mammoths and humans
lived side by side.
Can you imagine
living without
zip cars, helio blimps
and quadra-gliders?
No way, O'Shay.
How did they get around?
[RUMBLING]
BOTH:
Whoa!
[TIME HUNTER GROANS]
Look at the size
of this beast!
Amazing crushing
capabilities.
What are you doing?!
ALL:
Oh!
You wrecked it.
Great, Web,
you turned it
into sludge.
ASTRO:
What do you think
you're doing?
How dare you vandalize
the exhibit.
Out of my way,
old human.
ASTRO: Hands off!
Ahhh!
[ROARS]
[GRUNTS]
Ew! This thing's
gross!
I want one of
these creatures.
Not a fake.
The real thing.
Where are
they from?
It's not a "where."
It's a "when."
They're from
the Mesolithic period.
They haven't walked the earth
for 12,000 years.
So you're just
a little bit late.
Not so fast.
Twelve thousand years
is nothing to
a time hunter.
Activate time cylinder.
[GASPS]
We'll just set this
for the Mesolithic period.
Time travel? No one's been able
to accomplish that yet!
[LAUGHS]
Well, then it's time
to stop living in the past.
[ASTRO GRUNTS]
Dr. O'Shay!
[DR O'SHAY AND TIME HUNTER
GROANING]
[WEB SCREECHES]
[ASTRO GROANS]
Web, let's go.
Cyclops, now.
Astro! Get me out of here!
Zoran!
[GASPS]
[ASTRO GROANS]
Oh! Aargh!
Astro!
Astro? Zoran?
[GROANS]
Oh.
Where are we?
TIME HUNTER:
Not a "where,"
but a "when."
Twelve thousand years
in the past.
I don't want to be
Send me back
to the present.
I want to go home!
You are a squeaky little
machine. Where's your
on-off switch?
I happen to be a very advanced
robot with kokoro. So there.
A useless machine.
I've got all kinds
of robot superpowers.
So one word of advice.
Don't push it!
Ugh!
Eugh!
Better tell your little friend
to learn some manners.
Robots are ancient technology.
In the future we use
bioengineering
to enhance
our abilities.
I steal DNA from the animals
in different time periods,
then I use it to
upgrade my pets,
so they can compete in
the intergalactic monster clash
and become
grand champions.
Yeah. At least they will be
after this trip.
I'll give you a demonstration.
Show her!
I've personally customized
these beasts for extreme combat.
Now you can see how we fight
in my time period.
[CYCLOPS AND WEB GROANING]
[LAUGHS HYSTERICALLY]
[ROARS]
ZORAN:
Well, that was
impressive...not.
[LAUGHS]
All right, all right.
That's enough of that, you two.
They may need some improvement,
but a superboost
from some prehistoric DNA
should do the trick.
Now let's see if we can snare
one of those woolly mammoths.
Hmm.
Over there.
No. No woolly mammoths
over there.
Hmm.
So I struck out.
Let's try another area.
Hey, wait. Remember me?
The girl you gooped, huh?
Oh, gross. Huh?
[GROWLING]
Uh-oh.
Nice doggies.
[HOWLING]
Zoran! Where are y--?
Oh, yuck!
Whoa! Cut it out!
Easy there, big guy.
No time to play around.
I gotta find my sister.
She's somewhere around here.
I'm not really--
Oh, man!
Knock it off.
[GROWLING]
Oh!
[WHIMPERS]
Aargh!
[YELLING]
Wow! Thanks a lot.
I was so scared.
Oh, I mean,
I was slightly nervous.
Of course, I had it
all under control.
Ooh. Mm-hm. Hmm.
ZORAN:
Hey, wait up, caveboy.
You don't mind
if I call you caveboy,
do you?
The thing is I'm not
really from this time period,
and I gotta find a way
back home somehow.
[YELLING IN MESOLITHIC LANGUAGE]
Huh?
[REPLIES IN
MESOLITHIC LANGUAGE]
CAVEBOY:
Ah!
Ahngah.
Does "ahngah" mean friend?
Hope so.
Okay,
I got it.
I am an ahngah
and I've come here
in ahngah-ship.
Maguda.
Ah, thanks,
but I don't
actually eat.
I intake fuel
through energy cells.
Ever heard of 'em?
Guess not.
Baduda.
Uh. Right. Thanks.
[CAVEMAN MUMBLES CURIOUSLY]
[SNIGGERS HAPPILY]
Mmm.
[CRICKETS TWITTER]
Yum, yum-yum.
Ew.
That is so gross.
Mmm.
[CRICKET CHIRPS]
I never intake anything
that wiggles!
Oh!
ZORAN:
Ahhh!
Ah!
How about a little kitty treat?
[ROARS]
ZORAN:
Huh? Not us!
[CAVEMAN GRUNTS]
Aaargh!
Ooh.
[SCREAMS WITH FRIGHT]
Hey! Don't hurt my friend!
CAVEBOY:
Ooh!
Ooh, ah, ooh!
Whee!
Ha. Ha. Haaaa!
[CAVEBOY SCREAMS]
Take it easy.
Astro, it's you.
Stay back, Zoran.
This tiger thinks
we're snack food,
and those fangs
are pretty serious.
I'm a machine, okay?
You eat me, you're gonna
have a bad stomachache.
[ROARS]
[TIGER YOWLS]
Sorry about that.
ZORAN: Astro!
Huh?
[ZORAN LAUGHS]
Oh, hey!
[CAVE FAMILY GRUNT HAPPILY]
This is my
brother Astro.
He's an ahngah.
You know, ahngah, "friend."
I already learned
their language, of course.
Well, maybe not
all of it,
but I'm practically
a cavegirl now.
It's kind
of fun.
[SPEAKS CAVE LANGUAGE]
Uh, thanks,
but I don't eat.
I get power through
energy cells.
We just went
through all this.
Get ready to eat some insects,
the wiggly kind.
Hey, maybe you'll
understand this.
Check it out.
See?
Oh. Ah.
Oh. Ahh!
Oh, ow. Ooh.
Hey, careful.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Those are the ones we want.
Go after the little one.
He'll be easy.
[YOWLS]
[ROARS]
[SQUEAKS NERVOUSLY}
CYCLOPS:
Whoa!
[SCREECHES SHARPLY]
[TRUMPETS LOUDLY]
[MAMMOTH TRUMPETING]
Hey!
The birds!
Something scared 'em.
What?
I don't know. But I'm gonna
find out right now.
Oh!
Gonna fly!
ZORAN:
Wait for me!
I'm going too!
CAVEBOY:
Ahngah!
Hoooo! Aaaah!
Hey.
You're pretty fast
for a human kid. Not bad.
[SHRIEKS]
[ROARS]
You're a tough one.
That's perfect.
Your DNA is
just what I need.
Now, let's wrap
this up and get out
of this time period.
Huh? Who did that?
Right over here!
Let's rocket!
Go get him!
[ASTRO GROANS]
Let's go.
Bring it on!
Come on, give it your best shot,
slime boy.
[SHRIEKS]
ASTRO:
Strike one.
[WEB SCREECHING]
[MUMBLING]
[MEOWING]
TIME HUNTER: Robots.
ASTRO: Huh?
You old-fashioned machines
are no match
for the technology
of the future.
Here's a little demo
for you.
Oh.
Goodbye.
Aargh!
[GRUNTS]
Whoa!
No way! Argh!
[GRUNTING]
Arggh!
No way! Argh!
[LAUGHS]
I think I'll just
leave you up there.
In a few
thousand years,
you'll be nothing
but a rusty old fossil.
ZORAN: Astro!
BOTH: Huh?
Don't hurt
my brother!
That is amusing.
A big, bad slingshot.
[ROARS]
Huh? Ugh!
Aha! Ha-ha-ha!
[TRUMPETS ANGRILY]
[WHIMPERS]
Arggh!
[SHRIEKING]
That's enough!
You've got him,
but don't hurt him!
[GRUNTING]
Okay, you can put him down now.
I'll take it from here.
Easy, big boy.
I'm here to help.
Whoa, you've got to let him go!
If you don't, he'll take
you with him to the future!
Come on!
[TRUMPETS ANGRILY]
Come on! Let's
get back to our time.
[DEVICE BEEPS]
Huh? Wait!
Zoran!
Astro!
Grab my hand!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Zoran, are you
crazy or what?
You almost ended up
in the future.
Why did you do that?
Well, because I wanted
to get this thing.
His belt? You nabbed it?
Uh-huh.
It's a time tube. This is
our ride back home, Astro.
That's great.
Good job, Zoran.
And one more thing.
The cheetah.
That's the one he captured
back at the game preserve.
Uh-huh.
We had to save him
too, didn't we?
[TRUMPETS WEAKLY]
Here!
Now you're
a free mammoth.
[TRUMPETS]
ZORAN:
They're a family.
[ZORAN CHUCKLES]
Right.
Astro,
let's go home.
Once I set this for our time,
we'll be back there in a flash.
Hmm?
It's time for us
to go back home now,
so that means
we have to say goodbye.
Mahngah.
If it wasn't for you,
we would have been stuck
in this era forever.
We never met
a caveboy before.
And now we've got one
for a best friend!
Ooh. Oh?
Thanks for being
our ahngah.
Okay, stop there.
You can't come
to the future with us,
or you'd never see
your family again.
You wouldn't
want that.
[MURMURS]
[DEVICE BEEPS]
Oh? Ooh!
We'll never forget you,
caveboy.
Don't forget us
either, okay?
Ahngah.
[BOTH TRUMPET]
ZORAN:
Whoa!
BOTH:
Arggh!
Astro! Zoran!
[WHIMPERS]
One minute they're here,
the next,
they disappeared into time.
How can I bring them back?
[BOTH GRUNT]
Doctor!
Oh! Thank goodness
you've returned.
I was terribly
worried.
[BOTH GRUNT]
[BOTH LAUGH]
I scared
the time hunters away.
Well, Astro helped
a little bit.
Anyway...we saved
the mammoths!
That's right!
You should have seen 'em.
They're even more
humungous than we thought.
Now, just
hold on here.
You're saying you saw
mammoths and fought
time hunters?
But you were only
gone for a minute!
Well, doctor, that's
how time travel works.
And if those
time hunters come back,
we'll be ready!
And look what we brought
for the game preserve.
Huh?
Arggh! You saved
the cheetah.
I don't think
he realizes he's
been rescued.
He's hungry.
Don't eat
Dr. O'Shay, okay?
I'll take you back
to your family.
[PANTING]
Zoran,
check this out!
ZORAN:
The cave painting!
ASTRO:
It's a woolly mammoth,
just like the ones we rescued.
Hey!
Do you see that?
Wow!
Zoran, it must have been
painted after we left.
[CHUCKLES]
ASTRO:
Bet I know
who it was, too.
[TRIBAL MUSIC]
Ahngah. Ahngah.
[ANIMAL HOWLS]
[♪]