[♪]
ANNOUNCER:
Well, fans,
it's been a long time coming,
but it's finally here.
All the hard work,
all the training,
all the advanced
micro circuitry,
it all comes down to this:
The championship series
of Rocket Ball!
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
And here's the tip-off.
The ball goes to Team Omega.
Harley gets the ball.
Tosses it off to Carter.
Carter rockets
into enemy territory.
Harley scans the field,
determines optimal play,
computes trajectory...
He sets up the shot.
Whoa! A surprise move.
Harley launches
into cannonball mode.
Gets the ball.
He shoots.
He scores!
Goal!
It didn't take Harley long
to show everyone
why he's one of Rocket Ball's
all-time greatest players.
BOYS:
Harley! Harley! Harley!
Cheer all you want
for this foolish
little exhibition, my friends,
but know this:
You haven't seen anything yet.
So tell me,
what's this whole "rules" thing?
Well, people make rules
so they can live with each other
and with robots.
It's kind of complica-- Whoa!
That's the Rocket Ball
championship.
I forgot all about it.
Something else to learn.
Astro, wait!
[LAUGHING]
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
We've got an extra player
on the field.
All right, kid,
give it back.
Come on, let me play.
You crazy?
You can't just fly in here.
Says who?
Tobio?
Astro.
TENMA:
O'Shay...
that boy is not yours.
Sure, Astro saved the city from
Magnamite when it went crazy,
but now that he's interfering
in ball games,
shouldn't we do something?
REPORTER 2:
Yes, we should.
Can we have a comment?
Was there a problem
with his program?
Everyone, listen to me, please.
Astro doesn't have a program.
He has kokoro.
He thinks for himself.
Just like you and me.
Any questions?
Like a human?
That's impossible.
And what is kokoro anyway?
Yes, what is it?
Yes, and why don't you let Astro
answer for himself for once?
Yuko, could you please
take Astro home?
Sure.
The show's over, Astro.
REPORTER:
But we still have questions.
Listen to me!
Astro has emotions,
just like humans.
Yes, he's a robot,
but he's got a heart, a mind,
a spirit, a soul.
That's what kokoro is.
Can you prove that?
Show us something.
I don't know how I'm ever
going to explain it to them.
TAWASHI: Maybe you can't.
Huh?
Their questions do have
a ring of truth to them.
Inspector Tawashi.
Because, quite frankly,
even you don't know
how much power there is in that
little robot of yours, O'Shay.
Astro is not dangerous.
How do you know he's not?
You didn't create him.
Am I right?
But how--?
I'm a detective, remember?
Astro, or Tobio, was built
by the last director
of the Ministry of Science,
who burned down the place.
His name was Dr. Tenma.
TENMA:
Soon, robots will rule
the world!
[TENMA LAUGHING]
TAWASHI:
Right after he built Astro,
Tenma trashed all his research
and went underground.
He was
obviously insane.
And then quickly
disappeared.
So how can we trust
the robot that he built?
Astro has nothing to do
with Tenma now.
He's his own robot.
That might not be
such a good thing.
O'SHAY:
Robots were made to
help humans and protect them.
You understand that,
don't you, Astro?
I guess.
Good. Good. Don't ever forget
that a lot depends on you.
The whole future
of men and robots, Astro.
TENMA:
Tobio.
My Tobio.
I am the one who created you.
But even I don't know
the full extent of your powers.
Not until I test them.
And once I hack into Harley's
system with these sunglasses,
you will face
your greatest opponent yet.
Tobio, wake up!
[GASPS]
Big day today, Astro.
You're going
to a different game.
All right!
But it's not just-- Oh!
Doctor, you're late!
I'm coming.
Hurry, hurry. Come now.
Astro,
now pay close attention today
when Nora takes you
on a field trip
and teaches you how robots
and humans can play together.
NORA:
Astro, ready in five minutes.
Ten!
NORA:
See what I deal with all day?
ANNOUNCER:
We're just a few minutes away
from the tip-off
for game two of the Rocket Ball
Championship Series.
The players are in their locker
rooms right now,
recharging themselves.
And no one wants to win the
championship more than Harley.
TENMA:
What are you made of, Harley?
Will you do anything to win?
Anything at all?
[♪]
Hey, wait up.
BOY: Pass it.
Are these guys robots too?
Huh? Huh?
They wish.
They're just human.
Team Omega's pushing
towards the goal.
Yeah. Harley shakes
one defenseman, and then--
I'm supposed to learn, right?
Doctor's orders.
But first--
No, wait! No, wait!
Harley shoots.
Nice defense, huh?
Do I make the team?
I've seen that robot.
Yeah, I know.
He interfered
in the game yesterday.
Okay, so you put the ball
through here, right?
Whoa! One point for me.
But you're flying.
It's not fair.
Duh, it's more than not fair.
It's a foul.
Foul?
He probably doesn't know
how to play.
That's it, right?
What?
You can't play
if you don't know the rules.
Just think about it.
It'd be an absolute, total mess.
But Rocket Ball's
not in my database.
Hey, I can teach you.
Really?
Sure. I'm Nicholas.
And I'm Astro.
All right.
Let's do it.
Okay!
What a life that kid has,
all play and no work.
Huh?
Now, watch the seams.
Oh, you're tickling me.
So the idea's to score
a goal any way you can.
Except by flying.
ASTRO: No problem.
Play ball.
They can tackle me
if I've got the ball.
So I've gotta
get rid of it fast.
Ah!
Thanks. I think.
Humans are so easily amused.
Hey, Astro. Here.
Got it.
Oh, no.
But now what do I do?
Astro, over here.
Nicholas. Here it comes.
He shoots. He scores.
Game over.
Yeah! Great shot, Nicholas.
Huh?
[CRASH]
Astro, are you okay?
Did we score, Nicholas?
Yeah.
Then of course I'm okay.
We won.
And you know what? Your feet
never even left the ground.
Now I get it.
That computes.
We're just like Team Omega.
Harley's the best player
of them all.
They win the title every time.
Go Omega.
BOY: What happened to the ball?
I don't know. It was right here
a minute ago.
Over there.
Hey, bring that ball back here,
right now.
What is that?
It's a robot dog.
And they're programmed to always
obey every human command.
Hey!
Let's get him!
Can't take it.
GIRL: Gotcha.
NICHOLAS:
I'll have you reprogrammed, dog!
ROBOT:
Hey, Astro, wanna play?
Sorry.
No time for clowning around.
ASTRO:
Faster, Nicholas.
We almost got him.
He needs to be deactivated.
It's like he wants us
to follow him.
Where?
I have no idea.
Something's not right.
Let's not lose him.
Well, then we better hurry.
Let's go!
Bye-bye, silly humans.
Oh, they exhaust me.
Hey.
Where's Astro?
NICHOLAS:
This is starting to get weird.
Look, he stopped.
But where are we? Whoa.
ANNOUNCER:
And now, game two of the Rocket
Ball Championship Series!
O'SHAY:
How could you have lost him?
Do you have another virus?
You have no idea
how hard this job is.
Never mind.
I'll find him myself.
ASTRO:
Come on, Nicholas.
Astro, wait up.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Nice seats, huh?
ANNOUNCER:
And the tip-off goes
Team Omega's way.
But Harley looks like
he's missing a step or two.
He's right, there is
something wrong with Harley.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Unbelievable.
Harley just hit a player
who didn't even have the ball.
And now, the other players
are setting up
for a double-decker combo play.
But Harley won't go for it.
And here comes the ref.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
Oh, no!
What's going on with Harley?
O'SHAY:
Astro, why do you
always do this to me?
Ah, there you are. Rocket Ball.
Of course you'd go there.
Open the emergency
evacuation door.
COMPUTER:
System shutdown.
Locking all exits.
TENMA:
Tobio.
These are the most
powerful robots in the world.
But are they stronger
than you?
MAN: Hey. What's going on?
WOMAN: Open the door! Open up!
What's he gotten himself into?
Tobio...
Will you play them?
Or are you afraid?
[♪]
TENMA:
Well, Tobio?
What's it going to be?
Will you face
your fellow robots?
But I'm Astro.
I don't know any Tobio.
Astro, Tobio,
whoever you are, play us.
Or else...
[CROWD SCREAMING]
Do it, Tobio.
Or I'll make all these humans
very, very unhappy.
So remember, robots were made
to help humans
and to protect them.
Okay, Harley.
Let's play ball.
[CROWD CHEERING]
ANNOUNCER:
Looks like Astro's
going to play.
This is turning out
to be quite a game, folks.
Astro.
He's just too small
to do the job.
The kid doesn't
have a chance.
Yeah, he's gonna
be toast.
My ball.
Hey! Foul.
You can do it, Astro.
Pass. Now.
ANNOUNCER:
Astro passes.
Here's the return pass.
It goes up, up, up. Up.
Astro's got a long way to go
if he wants to get it.
Here it comes.
He leaps.
Yeah! That's it!
He's got it!
[CROWD CHEERS]
Aah!
Ah!
What is going on up here?
Check the power circuits
one more time.
And why haven't the police
gotten here yet?
What in the world is happening
with these robots?
Doctor, we don't know.
We are at a total loss.
Well, then let's
figure it out now.
Shoot me at Harley!
A-ha! Awesome!
Uh-oh, Astro doesn't have
anyone to pass to.
Now he's surrounded.
He's gonna get tackled.
No, no, he's making
a run for it.
But is there time?
Four seconds...
three, two.
One.
He scores!
Goal!
Way to go, Astro.
ANNOUNCER:
Game over.
Astro proved he could do it.
TENMA:
Hmm, I'm impressed, Tobio.
These robots do not come
any tougher than Harley
and Team Omega.
But they're not done
with you yet.
[ASTRO GRUNTING]
Astro, you can do it.
CROWD [CHANTING]:
Astro! Astro! Astro!
Astro! Astro!
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
That's it.
It's the sunglasses.
Astro, take off
Harley's sunglasses.
I'm on it.
Computing.
A neuro-light.
Someone's hacked
into his system.
Game over!
ANNOUNCER:
He did it.
Who'd have thought the little
guy could stop big Harley
in his tracks?
Astro!
Nicholas! Oh!
[CRASH]
Huh?
Sorry, but the audience
isn't allowed on the field.
Rules are rules.
Harley.
Back to your old self, I see.
Astro, look what you did.
CROWD [CHANTING]:
Astro! Astro! Astro!
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
TENMA:
Ah, yes, very impressive.
Tobio, you are the most
powerful robot ever built.
The humans love you.
But will they always?
Or will they turn their backs
on you someday?
This is far from over.
Huh. Hm.
Hmm.
Tenma's work.
O'SHAY:
When are you going to realize
he's not Tobio anymore?
He's Astro!
CROWD [CHANTING]:
Astro! Astro! Astro!
[♪]