[♪]
Now, Shadow,
I want you to test Astro
and push him farther
than he's ever gone before.
SHADOW: All of this time
I have been trying
to create the ultimate robot.
But in order to understand
the extent of Astro's powers,
I must turn the people
he trusts the most
against him.
And I will use the last thing
anyone would ever suspect.
You're my best friend,
Micro-Bear.
I know I am,
and you're my best friend too.
[LAUGHS]
[SIGHS]
Walter, is everything
all right?
I've been working on this new
project for over five weeks now,
and there's still so much to do.
I want to take a vacation
and just forget all about it.
You should go somewhere
warm and tropical.
I mean, no one needs a tan
more than you!
See you tomorrow.
Okay. Good night.
Somewhere tropical, huh?
[SIGHS]
ROBOT:
Poor Walter.
Huh? Uh, who's there?
Hmm?
My name's Micro-Bear.
Let's be friends.
Huh? But how do you
know my name?
I know everything
about you, Walter.
You have been working
at the Ministry of Science
for over 10 years,
and you feel that
it is time for a promotion.
Isn't that right, Walter?
That's incredible! But how--?
Like I said,
I know everything
because I'm your best friend.
Now, let's talk
about Astro.
Uh, yes.
[DROWSILY]
Astro...
Yes! That's it.
Come on, you can do it!
Hurry! Ken, Hurry!
Oh! I can't miss this shot!
[KEN GASPING]
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
He did it!
Ken, that was awesome!
You did it!
Did you see that shot?
That was so awesome!
What do you expect?
Kennedy learned everything
he knows about soccer from me.
Right, Astro?
Huh?
Oh. Yeah.
PLAYERS:
Yeah! Go, Ken.
[LAUGHS]
Astro, what's wrong?
It seems like you've
been acting really weird
ever since the game.
I know. It's great
that you won. But...
Well? But what?
When you kicked the final shot,
I saw your hand touch the ball.
It did, didn't it?
Oh!
Astro! Did you tell
anybody else about this?
Mm-mm.
It-- It was
an accident.
I know, but you should--
I told you it was an accident!
Ken, I think you--
It's not a big deal.
Even the ref said
the goal was good.
I can't go back
and tell them, not now!
Sure you can.
Forget it. You're just a robot.
You'll never understand.
O'SHAY:
Well, that can't be right.
According to this report,
the new model-android project
hasn't made any progress
in over a week.
The development team's
chief engineer
hasn't shown up
for work in days,
and the team's productivity
has dropped 70%.
Why, that is just ridiculous!
There should be no problem
with the vice chief filling in.
Apparently the vice-chief
is absent too.
In fact, over half of our staff
has been out sick since Monday.
Something's not right.
Yuko, I want you to
take over the project
until I can figure this out.
Uh, yes, sir.
[SIGHS]
Another project, huh?
As if I don't have enough
to do already.
Dr. O'Shay gives me
something else!
MICRO-BEAR: Poor Yuko.
Who's there?
MICRO-BEAR:
You could take some time off,
if only Dr. O'Shay
were more understanding.
I'm Micro-Bear.
Let's be friends.
I never thought
he'd get so angry.
It's just not like Kennedy.
MAN:
Of course.
What do you want me to do next,
Micro-Bear?
WOMAN: Now, Micro-Bear, what
would you like me to do next?
Hello! I'm Micro-Bear.
Let's be friends.
Okay.
Hmm. Wait a minute.
You look human on the outside,
but you're really just
a robot, aren't you?
That was weird.
MICRO-BEARS:
Let's be friends.
I see. So you and Kennedy
had a little fight?
Doctor, I don't know what
I should do about Kennedy.
I know you're upset, Astro,
but mark my words,
it's not the end of the world.
Huh? What do you mean?
Look, Astro, people
have disagreements all the time.
But if you did something
because you cared about Kennedy
and that's why you
had that fight,
I'm sure you'll be able
to make up with him.
And you'll be even better
friends than before.
That doesn't compute.
Well, give him another chance
and you'll see what I mean.
Okay, doctor, I'll try talking
to Kennedy again tomorrow.
O'SHAY:
Good night, Astro.
ASTRO:
Good night.
What? Ken's sick today?
Yeah. His mom called
this morning.
She said he wasn't
feeling well.
It's all my fault.
Heya, guys, did you notice Ken's
not the only one not here today?
Maybe something's going on
that we don't know about.
There you go again.
It's probably just the flu
or something.
WOMAN:
I'm sorry, Astro.
Kennedy says he doesn't feel
like seeing anybody right now.
Thank you.
Bye.
Wow! Ken must really
be mad at me.
Hey! That looked like that--
Maybe I should have
talked to Astro.
MICRO-BEAR:
You did the right thing,
Kennedy.
Astro's old news.
I'm your best friend now.
You're right, Micro-Bear.
O'SHAY:
This is quite alarming.
The Ministry of Science
isn't the only place
seeing an increase
in absentees.
The same phenomenon is happening
all across Metro City.
YUKO [ROBOTICALLY]:
Yes, Micro-Bear.
I will do anything you say.
Yuko?
Who in the world
are you talking to over there?
Oh, hello, doctor.
Well, a little teddy bear.
I didn't know
you played with toys.
Doctor, this is not a toy!
Micro-Bear is my friend.
Micro-Bear?
[♪]
Poor Tenma. You must be
so lonely here all by yourself.
Huh? What is
the meaning of this?
[CHIRPING]
Huh?
[ZORAN LAUGHS]
Oh, it's so cute!
Huh? Oh! Wh--?
[SIGHS]
[LATCH OPENS]
Hmm?
Poor doctor.
It's just like Yuko's
little teddy bear, isn't it?
Dr. O'Shay, aren't you
just sick and tired
of all those people
always telling you
that robots are bad
and should be destroyed?
Huh? How did you know that,
Micro-Bear?
I know everything
because I am your best friend
in the whole wide world.
It can't be! Ooh!
Come on!
Let's be friends!
[BEEPING]
[WHIRRING]
I know you are behind this,
Shadow.
You had better have
a good explanation.
SHADOW: I am using the bears
to take over Metro City.
Ridiculous!
It will never work.
One by one,
the people
are falling under my spell,
thanks to you, Tenma.
TENMA: What?
I used one of your
childhood memories
as inspiration.
That-- That's me!
SHADOW:
You are correct.
You created
this toy robot
as a companion to comfort you
in your loneliness.
He became your one
and only friend.
You never got over playing
with robots, did you, Tenma?
Don't be afraid, doctor. I won't
let anything happen to you.
You don't need anybody else.
You especially
don't need Astro.
He's been nothing but trouble
since the day he was created.
Do you understand?
Yes, Micro-Bear.
You're right.
I must get rid of Astro.
Dr. O'Shay. I--
Huh?
It's Micro-Bear.
Oh!
I don't feel so good!
This room is full of some kind
of weird gamma waves.
ASTRO:
Zoran's right.
Doctor!
Tell me, tell me, what do you
want me to do, Micro-Bear?
SHADOW: They were designed
after your creation, Tenma.
But these bears are
much more advanced.
I have programmed them
to brainwash the human mind.
And once under my control,
they will do anything
I command them.
Doctor, please
snap out of it!
Doctor!
Ahhhhh!
[GROANS]
Huh?
Doctor!
Astro! Zoran!
What on earth
happened?
What? Don't you
remember anything?
This isn't
over yet.
I'll be back for you
later, O'Shay!
[LAUGHS]
Goodbye!
Hey, wait!
Come back here!
Look at that!
ASTRO: There must be
a thousand of them!
Shadow, this has
gone on long enough!
You must stop this at once!
I am afraid
it is too late.
By tomorrow morning,
all of Metro City
will be under my power.
You can't be serious.
It has taken me some time,
but I have discovered
mankind's greatest weakness:
friendship.
And what are you
going to do
once you have brainwashed
all of Metro City?
So tell me, Shadow.
What will your plan
be then? Tell me!
Then we will see
how Astro reacts
when even his
closest friends
want him deactivated.
It's so cute,
just like me.
Can't you see,
Zoran?
These cute teddy bears
are hypnotizing people.
And if I don't
stop them,
they'll take over
the entire city.
MICRO-BEARS:
Let's be friends.
I'm Micro-Bear.
You will do as I say.
You will do as I s--
Astro must be stopped.
The Micro-Bears use gamma waves
to scramble people's minds.
But it doesn't work
on robots.
That's why you and Zoran
were unaffected.
There's got to be a way
to block the signal, right?
They are using
the same wavelength,
so you have to find the source
in order to shut them down.
I'll try to trace where
the signal is coming from
while you take a look around
the city for anything unusual.
But doctor,
where should I start?
That's it! I saw one of
the bears in Kennedy's window!
TENMA: Maybe Shadow
was right, Astro.
This could
turn out to be
your greatest test yet.
ASTRO:
Kennedy!
I know you're home.
Don't listen to Micro-Bear.
He's trying to brainwash you.
KENNEDY:
Go away, Astro!
Kennedy!
Why won't he just
leave me alone?
SHADOW:
It is now time to see
if Astro is as powerful
as Tenma thinks he is.
Kennedy, you must get rid
of Astro once and for all.
I don't know. Maybe
I should talk to him first.
Ahhh!
Huh?
What is that?
Whoa-oh!
BEAR:
Astro, surrender now
and join us,
or you will be destroyed.
Never!
Tell me, why are you
doing this?
Once the people of Metro City
are under my control,
they will do anything I want.
MICRO-BEARS: I am Micro-Bear.
I am your friend.
Oh!
I am Micro-Bear.
Now, that's a lot of bears!
Hmm?
ALL: I am Micro-Bear.
I am your friend.
The gamma waves are so strong!
I must stop them! Oh!
MICRO-BEARS: I am Micro-Bear.
I am your friend.
I am Micro-Bear.
Astro!
Don't help him,
Kennedy.
He's not your friend
anymore, remember? I am.
But, Micro,
he needs my help!
Don't forget what
he did to you, Kennedy.
I would never
do that to you
because I'm your
best friend now.
Maybe, you know,
you're right.
What's happening to me?
It feels like
I'm floating through space.
BEAR: You are becoming
one of us, Astro.
Don't fight it.
Together we can rule Metro City!
But-- But--
Kennedy, help me!
ASTRO:
Help me!
Help me, please!
Leave him.
Let's go back inside.
Oh, okay.
Wait!
Don't go! Ken, please!
MICRO-BEARS:
Forget about Kennedy
and be one of us, Astro.
ALL [CHANTING]:
One of us! One of us!
One of us! One of us.
Forget it!
I will never join you.
And I will not turn my back
on my friends either.
ASTRO:
Ken!
I know you're still mad at me,
but I need your help now!
I can't do it without you.
Please, don't leave me.
Micro-Bear is lying to you.
Don't listen to him.
He's trying to trick you.
No, Kennedy, please.
Remember how I always
came and cheered for you?
Astro!
[GRUNTS]
Oh!
ASTRO: Hey, Ken!
That was close!
Don't give up!
You can do it!
Yeah!
See, Ken, I'm your friend,
Astro, not Micro-Bear.
He's just trying to tell you
what you want to hear.
MICRO-BEAR: Oh!
KENNEDY: Astro!
[GROWLS]
What's going on?
The gamma waves aren't working!
Ken!
Ah!
Leave him alone!
Astro, I'm coming for you!
Hold on, Astro! Astro!
Ah! Ken!
I'm sorry, Astro.
I should have
listened to you.
It's okay.
Now let's get out of here.
What do you say?
Mm-hm!
All right. Hang on!
Let's rocket!
KEN: Whoa!
ASTRO: What you're trying
to do is wrong!
I will fight each
and every one of you,
and you can just take your
little toys somewhere else!
The choice is yours,
Micro-Bear.
BEAR:
Fine! You win this time.
BOTH: Huh?
You are stronger than I thought,
Astro.
BEAR:
But I will be back.
We did it, Ken!
We did it.
Micro-Bear's leaving,
but is it over?
Yes. Take a look
around us, Zoran.
Wow!
Astro, look!
The Micro-Bears are gone.
So do you think you've learned
anything by this, Shadow?
SHADOW: Astro is very strong,
as are his friends.
I never expected that the thing
I used against mankind
would end up saving it.
Do not underestimate anyone,
Shadow, especially Astro.
He will lead the machines
when the time comes.
I am sure of it.
Yes, Tenma. We must guide Astro
to ultimate victory.
Heh, heh, heh.
I knew you'd see it my way.
Go! Go!
Yeah! Yeah!
Go, go! You can do it!
You know, Alejo,
I still dont understand
why Kennedy asked
for a rematch today.
Well, the last game
didn't really count,
and he wanted
a second chance.
Hey, look!
Kennedy's got the ball.
You're right. Go for it, Ken!
It's mine!
Shoot it, Ken!
Shoot it!
[KEN GROANS]
Oh! Ken, that was really close.
KENNEDY:
Yeah!
[ALL CHEERING]
[♪]