[♪]
MAN:
Tobio.
BOY:
I'm here! Hello?
SCIENTIST:
Capacity passing 80 percent.
SCIENTIST 2:
Tobio's neural network
is beginning to respond.
[MACHINES WHIRRING]
Almost there.
You can do it.
BOY:
I can't see you. Where are you?
Come on! Increase power!
We can't.
We're at maximum now.
We need more! Call the
Magnamite power station.
Have them bring
all reserves on line.
Sir! That much
energy would--
Tell them it's on my authority.
I'll take personal
responsibility.
This is too important
to fail now.
He's almost charged.
Emergency orders
for Magnamite.
Activate all reserve stations
and reroute all power
to the Ministry of Science.
That would exceed
safety parameters.
Nonsense. Magnamite's job is
to send power where we say.
Now, give it the order.
Ah, yes.
The very same move I made.
O'SHAY:
Come on, Tobio. Wake up.
BOY:
I see you now!
I'm coming toward you!
No!
SCIENTIST:
Doctor, don't!
It's too dangerous!
Get back to
your posts now.
We've come...
too close to be stopped
by a loose cable.
[GRUNTS]
Huh?
[♪]
O'SHAY:
Hello, Tobio.
No, that's not right.
This is your new life.
I think you should have
a new name.
Uh, how about...? Um...
Astro.
Welcome to the world, Astro.
ROBOT:
Sir, systems
returning to normal,
but there's been
a relay imbalance.
Eight thousand megawatts
went into Magnamite
that never came out.
ADMINISTRATOR:
What do you mean,
"never came out"?
Where did the power go?
If even half the rumors
are true--
This robot's
a technological marvel.
And with some kind
of new artificial intelligence.
And weapons.
ALL:
Huh?
Oh, good, you're here.
Gentlemen, I'd like you
to meet Astro,
the most evolved robot
science has ever created.
You're kidding, right?
It looks like a child.
Can it even
do anything?
Don't let his look fool you.
He's learning
at an exponential rate.
And he has kokoro,
his own thoughts and spirit.
MAN:
Right.
Call us when it's learned
something useful.
Like how to sweep up.
Wait! Think of the future!
ASTRO:
Come in for a landing.
There's a clearing.
Ooh.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Now he talks.
Excuse me. Dr. O'Shay?
Uh, Yuko.
You're scheduled to return
phone calls from 1 to 2.
You're already
40 seconds late.
Fine. Nora, start Astro
on his lessons.
Leave it to me,
sir.
Nothing too difficult, now.
Uh...
Please, doctor.
O'SHAY:
Okay, okay.
Be good, Astro!
Ready?
Lesson one: obedience.
Whoa! What's that?
NORA:
Hey! You're not
paying attention!
Stop!
I'm in charge here.
Oh, please.
Oh, please be careful.
Oh, Dr. O'Shay will dismantle me
if you're damaged.
I'm supposed to be learning,
right?
Yes, and I'm supposed
to be teaching.
NORA:
Stop!
Oh, my circuits can't take it!
ASTRO:
Don't blow a gasket.
I'll be right back.
[CRASH]
ADMINISTRATOR:
We've been getting strange
readings from Magnamite all day.
It's malfunctioning.
And the police were just here.
They wanted to know
about the power outage,
so I sent them to you, doctor.
I was only
following your orders,
and I'm not
taking the blame for this!
[SIGHS]
MAN: I'm here to see Dr. O'Shay.
Huh?
Wait. You can't just
go in there.
I'm Detective Tawashi,
Metro City Police.
I demand an explanation
for your citywide blackout!
I can't sleep
with the lights on?
[GROANS]
[♪]
Wow!
Now, these are toys.
Hey, wait up.
Give me a lift.
[LAUGHING]
A robot that thinks for itself?
That's right.
It's called kokoro.
He has emotions, compassion,
a mind of his own.
If it acts on its own,
then it could be dangerous.
Astro's not an "it,"
and he always behaves.
You sure about that?
I'm positive!
[ASTRO SCREAMING]
Astro!
[SCREAMING]
Oh, no!
Hey!
Whoa!
I can fly!
Woo-hoo!
[LAUGHING]
Hey!
Oof!
Ah, looks delicious.
[SCREAMING]
ASTRO:
Oh, no!
[GRUNTING]
Look!
A balloon!
Children!
Yeah.
Not bad for a first flight.
Huh?
You missed one.
Hm?
Hey!
O'SHAY:
Yuko, you and Nora check
the park. I'll look downtown.
I don't want that Detective
Tawashi to find him first.
[SIRENS WAILING]
You heard me.
A flying robot
that looks like a kid.
ROBOT:
Error. Magnamite is rejecting
reroute instructions.
Send in the maintenance robots.
See if the power overload
blew one of its circuits.
ROBOT:
It's destroying
the maintenance bots! Emergency!
ASTRO:
Wow. Check it out.
Awesome.
Yeah!
Excuse me.
ADMINISTRATOR:
It's detaching itself
from the grid.
Emergency response
to Metro Power!
Magnamite is totally
out of control!
Wrap exactly 10 meters of cable
onto your spool.
Hey!
Can I spin him?
Stop.
Do not come closer.
Why not?
By order of Metro City.
Oh, it looks like fun!
This is not a game.
This is work.
Oh.
"Work"?
What do you mean, "work"?
Work is what robots
are programmed to do,
and every robot has a purpose.
A purpose?
Whoa!
Ahh!
Stand back. There's something
wrong with the power grid.
Magnamite has stopped
following our orders.
It's broken loose
and is moving on its own.
Dr. Tenma must've sabotaged it.
He knew what I'd need to do.
Have you tried a full reboot?
ADMINISTRATOR:
It's too late for that.
Magnamite's climbing
out of the plant.
We can't control it!
[CHUCKLING]
This is my fault.
I have to do something!
YUKO:
Just be careful, doctor.
Yuko, tell the police.
It's heading into the city.
[O'SHAY GRUNTING]
Huh?
[SCREAMS]
[♪]
Help! Help!
Doctor?
Yes, please.
Gotta fly!
Get away! Get away! Get away!
ASTRO:
Gotcha!
You're safe now, doctor.
You wait here.
Astro!
[SIRENS WAILING]
We can't let it cross the bridge
into the city!
What's its current location?
It's heading towards us,
underground!
TAWASHI:
Underground?
[GRUNTS, SCREAMS]
Fire!
Destroy it! Aim! Fire!
Their weapons
aren't making a scratch.
Magnamite's just absorbing
more energy.
But that means...
Don't stop. Keep going. More!
MAN:
Run!
MAN 2:
This is your last warning.
Now, cool your jets or else.
Fall back!
Huh?
Astro!
Tobio.
TAWASHI:
Get ready to fire again.
Aim for the center
of its power core.
No, wait.
You don't understand.
First position. Get ready!
Don't shoot!
Take aim.
If you fire at Magnamite again,
it could set off
a massive explosion!
Impossible!
Astro?
[♪]
That flying kid saved us.
Awesome!
Dr. O'Shay was right.
He is amazing.
[MAGNAMITE GROANING]
What's that?
Are you hurt?
Too much energy!
Too much energy?
I get it!
You're overloaded!
You need to release
some of that energy.
Astro. What's happening?
I've got a plan.
Give some to me.
Ready!
O'SHAY:
All that energy.
He has no way of knowing
if his body can take it.
Phew. You rest, I'll drive.
What happened?
It's incredible.
Magnamite is returning.
I don't believe it.
Well, prepare for reattachment.
Reboot the system.
Magnamite, next time
you're overly energetic,
just give me a shout.
ADMINISTRATOR:
System's back to normal.
Okay, see you later.
MAGNAMITE:
Thank you.
Of course!
His body is releasing
the excess energy as light.
Genius!
It's beautiful,
like a shooting star.
Astro, are you okay?
Hi there, doctor!
I think I've found
my purpose.
YUKO [OVER RADIO]:
Dr. O'Shay, come in.
You know, Astro,
I think you have.
Doctor.
Yes, Yuko?
Do you have any idea
what today's antics have done
to your schedule?
O'SHAY:
Uh, my schedule?
Yuko, a bridge between robots
and humans was born today.
My schedule is the least
of what's up in the air.
And so we begin again...
my Tobio.
[♪]