ANNOUNCER:
Previously on Astro Boy:
Make me even stronger.
Atlas is too strong
to ignore, Tobio.
Fight him now
or you will be destroyed.
I am the strongest robot
in the world!
I am Atlas!
[SCREAMS]
Humans are
the enemy.
They are not.
They created us.
And I'm gonna
make them wish they hadn't.
Atlas!
[♪]
[GRUNTING]
Help me, please!
Dai--
Daichi.
I'm not Daichi.
My name's Atlas, remember?
[GRUNTING]
[GASPING]
Daichi.
Huh.
Looks like all the good junk's
already been picked up
by the other scavengers.
Just my luck
to get the leftovers.
[BEEPING]
Huh? The sensors are picking up
a strong energy source.
Huh?
What in the world?
DRAKE: So you're saying
you found Atlas.
Better be sure it's really him,
I'm warning you.
Oh, it's him, all right.
He probably drifted here
on the solar winds.
DRAKE: Hmm, all right.
So I want you to bring him
back to Earth right away.
TARLIN: On my way.
Gordon!
Yes, sir.
Connect me to Dr. Pavlos
immediately.
GORDON: Right away.
This is going to be interesting.
ZORAN: Is this the biggest mall
in the whole wide universe?
Yes, Zoran, until they open up
another one two miles from here.
Cotton candy! Come on, Astro.
Sorry, Zoran, but I want to
go to the holograph arcade.
But I want cotton candy.
Well, I don't!
I want it, I want it,
I want it!
All right, all right.
I'll take Zoran down there.
You're coming?
Thank you, thank you,
thank you, thank you!
It's okay, Zoran.
Astro, why don't
you run along,
and we'll meet up again
in an hour.
Yay!
Zoran!
[CHUCKLES]
Ohh!
MAN: Step right up, kids.
Who wants to win a prize?
All you have to do
is answer my little quiz.
All right, the first question
is about science.
Oh!
Who is the director
of the Ministry of Science?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Okay, the young girl
over there.
Ah, it's Dr. O'Shay.
Ha, ha!
You win a prize.
[LAUGHING]
But really,
there was someone else
who should have been
the director, wasn't there?
I swear, you turn around for one
second and, poof, they're gone.
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
[GASPS]
Zoran, what are you doing?
You'll hurt somebody.
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMS]
I don't know what's wrong
with her. Maybe a short circuit.
But whatever it is,
you'd better stop her.
On it.
ASTRO: It's that headband.
This was only a rehearsal.
Huh?
Listen...
You've been warned.
Zoran, stop it.
Ohh. Huh?
What a mess! Who did this?
Doctor, this device
was controlling Zoran.
Hmm.
[LAUGHING EVILLY]
Hello, Dr. Pavlos.
I hear your experiment
went very well.
That's an understatement.
I've never seen O'Shay
look so scared,
like he was going to
turn tail and run.
Don't joke
about this, Pavlos.
Our organization's
given you millions
to help us eliminate
those robots.
This is important
to us.
Now, tell me, exactly what do
you plan to do about Astro?
Don't worry about him.
This special chip
will solve everything.
O'SHAY: I took this
from Zoran's headband.
It overrides a robot's
normal programming,
giving the operator
complete control over the robot.
That explains why
she was acting so weird,
but I still can't figure out who
would do something like this.
Well, the nanotechnology
in this device
is by far the most advanced
I've ever seen.
Do you think it could be
the work of Dr. Tenma?
ASTRO: I don't think so.
Huh?
It looks like Tenma's work,
all right,
but something doesn't compute.
Well, doctor?
Astro's right.
This isn't
Dr. Tenma's style.
He wants robots to think
and act for themselves.
I'm afraid we've got
a bigger problem here.
This little gadget
is so powerful,
it can turn any robot
into a puppet,
a very destructive puppet.
Really?
ALEJO:
New actuator device? Check.
Upgraded anti-gravity unit?
Check.
And it's all systems go.
We're ready for the next flight
of our quadra-glider.
Nothing can stop us now.
[ALL CHEERING]
ALL: Huh?
Astro?
Huh?
Yeah? What do
you want?
I've never seen you
so spaced-out before.
[LAUGHING]
Is everything okay
with you, Astro?
Yeah, everything's fine, really.
Just daydreaming.
[WHIRRING]
Oh!
BOYS: Huh?
Atlas!
ASTRO: Unbelievable!
You made it back!
Hey, I wonder
what he wants.
Atlas, where
have you been?
We've all been
searching for you.
What is wrong?
That chip.
A very destructive puppet.
Now what?
PAVLOS: Astro won't even
try to fight Atlas,
and that's
his biggest weakness.
He won't fight other robots.
But my next chip
will change all of that.
PAVLOS: Soon,
he'll be my puppet
and I'll be pulling
the strings.
[LAUGHING EVILLY]
Stop!
Oooh! Ahh!
Doctor, Atlas is back
and he's gone crazy.
He just attacked Astro
in the park.
It can't be!
[WHIMPERING]
BOYS:
Astro!
It's saying that the police are
searching for Atlas right now.
[THUD]
Did you hear me, doctor?
Unbelievable.
[STATIC]
Huh?
Dr. O'Shay, someone's
on the vid-phone.
Put them through.
Right.
I want to alert you, doctor,
Atlas has kidnapped
your prize robot.
Pavlos, what do you
want with Astro?
This once-promising scientist
that you and Tenma
had kicked out of the Ministry
of Science wants payback.
Wait. Forced out?
You expect us to believe that?
Everyone knows
what really happened.
One day
you just disappeared.
Do you want to know
the real story?
Tenma had
this insane idea
to make robots that could
think for themselves.
I told him that
even if it worked,
why would anyone
want robots with kokoro?
But he wouldn't listen.
And he went ahead
and built his robot.
Then he snapped. Tenma set fire
to the Ministry and ran off.
I was next in line
to replace Dr. Tenma
but the Ministry of Science
picked you, O'Shay.
And what was worse,
you believed in
the same thing Tenma did,
that robots should be
able to think for themselves
and have feelings.
So I went off
and built my own lab.
All I wanted to do
was stop the nightmare
that you and Tenma
put into motion.
And after months of research,
I came up with
something brilliant.
It's called the Nexus chip
and it will override kokoro,
making robots obey
as they should.
O'SHAY: So you were using Zoran
and Atlas to test this thing?
And now Atlas kidnapped Astro.
You're going to--
Exactly right.
Once I get ahold of Astro,
I'm going to fuse
the Nexus chip in his brain.
[LAUGHING EVILLY]
We must find Astro
immediately.
If we're too late,
it could be a disaster.
Yes, Dr. O'Shay. But where
should we begin the search?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Excuse us.
What are you
doing here?
We've come to help. I know
where to find Astro and Atlas.
And soon enough,
I'll have total control
over the world's
most powerful robot.
Just a few
more minutes
and then you won't
have to worry about
thinking for yourself anymore.
[GASPS]
Sorry, but I've got
a mind of my own,
and it's telling me
it's time to shut you down.
I hate kokoro.
My company's GPS satellites
have been tracking Atlas.
He apparently flew Astro
to the jungle
where there's some kind
of secret hideout.
A lab. And I'm sure that Atlas
and Astro are there right now.
PAVLOS: How can you
be on your feet?
After that beating
you took from Atlas,
you should
still be off-line.
Guess again, doc.
I wasn't injured.
The power from my jet boots
shielded me from his beam.
But then why would you
pretend to be off-line?
Can't you figure it out?
I needed to get you alone.
But why?
To talk some sense into you.
Your Nexus chips are dangerous.
You've got to
destroy them, doctor.
With all your power,
you could destroy them yourself.
That wouldn't solve the problem.
You would just make more.
You have to decide on your own
because it's
the right thing to do.
Such innocence.
All right, Astro,
I'll take care of the problem.
Huh? That was way too easy.
No, I'll keep my word
and take care of the problem,
except, Astro,
the problem is you!
[ASTRO YELLING]
That's weird.
Why aren't they chasing me?
Huh?
ASTRO: Atlas.
MAN: Estimated time
to arrival, 20 minutes.
You must have really
cared about Atlas
to put this much effort
into finding him.
You have no idea, doctor.
Atlas was like a son to me.
Those years,
I look back on them now
as the very best years
of my life.
Atlas, stop this!
[ASTRO YELLING]
It's the chip! Ohh!
[GROANING]
It's too powerful.
Huh?
[GROANING]
I've lost control of Atlas.
What is happening?
I must have tested that chip
a hundred times.
Then you should be
happy to know
that the chip itself
is still operative,
but I am blocking its signal.
Oh, Dr. Tenma!
[ATLAS GROANING]
ATLAS: Astro?
I could not let you do it.
My work with Astro
is far too important
to let some amateur come in
and try to ruin all my plans.
Still showing me
as little respect as ever,
aren't you, Tenma?
I'll put my Nexus chips in every
robot, in every computer--
What is your problem, Pavlos?
Huh?
You don't remember?
You seem to have
some sort of grudge against me,
but, frankly, I do not recall
doing anything to you.
All that humiliation you put me
through at the Ministry.
I guess I just wasn't
important enough to you.
But you'll remember this.
All I have to do
is jack up the power
so you can't block
my signal anymore.
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTING]
[WEAKLY]
Astro.
Mine's stronger.
[WHIMPERING]
My chips. Oh!
Gotta get out of here.
I'm hit. Help! Ahh!
[ASTRO GRUNTING]
[ENGINE WHINING]
Pavlos is in big trouble.
I need your help, Atlas.
I don't believe it.
You actually wanna help him
after all he's done to us?
[SCREAMING]
It's okay, doctor.
No, it's not.
The cooling system's damaged
and the engine's overheating.
The entire ship
is going to explode any second.
MAN: Shuttle approaching.
Huh?
[ALL YELLING]
Daichi.
Tokugawa.
The controls are dead.
The cooling system
isn't responding.
PAVLOS: I told you,
it's hopeless.
We're going to crash!
Wait. The temperature's
stopped rising.
Atlas?
Look at you, Astro,
trying so hard to save this rat.
You'll never change.
We have to help.
Oh...
Huh?
I won't be able to keep
the cooling system
active much longer.
I'm going to have to
lift the shuttle up higher.
Take Pavlos and
get out of there.
But, Atlas,
what about you?
Don't worry, Astro.
I'll be fine.
Hmm.
I mean it. You must go.
Atlas.
A long time ago,
Atlas said something to me.
He said he wanted
to go to a place
where he felt like
part of a family.
I never realized how much he
meant to me until he was gone.
Forgive me.
I was a fool, Daichi.
But I swear I will find you.
I promise.
You know, I still
don't understand
why the Nexus chip
suddenly stopped working.
Maybe someone was looking
over my shoulder and helping me.
You think so?
Yeah.
I just have
this feeling, doctor.
TENMA: I will always
be watching over you, Astro,
because I have
big plans for you.
[♪]