[♪]
ROBOT:
Driving. Driving.
[WELDER ARCING]
MAN 1:
Hey, not bad.
Yeah, this robot's got
better-looking parts
than you do.
ROBOT:
Driving.
Shh! Shh! Shh!
ROBOT: Driving.
MAN 1:
D-did you hear something?
Will you chill out?
These robots are long gone.
I've ripped out every part
and taken out every wire.
ROBOT:
Driving!
Driving...
MAN 2:
That's probably just
a busted voice module.
Must still have
a little charge left in it.
[COUNTRY MUSIC
PLAYING ON RADIO]
[MAN HUMMING]
ROBOT:
Driving.
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
[♪]
[ELECTRONIC BUZZING]
Driving!
[CARNIVAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Look at that.
Wait for me!
Welcome to Metro-musements.
This will be a fun field trip.
Astro, Alejo,
all senior pod members,
remember you're responsible
for looking after each
of your first-graders.
Okay, kids. What do you guys
think we should ride on first?
The Spiral of Doom!
The Jaws of Terror!
OTHERS:
The Whirl and Hurl!
Hey, come back. Let's start
with something simple,
like the petting zoo.
[SCREAMING EXCITEDLY]
[LAUGHING]
BOY 1: Hey, look at me.
BOY 2: Look at me.
[♪]
[HEAVY STOMPING]
[GRUNTING]
[ROARS]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
Driving.
[GRUNTING]
[LAUGHING]
BOY:
Come on!
Jack Fuller.
First grade, huh?
Uh-huh.
I know, what do you say
we go on a ride.
Which ones
do you like best?
Thanks. Maybe later.
ASTRO:
Okay, then how about maybe
we get some ice-cream cones?
Or maybe some cotton candy?
JACK:
Well, I'm not
really hungry.
Something wrong, Jack?
You can tell me.
No, it's nothing. You just
wouldn't understand, Astro.
Please, just leave me
alone, okay?
Well, let me help.
[GRUNTS]
No one can help.
ASTRO: Jack!
[CRYING]
[HORN BLOWS]
ASTRO:
Hey, guys.
Your friend Jack seems like he's
really upset about something.
Anybody have a clue?
He told me that
his robot friend disappeared.
Yeah, probably got eaten
by a Robot Grinder.
Lots of robots have
been stolen lately.
It's the Grinder.
He chews them up
while they sleep,
till there's nothing left
but rusty screws.
I think you've definitely had
enough sugar for today, Freddy.
But I better keep
an eye on Jack.
JACK:
Driving, driving ♪
[JACK SIGHS]
Where are you?
Where' d you go?
♪ Driving, driving ♪
[STOMPING IN DISTANCE]
[♪]
[SCREAMING]
Help! Someone help us!
Someone help us! Help!
Someone help!
[ROBOT GROWLING]
[ROARS]
Friend!
MAN [ON RADIO]:
Dr. O'Shay. Emergency.
10-91 in progress.
Robot on a rampage in Zone 12.
I need an ID on it right now.
I'll get right on it.
It's 50 feet tall with one red
eye and a really bad attitude.
[GROWLING]
O'SHAY:
Hmm, what's this?
Its body appears to be made up
of parts from many different
robots.
Feed these images to the primary
robot-control databank.
Yes, sir.
Check its parts against
every robot manufactured
in the last 10 years.
I want serial numbers and dates.
YUKO:
Will do.
[♪]
It's devouring all the metal
it can find.
And everything
it consumes makes it grow.
It's getting bigger
and stronger.
[GRUNTING]
[ROBOT GROWLING]
PILOT [ON RADIO]:
Attention all units.
The creature is headed straight
for the amusement park.
[♪]
PA ROBOT:
Attention. Attention, everyone.
The police have declared
a state of emergency.
Please leave the park
immediately.
This is an emergency.
Leave the park now.
Stay calm, stick together.
Let's go.
MAN:
Let's go, now.
[CROWD SCREAMING]
[ROBOT YELLING]
[SCREAMING]
Don't worry.
I'll get you guys out of here.
[SCREAMING]
ASTRO:
We're missing someone.
Jack Fuller.
[ROARS]
[GROWLING]
ROBOT:
Friend.
[WHIMPERS]
[YELLS]
Jack!
[GRUNTS]
Not another step.
Jack, run to the bus!
Jack, get moving.
Right now!
Astro!
[ASTRO GRUNTING]
Let's rocket!
Way to go, Astro!
Pick on someone your own size,
you big bully.
[YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
All units in place
and ready to attack, sir.
Wait. Hold your positions.
Look. It's-- It's Astro.
Don't put up a fight.
You're surrounded.
[GROWLING]
[YELLS]
[SCREAMING]
YUKO:
Dr. O'Shay.
Hmm?
We've got the results
of the analysis.
Transferring report
to the main monitor.
Right.
YUKO:
The data confirms
the creature
is composed of pieces
from at least
96 different robots.
The computer has identified
serial numbers
and dates for each one.
Yes, these dates indicate
that the robot parts
are all from older models.
And almost every one has been
reported either lost or stolen.
Hmm. Which seems to suggest...
That the creature
might be linked
to the underground
robo-theft ring.
Exactly. Those butchers think
nothing of destroying robots
just so they can sell off
the valuable parts
and dump the rest.
YUKO:
So this creature
is made up of pieces
of all those mangled
and discarded robots.
O'SHAY:
Yes, but only one of them can
serve as the core,
the heart and mind.
That's what we need to know:
Which is the core?
I'll get right on it.
[ROARING]
It's gone. It--
It vanished
beneath the surface
of the earth.
[ROBOT GROANS]
ROBOT:
Driving.
Inspector.
[PANTING]
I got your call.
What's happened to Astro?
TAWASHI:
Both he and the monster fell
down an old abandoned mineshaft
right here.
They're stuck now at the bottom.
Some 500 feet down.
We must get to them.
TAWASHI:
We can't. The soil
around the hole is too soft.
One wrong move
and it could all cave in.
O'SHAY:
Astro, is he--?
TAKASHI:
We've lost all contact with him.
It's now out of our hands.
All we can do is watch and wait.
[ROBOT GROANING]
Are you--? Are you all right?
ROBOT:
Together...
What?
Together with my friend.
Friend.
Memory chips. I got it.
You're showing me images
taken from your past.
[LAUGHING]
Huh? Hey, I know him.
It's Jack Fuller.
Jack.
♪ Driving, driving ♪
YUKO [ON RADIO]:
Dr. O'Shay, this is Yuko.
I've located the serial number
belonging to the core robot.
Good work.
O'SHAY:
Hmm. It's a QF65-177,
a household robot
used as chauffeur,
companion and protector.
This robot is fully armed
and dangerous.
If it senses any threat
to its master,
it will respond
with extreme force.
ROBOT:
♪ Driving, driving ♪
Now I get it.
You're Jack Fuller's
lost robot friend.
ROBOT:
Al...
"Al." That's your name,
isn't it?
PHILLIP:
Al. That was
what they called him.
According to
our android service files,
he worked for a Mr. and
Mrs. Fuller for over 10 years.
His duties included looking
after their only child,
Jack Fuller, age 6.
Not only was he Jack's chauffeur
to and from school,
but he also served
as the child's protector
and friend.
I see.
I've also discovered
that Jack's parents
filed a missing robot report
10 days ago.
This smells like robo-theft.
O'SHAY:
Our thoughts exactly.
The robo-theft ring
kidnapped Al,
took the parts they needed,
and then likely dumped
the rest of him.
Then his auto-repairing
circuitry
tried to reassemble himself
from parts of other robots.
TAWASHI:
Creating the vicious monster
that attacked
the amusement park.
Hmm. Inspector Tawashi,
it just doesn't add up.
Robots don't run amuck
for no reason at all.
Perhaps he's lost.
Or maybe he's looking
for something.
I don't care if he's looking
for his Aunt Petunia.
That monster swallowed
three roller coasters
and the Super Safari Ride.
Tomorrow this city's
gonna be crawling
with unemployed hippo-bots.
No matter what his reasons are,
he's going down. You got it?
Yes, inspector.
[AL GROANING]
I've gotta tell
the doctor about this.
[YELLING]
Friends don't desert friends.
PILOT [ON RADIO]:
Chopper 6 to headquarters.
Securing the area.
Everything seems calm.
Whoa!
Inspector Tawashi,
it's out of the mine.
TAWASHI [ON RADIO]:
Code red. I repeat, code red.
The creature is on the move,
and it's heading straight
for Metro City.
All units,
attack with full force.
No, inspector. If you do that,
they're liable to hurt Astro.
I have no choice, doctor.
I have a duty
to protect the lives
of 10 million citizens.
But, inspector...
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[BEEPING]
PILOT [ON RADIO]:
Missiles locked on target.
Fire!
AL:
Jack!
[GRUNTS]
[AL GROANING]
Jack...
[BEEPING]
PA ROBOT:
Danger. Danger.
Take shelter at once.
[CROWD SCREAMING]
Al?
Don't shoot! I've got it
under complete control.
Al.
Al!
[GASPS]
AL:
Jack?
Al?
[YELLING]
Don't shoot. No!
[SCREAMS]
Jack. My friend.
Cease fire! There's a child!
Jack, look out!
[SCREAMING]
My friend!
Jack?
Al.
Jack. Aww.
[GRUNTS]
Well, well.
It looks like
the robo-thieves
could steal everything
but Al's heart.
Mission accomplished.
All units return to base.
We'll take him back
and fix him up as good as new.
Al's a lucky robot.
Mm-hm.
And so am I.
[LAUGHING]
[♪]