[♪]
[CHILD LAUGHING]
Huh?
Uh, wh-who's there?
( gasps )
Whoa!
[THUD]
[HISSING]
Ahh!
Lying down on the job, huh?
You look like
you saw a ghost.
[CHILD CHUCKLES]
TAWASHI:
No one will set foot
in that museum now.
They think it's haunted
by some kind of ghost.
Mm-hm. Well, this ghost is
made of solar-charged polymers
with digital controls.
All so-called magic
has a scientific explanation.
I assure you it's merely
a robot with optical shields.
All the signs point to it. And
it so happens that a prototype
with opti-shields
was stolen recently.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
O'SHAY:
The robot is called Denkou,
and the thief
is by no means a magician.
It's Skunk.
Now, I know why you're here,
inspector, and the answer is no.
O'Shay, we need Astro
on this case.
Isn't that interesting?
The detective who hates robots
wants help from Astro.
Sorry.
This is his first day at school,
and I can't distract him.
You did what?
You put a robot in school?
O'SHAY:
Astro has amazing powers,
but he doesn't understand
people yet.
He needs the human experience.
WOMAN:
Class, I want you
to meet someone.
This is Astro.
Hey. Hi, everybody.
So, how's it going?
BOY: As if.
GIRL: Yeah, right.
[MURMURING]
TEACHER:
Astro.
Huh?
I'm sure everyone
will want to get to know you.
We always welcome
new students,
don't we, class?
Now, let's start
the lesson.
Robots have programming.
They don't need schools.
So why are you here
trying to act like a real kid?
We know you're just
a bunch of microchips and stuff.
And you're just a bunch
of potato chips.
His chips are
super-advanced.
My toaster
has advanced chips too,
but it doesn't come to class.
BOY:
Where is he?
Uh!
Huh?
It's him!
Ho-ho!
Synaptic hands. Gyro-boots.
Cranial contours.
Everything is state of the art.
Oh, I gotta see you
in action.
Do you take voice commands?
Of course. Don't you?
You want to give me
voice commands?
What a concept!
He's not some GP2, Alejo.
He thinks like a human.
Oh, yeah,
I knew that.
Huh. Leave it to geek-boy
to make friends with a robot.
Don't worry about him.
His brain's on autopilot.
Huh?
We'll bring you up to speed
on everything, bro.
Really?
Let's go.
Oh, forgot my book bag.
Where'd it go?
BOY: Here.
Oh, wow. Thanks!
Hm?
Oh, I think
I'm losing it.
MIYOKI:
We'll pick up
where we left off yesterday:
History module 427.
[BEEPS]
Whoa.
Whoa!
[LAUGHS]
Wh-what's happening?
Gotcha, bud.
[BIRDS CAW]
All our lessons
are holographic.
It's no biggie.
Check this out.
See the crow's nest?
In the 1500s, there were
no lasers or techno-grids.
Everything was powered
by the wind.
They used it
to discover whole new worlds.
But they had to keep
a sharp eye out for pirates.
And that's not all.
A sudden storm could sink
a ship in a nanosecond.
ALL:
Whoa!
Hey.
Hey!
Something's got my arm.
Get it off. Get it off!
Ah!
[GASPS]
Look out!
What is it?
Ugh!
Ah! It's a ghost!
Okay. Calm down.
There's no such thing
as ghosts.
GIRL:
There's something there.
ABERCROMBIE:
I never liked ghosts.
That's why
they're after me.
You gotta protect me
from that thing, Astro.
Oh, now he's
your best friend.
What happened to,
"Robots are just microchips"?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Ah! It's following me.
KENNEDY:
You need
a reality check.
He's right.
Get a grip.
Hold on, guys.
Take a look at those puddles.
Huh?
[YELPS]
[METAL CLANGS]
It's invisible.
That's impossible.
[BOY LAUGHS]
BOY:
Hey, knock it off.
Well, since you found me...
How'd you do that?
Easy. I have optical shields.
You're a robot?
Why'd you scare
Abercrombie in class?
He practically
lost his lunch.
When the ship moved,
I started to fall,
so I grabbed his arm.
Sorry,
Abercrombie.
My name's
Denkou.
Den-who?
That's great. With your
invisibility functions,
I bet you can do lots
of cool things.
But don't do it now.
It really creeps me out.
What were you doing
at school, anyway?
I was just hanging around.
But when I saw that ship,
well, I had to check it out.
So cool...like we were sailing.
ALEJO:
You like sailing?
Mm-hm.
Then let's do some real sailing.
Yeah.
ALEJO:
I made the
modifications myself.
I call it Sky Rider.
ABERCROMBIE: A sail bike?
KENNEDY: Unreal.
Let's go!
[ALL CHEERING, TALKING]
It's cool.
Why doesn't it work?
Well, theoretically it could,
but it's too heavy
to get off the ground.
You'd have to pedal about
a million miles an hour
to get any lift.
That's bogus.
We can still give it
a shot, can't we?
Sure.
Ha-ha!
ALL:
Ready, steady, go!
[GRUNTING]
Oh, there's no way.
I thought Astro was
strong enough to do it.
Astro,
rev up your gyros.
Don't hold back.
Okay.
[WHIRRING]
ALL:
Whoa!
We gotta help too.
Right.
ALL:
Push, push, push!
Push, push, push.
Push, push.
Woo-hoo!
Yay!
KENNEDY:
All right, we're really flying!
Hey, let it rip, Denkou.
Oh.
Yeah.
ALEJO:
And raise the flag.
The flag of the Sky Riders.
It'll be
our flag now.
Yeah, and let 'em know
who's coming.
ALL:
Whoa!
I hereby proclaim the Sky Riders
official flight crew.
Astro, Kennedy,
Abercrombie, me
and Denkou.
Me too?
ALEJO:
Well, of course.
We're a team.
SKUNK:
Have your fun now, Denkou,
'cause I got
big plans for you.
[EVIL LAUGH]
DENKOU:
We were really flying.
ABERCROMBIE:
I'm like
a natural speed demon.
ALEJO:
You're like a natural windbag.
Whoa.
ALEJO:
Speaking of windbags,
those are parade balloons
for tomorrow's Metro-Fest.
It's a big celebration.
Hey, we could join the parade.
How cool would that be?
All right. You up for it?
Mm-hm.
How about you,
Denkou?
You want me to go too?
Of course.
You're part of our crew,
and that means
we all stick together.
We're a team now,
you know?
Okay.
I'm out of here.
KENNEDY: Catch you later.
Bye!
So, which way's
your house, Denkou?
Mm, I'm not supposed
to tell anybody.
Who says?
He doesn't let me out,
so I kind of have to sneak away.
Why so mysterious?
I can't tell you,
or Mr. Skunk'll get mad.
Bye!
Skunk?
[ALARM SOUNDING]
[LAUGHING]
You've become very good
at playing this game, Denkou.
Thanks.
Do I get to keep some?
SKUNK:
You want a cut of the action?
Why not?
Here you go, kid.
Now, don't say I never
gave you nothing, okay?
Ahh.
Nora, you heard of a man
named Skunk?
Affirmative.
He's in my database.
His rap sheet
takes up 16 gigabytes.
I get dizzy just thinking
about scanning it.
Really?
Nora, open your data files.
I wanna see this guy's stats.
Fine. Then you do the dishes.
Oh, here it is.
Skunk was just
a small-time hoodlum
until he started using androids
in his crime sprees.
His specialty is turning
perfectly nice robots
into desperadoes.
That's it.
I've gotta help Denkou.
[KNOCKING]
Denkou!
Thank goodness
you're here.
Look.
I have to...
Oh, no.
DENKOU: Take one.
I got 'em in a game.
It's not a game.
Uh-huh. It's called,
"Now you see it, now you don't."
Here.
Oh, Denkou,
you have to take them back.
You just broke the law.
Did not. Mr. Skunk said
the treasure was ours.
And tomorrow, we're gonna take
King Solomon's crown.
You have to stay away
from Skunk.
But he's my friend.
I'm your friend.
Skunk's a thief.
He's gonna get you
in big trouble.
Do you understand that,
Denkou?
Ooh!
Why are you being
so mean to me?
I'm not mean.
It's the truth.
You--
You don't know
anything.
Just leave me alone.
Mr. Skunk...
he's my only friend.
Denkou!
I am your friend!
Wait!
Denkou.
[DISTANT SIRENS WAIL]
JAZZ:
You told Astro about the heist?
Mr. Skunk said
it was just a game.
You snap a wire, kid?
You don't shoot off
your mouth like that.
SKUNK: Whoa, lighten up, boys.
A squealer!
Mr. Skunk, the game we play
isn't bad, is it?
[LAUGHS]
Did Astro tell you that?
He was just teasing you,
that's all.
Really?
Of course.
Have I ever
lied to you?
Now go to sleep,
kid.
Okay. Good night.
That's what you get
for trusting a robot.
Now we gotta call off
the job tomorrow.
We're not
calling off anything.
So they know we're coming.
I like the challenge.
And once I get that crown...
Badda-bing!
Lights out
for little Denkou.
[EVIL LAUGHTER]
ASTRO:
We've gotta find a way
to stop her
before she gets
into more trouble.
What's the plan,
Astro?
Yeah, yeah.
We can help too.
Denkou said she was
going to steal something
called King Solomon's
crown.
And so where
would that be?
Yeah. Maybe we can
catch her
before she tries to
steal it.
You think?
Okay. I've got
a plan.
All right!
[FESTIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
ANNOUNCER:
And the 555th annual
Metro City Metro-Fest
is underway.
Welcome to Metro-Fest.
ANNOUNCER:
Please turn off all opti-phones
and electronic devices
as the floats are passing.
Target Alpha just passed
the parade, heading northwest.
They're going toward the museum.
All right,
this is the endgame.
Whatever happens,
don't let Denkou escape.
[PANTING]
[ALARM SOUNDING]
ASTRO:
Denkou!
Come on!
BOYS: Hey.
Come on,
it's us!
We've gotta
talk to you.
Did you tell?
ASTRO: No. We didn't
tell anyone.
Come down here.
I can't.
[GASPING]
There's no way out,
Denkou.
We can see you.
Your optical shields have
no effect in these arc lights.
If my men fire their phasers,
you'll be shut down permanently.
Wait. It's not her fault.
It's Skunk.
Don't worry.
Mr. Skunk gave me a guard belt
so no one can hurt me.
[GASPS]
An EMP device.
It can knock out
the city's electricity.
It's not a guard belt, Denkou.
Huh?
I don't believe you.
You told on me.
No, they followed us!
Mr. Skunk said this is the last
time we'll play the game.
And he promised to do
something nice for me after.
I don't want to make him
mad at me!
Wait!
Fire!
[GRUNTS]
Ahh!
Denkou.
OFFICER: Get that robot.
OFFICER 2:
Don't let her get away.
[SIRENS WAILING]
[GRUNTING]
Oh, you're here!
I'm always
here for you, kid.
Ow!
You're not mad at me
are you, Mr. Skunk?
Course not, kid.
You're the best.
So now I can go to school with
my friends like you promised?
You must be joking...
robot.
What's it doing?
Activating.
I tried to help you,
but you wanted
to be with your school friends.
See if your friends
can save you now.
Adiós, Denkou.
[LAUGHS]
No, wait! I'm sorry!
Please don't leave me alone!
I don't need to see my friends!
Please!
[FESTIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
ANNOUNCER:
And our next float celebrates
the magic of Metro-Fest.
Skunk, you can't escape.
Maybe. But if you keep chasing
me, the whole city goes down.
I think you'd better go after
the kid instead, don't you?
What are you saying?
That EMP gizmo
goes off in an hour.
TAWASHI:
Find Denkou.
Oh, no.
If the EMP device
detonates,
it'll knock out all the power
in Metro City.
That'd be a disaster
for everyone.
And it could be the end
of Denkou and all of us.
Denkou!
Huh?
Denkou. Denkou!
Denkou!
Uh, there she is!
[PANTING]
Huh?
Yo, Denkou.
It's us!
We're over here!
Huh?
Freeze!
Ahh!
Huh? Hey, you!
[LAUGHING]
Skunk is a gangster.
You know what that is?
We can see you.
Adiós, Denkou.
ASTRO:
Only five minutes left.
We gotta find her.
You're right.
Hey. The flags...
That's it.
Huh?
[GASPS]
Is that...our flag?
ALL:
Denkou!
My friends.
ALL:
Denkou!
Would you get up here?
Come on!
Do you see her?
There's too many people.
Oh, no!
Look!
There she is!
[CLOCK TICKING]
Wow!
Ooh!
WOMAN:
Amazing.
WOMAN 2:
He did it.
Yay!
Yeah!
All right!
OFFICER:
Let's get 'em. Now!
No! Danger's over.
Just leave the kids alone.
You saved my robot.
I built Denkou to help humanity,
not to harm it.
I know, Dr. Emile.
But after all,
it wasn't me who saved her.
It was her friends.
For you, Denkou.
Huh? What is it?
[GASPS]
The flag for the Sky Riders.
Can I take it home with me,
Astro?
Mm-hm.
See you
when you come back.
Yeah, we'll go sky-riding
again, only higher!
We're gonna set
a new record.
Yeah! I can't wait.
ASTRO: Bye.
KENNEDY: See you later.
Bye.
See ya.
[♪]