[♪]
MAN:
Working late again, huh, doc?
I'll call for your zip-car.
That is, unless you're planning
to have Astro fly you home.
[LAUGHS]
Very funny. I'd never
use Astro for that.
But I can't wait
for the new robot train.
[CACKLING]
Hey. Who's there?
[HELICOPTER WHIRRING]
[BOTH YELL]
[♪]
OFFICER:
Hurry!
[ALARM SOUNDING]
Destruction is beautiful.
And I have perfected
the art of destruction.
Three weeks from today,
you will witness my greatest
artistic masterpiece.
[LAUGHS]
Who on Earth was that?
[REGAL MUSIC PLAYING]
STATION VOICE:
Welcome to Alpine Station.
The green zone is for loading
and unloading only.
REPORTER:
Here in Metro City,
the new thinking robots
have entered
every aspect of daily life,
including the new
Metro City Railway.
Just imagine,
we're only moments away
from witnessing
the first ever robot train.
There's no engineer and no crew.
The train does it all.
Hmm.
Doctor, what's up?
I thought you were looking
forward to this trip.
Mm, uh...I am.
It's just that...
it's been three weeks
since the attack.
Humans worry too much.
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen,
presenting
"The Train With The Brain."
The locomotive
that's putting mankind
on the fast track
to the future:
The Neon Express!
[GASPING, MURMURING]
The Neon Express has
its own unique personality.
It has emotions and can
even think for itself.
[CHUCKLING]
I bet it has a one-track mind.
Dr. O'Shay,
what do you think
of our newest
robot celebrity?
I'm thrilled. This shows
that robots are no longer
just a bunch of gears
and gizmos.
When Neon Express
takes you somewhere,
he enjoys the journey
as much as you do.
He's your transportation
and your companion.
REPORTER:
So you think robot trains
will be the next big thing.
O'SHAY:
The future of robotic
transportation begins today
with the premier voyage
of the Neon Express.
OFFICER:
No sudden moves.
Hands where we can see 'em.
All right, Kato.
Your little clown routine
is over.
I don't know why you attacked
the Ministry of Science,
but I intend to find out.
[CHUCKLES]
KATO [VOICEOVER]:
Oh, you'll find out, all right,
when that train ride
turns into the biggest
train wreck in history.
[WHISTLE BLOWS]
[COMMUNICATOR RINGS]
Huh? Oh.
Oh, Detective Tawashi.
Your tip panned out, O'Shay.
We got the guy
who attacked the Ministry.
It's Kato, your ex-employee.
Wow, they caught him?
That's great.
Mm-hm.
Now we can relax and check out
the advanced functions
on Neon Express.
One frozen vanilla swirl.
Thanks, Frosty Bot.
You're welcome.
See ya.
Bye.
Oh!
[GASPS]
WOMAN:
My designer suit.
Do you know how much
it'll cost to have this cleaned?
Oh. I'm sorry.
WOMAN:
The fabric is imported
from the moon.
Excuse me.
Neo-tonic pulse.
Radial roto-rub.
And vapo-vanish.
Good as new.
Neon Express cleaning technology
for your convenience, ma'am.
It'll do, I suppose.
Hmph.
Hey, can you clean my room too?
No. And I don't do windows.
[♪]
You give up
painting and sculpting
to join the
Ministry of Science,
where you secretly
make explosives.
You don't want money.
No list of demands.
So, what's your game?
Spit it out.
Why did you do it?
It's my art.
Huh?
The universe creates,
and then it destroys.
Destruction is
the purest form of art.
What?! You wreck buildings
for art?
My next masterpiece
will be the destruction
of the Neon Express.
You mean...?
Call the control center. Hurry.
WOMAN [OVER PA]:
Welcome to the Neon Express.
For train schedules,
press or say 1.
For directions,
press or say two.
For an operator, press or say
zero or stay on the line.
TAWASHI:
Zero. Zero!
This is an emergency.
WOMAN:
One moment, please.
Orin, line 16 for you.
He says it's urgent.
Yes?
TAWASHI:
Stop the train now!
Are you crazy?
Who do you think you are?
The chief of police.
So listen carefully.
We have intelligence
that there's an explosive device
at the first tunnel.
Now, pull the brakes!
Neon Express,
this is Operations.
Do not enter the first tunnel.
Stop immediately.
NEON EXPRESS:
Negative, chief.
If I brake now, we'll have
a major catastrophe.
ORIN:
There's an explosive
at the entrance.
I'll have to increase speed
and try to whip past it.
[BEEPING]
[BEEPS]
Huh?
[BEEPING]
Doctor, there's a problem.
ENGINEER:
Transmitter's down.
Neon Express.
Come in, please.
Report your status,
please.
Try again.
There's
no point, sir.
All of our communication
lines are dead.
Neon Express is
on its own.
He's gonna
pay for this!
KATO:
Great artists need great works
to make their mark.
And I'm about to explode
onto the scene.
[LAUGHING]
Neon Express,
are you okay?
Well, physically, I'm fine.
Though emotionally,
I'm a little shaken up.
Thanks for asking.
The cars are soundproof
to human ears,
but Astro picked up
the sound of an explosion.
Correct. I've lost contact
with the control center.
Something is affecting
my electromagnetic output.
I'm trying to identify
the source,
but I can't get a reading.
What could it be?
An electro-parasite
could sabotage his system.
You're right.
A bug uploaded into your system
could take complete control.
Neon Express,
scan all the cars.
See if you can find a parasite.
If I run a scan,
the cars will go dark.
Don't you think that will
frighten our passengers?
Good point. A riot
is the last thing we need.
Hey, doctor, why don't
we just call it a light show?
Huh?
[CHIMES]
NEON EXPRESS:
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is a Neon Express
entertainment special.
To enhance
your travel experience,
we are about to bring you
a unique music and laser show.
So sit back and enjoy
the presentation.
[MYSTICAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Daddy. Look,
it's like a rainbow.
COMPUTER:
Scanning process underway.
Danger detected.
That's it.
NEON EXPRESS:
It's in the dining car.
Astro, how about it?
Let's go.
Huh?
Scanning.
Got it.
Is it the parasite?
No.
It's just a projector.
There must be a way
to reach that train.
We're trying, sir.
Well, try harder!
There are 900 passengers aboard.
And every one of them
is in danger
unless we can stop Kato's plan!
Time's running out!
Huh?
[CACKLES]
Welcome to the next phase
of my grand scheme.
With my artistic flair,
I've hidden
a hyper-acceleration virus
in a place your scanners
will never find.
It will make the train go
faster and faster
till it's out of control.
Oh, dear. The train's
going to crash.
NEON EXPRESS:
My velocity's increasing.
I can't help myself.
We need another scan
to find that hyper-virus.
There's no time.
I'm approaching a hairpin turn.
At this speed,
I'll derail.
We can't allow that.
We have to keep
the passengers safe.
There must be a way
to slow you down.
We have got to think.
Let me go outside.
With some teamwork, I know
I can keep your wheels on track.
Impossible.
I am going too fast.
We've got to try it.
Astro, here's
a micro-transmitter,
so you can hear us.
Right.
There's no time to waste.
We're approaching the tunnel.
[SCREAMING]
Astro, my wheels are lifting
off the track.
[GRUNTING]
NEON EXPRESS:
It's not working.
Oh! Whoa!
Don't give up!
NEON EXPRESS:
Tipping over.
You can do it, Astro. Increase
thrust, but keep it steady.
[GRUNTING]
Doctor...Neon Express
cleared the curve.
Well done, Astro. We're safe.
[BEEP]
YUKO:
Chief. We've got contact.
We're back online.
Finally.
We have to put
our heads together.
There must be something
we're missing.
Can you do another scan
for that hyper-virus?
I have done multiple searches
with ultra-enhanced
ray functions.
The result is still negative.
Hm, I better check with Astro.
TAWASHI:
Neon Express. Come in.
Are the passengers okay?
Ah, Tawashi.
The passengers are fine.
We're all going to crash,
and I just did my hair!
What do you mean,
we're gonna crash? Hey!
Stop this train
right now!
Yeah!
MAN 1: We'll make 'em stop.
MAN 2: Right.
ASTRO:
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I have your attention?
We seem to be experiencing
a slight malfunction,
but we're on top
of the problem.
Now, please, try to remain calm
and stay in your seats.
We won't let you down.
You heard what Astro said.
He's never let us down before,
so everything's gonna be okay.
Now, what do you suppose
your friends will say
when you get back home?
I bet they'll wanna know
all about your big adventure
with Astro.
[TRAIN SCREECHES]
Gotta find that hyper-virus
before it wrecks the train.
We interrupt this program
for breaking news.
A runaway train is heading
for Metro Station,
creating a potential code-red
disaster in exactly 18 minutes.
Make that 17 minutes.
[SCREAMING]
[DISTANT SIRENS WAILING]
TAWASHI:
O'Shay. Neon Express
is heading for Metro Station.
Not there.
The city's power supply
is right next
to the station.
Then stop the train!
O'SHAY:
We can't even slow it down.
If we jump the tracks
on the final curve,
we'll crash
right into the power station.
That's not an option.
You know how much energy
that station pumps out.
If it blows, this city
will be destroyed.
NEON EXPRESS:
Ladies and gentlemen,
Astro has a plan to safely
escort you off the train.
When he gives the word,
proceed to the exits
with maximum human velocity.
MAN:
What's he talking about?
I won the girls'
relay race.
All right.
Then you take the lead.
NEON EXPRESS:
Right now,
a special express train
is starting out for Metro City.
All clear.
NEON EXPRESS:
When we reach the Metro
switchyard,
we'll hit a stretch
of parallel track
so the two trains can run
side by side.
The doors will open,
and the trains
will hook together,
and you'll run across
to the other train.
But you'll only have
60 seconds to get across.
I hope you brought
your running shoes.
DRIVER:
We've gotta reach
the second track
before Neon Express
catches up to us.
There it is.
If it keeps speeding up,
it's going to hit us.
I'm increasing speed,
but I can't stay ahead of it.
That's it. It's gonna hit us.
Ah!
Wait. We're
picking up speed.
[GRUNTING]
ASTRO:
There's the split-off.
All right, tell the passengers
to get ready.
They've got 60 seconds,
starting now.
[SCREAMING]
You're going too, doc.
What? I can't leave. I've
got to stay with Neon Express.
[GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
DRIVER:
We're going too fast.
We're gonna crash! Ahh!
ASTRO:
Not if I can help it.
[GRUNTING]
[GRINDS]
Phew. Glad that's over.
Thanks.
Any time. Sorry I can't chat.
Gotta fly!
Astro!
All right, Neon Express.
From here on,
it's just us robots.
I'm with you, Astro.
Okay, let's track down
that hyper-virus.
We've already looked everywhere.
I'm afraid it's hopeless
to search further.
But we have to find it.
It's the only chance we have.
There's one other way, Astro.
At the next curve,
I can shift my weight
and crash in a place
where no one will be hurt.
I'm not important.
It's the people that matter.
No way! We're gonna save you
and the people.
Now let's do another search.
But the parasite's hidden
where it can't be identified.
That's what
the clown said.
Yeah, I remember.
With my artistic flair,
I've hidden
a hyper-acceleration virus
in a place your scanners
will never find.
Hey, that's it.
There's one place
that a scanner can't scan.
Whoa!
It can't scan itself.
So the hyper-virus must be
inside the scanner.
[GRUNTS]
There it is.
Uh-oh. Not good.
ASTRO:
Doctor, I found what we're
looking for, but...
What's that?
You've found the virus?
[CHEERING]
He did it.
But look. The train's
still moving at full speed.
[GRUNTS]
What's going on?
It's not slowing down.
If it gets any closer,
it's going to smash
into that power station.
I've got it. Let's rocket.
O'SHAY:
Astro, can you defuse it?
ASTRO:
No time, doctor.
It's gonna blow in 29 seconds.
O'SHAY:
Astro, be careful!
ROBOT:
Robot patrol to Astro.
We've cleared the tunnel
so you can fly that thing
out of here.
Coming through. Whoa!
Go for it, Astro.
[CHATTERING]
Astro, the fastest way out
is through the station's
Metro Mall.
Turn left at Mario's Pizzeria,
then step on it!
This way.
This way. Ah!
Here he comes.
Hurry. Whoa!
O'SHAY:
Astro, there's a barrier
dead ahead.
[GASPS]
[CROWD GASPS]
ASTRO:
Hey, doctor,
I had a blast.
Situation's under control.
MAN: He did it.
I'm coming home.
He did it!
Phew.
Your masterpiece turned out
to be a master flop.
Am I allowed
a glass of water?
[YELLING]
Huh?
[BEEPING]
There's no end
to my creativity.
Next time, prepare
to really be blown away.
[LAUGHS]
Until then...
Huh?
Where's Neon Express?
Over here!
Oh. Where are you, Astro?
We're all looking for you.
ASTRO:
I'm worried
about Neon Express.
He should have
been here already.
[DISTANT HORN, CHEERING]
You can stop worrying.
Your friend is all right.
[NEON EXPRESS SLOWING DOWN]
Yay! It's Neon Express!
Sorry for the delay,
but we'll be back
in express mode in no time.
By the way, I could use
an extra human engineer
to ride in the cab with me.
[LAUGHING]
I'll do it. I wanna ride
in the front!
Oh, dear.
Easy there.
[LAUGHTER]
It looks like we're back online.
And with robots like Astro
and Neon Express to help us,
we're on the fast track
to the future.
[♪]