[♪]
TENMA:
I'm sure of it.
Someday,
robots will rule humankind.
And when that
finally happens,
who is going to
lead the robots?
Astro.
But you've got to be ready
for that responsibility.
Because if you're not,
someone else will
do it for you.
[CROWD CHEERING]
ANNOUNCER [OVER LOUDSPEAKER]:
Now that he's been upgraded,
Harley is unstoppable.
Yay!
Yay! Yay!
Go, go, go!
Calm down,
Zoran!
ANNOUNCER:
Harley computes his next move.
Let's do it!
ANNOUNCER:
Harley shoots, and he--
Huh?
ALL:
You call yourself a champion?
Meet the real thing...
Pluto!
Go on. Try to score again.
Just try.
You're on.
I just don't believe it, folks.
Now I've seen everything.
Harley takes on the challenge.
No.
Don't!
Argh!
[WHIMPERS]
I've never seen
anything like this before--
Ha-ha-ha!
TENMA [OVER BIG SCREEN]:
So much for Harley.
Pluto showed him who's boss,
didn't he?
That voice.
Tenma.
TENMA:
Pluto wants to prove himself
against the strongest robots.
First, the Robot Squad,
then Hercules.
Then Epsilon.
And finally,
Astro.
And all of them will meet
the same fate
as Harley.
Ha-ha-ha!
You gonna fight him,
Astro?
Doctor?
No, never.
ROBOT:
Get him.
ROBOT 2:
Fire!
ROBOT:
You having any luck over there?
Negative.
Someone's got to get closer.
Okay, I'll go for it.
Unbelievable.
PLUTO:
Delta.
You've got some courage
coming after me.
Or is it stupidity?
You'll know after
I'm done with you.
DELTA:
Okay, guys, I've got him!
He's gonna pay for what he did.
Not!
Surprise!
Argh!
How did you...?
It's all in the programming,
Delta.
Two down,
three to go.
A robot that evolves?
That is the perfect word
for it.
Pluto's abilities just
keep improving.
Right. He can actually learn
from his opponents.
But why? How?
This has got to be
Tenma again.
All he wants is revenge.
He's a lunatic!
I say we send Astro up against
Pluto before it's too late!
No! That's much too dangerous.
TENMA [OVER BIG SCREENS]:
Pluto is the most advanced
robot ever built.
He will send all the others
to the scrap heap.
Do you think this Pluto guy
can beat Astro?
No. No way.
I don't know who'd win,
but I'd sure pay
a whole lot to see that.
ANNOUNCER [OVER LOUDSPEAKER]:
Hey there, fans.
We're here in Athenia today
to cover Big Hercules'
latest match.
[CROWD CHEERING]
He sees this as a warm-up
for his big bout with Pluto.
Wow, that was fast!
Pluto, where are you, coward?
REPORTER:
Epsilon is different from the
other robots Pluto challenged.
She can predict and control
the weather.
Right now,
she's predicting a tornado,
one that could
do serious damage.
But as you can see,
the weather's fine.
Not even a breeze.
Oh!
[WIND HOWLING]
Epsilon was right again!
And we're in very big trouble!
EPSILON:
Winds stop!
REPORTER:
Epsilon has done it again,
everyone.
She stopped a tornado.
REPORTER:
Can Astro really beat Pluto?
REPORTER 2:
What's your strategy
going to be?
Astro's not
going to fight Pluto.
REPORTER [OVER TV]:
Is he afraid?
No way!
Astro would never, ever run!
Am I right, Astro?
ASTRO:
I don't wanna fight,
but I'm not gonna run, either.
No late news for me tonight.
[TIRES SCREECH]
Tenma,
why are you doing
this to Astro?
Call off the match!
I cannot do it, O'Shay.
Why not?
Astro has to meet Pluto.
It is the next step
in his evolution.
He is going places
you never dreamed of.
His-- His evolution?
What in the world
are you up to this time?
Tenma!
Do not worry about Astro.
He is going
to get a lot stronger,
as long as he survives.
ZORAN:
Hey, where'd all these reporters
come from?
They're all waiting to see
what I'm gonna do about Pluto.
These people are gonna scare
away my feathered friend.
Feathered friend?
Huh?
Every single morning,
a bird from the forest comes by
to play with me.
We've become friends,
and I miss him.
Huh. She couldn't get a cat
like everybody else.
When's this ever going to end?
NORA: Home sweet home.
You're all wet.
What happened to you?
Ah, nothing.
ASTRO: Doctor?
Hmm?
I've decided
I'm going to take on Pluto.
You can't!
I have to!
I can't let him go around
hurting innocent robots anymore.
He has to be stopped!
He will, but not by you.
Robots just shouldn't be
fighting each other like this.
And besides,
this isn't really Pluto's fault.
He just does
what he's told to do.
This is all because
of Dr. Tenma.
TENMA:
You are the best robot
that has ever been built.
We will go far together, Astro.
ASTRO:
I don't work for you, Tenma.
ANNOUNCER [OVER LOUDSPEAKER]:
No surprise here, folks.
Hercules wins again.
Pluto, where are you?
Come face me.
Aw, I was so sure
Pluto would show up.
He was all talk.
You kept me waiting.
I'm worth it.
We'll see about that.
[SIRENS WAILING]
OFFICER [OVER LOUDSPEAKER]:
Pluto, you're under arrest.
Hold it!
I'll be the one to take him in.
Give it your best shot.
Ta-da!
Ever seen anything
this cute in your entire life?
Would you like to have it?
Hmm?
I made it just for you.
Maybe you'd like a bigger one.
Even better, huh?
If I have to.
REPORTER: What? Pluto's back?
You're saying Pluto's--?
--and he's fighting
Hercules right now.
Well, there's my cue.
Are you going to
fight Pluto now?
No way.
I'm just gonna talk to him.
No fair flying away!
You're gonna get in trouble!
Zoran, where's he going?
Oh...
Cheese.
ANNOUNCER [OVER LOUDSPEAKER]:
I sure didn't see
this one coming, fans.
Hercules hasn't been able
to do anything to Pluto.
And now he's got his lance
stuck in the ground.
Time to go home,
Herc.
Time for you, maybe.
You were overconfident.
PLUTO:
Detecting flaws
in Hercules' programming.
Huh?
You don't have a chance now,
you pathetic tin can.
You forget who you're fighting!
I am Hercules!
I-- Ugh!
Argh!
[CROWD CHEERING]
[WHIMPERS]
ANNOUNCER:
I don't believe it, folks!
Three down, two to go.
[BEEPING]
Astro's coming.
Pluto!
Hello, Astro.
And goodbye.
Not bad, kid.
Why are you doing this?
Because I have to.
My circuits!
Argh!
ASTRO:
Good as new, Pluto.
Why are you helping me?
I just tried to squash you.
You definitely did.
But you see, Pluto,
you and I are both robots.
Robots need to be friends
with each other.
Astro,
I was built for battle.
And only for that.
[SIRENS APPROACHING]
Wait. You shouldn't
try to move yet.
We'll finish this
some other time, kid.
ASTRO:
Don't bet on it, Pluto.
PLUTO:
Tell me something.
What is a friend, exactly?
TENMA:
That is a concept you do not
need to worry about.
It will just make you weaker.
And you don't want that,
now, do you?
Let me worry about
your programming.
You just rest up
for your next match.
Friend.
O'SHAY:
Astro, didn't you see
what Pluto did to Hercules?
He's a monster!
No, doctor.
Pluto is just like me.
He has kokoro, like I do.
Doubtful.
But if he does have a heart,
it's loyal to Tenma.
[REPORTERS SHOUTING]
All I want to do is go outside.
Huh?
NORA:
I've got an idea.
This way should be okay.
Thanks.
[REPORTERS SHOUTING]
NORA:
I'm sorry about all this.
[HOUDINI CHIRPING]
You came for me,
Houdini.
[CHIRPING]
I wish we could go outside.
I have an idea.
[WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
Hmm?
Gross!
[SCREAMING]
It worked!
Let's go.
Pluto.
Wha--?
You're Astro's little sister,
aren't you?
You have to do something for me.
It's important.
I need you to help me
find Astro.
No!
This is some kind of trick!
I would never help you!
I just want to talk to him,
that's all.
ZORAN:
Right, talk.
Well,
there's no way, get it?
No way. Never. Hmm!
Please help me...
friend.
MAN [OVER LOUDSPEAKER]:
Ha-ha!
I've been looking
all over for you, Pluto.
Ha-ha!
What are you doing way out here?
Who are you?
Don't be so confused, buddy.
I'm gonna explain everything.
All right, roll cameras.
This is gonna be pure gold.
I'm Grummitt, Pluto,
TV reporter extraordinaire.
Before you meet Astro,
you're gonna
face these other tough guys.
PLUTO:
What would I gain from this?
Nothing. But I'll gain plenty!
I'll sell this tape
all over town!
Now, go!
That's all there is?
First-round knockout?
Stay away!
Aah!
Are you all right?
Uh...
huh.
Good.
ASTRO:
Pluto!
Get away from her!
It's not what you think.
Pluto saved me.
No one hurts my sister.
You've crossed the line now,
Pluto.
So be it.
TENMA:
Our future will be determined
by this one last battle.
But even I have no idea
who's going to win.
ZORAN:
Astro! Pluto!
You both have to stop this!
[♪]