[♪]
NEWSREADER:
No one knows
where he came from,
no one even knows
who built him,
but we do know one thing.
This mysterious robot
always shows up
to help other robots.
The Blue Knight.
He helped rescue
the people on that airbus.
And saved my life too.
Yeah, and the Blue Knight thinks
humans want to destroy robots,
so he's always fighting
to protect them
when they're in trouble.
O'SHAY:
Unfortunately, some humans
still do want to destroy robots.
As more people realize
the immense value
that robots provide,
like they do on Hydra,
things will start to change.
Right!
And Hydra's a great
example of that!
O'SHAY:
It's the first
orbiting power plant
to be run entirely by robots.
Humans have never given robots
so much responsibility before.
In fact, they oversee
everything from maintenance
to programming the advanced
new processing vector.
MAN:
Here she is, boss. Hydra!
We'll be docking soon.
And then we'll get to see
exactly what makes
the competition tick.
Are you absolutely sure
you're ready to do this?
Ready? I'm the best hacker
there is.
Whatever you want from
Hydra's mainframe, it's yours.
Leave it to me.
Piece of cake!
DONNER:
It better be.
My company needs Hydra's new
processing vector program now,
even if we have to steal
to get it.
Let's not waste any time. Follow
my lead and stick to the plan.
Don't worry, boss.
With me on the team,
everything's gonna-- Huh?
Oh, what? Who?
Welcome to Hydra.
I am the chief robot here.
My name is Jasper.
I will be
your tour guide.
Great.
JASPER:
This is Hydra's
main energy source.
DONNER:
Incredible!
JASPER:
Thanks to Hydra's
new processing vector,
we have achieved a 300 percent
improvement over the--
Yeah, yeah.
But, Jasper, where's the control
room for this new vector thing?
Uh, it's off-limits.
The vector manages
all of Hydra's systems.
You can only observe
the computer on these monitors.
Jasper, tell us about
your safety system.
Sure.
We actually have
two safety systems,
one backing up the other
in case--
[GROANS]
Are you getting spacesick?
No, it's just my stomach
acting up again.
Shall I get
a medical droid for you?
No, I have my medicine,
but is there somewhere
I can get a glass of water?
JASPER:
I'll take you there.
I'll just stay
and watch the monitors.
Okay. I will
be right back.
See you soon.
Heh-heh.
This is too easy.
And I'm in!
[DONNER SIGHS]
Thank you.
I feel a lot better now.
I don't mean to rush you, sir,
but we need to get back
to your friend.
Huh?
We are not allowed
to leave visitors on the tour
by themselves.
Wait!
Uh...there's some things
I wanna know about this place.
Well...
THORNE:
Easy as a game of tick-tack-toe.
Security cracked,
winner takes all.
Ha-ha!
Hmm. And where is
the engine room?
I really have to be
getting back now.
Why don't you stay here awhile
and rest, sir?
Thorne. Thorne?
He's headed back to you.
Hurry!
THORNE:
Candy from a baby!
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
Download complete!
Hey! What is this?
We got a problem!
Mr. Thorne,
are you okay?
What happened?
I didn't do anything...
[WHISPERS]
much.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
ROBOT:
Systems malfunction.
What's going on?
Aah!
ROBOT 2:
Block K2 here.
We have a fire! It's--
Aah!
ROBOT 3:
Close number 2 valve!
Cooling system damaged!
CONTROL SYSTEM:
Power system damaged.
Code red! Code red!
Jasper, what's going on?
I'm not sure.
For some reason, the processing
vector is overheating.
You idiot!
This is not
the way we planned it!
It's not my fault!
I did exactly what you told me!
You're the one who wanted
to steal the program!
You wouldn't--
Sure I would!
This whole thing was your idea,
not mine, remember?
You better think
of another plan fast,
'cause I ain't
taking the blame for this.
You can go to jail!
WOMAN:
Attention! This is
the Space Energy Council.
What's the problem there,
Jasper?
Hydra, come in!
Jasper, can you hear me?
DONNER:
Uh, this is Hydra.
Who are you?
My name's Donner.
Yes?
I was on a tour. The robots made
some kind of operational error.
Hydra's going to explode!
There's no way to stop it!
What? Wait a--
Pretty smart, boss.
Made a mess up here
and now you're gonna make it
all simply disappear.
You just have to press
the self-destruct button.
We evacuate, the robots
get blown up,
and they take
all the blame for this.
Let's hope so!
Now, go disable all the telecoms
so the robots can't tell anyone
what really happened!
THORNE:
Silence is golden.
COMPUTER:
Emergency
self-destruct system ready.
Please enter password.
Once the password is activated,
Hydra will self-destruct
in two hours.
CONTROL SYSTEM:
Level red!
Lower the internal pressure
immediately!
Aah!
[YELPS]
I'll get help!
Forget it, Jasper!
It is too late for us.
Argh!
What are you waiting for?
COMPUTER:
Please enter password.
THORNE:
Just type in
anything you want!
It's just so the robots can't
cancel the self-destruct order.
It can be any word at all.
Just do it!
Now, we must shut off
all the valves in Section C.
Don't take your eyes
off the pressure gauges!
CONTROL SYSTEM:
Self-destruct system activated.
Self-destruct system
activated.
All crew members,
evacuate Hydra immediately.
What went wrong?
Please evacuate immediately.
Hurry up, will you?
JASPER:
Wait a minute!
Evacuate? Self-destruct?
What's going on?
I don't know.
This is your system.
Uh, the Space Council
tried to contact you.
The Space Council?
Yeah, they said they're sending
a rescue ship for you.
Just wait right here.
Where are you going?
Come on!
Containment shield activation
in five seconds!
Four, three, two, one.
Commencing shield activation.
THORNE:
The shield's supposed
to keep the explosion
from damaging
other space stations.
But it's also gonna keep
any of those robots
from leaving
before the explosion.
All of our problems are
gonna be solved by one big bang.
O'SHAY:
Hydra's robots are too advanced.
I can't believe they'd
make a mistake like this.
WOMAN:
But that's what we were told.
Unbelievable!
With all that energy, it will be
a disaster if Hydra explodes!
Doctor, there are hundreds
of robots on Hydra.
I've gotta help!
I can't let them all be
destroyed. It's just not right!
Hmm.
One hour, 38 minutes
and 8 seconds until detonation.
and 6 seconds until detonation.
One hour, 38 minutes
and 4 seconds until detonation.
COMPUTER:
Access denied.
Incorrect password.
Please enter correct password.
I can't do it!
ROBOT: Jasper!
Huh?
The temperature
is going up too fast.
We're all shutting down.
What do we do?
Move to the computer repair bay.
It will be a little cooler
there. Hurry!
But, Mr. Chairman,
you have to send a rescue team
for those robots.
If you don't,
they'll all be destroyed.
Listen, those are
just robots, O'Shay.
They're not living people.
Can't you tell the difference
between humans
and machines anymore?
Yes, but--
There's no time to argue.
Those robots are gonna
be blown to pieces.
Let me ask you, Astro,
what would happen
if some humans needed help here
while the rescue squad
was off saving those robots?
There wouldn't be anyone around
to save the humans,
would there?
But, sir--
I'm sorry.
Wait, please!
Astro, don't!
I'm going to Hydra and
I'm going to rescue everyone,
whether they're humans
or robots!
THORNE: Huh.
What did I tell you?
They're not sending anyone
to rescue the robots!
Well, they're just
a bunch of tin cans anyway.
DONNER:
Yeah, tin cans.
And I needed
to steal that program.
All for the sake of my company.
THORNE:
Yeah, sure, sure.
But you're not gonna have to
worry about them
much longer, boss.
Enough!
What do you know about it, fool?
Just be quiet
and stay at the monitor!
ASTRO:
So this is Hydra.
Hmm, wow.
Even though they have
their shield up,
I can feel the heat
from way out here!
If it gets much hotter
in there,
everyone inside will be...
I gotta move fast
and break through this shield!
No way!
The only chance to knock it down
is to blast both poles
of the shield at the same time!
But how can I--?
[DISTANT HORSE NEIGHING]
Huh?
The Blue Knight!
Excellent!
I'll fire at the top...
And at the same time,
I'll fire at the bottom.
Let's rocket!
Roar!
I can't believe it!
The shield is down! Ugh!
CONTROL SYSTEM:
Fifty minutes and 44 seconds
until detonation.
[GRUNTS]
No use.
ROBOT:
Look! The rescue squad!
Okay, who's in charge here?
I am!
I am the chief robot, Jasper.
There must be a way
to save the space station!
We need the password
to the self-destruct program.
Without it,
there's nothing we can do
to keep it from burning up.
Password?
The rescue squad
is coming, right?
Well, uh...
BLUE KNIGHT:
We're just the advance party.
Do not worry,
backup's on the way.
They'll be here
in just a few minutes.
In the meantime,
you all need to get to
the escape shuttle right away.
The path to the shuttle
is blocked. Look!
ASTRO:
Not a problem!
JASPER:
Come on, we must move fast!
The rescue squad's
not coming.
I know.
Huh?
BLUE KNIGHT:
If they find out these filthy
humans don't care about them,
they might give up.
And we can't have that, can we?
Uh-uh.
Now, let's get them
out of here!
All of them!
Forty-five minutes, 12 seconds
until detonation.
Forty-five minutes,
10 seconds--
Hurry, everybody, hurry!
Faster!
This way! The emergency
shuttle's already powered up!
ROBOT:
All right!
JASPER:
Keep moving!
We are almost there.
Runway's clear for-- Ohh!
It's molten ore
from the refinery!
Get back!
ROBOT:
We can't take off now!
We're trapped! Hopeless!
Stay calm! It's okay.
Astro's right.
The rescue squad is going to be
here for us any minute.
Aren't they?
Uh...
Gee, I...
Uh, Jasper, uh...
Uh...Astro?
Jasper, uh...
ASTRO:
We haven't been, um...
totally honest with you.
So there's
no rescue squad?
No. They're not coming.
[GASPS]
The chairman told us the
rescue squad's for humans only.
And we were afraid that
if you and the others found out,
you'd just give up.
But, look,
there's still hope.
Hope? You lied to us!
You tricked us!
How could you do that?
How could you?
Jasper, search
your memory banks.
There has got to be
a way to fix this.
I know there has to be!
Let's cross-reference
everything.
We'll find something!
There is one thing.
This is the plan
for the cooling system.
We might be able to use
the coolant in the pipes
to put out the fires, but it's
going to take a lot of force.
The Blue Knight!
Hmm.
ROBOT:
All right!
ROBOT 2:
The plan worked!
We did it!
We'll be able to launch
the shuttle now.
Almost time for Hydra
to go kablooie.
Hey, boss?
Where'd you go?
JASPER:
Everyone's on board.
Okay, Jasper!
Hit it!
Opening the gateway now!
All systems
now ready for launch.
Gravity system disengaged.
Firing the main engines.
Hey, isn't that--?
Mr. Donner?
Aah!
[GASPS]
DONNER:
Those robots
aren't going anywhere.
Not as long as they know
that I'm the one who's
responsible for this meltdown!
You will have
to deal with me now.
Let's rocket!
Rocket this!
That all you've got?
Grrr!
You will pay!
ASTRO:
No! Don't!
Argh!
ASTRO:
No!
Aah!
JASPER:
The shuttle
hit the docking bay!
He must be hurt!
Jasper, we need
to get out of here!
I know!
That's not the way!
But I've got
to help Donner.
But he's responsible
for all this!
Ugh.
JASPER:
Mr. Donner!
Huh?
Jasper?
You're alive!
But not for long.
So, did you come here
to say goodbye?
No, sir.
That's not why--
[GASPS]
Astro! Blue Knight!
He's hurt bad!
Ugh.
BLUE KNIGHT:
Don't move him.
These humans are
extremely fragile.
ASTRO:
But he's really hurt
and there's a crack
in the boot of his spacesuit.
If we don't get him to a doctor
soon, he's not going to make it.
The password!
CONTROL SYSTEM: Two minutes,
24 seconds until detonation.
You go.
Forget about me.
Just get out of here
while you still can!
Listen, just give me
the password
and you can save all of us
and yourself.
DONNER:
I'm nothing but a criminal now.
I'm going to lose everything.
But you still have
one thing left, Mr. Donner.
You've still got your life.
Robots work hard
to make your life easier.
We serve you and protect you.
Even when it gets hard,
we still do it with pride.
I don't understand humans.
Do a good thing now.
Make up for your crime.
You're right.
I'll tell you the password.
Ugh!
Argh!
CONTROL SYSTEM:
Countdown to detonation.
Ten...nine...
eight...seven...six...
five...four...three...
two...one...
Emergency self-destruct system
has been cancelled.
Wow! That was close!
Ugh.
"Forgive me." That was
the password he used.
CONTROL SYSTEM:
Emergency self-destruct system
has been cancelled.
If we were all just
lifeless machines to you,
why would anyone have to
forgive you for destroying us?
Deep down, I guess
I knew I was wrong.
ROBOT:
Jasper! Jasper!
Yes?
We're here for the human!
He needs a shuttle, doesn't he?
Sir, it's time to go.
Back home to Earth
with all of us.
Great teamwork,
Blue Knight.
Astro, do you now
understand my fight?
What?
We saved the robots
this time,
but there are other humans out
there determined to destroy us.
You can't continue
to fight for both sides.
Next time, I won't
hold anything back.
And I won't let you
or anyone else stop me.
Humans or robots, Astro?
You have to choose a side.
Hah!
ASTRO:
I choose both.
[♪]