[♪]
It's time to settle
this matter once and for all.
[BARKING, GROWLING]
[SCREAMS]
TOWER MAN:
Security system at C block
has been disabled.
All sections are shutting down!
The entire grid is crashing.
O'SHAY:
What's happening?
The security system
and all network communications
have been taken off-line.
What?
[ALL GASPING, SCREAMING]
Code red.
Huh?
[MAN YELLS]
MAN:
Get down!
It's poison gas.
I can't stop it.
It's burning its way
right through the insulation.
The gas will fill up
the building in no time.
We have to get
everyone out.
[GRUNTING]
Evacuate!
[ALL SHOUTING]
[SIREN WAILING]
TENMA:
Tobio.
As a special treat,
how would you like
to come to the Ministry
of Science with me?
Huh?
If you're good,
I'll take you there
myself next Sunday.
Really? Next Sunday?
You mean I'd finally get to
see where you work, Dad?
Oh!
Hey, Nora. Maybe you can
come with us.
Can Nora come
with us too, Dad?
No, she can't.
Why not?
Nora's my best friend.
Tobio, Nora is not your friend.
She's just a robot.
Hmm.
Oh!
You've outgrown
that scooter of yours.
So here.
I bought you a jet bike
of your very own.
Wow! It's the coolest bike
I've ever seen.
Can I ride it now, Dad? Can I?
You can ride it
as much as you want.
Once we're finished
at the Ministry.
This is the entrance
to Laboratory Seven.
Dad, what do you do here?
ASTRO:
What do you do here?
TENMA:
And so we begin. Again.
TAWASHI: How could
the Ministry of Science
be infiltrated
so easily?
It must be
the work of--
There's no doubt.
Dr. Tenma!
Hmm.
[MACHINERY CREAKING]
Back where it all began.
Hmm.
What's all this?
This is how we dispose of
unwanted robots.
[GASPS]
But what do you mean?
When robots
are outdated,
we break them apart and melt
them down to make new robots.
Think of it as...
recycling.
Oh, yes, that reminds me.
I have another surprise for you.
It's the most advanced
service robot ever built.
What about Nora?
Nora's a primitive model.
She's considered obsolete
by today's standards.
Obso--
But you don't mean--
This new design
is far superior.
The Nora 4000.
It's much more efficient than--
TOBIO:
Why won't you listen to me?
What's wrong?
You can't just
replace Nora.
She's always there for me
when you're not.
She is the only friend I've got.
Tobio.
Robots are nothing more
than manufactured machines,
and sometimes they have
to be replaced.
No!
Stay away from her.
I'll never let you hurt Nora.
Behave yourself!
Tobio, how dare you talk
back to me like that!
You never listen to me.
You don't even
really care about me.
What are you talking about?
Didn't I just buy you
a new jet bike?
[GRUNTS]
I don't want a jet bike!
I want a father!
[SOBBING]
Tobio.
[MACHINE BEEPING]
YUKO: Dr. Tenma's
reactivating the systems.
He's taken over
Laboratory Seven.
Did you say Lab Seven?
Yeah. That was the robot
disposal facility.
But what would he be doing
in a place like that?
Now that I have taken over
the Ministry of Science,
I have one request.
There is something
very important
I would like to discuss
with Tobio.
Allow me to speak with him,
one last time, in private,
just the two of us.
If you refuse,
I will detonate
the Pyro Annihilator.
One click and Metro City
will be gone forever.
[CACKLES]
Uh, we apologize
for the interruption.
It appears that Dr. Tenma has
intercepted our satellite feed
in order to voice his demand
to speak with Astro,
who he calls "Tobio."
Out of the question!
There is no telling
what Tenma will do.
Detective Tawashi.
Ignore his demands and dispatch
the Akita Squad to Lab Seven.
I have a responsibility
to protect the citizens
of Metro City.
Millions of lives
are at risk.
Your responsibility
is to put an end to this.
ASTRO:
Doctor!
I will go.
Astro!
Detective Tawashi's right.
There's too much at stake.
I have to go and see
what Tenma wants.
But Astro, wait!
You might never--
Argh!
Oh! No!
[YELLS] Astro!
I feel--
I feel like
I've been here before.
TENMA:
Tobio.
This is the Ministry
of Science. My kingdom.
Your kingdom?
The most powerful robots
in the world are built here.
And they're
all my creation.
I would say that makes me king
of all robots, wouldn't you?
Oh!
Dr. Tenma.
There you are.
ASTRO:
The detonating switch.
I've got to get it
away from him.
TENMA: I've been waiting
for you, Tobio.
ASTRO:
I'm not Tobio!
I am Astro.
You're mistaken.
You will always be the robot
that I created to replace Tobio.
His memories are
implanted in you, forever.
Awaken!
Tobio. You are finally reborn.
To-- To--
Tobio.
TENMA:
I swore not to make
the same mistake twice.
I tried to earn loyalty and
respect from my robot Tobio.
I thought I had succeeded.
But I was wrong.
[GASPS]
ASTRO:
Doctor! That robot's damaged.
She needs your help.
Not that old model. I'll build
a new one just for you.
But what about
this one?
Tobio, I told you that robot--
Listen to me!
[GASPS]
TENMA:
Again, rebellion.
As your robot mind developed,
you began to change.
Tobio.
That night, I brought you here,
to Lab Seven.
I had a theory
I needed to test.
I wanted to see
how you would respond
when you entered
this place.
How can you?
Doctor, I'm a robot too.
How can you do that to them?
You are not like
all those other robots.
You are special.
I don't understand.
I'm still just a robot.
You're much more
than that.
Tobio, I care about you
very much.
You don't.
If you cared about robots,
you wouldn't destroy them.
Does that mean you're going
to destroy me too?
[WAILING]
PHILIP:
Detective Tawashi.
We need to start evacuating
Metro City at once.
Delta.
Yes, sir.
Tell me. Is the robot squad
ready to go?
Affirmative.
Detective. Take me
with you. Please!
This is our job
now, doctor.
Evacuate immediately.
I can't.
Astro's in there,
and he may need my help.
Let go!
If you won't take me with you,
then I'll go there myself.
But doctor, it's too dangerous.
Don't go!
Delta!
DELTA: We've got him.
ASTRO: I rebelled against you
just like your son did.
That's why you shut down
my system, isn't it?
That's right.
But it was more than that alone.
As time went on,
you began to frighten me.
I scared you?
But how did I do that?
Perhaps you'll remember this.
[ELECTRICAL WHIRRING]
[GASPS]
You're evil.
You destroy robots as if they
don't mean anything at all.
TENMA:
Wait.
Come back.
[ASTRO WAILING]
Tobio!
Oh!
No!
Robots were invented
to serve mankind.
But I had created a robot
with a heart and a mind,
one with the ability
to rebel against humans,
totally unpredictable.
I became convinced that
in spite of my good intentions,
I had created a monster.
ASTRO:
I'm sorry.
I couldn't watch you
destroy those robots.
TENMA:
Tobio.
You have not yet learned
to control your true power.
ASTRO:
Will you forgive me?
I'm really sorry.
[GASPS]
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
Does this jog your memory?
This is the Kiru Ring I used
to shut down your system
that fateful day.
Dr. Tenma. Put that away.
You don't want to do this.
I never promised you
a happy reunion.
This time, you will decide
how it all ends.
TENMA:
After deactivating you,
I destroyed all of my
experimental robot prototypes.
I realized that robots would
only get stronger and smarter.
Soon they would be able
to overthrow humans.
The very thought tormented me
day and night.
I almost went mad.
[LAUGHS INSANELY]
But then Dr. O'Shay found
my robot Tobio, revived him
and named him...
Astro.
[KIRU RING CRACKLES]
TENMA:
As I watched you
gain control
of your tremendous power,
something inside of me changed.
Suddenly, my fear had vanished.
I witnessed an amazing robot
with a mind of its own,
free from human control.
After discovering
your astounding capabilities,
I began to envision
a glorious future
for the entire world.
For that reason,
I put obstacles in your path
so you could grow,
each challenge
greater than the last.
You had to evolve in order
to achieve your full potential.
For someday, the magnificent
robot that I created,
you, Tobio,
would be ruler of the world
I dreamt about.
Come back to me, Tobio.
That wonderful world
is still within our grasp.
I am the only one
who appreciates
your greatness, Tobio.
That's a lie!
It's your own greatness
you believe in.
You're the one who wants
to rule the entire world.
No, doctor!
I'll never take part
in your evil plan.
Very well.
Huh?
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
I will spare your friends
and Metro City.
But the explosions!
This is the third time
I have failed
in this wretched place.
Laboratory Seven
must be destroyed.
[SHOUTS] And I must be
destroyed along with it!
Doctor!
What did you--?
Yes, you reacted
as I feared you would.
Dr. Tenma, you knew
what I would say?
Goodbye.
You planned this?
[GASPS]
No! Dr. Tenma!
[GRUNTS]
Careful.
I do not want to
have to hurt you again.
[GASPS]
Come with me.
I can get us out of here.
Back. Stay away from me!
My time has come.
There's still time.
I can save us.
[GROANS]
Doctor!
I forgive you.
[GASPS]
[SIGHS]
[WAILING]
Tobio!
Astro!
DELTA:
It's too dangerous!
[GROANING]
Careful,
Dr. O'Shay.
Astro!
Doctor!
Are you all right?
TENMA: I was never fit
to be your father.
We both know it's true.
[GASPS]
Dr. Tenma.
DELTA:
Astro!
The explosions have completely
destroyed our only escape route.
The whole building's
about to blow.
[DELTA AND O'SHAY YELL]
BOTH:
Astro!
[YELLS]
LYON:
Today
the Federal Council
has approved
a fundamental change
to our constitution.
This legislation declares
the civil rights
of robots everywhere
in a worldwide
partnership with mankind.
Dr. O'Shay.
Today is a day
that I have
dreamed about for years,
but never truly
expected to see.
From this moment forward,
humans and robots
stand united as partners,
working together as a team.
Robots were first designed
to be tools for man,
mere machines
working to improve the lives
of the humans who owned them.
They were programmed to follow
our every command.
But then robots
were given kokoro,
and we soon learned
their hearts and minds
made them more like humans.
Some of us thought
that was a wonderful thing.
But others became fearful.
Through disagreements
and misunderstandings,
we entered into a dark period.
Many turned against
our robot friends.
How could we understand
their anger and resentment?
If we had stopped to consider
the feelings of robots,
the Robotonia Revolution
could have been avoided.
As we move forward,
we must learn
from our past mistakes
and make changes
to improve our future.
Above all, we must be
willing to forgive.
I speak now on behalf
of all humankind,
when I hereby declare
that robots are no longer
tools for man.
They are our equals,
our partners
and our friends.
And they are here to stay,
to share this wonderful
planet with us.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Big brother!
[GASPS]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[SOBS]
RENO:
Astro.
Hey!
We are so happy
for you.
Your dream
finally came true.
Hmm, yeah, but--
ALL:
But what?
Well, guys,
you can't stop dreaming.
Besides, something tells me
this is just the beginning.
Let's rocket!
[♪]