[♪]
ZORAN:
Wow! Look at the ocean!
It's so bright!
ASTRO:
That's the sun sparkling
across the tops
of the waves, Zoran.
Reminds me of my eyes.
Well, we're almost
at the Marine Center
and I can't wait to meet Gideon,
Reno's very first robot.
Reno designed him
for deep-sea navigation,
but gave him emotions and heart
like you.
Dr. O'Shay, you're still
gonna let us all
go on the test voyage
with Gideon tomorrow, right?
Yes, and Professor Poppotorre
is going to go along with you
so he can study the area too.
Reno told me
that Gideon was going to explore
a place called Hazard Pass.
Yes, it's a mysterious area
of the sea
where a lot of ships
have disappeared.
Where ships disappear?
That sounds scary.
Oh, scary indeed.
According to ancient legends,
a monster called
the Phantom Pirate
swallows up ships
as they sail through the pass.
Astro, you won't let
that big, scary pirate monster
swallow us up, will you?
Not a chance.
Gideon will help us
find a way to stop him first.
Besides, we'd leave
a metallic aftertaste.
[CHUCKLES]
O'SHAY: We have to do some
maintenance on the submarine.
Reno and Gideon are down below.
You two go on ahead.
Okay.
RENO:
What's the matter, Gideon?
You can't do
a real deep-sea investigation
if you get scared every time
you see something move.
I know. I'm sorry.
So much for robots
with feelings.
Give me an old-fashioned
heartless robot any day.
MAN: Talk about a porpoise
without a purpose.
Clam up now
or you're all fired.
Huh?
Er...
Okay, that's enough training
for today.
Reno?
Huh?
Glad you could make it here
to meet Gideon.
I hope you're not
too disappointed.
What do you mean, Reno?
I'm not so sure
it was a good idea
to give human emotions
to an undersea robot.
I wanted him to be fearless when
he investigated unknown waters.
But every time we do a test run,
he gets scared
before he's halfway down.
I should have never told him
about the Phantom Pirate.
The problem is, he can't learn
courage and bravery
until he experiences
those things for himself.
Well, I guess we'll have to
find out at tomorrow's dive,
but I won't be
holding my breath.
Big day's almost here,
little buddy.
I know you can do it.
POPPOTORRE:
Woo-hoo!
O'SHAY:
Okay, everyone.
Now, be careful.
Okay. Don't wait up.
Bye!
RENO:
Let's go, Gideon.
Okay!
POPPOTORRE:
Ah, here it is.
The Phantom Pirate's curse.
Hundreds of years ago,
a pirate ship sank very close
to Hazard Pass.
Some believe
that a phantom pirate
still guards
the priceless treasure
that sank along with it.
[SLURPING]
Now, a bounty like that
would be perfect
for financing my new
robotic dinosaur project.
I'd be the talk
of the robo-reptile world.
[CACKLING]
What is that?
It's still a secret,
one that I have treasured
for years.
[LAUGHS]
GIDEON: We've almost
reached the dive point.
ASTRO:
You mean this is Hazard Pass?
RENO:
Yep. If all goes well,
we'll soon be solving
our first underwater mystery.
And I'll take all
the credit for it.
[LAUGHS]
Okay, Gideon,
let's start diving.
Here we go.
It's a whole new world
down here.
Wow!
ZORAN:
And the water's so blue.
Hey, the deeper we get,
the darker the water is.
Look!
ZORAN: It's almost too dark
to see anything.
POPPOTORRE:
Now, if I was a phantom pirate,
this is just the kind of place
I would hide.
[LAUGHS]
Huh?
We can get a better view
from down below.
ALL:
Whoa!
[CLANG]
It's pitch-black.
The deep sea starts here.
RENO:
Yeah, once we get this deep,
the sunlight
doesn't even reach us.
[RUMBLING]
[YELLS]
[ALL SCREAMING]
What is it?
What's going on?
[GRUNTS]
RENO:
The sea currents are unstable!
Gideon, find us a safe route.
Er, okay.
GIDEON: Stable current 42 meters
off the starboard side.
I got it.
ALL:
Whoa!
Ah, we're saved.
Wow, Gideon's a whiz
with sea currents.
Good work, Gideon.
Warning. We are passing
the 3000-meter mark.
[WHIMPERING]
[CREAKING]
What's that sound?
The submarine's creaking
under the deep-water pressure.
Oh!
[SLURPING]
Watch this.
[BEEP]
Now, that's water pressure.
The deeper you go,
the greater the pressure.
If I were out there,
I'd be crushed to bits
in about three seconds.
Oh!
Does that mean we can't
all go swimming today?
Watch, Zoran.
The seafloor should be
coming into view.
Huh?
Oh.
Oh, well.
She'll be all right.
Oh, yeah.
I forgot she's a robot.
For a minute there, I thought
she was going to explode.
Hey, Gideon.
Why don't fish deep in the ocean
get squished
by the water pressure?
Well, Zoran,
water pressure only affects
things that have air in them,
like the submarine
you were riding in
and human lungs.
GIDEON:
Deep-sea fish
have oil in their bladders
instead of air.
Wow! You know everything.
Zoran, when are you
going to learn
to stop running off?
Oh, right after I learn a few
more things about the ocean
from Gideon.
I guess I should have
seen that answer coming.
[TITTERS]
Huh?
ZORAN: It looks like
there's a mountain over there.
GIDEON: Mountains are
very common on the ocean floor.
GIDEON: Wait! What's that
coming toward us?
[ALL GASP]
[GASPS]
Arggh!
[ZORAN SCREAMING]
POPPOTORRE:
He's gonna hit us!
Gideon, you've got to calm down!
Huh?
Gideon, it's just crabs
stirring up the sand.
[GIDEON AND ZORAN YELLING]
Zoran!
Huh?
RENO: Gideon, you can't keep
flipping out like that.
You put Zoran
in terrible danger.
I did almost
swallow a starfish.
But besides that,
it was really a lot of fun.
Sheesh. Scared to death
by a bunch of crabs.
Reno!
Gideon didn't know that they
were just some sand crabs.
Hmm?
ASTRO:
I'll bet you thought
that that big cloud of sand
was the Phantom Pirate,
didn't you, Gideon?
ZORAN:
The Phantom Pirate?
So Gideon really was
trying to save me.
Uh-huh.
Reno told me
that the Phantom Pirate
could devour ships,
and maybe robots too.
So I was afraid he would
go after Zoran and myself
if we stayed there.
I think I took in--
[HICCUPPING]
--a little too much water.
[HICCUPS]
We'll help you get rid
of your hiccups, okay?
Okay.
Should we scare them
out of him?
No, I don't think so.
He's been frightened enough
for one day.
Thanks, Reno. I agree.
Yeah, I'll just have
to loosen his dorsal fin
and let the water out.
That'll fix him.
But what I'm
really worried about
is how Gideon is going to
complete the investigation
and get all the data we need
if he keeps on chickening out.
He knows how to be afraid
because I scared him
with those dumb Phantom stories.
Maybe you were right, Astro.
He has to experience courage
for himself
before he can have any.
How do you know he'll ever be
brave enough to experience it?
Good question.
Yeah.
Because I designed him myself.
That's how I know.
Hm.
RENO:
Descending below 5000 meters.
Keep it steady.
ZORAN: It's kind of
eerie down here.
Gideon, how far are we
from the ocean floor?
Almost there.
87 meters until we're at
the very bottom of Hazard Pass.
Look! Right there!
RENO: Yeah, it's like an entire
graveyard of ships.
ZORAN: I think I saw
something move.
[ZORAN WHIMPERS]
Probably a fish
or something.
POPPOTORRE:
Ships ahoy!
Somewhere down there,
a pirate ship sank,
and it was carrying a chest
chock-full of treasure.
BOTH: Huh?
Treasure?
Come on. Last one out
has to walk the plank.
Ugh!
Arggh!
[RENO SCREAMING]
GIDEON: It's dangerous
to enter a sunken ship
without
checking it out first.
ASTRO:
Professor Poppotorre,
we don't have any idea
what could be inside that ship.
No worries.
That old tale
of the Phantom Pirate
was made up by treasure hunters
to keep folks away.
But the air in these bubble
scooters won't last forever.
Anchors aweigh!
ASTRO:
Professor!
POPPOTORRE:
Look at the hole in that thing!
ZORAN:
Boy!
Somebody got in a bunch
of trouble for that!
RENO: It's like it was shot
with a cannon or something.
ASTRO: Only if it was shot
from below.
That hole wasn't made
from a cannon.
Maybe we'll find a clue
somewhere inside the ship.
Okay, everyone,
stay here
and I'll check inside
to see if it's safe.
[SCREAMS]
Be brave, Gideon. Be brave.
Gideon!
Astro.
It looks like it's safe
for you guys to come in.
What are we waiting for, then?
All aboard!
ZORAN:
Whoa!
Professor, wait!
We gotta stay together.
Here, treasure,
treasure,
treasure, treasure.
Here, treasure.
ASTRO: I can't find a thing
that would tell us why it sank.
ZORAN: Wait a minute.
I hear something rumbling.
[BEEPING]
Huh?
What is it?
Danger nearby, coming closer.
Where?
Here, treasure, treasure...
Ahh!
Treasure!
Ooh! We're rich!
It's moving...very fast
straight toward us.
Oh, no!
[GIDEON'S CIRCUITS BEEPING]
It's underground,
coming straight up!
Back to the submarine.
Hurry!
RENO: Wait.
Where's the professor?
Huh?
Come to Papa. Come to Papa.
Give me-- Ugh!
ASTRO:
Professor!
This way!
[GRUNTING]
Yahh!
[POPPOTORRE SCREAMING]
Gotcha!
[GRUNTING]
[ALL YELL]
POPPOTORRE:
The Phantom!
[ZORAN SCREAMING]
[YELLING]
Courage, Gideon, courage!
[ASTRO GROANING]
[POPPOTORRE SCREAMS]
Professor!
If I don't slow this thing
down quick, it'll crack up!
Oh, no! We're running out
of oxygen.
[CRIES OUT]
Gideon, we've got to get
everyone back to the sub
as quickly as possible.
Astro, look! The submarine!
[METAL CREAKING]
I'll be right back.
Astro! Let me get it!
How?
I can read
the water currents.
Come on, Gideon!
Arggh!
[BOOM]
Gideon!
[METAL GROANING]
GIDEON: Phantom or no phantom,
this sub's not going anywhere!
Gideon, how brave!
Hurry!
[GRUNTS]
Gideon, let's get out of here.
Roger!
[GRUNTING]
[ALL SIGH]
Nice job.
No problem.
Transferring data now.
ASTRO & ZORAN:
Whoa!
RENO:
This is incredible!
You've got Hazard Pass
and the entire region
mapped out in detail!
You did it, Gideon!
Gideon's map even shows cracks
in the ocean floor.
See? That's where
the gases came from,
shooting up through the Earth's
crust like a volcano.
That's what sank
all those ships.
RENO: That solves the mystery
of the Phantom Pirate.
Phantom Pirate.
Never believed it.
Wasn't it you
that was screaming
about the Phantom earlier?
Who, me? Course not!
[CHUCKLES]
Let's get him.
[BOTH GROWL]
POPPOTORRE:
Ah! No tickling!
Hey!
ZORAN:
It looks like real gold!
Did I not mention
the gold cup
and how I'm using it
to fund my project?
Oh, give me that!
It belongs to the city as part
of our exploration agreement.
But my project,
my ancient dinosaur robot!
POPPOTORRE: I need that cup!
ZORAN: Stop it! Stop it!
Give me that back!
Gimme, gimme!
GIDEON:
Hey, Astro!
Do you remember
what you said
about experiencing courage
for the very first time?
Yeah.
Well, that's all it took.
I don't have to be afraid
of anything anymore,
not even a phantom pirate.
[LAUGHS]
Not even a bunch
of phantom crabs?
[TITTERING]
[LAUGHING]
ZORAN:
Look!
A monster in the harbor
with a big, scary nose!
ZORAN:
Oh, it's just Dr. O'Shay.
RENO:
To the harbor, Gideon.
Full speed ahead.
Land ahoy! Aye, aye, captain.
[ALL CHEERING AND LAUGHING]
RENO:
Ahoy!
All right!
[♪]