[♪]
YUKO:
Honestly, doctor,
if we left it to you,
you'd never take a vacation.
Now I want you to spend
this weekend just relaxing,
all right?
You'll love this resort.
O'SHAY:
Yeah, B-but...
YUKO:
I've got you scheduled
for golf at 6,
yoga at 10,
then hiking, tennis,
bowling, water aerobics--
O'SHAY:
Very relaxing.
I should be in a coma by dinner.
I'll pick you both up Monday.
Astro, you watch
over the doctor.
Right.
Look, everyone.
There's the town of Bella Notte.
Wow. Wonder what
that tent's for.
Dr. O'Shay!
Welcome to Bella Notte.
I'm Mayor Craven.
It's an honor to have
such a famous scientist
in our fair city.
O'SHAY:
Uh, thank you.
CRAVEN:
Now, I've arranged
a few activities for your visit:
Pickle judging, thumb wrestling
and a tour
of the kibble factory.
Doctor, look.
A robot circus
is coming into town.
Uh, did you say
a robot circus?
Oh, my, yes.
Definitely a must-see.
A traveling circus
composed entirely of robots.
They're really quite famous in
these parts. And I must say,
you haven't lived till you've--
GUSTAV: Hey, Craven.
Since when do you allow robots
to put up posters
for their so-called circus?
Uh, Mr. Gustav, I, uh...
Get in.
Yes, sir.
Uh, well,
if you'll excuse me.
GUSTAV:
Get in!
It looks like some robots
are starting to think they're
just like human beings.
I don't like it.
Friendly little town.
That's Mr. Gustav,
owner of Jade Refinery,
and the richest man in town.
He pretty much
runs this city.
All right. Let's just
go over this
one more time,
shall we, Mr. Mayor?
I don't like robots
and I don't want them
doing business in my city.
Robots need to know
their place.
They're servants
and nothing more.
That's the way
it's always been,
and that's the way
it's gonna stay. Got it?
Yes, sir.
Anyway, I've got plans
for that circus.
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls,
children of all ages...
welcome to the
super-sensational,
ultra-gyrational,
quite educational Robot Circus.
Let the show begin.
Yahoo!
Yeah!
BOTH:
Ta-daa!
[CHEERING]
ASTRO:
It's Mr. Gustav.
But why is he here?
I thought he hated robots.
[WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
Look out!
[CROWD SCREAMING]
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen,
please remain calm!
Don't panic!
[CROWD SCREAMING]
Please!
Stay calm, folks!
Cookie!
Whoa!
Bon-Bon,
throw me up there!
You bet.
Yee-haw!
Reno, be careful.
I'll be fine.
Oh. Oh! Whoa!
Huh?
[COOKIE YELLING]
Oh!
Ha-ha-ha.
You okay,
Cookie?
Safe.
Thanks.
O'SHAY:
Astro.
Are you hurt?
Doctor, that boy robot
is a human.
Wh-what?
What a terrible accident.
But we're all fine,
thanks to Astro.
That was no accident.
Astro says he saw the rope being
cut by one of Gustav's men. Oh?
RENO:
There you go.
All fixed up.
Now, let's see you move it.
Perfect.
Good as new.
Great job, Reno.
Reno, you've
repaired him already?
Sure.
Using just this
flexation sensor?
Yeah.
I use whatever works.
You know,
Reno made that gadget.
He's smarter than a barrel
full of, eh, smart things.
I agree.
Uh, Reno, I can see you have
an amazing talent for robotics.
He's a veritable
virtuoso.
He could be
a scientist.
Why, if he had the
proper education, he--
Aw, come on.
It's no big deal.
I think it's perfectly natural
for a robot to know
about robotics and stuff.
ASTRO:
Reno...
why are you pretending
to be a robot?
[SCREAMING]
I mean,
you're human.
What are you talking about?
I'm a robot.
You must have
a short circuit somewhere.
That's right.
He's a robot.
You're talking crazy.
Now get out of here.
Yeah.
Beat it!
Go away!
Stop it!
All of you!
What has gotten
into you?
Remember, these people
saved our circus. And us.
I apologize for my
overzealous friends.
We are all still
a bit shaken.
Now, if you'll excuse us,
we've got work to do.
Reno.
Reno, is it you?
Uh, huh?
You look different,
but I think--
Well, I mean, if it is you,
I'm sorry about before.
I didn't mean
to cause trouble.
Guess I'm busted, huh?
Mm-hm.
You see, I was abandoned
when I was a baby.
The folks in the circus, uh,
found me and took me in.
You mean, you were
raised by robots?
Sure. I've been
really lucky.
Since I was
a little kid,
I've had, like,
five fathers and one mom.
Of course, I go broke
every Father's Day,
but they're worth it.
Yeah, I can see they are.
You see that circus tent?
That's my home,
no matter where it is.
And those robots are my family.
The best family
in the whole world.
I owe them everything.
But why the disguise?
Because some folks might not
like the idea
of robots raising a human.
I care for my family,
and I know they care for me,
but if it ever got out
that I'm a human,
well, face it,
I'm just still a kid.
I could be
taken away from them.
That's why
it's gotta be a secret.
Too bad.
Well, then,
we'll just have to make sure
it stays a secret, won't we?
You bet, Astro. Thanks.
[GUSTAV GRUNTS]
I want that robot circus
crushed. Do you hear me?
Snoop around. Dig up
all the dirt you can.
Get me something
I can use against them!
Now, get going!
Mercy. We're in deep doughnuts.
BON-BON:
Mamma llama! Are you sure?
It's only
a matter of time
before Gustav
figures out our secret.
Boss, we've gotta get
out of here now.
If we stick around, we're
headed for big time trouble.
The boy is talented.
He should be in school. Pity.
Ahem.
Ah, Mr. Panna Cotta.
Doctor,
I have a favor to ask.
Craven...call out the police!
I want those circus
robots arrested.
B-b-but why?
They've been concealing
a human child.
They've obviously
kidnapped the boy.
As mayor, it's your duty
to see that justice is done!
Boy? But I didn't--
Of course not, you idiot.
They've kept him
disguised as a robot.
If you need proof, just
look at these photographs.
So you want me to take
this letter to Dr. O'Shay
at his hotel, right?
Yes, Reno. And be sure you hand
it to him personally.
You got it.
BOTH:
Reno.
Boss?
This is it.
We're leaving town now.
MARSHMALLOW: Right. Let's go.
BON-BON: Let's move it.
[SIRENS WAILING]
I'm sorry, Reno.
Dr. O'Shay said
he had to
run out
to do something.
Okay. I'll wait till
he gets back.
Huh?
They look like they're headed
toward the circus.
Aw, we've been
found out.
Hey! Huh?
Oh!
Aw, there he is,
the poor little guy.
The innocent victim
of this terrible crime.
Get off.
So sad.
Forced into a life
of treachery and deceit
after that ruthless gang
of circus robots kidnapped him.
Huh?
Ehh!
Where are they?
If they're caught,
will they be destroyed?
Reno, don't do it.
You will only
make things worse.
Fear not, my friends.
The robots will be
found and dismantled.
And this child
will be sent
to an orphanage
where he belongs.
Right, Mr. Mayor?
Y-yes.
It's just, well--
No!
It's the law!
Take the boy
into custody now.
Let him go.
I'm Reno's guardian.
Doctor!
I have the necessary
paperwork with me right here.
[GROWLS]
Fine. You may have
the boy, doctor,
but kidnapping
is a police matter.
Those robots
are criminals,
and they're headed
for the scrap heap.
And there's not a thing
you can do about that.
Doctor, I'm going to
help them.
And just how?
Are you planning
to fight the police?
RENO:
Hey, don't sweat it, Astro.
They'll never catch
my family. Or me.
Reno! Your family has gone.
Huh?
They have already
left town.
The ringmaster asked me
to be your guardian.
He wants you to come back
to the city with me
to study robotics.
I don't believe you.
My family would never go
and leave me.
The ringmaster gave you
a letter to deliver.
It's addressed
to you.
OFFICER:
They must still be close.
Keep searching.
PANNA COTTA:
Dear Reno, by the time you
read this, we'll be long gone.
We're sorry it had to
end this way.
But you must understand,
we have our own lives to live.
And dragging a human around
has frankly gotten to be
a burden for all of us.
You'll be better off
with Dr. O'Shay.
Please, don't try to find us.
[GRUNTS]
It's because
they care.
Huh?
It's because they care for him
that they're doing this.
[SIGHS]
End of the line, folks.
Good show.
At least Reno's safe.
Right. We had to pretend
we didn't want him,
or you know he'd have
tried to follow us.
Yeah. I'll bet Reno
will be a great
robotics engineer.
Well, that's what
we all wanted for him.
[YELLS]
JELLY BEANS: Boss.
Here they come.
ASTRO:
Mr. Panna Cotta.
Astro.
We've got to hurry.
Here, grab hold.
Does Dr. O'Shay
know about this?
He will in a minute.
[GASPS]
I am so
not liking this.
This way.
[BLOWS WHISTLE]
Wait.
There they are.
Over here.
Okay. Hang on.
MADELEINE:
Woo-hoo!
[YELLING]
CAPTAIN:
After him.
Whoa! Ugh!
Fire, fire, fire!
[YELLING]
ASTRO:
No!
[YELLING]
MAN:
What is it?
Why all the police?
MAN 2:
They've got those
robot kidnappers cornered.
Ha! Those tin troublemakers
will soon be history.
Are you okay, Astro?
Yeah, sure.
Unless you count great pain.
Fine.
Astro, we've decided to end this
in our own way.
Huh?
Hey, look.
They're coming out.
CAPTAIN:
Hold your fire.
What are they up to?
Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls.
Your attention, please.
[GASPS]
What are you waiting for?
Shoot them!
But why, Mr. Gustav?
They're not trying to escape.
[GROWLS]
PANNA COTTA:
We proudly present
the Robot Circus
in its farewell
performance.
[GASPS]
Astro.
Your spotlight, sir.
In the
center ring...
the fairest flower
of the high wire...
Mademoiselle
Madeleine.
Ta-daa!
MADELEINE:
It was 11 years ago, Reno,
the day we first met you.
The owner
of our circus retired,
and we were all tossed
into the scrap heap.
BON-BON:
So, what are we
gonna do?
No one wants to see us
perform anymore.
I wish they'd just melt us down
and get it over with.
[BABY SQUEALS]
Huh?
[CRYING]
It's a baby.
Hey. Don't cry.
Watch this.
Myaah!
Ahh!
Look.
He likes it.
Phew! He's gonna need
fresh diapers.
And we'll have to
buy him more food.
Buy?
With what?
MADELEINE:
And so we raised money
the only way we knew how.
To us, Reno, you were hope.
A reason to go on.
COOKIE:
Thank you. Very kind.
Every bit helps.
MADELEINE:
A reason to revive
the Robot Circus.
Cookie.
[CROWD APPLAUDING
AND CHEERING]
Ooh, all right. Yeah.
Wonderful.
RENO:
Bon-Bon.
[GRUNTS]
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Jelly Beans.
Ha-ha!
Marshmallow.
MARSHMALLOW:
We've had good times,
right, Reno?
Remember the fun summers?
[GRUNTING]
[LAUGHS]
MARSHMALLOW:
And the cold winters?
It'll warm you up.
RENO:
You've been my parents...
my teachers...
my best friends.
The only family
I've ever known.
Ta-daa!
[CROWD CHEERING, CLAPPING]
All right!
Ringmaster.
Stay back.
Huh?
Reno, you have
a gift.
Use it.
You're no longer
Reno the robot.
It's time to start
being human.
B-but I can't just leave you.
You must.
Go, and become a human
we can be proud of.
[CRYING]
[GROWLS]
Yeah, yeah.
Break out the violins.
Arrest them now!
CRAVEN:
No!
Everyone...these robots
never kidnapped anybody.
Gustav just made it up.
[GROWLS]
Craven!
Careful.
I've had enough
of your bullying!
I'm the mayor,
and I hereby clear
these robots of any crime.
And I invite them to be the
official circus of Bella Notte.
ALL:
Huh?
[CHEERING]
[GROWLING]
ASTRO:
Reno.
Dr. O'Shay,
I'm ready to go
to the city now.
Let's go.
Mm-hm.
ASTRO:
You sure you won't
get homesick
for the
robot circus, Reno?
Oh, maybe.
But no matter
how far apart we are,
we're still a family.
And when I'm
a robotics engineer,
I just come back
and help 'em.
Cool.
Well, the mayor really
spared no expense
for our grand reopening.
I wonder if Reno can see
the fireworks
from where he is.
I can barely see 'em.
Whose idea was it
to shoot 'em off in the daytime?
Come on, guys.
It's showtime.
All right!
Let's get going.
Yahoo!
Looks like
the show's starting.
Yeah. And so is...
my new life.
[♪]