[♪]
Both of you, stop!
You don't know each other
like I do!
No! Zoran!
Astro.
Hang on.
Astro, I wouldn't turn my back
if I were you.
We're gonna get you back
to Dr. O'Shay. Huh?
[♪]
What are you waiting for?
Finish him!
Why are you helping me?
We're robots. And robots need to
be friends and help each other.
PLUTO:
Now we're even.
Next time,
I will flatten you.
[PLUTO BLASTS OFF]
[♪]
Incredible.
So close to victory.
[SIRENS BLARING IN DISTANCE]
There. Good as new.
Go talk to her.
Bad news.
Couldn't fix you.
[CHUCKLES]
I was trying to stop you and
Pluto from hurting each other.
Huh?
W-well, I don't like
to fight either.
But Pluto has
to be stopped.
Actually, he's--
He's really kind of nice.
Huh?
[♪]
TAWASHI:
I've asked Epsilon
to help us find Pluto.
Her environmental satellites
are so sensitive,
they can detect his movements
from the heat he gives off.
Once I isolate his data,
I should be able to figure out
where he's been going
between battles.
I've entered all
the information.
Now the system needs a few
minutes to think it through.
O'SHAY:
Epsilon.
We heard you refused Pluto's
challenge. Why help us?
Pluto wants to destroy me.
I don't care
about my own survival.
I have to think about
those I protect.
Let me
show you.
My cats would
love this.
EPSILON:
The system's playing back
Pluto's movements
over the last few days
to find his base of operations.
There.
That's where
he keeps going.
City sector K-3.
That's right by
the Ministry of Science.
[♪]
[POUNDING]
So many visitors.
And I didn't even make tea.
Tenma. So it's you
that's behind Pluto.
[GASPS]
Always a pleasure.
You're creepy.
And evil.
Sending Pluto to harm
other robots.
[CHUCKLES]
TENMA:
He didn't do that. I did.
And Astro and Pluto
still have unfinished business.
Huh?
Tenma isn't the masked man?
Impossible.
Who is it then?
[RUMBLING]
Oh, oh. Something's coming up
from beneath us.
Fire!
[♪]
[YELLING]
Doctor!
[GRUNTING]
[YELLS]
O'Shay!
[RUMBLING]
SHADOW:
Astro...
if you want O'Shay back,
you know what to do.
Never!
TENMA:
Both sides have a prisoner.
A fair trade, I'd say.
Okay, spill it,
Tenma.
Who was that man
in the mask, huh?
A shadow.
Mine, to be exact.
Your shadow?
It's Pluto.
I'll go after him.
Right, Epsilon.
SHADOW:
Right this way, Astro.
[♪]
[GROANING]
Astro!
Doctor!
Huh?
[YELLS]
[YELLING]
[GRUNTING]
[♪]
Ahh!
Huh? Huh?
Dr. O'Shay!
PLUTO:
Epsilon.
You will fight me.
[SPLASH]
Underwater, eh?
Works for me.
EPSILON:
Analyzing water conditions.
The current is strongest
just around this cove,
forming riptide.
What is this...a game of tag?
Exactly.
[WATER RUSHING]
EPSILON:
And you're it.
When I'm in the water, I can
control its every movement.
PLUTO:
You must have a weakness.
Keep dreaming.
[DOLPHINS SQUEAKING]
Stay away!
I see.
Now I know how to
destroy you.
I have discovered your weakness.
You're bluffing.
And I'm done with playing.
[GASPS]
If you fire
your photons
anywhere near these volcanoes,
they'll erupt.
And that would destroy
millions of creatures.
Even altering the tides
could set them off.
Are you willing to risk that?
Well? Make your move.
How could you be so cruel?
To even toy
with such destruction.
Because you showed me the way.
[SCREAMS]
You were afraid
that pod of dolphins
was going to
get hurt by us.
Your desire to protect others
is what makes you weak.
[MOANS]
Don't you... have anything
you want to protect?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
You can't hold me! Oh!
[GRUNTS]
Oh!
Oh, good. I guess
this means you're awake.
Very funny. Now, who are you?
I am a scientist, like you.
I created Pluto.
You're the one who created
Pluto? I thought Tenma did.
He did, in a sense.
In another sense, he didn't.
[GROANS]
All these riddles. Just take off
your mask and show yourself!
Since you asked so nicely.
I don't believe it.
A robot.
Are you telling
me that a robot
is building other robots?
My name is Shadow.
I was built by
Dr. Tenma.
For tens of thousands of years,
human beings have hardly
evolved at all.
But robots...
Their ability
to evolve is miraculous.
The reason
I created Atlas
was to make
Astro have to evolve.
Atlas was so much stronger.
It was the only way
Astro could survive.
The plan worked
even better
than Dr. Tenma imagined.
So he kept building
stronger robots,
to keep making
Astro evolve.
And when Tenma
reached the limits
of his own capabilities,
he decided--
To build a robot
who builds robots.
Exactly.
Dr. Tenma realized that
if robots could learn
and adapt faster
than humans,
then a robot scientist
would make
even greater advances.
Huh?
And that's how Shadow built
Pluto, the ultimate robot.
Perfect to put Astro's
abilities to the test.
If you beat him, you will be
the king of all robots.
[♪]
Pluto!
Zoran. Are you
all fixed up?
Yep. Watch.
[CHUCKLES, GRUNTS]
[LAUGHS]
Back to normal.
Oh. Why do you
look so sad, Pluto?
I-I'm not sad.
You're imagining it.
Ah...for me?
I thought you'd like it.
[SIGHS]
PLUTO:
What's wrong?
ZORAN:
What's wrong
is that I like you.
And I wish you and Astro
didn't have to fight.
You should be
friends.
And I know
you think so too.
You're just trying
to hide it...right?
We can't be
friends.
Why not?
I was built for one reason:
to destroy Astro.
But he's my brother!
Pluto. Don't go!
Astro...this time
I'll demolish you!
SHADOW:
Astro...Pluto is waiting
at the Brocken Volcano.
We will exchange prisoners,
and then we will see
which of you
is the strongest robot
in the world.
Huh. Finally. They've been
hyping this bout forever.
Astro is stronger
than Pluto, right, Dad?
I guess we're about to find out.
I sure hope you're right.
Me too.
[♪]
ANNOUNCER:
Our cameras are
bringing it to you live,
as the robot battle of
the century is about to begin!
Tenma.
They should lock you up for good
and throw away the key!
Hey, Dr. O'Shay!
Dr. O'Shay!
Astro...if you want
to get Dr. O'Shay back,
you will have to
destroy Pluto.
Doctor!
Astro...fight me!
Forget it!
Fight yourself for all I care.
[GROWLS]
[GRUNTING]
You know, you really need
to control that anger.
You're right.
I know just what would
make me feel better.
TENMA:
Finally,
it comes to this.
Pluto defeated all the world's
strongest robots
and gained each
of their powers.
Now he brings them all
to bear on Astro,
who will evolve...
or be destroyed.
[MOANS]
Well, look at the mighty Astro.
This is going to be too easy.
[GRUNTING]
[♪]
[CROWD CHATTERING]
Astro, get up! Astro!
Go, Astro!
Go!
[YELLING]
[GRUNTING]
PLUTO:
Why are you bothering to get up?
You know you don't
stand a chance.
Can't quit.
ALL:
Astro! Astro! Astro!
[CHANTING CONTINUES]
My friends...
My friends are counting on me!
[♪]
Astro's gotten even stronger.
You see? Astro is evolving.
[GRUNTING]
How are you still going?
[MOANS]
All those people.
They're cheering me on!
It's for them!
[CROWD CHEERING]
I hear them.
Kids calling your name.
Why does that give you power?
Don't you have anything
you want to protect?
We're robots, and we all need
to be friends with each other.
Astro! Astro! Astro!
Friends. Your friends
are who you want to protect.
Both of you, stop right now!
Astro! Pluto!
ZORAN:
Why do you two
have to fight?
What are you doing? This is not
the time for chitchat!
You are enemies!
SHADOW:
It is no use.
Pluto's contact with Astro
has made him develop
a new trait: emotions.
TENMA:
Shadow...you saw
this coming, didn't you?
Yes. But don't worry.
There's still one more robot
for Astro to face.
One more? Huh?
[♪]
Pluto.
O'SHAY:
It's another one
just like Pluto!
SHADOW:
I call it Acheron.
It has all the same abilities
Pluto learned in his battles,
but with no emotions whatsoever.
Astro doesn't stand a chance
against it.
Shadow, why did you build
a second robot?
You ordered me to build a robot
that could defeat Astro.
I realized Pluto's heart
would be his weakness.
So I built a second Pluto,
with no heart at all.
[GRUNTS]
[♪]
[GROANING]
Astro!
Pluto!
Oh, no!
Pluto.
No! Don't do it, Pluto!
I finally found...
something...
I want to protect.
[♪]
Pluto!
PLUTO:
Astro, tell Zoran
that I said
thank you.
[GROANS]
Pluto!
[♪]
[CROWD GASPING]
[WHIMPERS]
What happened to Pluto?
He's okay, right?
He'll get up, right?
So, Shadow...
did you see this coming?
No.
But I see where
my mistake was.
Kokoro isn't
a weakness at all.
It makes
robots stronger.
You'll be back, and with even
stronger robots to test Astro.
That is crazy!
How much longer
does this have to go on?
You must stop him!
TENMA:
Why would I do that?
Shadow is going to keep
forcing Astro to evolve
until Astro is truly
king of all robots.
[♪]
ASTRO:
Goodbye, Pluto.
[♪]