[♪]
Wow!
How deep are we going again,
Dr. O'Shay?
DR. O'SHAY:
Three thousand meters
beneath the earth, Astro.
Geo Raider is an
amazing machine!
Chief! This is unbelievable!
The decision has been made,
Commander Damon!
But--
I'm afraid you have
no choice in the matter.
Since the Geo Raider's
mainframe
is experiencing
technical problems,
it's standard procedure
to switch over
to a backup system.
The problem is that
the backup is a robot!
You're not actually nervous
about working with a walking,
talking computer, are you?
No, sir, I am not.
But the last thing I need
is a robot with feelings
telling me
how to do my job!
DAMON: My crew
depends on me.
And in a tight situation,
there cannot be any confusion
as to who's in command!
O'SHAY: Is there
a problem here, chief?
Oh, forgive me, Dr. O'Shay.
This is Damon,
the team commander.
We were just discussing
the expedition.
Don't worry, commander.
I'm quite sure Astro will
prove very useful to you
and your crew too.
It looks like
I'm stuck with you.
But I want to make it clear
that I'm in charge around here.
Understand, robot?
Yes, sir!
DAMON:
This is Astro.
He's been brought in as a backup
to the Geo Raider's mainframe.
And he has promised that
he will stay out of our way.
Hey, everybody,
what's up?
It's time to meet the team.
Dr. Cho Tan-Meng, aerobiologist.
Hello.
Aerobiologist?
But the Geo Raider goes
underground, not into space.
Why, yes, but the environment
we'll be exploring
is like an alien world.
Man has never had the chance
to study the Earth's core.
This is a momentous
and historic day.
Yes, indeed. This voyage
is the first of its kind.
I can only imagine what types
of new and exciting discoveries
you'll be making.
Hmph! We'll see about that!
Uh-huh!
This is Boris Alucard,
the chief inspector
of the Subterranean
Development Project.
Great to
meet you, sir!
Hmph! Enough of this!
It's time!
Our underground
chariot awaits!
OPERATOR:
Geo Raider, prepare for launch!
They'll be in good hands
with Astro.
PILOT:
Initiate propulsion engines.
COMPUTER: Hydraulics online.
PILOT: Check.
[WHIRRING]
Now launching!
PILOT:
Three, two, one.
OPERATOR:
Depth: 200 meters...
250 meters...
ASTRO: My sensors are
picking up a miscalculation.
Computing...
Density level is--
[GASPS]
Commander, the area up ahead
is extremely dense.
We should slow down.
Maintain speed.
Huh?
COPILOT: Now entering bedrock.
PILOT: All systems green.
We're still in the outer layer.
If we continue at this speed,
the Geo Raider might get stuck
in the bedrock.
We have to slow down
or change course.
DAMON: The Geo Raider
is not a toy. It won't break.
And if we follow
your suggestions
and keep making detours
to avoid every rough spot,
we'll never reach our goal.
But, commander--
I need an order now!
Maintain course.
Full speed ahead.
Yes, sir.
Commander--
Your opinion is noted.
But the final decision
is mine.
Is that understood?
ASTRO: Yes, sir.
All systems green,
commander.
COMPUTER:
Breaking through bedrock.
Don't stop!
Too dangerous, sir.
If we get trapped down here,
the Geo Raider
will run out of air.
You know, for a robot,
you worry too much.
But, sir--
Calm down.
If anything happens to us
down here,
we have enough oxygen
on board to last a week.
All right,
if you're so smart,
what should we do
if we hit solid bedrock
just before we reach
the target point?
We'll just...
change the angle of entry.
That's one option--
ALUCARD: Hmph!
There's nothing I hate more
than a talking calculator
that thinks it has
all the answers.
Is it just me, or is it
getting hot in here?
I agree.
ASTRO: Commander,
according to my calculations,
the temperature is about
25 degrees higher than normal
for this depth.
I'll scan the area
and find out what's causing it.
We're probably closer
to the Earth's core
than we thought.
My sensors are telling me...
it's red-hot molten lava!
There has been an increase
in volcanic activity recently.
You're probably right,
commander.
Maybe we should stop
and evaluate our position.
Ridiculous!
We've come this far.
I refuse to let a little volcano
slow us down!
TAN-MENG:
Excuse me, sir,
but maybe Astro's right.
There's no way the Geo Raider
can withstand these conditions.
Rock density drops off
rapidly just ahead.
It looks like a cave.
That's strange.
We're deep underground,
but there's so much light.
Check it out! This is
what's producing the light.
A species of
phosphorescent moss?
I have to get a sample!
ASTRO:
I'll get it!
Hold it!
Take this communicator.
And report back.
Whoa!
Oh, this isn't ordinary moss.
Huh?
Commander! It's a chasm!
And it looks pretty deep too!
That's the path
we need to follow.
Return to the Geo Raider
at once, Astro!
The ground is unstable.
I'll continue to observe
from out here.
As you wish.
Whoa!
The ground's collapsing!
[CREW SCREAMING]
Hang on, everybody!
O'SHAY:
What's going on?
We lost the Geo Raider!
It's as if it just vanished.
Vanished?
[CREW GRUNTS]
Huh? What's that?
Yes! Yes! X marks the spot!
It's magnificent.
ALUCARD:
Well done, commander.
What do you think
you're up to, Mr. Alucard?
What are you
trying to do?
Don't be foolish--
Silence now! I'm assuming
full command of this vessel.
[GASPS]
Astro!
Commander?
Astro, this is a mutiny!
[CHUCKLING]
After all these years,
I've finally found it!
Do you know
what this is?
A Centra Crystal.
Exactly.
You're pretty smart for a robot,
I'll give you that much.
You see, many scientists
believe that these crystals
are going to generate
a new source of energy.
Every power company in the world
will want to get
their hands on this,
and now I've got what they want!
So that's what you were
after all along!
There is no Subterranean
Development Agency.
All I want is this.
Grrr!
[YELLS]
ALUCARD:
See?
We've made a far more
useful discovery
than some worthless
glowing moss.
I'd say that's
no ordinary crystal
you're holding there,
Mr. Alucard.
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
TAN-MENG: It's some type
of crystalline life form.
It's not just a mineral?
No.
The amoeba assumes a hard,
gem-like form when it's asleep.
[ALL GASP]
DAMON: What's happening?
TAN-MENG: I don't know.
[ALL WHIMPERING FEARFULLY]
[SCREAMS]
Look out!
ALUCARD:
Good job, robot.
So Centra Crystals are just some
sort of sleeping amoeba, huh?
No matter, they're still needed
for that next-generation
photonic energy source.
Let's get
out of here!
We need to take back as many
of these as we possibly can.
What?
[GASPING]
ALUCARD: Nobody said anything
about giant grasshoppers!
TAN-MENG:
Don't move!
[SCREAMS]
Get it off!
TAN-MENG: You can't
hold them off forever, Astro!
Get back to the ship!
You heard Astro. Move out!
DAMON:
It's not safe here!
I don't want to lose
a single crew member!
Maybe you betrayed me,
but I'm not going to
let you stay out here
and get eaten
by some giant bugs!
Come back!
We're not finished here!
You only take orders from me!
[GRUNTS]
TAN-MENG:
Look!
A whole ecosystem
has formed down here.
A world unknown
to mankind until now.
No!
[SCREAMING]
Astro!
[GASPS]
Oh!
[SCREAMING]
Get away!
I will exterminate you all!
Astro!
Well done.
TAN-MENG:
How strange.
It looks like the insects
are retreating.
The outside temperature
is rising unusually fast.
Mr. Alucard's laser may have
disturbed the volcano.
Well,
don't look at me!
Oh, it's erupting!
We have to get out of here.
Activate engine!
That lava is flowing fast.
Full speed ahead!
PILOT:
Yes, sir!
[SCREAMING AND GRUNTING]
It's no use!
We're not going to make it!
How can we--?
DAMON: We should be
incinerated by now!
Commander, take a look at this!
The Geo Raider's
riding on a large rock
that's being pushed up
by the lava.
But if the volcano erupts,
the town at the foot of the
mountain will be destroyed!
We have to contact them!
The damage
to the Geo Raider
has made communication
with the surface impossible.
Try again!
ASTRO: Commander, I'll go
and stop the lava from erupting
while you dig another tunnel
through the side
of the mountain.
It's the only way that we'll
be able to save the town.
I don't think so.
Even you won't be able
to hold back that lava, Astro.
But I--
If you make one mistake,
we're all done for!
I can do it, commander!
Commander, please!
All right, then.
Leave the other tunnel to us.
I'm counting on you.
[GRUNTING]
Transfer maximum energy
to the laser cannon at once!
Fire the laser! Now!
Don't stop!
Astro's depending on us!
You really believe
in that ridiculous robot?
I tell you, it's madness to
trust him with our very lives!
Astro said he could do it,
and I believe he can.
I just know he can.
The lava's
electromagnetic field,
it's affecting
my internal systems!
Gotta hang on...
a little longer.
Astro!
It worked!
He saved us!
You did it, Astro!
Astro?
Astro, respond!
Astro! Astro!
He was crazy
to match his strength
against the Earth itself.
Relax, Astro.
We're almost home.
Unbelievable!
I could have been rich if
it hadn't been for that robot.
Enough, Alucard.
I'm sure the judge will
want to hear all about it.
Hmph!
That underground ecosystem
is a valuable discovery.
I'm looking forward to taking
the Geo Raider back down.
ASTRO:
I am too.
And next time, let's take
some heavy-duty bug spray.
[CHUCKLING]
You're awake now, huh?
We have to go back down
as soon as possible.
There's so much
to learn!
Your opinion is noted.
But the final decision
is mine, understood?
Yes, sir.
And first, you should
get some rest.
Huh?
Because, Astro, I need you to be
ready for our next expedition.
Is that clear?
Yes, sir!
It's the Geo Raider!
They're back!
[ALL CHEERING]
O'SHAY:
Welcome home, Astro.
Welcome home.
[♪]