[♪]
MAN:
Astro. So small,
yet so powerful.
A creation of pure genius.
If only I could capture him
and deconstruct him,
I could discover
the secret of his power.
But gaining control
of such an energy force
would require a mind
so cunning, so demented,
so ruthless.
Who besides myself possesses
such qualities?
No one!
You're the worst
big brother ever.
You make me come
to the park with you,
and then you
won't play with me!
Wait a minute.
This was your idea!
I just didn't want you
to be lonely!
Hm!
Okay.
What do you
wanna play, Zoran?
Nothing, with you.
I just wanna pick flowers
by myself.
Hello?
Zoran? I told you, you can't
pick flowers in the park.
So all of a sudden
you're a park ranger now?
Argh!
Talking to her is like talking
to an unplugged computer. Huh?
With super strength!
Zoran,
put that down!
Ohh!
[SHRIEKS]
Not on me, show-off!
Whoa!
Both of you, stop!
You're going to make me
fry my circuits.
Zoran, you listen
to your big brother.
He's supposed to be setting
a good example...starting now.
What?
Zoran's the one
playing catch
with the jungle gym, not me.
Aww, who needs you?
I'm going home.
NORA:
Astro.
Ohh! Why do I have to
watch that brat?
ZORAN:
Okay. Add baking powder
and more baking powder.
I know Dr. O'Shay likes
pound cake, so I bet
he'll really love
a 2000-pound cake.
Wowee!
This cake's gonna be big enough
to feed everybody
in Metro City.
[LAUGHS]
Happy birthday, everybody.
[PANTING]
Whoa! Oh! Whoa!
Zoran...
did you do all this?
Hm. Yeah.
What?
Why is it that every time
you bake a cake
you make a mega-mess?
Aw...don't bake a cake,
don't pick flowers,
don't pick up
the playground equipment.
Oh, it's like I'm
in little-sister jail.
Hm?
Did anybody
ever tell you
you look just like
that famous Astro?
My brother's
not that famous.
You're his little sister,
aren't you?
But he's not the boss of me.
I do whatever I want.
Well, good for you.
And I bet you have
superpowers of your own
that are even
more impressive than Astro's.
Well, I am way cooler
than he is, that's for sure.
Of course. I could tell that
the minute I saw you.
Really? You think I'm cool?
Mm, Astro said
I shouldn't talk to strangers.
But I don't wanna talk about
him. Let's talk about me.
Well, I'm really strong, and I'm
quite a chef. Do you like cake?
'Cause I've got
tons of it at home.
Uh, what else about me?
Um...
Heh-heh-heh.
Where are you going,
Mr. What's-Your-Name?
Don't you wanna
hear more about me?
Whoa. I don't feel very good.
I hate it when Astro's right.
Zoran!
Zoran, where are you?
Huh?
MAN:
What's going on?
Everything okay?
Oh, no.
That's her!
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
What do you think?
MAN:
You're a fool!
Seeing Zoran's operating
system means nothing.
She's not
as powerful as Astro.
The only thing she has
in common
with her brother
is her artificial brain.
Wait a second.
The micro-robot's
still inside her.
Heh-heh-heh.
Which is just
the Astro bait I need.
ASTRO:
It's all my fault, Dr. O'Shay.
I should've kept
a closer eye on Zoran.
[TAPPING COMPUTER KEYS]
It's like she's asleep.
What's wrong with her?
Huh?
What is this?
A bug.
There's an ultra-microscopic
robo-bug inside Zoran's body.
MAN:
Doctor.
Major systems failure.
The robo-bug's shutting down
her internal power grid.
How could this thing
have gotten into her?
Tracing its movements.
The point of entry is her ear.
Who would do
such a thing?
and how do I stop it
before it destroys Zoran?
Doctor, there must be
something I can do.
I'm sorry, Astro.
Even with your superpowers,
you can't battle something
inside her body.
O'SHAY:
Ladies, gentlemen,
I'd like to thank you all
for attending
this emergency meeting.
You're the finest minds
in the scientific world.
That's why I desperately
need your help.
Can any of you
think of a way to remove
the microscopic robot
from Zoran's body?
Ahem.
Your only option is to
completely disassemble her.
No!
WOMAN:
Or an intense magnetic field
could extract
the foreign object.
Although damage to the robotic
patient will be unavoidable,
I'm sorry to say.
No!
We can't
hurt Zoran.
Astro's right.
There has to be a better way.
Huh?
Uh, who are you?
Dr. Minimini
of Inner World Technologies,
the leader
in micro-component repair.
Your infected robot
is the perfect candidate
for the virtual-exploration
system I've just invented.
Virtual-exploration system?
Allow me to demonstrate.
Ooh.
This system scans
an original body
to produce a microscopic
virtual copy,
which the original
can freely control.
This virtual copy can then
actually enter Zoran's body.
Amazing technology.
Yes.
But...it's still
experimental,
so it would be wrong
to send a human in.
Of course, it would work
with another robot.
Unfortunately, a robot with
the instinctive,
decision-making skills
of a human.
doesn't exist.
Professor...
I'll do it.
[CHUCKLES MANIACALLY]
[HELICOPTER WHIRS]
Welcome to Inner World
Technologies, Dr. O'Shay.
Let me show you the miracle
of virtual exploration.
Or, as I call it,
teeny-tiny technology.
[CHUCKLES]
The time has come...
Astro.
Ready to take a very small
step for robot-kind?
Yes, sir.
MINIMINI:
Nothing to worry about.
We're just scanning your body.
Now then...
[WHIRRING]
What do you think of my
miniaturization process so far,
Dr. O'Shay?
Incredible.
Just wait.
Now it's time to make
micro-Astro operational.
Enter the simulator,
Astro.
Yes, doctor.
Oh! Uh! Oh! Oh!
Huh?
What's going on?
Doctor?
MINIMINI:
Try to move, Astro.
Move? You mean, like this?
Amazing. It's like Astro himself
has been shrunk.
I get it. Whatever I do
in the simulator tank
is copied by the miniature me.
Check it out, Dr. O'Shay.
This is totally cool.
Ha, ha, ha! Whoa!
He'll master it
in no time.
My congratulations on your
system, Dr. Minimini.
Thank you.
Astro, your brainwaves
have been transferred
into this mini-Astro.
The mini-Astro is you.
I get it, Dr. Minimini.
Excellent. Then we've
got work to do.
Dr. O'Shay, you may begin
the procedure.
Astro, look at
the monitor.
The point of entry
is through Zoran's ear.
The robo-bug infecting
your sister's power grid
is currently in the
vicinity of her chest.
Uh, do you see it?
Yes, Dr. O'Shay.
All right. It's
up to you, Astro.
Go!
Zoran, I'm coming
to save you.
Dr. O'Shay...
I've definitely never been
in here before.
But why does it
feel so familiar?
O'SHAY [ON SPEAKER]:
Probably because I modeled
Zoran on your design.
But I could never replicate
the enormous strength
that your internal power chips
are capable of producing.
Careful, Astro.
You're getting very close
to the robo-bug now.
Got it.
Huh?
So that's the little monster
that's bugging Zoran.
Well, not for long.
O'SHAY:
Astro...wait!
Ugh! Whoa, whoa!
O'SHAY:
You're in Zoran's heart.
There's a lot of high-density
energy in there.
ASTRO:
I can't fight it in here.
It's too dangerous for Zoran.
O'SHAY:
That's strange.
The robo-bug's
just hanging around...
almost like it's
waiting for Astro.
[CACKLES MANIACALLY]
Argh!
You're out of here! Ugh!
[GRUNTING]
You can run,
but you can't hide!
O'SHAY:
Astro, be careful.
Somehow the robo-bug's
replenishing its energy
from Zoran's heart.
It may become too powerful
for even you.
I'm on it!
Hmm.
Where am I now?
Whoa. Huh?
Argh!
What's wrong, Astro?
There's a bunch
of Zorans in here.
And a bunch of me's too.
Astro, you are now inside
Zoran's electronic brain.
What you see are the stored
images of Zoran's memories.
Memories.
O'SHAY:
Both of your brains
are designed
to remember images
the same way.
It's a very delicate process.
So be extremely
careful in there.
Huh?
I never wanted to have
a sister like you.
Hey.
Well, I don't want a big brother
like you, Astro.
What's happening?
It's erasing Zoran's memories.
O'SHAY:
Astro, do something
before it destroys
Zoran's memory bank.
Stop!
Argh!
[GROANS]
Doctor, I'm losing power!
It's as if Astro's brain
is experiencing
what's happening to Zoran's.
Of course, it's because
I modeled her
artificial intelligence
system on Astro's.
This has gone beyond memories.
The robo-bug's attacking
Zoran's entire
electronic brain.
If we don't stop it,
Astro's brain
will suffer the same fate
and be paralyzed too.
Perfect.
What do you think you're doing,
Dr. Minimini?
[CHUCKLES MANIACALLY]
Let me lay it out for you.
I've got the original Astro
here in the simulator.
If his electronic brain
is paralyzed,
he'll fall under
my control forever.
What? Now I get it.
You've planned this,
Dr. Minimini.
But why would you do
such a terrible thing?
For Astro's power source,
of course.
Such enormous energy
from such a tiny mass.
I could make a fortune.
No!
Yes. And now
the power is mine.
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
TAWASHI:
You and Dr. Minimini
run a pretty nasty business.
Don't you?
[SHIVERS]
Tell me, what are a couple of
wanted weapons dealers
like you doing here
in this city?
So, where's your boss, huh?
Uh, I'm not sure.
MAN:
Inspector,
we're getting an emergency call
from the Ministry of Science.
What?
Ahh! Oh!
Don't shoot!
Astro's in
that thing.
Dr. Minimini, what do you
plan to do with him?
For starters, eliminate his
troublesome human emotions.
Then I can harness
his super power.
Reconfigured, I can turn him
into a superb weapon...
which will fetch a huge price
on the black market.
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
Astro. Astro, can you hear me?
Zoran...
Now, if you'll
excuse me,
I'm taking Astro
for a little walk.
Bye. Ah!
Astro.
Astro, can you hear me?
[ECHOING]
Astro!
Zoran.
Look...
I know sometimes I say snotty
things to you, big brother,
but... But...
But the truth is,
I don't really mean 'em.
In fact, I really wish
we could get along.
Huh?
Um...
because, well--
Well, because you're the
only big brother I've got.
Zoran...
Zoran!
I'm here to help you.
I'm going to save you!
O'SHAY:
Astro, get out of here fast!
Your real body's being stolen!
Huh? What?
[LAUGHS MANIACALLY]
BOTH:
Huh?
Goon, what's taking you so long?
Astro and I need a lift.
Ah, there you are. What?
[SIRENS WAIL]
Dr. Minimini, how'd you like
a lift to prison?!
[WHIMPERING]
Huh? Whoa.
No, stop! You're
ruining everything!
Ahh!
O'SHAY:
Astro...
you're okay!
Oh...
[SIGHS]
Dr. Minimini,
you are under arrest.
[SIGHS]
Big brother...
[MOANING]
Zoran,
I'm right here.
I...
You're awake.
You're okay.
Hope you don't mind,
I sort of peeked
at your dreams.
My dreams?
Yeah.
Well, I, um,
really want to
get along
with you too, Zoran,
'cause, um--
I, um--
Well,
you know, I--
I know,
big brother,
you're pretty
cool too!
[LAUGHS]
Now let's go
make another cake!
ASTRO:
Noo!
[♪]