[♪]
MAN [ON LOUDSPEAKER]:
Attention. Stop where you are.
This is the police.
OFFICER:
Stop!
We got him!
Heh-heh-heh.
SKUNK:
Sorry to let you boys down.
Whup!
[GRUNTS]
OFFICER:
He's up there!
You cops can't catch me
that easily.
Heh-heh-heh.
There he is.
Hey, boss!
Right on time.
[SIRENS WAILING]
Oh!
The cops!
MAN [ON LOUDSPEAKER]:
Don't move. There's no escape.
You are under arrest!
[CROWD CHATTERING]
I'll be out in no time!
You'll never keep me locked up!
Never!
O'SHAY:
So, Skunk's
been captured again.
And I hope this time
it's for good.
ASTRO:
Later, Nora. Bye, doctor!
NORA:
Astro, your lunch.
Uh, wait a minute,
it's Sunday.
Where are you going
so early in the morning?
Thanks, Nora.
I'll be at the new marine
park with my friends.
Miss Miyoki
is going with them.
I see.
Gotta fly!
Be careful.
NORA:
Have fun!
Ah, a new marine park.
ASTRO:
Ho-ho! Whoa!
Whoa!
Ha-ha-ha.
[CHEERING]
ALEJO:
What do you want
to do next?
How about
the Pirate's Plank?
Oh, we just
did that.
ABERCROMBIE:
But I wanna
go on it again!
[GIRL CRYING]
Huh?
My balloon!
Gotcha!
KENNEDY:
That's one way
to catch a fish.
Huh?
That big thing
in the water.
Wonder what it is.
Here you go.
Thank you.
Yeah!
Good save,
Astro!
Hey, guys,
I'll be right back, okay?
What?
So, welcome to
Invincible Prison Island.
Permanent home...
of our new guest, Skunk.
Careful, warden.
He's escaped from
three prisons so far.
Don't take
any chances with him.
I don't care
how clever he is.
He won't be pulling
any fast ones here.
Huh?
Uh!
My tie! Take him away!
[CELL DOOR CLOSES]
Hmm.
Nice joint.
I'll bust out of here
in no time.
Heh-heh-heh.
ASTRO:
What is it?
I don't hear
anything.
Nothing at all.
Oh!
MIYOKI:
Astro! Over here!
Everyone's already gone
to the submarine ride!
Miss Miyoki, what's that
big robot in the water?
His name's
Jumbo.
He's an old friend of mine.
We've known each other
since I was a kid.
Really?
MIYOKI:
About 20 years ago,
the first robots were
introduced to Metro City.
In honor, a robot
festival was held
to mark the new era
in technology.
Jumbo was part
of the celebration.
He was the world's
largest robot,
and built to entertain
the spectators.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Jumbo was a very
popular attraction.
And boy, did he make
the kids happy.
Yay! Hooray! All right!
Yay! Hooray!
My father helped build Jumbo...
so I was chosen
to give him flowers
at the opening ceremony.
Hey, that's awesome!
[CROWD CHEERING]
Jumbo, on behalf
of everyone,
I would like to
present you
these flowers
as a symbol
of our respect
and appreciation.
We hope that
man and robots
will build
a wonderful future together.
[MIYOKI GIGGLES]
Thank you.
I hope we can
always be friends.
[GASPS]
Robotics advanced quickly,
and Jumbo became overshadowed
by newer models.
It was decided
that Jumbo
would be deactivated
and left as a monument.
I grew up nearby
and missed
looking out the window
and seeing him
playing with kids.
As I got older,
I continued to visit him,
but it always made me sad
to see Jumbo out there
all alone and shut down.
It may have been
years ago,
but I still think of us
as being good friends.
O'SHAY:
Jumbo? Oh, that Jumbo!
So you know about him too,
doctor?
Well, of course.
He was a popular attraction
at the first Robot Festival.
Unfortunately...
after he was deactivated,
people forgot all about him.
It's sad.
I feel badly for him.
Well, doctor,
I know that Jumbo
hasn't forgotten all about them.
Huh?
MIYOKI:
Jumbo, my good friend.
GUARD:
Cell block C secured.
GUARD 2:
Locking down section D.
GUARD 3:
All systems clear.
TAWASHI:
I'm gonna be a pest
about this, warden,
'cause Skunk will do anything
to escape from prison.
We can't
underestimate him.
I insist that
you let me
help with the security,
at least in the beginning.
You worry
too much, detective.
This state-of-the-art prison
is completely isolated.
100 percent secure.
Not even a mouse
could slip through.
How about a Skunk?
He's been known
to make weapons
using the latest
robot technology.
That's exactly why
we have a Guardian Pulse,
to jam all
robot frequencies.
This high-tech device transmits
across the entire island.
The Guardian Pulse acts directly
on the robots' processors,
so they can't even budge.
No matter how advanced
the robot is,
if it even takes one step
in the affected area,
it's completely paralyzed.
Even that robot Astro
would be powerless here.
Heh-heh-heh.
Give kids
a new toy,
and they forget
their old ones.
But I, the great Skunk,
am different.
I envision the future
while cherishing the past.
REPORTER [OVER RADIO]:
Strong winds and heavy rain
are likely past midnight
tonight, so be careful.
Huh?
What is that?
MAN:
I'm flattered.
I'm glad you decided to join us
for your
last night...ever.
[SCREAMS]
[WHIMPERING]
What's the matter?
What's a robot
doing here?
Grrr.
[ALARM BLARING]
MAN [OVER LOUDSPEAKER]:
Intruder alert! Intruder alert!
Intruder Alert!
[SIRENS WAILING]
O'SHAY:
What? Impossible!
Jumbo attacking
Invincible Prison Island?
Switch the monitor
to on-site feed.
Right!
O'SHAY:
Oh. Oh, no!
How can this be?
Grrr.
Target in position.
Three...
two...one.
Hey, are we okay inside
this hunk of junk?
Aah!
JAZZ:
Ah, we're fine.
I reinforced Jumbo
with new defensive armor.
Hold on, boss!
We're coming
to give you a hand!
What the--? Ahh!
GUARD:
Look out!
[SIRENS WAILING]
We gotta
stop Jumbo now!
Ahh!
[OFFICERS YELLING]
The Guardian Pulse!
It's affecting the Akita Squad!
What's the status
of the Guardian Pulse?
MAN:
Full operation.
But--But--But why?
Why can that robot
still move?
O'SHAY:
Jumbo's such an old robot,
the Guardian Pulse
is too advanced to affect him.
[IN SLEEPY VOICE]
Doctor...what's going on?
Astro! Someone's
reactivated Jumbo,
and he is heading straight for
Invincible Prison Island!
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
What? Jumbo!
[SIRENS WAILING]
Shut down that
pulse now, warden.
That's a direct order!
[GUARDS YELLING]
Warden...
what shall we do?
Yes. Yes, all right.
Turn it off.
Turn it off right now.
Right away.
Got it.
[WHIMPERING]
Aah!
Look, that's much better.
A nice big hole.
Now it's not
so stuffy in there.
[WHIMPERS]
Where am I?
Oh, good.
[RUMBLING]
I got some company.
Hiya, boys.
How could this happen?
Our prison's high tech,
state-of-the-art.
And a beat-up,
rusty old robot
broke through!
[CRYING]
Well, It just goes
to show you boys
that even out-of-date robots
have their uses.
But look, here comes one
that has no use.
Hmm?
Huh?
Astro!
Don't worry.
Sit tight,
watch and learn.
Yeah, boss.
Yeah, okay.
All right, Skunk! I'm getting
real tired of your stink!
Aah!
Oh.
SKUNK:
Well, it looks like
the Guardian Pulse
has caught
your attention, Astro.
Argh!
You know, with that
pesky little Astro trapped,
we could
easily destroy him.
Shall we
crush him, boys?
Not if I can help it.
Grrr!
Ugh.
JAZZ:
Aah! Get off the controls!
SKUNK:
Both of you...
take care of--
Ahh! Her!
Yeah, boss!
Oh!
Haa! Ohh!
BLUES:
Look out!
SKUNK:
The Guardian Pulse!
You boys buckled in?
Yeah.
ALL:
Aah!
I've got you now!
ALL:
Astro!
ASTRO:
What goes around,
comes around!
[ALL SCREAM]
Astro! Help!
Miss Miyoki!
Huh?
SKUNK:
Astro, guess what.
You're too late. Now Jumbo's
gonna destroy Metro City.
Adios, Astro!
Attention, all units!
Code six emergency.
Jumbo is rampaging
toward the city.
ASTRO:
Miss Miyoki!
MIYOKI:
Astro!
Oh!
We'll cut off Jumbo right here!
Detective, wait!
Call off
the attack!
It is not
Jumbo's fault!
Nonsense.
Look at him.
He must be stopped.
And now!
Ready...
Aim and fire!
Oh, no, stop!
Jumbo!
Oh!
Astro!
Please stop!
Jumbo!
You don't want
to do this!
Remember...
you're peaceful!
Designed to help people...
not...destroy!
Ahh!
Astro!
Cease fire now!
Aah!
Jumbo!
Must stop him.
Too...big.
He won't stop!
Astro! Out of the way!
Wait!
Come back!
Jumbo, please stop!
Miss Miyoki!
MIYOKI:
Please!
Try to remember!
Remember back when
you and I became friends!
Jumbo!
You never hurt anyone!
ASTRO:
Oh. She's trying to get Jumbo
to remember who he really is.
Prepare to fire!
Aim at his head!
Full power!
Astro!
Argh.
That's it!
Launch fireworks in the air!
Fireworks?
But where?
ASTRO:
Over Jumbo, to help him remember
the Robot Festival
and cause his circuits to reboot
back to his old self!
What's he
talking about?
We don't have
any fireworks!
Inspector...
I think I know what we can do.
MIYOKI:
Jumbo! Jumbo, please!
Look at us! Everyone here
wants to be your friend!
Those criminals
weren't your friends!
They reprogrammed you!
No!
Aah!
[ASTRO GROANING]
Astro.
Run away.
Jumbo!
On behalf of everyone here,
I wish to present you
some flowers
as a symbol of our respect
and appreciation of you.
We hope that robots and man
will build a wonderful
future together.
[FIREWORKS CRACKLING]
You created fireworks
out of our laser rays!
If this doesn't work,
I'm afraid nothing will.
[FESTIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Jumbo!
Wow.
O'SHAY:
Jumbo's optical memory
has overridden Skunk's orders.
Now instead of trying
to destroy the city,
he's back to his old,
peaceful self once more.
Thank you. It is nice
to see you again.
KID:
Hey, wait for me.
I wanna see him next!
KID 2: Awesome!
KID 3:
Hey! Hey, wait up
for me! Hey, cool.
It is just awesome.
ASTRO:
It's great how things
worked out for Jumbo.
Thanks to you
and Dr. O'Shay.
Now Jumbo can stay
at the Ministry of Science
and play with
children again.
Look at all
his new friends.
I'm so glad
Jumbo's happy,
and useful once again.
ASTRO:
Good old Jumbo.
Making people happy
is the best use
a robot could have.
[♪]