[♪]
[WOMAN SINGING ELEGANTLY]
[PEOPLE CHATTING]
Where did he go?
This is Delta, Block D5.
No sign of Klaus.
Hurry!
Before he leaves the station.
Uh!
Oh.
Hey!
A3. The subject's
heading towards A3.
TAWASHI:
We can't let him get away.
Oh! Klaus!
Goodbye.
Huh?
Hold it right there, Klaus.
Ah! Somebody
come quick!
A robot's about to shoot
a human.
Stop him!
You have it all wrong. We were
chasing a robot, not a human.
Well, I think I know a man
when I see one.
Yeah, I saw him too.
Definitely not a robot.
ASTRO:
Klaus may look like a human,
but he's not.
He's really an undercover
police robot
programmed to look and act
just like a human.
Twelve hours ago,
he was considered one of
the best undercover agents.
MAN:
The plan is foolproof.
I set up a fake account
here at Burlane Corporation
so we can sell Hyper-IC
on the black market.
And don't worry,
you'll be well compensated.
Thank you, Mr. Robin.
You're much too generous.
So when can I see
the new Hyper-IC?
Give me a sec.
ROBIN: It's amazing how
such a tiny little device
is the key to producing weapons.
Honestly, when you first joined
the company,
I had my doubts about you.
I actually thought
you were a cop.
[LAUGHING]
Here's the latest version
of the--
Hmm?
KLAUS: The man you're looking
for is Cornelius Robin,
divisional vice president
of sales.
MAN:
Sales, we should have known.
I'll transmit
all the necessary evidence now.
Roger that. We'll see you
back at the station.
There's a zipcar
waiting for you.
Okay.
Klaus, nice work
on your final assignment.
MAN: Klaus just left
Burlane Corporation.
It's impressive that he managed
to get so close to Robin.
Data's in.
Send out a team
to pick up Robin.
And don't forget
to read him his rights.
[MAN HUMMING]
Hmm? Huh?
Hey there, Klaus.
Oh?
What?
Klaus's transmitter
just went dead.
What is he doing?
Klaus!
MAN: We've got a serious
problem here.
One of our police robots
has disappeared.
This is all
your fault, Cutter!
Klaus was
your responsibility!
From now on, Detective Tawashi
will lead the investigation.
Dr. O'Shay and Astro
will continue to assist
in the search.
Don't you think we're being
a bit overdramatic, Chief?
What if I said,
by tomorrow night
we wouldn't have to worry
about Klaus ever again?
What do you mean by that?
I planted a failsafe protocol
in every undercover
humanoid robot
to prevent them
from running away.
When a robot cuts off
its digital locator,
a virus is introduced
into its system.
If it doesn't turn itself in
within 24 hours,
it'll shut down.
Huh?
Permanently.
Of course, Klaus knows
full well about the virus.
This is outrageous!
What gives you the right
to go around implanting
robots with viruses?
Especially ones like Klaus,
who have hearts and emotions?
That was
a big mistake, doctor.
What's that mean?
That's the problem,
his heart.
He grew too close
to the people around him.
He got attached
to human comforts.
So much so that he
wants to be human!
[GROANING]
Hmm.
O'SHAY:
We have to find Klaus
before the virus spreads
to his central processor.
If we're not too late,
this microchip
should counteract the virus.
Okay, got it.
Astro, I'm sure Klaus had
a good reason for running away
yesterday afternoon.
I know he does.
MAN: No one's seen
or heard from him.
He didn't even pack a bag.
And no clues in his house
indicating where he went.
If we can't figure out
where he's going,
we can still find out
where he's coming from.
Delta, I need you and Astro
to go over Klaus's steps
right before he disappeared.
Yes, sir.
Great! Partners!
[GROANS]
Astro,
just so you know,
I have no intention
on saving Klaus.
Why not?
You guys were both
in the police department.
Weren't you,
Delta?
That's exactly why
I can't forgive him!
Huh?
We may be able
to think for ourselves,
but our prime directive
is to uphold the law.
It took years for police robots
to earn the people's trust.
By running out on us,
Klaus makes us all look bad.
Well, I'm sure Klaus can
explain why he did--
Astro, there's no excuse for a
police robot to disobey orders.
Ugh! Delta!
Goodbye.
ASTRO: I'm the only one left
on Klaus's side.
I've got to save him.
This is where the zipcar
was supposed to get Klaus
after he left
Burlane Corporation.
Very nice. So, what about it?
Well, maybe something
happened to him here.
Maybe he was forced to run away.
You're reading
way too much into this.
Let's go.
I know where we can find one of
his undercover android friends.
[GROANS]
Huh?
FEMALE VOICE:
And so the young man
was cursed
by the evil sorcerer.
But this was not the end
of his journey.
It was only the beginning.
In order to bring back
his precious memories...
[MOANS]
[BEAUTIFUL OPERA MUSIC PLAYING]
Klaus was the best undercover
robot I had ever seen.
I was honored to have
trained him myself.
After their police training,
the undercover robots
spend four weeks
living with their instructors
so they can learn the everyday
details of human life.
So he spent some time here
in this mansion?
Yes.
But unlike the others,
Klaus was a different breed.
I'm gonna need
more than that.
It was uncanny. I actually began
to think he was human.
Did you just say
what I think you just said?
FEMALE VOICE:
I've been working undercover
as a human for three years.
ASTRO:
Do you like pretending?
Well, I don't know if "like"
is how I would describe it.
This might sound strange,
but I spend so much time
living with humans,
that sometimes I forget
that I'm a robot.
Was Klaus like that also?
I really
don't know.
But when no one
was around,
Klaus liked to come here
to listen to music.
To music?
Yes.
All undercover robots
are programmed
to understand everything from
music theory and art history
to famous literary works.
It is essential
to their success
that they appear human
in every way possible.
However...
Klaus was different.
Would you mind if I listened
to that piece again,
Professor Salsed?
Not at all.
But it should be stored
in your memory files.
It is, but it's not quite the
same when I play it in my head.
You can actually appreciate
the difference between the two?
Sure.
[BEAUTIFUL OPERA MUSIC PLAYING]
[SINGING ALONG]
Huh?
SALSED: Klaus's development
was not limited to just music.
He also developed
a sense of family with myself
and my granddaughter Michelle.
Is that her?
Yes.
Her parents
both work on the moon,
so she doesn't see them
very often.
Klaus may have only lived here
a short time,
but he was like a father to her.
It's a shame that after
his latest assignment
with Burlane Corporation,
he was scheduled to be upgraded.
What?
Did you say upgraded?
Cutter didn't tell you?
It was all set
for today.
So? I get awesome upgrades
all the time.
They make me faster
and stronger.
This was a complete
system upgrade.
His personality and memories
would be erased.
Now it makes
total sense.
So in order to escape
being upgraded, Klaus fled.
Actually, he agreed
to have the upgrade.
Huh?
I don't buy it!
It's true, Delta.
That's why he left
this record with me.
It was given to him
by his instructor.
It was very special to him.
I remember it
like it was yesterday.
[BEAUTIFUL OPERA MUSIC PLAYING]
You're leaving behind
your favorite album?
For you. It means a lot to me,
and I want you to have it.
Why?
The new Klaus won't
appreciate it like I do.
I don't understand
why you have to be upgraded.
You're already the best we have.
So what if you
listen to music?
made friends?
Isn't that
what they wanted?
For us to be as human
as possible?
Why are they so afraid
of you, Klaus?
They just are,
and an order's
an order.
But, Klaus...
Remember me every time
you listen to that song.
All that Klaus
ever wanted
was to be the best
humanoid undercover agent.
Yes, but he still
disobeyed orders!
And that's a fact.
Do you have any idea
what could've changed his mind?
No, I don't,
I'm sorry.
Who is this woman?
That's Leah Jade,
an opera singer
from Xenon.
Her world tour begins...
any day now.
Let me check.
Actually, it's starting today.
Can you see where
today's show is?
It's in Wayland.
Wayland, huh?
Hmm.
Oh!
Astro! Where are you going?
Listen up.
Klaus is obsessed with Jade.
I know he's at this concert.
Now find him!
Huh?
Klaus. Follow me.
Hurry.
Hey, you all right?
No.
My systems are starting
to fail. Ugh!
Hang on. We need to install
this microchip right away.
Oh!
Hold it right there.
This is between
you and me, Cutter.
Leave these two
out of it.
Arggh!
Klaus.
A robot
giving orders to a human.
Your love for music
was just the start.
He's not giving orders.
He's just trying
to protect his friends.
There's no law
against listening to music!
[LAUGHING]
Huh?
You're so naive, Astro.
It's not just the music,
it's the art,
the books, the jobs,
it's everything
that belongs to humankind.
Robots were built to make
the lives of humans easier.
Instead, you're taking away
everything that's sacred to us.
Giving you hearts and emotions
was the last straw,
and I won't take it anymore!
Even if it means
eliminating you all myself!
That's crazy.
Robots are
your friends--
Arggh!
Klaus.
CUTTER:
Delta!
Bring the fugitive to me.
That is an order!
If you don't bring him now,
I'll destroy you too.
Delta.
Game's over, Astro.
Commissioned police robots
have to follow every order.
Huh?
Well, you see,
you're no longer
in charge of this case, Cutter,
so I'm no longer required
to follow your orders.
Harggh!
Whoa!
Are you okay, Astro?
Yeah.
Let's rocket!
Hold on, Klaus.
Let me install
the antivirus.
Hurry up.
They'll be here soon.
Thank you, Astro.
Klaus.
So why did you
run away?
Well...I was fully prepared
to have the upgrade.
I was about to return
to the police station
after the Burlane
Corporation mission.
But then I heard something.
Huh?
[BEAUTIFUL OPERA MUSIC PLAYING]
Leah Jade.
When I saw
she was performing live,
I had to see her just once.
I know that may sound
strange to you.
No. Huh?
DELTA:
It's the police...
in combat suits.
Take them all down!
And don't sweat it.
They're robots.
They can't shoot us.
Arggh!
Delta, aim for the shoulder pin.
They won't be hurt.
Arggh!
ASTRO:
This way.
ANNOUNCER:
Ladies and gentlemen,
Leah Jade.
No, Klaus.
Ahh!
Delta!
[GRUNTS]
KLAUS:
That's it.
Let's go.
[CROWD APPLAUDS & CHEERS]
[SINGING BEAUTIFUL OPERA SONG]
KLAUS:
Delta.
Now do you understand
why some humans hate robots?
DELTA:
Because we're different.
Because we're stronger!
Because we can do things
they cannot.
KLAUS: We may be made
out of machinery,
but we can still think
for ourselves.
And many of us
have feelings too.
ASTRO: Maybe they're not afraid
because we're different.
Maybe they're afraid
because...we're the same.
You might be right, Astro.
So why build us that way?
It's the end of
the road, Klaus. Huh?
DELTA: Klaus, I just have
one question for you.
Did you ever
actually want to be human?
I can honestly say
I never wanted to be a human.
The only thing I ever
really wanted was to be me.
Weapons up!
Ah!
No. Klaus!
Delta, you're a good officer.
Don't ever forget that.
Just stay true to yourself.
Wait!
Fire!
Arggh!
What?
[ALL SCREAMING]
Klaus.
You're scrap metal!
Oww!
TAWASHI:
Drop your weapons.
Tawashi?
Right now!
I'm not a robot,
so I will take you down.
[GRUNTS]
ANDO:
We never found Klaus's body.
TAWASHI: Well, he couldn't
have survived that fall.
The current must've washed
his parts out to sea.
Delta, I've got
something to show you.
Later, Astro,
I'm on duty right now.
I promise it'll only take
a split second.
Klaus is alive!
What did you just say?
BOTH:
Nothing, detective.
Hmm.
[BIRD SQUAWKS]
[♪]