[♪]
Later.
MAN: Help! I'm under attack!
Look out!
O'SHAY:
Get your beak off me!
Why did I program
this birdbrain anyway?
Doctor, you'd better not
hurt my Momo.
O'SHAY:
Me, hurt her?
She's just trying
to keep you on schedule.
Schedules are made
to be broken.
Fine, you tell the mayor
you're going to miss
his bimonthly breakfast
budget presentation.
You don't understand, Yuko.
I've just uncovered a crisis
that's bigger than bagels.
Oh, really?
This is an ecoscan.
It comes from satellite cameras
that take pictures
of the environment
all across the globe.
ASTRO:
Wow, it's beautiful.
O'SHAY:
It was.
But that was taken a month ago.
This is how it looks now.
ASTRO:
Oh, it's dying.
Do you know why?
O'SHAY:
No. That's why we need
your help, Astro.
I've collated
all the satellite data.
Can you do a cyber-analysis?
ASTRO:
Computing. Hmm.
There are
tiny traces of Dexanol-G.
It's poisonous.
I can't tell where it came from
but it's spreading fast.
If it reaches Metro City,
it will be a disaster.
And it all centers
on Dragon Lake,
which, according to legend,
is inhabited by dragons.
You don't believe that,
do you?
Please, Yuko,
I'm a trained scientist.
Astro, can you do a geoprobe?
ASTRO:
No problem.
Hey, there's a whole network
of underground tunnels.
If poison got in there, it'd
spread across the whole area.
But those tunnels would also
make great hiding places
for dragons.
O'SHAY: What?
ASTRO: Just kidding.
I wanted to make sure
you were paying attention.
O'SHAY:
Now, that's enough
nonsense about dragons.
The point is this needs
immediate attention.
It must be investigated.
I completely agree.
Yeah!
You do?
Then I'll go pack my bags.
No. I'll pack my bags.
You're staying here.
But this isn't your job.
It's my job to
keep you on schedule,
starting with
a little paperwork.
Whaa!
O'SHAY:
But this is dangerous, Yuko.
Anything could happen.
YUKO:
Oh, I think
I can handle it.
Plus, Doctor, I'm bringing
my personal bodyguard with me.
ASTRO:
Whoa, dragons!
So he's at it again,
the mystery man.
[CAR APPROACHES]
There it is.
Dragon Lake.
Are you from
the Ministry of Science?
That's our contact.
Right.
You must be Sara.
Mm-hm. Thanks for
your cyber-mail.
You don't know
how glad I am
to finally have some help with
this contamination problem.
Astro will get to
the bottom of it.
Oh, right.
The famous super robot.
Ha-ha.
YUKO:
I want to investigate
these areas first.
I'll take you.
Thanks.
Then I'd like to test
the lake's water quality.
Hey, what's this?
An old Dragon Lake souvenir.
Now it's just a piece of junk.
It's working.
Mm-hm.
But no one wants souvenirs
from Dragon Lake anymore.
We used to have
tons of tourists
all wanting to see
the legendary dragons.
There were news crews
and dragon hunters.
But then a real science team
did a high-tech investigation.
Guess what. No dragons.
Bye-bye, tourists.
Bye-bye, reporters.
Everything shut down.
And, of course, that was it
for the souvenirs.
I think it's pretty cool.
Okay, we'd better get
this show on the road.
Astro, we'll need
that search data you prepared.
I'll drive,
if that's okay with you.
Absolutely. We can use
all the help we can get.
Let's start on
the north side of the lake.
And as for you, Astro,
you're going for a swim.
ASTRO:
All right!
Whoa, these caves really do look
like they could be dragon lairs.
MAN:
Help! Help!
Huh?
Help me!
Oh, help!
I'm going down!
I'm going...
Up?
ASTRO:
Wake up. Hello?
Huh?
All right, you're okay.
Aah!
How did I get here?
Are you with the dragons?
I bet you are!
Oh! Huh?
You're not human,
are you?
What do you mean? Whoa!
Let me see.
Ah, you're an android,
one of those thinking robots.
Ha-ha-ha!
And they say I'm crazy.
This is the machine
I was telling you about.
Here, take a look.
I built it myself
to catch UMAs.
UMA? What's that?
It's not in my data bank.
It's short for
Unidentified Mysterious Animals.
I'm a great hunter. I haven't
actually caught anything yet.
I plan to track
the Loch Ness monster
and Bigfoot.
But first,
I'm gonna catch a dragon
and everyone will know
the truth about Dragon Lake.
You really believe
in this stuff, don't you?
Once I find them,
the whole world will believe it.
You just wait.
YUKO:
Astro gave me
all the stats on this area.
Do you really trust
his data, Yuko?
Astro's figures
are very reliable.
I've got a reading.
Let's pull over.
The terrain's
a little rugged here
but we'll see how close
we can get to it.
I'm afraid this is
as far as we can go.
Well, we can't stop now.
I'll just go on foot.
It's getting stronger.
[GASPS]
Old power units
from early-model robots.
They have poisonous chemicals,
and instead of disposing
of them properly,
someone's just
dumping them out here.
But who?
[GASPS]
Got it! Your dragon web
is all hooked up.
Thanks, Astro.
We're good to go.
This will attract
the dragons.
Gulliver, why are you
doing all this UMA stuff?
I mean, it's kind of
a weird job.
Astro, this is my calling.
Huh? What do you mean?
Well, it all started
when I was just a little boy.
My father
was a researcher.
His name was Oliver
and he traveled everywhere
searching for
mysterious creatures.
The last place he came to
was Dragon Lake
but no one knows
if he found the dragons!
Why not? I mean, what happened
to him after that?
He vanished.
We never heard from him again.
Sounds so mysterious.
GULLIVER:
All right! Is this a brilliant
invention or what?
Take a whiff of
that dragon scent.
Ugh, it stinks!
Hah, to you maybe,
but to a dragon it smells
like buttered popcorn.
[MACHINE ROARS]
That's a dragon call.
They can't resist it.
All right, this is
my moment of truth.
They'll be here
any minute.
[MACHINE CREAKS]
Ahh!
I thought those rubber bands
would hold it together
but maybe paperclips
would work better.
ASTRO:
Hey, there's something there.
Huh? Whoa!
It actually worked!
It's them!
Yeah.
[CROAKING]
GULLIVER: Frogs!
Millions of them.
You've gotta protect me!
But frogs don't hurt people.
I hate little, green,
slimy things!
Ah! Ooh! Ah!
[BEEPING]
[GULLIVER SHOUTS]
Well, the good news is
your trap works.
Ah, that's okay.
I kind of like it up here.
At least the froggies
can't get to me.
[CROAKS]
Oooh!
YUKO:
Power units.
There's thousands of them.
I've got to tell Astro
about this.
[METAL CLINKS]
Oh!
Oh, help me!
Aah!
SARA [OVER LOUDSPEAKER]:
Hello, Yuko.
YUKO:
Sara, be careful.
There's a snake down here.
Call for help.
Really? But, you see,
I like snakes, Yuko.
They're so cuddly.
Now that you've uncovered
our operation,
you'll have to deal with...
ALL:
The Repo Girls.
Ha-ha-ha!
Maybe we didn't find
a dragon today,
but we can always
try again tomorrow.
Do you always camp out
in places like this?
I used to live
in the city.
GULLIVER:
No adventure, no surprises.
Then one day, by accident,
I saw the data on Dragon Lake.
It reminded me of my father.
I realized I'd given up all the
dreams I had when I was a boy.
My father had never given up
on his dreams, so why had I?
The next day, I left the city
and I never looked back.
When the scientists said
there were no dragons here,
everyone gave up.
And when they stopped,
you started?
Exactly.
See, the dragons don't matter.
Huh?
It's the search that counts,
how you feel
while you're out there.
That's what my father said.
You know, I really miss him.
CHRIS:
We've got a fix on Astro.
He's out at the lakeshore
like a sitting duck.
What's our next move?
SARA:
The kid is snake food.
He'll barely make a snack.
Don't underestimate Astro.
You'll never
lay a finger on him.
Snakes don't have fingers,
but they do have fangs
and venom.
When my father disappeared,
it was hard for me.
But at least he was trying
to follow his dreams,
and that's what
I'm trying to do.
But what if you really found
a dragon or a monster,
what would you do?
Huh? I don't know.
[GASPS]
There's something
out there!
[EERIE WHINING]
They're huge!
They're real!
ASTRO:
They're monsters!
SARA [OVER LOUDSPEAKER]:
Hello, Astro.
Huh? The monster
sounds like Sara.
Bingo.
And I brought
something special for you.
Argh!
Astro!
Oh, I can't move.
This stuff is draining
my power modules.
No wonder.
It's Dexanol-G.
They used it to power old robots
till they found out
it's poisonous.
It will completely
destroy your circuits!
Time to get to work, girls.
BOTH:
Ready, Sara.
SARA:
All right,
let's dump this junk.
No! That stuff's toxic.
It'll destroy the lake!
As if I care.
Do you have any idea
how much money they pay out
to get rid of these chemicals?
Of course, we secretly
have to dump them
where no one will find them.
That's part of the fun!
And if a few lakes and rivers
get wrecked along the way,
oh, well.
And business is booming since
we splashed onto the scene.
Nature is so overrated
these days.
Now there's only one more robot
to dispose of: Astro!
SARA:
It's sink or swim time.
[GROANING]
I've gotta charge up.
Astro, get out of there!
You can neutralize
that stuff with heat.
Got it!
That'll fire
things up.
Let's rocket!
This ought to cool you off.
ASTRO:
Down, boy.
Come on, girls!
I'll take care of nature boy.
KARLA:
What? Whoa!
I'm so outta here.
[WOMEN SCREAMING]
Nice job, Astro!
SARA:
Hey, kid!
Aren't you forgetting somebody?
Take a look.
SARA:
Playtime's over.
Back off...
or I feed Yuko to my pet python.
Don't listen to her.
Let her go!
Argh!
Astro, you've got to stop them.
Don't worry about me.
Quiet, Yuko!
Leave her alone!
[SNAKE HISSES]
Get back!
Gulliver, get out of here
while you've got the chance.
I don't leave my friends
when they're in trouble.
We're in this together.
Ahh!
ALL:
Huh?
ASTRO:
Look. There's something
out in the lake.
Hey, it's a dragon, a real one.
I knew they were down there.
Sara!
Let's get out of here.
CHRIS:
I've gotta get a new gig.
That's enough. Keep moving.
Watch out!
Come on, let me go!
It wasn't my idea!
Let me down!
We love nature, I swear.
Ow! Get off my foot!
Yuko, are you okay?
I am now. We'll be able to save
this lake, thanks to you, Astro.
Well, I got some help from
my friend. Right, Gulliver?
ASTRO:
Gulliver?
What is it?
GULLIVER:
It's not a dragon.
It's a submarine.
It's probably been underwater
for decades.
When they shot those canisters,
it stirred up the lake.
That's what brought it
to the surface.
Did you
find something?
Well, what is it? Oh!
That's him,
isn't it?
My father.
I thought he forgot about me
when he went away,
but he was thinking
about me all along.
I guess he built this ship
to look like a dragon
so he'd blend in
with the real dragons.
Too bad there aren't
any real dragons.
But he followed his dream...
to the end.
GULLIVER:
Astro, I think it's time
for me to give up my hunting
and start a new life.
Are you going to go back
to the city, Gulliver?
Uh-uh.
I wanna help clean up
wilderness areas like this.
Instead of inventing traps
to catch UMAs,
I'll build machines
to protect nature.
You never know,
one of my inventions
might actually work some day.
Could you use some help
from a friend?
You bet!
Too bad there weren't
any dragons here after all.
It was a great dream.
[♪]