[♪]
FISHERMAN 1:
There she goes.
Okay, now reel in the net.
TRAWLER ROBOT:
Big catch. Big catch.
FISHERMAN 1:
Get ready to slice
and ice these fish, boys.
FISHERMAN 2:
Hey, why's this catch so heavy?
Oh, man.
Wow, that's one big can
of tuna, boys.
[BEEPS]
[FISHERMEN GASP]
[FISHERMEN YELLING]
Captain. Are you my captain?
[POWERS DOWN]
Huh?
O'SHAY:
You see, Astro, what we have
here is a very old Venus Robot.
Will it be okay?
I can patch him up,
but I'm not sure
that will help
him in the long run.
Let's see what information
we can pull up
about Venus Robots.
If memory serves me right,
these units were designed
over 20 years ago.
COMPUTER:
Venus Robots were created
by the Ministry of Science
at the height
of deep-space colonization.
Ordinary robots couldn't
withstand the high temperatures
and atmospheric pressure
found on the planet Venus.
So a very special breed
of robot was developed.
These explorer bots had
super-metallic bodies
and a high-powered
liquid-nitro cooling ray.
ASTRO:
Wow. Their nitro-rays could
freeze a whole planet.
O'SHAY:
Yes, if someone
programmed them that way.
Those nitro-rays are exactly
why many believed
the Venus Robots
were too dangerous.
Sadly, they were deactivated
and dumped
to the bottom of the ocean,
abandoned forever.
Poor Venus Robots.
Well, one malfunction could
have destroyed our whole planet.
And this was at a time
in history when humans feared
robots were already getting
much too powerful.
The robots should have been
disabled,
but this unit's sensory chips
indicate
it was totally operational
right up until it was caught
in that boat's fishing net.
Hmm. I'll run more tests.
VENUS ROBOT:
Have you seen our captain?
Captain?
ASTRO:
Dr. O'Shay says the Venus Robot
was still operating
20 years after it was
deactivated.
I wonder if there
are more like him. Torpedo!
ASTRO:
It's so dark.
I can't see a thing.
Activate high beams.
Huh?
Wow.
Amazing. A whole
underwater robot world.
Who are you?
I'm Astro. And I'm a robot
built by humans, just like you.
Humans?
No, we were built
by the captain.
Captain? But that's not
what Dr. O'Shay said.
Come. I will show you.
One of our brothers traveled
up to the human world
and did not return.
Do you know anything
about him?
Yes. He was damaged.
Damaged?
Uh-huh. But don't worry,
a scientist I know is doing
everything he can to save him.
I told him not to go
to the surface,
but he was so anxious
to find our captain.
Behold. This is a statue
of our captain.
Whoa.
LEADER:
We were all created
by this great being.
Now we await the day
the captain will return
and tell us what it is
we must do to serve him.
But I was told that you
were built by--
Astro, why were you created?
To help humans and robots
work together as friends.
We do not understand
that concept.
Well...
Astro, you now know
what our captain looks like.
If you see him,
please tell him we are eager
to begin our mission.
ASTRO:
All those robots want
to be is useful.
They don't even know
they were just thrown away.
TENMA:
Magnificent.
A shining example
of a robot's ability to adapt
in order to survive.
Now all they need
is someone to lead them.
And that someone will be me.
[TENMA LAUGHS]
And soon, they will use
their powerful capabilities
to put the world
under our control.
TENMA [OVER SPEAKER]:
Robots, arise.
I am your captain.
[ROBOTS MURMURING]
I have returned to give you
your long-awaited mission.
Captain.
O'SHAY:
Astro, your video proves
that the Venus Robots
have continued to evolve
below the sea.
They desperately wanted
to carry out the mission
they were programmed for,
even though they had
no idea what that mission was.
I wonder if they know how
powerful their nitro-rays are.
That's a good question, Astro.
We've got to alert
the authorities.
The world could be in danger.
Huh?
The doctor's right.
There's a very good reason
why the robots
were buried deep underwater.
If they were to fire their
nitro-rays, even by mistake,
they could flash-freeze
all of planet Earth.
Hmm.
But wait. You're not thinking
of destroying them.
Only as a last resort.
However, there may be
no other way.
Please, no!
Yahoo!
Aah! Look out! Out of my way!
[YELLS]
Bernie. Your hover ski.
Dude, he's being attacked.
MAN:
Oh, look out. Oh, I've never
seen anything like it. Quick!
MAN [OVER PA]:
All emergency personnel to your
stations. We are under attack.
This is not a drill.
Repeat, this is not...
YUKO:
How many are there?
I'm guessing 20,000.
Twenty at least.
We count 50,000 strong,
and they keep on coming.
What could they possibly want?
There's nowhere
to hide!
[CROWD SCREAMING]
REPORTER:
The robots from the sea are
crossing every barricade
the police put up.
They're advancing straight
into the heart of Metro City.
This is Metro-Sky News
with continued coverage
of the robot invasion.
Bring up the heat-sensor map.
We'll see if we can track them.
They're headed this way.
The Venus Robots look like
they're going to attack
the Ministry of Science.
I have to stop them.
TENMA:
No, Astro. Even you can't
stop an army this size.
They will accomplish
their mission at all costs.
[CHUCKLES]
This is it. When those
tin cans get within 50 meters,
attack with maximum force.
TAWASHI:
Ready.
Aim. Huh?
ASTRO:
Hold your fire. Those robots
are filled with liquid nitrogen.
If they explode, it could
freeze the entire world.
What?
They're not evil, just confused.
Let me talk to them.
Stay where you are.
[GROANS]
All right.
That's far enough.
Astro.
Why have you come here?
To attack Metro City?
The captain has returned,
and he gave us our mission.
What?
You must not stand
in our way.
Go tell the humans it is our job
to create a new world.
YUKO:
A new world?
I don't understand.
What does he mean
by that, doctor?
Hmm...
We are to go
to the Ministry of Science.
We will salute
when the captain signals us.
You're going to salute?
Oh, no.
Astro, they're going
to activate their nitro-rays.
Stop!
You're being tricked!
Tricked?
Those are freeze rays.
You can't salute.
This is not what you were
created for. Believe me.
If you follow those orders,
you will wipe out all human life
and only robots will survive.
Out of our way, Astro.
[GRUNTS]
We know our mission.
We will obey
the captain's orders.
I have a plan. How long will it
take them to reach us?
They're currently passing
through sector C.
At this rate, they'll be here
in less than five minutes.
We have to do something,
doctor.
Yes. All right, then.
We've only got one chance.
And in case I'm wrong, I want
the whole building evacuated.
MAN:
Look out!
Retreat! Pull out, men!
Stop. I can't let you do this.
YUKO:
Doctor,
as your personal assistant,
it is my duty to stay with
you for your safety.
Don't worry, Yuko.
My plan is to hook up
a direct feed
to the History Museum archives.
Then, while Astro stalls
the Venus Robots,
I'll project a holo-vid showing
them the truth
about their creator.
That's brilliant.
Mm-hmm.
I don't know who's behind this,
but the orders
you're following are false.
Get out of our way. We must
get to the top of that spire.
Huh?
Astro, keep stalling them.
Hmm? What the--?
TENMA [OVER SPEAKER]:
You can't win,
you foolish old man.
Huh? Come out into the open
where I can see you.
O'Shay, you're about
to witness the dawn
of a new ice age.
Don't catch a cold.
Dr. Tenma, you're controlling
the Venus Robots?
[LAUGHS]
All they want is to be useful,
doctor.
But that's madness.
Is it madness
or pure genius?
You're merely using
those robots
to carry out one of your
diabolical schemes.
Power, destruction.
That's all you're after.
The moment these Venus Robots
were considered useless,
humans just threw them away.
Now let's see how useless
these robotic creations are.
[O'SHAY YELLS]
It was in spite of humanity
that these robots
survived decades
beneath the sea.
They grew and evolved
on their own.
If you free all robots
from human control,
they will eventually join
together and conquer mankind.
That will never happen.
Oh, but it's happening right
before our very eyes, O'Shay.
Witness the declaration
of robot independence.
A rare moment in history.
All right, Tenma.
Maybe mankind was selfish
to build these robots and then
carelessly throw them away.
But this senseless destruction--
You're insane.
Or perhaps I'm the sanest
of all.
Robots.
Your time has come.
What's that?
[VENUS ROBOTS MURMURING]
TENMA:
I am your captain.
Show me the signal
that you are ready
to create a whole new world.
VENUS ROBOTS:
We are ready, captain.
Don't listen to him.
Don't follow his orders.
Dr. Tenma is not your captain.
I shall be the first robot
to the top of the spire
and salute our captain.
TENMA:
So you want to be a worthy
and useful robot?
Salute your captain.
No! Stop!
[WHIRRING]
All right. Let's rocket!
Oh, no!
Astro!
ASTRO:
I have to find
the nitrogen tank.
Got it.
Bombs away.
[GASPS]
[GRUNTS AND YELLS]
[GASPING]
Astro.
Oh, no. Astro!
Are you all right, Astro?
[GROANING]
Now do you believe me?
You see what your powers can do.
Your freezer rays
could turn the whole world
into an ice planet in seconds.
You were built
to be useful to humans.
And look how you created that
amazing robot world
beneath the sea.
You're not meant to attack
and destroy.
[VENUS ROBOTS MURMURING]
Then why did the captain
order us to do this?
Because he's a--
TENMA:
Do what I tell you.
It is the only way
for you to evolve,
to understand your true purpose
and achieve freedom.
LEADER:
If we freeze everything,
then we will be free?
TENMA:
It is my ultimate plan
for you to fulfill your mission
and find your freedom.
No. They'll never be free
by destroying the entire
human world.
Wait! Don't follow him.
Choose for yourself!
Listen to your hearts.
You may be robots,
but you have the power
to choose your future.
Oh, no.
O'SHAY:
I've got to hook up
that video feed
from the Robot History Museum.
It will jog their memory
modules.
[BARKS]
TENMA:
It's over, doctor.
Put a muzzle on it, Tenma.
Yuko, I-- I told you
to get to safety.
And give up a chance
to use this thing?
This may be our last hope, Yuko.
Cross your fingers.
YUKO:
It's working, Dr. O'Shay.
The holo-vid is projecting
into the sky.
O'SHAY:
Excellent. Excellent!
The robots are watching.
They're learning the real truth
about their creation.
At last
the experiments
are a success.
Now all of you will take
a journey into space,
where you will work
to transform Venus
into a beautiful new world.
And assure a new future
for all mankind.
We will serve humans.
That is our work.
To work for humans.
So that woman was
the Venus Robots' real captain?
Captain.
Beloved captain,
we now go to do our duty
and fulfill the dreams
of mankind.
Yes, go and make me proud.
Helen, I'm sorry the Ministry
scrubbed the Venus mission.
I know it meant a lot.
Once my robots reach
the ocean floor,
their memories
will be erased
and they'll never know how
great they could have been.
Look, Helen, it's not like
they were human,
just a bunch of
programmable hardware.
Farewell,
all my beautiful friends.
Surely, they understand now.
What's that?
TENMA:
What's wrong with you?
Why are you just standing
there?
Dr. Tenma.
Don't be fooled.
Don't listen to them.
I am your captain.
No, our captain would not
ask us to harm humans.
We will help humans.
Great. You finally understand.
How dare you interfere.
[GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
Doctor!
[GRUNTS]
[ROCKETS SPUTTERING]
[YELLING]
Astro!
[GRUNTING]
What a brilliant plan.
The Venus Robots
saved them both.
We wanna thank you
for saving us.
You are the ones who saved us.
Huh?
It is time to fulfill
our destiny.
We now know what our mission
has become.
What's that?
To live in peace
with all humans.
Goodbye.
Goodbye, friends.
So long. Bye!
O'SHAY:
This is video we got
from an unmanned surveillance
device that was sent down.
They abandoned their whole city.
But where do you think
they went?
I believe they've gone to an
even deeper part of the ocean,
to rebuild their civilization
with a new understanding.
[VENUS ROBOTS CHEERING]
LEADER:
Behold our new hero.
Astro, our friend.
[♪]