[♪]
TRAFFIC ROBOT:
And a one, and a two.
Okay, step lively there, folks.
The signal says "walk,"
not "crawl."
You think I got all day
to stand here?
Well, maybe I do, but I need you
to keep moving along.
Move along. Move along.
The special robot nominees
were announced this morning
for the first annual
Robot of the Year award,
which will honor the robot
who has best exemplified
the human-like qualities
of courage, heart and mind.
The gala event
will be held here,
aboard the world's
largest luxury liner,
the Carmela Queen.
Here to give us his thoughts
on this special occasion
is world-famous scientist
Dr. O'Shay.
Since the Blue Knight
incident...
Boys, I think
you'll wanna see this.
Cool! Yeah!
ALEJO:
Just think,
I knew him when!
But the truth is most robots
just simply want
to be our friends.
REPORTER:
Astro!
Huh? Hey!
Congratulations,
Astro.
[BOYS LAUGHING]
Cool!
Astro, tell the folks at home
how you feel about being
nominated for the big award.
Huh? I was?
ALEJO:
Yeah! Astro is
number one!
Well, Astro,
what do you say?
Uh, it's an honor
just to be nominated.
Ridiculous.
The fools are actually planning
to give a robot an award?
Robots are tools!
No matter.
Once they're onboard the ship,
I'll blast these "robots of
the year" into the next century!
Why do you hate
robots so much?
[GASPS]
I always tried to help you.
Don't you
remember?
I was your...
friend.
I told you before,
I don't know who you are!
Now, for the last time,
leave me alone!
[MOANS]
Why? Why won't he let me be?
How did I get into this mess?
I must be crazy,
flying in these conditions,
but I must get
to the robot factory.
[GROANS]
Yes, this is the chance
I've been waiting for,
to step out of
my father's shadow
and show everyone I can run
the family business
better than
he ever did.
Well, it's going to take
more than a little rain
to keep me away
from that factory.
[SCREAMING]
TV HOST:
Our next nominee is Epsilon,
a strong favorite for her work
in the fields of science
and the environment.
She's coming to us from
the uninhabited Caldera Island
where she is working with
a geological survey team.
Caldera Island?
Ten years ago...
Caldera Island was the site
of one of the largest
volcanic eruptions on record.
Coincidence?
No, it's more.
Timing like this,
it has to be destiny!
Epsilon's been busy surveying
the very large crater.
Come in, Epsilon. Come in!
Can you tell us
what you've discovered?
Yes. Pressure is building again
inside the magma chamber.
However, she's not likely to
erupt for...another six months.
DAN:
Return to base.
On my way.
Good work.
You did a fine job.
Epsilon,
over here.
Could you tell us
what you'll be
wearing tonight?
MAN: Hey!
Huh?
Captain, I think
you'll wanna see this.
There's something
buried here.
Huh.
It's a robot.
A type I've never
seen before.
ANNOUNCER:
Robots, ladies and gentlemen,
welcome aboard
the Carmela Queen.
Wow,
it's humongous!
Maybe next year
I'll be nominated
for an award.
Hey,
Harley!
Astro! It's been a while.
Wow!
It's Harley!
[LAUGHS]
I have all
of your holoposters.
If you want, you can
autograph them for me.
And then Astro can take
our picture together,
and then you could teach me
some cool moves.
Gordon here, boss.
Navi-computer will be online
in two minutes.
Then you'll be in complete
control of the ship.
DRAKE:
Good. Get out!
Roger!
Kato, this is Drake.
What's the delay?
Perfection takes time.
And it doesn't get
more perfect than this.
DRAKE:
Words mean nothing.
I want fireworks!
Relax, boss-man.
"Fireworks" doesn't
begin to describe it.
[LAUGHS]
The ship will be caught
in the eruption, then sink.
And then we'll hear no more
of thinking, feeling robots
or those
who support them.
[LAUGHS]
BUDDY'S VOICE:
Why?
Huh?
Why did you...abandon me there?
[PANTS DELIRIOUSLY]
Buddy!
[PANTS]
A thousand miles
from civilization.
Transmitter broken.
Only two days of food and water.
Huh?
It's hopeless.
I won't last the week
on this island.
Mr. Drake?
Huh?
What? You!
You're the new
artificial intelligence robot
scheduled for display
at the trade fair!
Cheer up, please.
I'm sure
you'll be rescued
before long.
ZORAN:
How long, huh?
Huh?
How long until
they announce the winner?
O'SHAY:
Patience, Zoran.
Patience.
ROBOT WAITRESS:
Hors d'oeuvres?
Canapés?
Motor oil?
[ALL LAUGH]
Epsilon,
are you excited?
Of course.
Whoa, what a sunset!
Hmm.
Huh? What's wrong?
Aren't you
having fun?
All day I've had
the feeling
something bad
was going to happen.
Huh.
DRAKE:
No, this couldn't
have gone better
if I'd
planned it myself.
Ha-ha, that's right! I did.
Right on schedule too.
Now, as the new captain
of the Carmela Queen,
I think I'll plot
a slight change in course.
Say, 20 degrees starboard.
Yes, that should do nicely.
Look at the unwitting fools!
Enjoy the party, my friends!
But I'm the one
with a reason to celebrate.
After 10 years, my long
nightmare is about to end,
but yours
is just beginning!
MC:
Now, before we announce
tonight's winner, Dr. O'Shay?
O'SHAY:
Thank you.
Each of our nominees
has displayed
the miraculous qualities
of heart,
mind and courage.
This made the job of picking
a winner rather difficult.
I'd like to dedicate today
to putting the past behind us
and finding a new
understanding between humans
and robots.
A new understanding between
humans and robots?
Never!
Day after day,
the robot brought me
whatever food he could gather.
I hadn't asked for help
and I didn't want any.
But there he was every day
just the same,
doing what he could
to ease my solitary existence.
At first, I didn't know
what to make of it.
Why was he doing all of this?
The last thing I wanted
was pity
from some walking
pile of scrap metal.
Huh?
Look,
Mr. Drake.
I found some papayas
this morning.
They're very
nutritious,
and I understand
that humans
find them
quite tasty.
What would you know
about it?
Stupid robot!
Are they good?
Oh, they're terrible.
You're completely
useless.
Go away!
I'm sorry. I'll just
dispose of the remainder.
Perhaps the sand crabs
will find them to their liking.
Don't trouble
yourself!
I'll just force myself
to eat the rest.
I'm just joking with you.
You're joking?
[LAUGHS]
He gave me
the strength to go on.
Me? I gave him a name.
I called him Buddy.
I was completely wrong
about robots.
Buddy, you're not just
a walking computer.
You have a heart
as well as a mind.
So do you, Mr. Drake.
MC:
Finally, ladies
and gentlemen...
here to name
the first annual
Robot of the Year award winner,
Dr. O'Shay.
Thank you.
It is an honor to present
this prestigious award tonight.
[DRUMROLL PLAYING]
And now, the moment
we've all been waiting for.
The winner of the
Robot of the Year award is...
Hi, Harley! Don't forget
to thank me in your speech.
KATO:
Every year, these award shows
run longer and longer.
And now...
Best Achievement
in Special Effects...
me!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
MAN:
What's happening?
[GRUNTS]
What on earth happened?
Oh! Volcano!
[RUMBLING]
Why, that's Caldera Island!
CAPTAIN:
But that's 100 miles
off our course!
It's also unlikely the volcano
could have erupted on its own.
Captain...this ship's navigation
is off-line!
We're headed
straight for the volcano!
Then reverse course
manually!
All crew members return
to their stations immediately!
SHIPMAN:
Someone hacked
the computer!
We're locked out of the system,
including manual controls.
Ahh!
Crashing the ship looks like
the least of our problems.
Harley, protect the others.
Epsilon, let's rocket!
We have to turn
this ship around now!
[GRUNTS]
DRAKE:
Sometimes I need to
get out of the office
to clear my head.
And trashing robots
in a rain of fire,
that beats golf
any day of the week.
[LAUGHS]
[DR. O'SHAY PANTING]
We're running out of time.
Have you hacked back in?
No, sir.
The passcodes have been
changed, and we are
denied access.
ROBOT:
Perhaps
I can help.
Clark, I can't think
of anyone
more qualified
for the job than you.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
Hmm, this is
a very strong encryption.
Fascinating!
I've never seen it before.
[GRUNTING]
Maybe working together, we can
turn the ship around somehow.
[GRUNTS]
Yes, but that would leave
the ship unprotected.
DRAKE:
Looks like I've left Astro
between a rock
and a hot place.
[LAUGHS]
[WHIMPERING]
What?
What's happening?
The volcano! It's gonna blow!
[PANTS]
Buddy!
Uh! Oh!
Buddy! He's in the jungle
and he may need help!
Huh?
Talk about timing.
Hey! Hey, I'm here!
I'm here!
Mr. Drake!
Climb onboard!
How did you ever find me here?
From your transmission!
You've been broadcasting
an SOS, didn't you know?
No, I--
Is there
something wrong,
Mr. Drake?
[MACHINE BEEPS RAPIDLY]
Buddy sent the signal.
And now you can
help me find him.
Who's Buddy?
Are there any other people
here besides you, sir?
Buddy's a...robot.
We don't have time
to go look for a robot!
Sir, you need to
come with us!
I'm not leaving this island
without him.
Buddy!
Come back!
That's right,
Buddy isn't just a robot.
He...he took care of me.
I can't abandon him!
I won't!
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
Buddy.
Leave the robot.
It's just a tool.
Just a tool?
That's right,
sir.
In the end,
it's people that
matter, not robots.
Yes. Yes, of course.
A robot...not a real person.
It was probably...
already too late.
Hey!
It's not possible!
Buddy, forgive me.
[WHIMPERS]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
MAN:
There's nothing we can do!
Help us.
Listen up!
The robots are doing
everything they can,
but there's plenty
we can do too.
ZORAN:
I found
a first aid kit.
Thanks.
[GRUNTS]
I got things handled over here.
Dr. O'Shay is right.
There's work to be done.
Yeah, we can
help each other.
MAN:
Come on, let's start by
moving the wounded to safety.
MAN 2:
Okay.
MAN 3:
Here, help me get this man
by the table.
DRAKE:
This is O'Shay's fault,
the old fool!
Making robots with kokoro.
And me...
I must have been deluded...
thinking that a robot
could have been my friend.
FACTORY CHIEF:
I'm proud to say
we've completed mass production
on our newest line.
I think you'll be pleased
with the result, Mr. Drake.
I give you
the most advanced
artificial intelligence
robot on the market.
What?!
What is this?
What...what have you done?
BUDDY'S VOICE:
Why?
[WHIMPERS]
Why did you leave me there?
You said I was your buddy.
No.
Stop it!
No!
Equipped with the latest
artificial hearts and minds,
you could say
they're almost human.
Enough!
The last thing
this world needs
is a lot of
soulless machines
tricking us into thinking
that they're human.
It's not gonna happen
on my watch!
CLARK:
I am in!
I broke the encryption!
Now to get this ship
turned around
and away
from that volcano.
Astro, look!
The ship is
turning around!
Great!
But...she's not
out of danger yet.
Huh?
EPSILON:
Astro!
What can we do?
I love a big finish!
[GROANS]
ZORAN:
It's Astro!
[ALL LAUGH]
No one told me he could do that!
Oh!
Oh! I'm losing altitude!
There.
Huh?
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMS]
[ASTRO GRUNTS]
Everybody's safe now
thanks to Astro and Epsilon.
[PEOPLE CHEERING]
MAN:
Epsilon...
you saved us!
Thank you very much!
Mmm!
MAN:
Yeah! Good job,
Epsilon!
[CHUCKLES]
MAN:
And Astro too!
Come on. Come on, start!
Do you need any help?
Are you okay in there?
[DISGUISING VOICE]
I'm fine!
Now get away from my ship before
you cause any more damage!
ASTRO:
Hey!
Now, that's a guy
that needs kokoro.
I wonder who he was.
REPORTER:
This morning,
the Carmela Queen
arrived safely in port.
Thanks to this year's
robot nominees,
no one onboard
was seriously hurt.
In recognition
of their heroism,
the judges decided that
the Robot of the Year award
would be split among
all five nominees.
The cause
of the mysterious incident
is still
under investigation.
DRAKE:
Medals and ribbons
prove nothing.
Robots are soulless tools.
They have no need of kokoro.
DAN:
Hey, that's Caldera Island,
where we dug you up.
I wonder
what happened
to the person
who called me Buddy.
I hope
he's doing well.
DAN:
It's too bad you don't
remember his name,
but unfortunately,
your memory chip
was too badly damaged.
Something
wrong?
No, I guess not.
Then come on.
I'll buy you a cup
of antifreeze.
[♪]