[♪]
What's going on? Who's there?
Where am I?
If anyone can hear me,
take me to the Moon Tower!
It's that robot Astro's fault
that I'm stuck in here!
Huh?
It can't be!
I am the energy source
that governs the secrets
of the universe.
The ancient people
called me "Firebird."
Please, Firebird,
I know you can help me
if you would just
tell me the secrets.
Those who seek the knowledge
must invoke the door of wisdom.
If you possess
the qualifications,
the Moon Tower will appear
and the door will open.
Take me to the tower,
Firebird!
I want to possess
the secrets of the universe.
If you are worthy
of the secrets,
they will find
their way to you.
What is revealed inside
the door of wisdom
will be determined
by your motives.
Choose your actions
carefully!
[SCREAMING]
[GRUNTS]
Huh?
Where am I?
If Firebird thinks
I'm going to wait
until the secrets find me...
FIREBIRD: If you are worthy
of the secrets,
they will find
their way to you.
...then she's got
another think coming.
In no time, I'll be ruling
the entire world.
But first I have to make it
to that Moon Tower door.
This time nothing's
going to get in my way!
O'SHAY: The Moon Tower
has disappeared?
Just when I was putting together
the investigation team.
Huh?
[SCREAMING]
Doctor, do you think
someone as evil as Rock
would carry around
a picture of his mother?
Hmm.
It does seem strange.
[COMMUNICATOR RINGS]
So nice to see you again,
doctor.
Huh? Five more minutes and
I'd have been in my pajamas.
I have uncovered
some very important information
about Rock.
Rock? What did you find?
Something very interesting.
The man grew up at a facility
designed to research
psychic power.
Is this some kind of joke?
Rock was born with the ability
to control other people
with his mind.
Hurry now! There's not
a single moment to lose!
Oh, it's past my bedtime.
I'll call you first thing
in the morning, doctor.
And I was hoping
to sleep in.
[SIGHS]
Driver, step on it,
will you?
I'm in a hurry.
We'll be there soon,
Mr. Deputy Chairman.
Everything will be...just fine.
SECRETARY:
He's here, sir.
Come in, come in.
Deputy Chairman,
nice to see you!
O'SHAY:
Well, hello, Chairman Lyon.
What can we do for you?
Good morning,
Dr. O'Shay.
My apologies
for such short notice,
but I have an extremely
urgent request.
My goodness, chairman.
Are the city sewer-bots
acting up again?
Worse than that.
I'm sending you to an island.
Did I do something wrong?
No, no, doctor. Of course not.
I need you to investigate
a strange occurrence
on Phoenix Island.
Oh.
What's on
Phoenix Island, doctor?
Ruins of
an ancient civilization
who, according to legend,
possessed psychic powers.
It's baffled scientists
for years.
LYON:
The people worshipped
a mysterious creature
called "Firebird."
The creature gave them
the ability
to communicate telepathically.
They could even move objects
with their minds
using telekinesis,
which is how they built
their tremendous buildings.
But recent unexplained
electromagnetic waves
appear to be coming
from the island.
We have no idea
what you'll find there
and it could be dangerous.
I'm sure you'll want
to take Astro with you.
Of course, chairman.
Astro and I will get
to the bottom of this.
Please conduct
this investigation
with the utmost secrecy.
I'm sure you know, doctor,
how quickly people can panic.
So good luck.
A top-secret mission.
Mm-hm.
Eh? What?
I haven't the vaguest idea
who I was just talking to.
Well, that puts Astro
into the mix, now, doesn't it?
Hello, Dr. O'Shay.
My name is Professor Atami.
Chairman Lyon
has asked me to join
your special
investigation team.
Professor!
So nice to meet you, finally.
I must say, your excellent
reputation precedes you.
MAN: There's an emergency call
for Dr. O'Shay.
Put it through, please.
Hello, Dr. O'Shay.
Pardon the interruption,
but I wanted to update you
with my latest findings.
O'SHAY: Do you have
more information about Rock?
Yes, apparently
something known as
the Psychic Power
Research Institute
obtained custody of him
when he was very young
and he received
extensive psychic training
throughout his childhood.
Extensive psychic training?
KISAGARI: They sought
only very bright children
appearing to have
unusually high levels of ESP,
extrasensory perception,
then held them captive
for testing.
I can't believe any scientist
would allow such
inhumane treatment.
Not only that, but it's rumored
that they were
brainwashing the children
in a plot to overthrow
the government.
Interestingly,
Rock escaped from the facility
when he was 12 years old.
Mr. Kisagari,
did you find out anything more
about the locket?
He wore that locket the entire
time he was at the institute.
And he's probably
worn it ever since.
Strange thing about it is
the locket was apparently empty
while he was at the institute.
Huh?
Empty?
We need more answers,
and I'll be in touch
as soon as I have some.
Goodbye.
If it was empty
when he was at the facility,
then whose photograph
is in it now?
ASTRO: I don't know,
but it must be important.
Why else would he wear it?
[GRUNTS]
ROCK:
What would they know?
The Phoenix Island ruins.
ASTRO: They must have used
telekinesis.
How else could they build that?
O'SHAY: Quite
an advanced civilization.
This way! The entrance
is over here!
ALL:
Oh!
Astro, would you
make sure it's safe?
Okay, professor.
Just be careful, Astro!
ATAMI:
Team!
I've found something strange
on these walls.
Huh?
I wonder what
these pillars are for?
O'SHAY: This chamber
does look rather unusual.
Take a close look
at the markings.
They're like nothing
I've ever seen before.
How fascinating!
MAN: Some kind
of ancient language.
WOMAN: This room's
a little creepy.
[MACHINE WHIRS]
ALL:
Huh?
O'SHAY:
What? Hey!
[ALL GASP]
Let us out of here!
What are you up to?
Welcome to the ancient
Phoenix Island prison
where victims were held
against their will.
What are you talking about?
Chairman Lyon will have
your hide for this.
Dr. O'Shay needs my help!
[GRUNTING]
Gotta be quicker than that, pal!
Psych!
Hey, Stoneface,
chill with the lasers!
[GRUNTS]
Professor Atami,
why are you doing this?
You'll see soon enough.
ASTRO: Doctor!
Huh?
Professor Atami,
what's going on here?
Perhaps you should call me
by my real name, Astro.
Wait. I've heard
that voice before.
ASTRO:
Rock!
I thought you were stuck
in that warp tunnel forever!
Let's just say a friend
sent me back on a mission.
ASTRO: Huh?
[BOTH GASP]
What is that?
Just stop!
One more step and your friends
will be burned to a crisp!
[GROWLS]
Pay attention, Astro!
You will use the power
on this island
to enable me to finally
access the Moon Tower!
That's impossible!
ROCK: This temple is like a
giant dimensional transmitter.
When you combine
your electronic brain energy
with the psychic power
of these ruins,
you should be able to summon
the Moon Tower to Earth.
But you have no idea
of the consequences
of combining all that energy!
Here, Rock. Take a look at this!
Huh?
The woman in this picture must
mean something special to you.
Think back to the time
when you were with your family.
[LAUGHS]
Well, what's wrong?
That's a fake picture I used
back in my days as a con man!
I cut it out from an ad
in a magazine.
I don't even know
who she is!
Huh?
I never cared for anyone
and no one ever cared for me,
not even my parents,
who freaked out when they
realized I was different
and then put me
in that crazy facility.
But, Rock...
[GASPS]
So are you going
to help me, Astro,
or do you want
to see them vaporized?
No, stop!
I'll help you
get the Moon Tower.
But, Astro--
Well, then, we'd better
get to it, my robot friend.
Time's a-wasting.
[MACHINE WHIRRS]
[GRUNTS]
Huh?
[ALL GASP]
[SCREAMING]
Look! It really is
the Moon Tower!
[SCREAMING]
[ALL GASP]
[LAUGHS]
Good job, Astro.
Oh, no! Astro!
Huh?
[GRUNTING]
Astro's okay!
[GRUNTS]
Now the time has finally come
to unlock the secrets.
[SCREAMING]
[ALL PANTING]
What's happening
inside the tower? Huh?
[COMMUNICATOR BEEPS]
Doctor, are you all right?
We're okay, Detective Tawashi.
We found the real
Professor Atami
and figured
you might be in trouble.
We're headed your way
right now.
Doctor, I found out
why Rock's locket was empty
while he was
at the psychic institute.
All of the children's
family photos were confiscated
to suppress
their childhood memories.
That way, they were easier
to brainwash.
What a terribly
cruel thing to do.
However, I did find
a picture of Rock's mother.
Oh?
Hey, compare it to the locket!
She is different.
[BOTH SCREAM]
[SCREAMS]
My hand!
I can't get it off!
[GROANS]
The Moon Tower!
It's starting to rise!
The tower's flying
back up into the air!
I gotta go find Rock
and help him, doctor.
But, Astro--
Rock, hang on!
[SCREAMING]
Astro!
[GROANING]
Rock, stop!
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
[SCREAMS]
FIREBIRD: The door of wisdom
is closed to an evil heart.
Your use of this knowledge
would only bring about
destruction and ruin.
Rock, look at this!
You've gotta have
some memories
from before you went
to that psychic place.
[SCREAMS]
Think back, Rock.
Where did you get this?
Rock, stop it!
[BOTH GROANING]
Whoa! Whooaah!
[BOTH SCREAMING]
Rock!
Take this!
[SCREAMS]
[SIGHS]
Mother.
Rock, this is for you.
I wish I could be with you,
darling, but I can't.
Not anymore.
But I promise I'll always
be watching over you.
[ALL GASP]
Is that...Firebird?
Your kind will not benefit
from the universal secrets
unless the knowledge is
entrusted to a worthy recipient.
I will wait
until that day comes.
[SIGHS]
Oh!
Watch out!
Rock!
Phew!
KISAGARI: Rock's parents
sent him to the facility
because they were told
it was best for him.
But, sadly, the people
at the facility
made him believe that his
parents had abandoned him.
Be careful! That man has
dangerous psychic powers.
He can manipulate people.
[LAUGHS]
Don't worry, I don't have
that power anymore.
Doctor, do you
think that Rock
will be able to start
a new life?
With your help, Astro,
I think he will.
[♪]