[♪]
KISAGARI: I know
you're out there, baby,
somewhere in those mean streets
of Metro City,
and I'm gonna find you.
Why? Because it's what I do.
I am a detective.
[LEAVES RUSTLING]
Gotcha, beautiful.
Hello, kitty! Meow!
Come here, Miss Fluffykins,
pretty girl!
Come on. I've got
cat treats for you.
Huh?
You're going down, young chaser!
BOY: Ouch!
Arggh.
Oh, sorry, kid. I thought
you were my client.
Hey, who are you, mister,
and why do you smell like fish?
Because I am a professional.
I'm Wally Kisagari,
finder of lost stuff.
In this case,
one Miss Fluffykins,
alias Itty Bitty Widdle Kitty.
What about you, kiddo?
I'm staying with
my aunt and uncle.
They live near here.
Till I can find my mom.
She's missing?
Mm-hm.
TAWASHI: Five more minutes
till Skunk makes his move,
and this time
I'm gonna to nail him.
I don't get it,
doctor.
Why would Skunk tell them
he's going to rob a bank?
Probably trying
to make the detective
look like a fool again.
I did not look like a fool
just because he told me
when and where
and what he was going to steal.
O'SHAY: A 2-ton statue
of pure gold
isn't exactly like
shoplifting a candy bar.
ASTRO:
How tight was security?
TAWASHI:
We took every precaution
known to science.
The statue was locked
in a watertight,
airtight, solid steel safe.
It was surrounded
by electric eyes,
and it had only one entrance.
I stationed round-the-clock
guards at that entrance.
Skunk couldn't possibly
get to that gold.
Mm-hm.
[BEEPING]
No!
ASTRO:
But Skunk stole
the gold anyway, huh.
TAWASHI: Yes, Astro.
Thanks for pointing that out.
Detective Tawashi's
a little sensitive
about this invisible
thief thing.
I tell you, Skunk must have
found a flaw
in our security system,
and used some kind of robot
to exploit it.
So, detective, that's why
you need Astro's help?
ASTRO:
Ready for action, sir.
DETECTIVE: Fine, this time
I've thought of everything.
Good luck, Skunk.
WOMAN: Please let me through.
Huh?
Hey, you can't
go through there!
I'm with
the Ministry of Science.
Dr. O'Shay?
Yuko!
You're exactly 4 minutes
and 17 seconds behind schedule.
Uh, my watch
stopped working.
MAN:
Detective, major trouble!
TAWASHI:
What's happening?
BOTH: Huh?
ASTRO:
The monitors are blank!
Something's blocking the signal
from the underground safe!
Who got in there, huh?
No one,
Detective Tawashi, sir.
You'd better
be right!
Yes, sir.
Just a second!
My ultrasonic hearing is
detecting molecular movement.
Huh?
Sir, that's
not possible.
We've been here
the whole time.
Can the bank president open
the vault door so we can check?
All right.
[ALL GASPING]
ASTRO: My thermal sensor
reads 2000 degrees!
DOCTOR: The gold's melting.
Oh!
ASTRO:
And turning into a robot!
That's a billion-dollar robot!
ALL: Whoa!
TAWASHI: We got him!
Dead end up ahead.
What?
ASTRO:
Where did it go?
How do you lose
a giant golden robot?
I'm picking up microscopic
traces of gold that lead...
there!
Detective, we've caught
a suspect right outside.
Boys, I think
I smell a skunk.
Hey, watch the trench coat, pal.
This baby is rented.
I'm Wally Kisagari,
finder of lost stuff.
Yuko! Set these flat foots
straight, will you?
Just because my license expired
doesn't mean
I'm not a detective.
He's my uncle.
[SIGHING]
ALL: Huh?
Uncle Wally, thanks to you
I've been humiliated
in front of my boss.
What in the world
are you doing here?
Sorry, sweetie,
can't tell you.
Very hush-hush case
I'm on.
Oh, please. What, are you
chasing another runaway cat?
You know why you're
my favorite niece?
Because you got spunk, kiddo.
Uncle Wally, you've got to go.
Right now!
Yeah, yeah, in a minute.
Step aside,
I need a peek
at the crime scene.
Momo!
Careful, bird brain!
Where's a cat when
you need one? Ugh!
Thanks.
Sorry, Uncle,
but you asked for that.
You want me to go?
Fine.
But using a robot
to kick me out,
that's cold.
[SIGHS]
What does he mean
by that?
Doesn't your uncle
like robots?
Sorry, Astro. He's
kind of old school that way.
[SNEEZES]
He doesn't like robots
or me working with robots.
Wait.
The clock's acting weird.
Ah. Typical side effect
of a supermagnet.
Huh?
ASTRO:
That's it!
The golden robot left behind
magnetic footprints!
He must know something.
Mr. Yuko's-uncle, sir!
Astro!
What?
I wasn't kidding.
My uncle's got robot issues.
WOMAN [ON RADIO]:
Detective Tawashi reports
the bank was robbed
by a disappearing golden robot.
Um, hey, guys.
Did-- Did I read that right?
Metro City's finest, bah!
If anybody asked me,
I could tell them
how they stole the gold.
ASTRO: Does it have
something to do
with a superpowerful magnet?
Ah, as a matter of fact,
it does.
Hey, Mr. Kisagari!
Is this a good time to talk?
It's never a good time
to talk to a robot.
Hey!
The only good robot
is nobot!
Ha, ha, ha!
That'll teach him!
Excuse me!
Huh? Electro-pest!
[HORNS BLARING]
ASTRO:
Wait up!
Eat my vapor trail!
[WOMAN SCREAMING]
Wally Kisagari
coming through!
Arggh! Arggh! Arggh! Arggh!
[SNICKERING]
Better reprogram
your little battery brain
before you try to tail
a trained detective.
[LAUGHS]
Welcome, sir.
Coffee, baby.
No moo juice.
Yes, sir.
Most amusing.
MAN:
That's the third game
in a row!
You're too good
for me, Astro.
MAN:
I give up!
Sorry. How about you?
Ah! I give up too.
What is it that's
so darn important?
Catching a crook named Skunk.
But we got to work together.
So are you in?
Metro City. I used to own
this high-tech town.
I could find anything
or anybody
anywhere, any time.
Now look at me.
Chasing lost cats and working
with a metal sidekick.
So you don't like me, and it's
just because I'm a robot, huh?
Depends.
Come with an electric toothbrush
or a coffee maker?
Mm-mm.
Figures.
Hey, check out
that fountain.
See the way those
cubes stick together
almost like they're bound
together by an invisible thread?
Huh? Yeah, cool!
What's the secret?
Some kind of magnetic force?
KISAGARI: You got it.
State-of-the-art technology.
Wow!
Huh?
What is that thing?
It's a miniature hypermagnetic
impulse generator.
Super-secret stuff.
So how did you get it?
Actually, a kid gave it to me
here in the park.
His mother is the scientist
who invented it,
and she's disappeared.
But how?
That is a good question.
BOY: My mom's an expert
in magnetic force.
She designed that fountain.
Whoa.
And she made this too.
It's my good luck charm.
Hmm, did that just
make the fountain move?
I'm not sure what it is,
but my mom told me
to take good care of it.
And then?
And then she disappeared.
You've got to
go find her, mister.
You can do it, can't you?
Please tell me
you can find my mom.
[CRIES]
Hey, don't cry. You're talking
to Wally Kisagari here.
Is that a good thing?
Not if I owe you money.
Ha, ha. Joking.
KISAGARI:
I immediately began
my investigation.
I interrogated witnesses,
I tracked down leads,
until my skillful detective
work finally paid off.
I got nothing.
I'd give my moustache
for a clue!
MAN [ON TELEVISION]:
And now the latest
on the Skunk case.
Huh?
Just as he promised,
Skunk stole
the pure gold statue
from a completely sealed
bank vault.
The only clue,
all of the clocks
in the immediate vicinity
were found to be
malfunctioning.
Broken clocks?
Analog clocks tend to be easily
affected by magnetic force.
[STATIC WHIRRING]
BOY: Mom?
Look at that!
WOMAN: That's very strange.
MAN: What's going on?
Huh?
Now, this is a clue.
I snuck into the locked room
where the golden statue
had been stolen.
ASTRO:
I get it.
You wanted to see if
some of the magnetic residue
was still at the crime scene.
Cool!
KISAGARI:
Yeah, not bad, robot.
Now, do you mind?
This is my story.
No mistake about it.
Somehow, Skunk used magnetic
force to steal that gold.
Oh, I see.
And that 14-karat robot
was a magnetic machine
that could break itself down
into tiny particles.
And coincidentally,
the only scientist
capable of building such
a machine has disappeared.
The little boy's mother!
Find her,
and we'll find Skunk.
Find Skunk and we'll
find the gold, right?
Who's the detective
here, kid?
But listen,
you've got to admit,
we make a pretty
good team, Mr. K.
Come on. What do
you say, partner?
Let me give you a little tip
about hard-boiled detectives.
We work alone. It's all
about living by your wits.
You gotta be on your toes,
think ahead.
You gotta be ready
for anything.
Huh? Like that?
Hmm?
ASTRO:
It's Miss Yuko's zip car.
Yikes! How did she
find me here?
She's probably looking for me,
since I'm supposed to be back
at the Ministry of Science.
This is why
I always work alone!
Huh? Wait, I'm coming with you!
Oh!
Uncle Wally?
When things get weird,
he's always around.
So this
drainage canal
is connected to the
underground duct at the bank.
Look, my watch here
is going crazy.
Skunk must have sent in
his magnetic robot through here.
Astro, look at this map.
This is the route
the magnetic robot took
for the first robbery,
and this route
to access the bank.
In both cases, the distance
the magno-bot traveled
was exactly the same.
Obviously, Skunk is no dummy.
He doesn't want to be
anywhere near the crime scene.
So he starts each caper
as far away as he possibly can
and still control
the magno-bot.
Which means
if we know where
he's going to commit
the next robbery,
we can find him
and the gold!
Maybe.
As long as Skunk gives us
advanced warning again,
and we move fast enough.
[BEEPING]
The next warning's just been
sent to Detective Tawashi.
Let's roll!
SKUNK:
Ready for some fun,
Akita Squad?
Let's try playing
a little game this time.
Instead of telling you
where I'm gonna rob,
how about I give you a hint?
A hint?
The treasure lies
where a golden waterfall flows
between four pillars.
What is this, a haiku?
Ha! You figure it out.
[SNICKERING]
What? A waterfall
in the middle of four pillars?
ASTRO:
Could this be what he
meant by four pillars?
But I don't see any
golden waterfall, do you?
ASTRO:
Look! This must be the golden
waterfall he was talking about.
But the four pillars
are nowhere in sight.
These are sort of
like pillars, right?
The International
Casino, huh?
Well, it's certainly the kind
of target Skunk would go after.
But you missed
something, sidekick.
No golden waterfall.
Whoa!
Now, that's a golden waterfall!
KISAGARI:
No doubt about it.
We've got his target.
Okay, now,
let's go get Skunk.
Right.
SKUNK:
Well, Dr. Kreinberg,
I couldn't have
done it without you.
Thanks to you and
your magnificent magnet,
I'm about to steal 20 billion
worth of gold bullion!
[MEN LAUGHING]
SKUNK:
So, Tawashi, finally figured
out my little hint, huh?
[SNICKERING]
Good work, losers.
Because I'm gonna access
the underground safe
through a tiny air vent.
You're despicable!
Using my technology
to create a bank-robbing robot.
Why, thank you, doctor.
I consider myself
a scientist too,
specializing in the science
of stealing!
Time for another experiment.
Ready, magno-bot?
ASTRO:
I'm picking up some magnetic
pulses just north of the casino.
Good work, Astro.
It's a lot easier
to smell out a Skunk
when you've got
a superhero sidekick.
Okay, Dr. Kreinberg,
time for your creation
to get busy.
No, I will not be your
lab assistant in crime.
Sorry, doctor.
If you won't let me
use your magnetic robot,
I'll have to play this card.
Want to go home again?
All right.
You win, Skunk.
Wait, it looks like there's
something wrong with
the power limiter.
Maybe this will
help you fix it.
Okay. I just have to
reconnect this circuit.
Huh?
Hey, what did you do?
You'll see.
MEN:
Arggh! Arggh!
Arggh!
She's turned the magnet
on us! Ugh!
Out of my way,
Dr. Double-Cross.
I can handle these controls!
The magnetic pulses
are getting stronger,
and my sensors indicate that
the source of the magnetism
is inside that truck!
Ah, looks like we trapped
a Skunk in its den.
Yes, sir. Huh?
Ah! That's the woman
I've been looking for.
BOTH: Arggh! Ugh!
magno-bot, get to work.
No!
SKUNK [ON SPEAKER]:
You look surprised, doctor.
Operating a giant
magno-bot is a snap,
like playing a video game.
So what do you say?
Let's play Squash the Scientist!
Can I play?
Ugh! Having fun yet?
No! I don't think so.
Ever played Dodge the Magnets?
Ugh! Ugh!
There's too many,
and they're too fast! Whoa!
My sidekick's
getting his side kicked!
Hold on, Astro!
What are you
going to do?
Time to level
the magnetic playing field.
Huh? Ugh! Oh! Ugh!
It's getting so hot.
The temperature's rising
higher and higher!
A magno-bot this
powerful
gives off super heat,
which means you're
about to have a meltdown!
[YELLING]
KISAGARI:
Pick on a magnet
your own size, Skunk.
Like this!
He's neutralized my magno-bot!
So who is
this bone brain anyway?
What's the matter, Skunk, huh?
Crime losing its attraction?
Grrr!
Kind of a scrappy
old codger, ain't you?
Ugh! Arggh!
Mr. Kisagari, no! Oh!
Ugh!
Are you all right?
Yeah. Fortunately,
my moustache broke my fall.
[GRUNTING]
We have to stop
that magno-crook!
If only I had that
good luck charm.
Good luck charm?
That's what
my son calls it.
Actually, it's a miniature
hypermagnetic impulse generator.
This is my good luck charm.
It's too late.
Maybe not, baby.
What? Where's my son?
He's safe.
Astro!
Catch this!
Got it!
Time for some magnetic justice!
Arggh!
Ah!
The controls
don't work.
Arggh! Let's beat it.
Right behind you!
Yeah!
[ALL YELLING]
[ALL COUGHING]
You're under arrest, Skunk!
Think again!
Get him, boys!
COP: Where did he go?
Hiya, Skunk. May I
have this slam dance?
ASTRO:
Nice move,
Mr. Kisagari!
Thanks, Astro.
Dr. O'Shay!
Astro, are you
sure you're okay?
Yeah!
There's nothing
to worry about
with me and Mr. K.
on the case.
Uncle Wally, you've been working
with Astro all this time?
I thought
you hated robots.
Hey, listen.
Just because a guy's
got a computer brain
doesn't mean he can't
be my sidekick.
Right, partner?
Yup!
[LAUGHING]
Thanks for everything,
Astro, Mr. Kisagari.
But now I want to
see my son.
Honey!
Mom!
Honey.
I missed you!
You know what I
usually do after a case?
What?
Go back to my
lonely bachelor pad
and put medicine
on my cat scratches.
Pretty sad,
huh?
Oh, that reminds me. I've still
got a lost kitty to find.
I'm afraid you can't
come with me, kid.
But if I ever need
another sidekick,
I'm calling the best robot
in Metro City.
Yeah?
You bet.
See you round, Astro.
But, Mr. K!
Mr. Kisagari, come back!
KISAGARI: Don't turn around,
Kisagari.
He'll see you crying like
a kitty without a cat toy.
Wait! You forgot
to take your zip car!
Huh?
Uh, I meant to do that!
[♪]