[♪]
CREW MAN:
There it is, Astro.
The Space Academy.
ASTRO:
Wow! It's even bigger
than I thought.
CREW MAN:
That's right.
And no better place for training
future astronauts
and rocket scientists.
ASTRO:
This is gonna be awesome.
I'll bet everyone here
has a blast.
[EXPLOSION]
[ALL YELLING]
Hmm? What?
What on earth
is going on here?
Uh, other than
the raging fireball,
not much, sir!
Huh? What in the...?
Oh!
Whoa! Argh!
Huh?
Grr!
[NERVOUSLY]
Yaah... Sorry!
Anton! Not again!
What have you gone and done?
Oh!
And
Dr. O'Shay--
ALL:
Whoa!
Gangway! Mad fireball!
Huh?
Gotta fly!
Hey!
[GASPS]
Ugh! No!
Whoa!
[GRUNTING]
Huh?
ASTRO:
Oh!
WOMAN:
Are you all right?
Yeah. Thanks.
Good.
That was a close one.
Was it ever!
That was an amazing save.
You just grabbed
that thing in midair
and yanked out exactly the right
wire to keep it from--
[STUTTERING]
You must be Astro.
My name is--
ANTON:
Briana!
Hi, Anton.
Much better.
Your latest invention
only wiped out half the school.
Whoa!
Hi. I'm Astro.
This is a CO2 engine, right?
Yep.
Great design!
Thanks.
You'd better invent
a disappearing machine
before the headmaster
finds you.
This is the third time you've
nearly destroyed the place.
Good thing you didn't
dent the Falcon.
ANTON:
That's for sure.
So that's the Falcon Two!
You know it?
The new
experimental starship.
I'm supposed to help
design its guidance system.
BOTH:
You!
That's right.
Oh.
Then we'll be
working together.
Huh?
Uh, you and me?
Whoa! Whoa!
Oh!
Uh, I gotta go
and do a, uh, thing.
Whoa!
Uh, I gotta go!
Bye!
Whoa!
Whoa! Whoa!
Bye!
BOTH:
Huh?
ASTRO:
This nervous feeling in my chest
just won't go away.
Internal temperature,
0.3 degrees higher than usual.
Hey, what are you doing?
Huh!
Whoa!
Cool circuits.
Excuse me?
Oh, sorry.
It's all right.
So how come
you're here, Anton?
Because I live here.
This is my room,
and these are all my inventions.
And you must be
my new roomie.
Well, then,
welcome to the Academy,
roomie.
All right!
ENGINEER:
So, Astro, what do you think of
our blueprint for Falcon Two?
ASTRO:
Hmm.
My analysis detects
three excess circuit paths,
which means 6 percent
of its power is wasted.
We need to bring it down
to no more than 2 percent.
Impossible. No one's ever
gotten it that low.
ASTRO:
If we bypass the grid,
we can get it
to zero.
ALL:
Zero?
Wha--
Whoa!
Uh...
Excuse me. I left
the bathtub running. Oh!
Ah!
It's up another 0.7 degrees.
What is happening to me?
Astro?
Huh?
I've been
looking for you.
That was truly amazing.
Oh...
Yes, a brilliant analysis.
You're just what
the program needs.
Say, do you smell
something burning?
Anyway, with you here,
I know we'll get Falcon Two
off the ground.
ASTRO:
Not a single
malfunctioning circuit.
What is wrong with me?
[ANTON SIGHS]
Huh?
What's the matter,
Anton? Can't sleep?
Astro, can I
tell you a secret?
Um, sure.
Well, the thing is--
Yeah?
Well...
I'm crazy about Briana!
Oh.
But I'm just too chicken
to tell her.
Would you
do it for me?
Huh?
I know, it's an awful
lot to ask,
but every time
I try to tell her,
my knees get
all wobbly.
[WHIMPERS]
You're the only one
who can help me.
Why me?
Because she respects you.
You're working
with her every day.
So maybe you could just
casually, you know,
ask her if she likes me.
I just-- I don't know
where else to turn, Astro.
Will you?
Uh, well, I--
Please don't say no!
I'm desperate. I really,
really like her a lot.
Hmm.
ASTRO:
"Dear Briana..."
Briana!
Astro! What's up?
I, uh-- Um...
Do you have time to go with me
to the cafeteria?
There are so many things
I want to ask about you.
Me? Uh...
Um, Anton--
Anton?
Yeah. Um, what do you
think of him?
Well, I think he has
a lot of potential.
He just needs to learn
to focus a little bit more.
His head is usually
somewhere in the clouds.
It's like he's always thinking
about something else.
If I had his smarts,
there'd be no stopping me.
The thing is, um, Anton asked me
to give you a letter.
A letter?
Hmm.
Letter! What letter?
I wrote it
and signed your name.
[YELPS]
Then she's reading it right now!
Oh!
Shh!
[SIGHS]
Sorry about that.
So then
the second penguin says,
"Why is that duck..."
BRIANA:
"Dear Briana,
"ever since the first time
I met you,
"I haven't been able
to take my eyes off of you.
"I've been waiting
to get up the courage
"to tell you how I feel.
You are so beautiful..."
ASTRO:
"And so very special.
"I've never met
anyone like you.
"And yet, I notice
you seem always to be alone.
"I know what it means to feel
different and to be lonely,
"to be so taken with a dream
"that everything else
seems unreal.
"To you, that dream
is space travel.
To me, that dream is you."
BRIANA:
"Signed, Anton."
[SIGHS]
Anton.
[DREAMILY]
Briana!
[COMPUTER KEYS CLICKING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Oh, hi! Hold on.
I'll get him.
Telephone!
It's Briana.
[GULPS]
She's waiting!
Hurry up.
[GULPS]
I can't do it, Astro!
You talk to her for me.
Huh?
Pretend you're me.
Disguise your voice.
Hmm.
[CLEARS THROAT]
[MIMICKING ANTON]
Hi, Briana. It's Anton.
What's up?
ANTON:
What!
Briana wants to see me!
Mm-hm.
Oh, no! This is
like a nightmare.
I thought it's
what you wanted.
It is! But I didn't think
it would really happen.
I don't know what to say.
I don't know what to do.
What if I say
something stupid
and she never
speaks to me again?
What if I can't stop babbling
like I am now?
Use this!
Huh?
What's this? An earphone?
ASTRO:
Put it in your ear,
and I'll tell you what to say.
Then, you just repeat my words.
Ask her about the Falcon.
Uh, Briana, I was
just wondering.
Why are you working so hard
on the Falcon ?
Because I want to go
beyond time.
Beyond time?
If-- If we surpass
the speed of light,
I believe we'll travel
through time.
But that's theoretically
impossible.
Yes.
That's what everyone
always tells me.
I don't blame you at all
for thinking I'm
a little bit foolish.
No, no, I never--
It's okay.
It's a normal reaction.
Now tell her that what
you meant to say was,
"Impossible goals are
the only ones worth having."
Uh, Briana,
what I meant to say was...
impossible goals are the only
ones worth having.
And I just know
that you can do it.
Anton, do you know
you're the only one
who didn't make fun of my plans?
That means so much to me.
[GULPS]
When I read your letter,
I knew we were the same.
And you understand me
like no one else.
Briana, where will you
go beyond time?
If I tell you, I know
you'll laugh at me.
[SHOUTS]
I will never
laugh at you!
Ugh!
Astro!
Anton?
What's wrong?
Uh, a dragonfly flew in my ear.
I hate that.
You asked me where
will I go beyond time.
It's kind of
hard to explain. But...
When I was a child,
my father taught me
about the stars.
He said the light
from the most distant stars
takes millions of years
to reach the Earth.
And I thought,
if I could become light,
then I could be like the stars
and travel to the farthest
corners of the cosmos.
The ultimate limits of time.
HEADMASTER:
And now it's time to name
this year's honors graduate,
that student who has earned
the right to take part
in a trans-galactic
space flight.
Today, the Academy
is proud to announce
the newest crew member
of the Falcon Two,
Cadet Briana Turner!
Cadet Turner,
please step forward.
[ALL CHEERING]
Isn't it great, Astro?
And I've got a special
graduation surprise for her.
What is it?
You'll see.
Astro, I really appreciate
all your help last night.
I don't think I could
have done it on my own.
Thanks to you, I feel
a lot more confident now.
That's good.
Maybe now you'll be able
to talk to her
without fainting.
Believe it!
From now on,
it's going to be
the real me all the way.
[LIGHT JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING]
ASTRO:
Ah!
Briana?
[WHISPERING]
Follow me.
I have a little
surprise for you.
Hmm?
Anton, we're not allowed
inside Falcon Two.
It's cool.
Nothing's off-limits
to a future astronaut.
Congratulations!
Congratulations.
Good luck, good luck.
You're number one.
♪ Briana, Briana, Briana! ♪
[GIGGLES]
You really are
a mad scientist.
Just made a few simple tweaks
to the ship's computer.
[ROCKETS FIRE]
[YELLS]
COMPUTER:
Initiate emergency
launch system.
Uh...is this part
of your surprise?
No! I've got nothing
to do with this.
ASTRO:
Anton!
Briana!
COMPUTER:
Autopilot mode
has been activated.
The ship will continue
in a straight course,
awaiting instructions.
Autopilot! Oh, no!
We gotta stop it!
Did you alter
the ship's computer?
A little.
I was trying to add
dancing rosebuds,
and I might have slightly
crashed the guidance system.
COMPUTER:
Impact with the moon
in 10 minutes and counting.
Is this acceptable?
No, it's not acceptable!
Huh?
COMPUTER:
The white button signals yes.
We will continue
on the current course.
ANTON:
Oh, this is not my day.
Astro designed this program.
He's the only one
who can fix it.
Oh, man.
I can't seem to do
anything right without Astro.
I wish he was whispering
in my ear again right now.
What do you mean?
Look, Briana.
All that stuff
I said last night...
That wasn't me talking.
That was Astro.
He told me what to say.
And he wrote the letter too.
I just wanted so much
for you to like me.
So you lied to me?
Uh...
Um...
Briana!
Huh?
Astro!
Anton!
ANTON:
Astro, I'm sorry.
I just meant to change
a few minor circuits.
No. My design was flawed.
It never occurred to me
that the program
might be altered
without addressing
the onboard drive circuit.
I'm going to try to repair
the main drive computer.
[BEEPS]
ANTON:
Astro.
Can't you just push the ship
in a different direction?
It won't work.
The automatic course correction
will just bring it
right back on track.
No response.
I can't stop it.
The escape pod!
No.
The escape pods
and the spacesuits
haven't been
installed yet.
COMPUTER:
Impact with the moon,
three minutes and counting.
Can't you just shut
the computer system down?
No good.
I designed the central processor
to hand over control
to the emergency backup system
in case of a shutdown.
Looks like I outsmarted myself
at every turn.
The perfect system.
Oh, how could I have done
such a foolish thing!
You can't give up.
There must be some way.
This system is a product
of Astro's brain, right?
So--
Astro must somehow defeat Astro.
But how?
Ah! Astro! You become
the backup system.
That's it!
Great idea.
If you can connect
Astro's central processor
with the ship's--
Then the ship's
guidance system
will become part of
Astro's electronic brain.
You ready, Astro?
Okay.
[GASPS]
Whoa!
[YELLING]
[♪]
Oh!
FALCON TWO:
I am Falcon Two.
Identify yourself.
I am--
[GROANS]
Astro's absorbing
masses of data.
I'm not sure
he can take it.
COMPUTER:
Impact with the moon,
30 seconds and counting.
[GROANING]
[WEAKLY]
Briana.
Yes?
Help me. Please help me.
Oh.
Astro, you can do it.
[GASPS]
I am--
I...am...Astro!
COMPUTER:
Ten seconds. Nine...
FALCON TWO:
You are...same.
We are...Astro!
We did it!
Falcon and Astro
are synchronized!
COMPUTER:
Zero. Impact.
Astro, your feelings
for Briana
gave you the strength
to overpower Falcon Two.
Now, that is
major kokoro!
Have a great
flight, Briana.
Congratulations.
They're lovely. Thank you.
You know, you two really
shouldn't have deceived me.
Uh--
We're sorry.
Sorry.
You didn't need
to put on an act for me.
Anton, I liked you for yourself
the minute I met you.
And, Astro, you have more
courage than any human I know.
I guess I should have
had the courage
to just be honest with you.
Now, when I get back,
I want you both to promise me
there'll be no more games.
Deal?
Deal.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Astro, you too.
Whoa!
Time for me to go.
Beyond time, Briana!
ALL:
Yeah! Briana!
[ALL CHEERING]
Well, there she goes,
my one and only.
Oh, we'll
see her again.
Yeah.
And when we do, may the best
man or boy or robot win.
Right.
[ASTRO AND ANTON LAUGHING]
[♪]