[♪]
Where am I?
And who are you?
Uh-- Uh--
Where's Jake?
Where's my father?
This is a hospital,
Hannah.
You were hurt when you
fell down the stairs.
Hannah,
you're awake.
How are you
feeling?
Uh, who are you,
and what are you doing here?
Well, you see,
I'm--
Wait!
Hey! Oh, let go!
Hey, let me
talk to Hannah!
Take him away.
Yes, sir.
Hey!
I need to ask her something
important. It's about Drake.
Mr. Drake,
what did you want to talk to me
in private about?
I have something very important
to show you, General Red.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hmm?
MAN:
Sorry to interrupt you, sir,
but I have an urgent call
from the Metro City Hospital
for the general.
Fine.
Put them through.
Hello, this is
Dr. Reynolds.
I've been treating
General Red's daughter Hannah.
DRAKE: And why are you
calling here so late?
I'm pleased to report
that the girl is now awake,
and so I wanted to notify
General Red
as soon as possible.
That is
wonderful news.
I will let him know
immediately.
Oh, and please, for personal
reasons, the general asks
that you keep this matter
strictly confidential.
Thank you very much.
[CHUCKLES]
BLUE KNIGHT:
We may be robots,
created by humans,
but we were given
hearts and minds,
and we have a right
to live freely on this planet.
We will never forget the cruelty
that we have suffered
under human rule.
The time has come for us
to take our stand
against mankind.
Against mankind?
We declare the birth
of a new nation,
ruled by robots,
where humans
are forbidden.
All salute...
Robotonia!
[ROBOTS CHEERING]
We interrupt our regularly
scheduled blimp-cast.
We have just learned
that the Blue Knight
is trying to create an
independent nation of robots.
ABERCROMBIE: What does
that mean, "independent"?
Well, Abercrombie,
I guess it means
they wanna be
on their own.
There's no way the robots
are going to get away with this.
Yeah, but if anybody
tries to stop them,
there's gonna be
a war.
[ALL GASP]
Hey, Astro?
If humans and robots
end up fighting each other,
what side
are you gonna be on?
I don't know.
GIRL: Astro's our friend.
He'll be on our side.
Right, Astro?
You really think he's gonna
betray the other robots?
GIRL 2:
He better be our friend.
GIRL:
Leave him alone.
BOY:
Why doesn't he answer?
GENERAL RED:
We already knew
that GP-IV models like Jake
were dangerous.
Now we have
solid evidence
that robots with emotions
are a threat to humanity.
That is simply
ridiculous!
You've got it
all wrong.
Have I?
The Blue Knight has already
declared war against us.
What more proof
do you need, doctor?
Nobody declared war,
general.
The Blue Knight
merely announced
the robots' independence
from humans.
Rebelling against mankind
is itself
a declaration of war.
Ah!
Could one small incident
escalate into
an all-out war?
Now try to sleep, Hannah.
You need your rest.
It all started with
a GP-IV robot
that had a grudge
against his owner.
The unsuspecting child
was thrown down the stairs.
She remains
in critical condition.
Thrown down?
But I just tripped and fell.
This horrific event has sent
shock waves through Metro City,
with angry citizens vowing
revenge against all robots.
BOY:
Hey, it's Astro!
Can I shake
your hand?
Sure.
WOMAN:
Stop!
ASTRO: Huh?
Get away from my boy!
MAN: Yeah, leave him alone!
Hands off him!
Who do you think you are?
GENERAL RED:
We must make the public safety
our first priority.
I am calling for
the immediate destruction
of all AI robots.
All AI robots?
You seem to forget
how many times
Astro has saved this city
and its people.
Chairman Lyon,
Mr. Drake has provided us
with some interesting
footage.
Exhibit A will show
another side of Astro.
What?!
Someday soon, robots will
overpower the human race.
Ah! Dr. Tenma!
This battle
will prove Astro's ability
to become the leader
of the new robot age.
COUNCILMAN:
So Astro is their true leader?
Mm-hm.
Tenma's plan
all along
was for Astro to become
the strongest robot on earth.
Because like Dr. Tenma,
Astro wants to destroy humanity.
Wait a minute!
Astro wants to help humans
and robots, not harm them.
As for you,
O'Shay,
you are guilty of hiding
this horrific plot from us.
And therefore you,
like Dr. Tenma,
have betrayed us all!
Congratulations,
my friends.
You are about to begin
a new life of freedom.
Welcome to Robotonia.
SUNDANCE:
Shadow, these guys
seem to be terribly banged-up
over here.
BUTCH:
They should probably be repaired
as soon as possible.
A unified vision
and complete teamwork,
far beyond what the human world
could ever achieve.
Detective Tawashi,
do you actually agree with
General Red's orders?
[SIGHS]
We must obey
whether we agree or not, Delta.
Proceed with the termination
plans as ordered.
NEWSCASTER [ON TV]:
The Blue Knight's actions
are having a ripple effect
throughout the region
as countless AI robots
are leaving for Robotonia.
[SIGHS]
I can't
let this happen.
O'SHAY:
Astro!
Oh, it's Dr. O'Shay.
Astro, Zoran--
The two of you
have to escape immediately.
The robot dismantle squad
is on their way here.
Oh!
Huh?
By authority
of the Federal Council,
General Red has ordered
immediate destruction
of all robots with AI.
Oh!
What?
Delta, how can you stand there
and do this?
No. They can't.
Not to robots.
I won't
let them!
Astro, you must
leave now.
No. I'm not going to
run away, doctor.
Go to Robotonia.
It's the only place
you'll be safe.
But--
But, doctor--
Arrest Astro
and Zoran.
[GROWLS]
Doctor, stop!
Hurry, Astro!
You're the only one
who can save the robots now.
Get out of here
before it's too late.
Huh?
Astro, go! Hurry!
[YUKO GRUNTING]
TAWASHI:
Fire!
Aaagh!
Why didn't you
obey my orders?
I'm not sure.
It must be that I know
in my own heart
that it is wrong.
Delta, you know
I'll have to report this.
Doctor!
[GROANS]
Good luck, Astro.
It's all up to you.
Let's rocket!
GENERAL RED: We have no time
to waste, Chairman Lyon.
Astro is every bit as powerful
as the Blue Knight.
If the two of them
join forces,
the rebel movement
will grow out of control,
and mankind will suffer
the consequences.
All right,
general.
I hereby grant you
full command
of the Ulysses
Armed Forces.
I am honored, sir.
O'SHAY:
Astro has to make it safely.
to Robotonia.
But as long as the police
have us under house arrest,
there's no way we'll know
for sure.
Momo?
Momo, you can
come out now.
[CHEEPS]
Breaking news.
The Federal Council
has named General Red
as commander in chief
of the Ulysses Forces.
The general plans to destroy
the fugitive robot Astro first
before continuing on
to conquer the Blue Knight.
What did he say?
CHAIRMAN LYON:
Without question,
robots have aided mankind
in its productivity
and supported our advancement
from the ocean floor
to outer space.
But now, the robots
have declared independence.
What's next? Taking control
of the entire planet?
This must stop
at once.
MAN:
Shut down the robots
MAN 2:
Kill the robots!
[ALL CLAMORING]
CHAIRMAN LYON: As Chairman
of the Federal Council
I have empowered
the Ulysses Forces
with a strategic
first-strike plan.
[ALL CHEERING]
Direct all squads
to the southern region.
Prepare attack formation.
Our target, Robotonia.
The first Ulysses squad
is moving out
for the initial assault.
Doctor, what if Astro doesn't
make it to Robotonia in time?
He has to.
BLUE KNIGHT:
And so it begins.
The hour of destiny
has finally arrived.
GENERAL RED: Request position
of lead demolition team.
Enemy sighted.
Locking sensors.
Target in range in 18 seconds.
Huh?
It is time.
Time to destroy
those foolish humans.
Blasted robot,
you're scrap metal!
[GUNFIRE]
[GRUNTING]
Hold your fire.
Stop your attack.
Aagh!
[GRUNTING]
Oh!
You can't escape now.
Aaagh! Aagh! Aagh!
[GRUNTING]
It's okay.
I don't think he's hurt.
Thanks.
HANS [ON RADIO]:
Demolition Team One,
do you copy?
Request status
of target.
Uh, target
out of sight.
Repeat, target
Almost there.
Just a little further
to Robotonia.
TENMA:
Astro...
the time has come
to lead the robots.
[SOBS]
Father, you should know
Jake would never hurt me.
[TAPPING]
[GASPS]
What in the world
are you doing out there?
[GRUNTS]
I'm trying to talk
to you, Hannah.
This is really
important.
You gotta
listen to me.
[GIGGLES]
Are you crazy?
I need to ask you
something.
GUARD:
You!
Aagh!
Come down
from there at once.
We have
an intruder.
[GASPS]
Reno's not an intruder.
He's my friend!
Jake didn't push you
down the stairs, did he?
Of course he didn't. I fell down
the stairs because I tripped.
Ugh!
Thank you, Hannah.
Be back to see you soon.
Ha-ha!
Oh! Ooh!
Aaagh!
[LAUGHS]
HANNAH:
Reno!
GUARD:
Stop where you are!
RENO:
Don't think so.
ASTRO:
Hmm. That's strange.
According to
my calculations,
Robotonia should be
right around here.
Uh-oh. It can't be!
HANS:
General, the Field Team
is now within 3 kilometers
of Robotonia.
Maintain speed.
Ready maximum firepower.
Engage the enemy
and fire at will.
BLUE KNIGHT:
Robots, secure battle stations.
Prepare for combat.
ROBOT:
Blue Knight?
Excuse me, but why do we have to
fight against the humans?
We are fighting
for our freedom.
But the humans,
will that really
make them happy
if we were to fight
and win our freedom?
We have
our own minds.
We must consider
our future
and take action
to ensure our own happiness.
BUTCH:
We are hopelessly lost.
Oh, no! We can't be!
I'm too young.
I'm starting to frost up!
[GROWLING]
I told you I didn't want
to go bobsledding.
This is
your fault!
"Just a quick ride
around the glacier."
Why won't you ever listen to me?
Ah-ha-ha!
Now we're
Popsicles.
[CRIES]
BOTH:
Huh?
[BOTH SCREAMING]
Two renegade robots
spotted ahead.
Elimination
in progress.
[SCREAMING]
ASTRO:
Gotcha!
[SUNDANCE SCREAMING]
Thanks, but I had
everything under control.
Yeah, sure.
Anything you say.
HANS: General Red, it looks like
we've located Astro again.
Don't let him
get away this time.
Exterminate
that pest, now!
You two hide here
for now.
Where are
you going?
I have to try to
persuade the humans
to stop attacking.
Persuade the humans?
He must have
a gyro gasket loose.
Ooh! Hmm.
But so do I.
Ha-ha-ha.
Uh-oh.
Hold your fire!
I'm not here to fight.
Ugh!
Oh!
[GROANING]
Stop your attack
and listen.
No one will win this war.
Both sides will suffer-- Huh?
BLUE KNIGHT:
Negotiations are meaningless.
Blue Knight.
Robots versus humans.
One will be victorious,
one will be destroyed.
Huh?
[GRUNTING]
Ah!
RENO:
I need to find Dr. O'Shay
and get him out of there.
Hannah?
Hannah!
Hannah's disappeared.
Find her.
You go round the back!
I'll take this side!
Where did she go?
Huh? Uh, Hannah!
Be quiet.
I need to see Jake.
He didn't do anything wrong.
Reno, can you
help me?
Mm-hm.
Mm.
[YELLING]
Humans, this is
as far as you go.
[YELLING]
MAN:
Look out!
Stop right there,
Blue Knight.
Get out of
my way, Astro,
before I have to
shoot you.
Then fire away.
I came here to stop
all this fighting,
and I am not
about to give up.
GENERAL RED: Don't stop
your cannon fire now.
Lock targets!
Destroy the Blue Knight
and Astro.
[GROWLS]
Aagh!
Is that all the power
you humans have?
Pitiful.
[GRUNTING]
Cease fire now,
Blue Knight.
Aaagh! Aaagh!
Ha!
[CHUCKLES]
[WEAKLY]
Stop fighting.
No one can win.
[GASPS]
[GROANS]
[ALL GASPING]
What on earth
is that thing?
BLUE KNIGHT:
Look closely, foolish humans.
This is
the new world order.
[GASPS]
Robotonia!
[♪]