[♪]
[BOTH GRUNT]
Bull's eye!
[SCREAMS]
We're too late!
They fired the pulsar laser
cannon and destroyed Robotonia!
They're safe.
Huh?
Robotonia survived.
O'SHAY:
What?
DELTA: Right before
the pulsar laser fired,
Astro and the Blue Knight
must have changed its course.
But how'd they do that?
I'm afraid you'll have to ask
Astro that question, doctor.
ASTRO:
Dr. O'Shay!
Astro!
That meddlesome robot
has interfered with my plans
for the last time!
The targeting cylinder on
the satellite is badly damaged.
We'll have to retreat until
it can be fully repaired, sir.
RED: No!
Huh?
We'll crush them with
our bare hands if we have to.
BOTH: Huh?
Stay on course
for Robotonia.
Prepare all laser cannons.
Full firepower!
We're not leaving until
we've destroyed them all!
We have no other choice now.
Their training
is complete.
I have ordered
the robot forces
to mobilize
and prepare for battle.
That time hasn't come yet.
Shadow?
Do we have no other choice
but to fight?
A full-scale assault
is not our only option.
But we have the power.
Attack now and we can secure
a victory and our future.
Blue Knight, there is more
than one future in this world.
I do not understand.
Hate only breeds
new hate.
However, there is still time
to search for the answer.
SHADOW:
I believe we have a guest.
Dr. Tenma,
I have been wanting to meet you
for a very long time.
Oh, but the pleasure
is all mine, Blue Knight.
This storm
is slowing us down.
At this rate, we'll barely
make it to Robotonia.
I hope it's not too late to tell
my father that Jake is innocent.
What's happening?
Shadow,
Dr. Tenma is here.
Welcome to Robotonia, doctor.
Hello, Shadow.
You've performed
even better than expected,
but it's time for you to learn
the real reason I created you.
HANS: Sir, the storm
is intensifying.
It's disrupting
our radar.
Hmm?
[MOUTHING INAUDIBLY]
Dr. O'Shay?
Teach him a lesson
and activate starboard tasers.
Stop this ridiculous attack
on Robotonia!
General, I'm begging you
to stop!
TENMA:
The time has finally come
for robots to take their
rightful place over humans.
Once we have succeeded,
we will need a suitable ruler,
one who possesses
both the wisdom and the power
to lead the robots
in this new world order.
Who do you
have in mind?
Myself, naturally.
However, to do so I must abandon
my human existence
and become a robot.
Once I have shed
my human imperfections
and am then reborn
as a machine,
I will fulfill my destiny
as your eternal leader.
Are you telling me
to transform you into a robot?
That is the real reason
I created you.
You have the ability
to transform me.
This is the moment
I have waited for,
the moment when I achieve
absolute robotic perfection.
There is no need.
What was that?
I'm sorry
to disappoint you,
but Robotonia
doesn't need you.
Doesn't need me?
What in the world
are you talking about?
Of course Robotonia needs me.
[GASPS]
It-- It can't be!
Your desire to become a robot
will never be fulfilled.
They now have me.
This can't be happening!
I have waited
all my life.
Years of
calculated planning!
I am your supreme leader!
You're not supreme.
You're just human.
[GASPS]
I created you.
How dare you stand there
and reject me like this?
How can you?
[SHOUTS] How can you?
O'SHAY:
Delta, force them to stop!
DELTA:
Yes, doctor!
HANS:
They're blocking our path!
Then prepare
the laser cannons.
Sir, there are people
on board.
RED: I don't care.
Yes, sir.
[MOUTHS INAUDIBLY]
What is she trying
to tell us?
Activate
the interface!
Oh! My daughter!
[MOUTHING INAUDIBLY]
[BOTH GASP]
Not you. Just the girl.
You'll be okay
by yourself, right?
Mm-hm.
Hannah!
Father!
I was so worried!
I thought the robots
kidnapped you!
No! You're wrong
about the robots, Father.
They would never hurt me!
Especially Jake.
What are you
talking about, Hannah?
Jake was angry with me so he
pushed you down the stairs.
You know that's
what happened, right?
No, it was an accident.
Jake didn't push me.
I fell down the stairs
because I tripped.
You're just confused,
Hannah.
We'll get you some rest,
and you'll be
feeling better in no time.
Stop! I'm not confused!
Why do you hate Jake
so much, Father?
This is fun!
Hey, wait!
Look at them!
They must have
just hatched.
I know you care for Jake,
but you can't just make up
stories to protect--
I'm not!
Father, you always taught me
never to lie,
but what's the use
if you won't believe me
when I'm telling you the truth?
Father, please!
[SOBS]
I promise I'm not lying
about Jake!
O'SHAY:
General, thank you
for finally believing
that Jake is innocent.
But it's too late.
Dr. O'Shay, these robots
now pose a dangerous threat.
Huh?
So you can't still be planning
to attack Robotonia?
To seek a truce now
would accomplish nothing.
This battle has gone too far.
There is no way to stop it.
You're wrong!
It no longer matters
what started this war.
The only important thing now
is who wins.
[GASPS]
GENERAL RED:
As long as Robotonia exists,
humanity is in danger.
But, Father, what's
going to happen to Jake
and the rest of
those innocent robots
who are still in Robotonia?
Hannah, the only way
to end this war
is to put an end to Robotonia
once and for all.
General,
if we keep fighting,
the humans will certainly
suffer as well.
Of course.
I realize that.
You have to wait until
I talk to the Blue Knight.
Hmm?
Please, general, give me
a chance to go to Robotonia
and try to reason
with him.
What could you possibly do
to make any difference, robot?
I can try to convince the Blue
Knight to put down his weapons
if you and your forces
will guarantee the safety
of all the robots in Robotonia
in return.
Very well.
But if the Blue Knight
doesn't do exactly as you say,
we will resume our plans
for an all-out attack.
And we will be victorious!
COUNCILMAN: Astro?
An ambassador for mankind?
COUNCILMAN 2: What is
the general thinking?
Of all the robots,
we're trusting one created
by that madman Dr. Tenma?
It's absurd!
What can you
be thinking?
We will trust him for now.
Mr. Chairman, are you sure
that it's wise?
General Red is the one
fighting on the front lines.
If he believes that Astro
should be our negotiator,
then the Federal Council
will stand by his decision.
[GRUNTS]
O'SHAY:
Good luck, Astro!
The future of humans and robots
is now up to you.
I see the humans have trained
you to do their work now.
No, it was my idea to come here,
Blue Knight, not theirs.
We must stop the fighting.
SHADOW: The time has come
to prove yourself, Astro.
The world will decide
if you are truly
as exceptional as they say.
We have breaking news.
There are several
new developments
in the Robotonia conflict.
Robot and human forces
have begun to mobilize
on both sides.
Huh?
MAN: Hey, look at that!
WOMAN: It's Astro!
There he is! There's Astro!
Huh? What happened
to the broadcast feed?
Where's that picture
coming from?
WOMAN: I don't know.
It's on all the stations.
Blue Knight,
I know you created Robotonia
so all robots could be free,
and they have the right,
but you'll never find freedom
if you continue to fight.
All you'll create
is more pain and suffering.
We have to stop
hating each other!
We need to work together.
The general will guarantee
the safety of all robots
in Robotonia
if you will put down
your weapons.
Blue Knight!
You want me to surrender?
[SCREAMS]
Astro!
[GRUNTS]
Please, Blue Knight,
try to trust humans
before it's too late.
As long as
intelligent robots exist,
humans will continue to fear us
and try to destroy us.
Either humans or robots
will have to disappear
from the earth.
And it will not be us!
Both the humans
and robots will suffer,
but the humans have caused this
and we have no other choice.
We will win our freedom
once and for all.
We'll all lose.
You must listen to me!
[GROANS]
[ROARS]
No!
Astro!
Huh?
Atlas!
I know why you're fighting,
Blue Knight,
but it's not worth it!
Pluto?
Astro is our friend.
I cannot make him my enemy.
HERCULES: Pluto, now is not the
time to fight among ourselves.
But I will always be
on Astro's side.
HERCULES:
By negotiating for the humans,
Astro chooses
to be on their side.
So if you're joining him,
then you are now our enemy.
[SIGHS]
Huh?
[SOBS]
Take a good look at this,
Blue Knight!
If this is the family
of a wounded soldier,
they'll blame robots,
all robots, forever,
because we chose to fight.
Look at this battlefield.
See the destruction
that's already been caused?
Is this what you wanted?
Hercules!
Rabia!
Atlas! Pluto!
When are we ever going to stop
fighting each other?
Astro's right!
Does anyone really think
that hurting each other
will bring us true happiness?
Blue Knight, a lot of humans
still believe in robots.
I know they do.
We can live peacefully
together.
A world with no war.
Oh, that's the future
I believe in.
If humans didn't want us here,
they wouldn't have created us.
But as we've become
more and more like them,
some humans have gotten scared.
Now it's up to us to show them
they have nothing
to be afraid of.
We can be friends.
Jake, where
are you going?
Home to be with Hannah,
where I belong.
What are you
talking about?
The humans will catch you,
and you'll be dismantled!
BUTCH:
You know, he's right for once.
He may be, but I am choosing
to go where I am happiest.
And that means
being with Hannah.
I know what I must do.
I'm going home.
But--
I too have wonderful memories.
I'm worried about my family.
ROBOT: They're my friends!
ROBOT 2: I want to be with them!
Jake, wait! I'm coming too!
HERCULES:
What are they doing?
[GASPS]
Blue Knight, I have great
respect for you and your cause,
but I do not wish
to fight the humans.
I am returning home
to my family.
HANNAH:
Jake!
Hannah!
Oh, Jake!
What in the world
are you doing here, Hannah?
HANNAH:
Jake, please forgive my father.
Please forgive
all of us humans.
KENNEDY:
Astro did it!
[ALL CHEER]
All right! Whoo-hoo!
Release all of the captured
robots. Send them home.
CREWMAN:
Yes, sir.
Do you think they'll ever
try to dismantle us again?
Only one way
to find out.
BLUE KNIGHT: It appears
there are other robots
who share your belief
in a peaceful future.
But there is more
than one future, Astro.
What Shadow said is
finally starting to make sense.
I don't understand.
Blue Knight!
Where are you going?
Come with us!
I will depart with the robots
who remain in Robotonia.
We will find our own future.
What do you mean,
"your own future"?
Shadow, I now understand
your words!
It's time for us to carry out
your ultimate plan!
Huh?
Whoa!
[GASPS]
Robotonia. It looks like...
some kind of spacecraft!
The Blue Knight thought
he needed a backup plan,
so he secretly constructed
a gigantic ship.
A flying city?
Yes.
He and the remaining robots must
be planning to leave the Earth
and search for an ideal homeland
somewhere off in outer space.
COUNCILMAN:
Chairman Lyon!
Should we authorize an attack
against their ship?
Robotonia no longer poses
any threat to humanity.
The war is now over!
Welcome, Pluto, Atlas.
Goodbye, Blue Knight,
and good luck.
Huh?
What is that?
They're only leaving
to strengthen their forces.
Then they'll return to Earth
to exterminate mankind!
We cannot let them escape!
[ASTRO GRUNTING]
ASTRO:
Must...stop it!
Huh?
[THUNDEROUS RUMBLING]
[GASPS]
Astro!
[ALL SCREAM]
[SOBBING]
It can't be.
No, Tobio!
I have already
lost you once before.
Please...
do not leave me again.
[♪]