[♪]
[PANTING]
Miss Hannah,
what's the hurry?
Jake's in the garden.
Miss Hannah, wait!
Oh! I hope her father
doesn't find out.
Jake!
Hey, Jake!
Oh.
Good afternoon,
Miss Hannah.
I want to help you
water the flowers.
Please, do not--
It's okay.
Oh.
Look at all
the pretty flowers.
I wish I could spend all day
in the garden with you, Jake.
Do not neglect
these flowers over here.
Okay.
Thank you for helping today.
What is going on here?
Huh?
JAKE:
Oh! General!
How many times
do I have to tell you
to stay away from
my daughter?
I am sorry, sir.
No, Father.
I wanted to help Jake
in the garden.
Robots are not
your friends, Hannah.
They are not like
you and me.
They are only tools
that work for humans
and nothing more.
Jake is not
a tool, Father.
He is my friend,
and he keeps me company.
He's here for me
whenever I'm lonely,
much more
than you ever are.
[GASPS]
Oh!
FEMALE BUTLER:
Oh, general, you're home!
Take Hannah
into the house.
Yes, sir. Come on--
No! I don't want to!
HANNAH:
I want to stay with Jake!
Father, don't
blame Jake, please!
I see that
in spite of my orders,
you still spend time
with Hannah.
Please, sir--
But that all ends now.
Tomorrow you will start
your new job
at the Waste Disposal
Treatment Center.
Pack up your belongings
and leave this house tonight!
Yes, sir.
Goodbye, Miss Hannah,
my friend.
Jake!
Miss Hannah.
Where are you going?
[GASPS]
What's this flower for?
From now on, you will
take care of it for me.
It's my father.
He ordered you
to leave, didn't he?
I'm sorry.
I'm going to talk to him.
Miss Hannah!
Miss Hannah,
please wait!
Don't do this!
Aaah...!
Miss Hannah!
Aaah!
What's going on?
[GASPS]
Hannah!
Hannah! Hannah!
Wake up!
Ugh...
Why won't she
wake up?
Miss Hannah.
[GRUNTS]
GENERAL:
Jake!
What have you done?
But, sir, I didn't--
Stay away,
robot!
You've done enough
already.
But-- But, sir, it was
just an accident, sir.
GENERAL:
Hannah! Hannah!
NEWSCASTER:
Last night, a young girl
was injured
at the hands of
a GP-IV model robot.
Hmm.
The girl has been identified
as the daughter
of General William Red,
a high-ranking member
of the Metro City
Armed Forces.
Doctor--
This must be
some kind of mistake.
The GP-IV model robot suspect,
known as Jake,
worked for the general
at his home
for the past
two and a half years.
According to hospital reports,
the young girl
is still unconscious
but in stable condition.
Oh, that is
just terrible.
Robots should never be
trusted with children.
Dr. O'Shay asked me to organize
the data on GP-IV robots,
but where
do I begin?
Miss Yuko!
Reno, I take it
you saw the news?
There's no way that robot
attacked a human.
It's against
his programming.
I know. Dr. O'Shay and Astro
are looking into it.
I'm going too.
Reno!
DR. O'SHAY:
Detective, I insist
you check these accusations
thoroughly.
Don't worry, O'Shay.
I'm on it.
Jake's upset.
I'd wait until he calms down
before you talk to him.
Don't tell me
how to do my job.
MAN:
Detective Tawashi.
BOTH:
Huh?
DR. O'SHAY:
Chairman Lyon?
What are you doing here?
Don't tell me--
There will be
a formal hearing
at the Federal Council
this afternoon
regarding this incident.
Formal hearing?
That's right.
We believe a public hearing
would be the best course
of action in this matter.
But I'm in the middle
of my investigation.
A waste of time,
detective.
Jake has already been entrusted
to the Council's care.
REPORTERS:
Chairman Lyon, Mr. Drake--
Oh, no.
REPORTER:
This is the first time
a robot will be put on trial.
How will it be conducted?
Naturally, it'll be a fair
and objective trial,
even if he is just a robot.
MAN:
This is outrageous.
Get back!
[CROWD SHOUTING]
Grrr. Jake!
Jake!
Reno!
You didn't really
hurt Hannah, did you?
Gotcha!
Leave me alone!
But I would never
hurt her.
POLICEMAN:
Keep moving.
Tell me,
how is Miss Hannah?
Has she woken up yet?
Reno!
Astro, Jake's
telling the truth.
I am positive
he didn't hurt Hannah.
I believe him too.
GENERAL:
Hannah, open your eyes.
General Red.
Mr. Drake,
Chairman Lyon.
I hope you don't mind,
but we thought
it would be a good idea
to see your daughter
with our own eyes
before the trial begins
this afternoon.
Um--
General, has her condition
improved at all?
I'm afraid not,
and the doctors aren't sure
how much she'll remember
once she wakes up.
DRAKE:
And, of course,
there is the possibility
that she will remain
in a coma forever.
If that happens,
I don't know what I'll do.
You see,
this is my fault.
I brought that miserable robot
into my home.
CHAIRMAN LYON:
General...
I will make sure Jake gets
suitable punishment
for what he has done
to your daughter.
I promise.
Thank you.
[♪]
After reviewing
the evidence presented today,
we believe that Jake
did not want to be transferred
to a new job,
and he intentionally hurt
the general's daughter
in an act of vengeance!
DR. O'SHAY:
Wait! Mr. Chairman!
You must allow Jake
to speak for himself.
The GP-IV model robot
possesses advanced
emotional capabilities.
COUNCILWOMAN:
Objection!
If he possesses
advanced emotional capabilities,
he also possesses
the ability to lie.
How can we trust
anything he says?
Doctor!
This court has found that there
is not one shred of evidence
that proves
Jake's innocence.
For the sake of
our peaceful society,
we must remove all robots
with violent tendencies
from our communities.
The court hereby sentences Jake
to be fully dismantled.
BOTH: Huh!
Huh?
[COUNCIL MEMBERS APPLAUD]
MALE NEWSCASTER:
Well, there you have it.
This historic trial
has come to an end.
So this is
what humans call justice.
REPORTERS:
Chairman Lyon! Chairman Lyon!
Do you have anything to say
about today's decision?
Once Hannah wakes up, we'll know
exactly what happened to her.
My judgment is final.
Now, robot, if you're really
as smart as they say,
stay out of this.
Mr. Chairman--
Please, wait!
I can't believe
this is happening.
DRAKE [ON TV]:
This is just the beginning.
Listen to me.
All GP-IV model robots
have the capacity
to turn against humans.
The next time,
it could be you.
The GP-IVs appear to be
loyal workers to you and me,
but behind their gentle faces,
they harbor feelings
of anger and resentment
toward all humans.
And just like Jake, they can
suddenly lash out at us
at any time.
Mark my words.
These robots are lethal weapons.
My baby!
Madam--
Stay away!
[♪]
Reno?
Astro.
What did you wanna
show me?
Take a look.
ASTRO:
What's going on?
RENO:
Rumors are flying
all over the city.
People think the GP-IVs
will revolt tonight in revenge
for what happened to Jake.
Huh!
Who started that?
I don't know.
But now that Chairman Lyon
and Mr. Drake
started working together,
no machine is safe.
They won't stop
until every robot in Metro City
is dismantled.
[CROWD SHOUTING]
[METAL CLATTERS]
[CAT SCREECHES]
Oh, no.
[CHUCKLES]
Like I've always said, a little
paranoia goes a long way.
Now, Kato, all we have to do
is stoke the fire.
Yes, sir.
With pleasure.
[EXPLOSION]
[CROWD SHOUTING]
[♪]
It's the robots!
He-- He's right!
We've got you now.
Let's destroy them!
Let's go!
Yeah! Get them!
This is bad, Astro.
That mob
has got to be stopped.
I'm on it!
Don't let those robots
get away!
Stop it!
Leave them alone.
They didn't hurt you.
Move it, Astro.
Stay out of our way.
DELTA:
That's enough!
You humans have caused
enough trouble for one night.
You can't order us around.
You're just another robot.
Come on. Let's go.
[ASTRO GROANS]
Aagh!
You guys aren't
going anywhere.
MAN:
Stop it, kid!
MAN 2:
Whose side are you on anyway?
Robots aren't the enemy.
Come on, you.
Hey!
Oh, hey!
Put me down!
Oh, Reno!
MAN:
Come on!
Let's go!
[GROANING]
Reno, are you okay?
I tried to
stop them, Astro.
I tried.
Reno.
Please help! We're trapped!
MAN: Ha-ha!
We've got you now.
We'll teach you robots
what happens
when you mess
with humans.
Yi-yaaagh!
Stop!
Aaagh!
Ugh!
Oh!
Aaagh!
Huh?
What's that?
The Blue Knight.
Now I will teach you
what happens
when you mess with robots.
Astro?
Leave now.
MAN:
Uh, guys? We gotta go!
Blue Knight!
Astro, why do you not
use your powers
against the humans?
How many innocent robots
must be destroyed
before you see
that man is the enemy.
[GASPS]
BLUE KNIGHT:
Open your eyes.
If you cannot fight
by my side,
then you are nothing
but a traitor to me.
[GROWLS]
MEN:
We're under attack!
Run!
Now, what on earth
is going on here?
SHADOW:
An age of change
is upon us.
It's been a long time,
Dr. O'Shay.
Uh, Shadow!
The robot scientist
created by Dr. Tenma!
What are you doing here?
SHADOW:
I'm the one who brought
the Blue Knight
into this world.
Huh! It was you?
SHADOW:
Yes.
Under Dr. Tenma's orders.
He hoped the Blue Knight
would help Astro evolve.
But instead, the Blue Knight
started to follow
his own agenda.
His own agenda?
SHADOW:
The Blue Knight
believes in robots
while Astro
believes in humans.
They will not stop
until they've destroyed
each other
and everything
around them.
MALE NEWSCASTER: In response to
last night's large-scale riot,
the Federal Council
has issued a recall
of all GP-IV model robots
due to programming defects.
In addition,
the Council
has granted authorities
the right to destroy
any GP-IV models
that do not cooperate.
Huh! This is bad.
Set a perimeter around the city
so no GP-IV robot can escape.
Does everyone
understand?
ALL:
Yes, sir!
Delta, I'm putting you
in charge of this operation.
I cannot...do this.
That is an order.
Now get to work.
Detective!
How could you
let this happen?
Those robots haven't
done anything wrong.
I thought
you'd understand.
Astro, since your friend
the Blue Knight
attacked those men
last night,
the entire city
is up in arms.
But it's just
not fair!
There's no other way.
I must do
whatever it takes
to put the minds
of our citizens at ease.
My only priority
right now
is to make this city
safe again.
[ASTRO SIGHS]
Now, go home,
Astro.
There's nothing
you can do here.
You're wrong.
Robots have emotions too.
Have you considered
their feelings?
The GP-IVs
have done nothing wrong
and now they face
being dismantled.
And that's not all.
What about the other robots
all over the city
that have to stand by
and watch their fellow
machines be destroyed?
What about
their feelings?
Have you thought about that,
Detective Tawashi?
[GROANS]
[CROWD MURMURING]
If you ask me,
they're all evil.
They're up to no good.
Down to their very last bolt,
you can't trust them.
That's the last
of them, sir.
What's the matter?
They can't do anything right.
Delta, you okay?
DELTA:
I used to be proud
to be the captain
of this squad.
I used to think that
we protected a society
in which both humans
and robots could live.
But now, what
have we become,
sending these robots
to their destruction?
ROBOT:
Mr. Delta?
We understand that
you are just doing your job.
But if you refuse,
they will send you away
to be destroyed
like the rest of us.
So please,
close the container door.
[GROWLS]
Not a single defect can be found
in the GP-IV's programming.
Chairman Lyon,
you're making a huge mistake.
I beg you, please,
do not go through with this.
You can beg
all you want, doctor,
but I assure you
that it won't do any good.
Reno!
Reno?
Huh?
This is the same hospital
where Hannah's staying.
Huh! Reno.
[DOOR OPENS]
Reno.
I wish Hannah
would wake up
and tell everybody
what really happened.
RENO:
Things have changed so much
in the last
couple of days
At least in her dreams,
she's still with Jake.
Astro, are things ever
gonna be the same again?
REPORTER:
As you can see,
the defective GP-IV model
robots are being transported
to a robot dismantling plant
just outside of Metro City.
[GROWLS]
WOMAN: Yeah!
MAN: Take them apart.
WOMAN:
We don't need them.
Get rid of them.
MAN:
Get those robots
outta here.
WOMAN:
Do it!
My only priority
right now
is to make this city
safe again.
Astro, you are nothing
but a traitor to me.
[BRAKES SQUEAL]
Huh?
TAWASHI:
Astro?
I can't let you
do this, general.
Until now,
humans and robots
have been able
to live together in peace.
Astro--
ASTRO:
But this will change everything.
Can't you see this is wrong?
Don't stop.
General! Astro--
I said don't stop!
[ENGINE ROARING]
[ASTRO GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
Astro!
Riot Squad, come in.
Do you copy?
GENERAL [OVER RADIO]:
Destroy Astro!
Aaagh!
[GASPS]
ASTRO:
It's the Blue Knight.
Ha!
Whatever you do,
don't let them take the GP-IVs.
Aaagh!
The Blue Knight
has struck again,
attacking the trucks
carrying the captured
GP-IV robots.
BLUE KNIGHT:
My fellow machines,
let us rise up
against the humans
and finally be free.
Delta, don't just
stand there.
Aaagh!
Say goodbye, humans.
Blue Knight!
[GROANING]
Astro!
Blue Knight!
You cannot hurt them.
I will show you
no more mercy.
[GASPS]
Aaagh! Aaagh! Aaagh!
Detective,
what's happening?
They've got
the trucks.
[GROANING]
Tonight, we take control
of our destiny.
Tonight,
we are free.
BLUE KNIGHT [ON TV]:
Robots everywhere, unite.
The revolution
has begun.
Huh?
Aah!
Aagh! Robots!
Ugh! Blue Knight!
[MOANING]
[GASPS]
Where am I?
It's a miracle.
You woke up.
I'll get the doctor.
POLICE BULLETIN:
Robots have rebelled
against humans.
For your safety,
stay inside
and lock your doors
and windows.
Robots?
Jake?
It can't be.
Hannah, you're awake.
What happened?
Do you know Jake?
Where is he?
Hannah...
Jake.
Jake!
POLICE BULLETIN:
The Federal Council
has declared
a state of emergency.
All robots should be considered
armed and dangerous.
[♪]