[♪]
KISAGARI:
Bright lights, big city,
old story.
Hatchling, fresh off the farm,
wants to spread her wings.
Drawn to Metro
like a duck to water.
Folks at home worried sick.
That's where I come in.
Name's Kisagari.
I'm a detective.
Hmm?
There, that's a ducky.
Another dead end.
Hmm.
The old MetroWorld
Amusement Park.
Shuttered up years ago.
Just a wild goose chase.
I'll find you yet.
You're a wily bird,
I'll give you that.
But now you're matching wits
against Kisag-g-g--
[SNEEZES]
Gotta get out of
this night air and into--
MAN: ...hot water with
the old lady.
MAN 2: Why is she
so mad at Norton?
He quit his job.
Swears he was attacked
down in the sewer by a ghost.
And he's not
the only one.
I heard it's been haunting
all the tunnels around here.
They also say,
first you hear a sound
like the rustling
of wings.
Yeah, the only sound
Norton heard
was the cuckoo clock
ringing in his head.
Cuckoo! Cuckoo! Cuckoo!
[RUSTLING]
BOTH:
Huh?
You hear something?
Like rustling wings?
[EERIE MOANING]
[ROARING]
[BOTH SCREAMING]
That ain't
no cuckoo bird!
ALEJO:
Did you see the news?
More workers were attacked
in the tunnels last night.
Ghost isn't just angry,
it's hungry.
If it finds you, you're lunch!
Not me.
I'm too bony.
Chill out,
you guys.
I bet Astro could knock
that ghost out with one punch.
So how about
it, Astro?
Up for a little extracurricular
ghost-busting this afternoon?
That sounds great.
All right!
You in, Abercrombie?
Sure. I'll watch
Astro's back.
But I can't.
ALL: Huh?
It's just that Dr. O'Shay has
a superimportant mission
for me to do today.
ALL:
Ohh!
No problem.
We can even go
without my brother.
Huh?
Too bad. Astro could've
shown that ghost who's boss.
Maybe another day.
ZORAN:
Hold it!
I said I'd bust
the ghost with you.
We'd have no chance without
Astro.
Yeah. We're not
superheroes, Zoran.
I am.
Upgrades?
ZORAN: So I can be
like my brother.
A whole new Zoran.
I wanna fly and breath fire and
be twice as strong as Astro.
Breathe fire?
Hmm.
All heroes need
cool signature moves.
So, Zoran, why all this sudden
desire for more powers?
It's not fair!
Why should my brother
be the only one
who gets to save the day
all the time?
But you have to understand,
you're truly wonderful
in so many other ways.
ASTRO: Doctor.
Huh?
I drained the radiation
from the power modules
I removed from
the downed robots.
And in the nick of time.
Nice work, Astro.
Mmm!
Huh?
Astro! Astro! Astro!
Hmm!
Hey!
What's eating
Zoran?
Astro,
it will pass.
How soon?
[SQUAWKS]
Momo!
Doctor, trouble. Another
six robots have gone down.
This is really getting
out of hand.
Yuko, can you pull up the video?
We should see this.
YUKO: On it.
ASTRO: It's like an epidemic!
We have to
find the cause!
I'll show them
who's tough!
When I take down that ghost,
they'll beg to hang with me.
Now, if I were a ghost,
where would I cry "boo"?
Where I'd get a good echo!
[SQUEAKING]
[YELLS]
[PANTING]
It's safe to come out now,
Mr. Ghost.
I've scared away the rats!
Oh, every robot knows
there's no such thing as ghosts.
Who am I kidding?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
Huh?
A ghost! Ahh!
[YELLS]
KISAGARI: I just had
this suit dry-cleaned.
And I think I broke
my tailbone.
Then you're really
not a ghost?
Almost, thanks to you.
O'SHAY:
People are getting worried.
Soon we'll have a real panic
on our hands.
Yes, but the good news
is Momo's found
what's been causing
all the robot shutdowns.
Look.
Oh, no, it's
detecting IS-13!
Yuko, IS-13
comes from Dexanol-G,
that toxic chemical used in
old robot energy modules, right?
Ah-huh, and it's
the same type of poison
that those horrible Repo Girls
released into Dragon Lake
when they were
illegally dumping there.
That is, until you
stopped them, Astro.
Hmm.
So obviously,
somewhere around here
something has been
leaking toxic waste.
Hmm. Wait!
Huh?
What's wrong, Astro?
For a moment, the whole city
seemed to bend and warp.
YUKO:
Astro's right.
Space itself has become unstable
around here.
I believe a large quantity
of toxic waste
has been dumped
into hyperspace.
Weakening the fabric
of space-time.
If this gets any worse, we could
be facing a catastrophic--
ASTRO:
Dimensional collapse!
O'SHAY: It could
tear our world apart.
[ALL LAUGHING]
KISAGARI: Oh,
you've never heard of
Wally Kisagari,
world-famous detective?
ZORAN:
No.
[SNEEZES]
So why are you
looking for a duck?
Because she's missing.
And you should know
many people recognize me
by my handsome profile.
Hmm. So do detectives
catch ducks to eat them?
Wait a minute, kid.
So you're telling me you
don't know what a detective is.
Mm-hm.
YUKO: Doctor, I've detected
a familiar energy signature
coming from
the dimensional warp.
The wormhole
projector.
Hmm.
O'SHAY: For an invention with
so much potential to do good,
it seems someone always
finds a way to misuse it.
We have to find
the criminals at once, Astro,
and stop them
from transporting
any more toxic waste
into hyperspace.
Got it.
King of the world!
Whoo-hoo!
ZORAN:
Oh, I get it.
So detectives make their
living collecting trash?
That's not trash.
Those are my files.
A good detective knows
everything about a case.
What's this?
Don't touch it!
[SCREAMING]
[COUGHING]
Do you have any idea how long it
took me to organize those files?
You're like a one-robot
demolition squad.
I'm sorry.
Hopeless!
You're right.
I am hopeless.
I'm not like my brother
Astro at all.
Your brother Astro?
You mean, you're
Astro's little sister?
Oh, everyone knows
about my brother.
Well, I taught him everything he
knows about being a detective.
Yes, sir, Astro's
one heck of a robot.
[LAUGHING]
Everyone likes Astro
better than me.
Well, there's
certainly nothing wrong
with trying to be
like your big brother.
He's a pretty
amazing robot.
Why does everyone
say that?
"You should be
more like Astro."
Well, no one tells Astro
to be more like me.
KISAGARI: So humans and robots
aren't so different after all.
I'll fix this.
Why are you
just sitting there?
Detective Kisagari and Detective
Zoran have a ghost to bust.
Really? What about your files?
Don't worry about them.
You did me a favor.
I never could find anything
in all this junk anyhow.
ASTRO:
This is bad!
That toxic energy
coming from the space warp
is messing up my search systems.
I'd better tell Dr. O'Shay.
KISAGARI: Pay attention, kid.
You're learning from the master.
Now we'll get to the bottom
of this ghost business.
It sure looks like the right
kind of hang-out for a ghost,
but what makes you think
it'll show up in this tunnel?
Take a gander.
These red dots are the tunnels
where it's been spotted.
I did some legwork and guess
what I found at every scene,
old broken holo-projectors
That's what's behind
this whole ghost scare, you see.
So you mean somebody's using
a hologram projector
to make this ghost appear?
There's an old saying, kiddo,
crack open a mystery and
you'll find the truth inside.
It's all a scam,
and here's the proof.
This is the only
tunnel left
with working
holo-projectors in it.
If I'm right,
Mr. Scary-Pants
should put in an appearance
before too long.
Now we just wait...
for our very
punctual ghost.
[BOTH SCREAMING]
[ROARING]
Thanks for helping me
and all, mister,
but we busted it so we can
just go home now, right?
It's just a holographic
projection. It can't hurt you.
Watch.
♪ Scaredy-ghost
Scaredy-ghost ♪
♪ Who's the one that's
scared the most, you are ♪
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
[ROARING]
It's almost like
he really heard you.
State-of-the-art graphics.
Still, why take chances?
Huh?
Zoran, run!
Come on, kiddo. Come on!
We've gotta make tracks
before it eats us.
This ghost, it's trying
to tell us something.
Yes. It's saying,
"You look tasty."
Can't you hear it?
It's so sad and trying
so hard to talk to me.
It sounds sad to you?
Sad or not,
that thing's dangerous,
and we're getting
out of here now.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
You're not afraid of that thing?
Hey, hey! you got
a screw loose or something?
Tell me, what do you want
to say to me?
Your world is
coming apart at the seams.
Yeah. That sounds bad.
Doctor, the warp in space
is spreading really fast.
Did you find anything yet?
According to
my calculations,
we have only one hour
till total dimensional collapse.
You must find
the wormhole projector
and reverse the effects
of the damage before then.
Right. Let's rocket!
Stop them.
They must not dump
any more
dangerous materials
into hyperspace.
Tell us, where do
we need to go?
Here.
Hmm? That's
the old amusement park.
[BOTH SCREAMING]
KISAGARI: Well, we're here.
Now what?
The ghost said the world
was about to fall apart.
There's some sort of awful
secret hidden around here.
Huh?
ZORAN:
After that ghost,
a haunted house
isn't spooky at all.
I've seen
that light before.
I think it's
coming from in here.
KISAGARI:
Aha!
This light is leaking out
from something down below.
So we're
going down too.
But how?
Follow me.
[BOTH SCREAMING}
Huh?
Oh.
Oh, okay,
that was scary.
Anyway, let's find a way down.
Hold on!
Well, I guess it's faster
than the stairs.
ZORAN: What is
this place?
KISAGARI: It reminds me
of a dream I had
after eating
too many sloppy joes.
ZORAN: You sure have
weird dreams.
Kid, you don't know
the half of it.
Do you feel that? It's like some
kind of really weird energy.
I think it may be
toxic industrial waste.
Why is it
all here?
SARA: Because this
is where we work.
Who's there?
[REPO GIRLS LAUGHING]
Three simple businesswomen
out to make an honest buck.
ALL:
The Repo Girls.
You know, it's rude to
drop in on people unannounced.
As you see, we're really not
set up to entertain company.
Just what kind
of sleazy racket
are you ladies
running here anyway?
Sorry, but we have to
get back to work.
King Nagha can keep you company.
Ahh!
No thanks!
But he's
very talented.
King Nagha, show our guests
what you can do!
[BOTH SCREAMING]
I just detected the wormhole
projector being activated.
No good,
I can't get an exact fix
because of the effects
of the dimensional warping.
Where's it sending
this stuff, huh?
Hyperspace.
There's no limit
to the amount
of dangerous waste
we can dispose of.
No fuss,
no muss.
If you keep this up,
the world's gonna fall apart.
This is what the ghost
warned us about.
Ghost? Oh, you met our friend.
You're behind that too?
I'm not surprised.
When we first activated
the projector,
we transported a robot which
hadn't completely shut down,
along with an unlucky duckling
that happened to fly in here.
Did you say duckling?
CHRIS:
It seems that during transport,
the robot and the duckling
bonded together
at the molecular level
creating that creepy ghost.
KARLA: The robot was
an old road maintenance bot
so it can synchronize
with the frequency
of the holo-projectors in
the tunnels in order to appear.
Now, if you'll excuse us, we
have toxic waste to transport.
But the ghost said
it would be dangerous
to transport any more trash
into hyperspace, so don't!
We don't work
for the ghost.
The people we work for
pay us a lot of money
to dispose
of this toxic stuff.
Besides, old junk
has to be thrown away
to make room for new junk.
You can just think of us
as responsible citizens
doing out part to protect
the environment.
[LAUGHING]
Crazy ladies!
I'll put a stop to you
if I have to pull that thing
apart with my bare hands!
Be careful!
[SCREAMING]
That does it!
Nobody messes with my friend!
Nagha, show the girl
you want to be her friend too.
[GROANING]
[SCREAMING]
If you like the ghost so much,
maybe you'll enjoy living
with him in hyperspace.
[REPO GIRLS LAUGHING]
Enough!
This is no place
for you. Run!
Astro wouldn't run
and neither will I
because I am Astro's sister.
Don't argue with me, Zoran!
Astro, help!
That voice, it's Zoran!
Time to go. Bye-bye.
Zoran, don't look, kiddo.
ASTRO:
Hold it!
ALL:
Huh?
Go, bro! Go, bro! Go, bro!
At last, the star of the show.
Pick on this!
Now I just connect
this to this and--
Hold it, Astro.
You aren't reversing
the projector, are you?
[SCREAMING]
[ALL GASPING]
[ALL SCREAMING]
Hey, my duck! Hah!
Be careful!
KISAGARI: Hey,
come back here!
Stop!
Gotcha!
[ALL SCREAMING]
So what are the odds
our probation officer
will overlook
this little slip-up?
[HEADS LAUGHING]
Astro! I wasn't scared.
I know you weren't, sis.
VOICE: Zoran.
Huh?
Thank you for listening
to our message.
Quack, quack,
quack.
Oh, you don't have to thank me,
little friend.
I'd say the whole world
owes you thanks.
Quack.
Oh, you agree with me,
do you?
ZORAN: You can
understand him, mister?
KISAGARI: Sure. After cat, duck
is like a second language to me.
[ALL LAUGHING]
In light of what happened,
I spoke to Zoran
and I offered
to upgrade her.
Yeah? What did
she say to that?
She said,
"No, thank you."
That even without
fire-breath,
she knows she's pretty special
just the way she is.
So I ended up solving
the whole case all by myself.
Guess who's
top robot now.
Me.
You know, talking to animals
is a pretty cool power.
Maybe I need
an upgrade.
Now, don't you start.
[KISAGARI SNEEZES]
That brother and sister are a
couple of good kids, er, robots.
Meow! Meow!
[YELLING]
[♪]