[♪]
MAN [ON RADIO]:
The majestic peak of Mount Elbe
rises to over 3000 meters
above sea level.
According to legend,
its giant snowcap
is home to a ruthless monster
that devours any creature
that crosses its path.
Indeed, several witnesses
lately have reported
seeing some kind
of monster
near the infamous peak.
Oh, my gosh.
ASTRO:
Well, if they're really
going to look for the monster,
maybe I could join
the search party.
Astro, you know
there's no such thing
as monsters.
It's probably AR-1,
the observatory robot
that disappeared
from the snowcap
12 years ago.
Cool.
Tell me more!
Well...the Chronos Project
was a very ambitious undertaking
that began years ago
on Mount Elbe.
You know, Yuko,
we probably still have
some of that footage.
Eh, Yuko?
Uh, right away, doctor.
[BEEPING]
DR. O'SHAY:
They established an observatory
and equipped it with Galileo,
our latest
plasma-wave telescope.
They were hoping to observe
the Chronos star system
deep in space.
There are 200 billion stars
in our galaxy.
Approximately
750 million of them
are surrounded
by planets.
But we believe
the Chronos system
to be the one
most like our own.
In fact,
we may find a planet
and inhabitants there
just like on Earth.
So the observatory on Mount Elbe
was built to search
the Chronos system
and perhaps find
extraterrestrial life,
which of course
would be--
ASTRO:
Out of this world!
DR. O'SHAY:
The robot AR-1
was dispatched to the snowcap
to manage the observatory.
However, six months later--
Both AR-1 and the telescope
just vanished into thin air.
When the investigation team
got there,
the base was wrecked,
and there was no sign of AR-1.
They concluded that
the observatory
had been destroyed
by a terrible avalanche.
And with
the Galileo telescope gone,
the Chronos Project
was cancelled.
But I've heard
they are sending out
another investigation team
to the snowcap.
I'd like you to send me
to represent the Ministry.
But you shouldn't go
to the snowcap.
There could be another
dangerous avalanche.
Astro, if we find AR-1,
we can really determine
what happened 12 years ago.
I don't care
about the danger.
I need to find out
the real truth.
Hmm.
All right, Yuko.
If you really want to
join the team, then you will.
But, doctor!
Thank you,
doctor.
Momo.
I just
don't get it.
Doctor, why did Yuko
get so upset
when you mentioned
the Chronos Project?
I'm afraid you will have to ask
Yuko that question, Astro.
Regardless, please keep
a close watch on her.
Of course.
YUKO:
It's the steepest mountain
in the entire range.
Guess that means
no snowboarding.
Huh?
You must be here
representing the Ministry
of Science.
Yep.
Then you may
have heard
of the world-renowned
planetologist Dr. Bruder.
He'll be leading
our expedition.
Hmm.
My name's
Astro.
I am Yuko Kisagari.
How do you do?
Kisagari?
[GASPS]
Huh?
Don't you even try
getting in the way
of our investigation.
YUKO:
Well, that was rather cold.
[ENGINES FIRING]
Oh, my.
Here's the wreckage
from the avalanche.
If AR-1 had
activated the
defense shield
when the avalanche
occurred,
none of this
would have
ever happened.
That robot belongs
on the scrapheap.
ASTRO:
Something doesn't add up.
How did an avalanche
from the peak
make it all the way
to the observatory?
Once it reached the edge
of this flat plane,
it should have
stopped.
[EQUIPMENT TRILLS]
Huh?
I'm getting a reading
from the energy scanner.
[PULSING]
[RAPID BEEPING]
Who else could it be
all the way out here but AR-1?
We should have expected
the Ministry of Science
to find him
in record time.
Okay,
Astro.
We're going to need you
to lead us
where you think
AR-1 is.
No time to waste.
Got it.
[YUKO PANTING]
ASTRO:
AR-1!
Ugh!
[WHIRRING]
[RAPID BEEPING]
A little recharging
and a thermo-boost,
and he'll be
good as new.
Okay, snowman,
time to wake up.
AR-1, say something
to us!
Huh?
[PANTING]
Oh!
Shackleton.
[POWERING UP]
BOTH:
Hmm?
Are you Shackleton?
That's what people used to
call you years ago.
Am I right?
Yes. My name is Shackleton.
I can recharge
his energy
and just wait here
with him until he's ready.
He can't seem
to access his memory.
But with an overhaul
from the Ministry of Science,
he'll be back to
his old self.
Astro,
I sure hope so.
What is it?
He and I spent
much of my childhood
together.
After Shackleton
disappeared,
my father was never
quite the same,
right up
until he died.
But why did it
upset your father so much?
Astro, my father
was Richard Kisagari.
He was the planetologist
in charge
of the entire
Chronos Project
12 years ago.
Huh?
DR. BRUDER:
"Memory temporarily
unavailable"?
Thing's not even worth
the metal it's made of.
Everything recorded
before the avalanche
is inside
that robot.
No reason to waste our time here
if we can't get the data.
Somehow I've got to
take ownership of that data.
Once I publish it,
my name will be frozen
into scientific history.
It won't be if those two
manage to take him back
to the Ministry of Science
and make all that data
a matter of public knowledge.
I know that,
you egghead!
[CHOKES]
[SIGHS]
I've had a bad feeling
about this
ever since Kisagari's
daughter showed up.
Hmm, how am I going to get
inside of Shackleton's head?
[GROANS]
Shackleton.
Don't try to
move too much.
Just relax.
Has any more
of your memory
come back?
[SPEAKING INAUDIBLY]
[GROANS]
What's wrong,
Shackleton?
DR. BRUDER:
Well, well.
There you are.
ASTRO:
Looking for us?
No, just Shackleton,
actually.
We need to do
a little brain surgery.
Hey, what do
you mean?
You can't remove
the chip in his brain.
He'll lose all access
to his memories.
He's just a robot.
You can install
a new memory chip
and he can start learning again
from the beginning.
A robot's memories
are more than just data.
Well, I must admit,
I'm intrigued
by your sentimental respect
for a machine,
though I'm not surprised,
since you are a Kisagari.
The fact remains that memories
don't belong to the robot.
They're the sole property
of its human owner.
Since Shackleton
originally belonged
to the Comparative
Planetology Society,
I'll take possession
of that memory chip.
Freeze! You're not laying
a finger on Shackleton!
Guess I'll have to
convince you otherwise!
[YUKO SCREAMS]
Let go of her!
[SHACKLETON GROANS]
[MOANS]
[POWERS UP]
Leave her alone!
Ugh!
Shoot that worthless robot!
Arggh!
YUKO:
Astro!
Yuko, run for it!
Shackleton!
Ouch! Arggh!
[PANTING]
Shackleton, come on!
[VEHICLE IGNITION FIRES]
BOTH:
Ugh!
A crevasse!
Oh!
[SIGHS]
ASTRO:
Yuko!
Stop! The engine's smoking.
Look behind you!
Are you sure
you're all right?
Considering I almost exploded,
I'm fine.
Yuko, I'd never
let that happen
to you.
I know.
Thank you, Astro.
Hmm.
[LAUGHS]
Ah!
BOTH:
Huh?
I once knew
a young girl who looked
just like you.
That young girl was me.
I'm grown up now.
Oh?
Shackleton,
I need to fill you in.
I don't believe it.
I have lost 12 years?
The observatory gone?
The Galileo telescope too?
But most important,
Dr. Kisagari.
Shackleton.
He is part of
my permanent memory.
Mine too.
I can still see him
in my mind.
It's very sad when people
you care about go away,
but their memories give you
the strength to go on.
It does get easier.
The memories are like yesterday.
DR. KISAGARI:
This is Galileo,
the first and only
plasma-wave telescope
in the world.
And you're going
to take charge
of the telescope
all by yourself,
Shackleton?
Yes.
You'll do fine,
Shackleton.
I'm absolutely
sure of it.
Yes, doctor.
Soon you'll be observing stars
that no one on this earth
has ever seen.
For centuries, astronomers
have gazed upward
and dreamed
of finding intelligent life
somewhere in
the distant universe.
Now, my friend, it's up to you.
How exciting is that,
Shackleton?
SHACKLETON:
I was so proud.
I was carrying out
mankind's dream,
to search for life
beyond our world.
But--
Shackleton?
This doesn't match
any of my logic structures.
How could Galileo
be lost?
Shackleton.
Tell us what really
happened here
on the day
of the avalanche.
[WHOOSH]
Huh?
Blue light in the sky.
SHACKLETON:
Oh, no.
I've seen that before.
We've got trouble.
[WHOOSH]
Hey, w-what was
that sound?
Maybe it's the snowcap monster
coming to eat us.
That's a superstition.
Now, find another route
and catch those three!
[WHOOSH]
MAN:
Arggh! The monster!
Stop!
Wait a minute!
Stop right there!
[PANTING]
Doctor,
what should we do?
Well, we're not
giving up.
ASTRO:
It's piezoelectricity.
Ground shifts here
can cause
an electrical discharge
and an avalanche.
But because
of all the vibrations,
the avalanche will keep going
when it hits this flat plane.
It's the dead hollows.
ASTRO AND YUKO:
What?
That's what's causing
the vibrations.
This mountain has empty spaces
called dead hollows.
The greenhouse effect
of the last century
has melted the ice layer
creating these empty
tunnels.
When the wind blows
through the dead hollows,
it creates a strange sound
and causes the mountain
to shake.
That sound must be
what they call
the monster's roar.
[GASPS]
Huh?
We must go
and dig up Galileo.
Galileo?
The telescope was not destroyed.
It is safe.
How do you
know that?
I did not use the defense shield
on the day of the avalanche
because I had to
protect Galileo.
[CIRCUITS BEEP]
My disaster simulation
program determined
that Galileo would be damaged
even if the shield
were used.
I chose to sacrifice the base
to protect Galileo.
Then I used the defense
shield's power to melt the ice
and store the telescope
safely underwater.
I knew that the water
would cushion the telescope
from the shock
of the avalanche.
YUKO:
You mean Galileo
is here somewhere
in a hole
covered by ice?
If an avalanche hits it
this time,
it will be
demolished!
I protected it here.
[WHIRRING]
[RAPID BEEPING]
There it is!
[RUMBLING]
Huh?
Avalanche!
Get it quick, Astro!
You can do it!
I can't melt the ice
with my digibeam,
or it will destroy Galileo.
But, Astro,
we're so close to it now.
All their hard work:
we can't let it be destroyed.
And we won't, Yuko.
My father died
before getting a chance
to witness the data
from his plasma-wave telescope.
The only way
to continue
his research is to
save Galileo.
I'll have to stop the avalanche.
SHACKLETON AND YUKO:
What?
I'll block
the dead hollows.
If I get rid of the vibrations,
the snow should stop moving.
The avalanche
will reach this point
in 4 minutes
and 12 seconds!
Shackleton, tell me,
where are the dead hollows?
Yuko, you must
leave now!
But, Astro...
[PULSING]
SHACKLETON:
There are four dead hollows
in all.
One of them is on the north face
of the mountain,
89 meters up,
17 meters eastward.
Ugh!
[GROANING]
SHACKLETON:
The next is 92 meters down,
40 meters west.
Now go to the south face,
down to the foot
of the cliff.
There are two there.
[GRIMACES]
SHACKLETON:
Astro,
the far end of the last hollow
is still open.
Huh?
I've got to
save them!
We'll be
human icicles!
[WHIMPERS]
[BOTH SCREAM]
Oh?
BOTH:
Are we really flying?
SHACKLETON:
Astro, where are you?
Nineteen seconds to go.
Here it comes!
ASTRO:
Gotta fly...faster!
[GASPS]
Good shot!
It's not
stopping!
[SIGHS]
Congratulations, Yuko.
You did it!
Astro.
ASTRO:
Well, we got Shackleton
and Galileo back.
Guess we can resume
the Chronos Project.
I will continue my work
until my task is completed.
Dr. Kisagari sent me
on a mission to
fulfill a dream.
He knew he could
trust you.
Yes.
SHACKLETON:
We must keep alive
the dream of finding
other life in the universe.
We owe that
to Dr. Kisagari.
YUKO:
Yes.
We do.
[♪]