[♪]
TENMA: Tobio, I have already
lost you once.
Dr. O'Shay, Astro's
gonna be okay, isn't he?
O'SHAY: I certainly
hope so, Zoran.
[GRUNTS]
Okay, let's try again.
A week has passed
since Astro was taken
to the Ministry of Science
after the incident
in Robotonia.
There has been no word
on his condition
or if he can be repaired.
Zoran.
Don't worry.
Astro will come home.
Mm-hm.
Come on, Astro!
You can do it!
[GRUNTS]
This time it's got to work!
[GASPS]
[SIGHS]
We've done everything
we possibly can,
and he still won't wake up.
Astro, please come back to us!
NEWSCASTER:
The Ministry of Science
has issued a statement.
After several attempts,
they still have not
been able to revive Astro.
[CACKLING]
Dr. O'Shay can try all he wants,
but I assure you,
Astro will not be restored.
Now is the perfect time to rid
the world of AI robots forever!
We must not let
this opportunity slip away.
WOMAN: Mr. Drake,
on behalf of my colleagues,
I'm sorry to say
that you're
on your own this time.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Watch this!
NEWSCASTER:
Choosing to leave Robotonia,
the robots returned home,
and people welcomed them
with open arms.
OLD MAN:
The Robotonia incident
brought humans and robots
closer together.
Rather ironic,
wouldn't you say?
Wait! Don't go!
Don't you see?
If anyone
were to find out
that we were
associated with you,
we'd be branded
as outlaws.
They'll...be sorry.
SHADOW:
Soon we'll find a place
we can call home.
Shadow, what do you think
Dr. Tenma will do
if Astro cannot be restored?
Tenma's a madman.
He'll find a way
to bring Astro back.
And when he does,
Astro will have to face
his greatest challenge of all.
BLUE KNIGHT:
And what would that be?
SHADOW:
His father.
O'SHAY:
Please forgive me, Astro.
I've done everything
in my power.
Forgive me!
[WHIMPERS]
TENMA:
Dr. O'Shay.
You seem to be
at an impasse.
Tenma!
Only I have the data
to bring Astro back to life.
If you want to see Astro again,
you will do as I say.
[GROWLS]
[BEEPING]
Hmm.
O'SHAY:
Huh?
This... This is...
Tell me, Tenma.
Will you really
help Astro,
or is this another one
of your tricks?
There are no tricks,
only conditions.
Conditions?
The restoration work
will be done
in my laboratory,
by myself.
Alone.
And once Astro
has been fully restored,
you will say nothing
of my whereabouts.
So do we have a deal,
Dr. O'Shay?
[GROWLS]
All right.
You have my word.
Excellent.
Then leave Astro.
I will make contact with you
in one month.
Tobio, come back to me.
Dr. O'Shay, why is it taking
so long to fix Astro?
Please, give us
a little more time.
The Ministry of Science
is doing everything in its power
to make sure that Astro
is fully restored.
[SIGHS]
YUKO:
Are you all right?
You're awfully quiet,
doctor.
I just hope I did
the right thing, Yuko,
handing Astro
over to Dr. Tenma.
I know, but you had
no other choice.
Tobio.
You will be reborn.
And this time
I will not make
the same mistake
as when I first created you.
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
ASTRO: Where-- Where am I?
O'SHAY: Whoa!
Ooh! Ow! Ow! Oh! Oh.
[GROANING]
ZORAN: Doctor,
did you forget
how to use the stairs?
No, Zoran.
I'm just in a hurry.
This is
an exciting day.
It's Astro.
That's right. Dr. Tenma
contacted me this morning!
[SQUEALS]
I have to get ready!
Ha! Ha!
We'll have a party!
Zoran,
the party can wait.
Right now,
let's go get Astro.
Mm-hm.
ZORAN:
Dr. O'Shay...
do you think
Astro will remember me?
Do you think
he missed me?
Ha, ha, ha! Of course
he'll remember you, Zoran.
What in the world
is going on?
TENMA:
Dr. O'Shay. Welcome.
O'SHAY:
Dr. Tenma, what have you done
to this place?
Why have you gone
to all this work?
BOTH: Huh?
Ah!
Hi, everybody!
Ah! Astro!
[SQUEALS AND SHOUTS]
Oh, thank goodness
you're back!
[GIGGLES]
Stop it!
I'm sorry,
sir,
but who are
these people?
What did you say?
It's nice to meet you.
My name is Tobio.
[BOTH GASP]
Uh, Tobio?
TENMA:
You heard him.
He's Tobio.
No, he's not!
You're not Tobio!
You're my brother, Astro!
"Astro"? Who's that?
And who are you?
[WAILS]
How can you forget me?
I'm the only sister
you've got!
Tenma!
You've erased
Astro's memories,
haven't you?
I knew I never should
have trusted you!
It's getting late.
I think you
should leave now.
Let's take Astro back
to the Ministry of Science.
His memories
can't be lost forever!
See if he wants
to go with you.
Go ahead. Ask him.
You bet I will!
Astro, are you
ready to come home?
Mister, I don't understand.
This is my home.
Oh, no!
Ooh! That's it!
You're coming with us now!
Oooh!
We are leaving!
[MOANS]
[SCREAMS]
O'SHAY:
Zoran, we can't force him
to come home
if he doesn't want to.
But--
I know what you're thinking.
However, for now we must
respect his choice to stay here.
O'Shay, I have kept
my promise.
Now you must keep yours.
Yes, I know.
Doctor, let's talk
to Detective Tawashi
and have Tenma arrested
for kidnapping.
I can't.
As a condition
for saving Astro,
I gave Dr. Tenma my word
that I would not tell anyone
where he lives.
But--
O'SHAY:
We have to find
another way.
Well, so when in the world
is Astro gonna come back?
Dr. O'Shay said that he's
doing everything he can.
ZORAN:
Hey, you guys!
ALL: Huh?
I need your help
to rescue Astro. Please!
ALL:
Rescue Astro?
Mm-hm.
TENMA:
Tobio...
we are going to spend
so much time together.
We can go
camping and fishing,
and nobody will bother us.
I promise.
Oh! I got a bite!
[GROWLS]
It looks as if the virtual
machine is not working.
We're finished
for today.
Hmm.
Oh!
Wait, Father!
I just remembered
something.
Remembered?
Yes.
You and I really went
to a river just like this
once before,
didn't we?
Yeah, I know we did.
That's right.
You tried to scoop up
the fish
that was on my hook,
but--
W-w-whoa!
--you slipped and you fell
into the water.
ASTRO:
Don't you remember?
You're confused, Tobio!
Tobio.
You must not think
of unnecessary things.
This house is all the world
you and I need now. Understand?
Yes, Father.
Hmm.
That's a good boy.
[INTERCOM RINGING]
KENNEDY: Zoran, you sure
this is the right place?
ZORAN: This is definitely
Dr. Tenma's house all right.
We should check it out
just to be sure.
ZORAN:
Wait!
If we go
to the front door,
he's not going
to let us see Astro!
Then we need to sneak in
from the back!
Come on!
BOTH: Mm-hm.
[GROWLING]
[YELLS]
[ALL SHRIEKING]
[PANTING]
Hold on! Somehow we got to
get Astro to come outside.
Hmm...
I have an idea.
[BAND PLAYING UPBEAT MUSIC]
Oooh!
WOMAN:
Ooh, my!
ALL: Waaaah!
ALL: Whoa!
[KIDS YELLING OUTSIDE
Huh?
TENMA:
Tobio!
What have I told you?
I do not want you to concern
yourself with the outside world.
Um...
Yes, Father.
[LAUGHING]
I've found you.
ALEJO: Okay.
If we can't rescue Astro
from the ground,
then we'll just rescue him
from the sky.
[LAUGHING]
Great idea, Alejo.
This is a Quadra-Glider, Zoran.
Astro is one of the founding
members of the Sky Riders.
The Sky Riders?
KENNEDY:
That's right!
Once Astro sees the flag
of the Sky Riders,
he's got to remember us!
Yeah, it's got to work!
Now, let's go!
ALL:
Astro, here we come!
Hmm.
ZORAN:
Astro!
ALEJO:
Hey, Astro!
Wow.
What is that thing?
KENNEDY:
Astro! We came to rescue you!
You've got to
get out of there!
You're being held prisoner
by a lunatic!
Huh? What are they
talking about?
Astro, we're your friends!
Don't you remember?
Friends.
TENMA:
Tobio!
[GASPS]
[GROWLS]
Don't you see?
I will not let anyone
interfere with my plan!
[ALL GASP]
KENNEDY:
What is that?
Whoa!
Oh, man!
That's Quake,
the largest manned battle-bot
in the world!
Astro, I will crush you,
if it's the last thing I do!
[BARKING]
DRAKE: Get out of my way,
you robo-mutts!
Don't play stupid, doctor.
You're not fooling anyone.
I know you're
hiding something,
so why don't you
tell me
before I have to take you
down to the station!
Detective, uh...
Look, I don't have all day.
Now, where is Astro?
I'm waiting.
YUKO: Emergency call
for Detective Tawashi.
Sir, we've got a situation.
Somebody's stolen Quake
and is destroying
everything in its path.
Wait a minute!
That looks like Section K220!
[ASTRO GASPS]
[CACKLING]
We have to do something!
Okay, we have to get
that thing's attention!
DRAKE:
Astro! Tenma!
You two aren't
getting away this time!
ALL: Attack!
I'll teach you brats
to mind your own business!
Huh?
Let's rocket!
Tobio, no!
[ALL SHOUTING]
Astro!
Not so fast, Astro!
Way to go, Astro!
[ALL CHEERING]
[LAUGHS]
Get your stinking
hands off me!
I'm no criminal!
It's gonna be good to finally
see you locked up, Drake.
What?
Take him away!
The robots!
They must be destroyed!
Every last
one of them!
ASTRO:
So...
all of these pictures
are fake, aren't they?
Because I'm
just a robot.
Oh, no, you are
more than a robot!
You are Tobio!
What about my memories?
W-w-whoa!
Are you all right, doctor?
Thank you, Astro.
My name's not Tobio,
is it?
It's Astro!
No!
No! No! No!
You are Tobio!
You will always be Tobio!
Dr. Tenma.
Dr. O'Shay.
TENMA: What are you
doing here?
We came to take Astro
home with us.
Ready?
ALL: Astro!
Aha!
ASTRO:
Zoran! Alejo!
Kennedy!
Abercrombie!
Miss Yuko!
[SQUAWKS]
ASTRO [CHUCKLING]:
Momo!
And Dr. O'Shay.
How could I ever forget?
[O'SHAY LAUGHING]
We missed you.
Huh?
Where is
Dr. Tenma?
YUKO: He's right
over here...
Huh?
YUKO: Well, he was here
just a minute ago.
[PLAYS DARK EVIL MUSIC]
[YELLS]
I won't... I won't give up!
Tobio is mine!
It is time to move out,
my loyal robots.
All systems
are back to normal.
Thank you, doctor.
[ALARM BLARING]
We've got a security breach!
Robot dogs.
Hundreds of them!
And they're headed
for the lab!
Huh?
Arggh!
[LAUGHING]
[SCREAMS]
TENMA:
It is time to settle this matter
once and for all!
[♪]