[♪]
[HORSE NEIGHING]
ASTRO:
So.
Who's
this Blue Knight guy?
DELIVERY ROBOT:
He's a robot.
But that's all
anyone knows.
There have been some rumors
going around, though.
W-what rumors?
Well, you didn't hear it
from me,
but I heard
the Blue Knight secretly
attacked a robot transport boat
in the middle of the night
and then took out an entire
shipping warehouse.
WOMAN:
Still behind me, huh?
DELIVERY ROBOT:
You don't want
to be on his bad side,
because the Blue Knight
will take on anyone, anywhere.
Sounds like this guy
is a big bully.
No.
He's fighting to save robots
that are being mistreated
by their masters.
He doesn't care what laws
he has to break either.
Whatever you do,
don't try to stop him.
WOMAN:
Target sighted.
Astro!
MAN [OVER RADIO]:
Initiate transformation.
[GIRLISHLY]
Help me!
[GASPING FEARFULLY]
Help me! Help me!
[GRUNTS]
Oh?
Help me!
What's the matter?
The Blue Knight!
He's chasing me.
The Blue Knight?
Where?
Up there. There!
Wow! That must be him.
[SIREN WAILING]
[HORSE NEIGHING]
Oh!
I'll go up there and--
No, don't.
It's all right now.
You've saved me.
I've been reading
all about you in the papers.
You're a real hero.
I'm grateful to you.
Oh, I didn't do anything.
Well, you're a hero to me.
Please, let me
shake your hand.
I'll never forget this, Astro.
You're incredible.
Astro, you fool.
If only everything
was this easy.
MAN: You sound
a little worried.
Worried?
Yeah.
Not afraid of that big blue guy
on the horse, are you?
Quiet! The Blue Knight
doesn't scare me.
I've handled robots
that were worse than him.
MAN:
Katari!
It is extremely important to me
that the Blue Knight doesn't
find out about our plan.
He could ruin everything.
Do you understand that?
Yes.
Completely.
Very good.
Now I'm almost ready to put
Project Mach Fifteen in motion.
And once I do, there won't be
time for these petty arguments.
If this project's a success,
the world will be
a much different place.
Because there won't be
any more of those obnoxious
robots around to question us!
CAPTAIN [OVER SPEAKER]:
I want to thank you all
for flying
on the Mach Fifteen today.
Right now,
we're passing over
the brand-new
Sonic Shuttles Launch Center.
And if you look to the left,
you'll see the Green Glade
housing development,
where new homes
are priced very reasonably.
Ah! Oh!
Cocoa, sir?
Sure.
When do we arrive?
Our estimated time of arrival
is half an hour.
Perfect.
I'll make the conference
with plenty of time
to spare, hmm?
MAN [OVER RADIO]:
Hello!
August City
Airport Control.
WOMAN [OVER RADIO]:
I advise you
to listen very carefully.
MAN:
Who is this?
Please identify yourself.
Ma'am, I repeat, who are you?
WOMAN:
Enough. Pay close attention.
There's a wormhole projector
on the Mach Fifteen--
What? A wormhole projector?
Oh, no.
A thing like that
could send
the Mach Fifteen
into another dimension.
It could.
But how do we know this nutcase
is telling the truth?
Hey, give us some proof here.
You want proof?
Just look out your window.
[GULPS]
MAN:
Wow! What's that up there?
[HIGH-PITCHED WHIRRING]
Mach Ten! Mach Ten!
Come in! Come in!
Al,
it's all right.
It's being repaired.
There was nobody onboard.
WOMAN [OVER RADIO]:
That was just a demonstration.
But we'll do the same thing
to the Mach Fifteen
and all its passengers
unless you give us
everything we ask for.
We'll contact you again soon
with our demands.
Listen, lady.
When the police find out
who you are,
you're going to be
in big trouble.
The police can't do
anything to me.
DETECTIVE TAWASHI:
Two wormhole projectors
were stolen from
the university last week,
so she means business.
If the Mach Fifteen
changes course or altitude,
she says the projector
will activate.
And another thing.
There's a huge storm brewing
right in Mach Fifteen's path.
You all have to
get to the Mach Fifteen
before it hits that storm.
Find a way in
and then dismantle
that wormhole projector.
POLICEMAN:
Inspector! Look at the monitor.
We're being signal-jacked.
Huh?
[STATIC CRACKLING]
We are
the Robot Liberation Army.
Huh?
We put the wormhole projector
on the Mach Fifteen.
[ALL GASPING]
I have a horrible feeling
about this.
Our demands are simple.
Every robot is to be set free
from its owner
immediately.
Or we'll activate
the wormhole projector
and that will be the end
of the Mach Fifteen.
[GASPS]
She'll pay for this!
[ALL MUTTERING]
The Robot Liberation Army
has the support of the world's
most powerful robots,
including the greatest
of them all,
Astro.
[GASPS]
That's a lie!
I've only met her once.
ASTRO:
She asked me for help!
WOMAN:
Astro has assured us
we will succeed.
Astro?
MAN 1:
I was afraid this would happen.
MAN 2: See what happens
when you give them kokoru?
Well, for sure,
you can't trust a robot.
Astro's betrayed
everyone who's ever helped him.
He's living proof
that robots can't be trusted.
DRAKE [OVER TV]:
We humans need to mobilize
before it's too late.
Stand up! Fight the robots!
Eliminate all of them.
Otherwise they'll take over,
and we'll be serving them!
MAN [OVER AIRSHIP INTERCOM]:
Detective Tawashi!
We've located Astro
and are in pursuit.
I'm sorry
about this, Astro.
But I've been ordered
to drain your energy.
This is all a mistake.
I should be helping those people
on the Mach Fifteen.
Don't you worry
about the Mach Fifteen.
We're sending a rescue team
up there to help them right now.
And it's going to be
a human rescue team.
No robots allowed.
You just rest
right here, Astro.
But wait!
Detective, wait!
[GROANING]
Huh...
NEWSCASTER:
There have been
dozens of anti-robot
demonstrations already.
And more
are reportedly planned.
That's perfect!
Guys, let's go.
Get rid of that overgrown
marionette for me.
MAN:
Yes, sir!
It's all your fault
for making those robots
in the first place.
Now they're trying
to take over the world
and your little Astro
is right in the lead.
Oh! Calm down, sir!
Huh?
MAN:
Back off, robot!
Are you all right?
You should be
ashamed of yourself.
She didn't do
anything to you.
And Astro hasn't done
anything to you either.
You're right. He hasn't
done anything to me.
And I'll make sure
he never gets the chance.
[ASTRO GROANING]
If-- If I had more energy,
I could help all those people.
[ALARM WAILING]
Huh?
ASTRO:
Blue Knight!
I am not your enemy, Astro.
I came here to help you.
[GRUNTS]
All the energy you need
is in there.
The choice is yours.
[ALL GRUNTING]
That--
That was the Blue Knight!
COMMANDER [OVER RADIO]:
Airship Mach Fifteen!
This is the air police.
This is airship Mach Fifteen.
Hurry! Please! We're headed
right for the storm.
COMMANDER [OVER RADIO]:
Unit Two. Status report.
PILOT [OVER RADIO]:
This wind's
going to make it hard to
transfer to the Mach Fifteen.
So, what are we going to do?
PILOT: Commander,
somebody's closing on us fast.
COMMANDER:
Who?
PILOT:
It's--
It looks like Astro
and the Blue Knight.
CAPTAIN [OVER RADIO]:
Now we're in real trouble.
Look out.
Huh?
Blue Knight! On your left!
Be careful!
[SHOTS FIRING]
PILOT [OVER RADIO]:
Astro and the Blue Knight
are headed towards
the Mach Fifteen.
MAN [OVER RADIO]:
Not for long.
Locked on target.
COMMANDER [OVER RADIO]:
Careful now!
[MAN YELLING]
No! Whoa!
[YELLS]
We're losing power in our
portside antigravity engine.
Activate auxiliary engines!
Maintain altitude!
Somebody tell me
what's going on up there.
PILOT [OVER RADIO]:
Commander!
Look up ahead.
The storm clouds.
COMMANDER:
I have never seen
so much lightning.
CAPTAIN:
No way to avoid it now.
COMMANDER [OVER RADIO]:
Rescue team, pull back!
What's happening?
We're going
right into the storm.
Astro!
I can't believe
you're here.
[ALL MURMURING]
Everybody, listen!
The Robot Liberation Army
doesn't exist.
It's just a trick by some people
who hate robots.
Now it's all starting
to make sense.
We have to find that wormhole
projector right away.
Why should I believe
any of this?
You're just
a stinking--
[YELLS]
Oh!
[ALL SCREAMING]
WOMAN:
What's happening? Oh, no!
WOMAN: Everyone,
please calm down.
There's no reason
to panic.
Go back and fasten
your seat belts.
FEMALE FIRST OFFICER:
Temperature rising
in starboard engine.
Do what you can
to keep it running.
Captain!
Is there any sign
of the wormhole projector?
No. We couldn't find
a trace of it.
Doctor?
Maybe it's on
the outside of the ship.
Hmm.
O'SHAY [OVER RADIO]:
Astro, can you hear me?
Use your spectra-graphic
vision, but be very careful.
If that projector
is activated--
ASTRO:
There!
Huh?
I've found the projector,
doctor.
O'SHAY:
Good work, Astro.
DRAKE: So, Astro.
You've found the device.
I have a feeling
you're going to wish you hadn't.
[GROANING]
[ELECTRONIC RINGING]
Huh?
Oh, no! It's set to activate
if it's removed!
Great job, Astro.
Now throw it!
[GRUNTS]
[GRUNTING]
Oh, no! It's the wormhole!
We're being pulled
into the wormhole!
[GROANING]
[ALL SCREAMING]
The ship's
going to disintegrate.
[GROANING]
[GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
We got to keep it
from going into the wormhole!
[GRUNTING TIREDLY]
[ASTRO AND BLUE KNIGHT GRUNTING]
It should be okay now.
But we have to get it
to the airport right away.
Huh?
The controls
are barely working now.
What's the matter
with them?
There was too much damage
from the wormhole.
We're losing power.
[WOMAN YELLS]
All engines are down!
O'SHAY [OVER RADIO]:
Astro! We've lost power.
You've got
to keep us in the air.
[GRUNTING]
I'm running out of energy!
There may not be time.
If we can't make it
to the airport,
we'll just have to find
somewhere else to land.
ASTRO:
There! That's Highway Five.
It has a 3-mile straightaway.
It just might work!
ASTRO [OVER RADIO]:
Drop your landing gear,
captain.
It's going to be a bumpy ride.
You got it.
Argh! I can't hold on!
We're going to hit
those energy lines.
[ELECTRICAL WHINING]
[ELECTRICAL FIZZING]
[YELLING]
Oh, no!
We can't even
see the runway!
Astro, are you okay out there?
So far!
O'SHAY [OVER RADIO]:
Can you use your searchlights?
ASTRO:
No. They're giving out on me.
BLUE KNIGHT:
Here.
I'll light it up.
[GRUNTS]
Uh, looks like
we're going to be okay now.
Drop the emergency gear.
FIRST OFFICER:
Roger.
CAPTAIN:
And tell the passengers
to brace themselves.
[ALL SCREAMING]
There's no way out.
We've got to turn this thing.
Captain, sharp left!
I'll try.
[PASSENGERS WAILING]
Huh? We've stopped.
[TWITTERING]
Argh!
I can't
believe it.
PASSENGER:
Oh! They did it! It's over!
[ALL CHEERING]
PASSENGER:
The robots saved us.
PASSENGER 2:
Whoo!
DRAKE:
We can't do anything right!
We may not be stronger than
the robots, but we are smarter.
And we are not giving up.
ASTRO:
Blue Knight,
without your help,
none of these people
would be here right now.
[ALL CHEERING]
BLUE KNIGHT:
I didn't do it for them.
You didn't?
I did it for the robots.
Especially the ones
the humans mistreat.
Astro,
do you really think
humans and robots can someday
stop all their fighting
and work together?
I really do.
Even after humans caused
all this trouble for you and me?
Uh...
Yeah, I really do
believe in them.
Who built you, anyway?
Someone who's very committed
to the future of robotics.
[DELICATE CHIMING]
Hey! Here comes the rescue team.
Come on.
Huh?
Where did he--?
Oh!
O'SHAY:
Hey! Astro!
We're
down here!
Doctor!
Ah! I'm so glad you're
all right. I was worried!
Huh?
Where did
the Blue Knight go?
I have no idea,
but I bet he'll be back.
O'SHAY:
He is quite a mystery, isn't he?
ASTRO:
Not to me.
[♪]