[♪]
--proving that robots can
yodel with the best of them.
Now, Dr. O'Shay,
are you saying robots
like Astro
will soon be as common
as DNA rechargers?
Not quite.
But robots
with kokoro,
or the human-like emotions
that Astro has,
are becoming more
and more prevalent.
These feeling robots
are capable of filling jobs
in nearly every profession,
with the possible exception of
politicians and lawyers, ha-ha.
Speaking of which, doctor,
we've heard that you're
currently working on
a brand-new kokoro robot.
O'SHAY:
Yes, it's true.
And it will be a special model
with some
very unique abilities.
ASTRO:
I have a sibling?
Should I have it removed?
YUKO:
Ha-ha-ha. No, Astro.
It means
you have a little sister.
You'll see. Dr. O'Shay
just finished building her.
I'm taking you
to meet her now.
Awesome.
My very first relative.
Now, be patient
with her.
She might be
a little shy.
O'SHAY:
Ow!
Let go! Aah! Aah!
Ha-ha-ha!
ASTRO:
Stop that!
Hey! Stop it!
Cut it out!
[WHIMPERING]
I'm sorry.
Please don't cry.
But you were hurting
the doctor.
I know it's hard to believe,
but that is his real nose.
No way.
It used to be.
Well,
humans are different.
Their parts
don't unscrew.
Astro, this is your
little sister, Zoran.
Nice to meet you,
Zoran.
I'm your big brother,
Astro.
Big brother? I'm Zoran!
Nice to meet you, nice to
meet you, nice to meet you,
nice to meet you,
nice to meet you...
BOTH: Ha-ha-ha.
Zoran isn't as powerful
as you, Astro,
but she has
a special ability.
ASTRO: She's annoying?
Hmm...
Aah!
Hey! Come back,
birdie!
Uh-oh.
Better catch her, Astro.
ASTRO:
I'll head her off.
Perhaps we should
follow them, doctor.
No, let's let Astro
deal with her.
I think learning
to look after a sister
can be an important lesson
for both of them.
After all, Astro's capable of
battling megabots and meteors.
He should be able to handle
his own sister.
Uh, I hope.
ZORAN:
Gangway!
Yah!
Ha-ha!
Hey, watch it.
Oof!
Sorry.
Please excuse her. Sorry.
Whoa!
ZORAN:
Ooh.
[ZORAN LAUGHING]
Hot dogs! Get your hot dogs
right here. Big and juicy.
Zoran!
Huh?
VENDOR:
Hey you, kid!
Bring that back!
Grrr.
Sorry.
ZORAN:
Wow! Ooh!
Hee-hee-hee.
Whee! Huh?
Oh.
Ohhh.
[WHIMPERING]
Hey, he's alive. Huh?
Oh, no.
Why are
the birds all scared?
ASTRO:
Zoran!
Zoran.
Oh, hi, big brother.
Boy, for a little kid,
you sure can run.
Hey, what happened
to the bird?
I don't know.
I think he bumped into
the other birds and fell.
Gee, he sure does like to eat,
doesn't he?
I guess that means he's
feeling a little better, huh?
Isn't that right,
Houdini?
That's his new name.
'Cause he appeared
out of nowhere.
Just like magic.
All right, everyone,
time to get ready for bed.
Okay, Nora.
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Watch this, brother.
Zoran!
Beds are not for jumping.
No?
No, and starting tomorrow,
I'm gonna have to
teach you some manners.
[BELCHING]
ZORAN: And I'll teach you
how to jump
on the bed.
[HOUDINI CHIRPING]
Huh?
What's wrong, Houdini?
[CHIRPING]
[WHIMPERING]
ZORAN:
I swear it's true.
A big, humongous,
gigantic robot bird.
Did I mention
it was big, huh?
See, Zoran,
that's what's called a dream.
"Dream-shmeam."
Are the birds dreaming too?
Houdini says they're all
leaving the city
because they're
afraid of the monster.
Ha-ha-ha!
Are you saying Houdini
spoke to you?
Well, he might not
use real words,
but I can understand
what he's feeling.
Astro.
Huh?
Dr. O'Shay
called.
He said he needs you right away
at the Ministry of Science.
All right,
got it.
Zoran, you stay home and mind
Nora till I get back, okay?
Ugh!
The monster?
Fine, we'll catch him.
What could go wrong?
A little kid and a bird?
Right?
[CHIRPS]
I'm here.
Ah, Astro. I wanted you
to look at this video.
Giant robot bird.
Exactly.
A helio-blimp camera
just happened to
record it last night.
Hmm. Maybe Zoran's story
was real after all.
What do you mean? What story?
She said she saw a flying
monster robot last night.
And that the birds are
all leaving Metro City
because they're afraid of it.
Well, it must be true
that Zoran's special ability
is to communicate with animals.
No wonder.
That's how she could tell
what Houdini was feeling.
But what could it be?
Why on earth would anyone
want to make such a robot?
ASTRO:
You know, it looks like that
fossil you showed me last week.
Huh? Astro, I believe
you're right.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
YUKO:
What's that?
That, Yuko, is Andromedes Rex,
a Jurassic-age giant pterosaur.
Its skeleton was unearthed
last year in Africa.
Now, let's compare that
with our robot friend.
[ALL GASP]
YUKO & ASTRO:
They match.
Hmm. Which means that
someone used Andromedes
as the model
to build this robot.
Houdini, are you sure
this is the right way?
I haven't seen
a monster robot anywhere.
Or a bathroom either,
for that matter.
Maybe it's hiding.
If it is,
it's a very good "hider."
Huh?
[CHIRPING FEARFULLY]
Aw, don't be scared,
Houdini.
I'm right here,
and I'll protect you.
I wonder what it is.
Looks very suspicious.
[CHIRPING]
Huh?
Hmm...
Hey. This is so cool.
[CHIRPING]
Yah!
Ahhh...
[ALARM BLARING]
It's an intruder.
Yeah, and it's a robot.
[CHIRPING]
[QUIETLY]
I wonder how they knew that.
GUARD:
The steel bars on
the emergency exit were bent.
[LOUDLY]
Oh, that's right!
[CHIRPING]
What the--?
A kid. Stop her.
[CHIRPING CONTINUES]
Aah!
I knew
it wasn't a dream.
I just wish Astro was here
to see this.
GUARD: She came this way.
Huh?
Uh-oh.
Over here.
Say, now, you boys
getting hungry already?
Grr. Oh, it's just you.
Well, here's my
"specialité de la dungeon,"
rat and spider stew.
Mmm, good.
No, thanks.
Look, you crazy old man,
if you see a little kid robot
running around,
you'll let us know, okay?
Heh!
Okay, little one,
the coast is clear.
Phew! Boy, that was close.
Thanks for helping me.
Doesn't that get
in your way?
Sure, but--
Woo-hoo! Yippee!
Hot diggity! Ha-ha!
Thanks, kiddo.
I've been chained up for months.
Ha-ha-ha.
Hi, I'm Zoran.
Uh, what's your name?
Hi, Zoran. My name is...
ASTRO:
Professor Poppotore?
Mm-hmm.
He's the world's
leading authority
on Jurassic-era wildlife.
Last year, the
Natural History Museum asked him
to create a full-scale model
of the Andromedes pterosaur,
as a robot.
Is that what Zoran saw?
No, it was
never finished.
The project became too costly,
so the museum cancelled it.
Poppotore was heartbroken.
Then he just vanished.
I didn't want to
see anyone.
Then, one day, a man
named Katari came to my house.
He claimed to be head of a
scientific-research foundation.
Professor, your project is
too important to abandon.
We at the foundation
want to provide funds
for you to finish it.
POPPOTORE:
Naturally, I was thrilled.
We worked hand in hand
to build the robot.
But when it was done,
I found out their real purpose,
so they locked me up.
What do they want with it?
They'll use it
to destroy Metro City!
ZORAN:
What?
Katari and his gang of thugs
are members of
the anti-robot movement.
Their evil plan
is to make people everywhere
deathly afraid of robots.
[GASPS]
Here we are.
Now stay down.
If we pass any guards,
keep very quiet.
The exit is
just up ahead.
Uh-oh!
Hey, you.
What've you got
in that box?
Ah, well...
Just some birds for research.
Well, move along now.
And don't let me catch you
loitering in these halls.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Old fool. Huh?
Hey!
Looking for this? Here!
Argh.
Come on!
[BOTH PANTING]
Freeze!
This way.
No. That way is a--
[GASPS]
[WHIP CRACKS]
Playing hide-and-seek,
you little pink punk?
You better let us go.
Sorry, but playtime is over.
For both of you.
We'll see about that!
No, Zoran. That whip
is too dangerous.
Huh?
It'll drain your power cells.
Zoran, Astro's sister? Ha!
Perfect.
[KATARI CHUCKLES]
Aah!
Zoran!
Why, you...
Aah!
Whoa!
Professor.
Professor
Poppotore!
You monster!
Take her away.
Professor.
Ohh.
Huh?
Ah!
I...
I've gotta save that kid.
[RUMBLING]
Yikes!
Right after I save me!
[WHIMPERING]
Doctor, the Andromedes
has been sighted.
What?
In district 13-K.
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
Look.
Here come the images.
It's attacking the city!
[SNORING]
Hey, look at
the big bird.
MAN:
It's a monster robot!
It's Astro!
[SNARLS]
I've got bad news,
buzzard-beak.
I'm changing your flight plan!
Ah!
Ahhh!
What's this?
Someone's sending us
an image.
It's Zoran. But what--?
KATARI:
Tell Astro his sister
is inside the Andromedes.
Who is this?
Show yourself at once--
Hmm.
All citizens,
evacuate the city.
Astro.
Kind of busy.
I need you to scan
the interior
of the Andromedes robot.
Yah!
Scanning.
Zoran!
ASTRO:
I can't attack the robot
without hurting her.
Ah!
MAN:
What's Astro doing?
KATARI:
Astro can't help you now.
This is what we get for
allowing robots into our lives.
You can't trust robots.
They'll turn on you.
We should destroy
them all.
WOMAN: He's right.
BOY: They should be destroyed!
MAN:
Destroy them.
Destroy robots.
Whoa!
ZORAN:
But I swear it's true.
A big, humongous,
gigantic robot bird.
Did I mention it was big, huh?
ASTRO:
I should've believed her.
But I'm gonna save her now.
Argh!
Astro!
Ugh!
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
I need to draw this thing
away from the city, fast.
ASTRO:
There must be an opening
into the robot somewhere.
Scanning.
I can't find an opening
anywhere.
How am I going to get to Zoran?
Huh?
Argh!
Aah!
[PANTING]
Dr. O'Shay.
Dr. O'Shay. Hello?
Where are you?
ASTRO:
There's got to be a way
to get inside that thing.
O'SHAY [OVER SPEAKER]:
Astro.
Doctor.
Astro, I am
Professor Poppotore.
Once the Andromedes robot
fires its laser,
it takes three seconds
to recharge.
In those
three seconds,
you can leap inside
through its mouth.
Got it.
Astro, behind you.
Ahhh!
He's hit!
Astro!
ASTRO:
Oh, Zoran...
[WEAKLY]
Ohhh...
Brother...
Astro!
ZORAN:
Huh?
Ah!
Ugh!
Go in now!
Brother!
Zoran!
Aah!
Yeah!
Yes.
My work, all gone.
WOMAN:
He did it! Good going, Astro!
KATARI:
You win again, Astro.
But this still isn't over.
MAN: Way to go, Astro!
WOMAN: He did it!
Well, thank goodness
that's over, doctor.
From now on, I've decided
to restrict my work
to the study of
fossilized insects.
Oh?
I was thinking
of starting
with a giant,
flame-throwing tarantula.
I could test it out
in a shopping mall.
I mean, after all,
what could possibly go wrong?
Then if
that works,
I could cross
a cockroach with a T-rex--
Have you gone insane?
[CRYING]
[WAILING]
Zoran, I'm sorry
I didn't believe you.
[SNIFFLES]
But from now on,
you're not to go running off
without telling me,
do you understand?
Mm-hmm.
And no more jumping on the bed
or giving me wedgies.
Mm-hmm.
And you're going to
listen to my words
and follow
my instructions.
Mm-mmm.
Huh?
I don't got to,
because I'm too cute.
Zoran!
[CHIRPING]
Ha-ha! I'm trouble in pink.
Wait, Zoran!
Come back!
ZORAN: In your dreams.
ASTRO: Zoran!
[ZORAN LAUGHING]
[♪]