[♪]
[WONDROUS CHIMING]
All clear.
[HISSING]
[FURIOUS HISSING]
[CRASH]
[GROWLING]
[GLASS CRASHING]
[ALARM RINGS]
SECURITY ROBOT:
Stop the intruder!
[SHATTERING]
[YELLS]
NEWSCASTER:
This marks the third
high-profile Lumanite robbery
this month.
As you may recall,
Lumanite is a rare crystal
found only on the moon.
It has been reported
that highly-trained animals
such as wolves and snakes
were used
to carry out the operation.
I told them
Lumanite should
never be allowed
to leave
the Ministry of Science.
We just don't know
enough about it.
Now, where did Astro
run off to?
Someone has to stop these
thieves before it's too late.
[METALLIC RINGING]
Whoa!
[GROWLING]
If it isn't the big bad wolf!
[GROWLS]
[GRUNTS]
[GASPS]
I got you!
Huh?
[HISSING]
What? It morphed!
Not so fast!
Prepare for
emergency landing!
Whoa!
MAN:
Bull's eye!
[CHUCKLING]
[SCREAMS]
[SCREAMING]
[MYSTERIOUS HISSING]
Oh!
PENELOPE:
Hang on.
[MYSTERIOUS RINGING]
[GASPS]
Are you okay?
[GROANS]
I-I think so.
I'm good.
Hi. I'm Astro.
My name is--
My name is Penelope.
Penelope, did you see
a swan around here?
I have to go.
Uh!
Penelope, I--
[YELLS IN PAIN]
Penelope?
Mr. Rock, please don't
make me do this again.
I'm afraid that's not an option.
Now look at me.
Ah...
You will now transform
into an unsuspecting dog.
That's a good girl.
I hope you didn't
say anything to Astro.
[WHIMPERS]
Ha! Doesn't matter.
Could actually be a good thing.
You can't keep pushing yourself
like this, Astro.
I have to.
I wonder what these thieves
want with Lumanite.
If Dr. Saruta was around,
I bet he'd know
what they're up to.
Who's Dr. Saruta?
An old friend who I haven't seen
in a long time.
How long has it been now?
I guess it's been
about five years
since we made that amazing
discovery together
at the bottom of a crater
on the dark side of the moon.
Dr. Saruta and I
were assigned to the Lunar
Surface Investigation Team.
We were on our way
back to the base
when we discovered
a great rock fortress.
It was made out of an unknown
mineral substance
which came to be known
as Lumanite.
DR. O'SHAY:
Uh, what is it?
It looks like it could be
a map of our solar system.
But the planets
aren't aligned correctly.
[BEEPING]
[WHIRRING]
BOTH:
Huh?
MAN:
Uh, maybe I should
just wait out here.
Uh, what?
DR. O'SHAY:
Its technology
was far beyond
anything we had ever seen.
As soon as we entered
the fortress,
the environment
changed.
It could suddenly
sustain human life.
COMPUTER:
Oxygen level normal.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
DR. O'SHAY:
What is this place?
VOICE:
Welcome to the Moon Tower.
Who said that?
VOICE:
I am an Altieri.
Here lie the secrets
of the universe.
DR. O'SHAY:
We had no idea
such a place or a species
even existed.
ALTIERI:
Those who wish to
unlock the secrets
must touch the panel.
Hmm.
Uh,
I wouldn't
do it.
Could be
a trap.
Saruta!
SARUTA:
It's a chance we have to take.
If the Altieri
is telling the truth,
the answers to
all the world's problems
could be
behind this panel.
ALTIERI:
Because you have
placed your trust in me,
I will now reveal myself
to you.
Ah!
Huh?
Argh!
[UNEARTHLY WAILING]
No!
SARUTA:
You idiots!
How? How could you
be so foolish?
We could have had it all.
The walls! They're caving in.
MAN:
Argh! Run for your lives!
O'SHAY:
We barely made it
out of there alive.
But once we did,
the Moon Tower suddenly
vanished into thin air,
like it had never
existed at all.
All that remained
were a few dozen
pieces of Lumanite
and the cells
of the Altieri.
I returned to Earth
to study the Lumanite,
while Saruta
stayed on the moon.
There, he researched
the Altieri cells
and tried to find a way
to bring them back to life.
Well, so, what happened?
One day, Saruta took the Altieri
out of the laboratory
and disappeared.
A search team was dispatched.
But no one ever saw him again.
[MAN GROANING]
You idiots!
How could you?
[UNEARTHLY WAILING]
[GASPS]
[SIGHS]
[KNOCKING]
Who is it?
Doctor,
I'm afraid
I wasn't able to buy
as much Lumanite
as we had hoped
for this evening.
I understand.
There was only a limited supply
to begin with.
But without it,
Penelope can't survive
much longer.
And of course you won't be able
to reestablish contact
with the Moon Tower.
The Tower is
in another dimension now,
and although
Lumanite contains
the properties for
interdimensional communication,
it's far too...dangerous.
Dangerous because the human body
can't stand the strain.
Am I right?
Yes. Contact does require
a human element.
SARUTA:
I tried to make contact
last year.
[SCREAMS]
It nearly destroyed me.
Look at me! I'm lucky
to even be here.
The human body
is too primitive a species.
Dr. Saruta, could a robot
with Kokoro actually
make contact?
Well...I guess
it's a possibility.
ASTRO:
Zoran!
Oh. Zoran!
Where did she go now?
I let her out of my sight
for one second, and I can't--
Huh?
Well, you must
be Astro.
Yeah,
that's me.
Who are you?
The name's Rock.
Seems we have
something in common.
A mutual friend
named Penelope.
Do you know her?
That's exactly
why I'm here.
She'd like to see you.
Awesome!
I didn't get a chance
to thank her
for helping me
the other day.
Well, now you can.
Follow me.
Astro!
Wait up for me!
Zoran. Where were you?
I, uh...
was playing rocket ball.
Zoran, what did
Dr. O'Shay say
about spending
all your allowance?
Go home and tell him
I went to see a friend.
ROCK:
Astro.
Time's a-wasting.
Bye! Gotta fly!
Can I come too?
MAN:
Do you recognize
the man in this picture?
That's--
That's Dr. Saruta!
You know what?
I think you're right.
And this picture
was only taken last month,
which means Saruta's
no longer missing,
which in turn means
that I've solved
another case.
I'm a better detective
than I thought I was.
I actually meant,
do you recognize him?
DR. O'SHAY:
Who is he?
He goes by
the name of Rock,
and he's some kind
of criminal mastermind.
There's very little
data on him,
but we do know that he showed
up last year out of nowhere
and took over an entire gang
in a single day.
I wish Nora
cleaned that fast.
It's rumored
he has hypnotic powers.
No one can disobey his orders.
He was well on his way
to becoming
the biggest
crime lord in Metro City.
Then one day he just up
and disappeared.
That is, until last month.
Hmm, maybe my wife
has hypnotic powers.
I seem to do
everything she says. Hmm.
I don't get it.
Why in the world
would Dr. Saruta
get involved with someone
like this Rock character?
Well, the Lumanite
robberies
did begin the same time
Rock resurfaced.
And Saruta was the world's
leading Lumanite expert.
Hmm, well,
it does sound a little
too coincidental.
I wonder
what they're up to.
ZORAN:
I'm home!
Hi, Wally.
Hello.
What do you
have there, Zoran?
Oh, you mean
in these shopping bags?
Nothing.
Huh?
Hey! That's the guy
Astro just left with.
BOTH:
Where did he go?
How do you feel,
Penelope?
Doctor...you really
should be in bed.
There's no time
for that now.
We're running out
of Lumanite,
and I have to
find a new way
to contact the Moon Tower
so we can get
some more,
or at least send
you back home
to your people.
[GROANS]
[GASPS]
[COUGHS]
[UNEARTHLY RINGING]
[GASPS WITH RELIEF]
It's strange.
Every time I come in here,
I feel stronger.
Well, I'd better
get back to work.
Good luck.
ASTRO:
Whoa!
Astro!
Penelope!
Astro, what are you
doing here?
I was about to ask you
the same thing.
Huh?
That's Lumanite.
You better
keep that safe.
There's already been
three Lumanite robberies
this week.
SARUTA:
Astro, did you say
robberies?
Uh-huh!
They began last month.
That's when
we started to
run out.
Tell me you and Rock
bought this Lumanite.
PENELOPE:
Doctor, I am so ashamed.
Rock said stealing it
was the only way.
And at the time,
it made sense.
I don't understand.
There was no Lumanite for sale,
and I can't control
your illness without it.
Control
my illness?
You feel better because
I possess the power to heal.
And with no Lumanite,
I'm too weak to help.
You're like a father to me.
I just couldn't let that happen.
I'm sorry.
How can
you heal people?
You see, I'm not from Earth.
I'm not even human.
I'm an Altieri, Astro.
A shape-shifter.
You're the swan?
Penelope's a shape-shifter?
It's complicated.
But I think I can
make you understand.
I managed to collect
all of the Altieri's cells
from the Moon Tower
and bring them back
to the Lunar Observation Base,
where I began to regenerate
them in the lab.
Oh, my!
Through telepathy,
the Altieri told me about
their incredible civilization.
They are a highly advanced
and compassionate species,
free from earthly problems
like poverty, famine and war.
The Moon Tower was one of many
the Altieri scattered
throughout the galaxy
to watch over
various life forms
and share the secrets
of the universe with them
when each species
was deemed ready.
The tower we found on the moon
had been there
for over 10,000 years,
waiting for our arrival.
When I transferred my findings
to the Ministry of Defense,
they felt the Altieri
required further study
and wanted me to
bring it back to Earth
to perform dangerous
experiments on it.
I couldn't let them do that.
So I decided to return
the Altieri
to where
we found it.
As I headed for the crater,
my ship crashed.
Just before
I ran out of oxygen,
a beautiful girl
appeared in front of me.
[UNEARTHLY MUSIC]
At first, I thought
I was hallucinating,
because she looked
exactly like my daughter.
But it was the Altieri.
It had read my mind
and transformed into something
that comforted me.
It's okay. Think of any place
you'd like to be right now.
Hmm.
[WHIRRING]
When I woke up,
I was back at my home
here in Metro City.
Since then,
the doctor's been
hiding me here in his lab,
keeping me safe from
the Ministry of Defense.
Without Lumanite,
the Earth's atmosphere
turns Penelope to stone.
But Lumanite
has a short half-life
and we keep
running out.
And somehow Rock convinced you
he could find some more?
Yes. He said he had the money to
purchase more Lumanite for us.
He claimed to be
a wealthy investor
interested in helping me
fund my research.
I knew
it was too good
to be true.
But still--
I know.
You were thinking
about Penelope.
We're now
down to our final
piece of Lumanite.
The only way
Penelope can survive
is if we can
make contact with
the Moon Tower again.
How are you
going to do that?
I wish
I knew.
ROCK:
I know. And Astro's
gonna help us.
We need
your mechanized strength
and Kokoro
to establish contact.
Astro's
electronic brain
still might not
be able to stand up to
the intense pressure.
He could be
completely destroyed.
There must be
another way.
There is no other way.
Besides, he's just a machine.
Who cares what happens?
Oh!
Why, you!
You never wanted
to help my research.
You just wanted
to find the Moon Tower
so you could learn its secrets
and exploit them.
You got me.
With the secrets of the Moon
Tower, I could rule the world.
And there's no one
more qualified to handle
that responsibility than me.
Throughout history, someone has
always risen to power
and failed because
they lacked knowledge.
This time
will be different, Astro.
You're crazy if you think
I'm gonna help someone like you.
Is that right?
How about if I do this?
[CRYING]
Penelope!
Stop! You're going to
hurt her.
Astro, Penelope's fate
is entirely up to you.
Okay. Fine.
I'll do it for her.
Astro's signal
is getting stronger.
Then Rock's hideout must be
around here somewhere.
I'm sorry, Astro.
[WHIRRING]
[WAILING]
VOICE:
Who calls upon the Altieri?
[SHOUTING]
My name is Astro!
ROCK:
Look!
It's working! The Tower
is back on the moon!
Not so fast, Rock.
Saruta!
O'Shay? Is that you?
I got ya!
Huh?
Whoa!
Thanks for the memories.
Dr. O'Shay!
Astro, are you
all right?
Yes.
We gotta stop Rock!
Huh?
Oh...
[MOANING]
No!
[GROWLING]
Penelope,
take care of
Astro.
[GROWLS]
Penelope!
[YELLS]
[GROWLING]
Rock, you will never
get away with this.
I can and I will.
It's been a pleasure
working with you, doctor.
But alas, I must be going now.
Penelope!
It's me! Astro!
What?!
No!
Uh! Stop!
Whaa!
Oh, Penelope.
Oh, what have I done?
Oh!
It's time to use
those little powers
of yours
to teleport me
to the Moon Tower.
I just can't.
Traveling through
the warp tunnel
is too dangerous
for humans.
You could be lost forever.
Not if you come
with me.
Never.
SARUTA:
Penelope.
Penelope!
Whatever you do,
don't listen to him.
Do it, or else
I'll zap the doctor.
Doctor!
Penelope.
Hmm?
[SIGHS]
All right, I'll do it.
Doctor, give me the Lumanite.
Penelope, don't.
[METALLIC WHOOSHING]
Please, Rock,
I beg you.
Back off!
[GASPS]
That's it.
PENELOPE:
Look out! Argh!
[GASPS]
[YELLING]
ASTRO:
I wonder what this is.
Come back!
Rats. He got away.
Penelope.
Rock took the last piece
of Lumanite with him
into the warp tunnel,
leaving Penelope
to turn into stone.
But don't worry about Rock.
Without Penelope by his side,
he'll be trapped
in the warp tunnel forever.
[YELLING]
What's going on?
Someone get me out of here!
What about Penelope?
Will she be okay, doc?
I brought her back once before
and I'll do it again.
Even if it's
the last thing I do.
And we'll help.
[♪]