[♪]
ROBOT:
Once upon a time,
in a castle far, far away,
there lived
a beautiful princess.
She had everything she wanted,
and yet she was very lonely.
Then, one day,
something strange and wonderful
fluttered into
the castle garden.
Was it a happy butterfly?
Was it a lost nightingale?
Oh, my, no!
It was something magical.
Something with three antennas.
Can you guess what it was?
Can you?
[YELPS]
Cut to the chase, Friday!
Now, what in the world was it?
Nina!
I was just
getting to that!
Well, then
get to it quicker!
I'm getting older
by the minute, you know?
Nina, try to be
a little more patient.
Where were we?
Oh, that's right.
The creature with three antennas
was a pigwidgin!
Pigwidgin?
[LAUGHS]
What a stupid-sounding word!
You made that up!
Hey!
What's this thing?
The three antennas
of a pigwidgin,
a magical flying fairy.
Oh, there is
no such thing!
The first antenna
can find love,
the second antenna
can find friendship,
and the third one
can find--
[SCREAMS]
So let me guess.
A robot
who's not boring.
[CLEARS THROAT]
And the third one
can help you find your dreams.
A pigwidgin can grant
your every wish.
Yeah?
[PHONE RINGS]
Yes. And so
the lonely princess was--
Happy birthday, Nina!
Did you like
all the birthday presents
Daddy asked his secretary
to send you?
Uh, I guess so.
But didn't I give you
every single thing
you asked for, sweetheart?
What about the custom-made
giraffe umbrella
or the solid gold
skateboard
or Friday,
the storyteller robot?
Boring!
Been there,
played with that!
And Friday just tells
stupid stories.
Well, then, what is it
you do want, my darling?
Tell me! I'll get you
anything money can buy.
[SIGHS]
What I want is...
What I want...
DADDY:
Yes?
A pigwidgin!
A what?
It's a kind of fairy.
If you really love me,
that's what you'll get me.
Uh, but, Nina--
That'll teach him!
Daddy never ever comes home
to play with me.
He's always working.
FRIDAY:
Nina...
now I finally
understand.
Huh?
You should have told me
that that was
what you wanted.
Huh?
I've got an idea
that will fix everything!
ABERCROMBIE:
Nail it down
good and tight!
I don't want any doors
falling off!
[LAUGHS]
All right!
Phase two of my tree house
is looking good!
Hey, why is it
your tree house?
We're the ones who are
doing all the work!
You haven't
done anything!
Yeah, that's 'cause
I am the idea guy,
the one with the vision.
All you clowns gotta do
is follow my blueprints.
A monkey could build this thing!
Why not?
A monkey designed it.
We need some more vines.
Astro went to the park
to get some more.
[GRUNTS]
Huh?
What is it?
[YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
[GROANS]
I did it! I did it!
I finally caught one!
Uh, is there something
I can help you with?
Hmm?
Aah! You're not
a pigwidgin!
You emit
a non-human frequency,
but you're bigger
and heavier and you don't
have any wings!
I'm sorry.
No, I'm not a
pigwidge...whatever.
I'm Astro. Who are you?
BOYS:
Friday?
Mm-hm. That's me.
I'm a storyteller robot.
I'm programmed with fairy tales
from all over the world.
Hey, cool job!
So is that why
you're looking for
a pigwidgin?
It's going to be
a gift for a lonely
little girl I know.
ABERCROMBIE:
Oh, baloney!
Fairy tales
are bogus!
They are not!
Yeah, Friday.
Who believes in wizards
and elves and pixies?
I agree. Magical
creatures like those
are purely fictional.
[SHRIEKS]
Three more fairy folk
have just vanished!
BOYS:
What?
It's true!
Fairies and gnomes
and pigwidgins are born
whenever
a child smiles.
But whenever a child says
he doesn't believe,
one of them
disappears forever!
Friday,
wait!
What do these magical
creatures look like?
Well, of course,
there are many
different kinds.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Now, the ones that live
in the water are called mermaids
and they have fish tails
instead of legs.
In a forest, there are
the gnomes and the elves.
In a garden,
you'll find singing sprites
for the musically inclined.
While the fog phantoms
hardly have any shape at all.
And then there are
many, many others.
BOYS:
Wow!
Of course,
if you don't want to
help me find one,
I'll understand.
ALEJO:
Well...
ASTRO:
I don't get it.
Why are we searching
the City Hall attic?
FRIDAY:
Well, pigwidgins are
very civic-minded
and they love
the dark.
I haven't
seen anything yet.
They're
very good hiders.
Alejo, do you think
they really could exist?
Scientifically,
it's highly improbable.
ABERCROMBIE:
Scientifically,
this is nutso.
We should be building
our tree house!
I'm sensing
a strange frequency!
Up ahead in the darkness,
something not quite human!
[ALL SCREAMING]
Bats!
ABERCROMBIE:
I hate bats!
[FRIDAY SHRIEKS]
Well,
that went well.
What did you expect? I told you
there was no such thing as--
Shhh!
You'd better not say it,
or a pixie or elf
or something might vanish.
He's right.
You're gonna vanish if we don't
finish this tree house!
MAN:
It is finished,
just as you ordered.
Now, shall
we try it?
[MACHINE HUMS]
Friday!
Uh!
Gotcha!
Where have you
been sneaking out to
every day? Don't deny it!
Actually, I'm trying
to catch a pigwidgin.
A pigwidgin?
But that's what
I told Daddy I wanted.
Is it for me?
Thank you, Friday!
You're the best!
Oh, Nina.
[BOTH SHRIEK]
I'll be back soon, Nina.
You stay here
and be a good girl.
FRIDAY:
Are we ready to catch
a pigwidgin, men?
Whoosh! Pow!
Hey!
We'll swoop down
on 'em
and catch 'em
before they know
what hit 'em!
Yeah!
No?
You know, I'm getting
sick and tired
of listening to you
yammering on about fairies.
Right! So let's be off,
fearless fairy hunters!
Why don't you be off,
and we'll catch up?
[GIRL GRUNTS]
BOTH:
Huh?
Phew!
All right, next time
I come here,
there'd better be
an elevator!
These goofs are the best
you could round up?
Excuse me,
who are you?
Nina!
BOYS:
Huh?
You followed me here,
didn't you?
[GIGGLES]
You must be the little girl
who wants Friday
to catch her a pigwidgin.
Bingo!
So let's get started.
Now!
FRIDAY:
All magical creatures
respond to the vibrational
frequencies of Mother Earth,
which is why one commonly finds
their nests and dwellings
deep underground.
Oh!
My shoes!
They're ruined!
It's just
water.
It's dirty and it's wet,
and I hate it!
[LAUGHING]
Maybe you should have
known better
than to wear your
fancy-schmancy shoes down here.
Halt, speed bump!
What?
Speak up!
[WHISPERING]
I can't hear you.
Carry me,
you idiot!
Are you cracked?
Why would I do that?
Because I'm not walking
another step until you do.
Like I care!
Calm down,
Abercrombie.
Nina,
I'll carry you.
Humph!
Are you sure
it's no trouble, Astro?
I'm fine.
Funny hair!
Nina, could you
not do that?
Astro's way too nice.
[LAUGHS]
Hmm?
Something's
coming!
Is it a fairy?
Maybe
it's a pigwidgin!
[MONSTER LAUGHING]
[ALL GASP]
Was that a fairy?
That's-- That's...
Ever seen anything
like that?
ALEJO:
Yeah, I have.
But where?
Right here!
Huh?
ALEJO:
He's right!
That's it!
Here it comes again!
[MONSTER LAUGHING]
[BOTH SCREAM]
That is definitely not a fairy.
[LAUGHING]
[SCREAMS]
Hold still,
you monster!
I'll get you! I'll get you!
W-w-what is that?
It's yucky!
[FRIDAY GRUNTS]
Aah! Run, Astro!
[SCREAMS]
Hey, this thing's
just a hologram.
Who cares?
Make it go away now!
It's gone!
So am I, home!
Now, step on it!
[SIRENS WAILING]
Huh?
Detective Tawashi!
Astro.
Did something
happen here?
Sure did.
The owner of this
jewelry store was attacked,
and the store was robbed.
She said it was
some kind of monster.
Monster?
Us too! A big-old, ugly
green thing chased us!
What was that?
Astro, is that true?
Yes, sir.
Hmm.
There have been
five reports today
of people attacked
by monsters.
And while the victims
run away in terror,
expensive items
mysteriously disappear.
Detective!
Please catch
that awful thing quickly!
I can't get the memory
of that horrible creature
out of my mind.
Strange, but
it looked so much
like a dog that chased me
when I was just a child.
Hey, the monster
that attacked us
looked just like
Abercrombie's drawing!
Uh-huh!
The dog from her childhood,
the monster Abercrombie drew...
Both of the images
came from their minds.
So what are you saying?
Something must be taking
the images from their thoughts
and projecting them
as holograms.
I think maybe that's where all
the monsters are coming from.
But who would be
capable of that?
I don't know.
But it'd have to be someone
very ruthless
and very, very smart.
Uh...so you're telling me that
monster came out of my mind?
Then it's your fault!
Huh?
You dreamed up
that awful thing
on purpose
just to
frighten me because
you don't like me!
No, I didn't!
What are you talking about?
I'm out of here!
Hey, wait!
FRIDAY:
Nina, wait!
[LAUGHING]
Nina, please!
Open the door!
Nina!
Go away! Leave me alone!
Phooey!
I hate you
and all your dumb friends!
If the monsters
in my mind turn real,
I'll have them
stomp the whole city.
Huh?
What are those?
Fairies?
ASTRO:
Nina!
Astro!
How do you like
the fairies?
Me and the other guys
made them just for you.
For me?
Sure!
ABERCROMBIE: Hey!
Oh!
[GRUNTS]
Nina!
Why'd you do this?
Tell me!
Because I'm sorry
my drawing scared you.
It scared me too.
Ha-ha!
You wanna go
fairy hunting again?
Really?
Uh, I mean, I really
can't waste my time
on such childish things
as chasing fairies.
Nina, we're going
to go fairy hunting.
Are you coming or not?
Well, I suppose if you insist.
It would be rude not to.
FRIDAY:
Then we're off!
Whoa!
Woo-hoo!
[LAUGHING]
The fearless fairy hunters
ride again!
Yahoo!
Nina!
Daddy!
[BOTH LAUGHING]
I've got a big surprise
for you. Something
you really wanted.
Really?
Well, what is it?
It's coming today
and it's expensive.
Your very own fairy!
What?
Sir, you bought
a fairy?
Of course.
Why, there's nothing
in this world
that you can't buy
with enough money.
Oh, Daddy! How could you?
You've ruined everything!
Nina!
But...what did I say?
ASTRO:
I think she wants to
find her own fairy
with her new friends.
Huh?
Sir, how could you
buy a fairy?
Oh, it's
not real.
I had a machine
created that could
project a hologram
from the image
of a fairy
in Nina's mind.
If she could imagine a fairy,
the machine
could make it seem real.
That's awesome! Did you
design this machine yourself?
Er, no. A strange little man
approached me with the idea.
He called himself...
Dr. Minimini.
Dr. Minimini?
He's no good!
What?
DR. O'SHAY:
Astro, are you there?
Yes, doctor?
You're needed at once.
The Central Bank
is swarming with monsters.
What?
I just got a call
from the police.
They said monsters
are appearing out of thin air
and attacking everyone!
Doctor, tell them to look
for a machine nearby.
A machine?
Yes, a device
that can take
mental images
and make them visible.
But who in the world
would build something like that?
Dr. Minimini.
What?
I heard Minimini
broke out of prison
and is still
on the loose.
Could he be up to
his old tricks?
[SIRENS WAILING]
[SOBBING]
Nina?
Daddy just doesn't get it.
He thinks all I want
are things...you can buy!
But he's wrong!
Nina, nobody
bought us, and
we're your friends.
What?
He's right!
Yeah, we're here just
because we like you,
and your dad didn't
have to pay us
anything at all.
We're really...friends?
ABERCROMBIE:
Sure! Fearless fairy hunters
stick together!
Yeah!
[GASPS]
ALL:
A fairy!
NINA:
A fairy
with three antennas!
It's a real live pigwidgin!
[SCREAMS]
[PEOPLE SCREAMING]
What in the world
is going on in here?
[CACKLING]
Run, run,
you ignorant fools!
You're all just running
from your own worst fears!
All my machine does is help you
see what they look like.
And while you run from your
fears, I can loot the city!
There!
That must be it!
Astro!
Everyone, listen to me!
These monsters are just
illusions. They can't harm you!
He's right!
They went right through him!
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Move out!
Earthquake!
No, it's not.
Someone's down there!
Aha!
Minimini!
Astro! So glad
you could drop in.
The bank just closed!
[LAUGHING]
Not till I make
one last withdrawal.
I'm about to take you out!
Ahhh!
Sorry, Astro,
but this monster
is no illusion.
Huh?
[GRUNTS]
Hey, come back!
You can't go in there.
ABERCROMBIE:
Nina!
[SHRIEKS]
[MONSTERS MOANING EERILY]
Oh, no! No!
Ahh!
Nina!
No one's allowed in.
It's too dangerous.
That's my daughter
in there!
Hey!
Nina!
Daddy!
I'm here, Nina.
[BOTH GROAN]
[PANTING]
Nina, tell me,
are you all right?
Uh-huh.
DADDY:
What's that doing here?
What is
it, Daddy?
It's the machine
I had Dr. Minimini build
to make the fairies
in your mind come to life.
You mean
this machine
can really take pictures
of what's in your mind?
Yes,
it--
[BOTH SCREAM]
[SCREAMS]
Daddy!
Daddy, Daddy!
Huh?
What's this?
[ASTRO GRUNTING]
Yeah!
Huh?
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMS]
These are...
These are all me!
ABERCROMBIE:
Look at them!
They're all
different images of Nina!
[MOANS]
Daddy, Daddy!
Huh?
[GASPS]
Will you
look at that?
It's me!
That's right,
sweetheart.
All my precious
memories of you.
Oh!
Wow!
They're
disappearing!
I'm so sorry, Nina.
I just wanted you
to have your fairies.
Daddy, don't worry.
I found something
much better than fairies.
Oh?
Friends who make me smile.
ASTRO:
Hey, guys!
Astro, you missed
the Nina bubbles.
And whenever kids smile,
fairies are born.
Isn't that right, Friday?
Absolutely, Nina!
[♪]