[♪]
YUKO:
Dr. O'Shay, come quick!
The Juno 5 satellite
has veered out of orbit.
It's headed straight for Earth!
O'SHAY:
Juno 5?
Get General Talbot
on the com at once!
General, why is that antique
still in space?
Because, doctor, it costs money
to retrieve it.
Money? Juno's a megaweapon.
It has a nuclear plasma drive.
It could destroy a city!
OPERATOR:
It's approaching
the southern hemisphere, sir.
It's headed for Antarctica.
TALBOT:
Good. No one will be hurt.
O'SHAY:
Good? It's a disaster!
The explosion on impact
will generate enough steam
to melt the polar icecap
and flood the Earth!
TALBOT:
Then we'll shoot it down
with a missile.
It's too close.
If we destroy it now,
the blast will poison
the Earth's ozone layer.
TALBOT:
There must be some way.
Let's rocket!
It may be too late.
If we could just
slow it down enough
to bring it in
for a soft landing.
Professor, it's Astro.
[BEEPING]
Astro, be careful.
[GRUNTING]
Ow! That's going
to leave a dent!
[GROANS]
YUKO:
He's slowing it down!
Argh!
O'SHAY:
But his body's not made
to withstand that much heat.
Another satellite!
[GROANS]
SCIENTIST:
He's got it under control!
It's going to land safely!
O'SHAY:
Good job, Astro.
[BOTH SIGH]
[ASTRO GROANS]
Oh!
Uh, sorry to crash and run.
Chill, guys. I'm just fine. Ah!
O'SHAY:
Astro!
Are you all right?
What's happening?
We're still in trouble!
ASTRO:
I saw another satellite
even bigger than Juno.
It's starting to malfunction.
I need to go stop it
before it falls to Earth
and destroys--
Argh!
[ASTRO'S VOICE FADING]
Astro! What happened?
Astro!
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
[BUZZING]
[PLAYING BRIGHT TUNE]
[PEOPLE CHEERING]
[MECHANICAL WHIRRING]
[BUZZING]
[TOOL HUMS]
I wish I had better parts
to fix you up with, kid.
[ACCORDION MUSIC PLAYING]
[KNOCK AT DOOR]
Boon, what's going on?
Hey there, Munk.
So who's
the new robot?
I don't know. I found him
dumped on the hill out back.
Does he have a name?
Name?
My name is, um...
BOON:
Looks like his memory
circuits are a little scrambled.
What is my name?
How should I know?
Look, now that
you're all fixed up,
maybe you better
run on home, kid.
I don't know...
where that is.
[BUZZING]
There's something important
I'm supposed to do.
But I can't remember
what it is.
Poor kid.
Programming zapped.
Lost his memory.
He doesn't know
who or what he is.
Astro, I know you're out there
somewhere, but where?
[BEEPING]
Hey kid.
Huh?
If you're going to stick around,
you'd better learn
to treasure-hunt
like the rest of us.
Trick is to find the choice
stuff among all this scrap.
Now, watch and learn
from the master.
[BUZZES]
Hmm.
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
Okay...
[GROANS]
Kid! Lift with your knees!
[YELLING]
Almost!
[ASTRO AND BOON GROANING]
Hmm?
Huh?
Wha--?
What power!
Ha-ha-ha!
Huh?
That's some robot, huh?
Did you build him,
Boon?
I wish.
[BUZZES]
Hey, Boon, look
what I found!
[GASPS]
Give me that!
Get away from me!
[BUZZING]
Hmm?
JAKE:
Kid, that little gadget
you found.
It's an all-purpose automatic
repair unit invented by Boon.
MUNK:
Yeah.
A little piece of himself
he was trying to forget.
I just don't
understand.
JAKE:
You see, Boon wasn't
always a scavenger
here in Outland.
JAKE:
There was a time
when he was one of the world's
most famous robotics engineers,
and the inventor
of the Boon Unit,
a device which could repair
any mechanical defect.
To introduce it,
he built a floating laboratory
and took it around the world
repairing broken robots.
He even used robot technicians
to help.
The project was a huge success.
JAKE:
And Boon was
on top of the world.
But, you know,
it's a funny thing
about the top
of the world.
There's only one direction left
a man can go.
Down.
Something went terribly wrong,
and the system that could
repair any problem
broke down and sank
to the bottom of the sea.
That's right.
Boon didn't know
what had gone wrong.
But the people who lost
their robots blamed Boon
and called his invention
a fake.
The Boon Unit is not a fake!
Argh!
There has to be another reason.
You've got to believe me.
JAKE:
But no one did.
Boon was arrested for cheating
people out of their money.
He was sent to prison
and every Boon Unit was
collected and destroyed.
Let me out! I tell you,
the Boon Unit works!
JAKE:
But Boon just wouldn't
let it rest. That's right.
He claimed his lab had been
sabotaged by rival companies.
[ALARM BLARES]
JAKE:
Finally, one night,
Boon escaped.
He made his way here,
to the Outland,
where people come
to forget their past.
So, does the fairy tale
end there, Jake?
Boon.
Hey, man.
Maybe this kid's
turned your luck around.
You never can tell.
That's right.
I guess he's still
mad at me.
It's not you.
Suddenly finding
that old piece of his past
has stirred up memories.
And maybe
he's a little scared.
Of what?
The truth.
He always claimed the Boon Unit
worked perfectly,
that it wasn't to blame
for what happened.
But now you've dug up
the real thing.
Well, what if
he examines it
and finds some flaw
he missed before?
JAKE:
What if the Boon Unit
really was to blame?
O'SHAY:
He couldn't have just vanished!
I know he's out there!
Just keep searching.
We can't give up!
[BEEPING]
What's up, Robot Boy?
I can't seem to find
Boon anywhere.
Just give him
a little time.
Hey, I've never seen you
without your mask.
No?
Sometimes it's best
not to be recognized at all.
Wonderful!
A magnificent piece of art!
Looks just like
my wife, Bunny.
She'll love it!
It's worth
every penny.
Hey, Jake, how much did you get
for your latest creation?
[WHISTLES]
I think Jake's
buying dinner!
[ALL CHEERING AND LAUGHING]
Boon!
There you are. I've looked
everywhere for you!
[SIGHS]
ASTRO: Hmm?
ROBOT: Attention, all citizens.
Be on the lookout
for "Tuna Lips" Tony,
wanted for fish smuggling.
The suspect is
armed and smelly.
Next on our most-wanted list
is J.S. Boon, who escaped
from prison 10 years ago.
If you have seen this man
or know anything about his
whereabouts, please report--
Hey! It's Boon!
Do you know the whereabouts
of this man?
Uh-huh.
He's right over there.
At last!
Boon!
Run!
It's the bounty hunter.
What?
Let's move!
JAKE:
Watch it!
Freeze! You're coming with me!
Argh!
I don't think so!
Don't forget to write.
[BUZZING]
Sorry. I didn't know
you were hiding.
I'm afraid I'm wanted
by the law, kid.
Oh.
Then they're wrong!
I know you're innocent.
Thanks, kid.
YUKO:
Still no sign of Astro,
professor.
Then we'll check the visual
memory of every single robot.
Somebody somewhere
must have seen Astro!
Every robot, sir?
It's our only hope...
if it's not too late.
[BEEPING]
Huh?
Hey!
TIARA: What's that?
[GROANS]
[GASPS]
[BUZZING]
Hey!
What's wrong, huh?
He's totally shut down.
YUKO:
Sir, we've got data
on that second
malfunctioning satellite.
It's called Ganymede.
It's 10 times larger
and more explosive than Juno.
After three more orbits,
its gyrosystem will be overcome
by Earth's gravity
and will crash to the surface.
So we're right back
where we were before.
Our only hope
is Astro.
Where is he?
Why haven't you found him yet?
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Have you sent that robot's
visual memory
to the Ministry
of Science yet?
We're still fixing it.
Get it sent!
You can fix it later.
YUKO:
No luck, sir. No robot
has reported seeing Astro.
Maybe there is no Astro.
Maybe he was destroyed
by the satellite.
SCIENTIST:
If he was destroyed, then--
Then it's the end of the world!
O'SHAY:
Don't lose hope.
It's not the end yet
for Astro
or the world.
[RINGING]
Professor! They found
a visual record.
BOUNTY ROBOT:
If you've seen this man
or know anything about his
whereabouts, please report--
It's Boon!
Astro!
Can't you fix him
with the Boon Unit?
No, his circuitry
is far too advanced.
I've done all I can do
with him.
Oh, man, there must be something
in this dump that'll help!
Couldn't you weld a toaster
to his nose or something?
Huh?
Aha!
Astro! Astro!
O'SHAY:
The heat from Juno
damaged his memory circuits,
giving him amnesia.
Then something
sparked a memory,
causing the damaged circuit
to shut down completely.
Hmm.
Someone gave him excellent
emergency treatment.
Boon was the one
who fixed him up.
Boon?
TIARA: Yeah.
J.S. Boon? You're--?
An escaped prisoner.
Don't worry.
I won't run.
Not 'til I know
Astro's going to be okay.
Hmm.
BOTH:
Ah!
O'SHAY: Well.
Doctor?
Astro!
Dr. O'Shay!
Oh!
There's another satellite,
and it's going to fall
in three days.
Hey, kid, you've had amnesia
for three days. Time's up.
Huh?
He's right.
It's called Ganymede.
But we're out of time.
I've got to stop it!
Astro!
[GROANS]
Go get them, Astro!
Yes, sir!
Let's rocket!
That's one
gutsy kid.
Is that an original
Boon Unit?
It is.
Doctor, would you
lend me your transport?
But why?
Yes, of course.
Let's go!
Hey, where's
everybody going?
To try to fix Ganymede
with the Boon Unit!
BOON:
Astro can slow Ganymede down.
But he'll need something
to redirect it from Earth.
You really believe the Boon Unit
can do it?
As much as you believe
in Astro, doctor.
Remember, it's my
long-lost child.
Argh!
[GRUNTING]
O'SHAY: Astro!
Huh?
Doctor! Boon!
BOON:
Hang on, kid.
We're here to help.
Kid, insert this Boon Unit
into Ganymede's main engine.
It'll repair whatever's
broken down inside it.
Try to set it in the drive port.
Argh!
Wow!
[ALL GASPING]
You did it, kid!
And the Boon Unit worked!
It repaired Ganymede.
What just happened?
Oh, nothing special.
Astro, he just saved the world.
That's all.
Not too shabby.
I knew Boon was right
about his Boon Unit.
O'SHAY:
Our deepest thanks.
This will
clear your name
with the Science Board
and the law.
Aha!
Boon spotted. Boon spotted.
I got you this time.
Let me at him!
ASTRO:
Wait! He's innocent.
No, not you again. No.
Stop that. Boon isn't
on the run anymore.
Not even
a little?
The Boon Unit worked perfectly.
It proves he wasn't a crook.
Isn't that right,
Boon?
BOON:
Thanks to you.
I owe you one, kid.
No prob.
MUNK:
We all do.
You're welcome back anytime.
Doctor.
Welcome back, Astro.
Happy endings make me:
[BUZZING]
[ALL LAUGHING]
[♪]