[♪]
Once we reach the asteroid,
you will all work
until the satellite installation
is complete.
Or until you break down,
whichever comes first.
Um, you'll have to
excuse me, sir,
but I'm afraid
that we are not accustomed
to working under
such harsh conditions.
That's right,
captain.
We are merely
Class B Cleaning-bots.
Please allow me
to demonstrate.
Whoa! Aagh!
Get! Stop it!
We can clean
just about anything, sir.
Plus, as an added bonus,
we come equipped with
a special grooming upgrade
to get into those
hard-to-reach spots.
Any requests?
[GROWLS]
Touch me again,
and I'll have you dismantled!
Aye-aye, captain.
Yes, sir.
[RUMBLING]
What now?
MAN [ON RADIO]:
Captain, we have a problem.
We're being attacked.
We should re--
I am the Blue Knight.
Release the robots immediately
or deal with me.
Just what I need,
more useless robots.
Shoot them down.
Here he comes, sir.
I said blast them
out of the sky.
Aagh!
Aaah!
[GROWLS]
[PANTING]
Do you wish
to surrender?
No. Never.
Turn around
now, human.
[GROWLS]
[OVER INTERCOM]
My fellow robots,
this is the Blue Knight.
ROBOT:
Can it really be him?
I have taken command
of the ship.
You are free.
Yay!
We've been saved!
The Blue Knight saved us.
Hooray!
Now for
your next task.
I want you to persuade Astro
to join the cause.
Our top story, another
fully loaded cargo ship
transporting
a company of Service-bots
was hijacked by the Blue Knight
and his gang
of so-called freedom fighters
earlier today.
That brings
the number of robots
abducted by
the Blue Knight to--
That's why robots
shouldn't be trusted.
MAN:
It's a shame.
[SIGHS]
Huh?
ROBOT:
Those robots were not abducted.
They were rescued.
The Blue Knight
is not the enemy.
He is the defender
of robots.
I better
check this out.
ROBOT:
Wow!
So this island is the secret
base of the Blue Knight.
This is wonderful!
ROBOT:
We will finally be safe here.
Oh, I can't wait
to start cleaning.
ROBOT: I have been
waiting for you.
Huh?
Welcome to Steel Island.
BLUE KNIGHT:
Shadow!
SHADOW:
You are now free.
You can choose
whether to stay here
or return
to human society.
The choice
is all yours.
With all due respect,
Shadow,
these robots
were being abused
by the humans
who owned them.
I cannot allow them
to choose.
They will be safe
here on Steel Island.
Blue Knight,
if we do not allow them
to choose their own fate,
we'd be no better
than the humans.
Uh, but--
If any of them
wish to return,
do not stand
in their way.
Prepare the Stealth Ship.
ROBOTS:
Goodbye. Good luck.
We'll see you soon.
See you soon. Good luck.
Will they be
all right?
Well, that depends.
How much do you trust humans?
As long as we are
mistreated by humans,
there is no true freedom
for us.
Aagh! Aagh!
Take that,
you filthy human!
Help me! Help me!
Zoran?
Aah!
Ugh!
Ooh.
Ha-ha! Gotcha!
Zoran, what are
you doing?
Don't you know?
I'm the Blue Knight,
and Nora's the evil human
mistreating robots.
Stop playing around.
It isn't funny.
Why? What's wrong?
The Blue Knight's the defender
of robots, isn't he?
Yeah. Sure. But, Zoran--
Whose side
are you on, anyway?
Come on, Nora. Let's go play
somewhere else.
No, not again.
NORA:
Oh!
MAN: Why does the Blue Knight
keep interfering in my business?
Robots are tools
and nothing more.
They must learn to respect us
or else suffer the consequences.
Is that clear?
Yes, sir.
Then don't just stand there.
Find the Blue Knight's hideout
and turn him into scrap metal.
Robot dogs?
How did they
get past the guards?
[GROWLS]
Aaagh!
Gordon!
TENMA:
Mr. Drake.
Huh?
You're-- You're--
Dr. Tenma!
At your service.
Hmm.
I still don't understand
why robots and humans
have to fight.
It's pointless.
Astro, you must
listen to me.
Dr. Tenma!
The Blue Knight
needs your help.
The cargo ship
that was attacked yesterday
belongs to a man
who steals robots
and makes them work in his
intergalactic mining factories.
Drake seeks revenge against
the Blue Knight.
He will hunt him down and
destroy him once and for all.
[GRUNTS]
Astro, go to Steel Island.
To Steel Island?
Yes.
It is an abandoned steel rig
in the middle of the ocean.
The Blue Knight
is hiding there
with all of the robots
he has rescued.
Join them, Astro,
and put a stop to Drake's plan.
[YAWNS]
What's wrong, Astro?
Who are you
talking to?
Zoran,
I've got to go
to Steel Island.
But I wanna come.
ZORAN:
Hey, wait.
Astro!
The time has come
to prove to the humans
that you are truly
the ruler of all robots.
ROBOT:
Oh, my, my, my.
So much to clean,
so little time.
This really is
a wonderful place.
Don't you agree,
Butch?
Yes. But what will happen
if the humans find us here?
Who's going to
come looking for us out here,
in the middle of nowhere?
Anyway, if they do,
I'll make them wish they hadn't.
Aaagh!
[SCREAMING]
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
We meet again.
Eee-aah!
It's Captain Gordon.
Emergency.
We are under attack.
The self-defense system
is not responding.
Filthy humans.
How did they find this place?
Aaagh! Aaagh!
Come on.
We have to do something.
Ha-ha-ha!
You lose, Blue Knight.
You finally messed with
the wrong human.
Mr. Drake, looks like
something's
coming up from behind.
In fact--
What is it?
Uh, it's--
It's Astro!
Leave him alone!
Huh?
I think this
belongs to you.
And I've got something
for you, Astro.
[MAN SHOUTING]
Aaagh!
Ugh!
Aaah!
You'll pay
for this.
[GRUNTING]
Just look at Astro.
You knew all along
he would come and fight,
didn't you, Tenma?
Of course I did,
my faithful Shadow.
Do not doubt me.
The way the Blue Knight
has turned against man
is how all robots
will eventually evolve.
[GRUNTING]
TENMA:
Including Astro.
[GROANS]
Astro needs to
stop doubting
and act upon
his anger.
Aaagh!
What have I done?
[GRUNTING]
Are you all right?
Ugh!
Aaagh! Aaagh!
Never let your guard down
in battle, foolish robot.
Aaagh!
[GORDON CACKLES]
How does it feel, Blue Knight,
now that the tables
have turned?
Blue Knight!
Aaaagh!
[CACKLES]
Aaagh!
It's a mistake to underestimate
the Blue Knight.
Aaagh!
Aaaaagh!
No, don't shoot!
[GROWLS]
Aaagh!
No! Stop!
Astro, I'm disappointed.
Why do you keep
sticking up for them?
I agree that what the humans
are doing is wrong.
But that still doesn't
give you the right to hurt them.
If you will not join me
and fight these pathetic humans,
then you too
are my enemy.
Astro, don't you see?
Your fate is to fight
alongside the Blue Knight,
not against him.
ZORAN:
Doctor, look!
Over there!
I just hope we're not too late.
[CACKLES]
Now let's show these robots
who they're dealing with. Kato?
All set.
Any time you're ready.
Good.
I'll make every last one of them
wish they were never built.
What about Gordon?
Who cares?
Destroy Steel Island.
Don't do this,
Blue Knight.
Let's go, Astro. Ha!
What's happening?
Hey, Astro?
Like I always say, destruction
is the purest form of art.
Huh?
Hang on, Zoran.
Aaagh! Aaah!
Whoa!
ROBOT:
Help!
Hey, boss, you're not gonna
leave us here, are you?
The brace supporting the island
has been destroyed.
What?
Steel Island and everything
on it will sink.
Now's not the time
for us to fight.
[DRAKE CACKLES]
This must be
my lucky day.
I will crush
the Blue Knight and Astro
all in one shot.
[LAUGHS EVILLY]
Oh, no!
Listen up. We are going to
evacuate the island.
Get to
the Stealth Ship now!
ROBOT:
Run! Run!
It looks like Astro
has failed you, Tenma.
No.
There is still time
for Astro.
You will see, Shadow.
Mr. Drake, there's
an emergency message.
What?
From who?
It's from
Dr. Tenma, sir.
Put it through.
Yes, sir.
You have not won
this battle yet, Drake.
What do you mean?
Take a look.
This is the Blue Knight's
Stealth Ship.
What is going on here?
I thought we destroyed
all of their ships.
TENMA:
Not quite.
There's still time
before the island sinks.
Don't panic.
Hurry, everyone.
Hurry!
This way!
Get on the ship! Go!
Stealth Ship!
I have a few surprises
myself.
Charge the laser cannon.
Yes, sir.
Huh?
It didn't work,
Mr. Drake.
The ship must have
a shield.
Impossible.
Keep firing.
Kato?
Just trust me.
Doctor, the tower!
Oh, no!
Run, Zoran!
Ugh!
Zoran!
[YELLS]
Astro!
Blue Knight!
[GROANS]
Astro, I can
take it from here.
Make sure nothing happens
to the Stealth Ship.
Let's rocket!
[GROANS]
Hmm, wait till they find out
their shield doesn't
work underwater.
Ugh!
Astro destroyed
the laser cannon.
No!
Hold your fire.
Why can't you
leave these robots alone?
Because robots
should never have
the ability to think
for themselves.
And if they choose
to defy me,
I choose
to demolish them!
Oh, no.
This is Kato.
Good news, sir.
Proceed with plan B.
Perfect timing, Kato.
Astro?
This will
blow you away.
No, he can't!
When I push this button,
the Blue Knight's ship
is going to become
another wreck
at the bottom of the ocean.
[CACKLING]
Isn't this exciting?
What is the great Astro
going to do now?
[DRAKE CACKLES]
Aaaagh!
Huh?
I won't let you!
I won't let you destroy
those innocent robots.
You have kokoro, Astro.
You can't hurt me.
If you trigger the detonation,
then I will.
Interesting.
Shall we give it a try?
[GROWLS]
[CACKLES]
TENMA:
That's it, Astro. You can do it.
Let your anger rise
and strike out against humanity.
O'SHAY [ON RADIO]:
Astro, don't shoot.
Huh?
You cannot harm
humans, Astro.
Not for any reason.
Ha!
So the mighty Astro
can't do it after all, huh?
Guess again.
[GASPS]
Aaagh!
[YELLING]
I don't believe it.
Astro's beam was deflected.
TENMA: I must admit,
I didn't see that coming.
[GROANS]
That was close,
but you failed, Astro.
Now say goodbye
to your friends.
[GRUNTING]
What happened?
Don't you see?
He wasn't aiming for you.
He meant for his beam
to be deflected
and knock out
our antenna.
I don't believe it!
Aaagh!
Blast them into the water!
Roger.
It's the Blue Knight, sir.
We're being attacked.
I can see that,
you fool!
Finish them off!
Stop it!
Don't do this,
Blue Knight.
You've done enough
already.
Astro, you'll
never learn.
Astro, Blue Knight,
mark my words,
you'll pay for this.
Oh, yes,
you'll both pay for this.
The island is sinking.
But I wasn't done
cleaning.
Do you think
that the Blue Knight
will ever learn to change,
Dr. O'Shay?
I don't know, Astro.
I don't know.
But today
you took a stand
and showed
both man and robot
that fighting
is not the answer.
I'm very proud of you.
BLUE KNIGHT: Astro!
Huh?
Thank you for helping me
save the others.
But this partnership
is over.
I will not let you
get in our way again.
And we will fight
to the end.
Hyah!
Blue Knight, wait!
[ORGAN PLAYING
DARK, ELEGANT SONG]
TENMA:
Astro!
Do not disappoint me
again.
The time has come
for you to rise
and prepare for
the biggest battle of all.
[♪]