(pleasant electronic music accent)
(paper rustling over howling wind)
(wind howling)
(wood creaking)
(paper thwacking)
(goats bleating)
(paper crinkling)
(rope rustling)
(stone thuds)
(rousing orchestral music)
(dogs barking)
(townspeople chattering)
(boy chattering excitedly
in made-up language)
(townspeople chattering in confusion)
(townspeople shouting)
(bird chirping)
(townspeople grunting excitedly)
(wood thudding)
(wood rattling)
(door thuds)
(distant bird shrieking)
(machinery rumbling)
(distant dog barking
over muffled rumbling)
(cups rattling)
(cup clangs to floor)
(plate shattering)
(child screaming)
(dog barking)
(pounding percussion accents)
(rousing orchestral music)
(fireworks shrieking)
(explosion rumbling)
(rousing and pleasant orchestral music)
(fireworks popping)
(robot buzzing)
(rousing and pleasant orchestral music)
(fireworks rumbling)
(townspeople gasping)
(explosions rumbling over
rousing orchestral music)
(tinkling music box tones)
(rousing and pleasant orchestral music)
(robots screeching through the air)
(pleasant orchestral music)
(explosion rumbling)
(crowd gasping and applauding)
(rousing and pleasant orchestral music)
(wind howling)
(thunder rumbling and cracking)
(ominous electronic music)
(rat squeaking)
(gears rattling)
(quietly tense electronic music)
(rat squeaking)
(thunder rumbling over
pulsing electricity)
(equipment humming)
(electricity crackling)
(gear rattling)
(equipment buzzing)
(rhythmic electronic music)
(thunder rumbling)
(electricity crackling)
(lever crunching)
(gears rattling)
(electricity buzzing and crackling)
(equipment screeching)
(footsteps pattering)
(wheel rattling)
(equipment cracking)
(metal clanging)
(footsteps pattering)
(machinery creaking)
(lever crunching)
(footsteps pattering)
(gears whirring)
(machinery crunching)
(machinery creaking)
(metal clanging)
(man thuds to floor)
(machinery creaking)
(metal cracking)
(machinery creaking to a stop)
(pleasant electronic tones
over thumping heartbeats)
(metal cracking and creaking)
(metal tinging)
(metal cracking and hissing)
(mysterious string tones
over rhythmic percussion)
(metal cracking and popping)
(robot hissing)
(lever crunching)
(gears rattling)
(metal popping)
(mysterious string tones
over rhythmic percussion)
(metal clanging)
(metal popping)
(equipment rattling)
(robot hissing)
(footstep thudding)
(metal popping)
(metal creaking)
(mysterious string tones)
(footsteps thudding)
(mysterious strings tones over
dramatic orchestral music)
(robot hissing)
(equipment cracking and rumbling)
(dramatic orchestral music)
(objects rumbling to ground)
(building rumbling over
dramatic orchestral music)
(robot rattling)
(man thuds to ground)
(lips smacking)
(metal rumbling)
(objects crashing to floor)
(whooshing electronic accent)
(mysterious electronic accent)
(dreamy and pleasant synth music)
(rockets whooshing)
(rhythmic and pleasant synth music)
(rocket whooshing)
(camera snapping)
(beams whooshing)
(roller coaster whooshing)
(rhythmic and pleasant synth rock music)
(tinkling chime accent)
(footsteps crunching)
(rhythmic and pleasant synth rock music)
(tinkling chime accent)
(crowd chattering)
(footsteps pattering)
(dreamy synth music)
(tinkling chime accent)
(buzzing electronic accent)
(dreamy synth music)
(footsteps crunching)
(robot crunches to ground)
(footsteps pattering)
(robot buzzing)
(dreamy synth music)
(machinery buzzing)
(slap cracking)
(car whooshing)
(pulsing electronic effects)
(girl whooshing through the air)
(robot whooshing)
(pleasant synth music)
(girl whooshing through the air)
(pulsing electronic effects)
(echoing popping effects)
(pleasant synth music)
(girl whooshing through the air)
(tinkling electronic accent)
(pleasant synth music)
(slap cracking)
(girl whooshing through the air)
(pulsing electronic effects)
(tense synth music)
(robot whooshing through the air)
(robot rumbling)
(beams whooshing over tense synth music)
(robot whooshing through the air)
(beam whooshing)
(tense synth music)
(metal cracking)
(punches thudding)
(girl whooshing through the air)
(robot rumbling)
(boy whooshing through the air)
(tense synth music)
(arm whooshing)
(girl whooshing through the air)
(arm snapping)
(eyes buzzing)
(tense synth music)
(beams whooshing)
(arm crunching)
(pleasant synth music)
(tinkling electronic effects)
(tinkling chime accent)
(boy whooshing through the air)
(tinkling electronic effects)
(electricity humming)
(strike whooshing)
(screeching electronic accent)
(boy whooshing through the air)
(electricity buzzing and rumbling)
(pleasant synth music)
(footsteps pattering)
(pleasant, vaguely mysterious
electronic music and strings)
(jangling percussion tones)
(airy and pleasant synth music)
(birds chirping)
(flowing and pleasant synth music)
(warm and pleasant synth music)
(jangling percussion tones)
(thunder rumbling)
(dramatic and expressive synth music)
(buzzing electronic accents)
(buzzing electronic accent)
(dramatic and expressive synth music)
(bright and pleasant synth music)
(expressive and flowing piano music)
(tinkling electronic tones
over expressive piano)
(expressive piano and electronic music)
(jangling percussion tones
over bright synth music)
(pulsing electronic tones)
(explosion rumbling over
tense, menacing synth music)
(ominous and tense synth music)
(explosion rumbling)
(glass shattering)
(rope whooshing)
(ominous and tense synth music)
(strike buzzing)
(eyes buzzing)
(building cracking)
(cord whooshing)
(strike thudding)
(robot clangs to ground)
(cord whooshing)
(tense and menacing synth music)
(electricity crackling)
(robot chuckling maniacally)
(tense synth music)
(driving synth rock music)
(rocket whooshing)
(ropes pulsing and whooshing)
(pulsing electronic effects)
(stomp thudding)
(stomps thudding and pulsing)
(driving synth rock music)
(explosion rumbling)
(beams pulsing)
(explosions rumbling)
(beams whooshing)
(robot groaning)
(hand snapping)
(buzzing electronic effects
over driving synth music)
(robot cracking)
(gunfire rattling)
(robot cracking and rumbling)
(robot pulsing)
(beams whooshing and pulsing)
(explosion rumbling)
(driving synth rock music
with snarling guitar)
(robot buzzing)
(gunfire cracking)
(body thuds to ground)
(sinister synth music)
(pulsing electronic effects)
(robot hissing)
(eyes buzzing)
(joints crunching)
(robot whooshing through the air)
(feet cracking to ground)
(eyes buzzing)
(snapping electronic effect)
(sinister synth music)
(robot pulsing)
(gunfire rattling)
(feet crunching)
(metal cracking)
(explosion rumbling)
(beams pulsing)
(explosions rumbling)
(peppy synth rock music)
(metal crunching)
(beams pulsing)
(explosion rumbling)
(peppy synth rock music)
(strikes thudding)
(buzzing electronic effects)
(punch thudding)
(peppy synth rock music)
(beam buzzing)
(body thudding to ground)
(beam crunching)
(peppy synth rock music
with snarling guitar)
(punches thudding)
(driving synth rock music
with snarling guitar)
(punch crunching)
(body thuds against wall)
(body thuds to ground)
(peppy synth rock music
with snarling guitar)
(snarling guitar music accent)
- [Man] Morning.
- Morning.
- [Street Vendor] Lady
pickers, fresh lady--
- [Man] G'day!
(footsteps pattering)
- [Woman] Hello, dear, just
give me a minute to finish my--
- [Woman] Not today, thank you.
(footsteps pattering)
- [Man] Hang on, I'm coming!
(strikes thwacking)
- [Man] Fine shot!
(man groans)
- [Man] Stop, wait!
Stop this nonsense at
once, you little ruffians!
At once, do you hear,
how dare you treat me--
- You heard what the man said!
- I sure did, so I guess we
better do as he says, right?
- Respect they deserve,
what's going on here?
- [Boy] Just one last kick!
(kick thwacking)
- [Man] (shouts) Someone call the police!
(children laughing)
- [Boy] He's so far up,
he'll never come down!
(children laughing)
It takes all the fun out of it!
(expressive and somber piano music)
(spoon rattling)
(man slurping)
- Good soup.
(silverware rattling over
expressive piano music)
But you usually serve it piping hot,
and this time, it's almost cold, curious!
(expressive and somber piano music)
(footsteps pattering)
- Mother, I'm leaving now.
After class, I'll come right home.
(footsteps pattering)
- Ta-ta!
(car buzzing)
Ever since my wife got a promotion,
she's always on the go.
She's what you might
call a true career woman.
I almost envy her.
Well, no, it's not that I'm jealous,
but she's an aggressive business woman
and generally more meticulous
than her male coworkers.
(car humming)
They accuse her of being un-ladylike,
but that's only because
she's so self-assured.
Men aren't used to that, I
suppose it makes them insecure.
(dog barking)
(children laughing)
- [Shepherd] Thanks!
- My colleagues think
that I let our situation
get out of hand, that I'm
a bit too pro-feminist.
(cars buzzing)
(water bubbling)
Well, just because my
consciousness about women
has been raised higher than theirs
doesn't mean I haven't
got a mind of my own.
(birds chirping)
(arm snapping)
(water splashing)
(chuckles) Right.
(birds chirping)
(bot buzzing)
- [Robotic Voice] Break time terminated.
- Hey, don't sneak up on me like that!
- [Robotic Voice] Absent from
workstation, explanation?
- None.
- [Robotic Voice] Return to workstation.
- Yes, right then, I hear you!
(footsteps clacking)
(bot buzzing)
(birds chirping)
(footsteps crunching)
I have a secret, I suppose
you could call it a project,
something I've been working on for years.
(expressive and somber piano music)
(door creaking)
Of course, my family
knows nothing about it.
(footsteps clacking)
I suppose I could trace it all
the way back to my childhood.
(expressive and somber piano music)
(footsteps clacking)
(tools crunching)
(expressive and somber piano music)
(man sighs)
I never knew my mother,
never experienced the warmth
of parental love and understanding.
Ever since I can remember,
I've longed to be happily married
and to raise a family of my own,
and in that way, to know
what it is to be loved.
(rain pattering over expressive
and somber piano music)
But now, I know that it wasn't
really marriage I longed for,
but something more
basic, more fundamental.
(footsteps clacking)
- [Man] We're on our way to the club.
- [Man] You go ahead.
(footsteps pattering)
(water splashing)
- [Man] See you later then,
we'll save you a seat!
- Yes, you do that!
(footsteps pattering)
(birds chirping)
(footsteps clacking)
(clock ticking)
- [Girl] (giggles) When are
you going to give me a name?
- [Man] Meow, meow, meow!
- (laughs) Hmm.
I'm not a pet!
(man gasps)
- [Man] Of course not, you're a machine.
(clock ticking)
- You see, I want someone to love me,
and for that, I need a name.
- What, why did you say that?
How could you say that?
I never programmed you to say those words.
(clock ticking)
- You must be very lonely.
- (scoffs) Psychoanalyzed
by a machine, what next?
Just out of curiosity, what
led you to that conclusion?
- [Girl] Your voice
tells me that you, too,
are new to this world,
that we are both children.
- You heard all that in my voice, did you?
Amazing!
(clock ticking)
(metal rattling)
(footsteps pattering)
(clock ticking over somber piano)
(man gasps over shattering glass)
- Make me feel that I'm alive.
Talk to me, respond to my existence!
(toy buzzing over somber piano music)
For what purpose do I exist?
To be alone is to be in pain.
- [Man] A machine feels no pain,
a machine can't feel at all!
You'll never know the sensual
pleasure of a fine meal
or possess a real identity of your own.
(toy buzzing)
- You believe that you know
your own desires and
dreams better than anyone.
Why shouldn't I believe the same thing?
You didn't create yourself
any more than I did.
(toy buzzing)
I want to experience life,
the excitement of living for myself!
Such a strange look, I don't
understand what it means.
(expressive and somber piano music)
(toy rattling)
(screws tinging on floor)
(footsteps pattering on floor)
(expressive and somber piano music)
(man gasps)
(toy tinging on floor)
(toys rattling)
(glass shattering)
(dress rustling)
(footsteps clacking)
(trunk thudding)
(glass tinging)
(man gasping desperately)
(expressive and somber piano music)
(man gasping)
(wrench rattling)
(pulsing electronic effects)
(expressive and somber piano music)
(toys rattling over expressive
and somber piano music)
(birds chirping over expressive
(distant car buzzing)
(birds chirping)
(door rattling)
(girl gasping)
- [Man] Leaving so soon?
- Afraid so, but we'll be
back again soon, Father.
Now you be nice to Mother.
Darling, come say goodbye to Grandpa.
(birds chirping)
- Goodbye, Grandpa.
Next time, you must make me a toy!
- Only if you promise to take
good care of your mother, hmm?
- Kay!
(footsteps pattering)
Goodbye!
(birds chirping)
(toy rattling)
(distant whistle screeching)
(birds chirping)
(expressive and somber piano music)
(toy rattling)
(explosion rumbling)
- [Girl] I'm still waiting for my prince
to rescue me from my solitude.
(liquid bubbling)
(explosions rumbling)
(somber piano music)
(liquid bubbling over somber piano music)
(knees thudding to ground)
(metal jingling)
(face clanging to ground)
(expressive piano music)
- [Man] I was never strong enough
to be your knight in shining armor.
Forgive me.
(expressive piano music)
(door creaking)
(footsteps clacking)
(wind howling over expressive piano music)
(tear clacking)
- Sweetheart, the wind
is starting to pick up.
Why don't you come in now, Dear.
(window rattling)
(wind howling)
(toy rattling)
(expressive electronic music and piano)
Come, Dear, don't be difficult.
If you stay outside any longer,
you'll catch your death!
Darling?
(hopeful piano music)
Sweetheart?
(woman gasps)
(hopeful piano music)
(woman gasping)
(flowing and hopeful piano music)
(toy rattling)
(toy rattling over hopeful piano music)
(metal clanging)
(townspeople screaming)
- Out of my way!
(townspeople shouting and screaming)
Of all the nerve!
(building cracking and rumbling)
(rhythmic and percussive electronic music)
(Jonathan cackling maniacally)
- Destroy, destroy!
Let this heathen's haven be
smashed to pieces (cackles)!
Their fate is in our hands,
my beautiful Automoton!
My walking doll, my Tinkerbelle (cackles)!
Let's go get 'em (cackles)!
Nothing is impossible
for a genius like me!
(wood cracking and rumbling)
This avaricious, greedy nation, Japan,
will soon be under my control!
A millennium of glory is at hand (laughs)!
A vast expanse of gold as
far as the eye can see!
Where shall I strike next?
- Enough's enough, that's it!
The time has come to defend our honor!
Yaori, you ready?
- Sure, but I don't think this machine
was built to defend anyone's honor.
- She's right, this machine
was built for the parade.
- [Kichi] That's our point, you nitwit!
Chubby, start shoveling that coal!
- You got it!
- [Kichi] Denjiro, all set down there?
- I'm set.
- Right, attack!
Forward!
(robot rumbling)
(rousing percussion music)
- What?
- Whoever you are,
you're messin' around with
the wrong bunch, mister!
You've had it, understand?
How dare you disturb the
peace and tranquility
of this special day when
our entire community
is preparing to celebrate the
opening of the new harbor!
This steam-driven behemoth
is under my command,
and I will use it to drive you
and your bloated monstrosity
back to wherever you came from!
Prepare to be destroyed!
Engage the enemy!
(whistle screeching)
Now Denjiro, right leg up!
- Okay.
(wood rattling and rumbling)
(kick thwacking)
(house rumbling and cracking)
Aw, you jackass!
We can't fight the enemy with sawdust!
Take it easy.
(footstep rumbling)
- [Villager] What the hell is happening?
(buildings rumbling)
- (growls) This is unforgivable!
Do you think that you
can move and maneuver
in the same way as my own machine,
a device which was created by me,
the world's greatest genius, do you?
Come on, get out of the way!
(growls) I'll show you, you dilettante!
- [Denjiro] Hey, Kichi,
somebody just came out of that thing!
- What, hold it right there, Denjiro!
Hmm, let's see now, where is he?
Where is he?
(gasps) I see him, I see him!
Oh my gosh (gulps)!
Toki, there's a foreigner,
what do we do now?
- [Toki] I say we see what he's up to.
- Hear this, I am the world's
most brilliant scientist,
Jonathan Jamison Volkeson III!
No doubt, the world's greatest genius!
I will not allow the course
chartered by my fearless intellect
to be changed by anyone, including you!
If you do not retreat at once,
I warn you, you will be annihilated.
I'll give you, let's see now, um,
ah, just three seconds more.
Three, two, one.
What a terribly unfortunate situation!
I pray that your souls may rest with God,
but time's up, I'm afraid!
- [Kichi] What a predicament!
What's he saying, Toki?
- Whoa, foreign language is
hard enough to translate,
but English through a
megaphone is impossible!
(cannon rumbling)
(explosion rumbling)
- (gasps) Oh!
(Denjiro gasping)
- [Kichi] Chubby, they're
firing, they're shooting at us!
Get up here on the double!
(crank rattling)
- Domination angle, 12 degrees.
Wind speed, three knots.
Fire!
(cannon rumbling)
(Yaori gasps)
(explosion rumbling)
- What's going on here?
- The bastard hit us, that's what!
- Just what the hell is going on here?
- I just answered that question!
- Excuse me!
(rousing electronic music)
- Yo, Kichi, here I am, boss.
(wood cracking)
(gasps) That's for launching
fireworks, that's no good!
- Wrong, it's our secret weapon.
(Jonathan chuckling over rustling brush)
Right, you ready?
(Chubby grunts)
- We show him!
(fuse hissing)
(cannon rumbling)
(fireworks screeching)
(explosion rumbling and popping)
(both cheering)
- Huh, what the?
- [Chubby] Look at that,
it's still standing!
What's it made of?
- [Kichi] That thing's
wow, well-built indeed!
(cannon rumbling)
(cannonball screeching)
(explosion rumbling)
- I'm not into the all dying one, ah well!
- So what do we do now, boss?
- We have no choice, we
keep on firing at him!
- That just might kill him, you know!
- (growls) You're gonna do
it, do you understand me?
Ready, aim,
(fuse hissing)
fire!
(cannon rumbling)
(explosion rumbling)
- (cackles) Their puny
little weapons can't hurt us,
can they, my pretty one (laughing)?
Huh?
(pounding timpani accents)
(explosions popping and rumbling)
(coughing) I won't allow it!
This can't be happening (coughs)!
- All right!
- Yes!
- Hey, boss, you really
clobbered that guy!
- Ha, that's nothing.
This next shot'll turn
that clown into dust!
(robot cracking and rumbling)
- Now you'll learn the true
power of my incredible genius!
- Hold on, what do you think you're doing?
- (groans) What's wrong?
- All you've done so far is destroy
half the buildings in the neighborhood!
- Oh, is that so?
Listen, pig slop!
- You egotistical gloryhound!
- [Toki] Excuse me!
(Kichi growling)
- I'm busy now!
- Ha, would you listen to Mister It, you--
- I've had just about enough of this!
(gears rattling)
- It appears that last
volley affected our mobility!
- [Kichi] Save it for later.
I told you I'm busy!
- (groans) You never listen!
Why don't you shut that big mouth of yours
for once and learn something?
- [Kichi] Ha, from you,
don't make me laugh!
- Your head should be stuffed and shown
in a museum somewhere so
that everyone will know
what a real pea-brained
idiot looks like, so there!
- [Kichi] And if they had an ugly museum,
you'd be the prime exhibit!
Why you, I oughta!
(Yaori blows a raspberry)
- Sheez, they're really
going at it this time!
I gotta break this up.
(gears rattling)
(footsteps clacking)
Stop arguing!
- Ya!
- On the other hand, if
you wanna argue, you can--
(shoe thwacking)
(robot rumbling and creaking)
- What?
I don't believe it!
All of the batteries have gone dead!
- Excuse me, Kichi,
but can we go home now?
We're out of coal.
- [Kichi] So, rip out
anything made of wood
and use that instead!
(Jonathan groaning)
(wood cracking)
(rousing orchestral music)
(footstep rumbling)
- I'll never give up, not ever!
- I'll never give up (groans)!
(Jonathan groaning)
- Now you will see the power
of my genius unleashed!
(robot groaning and creaking)
- [Kichi] Right arm forward!
- Oh, right!
(gears clanking)
(arms rumbling)
- We've got him now!
Yaori, move the left arm forward!
- At once.
- Good!
- [Yaori] Emperor Kichi.
- Huh, what did she mean by that?
(wood creaking)
- A-ha, I think I got him!
- [Kichi] Don't let go!
Hang on, Toki, hang on!
- Whatever you say!
- [Kichi] Hold on, it's
gonna be a rough ride!
(Chubby gasping)
Ready, Denjiro?
- Any time you are.
- Now left leg back, Denjiro.
(gears clanking)
(wood shuddering and creaking)
Banzai!
(wood creaking)
(wood snapping)
(wood rumbling and cracking)
(water splashing)
(robot rumbling to ground)
(water roaring)
- Oh, so many beautiful buildings in ruin,
it's just horrible!
On the other hand, this side looks okay.
(playful orchestral music)
- We won!
- Oh, yeah, some victory.
- So much for the parade.
- At least we're all alive.
- Hey, look at that!
The rising sun of Japan!
- The sun is setting, dimwit!
(Kichi growling)
Oh, you mean symbolically, sort of.
- The fighting's over, and
we've defeated the invader,
and our beloved town is peaceful again.
If you ask me, not a bad day's work, huh?
- Huh?
- Ya wanna?
(Yaori growling)
(strike crunching)
(Kichi growling)
Ya!
(piercing percussion accents)
- Ha, so the fools think that
they've beaten me (cackles)!
But they haven't seen the last of me!
Not by a longshot, and
speaking of longshots,
just wait till they face my self-propelled
autotargeting artillery!
Nothing is impossible for
a genius like me, right?
Of course, I'm right!
I'm always right (cackling maniacally)!
(thudding percussion accent)
(crowd muttering over
muffled traffic humming)
(distant car horns honking)
(menacing synth accents)
(ominous and tense synth music)
(ominous and rhythmic synth music)
(buzzing electronic accent)
(ominous and tense synth music)
(explosions rumbling)
(pulsing electronic accent)
(ominous and tense synth music)
(explosion rumbling)
(robot whooshing)
(buzzing electronic tones)
(ominous and tense synth rock music)
(beams pulsing)
(ground rumbling)
(ominous and tense synth rock music)
(beams pulsing)
(tense and menacing orchestral rock music)
(sputtering electronic tones)
(buzzing electronic accents)
(tense and menacing orchestral rock music)
(menacing orchestral music accents)
(ominous and menacing orchestral music)
(bubbling electronic tones
over menacing orchestral music)
(cymbals crashing)
(bubbling electronic tones
over menacing orchestral music)
(anxious snare drum accent)
(tense and menacing orchestral music)
(tense and menacing orchestral rock music)
(buzzing electronic accent)
(mallet thudding)
(tense and menacing orchestral rock music)
(beam buzzing)
(jingling discordant percussion tones)
(ominous and tense synth music)
(explosion rumbling)
(tense and menacing orchestral rock music)
(strike whooshing)
(muffled trumpeting tones)
(tense orchestral accents)
(ominous and tense synth music)
(tense and menacing orchestral rock music)
(explosions rumbling)
(metal clanging)
(tense and menacing orchestral rock music)
(metal rumbling to ground)
(buzzing electronic accent)
(robot whooshing)
(metal cracking and rumbling)
(tense and percussive synth music)
(ominous and tense synth music)
(quietly tense and uneasy synth music)
(motorbike rumbling)
(explosion popping)
(metal rattling)
(crowd chattering)
(wind howling)
(pleasant synth music)
(machinery rumbling)
(machinery buzzing)
(pleasant synth and orchestral music)
(machinery rumbling and hissing)
(whistles screeching)
(explosions rumbling)
(pleasant orchestral music)
(camel groaning)
(pleasant orchestral music
with tinkling keyboard tones)
(pulsing electronic accent)
(pleasant orchestral music
with tinkling keyboard tones)
(children gasping)
(button clicks)
(ball buzzing and pulsing)
(pleasant mallet percussion accent)
(pleasant music box melody)
(children gasping)
(children laughing and clapping)
(tinkling electronic tones)
(beams buzzing)
(explosion rumbling)
(rousing orchestral music)
(noisy ambient tones)
(pleasant orchestral music and synth)