Okay, then.
You can do this, Chocola.
[CHOCOLA]
There we go.
You think Master made
it to his destination?
The strawberry farm he's
visiting is pretty far away,
so I doubt he's
arrived there yet.
[CHOCOLA]
That's true.
Hopefully he'll find lots of
yummy strawberries!
Master has the best judgment
when it comes to
business and food.
[AZUKI]
We're back!
And we bought a ton of supplies.
This way we'll be
ready for anything.
We got meat croquettes,
pumpkin croquettes,
and crab cream croquettes!
I didn't know you both
were so into croquettes.
We're not. The store was just
pushing their sales super hard.
Yeah, and of course
we couldn't resist.
--[crash]
--[COCONUT yells]
[CINNAMON]
You okay?
Why are you smashing our
windows, you clumsy cat?
It was obviously an accident!
Give me a break, Azuki!
[KASHOU]
I hope everyone's all right.
And that the storm
preparations are almost done.
Oh, well. As long
as they're together,
that's all that matters.
[CONDUCTOR 07A]
Attention passengers.
Due to the weather, we are
making an emergency stop.
[PASSENGER 07A]
For real?
[PASSENGER 07B] But we're
in the middle of nowhere.
[CONDUCTOR 07A]
We're currently experiencing
extremely strong winds.
As a precaution, all trains
have been brought to a stop.
Operations will resume
once the weather
conditions have improved.
All regions should be
prepared for heavy rain,
strong winds and high waves,
especially in Eastern
and Northern Japan.
The storm will hit its peak
tomorrow morning and is...
So this may sound weird,
but I kind of like storms.
I don't know why.
You can't sunbathe when it's
all rainy and gross outside.
That's true, but...
...I just think that storms
feel really exciting, you know?
I can't believe Shigure
went out in this weather.
I hope she makes it
back before it gets worse.
It was a "Cat Meeting," right?
Yes, something like that.
Basically it's an
in-person gathering
for her online
group of cat lovers.
But shouldn't she have
been back home by now?
[MAPLE] Don't worry, she's in
a car, so I'm sure she's fine.
[CHOCOLA grunts]
Okay, Cacao, it's my turn.
[CACAO giggles]
Right. Chocola?
Okay...
This one!
Wait a sec. That card
could be a decoy!
But what if she's
trying to trick Chocola?
This one then!
No way!
Your poker face sucks.
I win.
Why does Chocola always lose?
[phone ringing]
Oh!
Hello, Shigure?
Sorry I'm taking so long.
Traffic is really bad.
I don't think I'm gonna
make it home tonight.
[MAPLE] Did your meeting
run late or something?
Well, we got excited
talking about cats
and lost track of the time.
Ah.
No worries, we'll be okay here.
You should book a
hotel room or something.
[SHIGURE]
Yeah, that's the plan.
I'm counting on you to take care
of the house and each other.
This really stinks.
I hate the thought of
having to be away from
my cats for the night.
So that's what's happening.
Looks like we're on
our own for now.
That's crazy. I hope
Shigure will be okay.
[AZUKI] The weather is
getting pretty wild, huh?
Whoa. It's getting wild?
As in it might lose control?
No way. But, then...
...what will happen to us if
it gets too crazy out there?
I'm begging you,
weather, be gentle with me!
Please!
I'm gonna go have a
chat with the weather!
Hey, don't go out there!
Do you wanna order a pizza?
Like they'd even deliver!
But look at all
this delicious cheese.
It says it's super
rich and melty.
Chocola thinks
it's a great idea!
[CHOCOLA, AZUKI]
What?
--[AZUKI] A blackout?
--[COCONUT] Just stay calm!
How scary. Anything could
happen to us in the dark!
Cacao! Don't move! [groans]
Did you seriously not see that?
Yeah, what kind of cat are you?
[MAPLE gasps]
Come on, Vanilla,
stop scaring everybody.
I thought my heart was
gonna pop outta my chest.
[CHOCOLA] What?! Hearts
can pop out like that?!
Man, having no power
is kind of boring, huh?
[COCONUT]
Wanna play a word game?
I've got it. What if we
all had a riddle contest?
Uhh... But Chocola's not
good at solving riddles.
I know.
I could tell everybody a story
to try to help pass the time.
Sure, why not?
Sounds like a lot of fun!
[CHOCOLA]
Tell us! Tell us!
Okay, then.
It's an excellent story.
A long, long time ago,
there were two cats
walking through
the forest one night.
[MAPLE]
Hold up.
Is there a reason why
I'm a character in this?
[COCONUT]
We're trying to listen.
--[AZUKI] No way!
--[chattering]
What's that? Sounds
like a party or something.
[MAPLE] It seems to be
coming from that direction.
[BOTH gasp]
[VANILLA] Much to their
surprise, they had stumbled upon
a group of cats who seemed
to be having some
sort of drinking party.
How odd.
What are all these
cats doing here?
Well, it would
seem we have guests.
[MAPLE] Why are you out here
in the middle of the woods?
Jeez, what's up with
the interrogation?
How 'bout you come join us?
More people just means more fun!
Have some.
One sip shouldn't hurt.
Oh, wow, this is amazing!
I've never had such tasty
cat nip juice before!
It's great!
Go on. Have another one.
Thanks so much!
[VANILLA] And so, the two
travelers joined in on the fun
and spent the whole night
partying with their new friends.
No, not there.
[MAPLE]
What happened to everyone?
Why would they just up and leave
in the middle of the night?
Huh?
[SHIGURE]
One... two...
What a relief. I'm glad
someone's still here.
The deep-fried tofu
looks delicious.
...five... six...
[MAPLE]
Strange. Were you at the party?
I don't recognize you.
[SHIGURE] I counted all of
them, but I'm missing one.
[yelps] Hey, wake up!
Stop, I said to
be gentle with me.
This is no time to be sleeping!
[MAPLE panting]
[sighs]
[CINNAMON grunts]
Something wrong?
Yes, this whole night is crazy!
Didn't you see the ghastly
woman in the well, too?
[CINNAMON] My goodness,
that sounds terrifying.
No joke, it scared
the life out of me.
[gasps]
[MAPLE screams]
Whoa.
Awesome, that story
was super fun and scary!
Yeah, it was a real blast.
A real thriller of tale.
It was great! Right?
[VANILLA]
Do you really think so?
[ALL gasp]
[ALL whimper]
I'm happy you all enjoyed it.
[COCONUT]
What the--? How'd you do that?
[VANILLA]
It was a make-up trick.
Come on, are you serious?
Since when could make-up
remove your face?
Well... time for the next story.
[MAPLE]
Let's do something else.
Maple, I have to tell
at least 100 stories.
Otherwise I won't be
able to summon the ghosts.
Why would you even want to?!
[COCONUT]
Hey, the power's back!
[sighs] Could we maybe try
telling a happier story?
[CHOCOLA]
Then just leave it to Chocola!
Get ready, because
this is a good one!
[CHOCOLA] Once upon
a time, in a land far away,
two close sisters
decided to go on a picnic.
[VANILLA] Chocola and I
are the close sisters.
I approve.
[CHOCOLA] But, the two
of them soon got lost.
They couldn't figure out
how to get back home.
--[CHOCOLA] Wow!
--[VANILLA] Ohh.
[CHOCOLA] Luckily, they
stumbled upon a huge house
made entirely of sweets!
[CHOCOLA]
This fence is delicious!
[VANILLA]
I'm stuffed.
[CHOCOLA]
From that day on,
the two sisters lived
happily ever after
in the conveniently
abandoned dessert house.
That's the end of the story!
What?
Is that really the whole thing?
Yep! That's all of it!
Didn't you think it was fun?
Oh, uh, well, it was fun, but
it didn't have much of a point.
Nope.
Actually, the story
isn't over quite yet.
I would like to add to it.
Think of this
next part as a sequel.
Several days
passed as the sisters
enjoyed their
new house of sweets.
They had formed a daily routine.
[VANILLA humming]
Chocola's home.
[VANILLA]
Welcome back!
Oh, man. The boss
was so annoying today.
Chocola's pretty tired.
Sounds like you worked hard.
Any idea what you'd
like to do first?
You could eat dinner...
...or take a bath...
...or bathe me.
[AZUKI]
Stop!
I'm ending this story.
[VANILLA] It was just
getting good, though.
Let's keep it PG.
But... I wanna
know how it ended.
Fine, have it your way.
I can always tell
a different fairytale.
Once upon a time
in a faraway land,
there lived a cat who made an
honest living chopping bamboo.
[COCONUT] Like I always say, if
it's glowing it's gotta be good!
I bet there's probably
gold in there or something.
[VANILLA] From the magical
bamboo, she appeared--
a ghastly woman.
[COCONUT]
Like from the well?!
[AZUKI]
Reusing gags, are we?
[VANILLA]
Okay, I'll tell another one.
You'll like this.
The young cat waved goodbye
to the sea turtle after a long,
but wonderful journey
to the dragon palace.
[stomach rumbles]
[VANILLA] But when she
opened the treasure casket
she had received as a gift,
out popped the ghastliest woman.
[AZUKI]
Again?
[CINNAMON]
It's kind of predictable.
[VANILLA]
Huh?
I'm over your weird
stories, Vanilla.
Sit back, relax,
and let an old pro
show you how it's really done.
[VANILLA grunts]
[MAPLE]
Like any other day,
the lumberjack was hard
at work, chopping wood.
[gasps]
[MAPLE] Unfortunately,
her axe fell into a fountain.
[VANILLA] And from the water
emerged... a ghastly woman!
[MAPLE]
No!
There aren't any stupid
ghosts in this story!
What? So it's not
even scary? Weird.
It's not supposed to be, okay?
Ehem. Now then,
where was I again?
Oh, yes, so from the
fountain emerged... a goddess.
Tell me, o honest woodcutter,
which of these belongs to you?
Is it the gold
or the silver one?
It's both.
Yes, so I see. It's
neither of them, then-- Huh?
I dropped both of them.
[CINNAMON]
Say what?
[VANILLA]
They're both mine.
Oh, um... They are?
Are you certain?
Look, if you're lying to me,
then you're gonna
be in big trouble--
Stop beating around
the bush and hand them over.
If you don't,
I'll drain your fountain--
the whole thing.
I'll compensate you.
Give them up,
and I'll let you read my
super-secret fantasy diary,
detailing the
intimate activities
between myself and Chocola.
[CINNAMON]
Intimate you say?
Done.
[panting]
Holy wow, pistil to pistil!
You've just opened up
a whole new world for me!
Reading this,
I just can't help myself.
Reading these intimate
details is making me so wet!
[sighs] Thanks so much for
this enlightening experience.
You may take both
the gold and silver axes.
Yes, score.
[MAPLE] And thus, the lumberjack
was able to get both--
Stop the story!
You guys know I'm not actually
a huge pervert, don't you?
[GROUP]
Huh?
Plus that's really mean.
You've gone too far with
your creative liberties!
We're sorry, you make
a pretty fair point.
Yeah, we didn't mean it.
It should be dreamier!
Less lewd and more
like a real fairytale!
In that case... I've got one.
Once upon a time,
three cats found a lamp
on the side of the road.
[AZUKI]
What's this thing?
Maybe someone dropped it?
Looks kinda old and dirty.
For real.
[ALL gasp]
[COCONUT] There was a puff
of a smoke and out came a...
...ghastly woman.
[COCONUT clears throat]
Out came a magical genie!
How may I serve you, my Masters?
[MAPLE]
Now that's a creative liberty.
[CHOCOLA] Master is
awesome no matter what he is!
What the heck?
[KASHOU] I will grant
each of you one wish.
Whatever you desire.
--[CHOCOLA] Amazing!
--[AZUKI] Seriously?
Then Chocola wants
to eat a huge fish--
the biggest fish ever!
As you wish, Master.
[CHOCOLA gasps]
[CHOCOLA]
Wow!
You think it's a tuna or a--
A shark! [yells]
Why is there a
shark in the river?
I'm more interested
to know how it can fly.
Now, what's your desire,
Young Master?
--[CINNAMON] Um, about that...
--[KASHOU] Hm?
The thing is...
...what I want...
[KASHOU] You can wish
for anything you please.
[CINNAMON gulps]
I wish for-- [bleep]
What the heck is wrong
with you?! How can you say...
[MAPLE]
Try and have a little decency.
[CINNAMON]
But that wasn't even me!
It was just part of the story!
I'm sure.
What a terrible excuse.
Right, next story.
How 'bout a palette cleanser?
[COCONUT]
When the cat woke up,
she was in a land
filled with tiny people.
This is kind of bizarre.
Princess, the
giant has awakened!
What now?
I wonder if she has come
here to invade our country.
Do you want us
to hang her, Princess?
Or burn her at the stake?
Or better yet, we could peel
off her toenails one by one!
[AZUKI grunting]
[AZUKI] Aw, yeah!
I'm finally the biggest, baby!
[COCONUT]
The giant's rampage knew no end.
The earth shattered
beneath her feet,
and the demonic fire she
breathed melted their walls.
[AZUKI]
Hey. What kind of story is that?
I just wanted to
give you your wish
since the genie never
got to in the last story.
And what on earth makes
you think that's my wish?
I thought you'd
want to get bigger?
Uh, hard pass. I'm not
a monster, y'know.
Wow, that was
a pretty good story.
[AZUKI]
In what universe?
Here, this one is a favorite.
[CINNAMON]
Matches for sale.
Uh, would you like to
buy some matches, sir?
[MAPLE] The cat tried
her best to sell the matches,
but nobody would buy from her.
Would you like some matches?
I guess I won't be
eating tonight either.
[CINNAMON] I know. I'll use
these matches to stay warm.
[CINNAMON]
How nice. That looks so cozy.
I wish I could join them.
It looks so intimate.
No.
I was so close to
being part of that dream.
[CINNAMON] I bet that cat
cuddle party is so warm.
This daydream...
...I can't help it.
It makes me wet.
[MAPLE] And though
she met a terrible fate,
the poor cat's expression
was at least one of happiness.
[CINNAMON]
Come on, May.
Do you have like a grudge
against me or something?
[MAPLE] No, I just thought it
was the perfect role for you.
Well, I don't
appreciate everyone
treating me like a big pervert.
Right! Leave it to me,
I've got a great story.
Once, there was a princess
who bit into a poison apple
and fell into a deep sleep.
Is the princess gonna
nap all day or what?
She's gonna miss tea time
if she doesn't wake up soon.
How terrible.
We simply must find a way to
wake her up as fast as possible!
Chocola has an awesome idea!
Tickle, tickle, tickle, tickle!
There's no response.
It's almost like
she's dead or something.
I'm gonna go get a shovel.
We can't bury her!
Cremation?
[COCONUT]
Neither! She's not even dead!
[AZUKI]
Hmm... Still nothing, huh?
Stop writing on her!
That was kind of you.
[COCONUT]
Though the scribble on her head
makes it look sorta dumb.
Listen, everyone,
I think I know what to do.
This is probably a curse,
so all she needs is a kiss
from someone she loves
in order to break the spell!
--[GROUP gasps]
--[AZUKI, COCONUT] Kiss?
Yes, AKA a smoochie smooch.
Uhh... Wait, as in you
want one of us to kiss her?
This is all so sudden.
C'mon, it's for the princess.
We have to do this!
Yes. I agree as well.
[COCONUT gasps]
Fine, whatever. She can have
my first kiss. It's no biggie.
[gasps]
[CINNAMON]
Do your best!
Uh... then in that case,
Okay. Mine, too.
[VANILLA, AZUKI]
Cool, give it a shot.
Uh?
[CINNAMON panting]
[AZUKI] She leaned in close
to give the princess a kiss,
and then she--
[COCONUT, MAPLE]
What?
[AZUKI]
Another blackout?
[COCONUT]
That scared me.
[CHOCOLA] Chocola totally
forgot about the storm!
But I wanna hear
how the story ends.
[clacking]
Do you hear that weird noise?
Yeah, I wonder what it could be?
Kinda sounds like it's
getting closer, doesn't it?
Stop that! You're just
trying to scare us!
--[door opens]
--[yelps]
Was that...
...the front door?
Oh! I bet this is
just Vanilla again!
You're right. It's probably
another one of her pranks.
Vanilla does love
teasing people.
It isn't me this time.
[MAPLE]
Mm? How did you get there?
Oh, thank you so much, Cacao.
Now Chocola can see!
There's nothing
for us to be afraid of.
[ALL scream]
I didn't want to
be alone all night,
so I just decided to walk home.
[ALL groan]
What?