Hello there.
Tell me, do you know about cats?
They've got cute ears
that wiggle and twitch.
Tails that respond
to their emotions.
All attached to a human-like
creature of the utmost charm!
[SHIGURE]
Does that pique your interest?
If they sound appealing to you,
please visit our patisserie.
We have the cutest cats
you've ever seen.
All waiting to serve you!
[ALL] Hi and welcome!
To the patisserie La Soleil!
What's this?
She's gone?
Where are you, kitty?
Come out, come out,
wherever you are!
[door opens]
[AZUKI]
What's with all the shouting?
It's too early for
all this commotion.
The thing is,
I can't find her anywhere.
You're talking about
the new kitten, right?
Weird, I thought she slept
in your room last night?
Don't tell me she's lost.
What? How on earth would
she get lost inside the house?
It's not like she's Coconut.
What was that?
Oh? You want some?
Can we please not start
the day with fighting?
Oh, wow. I wish
I had their energy.
[COCONUT] How can something
so small be so loud?!
[gasps]
What is it?
[ALL gasp]
[SHIGURE]
Oh, my.
Why is she sleeping
in the bathroom?
[CINNAMON giggles]
I suppose the warm toilet seat
just seemed like
a good place to sleep.
[CHOCOLA]
I wonder...
Do you think she's eating
breakfast, too, right now?
[gasps]
Yeah? What's up?
Um...
That's not jam,
it's soy sauce-boiled laver.
[CHOCOLA yelps]
The early morning makes
you kinda spacey, huh?
It's so adorable.
Chocola is not spacey!
In fact... uh...
This was on purpose!
Your excuses are cute,
too, just like you.
Oh, wow, this is
actually delicious!
Well, that was unexpected.
[KASHOU chuckles]
Did she remember
to brush her teeth?
Chocola.
Huh?
Look.
[CHOCOLA gasps]
[CHOCOLA groans]
[CHOCOLA]
It'll be okay!
Shigure is there and
so is everyone else.
Chocola isn't even
worried about the kitten!
She's just on Chocola's
mind a teensy bit.
Well, if I were you,
I would worry more about myself.
What the--?
Tell me, are you really that
worried about her, Chocola?
Where's your house at?
[KITTEN]
Hm?
Do you have a name?
[KITTEN]
Hm?
I still have a lot of questions.
We never found out her name
or where she comes from.
[VANILLA]
Mm...
Here we go, Sugarcane.
We always have to wash our hands
before we eat a meal, okay?
Who's Sugarcane?
It's her. Can't just
call her the kitten, right?
Everybody needs a name.
Well, sure, she needs
to be called something,
but not just anything.
You should at least put some
thought into giving
her a good name.
[CINNAMON]
"How to name a baby kitten"?
Oh, a baby?
As in a pistil and
a stamen together?
Nine months of gestation.
[gasping]
[MAPLE gasps] I don't know what
you're thinking about right now,
but please cut it out.
I agree with Maple,
you're gonna be a bad
influence on the kitten!
No, Sugarcane!
Avert thine eyes!
Wait just a moment, Azuki.
You shouldn't name the kitten
without her permission.
Besides, if she is lost,
then it's quite likely
she already has a name.
Also, can you put
your phone away
while we're eating, Maple?
It's important to
have good manners.
[COCONUT]
Okay. You can sit right here.
You're such a good kitty, huh?
And so adorable!
Okay, everyone.
It's time to eat.
Thanks for the food.
[GROUP]
Hold on. Where'd
the kitten run off to?
Goodness!
Uh, what's she doing down there?
Wow, you guys are
really working hard.
Yeah, we can take over
if you need a little break.
Oh, Azuki, Coconut.
Is she, um,
you know, doing okay?
Uh, who's "she"?
Wait, you mean Sugarcane, right?
[BOTH]
Her name's Sugarcane?
Would you stop calling her that?
Shigure told you not to name her
without permission, remember?
She's doing just
fine, by the way.
In fact, she finished her
entire breakfast this morning.
Though she does
have the ability to
disappear and reappear
in the strangest places.
That's so true! Yeah!
She's super delusive, right?
I'm pretty sure you mean
she's super elusive.
Well, what's important
is that she's okay.
Honestly, the girl's
really low maintenance.
Good to hear.
Well then, sounds like
everything's great.
By the way,
she likes dried fish.
If you give her
some for a snack,
she'll probably appreciate it!
[AZUKI]
Okay then, noted.
[COCONUT]
Yeah, we'll give it a try.
[SHIGURE]
Yes, I see.
So, as of right now, there
aren't currently any reports
of lost cats that match
her description then?
Okay, I appreciate your time.
[SHIGURE]
Let's see.
Lost cats... lost cats...
Right.
I'm a big sister now,
so I've gotta stay sharp!
[COCONUT] I've gotten used to
the job, so I can handle this.
Easy peasy!
[meows]
[growling]
[giggles]
[COCONUT groaning] What am
I even doing with my life?
I'm such a bad big sister.
Uh, listen, Nuts, can you
please go and grab some more
of the to-go boxes
from the back room?
We need to restock
all of the sizes.
But be careful,
they're pretty heavy.
'Kay! Don't you worry,
I can handle it!
She's so easy to read sometimes.
Right, then. Guess I'd
better get back to work!
[AZUKI humming]
Thank you so much
for waiting! Here.
[AZUKI] Let's see, two
seasonal special short cakes,
along with one cherry
and cassis cheesecake,
and, then three crème brulées.
For all six items together,
it'll be... 2200 yen, please.
[VANILLA, CHOCOLA]
Ohh!
Thank you, please come again!
Don't you think Azuki
is just ameowzing?
She's the eldest cat
of the Minaduki family,
so of course she's
very competent.
[AZUKI] Sheesh. When
it comes to this shop,
there's just no
rest for the weary.
Azuki? I finished
refilling the to-go boxes
like you asked me to.
Ah. Thanks a bunch.
Things seem to've
slowed down a little.
Do you need help with
anything back here?
Not really, I think I've got a
pretty good handle on all of it.
And besides, you're still
just a growing kitten.
It's important not
to stretch yourself thin.
Heh... Except I'm not
the one stretching, am I?
Need some help
with that, squirt?
[AZUKI gasps]
No! That's okay!
[COCONUT]
Oh, come on.
Life's too short not to
ask for a little help, right?
Excuse you? Jerk!
Heh. Aw, you having a small
problem reaching me, Azuki?
[AZUKI growls, yells]
[VANILLA, CHOCOLA gasp]
[COCONUT]
Punch harder!
For those two, this is
just business as usual.
Don't worry.
On today's feature, we're
checking out a popular aquarium!
Follow me inside
as we take a closer look.
Wow! Isn't it beautiful?
[rumbling]
Oh, my, sounds like
you're hungry.
Nice timing!
It's three o'clock,
so let's have tea.
Wow. You're pretty serious
about this stuff, aren't you?
Her first time having
tea should be perfect,
otherwise she won't
learn how to appreciate it.
Oh, that makes sense.
Well, in that case,
let's dig in--
Wait, hold on a minute!
Darjeeling is one of the
three great teas of the world.
It's best for drinking straight.
Assam is good with milk.
And last but not least,
this one is Earl Grey.
Uhh, I'm sorry, but
what are you doing?
I said the first time
needs to be perfect,
so I'm enrolling her into
my elite tea training program!
Okay. In order to
make delicious tea,
it is important to mind
the water temperature.
The first thing you do is boil
fresh water at 100 degrees,
then pre-pour some
hot water into the cups
and pots to warm them up.
Then you put in the tea leaves,
add the boiled water,
and let it steep for a moment.
Take care not to let the
temperature drop too much.
There! And that is your
first lesson in tea!
She's gone?
[CINNAMON] Aha. This is
where you disappeared to.
What? You prefer that over
my tea party? Seriously?
Now, now, different cats
just prefer different
things, that's all.
Ohh, she likes it!
Isn't that wonderful?
Whatever makes
her happy, I guess.
[CHOCOLA]
You like it?
[KITTEN]
Mm-hm.
[CHOCOLA] Perfect!
Eat as much as you like.
Are you already full?
I'm not surprised you
love that snack so much.
They're super high quality.
[BOTH]
Hmm?
[MAPLE] "A long time
ago in a land far away,
an old man and
woman lived together.
The woman left home one day."
[CINNAMON]
Hi, Mama Bear, I'm home.
Welcome home, Papa Bear.
What would you like to do first,
have dinner or take a bath?
Or something else?
Like bathe me?
Here, give it a try.
Yeah, come on, it's easy!
Like this, see?
Pretty cool, huh?
Not to mention fun!
[BOTH gasp, groan]
Should I even bother asking
what you two are doing?
Well, the kitten seemed
like she was lonely.
We thought she might
want to play, so...
Yeah, but... nothing seems
to pique her interest.
[SHIGURE] I think we
should just leave her be.
It's possible that the thing
she needs most right now
is a little bit
of time to herself.
[SHIGURE]
These are some toys that
the Minaduki cats have
enjoyed over the years.
Feel free to play with
whatever ones you like.
Oh! That's an old favorite.
In fact, Chocola played
with it all the time
when she was smaller.
[CHOCOLA]
Thank you! Come visit us again!
[VANILLA]
We appreciate your business.
[bell rings, door closes]
Good work out there today.
If it's okay with you,
we're gonna take off soon.
[gasps] Hey, Azuki? Um...
Yeah? You need something?
Well, uh, it's nothing much.
Never mind,
but thank you. [laughs]
[AZUKI]
Hmm...
Yeah. Chocola's positive
that everything is hunky-dory!
The kitten is in good hands.
Right, let's go.
Hey, everybody!
Huh? Where's Sugarcane?
Sheesh. Now, Azuki,
what did I tell you about giving
the kitten a name
without her permission?
Speaking of, could you
two please go get her?
Dinner's almost ready.
[MAPLE, CINNAMON]
Sure.
[MAPLE]
She's gone?
How odd.
[COCONUT]
I can't find her anywhere.
Maybe she's not
in the house at all.
Perhaps she's outside.
Let's all go look together.
Hey! Sugarcane!
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
It's dinner time, kitty!
Come on, where are you?
I guess I have no choice.
These are desperate times.
[COCONUT]
She can't resist catnip!
[CINNAMON, MAPLE, AZUKI gasp]
Don't be nuts, Nuts!
Yeah, don't open that jar!
[ALL sigh]
Of course this happens.
No surprise there.
[phone rings]
Hi, this is
Patisserie La Soleil.
Oh, hey, what's up, Shigure?
Did you need something?
Uh-huh. [gasps]
[VANILLA]
Hm?
[phone clicks]
[CHOCOLA yells]
Please let Chocola go!
The shop is still open, you
can't run off whenever you like.
I have to leave. It's the
kitten--she's gone missing!
Shigure told me!
[KASHOU, VANILLA gasp]
They searched everywhere,
but she wasn't inside the house.
Her shoes are gone,
so she must have gone outside.
Which means we should...
Right. Understood.
I can stay and
handle things here.
There's no time to waste,
you should go and look for her.
Wait, you're sure
it's okay? But you said...
It's no problem, don't worry.
We'll be just fine here.
Trust me, I can handle
things until you get back.
Yeah, and we'll join you
as soon as we close up here.
[VANILLA]
Now get moving.
Thank you so much, Vanilla!
And you, too, Master,
Chocola will hurry!
Where are you?
Answer me! Tell Chocola
where you are!
[AZUKI]
Sugarcane!
[COCONUT]
Where'd you run off to?
You check over there
and I'll head this way.
We'll find her. Now move!
I'm on it!
Hey! Hold up!
Huh?
Oopsies, wrong kitten!
Please forgive Chocola!
[CINNAMON] Excuse me, but
have you seen a small kitten?
No.
[MAPLE] She's wearing
a hat, 'bout this tall.
[MAN 03A]
No, sorry.
[CHOCOLA] What if she's
lonely all by herself?
[CHOCOLA] What if she's scared
and doesn't know what to do?
What if she's crying right now?
[CHOCOLA yelps]
[WOMAN 03B gasps]
No! Chocola has to find her!
[CHOCOLA]
Not here.
Chocola thought that the kitten
might come back to this place.
Where did you run off to?
[KITTEN]
Here.
[gasps]
[gasps] It's you!
[CHOCOLA laughs, crying]
But why? Why did you disappear
on everyone like that?
You scared them and Chocola.
You scared everyone!
[CHOCOLA cries]
With you.
[CHOCOLA]
Huh?
I wanna stay with you.
[chattering]
[door opens, bell chimes]
Oh, wow, you found her!
You scoundrel!
You had us all worried sick.
Well, all that matters is
that you're back safe and sound.
It's such a relief.
It's late. We've
had a long night,
so it's time for
us to head home.
[CHOCOLA]
Mm. Hold on, I have a request.
Yes? Go on.
[CHOCOLA]
About the kitten...
If you must, you can cut
Chocola's food in half.
And Chocola will
dress and bathe her.
And she'll potty train her!
If the kitten gets in trouble,
you may scold Chocola!
So, please, please...
Please let the kitten
stay with us!
Chocola is begging you!
Master.
If this is what Chocola wants,
then I will back her up.
I'll beg, as well.
So, please.
[KASHOU chuckles]
You know what's funny?
I don't ever remember
telling you guys
that she couldn't stay here.
Wait, does that mean...?
Yes, but only if you
take good care of her.
There's only two of you
here, so what's one more?
Oh, thank you!
This is great news!
Now we can live
together forever!
It's wonderful, isn't it? It is!
Chocola is so, so, so, so happy!
[CHOCOLA giggling]