[gasps]
Do you enjoy hanging out
in the corner or something?
Uh...
Look, I don't know
what's going on,
but hiding won't
change anything.
[CINNAMON gasps]
[MAPLE chuckles]
[CINNAMON]
Mm...
Time to stand tall
and face your fears.
[giggles]
Thank you, May...
...for getting on to me,
and not letting me hide.
I promise... today is
a day I'll never forget.
[CHOCOLA laughing]
[VANILLA chuckles]
[MAPLE, CINNAMON laugh]
[MAPLE laughs]
[CINNAMON giggles]
[machinery beeps, rings]
--[STAFF 09A] Three, two, one...
--[COCONUT whimpering]
--[BOTH scream]
--[STAFF 09A] Buh-bye!
--[COCONUT screaming]
--[AZUKI laughing]
[SHIGURE laughs]
Perfect.
I managed to capture their
adorable smiles on camera!
I feel like the amusement
park is the perfect place
to spend a much-needed day off.
Right, Kashou?
Uh-huh.
Everyone works really hard,
so this was a good idea.
They all deserve
to have a little fun.
Especially since Cacao
is still just a kitten.
It's important for
her to play outside.
[CHOCOLA]
Cacao.
[CACAO]
Mm?
Hold still, okay?
Chocola.
What's up?
Just hold still.
[chuckles] So what do
you wanna do next?
Uh? That one.
[MAPLE screams]
[MAPLE screaming]
[MAPLE whimpers]
Oh, come on, was the haunted
house really that scary?
I'd hate to have to
call you a scaredy cat.
What? I'm not scared.
I was obviously just pretending.
I have to put on an act
for the ghosts' sake.
I don't wanna hurt
their feelings.
Yeah, okay, tell yourself
whatever makes you feel better,
but I know you have to leave
the bathroom door open at night.
Hey, careful, Azuki,
we have to keep the fact
that May leaves it wide
open at night a secret.
Whoa. Why would you
phrase it like that?
You're such a weirdo.
I'm sorry.
Notice she didn't deny it.
Maple has always been
easy to scare, hasn't she?
Yeah. That's the truth.
--[CHOCOLA] Huh?
--[CACAO] Gotta pee.
Oh, you do? Uh...
[CHOCOLA gasps]
There!
Chocola will take you.
Seems those two are getting
along really well, huh?
Indeed, Chocola is settling
into the big sister role.
It's quite adorable.
I'm proud.
Ah, that's much better.
[CACAO]
Uh.
[CHOCOLA]
Hey there! Thanks for waiting!
No problem, but what
happened to Cacao?
[CHOCOLA]
Huh?
[yelps] She was just here!
Where'd she go?
Oh no, Cacao is gone forever!
Um, Chocola.
[CHOCOLA gasps]
[VANILLA]
She's there.
[CHOCOLA]
Huh?
[CHOCOLA gasps]
You're right!
Hey!
Don't run off! You scared us.
Did you want to watch?
[CACAO]
Mm.
[CINNAMON]
Oh, wow, look, May!
It's the Cat Witches show!
--[MAPLE] Uh.
--[CINNAMON] Do you remember?
Oh, yeah, isn't that the anime
you guys watched when
you were both kittens?
Man, is it still running?
Yes, it's actually
quite popular.
The one that Maple and
Cinnamon used to watch
was the first season.
But now it's on
its third season.
Ah. It's probably way different
than what we would know.
Yeah, but I heard somewhere
that the opening theme
song is still the same!
At least that
much hasn't changed.
Oh...
[MAPLE] One day, I'm
gonna be a famous singer!
When I grow up, I swear
I'll make my dream come true!
[MC 09A]
Oh, no!
Bad news!
It seems the kitties
have been captured!
How on earth will
we manage to rescue
these poor, distressed cats?
This is so bad!
What should we do, huh?
Oh, no!
[gasps] What?
How did Cinnamon get up there?
Did you miss it?
The bad guy came
through the crowd
and she practically begged
him to take her hostage.
[CINNAMON grunts]
What should I do?
Someone help me!
Being tied up
makes me super wet!
Is it me, or is she into it?
The only way we can free
these poor, defenseless kitties
is with the power of a song!
Is there anyone in the audience
who has the courage
to be a hero?
Who will sing to save them?
[AUDIENCE]
Uhh...
[KASHOU] Huh? Nobody here
is raising their hands.
Kids these days are a lot
more shy than they used to be.
[inhales] I said help!
If only that American Curl
cat would save me!
She's so cool
and big sister like!
Sometimes she gets scared,
but she's still awesome!
[GROUP]
Uh...
Yo. It sounds like that's you.
Me? But why should I have to go?
If you come up here
and help me,
then I promise to keep that
super embarrassing
thing a secret!
Okay?
[GROUP]
Embarrassing?
Remember when we were
at the haunted house
and you were so scared
you accidentally pe--
Please just stop talking! Jeez!
There are certain things you
don't talk about in public!
But fine, whatever!
I guess I can go
sing the stupid song.
Man, I don't get why I have
to be the one to do this.
Sorry to put you on the spot.
As well you should be!
But it doesn't matter.
I'll just do my best.
[inhales]
[AUDIENCE clapping, cheering]
That was cool! Super cool!
Chocola was blown away!
Yeah, it was pretty impressive!
[AZUKI]
Pawesome stuff!
She's the pride of
the Minaduki family.
Guys, I just took the most
beautiful picture ever.
Wow, that was excellent.
I don't think we've ever had a
volunteer sing so beautifully!
Um, wow. Seriously? Uh...
Well, thanks. Thanks so much!
Really!
[AUDIENCE whistles, cheers]
[CHOCOLA sighs]
What an incredible day!
Yes, it was. I found everything
to be quite enjoyable.
The amusement park
was super fun.
And I got to hear May's singing
for the first time in a while!
[MAPLE] Okay, I'm done with
my shift, so I'm heading out.
Good work.
--Wait! I'm not finished
--[door opens, closes]
--getting dressed yet.
[MAPLE]
I'm home.
[CINNAMON] You were out
pretty late. Where were you?
[MAPLE]
It's none of your business.
Man, I'm starving.
Okay...
Yes. Sounds good.
It's no problem.
I can be there at
there at that time.
[ALL]
Hmm?
Um, May?
[MAPLE gasps]
All right, bye!
[KASHOU]
See you.
Bye, see ya later!
Bye.
Nice work today, guys!
[door closes]
[CINNAMON]
Private phone calls.
A lack of sleep and
sneaking off after work.
[CINNAMON]
This is suspicious.
I'm too worried.
I can't just leave this alone!
Um, May? Where'd she go?
But... why come out here?
This part of town
is super shady!
[CINNAMON gasps]
[CINNAMON]
Wait.
Could that be it?
No! Don't do it, May! You can't!
I don't believe she's
doing adult things!
It's too terrible to imagine.
Even though I want to!
[MAPLE]
Hm? Cinnamon?
Hold on a second.
What are you doing
in this part of town?
It's not what you think!
I wasn't secretly following you
because I was worried
about you or whatever!
And it's definitely nothing
that's pervy or weird!
You got another job?
Yeah, but, I promise it
wasn't anything too indecent.
In fact, this business is
completely 100% legitimate.
Like she would only let
the customer get handsy
if they asked for
special permission.
And if it was their first time,
then she would be extra gentle
and show them what to do.
Even though Maple
just started this job,
she's already earning
a fantastic rep
with new customers!
That's enough!
How do you manage to make
everything sound so raunchy
when it's not?
Huh? Do I really?
What I don't get
is why you feel like you need
to work at a music store at all.
Yeah, I thought
we provided you with
all the things you need already.
[MAPLE]
It's because...
I-- I want to become
a great singer!
[BOTH gasp]
Oh, May.
So I did a little bit of
quick research online,
and I read that learning
an instrument is a good way
to get started when you want
to learn to sing better.
That's why.
I got another job, so
I could buy myself a guitar.
Why a guitar, specifically?
Well, I thought it would
be good to learn an instrument
that I could play while singing,
which is why I chose a guitar.
Then I'd be able
to perform solo.
You should have
just said something.
That problem's
easy enough to fix.
Yes, that's true.
We could just buy you a guitar.
No, that defeats the purpose.
I have to buy it.
It's the very first step
in making my dream come true!
I have to earn it.
[SHIGURE]
Maple.
You know what, I actually
understand how you feel.
After all, I am the one
who decided to leave home
and chase his dream of
opening up a patisserie.
Yeah, that's true.
Hey, wait!
I know I saw something earlier.
Oh, I found it.
[KASHOU]
Check it out.
Why not try entering?
[MAPLE]
A singing contest?
[gasps]
[KASHOU] If you really
want to be a singer,
then this would be
a good place to start.
Hey there!
You're doing great!
Isn't this extra
training kinda tough?
Especially with
working at the café?
Stamina is a big part
to being a good singer.
And I can't give up when I still
have a long way to go, so...
Wow, your dedication
is super impressive!
So why were you blowing
into a plastic bottle?
And what was that
exercise you were doing?
The one with your legs?
[MAPLE]
Oh, that?
It trains my lung capacity and
abdominal breathing techniques.
Wow.
Hey, I know!
Since you're going to be
singing the "Cat Witches" song
at the contest, what if you
also cosplayed as one of them?
I don't know. That costume is
from back when we were kittens.
There's no way it
would fit me now.
[CINNAMON]
It'll be perfect!
I can adjust it for you.
No thanks. I don't
want to wear a cosplay.
Aw... Oh, come on, May.
I just wanna help you achieve
your dream, is that so bad?
It's not, but I never asked for
your help in the first place.
So don't even bother.
It's fine! I'm helping you
because I want you to succeed.
Don't worry about me.
[CINNAMON]
The big day is finally here!
Oh! Please excuse me, guys!
[GROUP]
Huh?
[toilet flushes]
[sighs]
[MAPLE grunts]
Nope, one more time! Ah!
Seriously?
--[toilet flushes]
--[sighs]
[AZUKI]
Are you sure you're ready?
Don't pee yourself on stage.
What? I would never do such a
thing, I'm not a kitten anymore!
Okay, Cinnamon is gonna
help you get ready backstage.
But don't you worry,
we'll all be cheering
for you in the crowd!
You mean, like, everyone?
But I thought that Kashou,
Vanilla, and Chocola
had to stay and
run the patisserie.
Nope, he decided to close it
for this special occasion.
Isn't that wonderful
news, Maple?
Huh? Are you serious?
He doesn't need to miss out on
business over a dumb contest.
Please, don't be ridiculous.
This is our precious
child's big day.
I must engrave this memory in
my brain or regret it forever.
Don't worry. I'm gonna
capture the whole thing on video
and upload it to my blog!
[gasps]
[ANNOUNCER 09A]
Hello!
Are you ready for the
annual singing contest,
Song Paradise?
We have local bands,
internet idols,
and other competitors today!
Hold onto your seats!
This is shaping up to be
a very interesting competition!
But wait, there's more!
All of our judges today are real
music industry professionals!
And it's all held
right here in NKP Hall.
The Song Paradise
contest is sure
to be quite the experience
for everyone involved!
Are you ready to get started?
[CROWD cheering]
[MINADUKI HOUSEHOLD]
Go, Maple!
[gasps]
You've got this in the bag,
so break a leg up there!
Do your best, okay?
[CINNAMON]
It's almost May's turn to sing.
Why isn't she back here
with everybody else?
[CINNAMON grunts]
[gasps] Oh, good!
May!
C'mon.
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
We need to go
back inside quickly
or you'll miss
your turn to sing.
So hurry up. We can't be late.
[CINNAMON]
What's wrong?
[MAPLE]
I can't.
[CINNAMON]
What?
I quit.
I'm not going.
[CINNAMON gasps]
[MAPLE] The other contestants
are either super popular
or are on the
verge of being pros.
And all of the judges are
editors at music magazines.
Or they're some
famous producers.
If I go out there, I'll just
make a huge fool of myself.
Um, hey, hold on.
Where are you going?
Back home. No way I'm going
on stage just to look bad.
[MAPLE gasps]
What was that for?!
[CINNAMON]
To snap you out of this.
I just want you to
see how cool you are!
But now... you're gonna run away
because you might look bad?
You did so much work
to make this day happen,
but you wanna give up?
Well that's not cool, okay?
[gasps]
[MAPLE]
But... I can't.
[CINNAMON gasps]
I'm just really scared.
What if I mess everything up?
[MAPLE] Everybody worked
so hard to help me prepare.
And they all took off of work.
They cheered me on.
That's why... I'm frightened.
'Cause...
Because... what if I get
on stage and blow it?!
[gasps]
What happens if I end up
bombing the competition
and let everyone I love
down in the process?
[CINNAMON]
Don't worry.
Everything will be okay.
I know it.
Know how?
'Cause of you.
Because of the way you acted
when I first came
to live with everyone.
I didn't really fit in,
so I was hiding in
the corner of the room.
And you came and scolded me.
Look, I don't really
know what's going on,
but hiding won't
change anything.
[CINNAMON]
That's what you told me,
and then you
offered me your hand.
[MAPLE gasps]
[CINNAMON]
We made a promise.
Do you remember it?
Listen.
Promise me we'll
always be friends.
I want to be able to stay by
your side forever!
So no matter what kind of
things happen in the future,
whether those things
are good or bad,
I can be right there to
help you if you need it!
[CINNAMON]
See? That's why.
If you're afraid, I'm more
than happy to offer you my hand.
A wise cat once said,
"Hiding won't change anything."
Thanks, Cinnamon.
[CINNAMON]
Time to stand tall.
[CROWD clapping]
Next up is contestant number 22,
Miss Maple Minaduki.
[inhales]
[ALL]
Congratulations on winning!
[MAPLE]
Thanks, everyone!
[KASHOU] I bet you're
happy you got your guitar.
Yep.
Now, starting tomorrow,
I can practice singing
to my heart's content!
--[CACAO] Hey.
--Huh?
Will you sing something?
--[MAPLE] What?
--[GROUP] Hm?
Yeah. Sing something!
How about a little encore?
But the competition
ended forever ago.
[CINNAMON]
Please, May?
Huh?
I would love to hear you sing.
[MAPLE] Mm... Since
you won't stop asking,
I guess I'll sing something to
show you guys my gratitude.
[ALL chuckle]
Let's hear it...
...once more.