Hello there.
Tell me, do you know about cats?
They've got cute ears
that wiggle and twitch.
Tails that respond
to their emotions.
All attached to a human-like
creature of the utmost charm!
[SHIGURE]
Does that pique your interest?
If they sound appealing to you,
please visit our patisserie.
We have the cutest cats
you've ever seen.
All waiting to serve you!
[ALL] Hi and welcome!
To the patisserie La Soleil!
♪ Got the ponzu,
got the ponzu. ♪
♪ Chocola went and bought you! ♪
♪ Gonna put you all over tuna! ♪
Thanks for waiting!
[gasps]
[CHOCOLA] Hold on a sec,
did you follow Chocola home?
[KITTEN]
Mm.
[CHOCOLA]
Oh! You can't do that!
If you wander off
without telling anybody,
your master will
worry about you!
My master? Who is that?
You're kidding.
Are you saying you're
a master-less kitty?
Then that makes you...
...just like Chocola and
Vanilla were way back then.
--[KASHOU] Oh, hey.
--[CHOCOLA yelps]
[KASHOU]
I didn't hear you come in.
Yep! Chocola's home! Hello!
Why are you waiting by
the door? Do you need a hand?
[CHOCOLA]
What?! Oh! Of course not!
I'm, uh, just trying to
catch my breath or something!
[gasps]
You're sweating kind of
a lot, are you all right?
Do you have a fever?
No, no, no, Chocola is fine!
She just ran all the way
to the store and back so
she's tired!
[KASHOU chuckles] I guess
you couldn't wait any longer
to eat that tuna, could you?
Uh, yeah.
Well, let's go dig in.
Vanilla won't be able
to wait much longer, either.
I'll make sure she doesn't
start before you get changed.
[CHOCOLA]
Okay!
[CHOCOLA gasps] Listen.
Chocola will handle this.
Just follow close
behind me, got it?
[CHOCOLA]
Good.
Now's our chance to sneak
quietly into the bedroom.
[CHOCOLA yelps]
Oh my gosh, Vanilla!
I thought you would
be in the kitchen!
Waiting in front of the tuna
when I couldn't eat
any was way too painful,
so I came to our room instead.
Right, that makes sense!
Definitely normal for both
of us to be here! [chuckles]
You're being weird.
What's going on?
Is something the matter?
[CHOCOLA gasps]
Oh, I know! Here, take this!
[gasps]
You did very well with your
errands, Chocola. Great job.
After dinner,
I'll give you a reward
for all the running you did.
How does a nice,
long massage sound to you?
[CHOCOLA]
It'd sound better if you didn't
do that creepy thing
with your hands.
It'll be nice. You should
look forward to it.
[VANILLA]
Master, the ponzu has arrived
so we can eat whenever you like.
[sighs]
Wait. She's not here!
Where could she have gone?
Ahh...
[CHOCOLA] Hey, what do you
think you're doing in here?
[VANILLA]
Chocola.
[CHOCOLA yelps]
Hey. Hurry up already.
It's a crime to leave such nice
tuna sitting out for so long.
[CHOCOLA]
Oh.
[VANILLA]
♪ Ponzu, ponzu! ♪
♪ Tuna tastes the
best, it's true, ♪
♪ with ponzu here
for me and you! ♪
[CHOCOLA]
Will she be okay by herself?
Uh, wait! Master!
Where are you going?
Huh? Just to the restroom.
What?!
No, no, no! You can't!
You have to stay!
[KASHOU gasps]
Hey, what's gotten into you?
Well, uh, you see,
it's super dangerous
in the bathroom!
Huh?
Ghosts, Yeah, there are ghosts
that live in the toilet!
You might get scared
and pee your pants!
Just do your
business in the corner!
Don't be ridiculous!
I'm a person, not a cat!
You know we're not
kittens anymore, Master.
We don't just do
it in random places.
Cinnamon does sometimes.
But that's only when
she gets too excited.
[sneezes]
I wonder. Someone must
be saying stuff about me.
Let go! I can't
hold it in forever.
Don't worry, Chocola promises
to clean up after her master!
[KASHOU]
Ugh. I've had enough of this.
[CHOCOLA yells]
[CHOCOLA]
No!
Wait, what?
How did she?
[VANILLA]
Hmm.
Finally, time to eat.
This is bliss. I'm in heaven!
Yeah, It's pretty
fantastic, isn't it?
The next time you see Shigure,
remember to thank
her for sending it over
with Maple and Cinnamon.
And not only
is the tuna delicious...
The harmony with the ponzu...
It's exquisite!
[CHOCOLA]
Where did she go?
She can't have gotten far.
Oh, no!
What if she sat down on the
toilet, but then got sucked in
and was flushed away?!
What's the matter, Chocola?
Aren't you hungry?
Hey, what's going on?
--[door opens, closes]
--She was so happy to eat.
What's gotten into her?
You know what this means.
I must quickly eat
her share of the tuna
before it starts to go bad.
It definitely does
not mean that.
[CHOCOLA gasps]
I knew it!
Hey, are you okay down there?
Say something
if you can hear me!
So... now what do I do?
How can Chocola possibly pull
her out of there? It's hopeless!
[gasps] Wait a second!
That's it! The perfect answer!
Chocola will use the
plunger to save the kitten!
Okay. It should be with the
cleaning supplies in the bakery.
Uh!
[CHOCOLA]
Thank goodness!
Chocola was so worried
something terrible happened,
but you're okay! [cries]
--[CHOCOLA] Thank goodness!
--[stomach rumbles]
I'm hungry. I wanna eat.
Oh, right, of course you would.
It is dinner time after all.
Apologies for not
noticing sooner.
Chocola will bring
you something,
so wait right here, okay?
[door opens, closes]
[CHOCOLA]
Thank you very much!
[CHOCOLA grunting]
--[door opens, closes]
--Now what is she up to?
I swear.
Here you go.
You can nibble on some
of these yummy snacks!
Smell them!
[sniffs]
Ahh...
You like it?
[KITTEN]
Mm-hm.
Perfect! Eat as
much as you like.
You must be thirsty, too, huh?
Can Chocola bring you
anything to drink?
I want milk.
Oh. Uh, does that mean...
Chocola has to...?
I can't!
What are you yelling about?
Chocola is going to
have to-- But how do I?
[CHOCOLA gasps]
[VANILLA]
Stare.
So where'd she come from?
Did you let her in?
Oh, her?
This is just... Uh, well.
She-- How should Chocola say?
[CHOCOLA whimpering]
She's so... cute.
Huh?
I understand,
but that doesn't matter.
We're cats.
And that means we
belong to our master.
He trusts us not to sneak around
and do things like
this behind his back.
Yeah. I know that.
Why didn't you ask
him permission
before you brought
her home with you?
Do you remember?
It was right after
the store opened.
Everyone was about
to leave for the day.
And he said something
that made Chocola worry.
Whew. Looks like
it's quittin' time!
That was a super
busy opening day.
There were so many customers!
We're off to a great start.
Looks like you have
a hit on your hands!
We have no way of knowing
whether that
popularity will last.
This place has barely
opened, so it's a novelty.
Listen, you, don't
be such a bummer!
We all know that
your patisserie is
the only business in town
with so many adorable cats!
With a cats' paradise like this,
Japan is, no, wait, the entire
world is yours for the taking!
[KASHOU]
Uh...
I'm gonna stay local
for the time being.
She's right! And Chocola's
gonna do her best
to make this place a
gigantor success for you!
You have my help, too.
Ugh, I'm so envious
of you girls.
Getting to live
and work here means
you can have Master Kashou's
sweets whenever you want!
[CHOCOLA giggles]
Got room for one more since
I'm slingin' sweets, too?
That's not gonna happen.
I never even planned on having
Chocola and Vanilla here.
The bakery is enough
of a handful on its own.
Sorry, Coconut.
Having more cats here
just isn't an option.
That is true.
Although, we have to talk
to him if we want her to stay.
But what happens if we ask him
and Master says we
can't keep her here?
[gasps]
[VANILLA] He wouldn't put
her out on the street.
I assure you.
He took care of us and
he'll take care of her, too.
Not a chance.
Oh, no!
Well, that was unexpected.
But-- But why not, Master?
Listen, to begin with,
we need to figure out if she's
actually abandoned or not.
We can't just take her
in because you found her.
But that's not fair!
[KASHOU] Maybe she wandered
out of the house and got lost.
Someone could be
looking for her.
What would happen then?
[VANILLA, CHOCOLA gasp]
In that case, it's up
to Chocola to get out there
and help her find her master!
If she does have
a master somewhere,
then luring her
to the house with food
and keeping her here
makes Chocola a kidnapper.
Wha--?
Don't worry about that.
Here, how's this?
The best way we can help right
now is by asking an expert.
[yawns]
Meow.
Don't interrupt me!
You're not the only one
allowed to play with it!
Come on, please don't fight,
you two. You can take turns.
[cat phone meows]
Hello?
Oh! Hey, brother!
How was the tuna
I sent with the girls?
Huh?
[BOTH]
[CINNAMON, MAPLE]
Huh?
You can count on me.
I'll leave immediately and
be there as soon as possible.
Thank you so much for
coming over this late.
Sure. I'm a human after all.
It's my honor and privilege.
I'll respond 24/7 to any and all
cat-related problems and needs!
Uh... Yeah, okay.
So I told you pretty much the
whole situation over the phone.
Not a chance.
[CHOCOLA yelps]
Yet another unexpected
turn of events.
Abandoning a cat is
simply unthinkable!
I refuse to allow it!
If you treat cats like that,
you're a villain who should be
forced to dig a hole
and fill it over and over
for no fewer than 30 years!
[KASHOU]
That's cruel and unusual.
Hang on.
What makes you automatically
assume this cat was abandoned?
Oh! I don't know for sure yet.
You said there's a possibility
that she just wandered
off and got lost, right?
I tried asking her about it
while you were on your way over,
but I couldn't get
a straight answer out of her.
We asked who her
master was, and she said...
"Huh?"
And we asked where her
house was, and she said...
"Huh?"
Oh, goodness.
That's not very
helpful to us, is it?
All right, then.
If that's all we got,
then I'll ask around
the cat owners' network
to see if anyone's
lost a kitten recently
and we can move
forward from there.
I appreciate it.
I've always got your back!
You know there's absolutely
nothing in this world
that I wouldn't do for cats
and my dear older brother!
So first things first, then.
[SHIGURE]
I'll handle it.
Until we find her master,
she can come live with
me and the other cats!
Everything will be fine.
Shigure's an expert on cats
and always knows
the right thing to do!
She'd never let anything
happen to that kitten.
Yeah, you're right.
[sniffing]
Hey now, would you quit
sniffing the new kid so much?
You're gonna
totally freak her out.
Anyone would be
scared by someone
as freakishly huge
as you hovering over them.
Aww, I'm sorry. I'm curious!
I understand.
You have to admit,
having a new cat in the
house is pretty exhilarating!
What, you too, Cinnamon?
[CINNAMON]
Of course!
I feel the same way as I did
when I first met you, May!
She's irresistible!
Whoa! Hang on.
This is starting to sound a
little weird, so reel it back.
[SHIGURE]
Calm down, everyone.
I understand that
you're all excited,
but please try not
to bother her too much.
This is a new environment, and
she might be a little nervous.
So let's just leave her alone
until she gets
comfortable, okay?
[AZUKI] Uhh... Hey,
here's a crazy idea--
have you ever considered
taking your own advice?
[SHIGURE gasps]
Oh. Uh, the photos?
No! This is just a
record of her growth!
And, uh, if I take these
and put 'em online then,
maybe it'll be easier for her
master to find her here, y'know?
Yeah, no.
What are the odds those will
go straight into her
personal collection?
Oh, def.
All right, everyone.
It's getting late,
so time for a bath!
Maple, you always
take the longest,
so try to wrap up
quickly tonight, please.
Fine.
And hurry to bed
when you're done.
You have to get enough sleep!
Staying up too late
can make you sick
and do terrible
things to your fur.
Hey, Master Shigure?
[SHIGURE]
Yeah?
Where do you want the new girl
to sleep for the time being?
[SHIGURE]
Uh... Let's see.
I guess until she
gets used to the house,
I'll have her sleep in my room.
What? She gets to sleep
with Master Shigure?
[AZUKI]
What's your problem, Nuts?
Feeling a little jealous?
That's cute.
You may have grown
up to be gigantic,
but you're still a little kitten
on the inside, aren't you?
Well, you sure have a
pretty big mouth on you
for someone who's still
kitten-sized all over, y'know!
Excuse me?
[COCONUT]
You heard me, shortcake!
[AZUKI]
I am not that small!
[SHIGURE]
Hey, hey! Settle down, you two.
Let's get the bath ready,
so you can go to bed.
[GROUP]
Okay.
Great! How 'bout you come
bathe with me, little one?
[KITTEN]
Mm...
[SHIGURE]
You had a big day, didn't you?
I bet it'll feel refreshing
to be squeaky clean!
Huh?
[SHIGURE]
I wonder how long
she's been wearing
those clothes.
They look pretty dirty
and kinda beaten up.
Oh, I got it!
I think I have some old clothes
that the other cats wore
when they were small.
I'll find some for
you to wear tomorrow.
Here we go.
Let's start with the shampoo!
[KITTEN hissing]
Oh, uh.
Guess you're not a big fan
of the shower, are you?
Don't worry,
I promise it won't hurt!
Just relax and stay calm.
I promise you'll get used to it!
Oh, wow. Your hair has gotten
pretty matted under that hat.
No worries, let's lather
it up and make it shine!
And of course,
can't forget to clean your tail!
'Kay! Just one more
rinse and then we're done.
[SHIGURE humming]
Those are my pajamas from
when I was about your size.
They're not quite small
enough for you though.
But still, you're so cute!
Ahh! That post-shampoo smell
and your fluffy, minty hair are
too adorable. I can't handle it!
Oh! [giggles]
Oh! Sorry, I got
a little carried away!
You must be worn
out by now, huh?
Give me one second and
I'll get us all tucked in.
[sniffing]
[SHIGURE]
There we go! Perfect.
Ready? Come lie down!
Uh...
Looks like the mat's
more comfortable for you.
But... just to make sure
you don't catch a cold,
let's get you a blanket.
[SHIGURE]
Oh.
Poor thing must have
been really exhausted
if she's already
out like a light.
Sweet dreams.
See you in the morning.
[CHOCOLA] Do you think
she's fallen asleep already?
[VANILLA]
You worried about her?
Well, Chocola hopes
that she's behaving well
at the other house.
I'm sure she's getting
along just fine with everybody.
Yeah.
So what are you
thinking about, Vanilla?
That I'll always
be here with you.
You promise?
Hey, that's just
a little too much.
[CHOCOLA] I guess we
should get to sleep now.
[VANILLA]
Yes.
Sleep well, Vanilla.
Have sweet dreams, Chocola.