[CHOCOLA, VANILLA]
It's good to see you again!
Which tasty treat
can we get you today?
[CHIYO'S MOTHER] Just the usual.
This one and that one!
'Kay, coming right up!
Cacao! [giggles]
Hi! You okay?
[CACAO]
Mm. Let's play.
Oh. I can't today, Cacao.
I'm sorry, my Mom said we have
to go straight home today.
[VANILLA] Please enjoy them
while they're still fresh.
[CHIYO'S MOTHER]
Of course. Thank you so much.
Chiyo! Time to go.
'Kay. Gimme one second!
[sighs] Wait, I have an idea!
You should just
come to my house!
That way we can play a lot!
[CACAO grunts]
Uh? What can we do for ya?
Are you getting hungry?
[CACAO]
I wanna go.
[CHOCOLA, VANILLA]
Huh?
Go where?
Chiyo's house... to play.
[CHOCOLA, VANILLA]
What?
You don't even
have your bell yet.
How do we know you
can get there safely?
We don't want to worry
about you getting lost again!
[CHIYO'S MOTHER]
We could pick her up.
We'd love to have her visit!
Why don't we do
a sleepover next weekend?
[CHOCOLA, VANILLA gasp]
Thank you, Mom, that's awesome!
That would be so much fun,
Cacao! Please spend the night!
[CACAO]
Mm.
She wants to go.
To a sleepover?!
[VANILLA]
Let's see.
Here are your pajamas
and some clean underwear.
And don't forget... your
toothbrush and toothpaste.
I also have a hot water
bottle and a body warmer
just in case it gets cold.
You should pack an alarm clock
so you don't oversleep.
And your bath set is good to go.
And if you want some
dried fish... Here.
I bought it in bulk.
Take 'em all.
[CHOCOLA]
Wait, there's one more thing!
Ah! Found him!
There! Ta-da!
When Chocola was a kitten,
Mr. Bear was her favorite!
Any time you feel lonely,
you can think about Chocola
and give him a hug!
[CACAO]
Uh...
Can you think of
anything we forgot?
Just in case,
I sewed our contact information
to the inside of your backpack!
You're so reliable!
Way to go, Vanilla!
Phew! Now you're good to go!
[CACAO]
Uh...
[CACAO grunting]
[CHOCOLA, VANILLA]
Cacao!
[KASHOU]
Hey, hey, what's going on?
She's only spending one night
and she'll be back in no time.
She doesn't need
that much stuff.
Does, too! We had to make sure
she was ready for anything!
We considered every
possible contingency
and created the
ultimate sleepover set
to make sure
they're accounted for.
[CHOCOLA]
Mm.
I know how worried you are,
but you have to
think realistically
about how much she can carry.
--[VANILLA gasps]
--[CHOCOLA yelps]
[KASHOU]
Hm...
Okay. You win.
Sorry.
[CHIYO]
Cacao!
Hi, everybody!
You ready?
Thank you so much for allowing
Cacao to stay the night.
I hope it's not too
much trouble for you.
Of course not.
We love her and we're
happy to have her.
Look at that.
Shigure's acting
like a grown-up.
Then we should follow her lead
and act like grown-ups, too.
[CHOCOLA]
Mm.
Ahem. Thank you
for your hospitality.
We hope Cacao is
too much trouble for you.
[CHIYO'S MOTHER]
What? Too much?
--You misspoke just now.
--Huh?
I think you mean
"not too much trouble."
Oh, for sure,
not too much trouble!
Thank you. I promise she's not.
So don't you worry
about a thing!
[SHIGURE] My card has all
of my contact information.
I'll be around
if you need anything.
Please don't
hesitate to call me!
[CHIYO'S MOTHER]
Got it, thank you!
[CHOCOLA]
Cacao.
You should find out where
the toilet is first thing, okay?
[VANILLA] Remember to
say please and thank you
and be grateful
for the food at dinner.
[CACAO]
Mm.
Are you gonna be all right?
Don't worry.
Cacao is a smart kitten.
I know she's going
to be just fine.
Oh!
Here. I think you're gonna
wanna have this with you.
[CACAO]
Mm.
[VANILLA]
Not yet!
Keep that in your pocket and
read it as soon as
you get to their house.
Are you ready to go, Cacao?
Um, yes.
[CHOCOLA whimpers]
[VANILLA]
Don't forget us.
[SHIGURE]
Come on, let's head back home.
[CHOCOLA]
But she's right there!
We don't wanna leave her alone.
If you love your child, you
have to let 'em see the world.
You want her to
learn and grow, right?
I think this is a great
opportunity for her.
I got ya down for
three shortcakes.
[CHOCOLA, VANILLA]
We're home...
Hi, welcome back.
So then, was it as heartbreaking
as we all expected?
No! Chocola didn't cry!
Really, now?
So you didn't cling to her and
wail about never letting go
and how there was still
time for you to go with her?
[CINNAMON giggles]
I know you're teasing, but
think of how cute it would be
to see Chocola do that for real!
That wouldn't happen!
Chocola isn't a baby anymore.
[VANILLA] I think you'll find
the two of us
have no problem spending a night
away from Cacao.
[KASHOU] Wait a sec, the cacao.
[BOTH gasp]
We've run out of beans.
Would someone
mind refilling this?
Right. Cacao beans.
I thought... that maybe
she had decided to come home.
I figured as much.
You can't handle this at all.
[CHIYO'S MOTHER]
Here you are.
Please make yourself at home
and don't be afraid to relax!
Okay, Cacao?
[gasps]
[CHIYO] Is that the paper
Vanilla gave you?
Hello there.
My name's Cacao.
I hope my presence here
does not cause any
inconvenience for you all.
Take this as a
token of my gratitude.
Oh. Kaminari-Okoshi.
Well, thank you!
You're so grown up! That's cool!
[CACAO grunts]
Okay, so you wanted three of
these Fondant au Choco-meows.
Chocola. What'd you say?
[CHOCOLA gasps]
Right! Sorry! Um, three
Fon-cat Choco-meows.
We'll have those three
Fondant au Chocolats
right out for you, miss.
Vanilla! That's too many!
Yes. Sorry, I must
be distracted.
[CHOCOLA] Please excuse
us! We'll repack them!
Do you think
those two are okay?
I think they're just
concerned about Cacao.
Yeah. That's really sweet.
They're basically
still kittens, too.
[CHIYO laughs]
Come on, Cacao,
you can make that jump!
Wah!
--[CACAO gasps]
--[CHIYO laughs]
What's it gonna be, Cacao?
A shark or something?
It's a fish.
[CHIYO]
I see. So cute.
[CHOCOLA]
Do you need help with anything?
Yes, please. Would you
mind getting the bowls?
[CHOCOLA]
Okay.
Let's set the table.
[KASHOU]
Hm? Something wrong?
[CHOCOLA]
Uh, nope!
It's nothing, Master,
everything is fine!
[VANILLA grunts, gasps]
I forgot that Cacao isn't here.
I hope you two are
ready for dinner!
I made soy
sauce-boiled dried fish!
[whimpers] Chocola knows how
much Cacao loves dried fish.
How can you expect us to eat her
favorite food without her?
She's not wrong.
If it's not too much trouble,
I'd like to save this meal.
Then we can eat it
when Cacao comes home.
[KASHOU]
Uh... Sure. Okay.
[CHIYO] Mm! Mom's meatloaf
is always super good!
Great job, Cacao!
You really did a number
on your vegetables!
I'm so glad!
[CHIYO]
Mm.
[CHIYO grunts] Well I'm gonna
eat all my veggies, too!
[CHIYO'S MOTHER giggles]
[CHIYO]
Check this out.
Now we can take a bath together!
[CACAO grunts]
[CHIYO]
What do ya say?
[CACAO grunts]
Hey, are you okay?
Are you afraid of
being in the water?
Yeah, I guess so.
Wait! I know!
Look! I found all these
toys! So it'll be fun.
'Kay?
[CACAO]
Mm...
Fine, then. Pew!
[CACAO grunts]
See, that wasn't so bad and
you were really brave, Cacao!
Now, give this a shot
and see what you think!
[BOTH giggling]
[CHIYO]
Hey!
[CHIYO, CACAO giggling]
[VANILLA]
How's that? Got enough shampoo?
[CHOCOLA sighs]
Don't sigh.
They say being negative
is supposed to be bad luck!
Huh? Oh, right.
[CHOCOLA sighs]
[VANILLA]
Hm... [gasps]
[CHOCOLA gasps]
Hey, stop that!
Hey! That really
tickles, Vanilla!
But... Chocola can do that, too!
[BOTH giggling]
[BOTH sigh]
A warm soak is nice
after a long day like this.
Huh? Chocola?
The bath seems a lot
bigger than normal tonight.
No, it's still the same.
Doesn't feel like it.
There! All done.
[CACAO gasps]
Oh! That's my mom. I drew it.
You drew her?
I wanted to make
something really special
for her last Mother's Day.
Mom always works
really hard for me,
so I drew it to say thank you.
She loved it so much
that she framed it
and then put it up on the wall!
Hey, Vanilla?
What's up? Are you okay?
The bath was bad enough,
but Chocola is sad that
the bed feels bigger, too.
Yeah. It does, huh?
We're so used to
Cacao being here now.
So when you sounded
okay with it before,
you were just fakin' it?
Well, I figured
if I could pretend
like everything was normal,
maybe it would help
you not to be so upset.
Thanks so much, Vanilla.
Huh? Don't mention it.
[sighs] Chocola didn't
realize until now.
Cacao coming to live with us
and being around all the time
got normal really fast.
Yes.
Chocola wants us
to share the bed again
when Cacao comes home, okay?
Of course.
But for tonight,
I have my sweet
Chocola all to myself.
[CHOCOLA gasps]
[CHOCOLA] Vanilla! You're
squeezing a little too tight.
[VANILLA]
Sorry. Can't let go, good-night.
[KASHOU]
Thank you for bringing her home.
And thanks again for having her.
It was our pleasure,
she was a delight.
Please come over again!
That was so fun!
[CACAO]
Mm!
[CHOCOLA, VANILLA]
Cacao! We're glad you're home!
We missed you!
Come jump into our arms!
[BOTH gasp]
--[VANILLA] Uh...
--[CHOCOLA] Wait, hang on!
Where are you going?
[CHOCOLA]
Hello?
We're coming in.
[BOTH gasp]
[CHOCOLA]
What is this?
[VANILLA] What is that
box still doing here?
Do you think Cacao
is hiding inside it?
Hello?
But why?!
No way.
Thank you, please come
back to see us soon!
A-ha! Guess she's about to start
her rebellious phase, then.
[VANILLA, CHOCOLA]
What is that?
You'll find out soon.
Like, take Nuts for example.
[AZUKI]
Hey, I'm back.
Hi, big sis! Welcome home!
She was totally
respectful and sweet
in her kitten days,
if you can imagine it.
It's kinda hard to believe.
I've never seen her do
anything like that.
Yeah, now she's grown
past her rebellious phase.
And all that cuteness
is gone forever.
[COCONUT]
Hmph.
But sometimes that's
just a part of growing up
and you gotta let it happen.
Cacao's not gonna
love you any less.
Just try to give her space.
Does it have to be?
Can't we take care of her?
[knocking]
Is it okay if we come in now?
Even though we shouldn't have
to ask 'cause it's our room.
[rustling]
[CHOCOLA] It sounds like she's
still doin' something in there.
Then our mission, should
we choose to accept it,
is to successfully engage
Cacao in conversation.
[CHOCOLA inhales, exhales]
Hello, Cacao?
Please be a good girl
and come out of the box.
[CHOCOLA]
Hmm...
[gasps]
[yelps]
Astounding.
There's only one
explanation for this.
She spent one
night away from home
and completely
forgot who we are.
[CHOCOLA]
That's im-paw-ssible... right?
[VANILLA grunts]
Doesn't matter!
We're gonna bring
everyone in on this
and together we'll make Cacao
come out no matter what!
[VANILLA]
Cacao.
Surely you want to
come out of the box
for some of this fresh
cooked saury, don't you?
You know how hard
it can be to find them
when they're out of season!
--[VANILLA] No.
--[CHOCOLA] Ow, hey!
My eyes are starting to water
really badly for some reason.
You're imagining it.
Don't stop now. It smells
really good in here.
[coughs]
[GROUP coughing]
Whoa! What do you
think you're doing?
The room's full of smoke!
[CINNAMON]
Somebody hurry. Open a window!
[AZUKI coughs]
[MAPLE coughs]
Epic failure.
We were trying to smoke
the fish to lure her out.
But we got carried away and
almost smoked ourselves, too.
Ya shoulda listened.
I promise I'm right.
It's just a phase.
You should leave her alone.
Not possible.
People don't
change that quickly!
[GROUP]
Hmm...
Oh, I know!
I just got an amazing idea.
Here you go, May!
What's this?
It's a portable karaoke machine.
What? Are you saying she'll
come out if I start singing?
[giggles] I call it...
...Project Amano-Iwato!
[MAPLE]
Amano-what now?
[CINNAMON]
There's an old story about
a sun goddess who hid in a cave
and took all the
light from the land.
So the other gods decided
to throw a huge festival.
When she heard them having fun,
she couldn't help but come out!
Oh, so you're saying if
we throw a party of our own...
Then she might leave the box!
Because we'll be
having fun without her!
Please don't take
fairy tales literally.
So? Try it.
Use your amazing
voice to help us out!
[COCONUT]
I'm always down to party!
[MAPLE]
Hmm. Fine. If you insist.
Oh, May! That song?
It's perfect! What a plan.
And now I'm getting super wet!
Can't handle it.
Cut it out for once! This
should not be arousing you!
[ALL gasp]
Cacao!
[CACAO]
Shh.
So cold!
That was brutal.
Definitely the harshest
criticism I've ever received.
Okay, enough already.
You guys get it now,
so leave her alone, okay?
[GROUP]
'Kay...
[KASHOU]
Cacao still won't come out, huh?
Yeah. It's been a whole day.
She'll barely even stick
her head out of that box.
And she won't
tell you what's up?
I wonder if she feels
sick or something,
'cause it's really not
like her to miss a meal.
[gasps] Soy sauce-dried fish!
Yes. And surely
her favorite dish
would get through to her, right?
Chocola thinks we just
found our secret weapon!
Please excuse us!
You can eat without us,
we gotta go meow!
We'll take this to Cacao
and she'll be back to
normal before ya know it.
All right. Better get goin'.
[knocking]
Hi, Cacao!
I hope you're
ready for dinner now.
We brought you Master's handmade
soy sauce-boiled dried fish.
Look! It's your favorite dish!
[CHOCOLA gasps]
Ah! Come on!
She just licked it clean
and sent it right back.
Well, that's it.
Chocola thinks there's nothing
left to do but wait this out.
Not quite.
We still have one option left
and I think we need
to give it a try.
[CHOCOLA grunts]
Azu said to leave Cacao alone,
so she can grow up.
But if she won't talk to us...
...then the only
thing we can do...
...is to break her out by force!
[BOTH yell]
[BOTH gasp, groan]
[BOTH groan]
Cacao!
We've been worried
sick about you!
What were you doing in there?
[CHOCOLA, VANILLA]
Huh?
[CACAO]
To Chocola and Vanilla.
Thank you.
You always want to play with me.
I like it.
[CHOCOLA, VANILLA gasp]
It's nice 'cause
sometimes I get bored.
But we can always
play with a ball.
And sometimes we play
with a cat teaser, too.
So thank you.
Also... thank you for
showing me the ocean.
It was very big, and pretty,
and I was surprised.
Thank you for taking me
with you to the amusement park.
It was exciting and very fun.
Thank you for letting me
eat lots of moving sushi.
It was neat to watch,
and it was delicious.
And most of all...
...thank you for saying you
want me to stay here with you.
It made me very happy.
I am home.
[BOTH gasp]
Oh, Cacao.
[CHOCOLA, VANILLA gasp]
[CHOCOLA]
Is this for us to keep?
Uh.
[BOTH gasp]
It's us.
Did you spend
all day drawing this?
[CACAO]
Mm.
Chocola, Vanilla,
I love you.
I want to stay.
[CHOCOLA]
Cacao!
[VANILLA]
Thank you!
Chocola loves you,
too, a whole bunch!
[VANILLA] Mm! I promise
we'll always be together!
[CACAO gasps]
[VANILLA, CHOCOLA
crying, laughing]
Good-night.