Yummy. I couldn't
swallow another bite.
Wow, everything
looks so tasty. Yum.
It's delicious, right? Eat up!
This is making me wet.
I'm not scared.
Nope, not at all.
[sighs]
[COCONUT]
Aw, man, this sucks!
Those mosquitoes
really got me good!
[AZUKI] Serves you
right for being stupid.
Sure, it may be hot,
but you had to know sleeping
outside was a bad idea.
Ah.
Speaking of sleeping,
how did you get that
big red mark on your face?
Huh? What mark?
Oh! This is nothing!
Just forget about it!
Nothing, my tail!
Let me guess, you were sleeping
on the roof again, weren't you?
Of course not!
I don't do that anymore!
I'm not a baby like you are!
I'm just stating the facts here!
Your facts are outdated!
[BOTH growling]
[MAPLE] Now, now.
That's enough out of you two.
Yeah, please don't argue
first thing in the morning!
[AZUKI, COCONUT]
Hmph!
Where's Shigure at?
[AZUKI]
I dunno, I haven't seen her.
Weird, I wonder what's up.
It isn't like her to oversleep.
[COCONUT] You're right. I hope
she's still gonna make breakfast
like she said she would.
Shigure always makes
the tastiest fish dishes!
And her miso soup's delish!
I can't wait to chow down!
All you think about
is stuffing your face.
Oh.
Oh, hey, Shigure!
Hello there, everyone.
Good morning.
Morning, Shigure!
You making fish?
Is it me or does she seem off?
Yeah, where's her usual energy?
Uh, what is this?
Oh, my, what a beautiful
block of charcoal.
[COCONUT giggles] Regardless,
the miso soup's gotta be good!
Don't mind if I do! Yum!
[COCONUT coughing]
[AZUKI] Hmm. Kinda seems
like you were wrong.
Gross! It's bad!
Way too salty!
[CINNAMON, MAPLE]
Ew.
[MAPLE]
Ugh.
I guess she overdid
it with the miso.
I dunno. Maple's kind
of high maintenance,
so I don't think
I'd let her be the judge.
Who asked you?
Well, either way,
this isn't normal.
Do you think
something bad happened?
[GROUP]
Ahh...
[CINNAMON] We never figured out
what was wrong with Shigure.
Nope.
We couldn't get more than two
words out of her all day long.
Maybe it's heat exhaustion.
Oh. Yeah.
The weather's been crazy hot,
so it's probably getting to her.
Uh-huh. And on top of
her usual household chores,
she's also been working on
advertising for Kashou's shop.
She must really be exhausted.
Hey, I know!
If we all pitch in and help her
finish everything she has to do,
maybe she'll be able to
get some of her energy back!
[MAPLE]
Good idea!
I'm in!
Yeah, I'm happy to help!
All right, fine.
Count me in, too.
Huh. We haven't
done this in a while.
Oh, right!
I guess we haven't.
One, two. One, two.
♪ Cleaning,
cleaning, cleaning. ♪
[yelps]
[yells]
[CINNAMON]
Shigure! My tail!
It's stuck in the vacuum!
Please turn it off, okay?
It's sucking me inside!
[CINNAMON cries]
Hey! Pay attention, Shigure!
She's about to
lose all of her fur!
[gasps]
Huh? What happened?
[CINNAMON whimpers]
[CINNAMON] The vacuum sucking,
combined with you grabbing,
is creating a really
pleasant sensation.
It's almost more
than I can handle.
It's making me so wet!
[MAPLE] Oh, come on,
Cinnamon, seriously?!
This is no time
to be getting wet!
Hey, Shigure? Do you want
us to hang these out here?
Uh, did you hear me? Hold on.
[AZUKI gasps]
What's with those panties?
No one would wear these!
Like, not even
Chocola or Vanilla!
Maybe Cacao left them behind.
[COCONUT]
Check it out, Azuki!
They're like little kid panties!
[AZUKI] Shut up! They're cute!
What's wrong with that?!
Wow, why did that set you off?
They belong to you, don't they?
[AZUKI gasps]
Don't be stupid.
I wouldn't be caught
dead in those things!
I am an adult cat!
[COCONUT]
Are you sure?
[AZUKI]
Just hang them up already!
[sighs]
[BOTH gasp]
[AZUKI, COCONUT] She's only
hanging the panties...
Looks like our plan didn't work.
Maybe the hot weather
isn't what's bothering her.
[COCONUT] I just want her
to be her normal self again.
Better be careful
what you wish for, Nuts.
When I think of Shigure's
normal self, I think...
[laughing]
Perfect angle! This is going
to be excellent! [laughs]
Ooh, yes please, if you insist!
Don't mind if I do!
[giggles] You're right.
Shigure can be very assertive
first thing in the mornings.
Stop getting moist over
something that already happened!
Why don't we let her
stay the way she is, then?
Less creepy.
That's unacceptable!
We can't give up!
There's gotta be
something we can do
to bring back the Shigure
we all know and love!
[door opens]
[SHIGURE]
I'm home.
[ALL]
Good to see you!
Um, what's this about?
So much food.
Don't be shy.
Have a seat, Shigure!
Uh, right.
Have some honey toast!
It's my favorite, so I'm sure
you'll enjoy it just as much!
There's some
boiled mackerel, too.
And it's fresh
from the local store!
[COCONUT]
I made you tuna sashimi!
I worked real hard!
[gasps]
[AZUKI]
And last but not least,
a big helping of
dried bonito shavings
from Makurazaki on
tofu, from yours truly!
I had saved it for
a special occasion,
but I'm giving it to you!
So savor every bite, okay?
I really appreciate all of this.
It's just that...
...I, sadly, don't have much
of an appetite at the moment.
[GROUP]
Huh?
I'm terribly sorry everyone.
But please, feel free to
enjoy it all amongst yourselves.
Okay, I'm seriously
worried about Shigure now.
But not worried enough
to stop pigging out, I see.
It's so odd.
You'd think that after all this,
we would've at least figured out
what's causing her
to act this way.
Hey, here's an idea.
Maybe it's 'cause
she misses Kashou.
That's a possibility.
She does love her
brother a bit too much.
[ALL]
Hmm...
[SHIGURE] Wow, I could
look at Kashou's photograph
all day long!
[giggling]
I'm so happy you're
finally home, big brother!
Ready for dinner?
Or perhaps your bath?
Ooh, wait, I know.
Would you like me?
Knock, knock, Kashou!
I'm here to help you wash all
of your hard-to-reach places!
[SHIGURE yelps]
[SHIGURE]
Aw, you're so mean!
You know that my love for you
is as vast and deep
as the Marianas Trench!
As twisted as that is,
we probably guessed it right.
When his shop opened
he did stop coming around,
so I'm sure Shigure
really misses him.
Case closed! That's it!
She's been acting weird
because she wants to see
her beloved big brother.
That makes sense.
Definitely a possibility.
[ALL]
Mm-hm.
But what can we do about it
that'll help her feel better?
Easy!
We'll set up a time for the
two of them to see each other!
[COCONUT, AZUKI]
Mm.
Let's do this!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Um... Why exactly am I dressed
in the patisserie's uniform?
Well, it's because
of the cats back home.
They said you could
use a little pick me up.
Hence the outfit. 'Cause nothing
makes someone feel better
than looking super cute.
Absolutely!
You just need to do something
to take your mind off things
and working here will help you
forget whatever's bothering mew!
[SHIGURE]
Yeah, but...
...I don't think wearing these
clothes will make a difference.
[VANILLA]
Don't worry.
All you have to do
is put on these cat ears,
then you'll look
like a real cat.
Here.
[CHOCOLA, VANILLA gasp]
Oh, wow, so cute.
[gasps, grunts]
[SHIGURE]
Mm!
Hi and welcome to our café!
Um, would this table here work
okay for the two of you ladies?
Meow?
[SHIGURE] Right, thank you
both so much for waiting--
[SHIGURE yelps]
[crash]
[crying]
[MAPLE]
How is Shigure doing?
[BOTH gasp]
Bet she's nailing it, right?
More like she's failing it.
You should probably
see for yourselves.
I just knew this would happen.
I mean, what was I thinking
trying to serve customers?
It's too much for
an introvert like me.
[ALL sigh]
Looks like we've only
managed to make things worse.
[CHOCOLA]
Chocola is at a loss.
What can we do to make
Shigure feel better?
I suppose we have
no other choice.
I will go out and buy her
some tasty vanilla ice cream!
[AZUKI]
Hold up.
We should buy her red bean.
It's way better.
Oh, please, everyone knows
that coconut bars are the best.
What? No way! Red bean ice cream
has the most firmness!
This is no time
for your bickering.
This is supposed
to be about Shigure!
[KASHOU]
What's going on? A cat meeting?
[GROUP]
Hm?
Kashou.
Did you guys say
something about Shigure?
[MAPLE]
We have no choice.
We're going to have
to involve Kashou.
[GROUP]
Right!
Uh...
You heard correctly.
Your sister needs your help!
[GROUP]
Please, Kashou!
Thank you so much, Cacao!
No prob. You're
welcome. Thank you.
Of course, I'm always
happy when I get to see you!
Well then, have a
good rest of your day!
[CHOCOLA]
Ahh. It smells great!
Is that herbal?
Yes!
I took the liberty of
making some chamomile tea,
since it has a
nice, calming effect.
[KASHOU] I brought
a matcha green tea roll cake.
It's one of Shigure's favorites.
We'll try to give the
two of you some space,
so you can spend
some time together.
Now, go out there
and console her
in the wettest
way possible, okay?
I'll probably pass
on the last part.
Anyway, why exactly
does this matter so much?
It's obvious!
You're never around anymore.
This is a good chance
to spoil Shigure a bit.
Uh, yeah.
Well, you have a fair point.
We do talk a lot less,
especially since I moved out
and opened up the patisserie.
Go chat with her!
I'm positive it will help.
[GROUP]
Mm-hm.
Sorry if I made you worry.
I didn't mean to cause trouble.
[KASHOU]
It's okay.
Do you maybe want to tell me why
you've been
feeling so bad lately?
Unfortunately, I don't
really know why I feel down.
I just do, and I wish I could
explain it better, but I can't.
Is it me?
No, believe it or not,
I don't think it's you.
I know the café was your dream.
I wanna support that.
And sure, there are times
I wish you'd stop by more,
but I understand you're busy.
Aw, Shigure.
I want La Soleil to
succeed as much as you do.
It makes me happy
to see it thriving.
And no matter what, I'll
always be here to help you
however I can.
[ALL whimper]
That's so beautiful.
Oh, Shigure.
She's so admirable.
Sisterly love.
It's beyond wonderful
and full of devotion!
[SHIGURE]
Okay.
I should let you
get back to work.
Thanks for talking to me.
Come visit whenever you want.
I will.
It's such a happy ending!
She totally made off
with those cat ears.
[AZUKI]
Hmm...
What's the matter, Azuki?
Even after Kashou,
there's still something
about this that
doesn't feel quite right.
She's still off
somehow, you know?
You're right.
Like she's not aware
of her surroundings.
So you're saying
she's still upset?
[MAPLE] Great, we've all
turned into complete stalkers.
This isn't the way
back to our house.
For real.
Where is she going?
Why is she just
wondering around?
[AZUKI]
This is so weird!
Why would she come out here
to the middle of nowhere
instead of going back home?
[COCONUT]
What's her deal?
I thought talking to Kashou
helped her feel better.
If that were true, then
why would she come out here?
This is kinda creepy.
[CINNAMON gasps]
Could it be?
I think I saw this on
television the other night!
A woman lost her love,
and in a moment of despair
threw herself off of a cliff!
[MAPLE, COCONUT, AZUKI gasp]
It all makes sense now.
She must feel guilty about her
forbidden love for her brother.
Shigure knows it can never be a
reality so she's going to jump!
Yeah, I don't know. You sure?
[MAPLE]
Sounds far-fetched?
[AZUKI]
There's no way, right, guys?
[CINNAMON]
Shigure, don't! No!
--[COCONUT] It's not worth it!
--[MAPLE] Stop! Don't do it!
Aw, man, this sucks.
Hey!
[GROUP shouting]
Huh?
Please, Shigure,
we're begging you!
Don't you dare leave us alone!
It's gonna be okay!
What are you doing here?
You idiot!
You've been acting
so weird lately
that we're all
worried sick about you!
Yes, that's right!
Usually,
your days are filled
with following us around
and taking our pictures
like a cat-obsessed paparazzi.
[MAPLE] You've always
treasured those photos.
Remember how posting
them on your blog
brought you so much joy?
[COCONUT]
And when I was still a kitten,
you were there to
take care of me.
No matter what, I knew
I could count on you!
[AZUKI] You're so kind,
Shigure, and caring.
You take care of us
through thick and thin,
rain or shine, all the time!
And that's why...
[GROUP]
...we love you!
[gasps]
[cackling]
She's laughing?
But why?
[SHIGURE continues cackling]
Uh, she's acting kind of crazy.
This is really
weirding me out, you guys.
It's finally
happening, my loves!
I've been waiting for so long!
So long! [laughs]
[SHIGURE yells]
[AZUKI yells]
[yelling]
Azuki! [gasps]
[CINNAMON gasps, yelps]
[MAPLE]
No!
[ALL screaming]
[SHIGURE] Okay, I think
I've finally figured out
why I've been feeling so down.
[GROUP]
Huh?
[SHIGURE] I only just realized
it once you were all hugging me.
I think the summer
heat might be to blame.
During the winter,
when it's colder,
you would all come and
snuggle with me every night.
But because it's
been so hot lately,
you've stopped being cuddly
and instead have opted
for cooler places to sleep.
That's why... I was
feeling so depressed.
I was sick and suffering
from a lack of cats.
It's a disorder known
as acute cat deprivation!
[GROUP]
Wait, that's seriously why?
[SHIGURE] Usually,
I go to that cliff side because
I want to be alone and
try to sort out my problems.
Honestly, I never would
have expected you guys
to be so worried that
you'd end up following me.
Thank you so much
for your concern.
Come on, Shigure,
don't be like that.
Of course we were worried.
But in the future,
just tell us these things.
Yeah, for real!
No need to hold back.
And, just for tonight,
we can cuddle.
I'm in. Let's
all be wet together!
[ALL chattering]
Aw, you guys, this
is just what I needed.