[CHOCOLA, VANILLA]
Thank you very much!
We hope that you'll
visit us again soon.
[door opens, closes]
Ahh! Did you see how
hard Chocola worked today?
Business wasn't very heavy,
but it wasn't slow either.
We both worked moderately hard.
[CHOCOLA] Boy, dinner
can't come fast enough.
Chocola's starving!
--[CHOCOLA gasps]
--[VANILLA grunts]
[VANILLA] What's up with
the sudden stop? Huh?
[VANILLA]
Cacao?
Aw, were you waiting
to welcome us back?
[CACAO]
Mm.
[BOTH gasp]
Thanks, Cacao,
that's very sweet.
Chocola, don't be so greedy,
I want to give her love, too.
[CHOCOLA giggles]
This sort of reminds Chocola--
we used to wait like this for
the master to get back home,
when we were little kittens.
Then maybe we should wait to
welcome him home again today.
I bet he'll even
pat us on the head.
Yeah, yeah, yeah! Great idea!
[sighs] Boy, am I exhausted.
Uh?
[CHOCOLA, VANILLA]
Welcome home, Master!
--[CHOCOLA] Great work today!
--[VANILLA] Great work!
Yeah. Good to be
back. Thank you.
[KASHOU sighs]
Uh, Master?
Not even one head pat?
That was a rather
cold reception.
Uh.
[CHOCOLA gasps]
It looks so yummy!
--I'll have some now.
--Chocola will have some now.
[BOTH]
Thanks.
Wow, Master, everything you made
for dinner tonight
is really delicious!
Good to hear.
[CHOCOLA]
Know what else?
Chocola noticed that you
made the rice extra fluffy!
[KASHOU]
Uh-huh.
Today was really busy.
But Chocola worked super hard
and served all the customers!
Cool.
[CHOCOLA grunts]
Chocola, Master is trying
to eat so please be quiet.
Fine.
[KASHOU]
I think I'm full.
Oh, but you barely ate.
Dinner was so weird.
Master barely touched his food
and worse he barely
spoke to Chocola!
He might just have
a lot on his mind,
like maybe there's problem
with the shop, you know?
No way, do you
really think that's it?
Listen up.
If there is anything
you want to confess,
then now would be the
most appropriate time.
Besides, if you turn
yourself in now,
then I'm sure your
punishment will be lighter.
Are you serious, nya?
Well, there's a
slight possibility
that the other day
when nobody was looking,
Chocola took the
teeniest little taste
of the whipped cream.
And maybe while Chocola
was carrying lots of plates...
...she might have tripped
and broke one or two.
You think Master
knows about Chocola?
[VANILLA] Sounds like you've
been a very naughty kitty.
--[CHOCOLA yelling]
--It's time for noogies.
Beware the noogie.
The noogie monster attacks.
[CHOCOLA] Chocola promises
she'll never do it again,
so stop torturing her, Vanilla!
Well, all things considered,
even if we ignore
your evil deeds...
You punished me!
...when I really think about it,
Master seemed worried.
Huh? What do you
think it was about?
Maybe he ate a bad
fish or something.
I highly doubt that's the issue.
You see, when I went
into the kitchen earlier...
[gasps]
[KASHOU] It's just not
working out! What should I do?
So what do you think it means?
It's just a hunch,
but I suspect he may be
struggling financially.
The shop did have fewer
customers than usual.
What will we do if he
continues to struggle?
We'll have to save money
by rationing our food.
[CHOCOLA gasps]
Ration our food?
So we'll only get a
single dried fish a day?
[rumbling]
But Chocola will
starve! She'll die!
[VANILLA]
It'll be fine.
There's nothing for you
to worry about, okay?
If we just solve
Master's problem for him,
he won't have to be
sad anymore, right?
[CHOCOLA]
Mm-mm. Great idea!
We have to do whatever
we can to help our master!
[VANILLA] If we want to
bring in more business,
then we need to let
people know we exist first.
Okay, then we'll hand
out a ton of shop cards!
Yeah!
[CACAO]
Hm?
Oh, I forgot.
You've probably
never seen anything
like shop cards before,
have you, Cacao?
Check it out, it has the name of
our patisserie on it and a map.
If we hand these out
to the people passing by,
then they'll know
where our shop is
when they want
to come buy a cake.
Then we won't have
to ration our food.
[CACAO grunts]
Please visit our shop,
Patisserie La Soleil!
We have lots of
delicious desserts!
All of our cakes and
sweets are really yummy.
Patisserie La Soleil!
Please visit us for
all of your cake needs!
[CINNAMON]
What's this? Hey, guys.
What are you doing
out here so early?
It's Maple and Cinnamon.
Hey, you have perfect timing!
[CINNAMON] I see, the
shop's sales are suffering?
So do you guys
have any good ideas
on how we could bring
in more customers?
Let's see...
There's no doubt about it.
We might have to
take drastic measures.
[CINNAMON gasps]
Uh, what do you mean by drastic?
Are you talking about...
...stripping down in front of a
crowd for money or something?
'Cause that would definitely...
...make me super wet!
Yeah, hard no.
That's not even close to
where I was going with this.
Your order's ready,
five tiramisus, right?
Here you go.
Thanks, are you ready?
[CINNAMON giggles]
[camera clicks]
[GIRL 05A]
Wow, so cute!
See you later, kitties!
[MAPLE]
What do you think?
My idea to boost sales
by offering a free photo
with every cake
purchase is doing great.
I posted it yesterday,
but I never imagined word
would spread so quickly.
As usual, you always
have the best ideas, May!
Oh, wow, we're busy!
It's your turn to take
the next photo, okay?
--[CHOCOLA] You got it!
--[VANILLA] Right.
Don't worry, you can
leave everything to us.
[CHOCOLA] Thank you for waiting!
Here are the cakes you ordered.
Please don't hesitate to ask
if you need anything else.
Thanks. We appreciate your help.
Okay, say cheese!
[camera clicks]
Chocola, you're way
too close to the camera.
And what's with that fake smile?
[camera clicking]
Okay, then Chocola
will up her game, too!
[BOTH grunt]
[CHOCOLA]
Like this?
[VANILLA]
Yeah.
[CACAO grunts]
So many people.
The orders are flying
in for some reason.
I'll just have to
work harder, then!
[CACAO grunts]
[gasps]
[grunts]
[BOTH grunt]
[CHIYO]
Sorry about that! Are you okay?
You're not hurt, are you?
[CACAO grunts]
[CHIYO] Aw, hi there,
kitty! You're so cute.
[grunts]
Uh, what is it? Something wrong?
[rumbling]
[CHIYO] I bought this taiyaki
from a stall in the park.
It's super yummy.
Here. Do you like the head part
or the tail part better?
How 'bout you
take the head then?
Here ya go.
[CACAO]
Mm!
My name's Chiyo.
Well, do you have
a name or anything?
So is your house near here?
[CACAO]
Mm-mm...
Then where is your master?
[CACAO]
Mm-mm...
Wait, don't tell me.
Are you lost?
[CACAO grunts]
That's terrible.
Don't worry about a
thing--I'm on the case!
[CHIYO]
Let's go, follow me!
Hello?
Weird. There's no one here, but
usually the police are the ones
who help with lost kitties.
Uh, it's fine! We can
probably try something else.
I just need to
think for a second.
Let's see.
Oh, I know, we can
ask an adult for help!
Wait! Excuse me, ma'am!
Sorry, but I found a kitty cat,
and I'm having trouble
finding out where she lives.
A cat? Where is she?
[CHIYO]
Whoa, she's gone?
Wait, kitty! Where are you?
[gasps]
[CHIYO]
Hey! There she is!
What?!
Why would she leave without me?
[AZUKI]
Hmm... Let's see.
We should get
this one for Kashou!
Red bean ice cream!
Sure, if you like
disgusting things.
But I think this
one's way better!
A coconut ice bar!
Don't be stupid!
Everyone knows that red bean
ice cream is the coldest!
Oh? I guess you
and that ice cream
have something in common, then!
[BOTH growling]
[AZUKI]
Huh?
Wait!
That's weird. I thought
I saw Cacao walk by.
But she shouldn't
be out here, right?
Cacao?
[CHIYO panting]
Why'd you run off
like that, kitty?
[CHIYO]
Hold on, is this your house?
[CACAO]
Mm-mm...
Oh, that's too bad.
[CHIYO]
Cakes...
Hey, wait a minute.
Are you saying that
your house is a cake shop?
[CACAO]
Mm.
Wow! That's great news!
We can just check all the cake
shops until we find yours!
This one?
Here?
[CHIYO]
I feel like we've
looked everywhere.
Do you maybe have
any other clues?
[CACAO]
Mm-mm...
Oh...
Uh-oh.
It's a dead end.
Oops, I guess we took
a wrong turn somewhere.
Everything's gonna be okay.
The main street should
be right around here.
[CHIYO gasps]
Uh, don't worry.
It's just a crow.
[CHIYO, CACAO]
Uhh...
Come on.
--[CROWS squawking]
--[CHIYO, CACAO yell]
[CHIYO]
Wait!
You're too fast, kitty!
No!
[BOTH gasp]
[grunts]
Poor kitty!
Can you stand okay? Let's go!
Hurry! This way!
[CACAO, CHIYO panting]
--[CROW squawks]
--[BOTH gasp]
[CHIYO]
For real?!
[BOTH yell]
Oh, no, what do we do now?
--[rustling]
--[BOTH gasp]
Hey!
Wait for me, kitty!
[gasps]
[screams]
[CACAO hissing]
[yowling]
Wow. They finally left.
It was so cool how you
scared off those crows.
I wanna thank you for your help,
so name your price
and I'll do it.
Taiyaki.
Oh. You must really
like that stuff.
Okey-doke, as soon as we find
a vendor, I'll buy you one.
[BOTH gasp]
[CHIYO giggles]
This takes me back.
It's like when we
lived in our old house.
Our family used
to live with a cat.
[CHIYO] We were all staying
with my grandma at the time.
The cat and I would
eat taiyaki together.
She would always play
with me. It was so fun.
[CHIYO]
But then one day,
my daddy got a new job
and told us we had to move.
No way! I refuse to
leave without the kitty!
[CHIYO] I was so mad, I ran
out of the house and got lost.
But then the kitty
came to find me.
Your grandmother and
the others are very worried.
So let's go back now, okay?
'Kay.
[CHIYO gasps]
What was that for?
Are you worried
about me or something?
[CACAO]
Mm.
Aw, you're so sweet, kitty.
I'm Cacao.
Huh?
Like the cake?
Wait, that makes sense.
You're saying your
name is Cacao, right?
Chiyo...
[CACAO]
...thank you.
I'm so happy
you're speaking to me.
[CHIYO gasps]
What's that?
[KASHOU]
I have a question.
What's the deal with this photo?
Oh. You see...
Well, it's actually
a great story.
We wanted to bring
in more business
for the café, so, you know...
[KASHOU] So that's what's
been going on today.
I'm not worried
about business at all.
In fact, our sales have
been perfectly fine.
[CHOCOLA, VANILLA gasp]
See for yourself.
I couldn't come up with a new
cake for the summer season.
That's what's been
on my mind lately.
So we won't have
to ration our food?
I see. We jumped to conclusions.
[KASHOU] We're a patisserie,
not a maid café.
Please don't do
those things again.
[CHOCOLA, VANILLA]
Okay.
But... I appreciate you working
hard to bring in more business.
And because of you guys,
I was able to think
of a new cake idea.
Thank you, Chocola...
and Vanilla.
You're welcome, master!
You're welcome.
Cacao, huh?
That's right, have you
seen her around today?
I don't know.
We've been pretty busy
so it's hard to say
if I've seen her or not.
Hey, Nuts. Do you
think it's possible that
we actually saw her out
on the streets, then?
Don't be silly.
[VANILLA] Hold on,
you think you saw her earlier?
Where was she?
She was by the
apartment complex.
This is terrible.
What if Cacao got lost again?
We have to find her.
[KASHOU]
Wait a moment.
[BOTH gasp]
What is it, Master?
Shouldn't Cacao be waiting
for us back at home?
Yeah. Well, she's
supposed to be.
Are you here, Cacao?
Hello?
[VANILLA]
No luck.
Check the living room.
Good idea.
--[KASHOU] Uh...
--[CHOCOLA, VANILLA grunt]
Master!
Hey, can you warn
us before stopping?
Cacao!
So she was in here.
[KASHOU] I suppose you
were waiting to greet us, huh?
That's so sweet.
Thank goodness,
Chocola was worried!
You freak out about everything.
[CHOCOLA]
Chocola was not freaking out!
Besides, Vanilla,
you were worried, too!
She got home. Thank goodness.
You're so cute.
Want Chocola to entertain you?
We all know she'll likely
end up entertaining you.
[CHOCOLA giggles]