[MAPLE grunts]
Yep. That's perfect.
Cinnamon.
I need to cool the noodles.
Would you mind getting
some ice ready?
Sure!
Ahh...
Ready over here if you are.
What's taking so...?
[CINNAMON]
This is heaven.
[MAPLE]
What do you think you're doing?
Aw. C'mon, share with me.
I want one of those, too.
[AZUKI] That's a hot mess
if I've ever seen one.
Hey, Azuki.
Hang these, too, please!
'Kay.
What a lovely day.
It's crazy hot though.
[CINNAMON grunts]
[SHIGURE]
Cinnamon, 92.5 centimeters.
You've gotten
bigger since last time!
No, you're kidding me.
How's there no end to this?
She's huge and Azuki
hasn't changed at all!
Hey! What the--?
Why'd you drag me into this?!
[COCONUT]
I just call 'em like I see 'em.
Well, there's something
that definitely hasn't changed.
[door opens]
[CHOCOLA]
We're home!
Technically, this
isn't home anymore.
[SHIGURE
Good to see ya!
We decided to get a head start
on the health checks
while we waited for you.
We're doing measurements.
Could you please come
to the living room?
[SHIGURE] Now, look straight
ahead for me, please.
Good, that's perfect.
Hold still for just a sec.
Cacao, 109.
Cacao, 109 centimeters. Got it.
Yep. You're growing up
at exactly the right speed.
She's gonna be big
and strong one day!
That's partially
thanks to us, you know.
Since we're raising her well.
Chocola's proud of us!
If she keeps
growing at this rate,
it won't be too long before
she totally outgrows you, Azuki.
What? That could never happen.
Jealous much?
When I was her age,
I was already lots bigger
than you in every way.
Can it! You're full o' hot air.
Hey, are you making
fun of my puffy cheeks?
You just hear
what you wanna hear.
Maybe you should
clean your ears out!
Say that again!
Come at me!
[COCONUT growls]
[COCONUT yowls]
[AZUKI yowls]
Oh, dear.
No growth in this
area, that's for sure.
Not that I'm surprised
or anything, but...
[BOTH growling]
Let's wrap up this
round of health checks
with everybody's favorite--
the kinetic eyesight test!
[GROUP]
'Kay.
You know how this works.
Something appears on the
screen and you say what it is.
[CACAO]
Uh-hm.
All right, let's get started.
On your marks...
...get set...
[mouse clicking]
Now, everyone,
please say it together.
[ALL] "I really, really, really,
really, really love Shigure."
That's correct.
Time to move on to the next one.
[ALL] It says, "I want
to be by Shigure's side
even if it's really hot out."
Wonderful!
You're all a hundred
percent so far.
Just warning you, this last
one is a little bit long.
[ALL] "We would love for
Shigure to take lots and lots
of photos of us even if
they get a little spicy."
--[SHIGURE giggling]
--[camera clicking]
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but I'm fairly certain
this counts as entrapment.
[giggles] And the fact
that you caught that,
just shows how much you've
grown!
[ALL groan]
[CHOCOLA]
Mm?
It's just watermelon.
Give it a try, it's good!
[CACAO grunts]
Like this. Watch Chocola.
Mm! [giggles]
So yummy.
Ahh...
[CACAO gasps]
[VANILLA, CHOCOLA]
Huh?
[CHOCOLA giggles]
Uh? Is something wrong?
Oh. Yeah, these things
are full of seeds.
You just gotta spit 'em out.
[VANILLA]
That's right.
Be careful not to swallow any...
...or you'll grow
one in your tummy.
[CACAO gasps]
[CHOCOLA]
Watch this, Cacao.
Chocola's gonna show you
how the pros do it!
Pew, pew, pew, pew, pew!
Ahh...
Wow. I think that's
the first time
I've ever seen her look
at you with such admiration.
Huh?! This can't
be the first time!
It is.
[CHOCOLA]
Oh, no.
Man, this sure is a perfect
summer day, isn't it?
[MAPLE]
I agree.
I wish I hadn't gotten
all sweaty and icky
when I was boiling
noodles though.
I've heard that sweating a lot
can help you stay in shape.
It's kind of like a diet.
I don't need to sweat
or go on a diet, thanks!
No. I didn't mean
it like that, May.
I think you look cute
when you're plumpy.
I just said I'm not plumpy!
[COCONUT sighs]
I always want to hit the beach
when it's this hot outside.
There's an idea.
We should go then!
We had a beach day after
our last health checkups,
so why don't we have another?
I wouldn't say we
made a "day" of it
when all we did was
dip our feet in the water.
[COCONUT] In that case,
all the more reason to go back!
Let's do this right!
Chocola wants to go
to the beach, too!
Yes. That sounds fun.
Excellent! Let's do it.
[CINNAMON, MAPLE,
AZUKI, COCONUT gasp]
Time to get ready!
--[SHIGURE] Not yet.
--[CHOCOLA] Huh?
We'll go soon. But first
we have an important mission.
[CHOCOLA, VANILLA gasp]
Swimsuits, huh?
Not sure what I expected
the big mission to be,
but this wasn't it.
She looked like
she meant business,
so I assumed it would
actually be something important.
What are you talking about?
Cacao's first beach
trip has to be special.
So it's crucial that we find her
the cutest possible
bathing suit! [chuckles]
[CHOCOLA]
Chocola agrees that we need to
find something
super cute for Cacao.
But Chocola's not so sure all of
us need new swimsuits.
I agree. It seems like a lot,
and I'd be happy to wear the one
you bought for me last summer.
Uh, well, I think...
...I might want to pick
up a new one this year.
If that's okay.
I'm afraid last year's
won't fit me anymore.
[GROUP]
Uhh...
[MINADUKI CATS gasp]
How about this style?
I think a more mature look
would really work for me.
[AZUKI]
Yeah, maybe.
A loin cloth is
more up your alley.
[COCONUT]
Why that?!
Hey! Look, May.
Try this one on. [giggles]
It's perfect for you.
[MAPLE]
Hmm?
[MAPLE yells]
You can't expect me to wear
that thing out in public!
I would get arrested!
Aww. Come on.
I'd wear it myself, but I think
it's more your type of suit.
We need to find the
purr-fect swimsuit for Cacao!
[VANILLA]
Hm? Chocola.
Maybe we should look
in that section...
...for kids' suits.
Presenting the first look
that Chocola picked out.
Ta-da!
[GROUP gasps]
I picked this.
Ta-da!
[GROUP]
Aww...
[BOTH]
And for our final look... Ta-da!
Yeah, please
don't pick that one.
Agreed. Put it back.
[registers dings]
[SHIGURE] All right!
Does everybody have their bags?
Let's take a short
break and then go home.
Oh, hey!
Let's run by the
food court downstairs.
They have the best
taiyaki there.
It's super crispy and packed
full of extra red bean paste!
[CHOCOLA gasps] Yes! That
sounds amazing! Let's do it!
[ALL chattering]
[CACAO]
Hm?
[VANILLA]
Cacao... Is something wrong?
[CACAO gasps]
What's the big deal?
[GROUP]
Huh?
Sorry, kiddo, but sadly,
that's one fish you can't eat.
That one's a toy! You fill
it with air until it floats
and then you can ride
it around in the ocean.
[CACAO]
Ahh...
[gasps]
You just did the exact opposite
of talking her out of it.
I think she wants it more now.
What?
[register dings]
Shigure, thank you so much.
You bought everyone new swimwear
and now Cacao's toy, too.
Oh, don't mention it!
I'll get my money's
worth out of it.
[GROUP grunts]
'Kay, this is your first real
beach trip so listen up!
If you want to go, then you
have to pass a test first.
And that test...
...is to put your
face under the water!
[CACAO whimpers]
It's not that big of a deal,
but let Chocola
show you how it's done.
See? Now you give it a try!
[CACAO]
Mm...
[gasps, grunts]
Hey, don't look at
Chocola like that!
This is super basic stuff.
How will you enjoy the
beach if you can't get wet?
[gasps]
[CHOCOLA] Here, Chocola will
even do it with you this time.
Let's count to three and we'll
dip in and out real quick, okay?
Ready? One, two...
[inhales] ...three!
[CACAO]
Uhh...
Ah!
Uh?
[CHOCOLA gasps]
You did great, Cacao!
Not exactly. You're really
gullible, do you know that?
[CHOCOLA]
Huh?
[KASHOU]
What? A beach day?
Yeah, sure.
I could go as long as
it's not on a work day.
[KASHOU]
Okay. Sounds good.
We can be there around noon
if that works for you.
[CACAO]
Oh...
Ah...
[CACAO]
Ah...!
We'll see you then.
Oh?
[CACAO grunts]
[CHOCOLA groans]
Chocola, you did great and all,
but it's best to inflate them
after you get to the beach.
[CHOCOLA gasps]
Wha...?!
[AZUKI, COCONUT laugh]
[MAPLE, CINNAMON giggle]
[COCONUT grunts]
I've decided our base is here!
[AZUKI] Ooh, she put on a
swimsuit and now she's "alpha."
[CHOCOLA]
Hey, guys!
[GROUP]
Hm?
[CHOCOLA]
Sorry to keep you waiting!
[CHOCOLA giggles]
Awesome. Everyone's here,
so ya know what that means!
[BOTH]
Swimmin' time!
[COCONUT laughs]
[AZUKI laughs]
[MAPLE]
Take that!
[CINNAMON gasps]
[CHOCOLA laughs]
[CACAO gasps]
[VANILLA chuckles]
[COCONUT grunts]
[CINNAMON gasps]
[CHOCOLA laughs]
[VANILLA grunts]
[CACAO grunts]
[MAPLE gasps]
[AZUKI giggles]
To the right, to the right!
It's your chopstick hand!
Yeah! You gotta turn a little!
There you go.
It's in front of you!
[CINNAMON gasps]
[CINNAMON grunts]
[CINNAMON yelps]
[CINNAMON] Why is she only
coming after me? [cries]
[BOTH] Because you
got mad melons, girl.
[AZUKI]
Ahh...
Yeah? How'd it turn out?
[SHIGURE giggles]
Look at all the beautiful
new treasures
I'm adding to my collection.
[KASHOU]
Hey, you okay, Vanilla?
Something's wrong.
We can't find Cacao.
[KASHOU, SHIGURE gasp]
[CHOCOLA]
Uh...
[KASHOU]
Hmm...
Did you find her?
[SHIGURE]
Not yet.
Hey! Look, she's way out there!
[SHIGURE gasps]
Oh, no, she could get
pulled into the undertow!
Chocola can help!
[SHIGURE]
No, it's too dangerous.
We have to find a lifeguard.
[GIRL 12A]
Don't worry, I'm on it!
[GROUP gasps]
[panting]
I don't know how we
can ever repay you.
Thank you for saving her.
Yes, you have our deepest
gratitude for all your help.
Chocola agrees. That could
have been mewserable.
It's not a big deal. I just
did what anyone would've done.
[SHIGURE]
No!
You rescued her
and I won't forget it,
so I owe you the same debt
I would if you had saved me.
Please, let me
thank you somehow!
Okay. Um...
[gasps]
Well, if you come check out my
shop, then we can call it even!
A shop? What kind?
These fried noodles
are delicious!
Yeah and this
ramen's pretty tasty.
[SHIGURE] For a small
clubhouse, this is impressive.
Their menu has lots of variety.
The location's not
the best, but...
...I think their problem
is advertising.
People would swarm this place
if they knew it was here.
I've got an idea.
To show our thanks,
we'll make this the most
popular place on the beach!
Huh?
[CHOCOLA]
Come and get your snacks at
Beach Clubhouse Orange!
These adorable cats
are ready to serve you!
[COCONUT]
Wow, this is great!
[AZUKI] That little
snack shack, Orange,
at the edge of the beach
sure is incredible, isn't it?
Their food rocks!
It's the best place ever!
[BOTH]
Hm?
[CROWD gasps, cheers]
There's more where
that came from,
so come visit us at the Beach
Clubhouse Orange today!
We served up some tunes.
Now let us serve you lunch!
[CROWD cheers]
[BEACH GOER 12E gasps]
Hey, take a look at this.
"An industry first,
this beach restaurant
is staffed with cats!"
[BEACH GOER 12F]
Aww! That sounds fun!
Let's check it out!
Yeah!
[gasps]
[GIRL 12A]
Are you... for real?
We've never had
a turnout like this!
'Kay. Got one grilled corn and
one frankfurter coming right up!
I have a lemon shaved ice
and a sweet milk shaved ice.
Will that be all?
[AZUKI]
Whew, that's hot.
If this keeps up,
I'm gonna get barbecued, too.
[COCONUT giggles]
Here, thank you for waiting!
[CACAO]
Mm...
Be right back!
I'll run this curry out.
Sounds good. Thank you, sis!
And thank you.
Sorry to make you cook
after everything you've done.
Seriously, don't mention it.
Your sister rescued
a member of our family,
so this is the least we can do.
Excuse me. Can we order?
[CHOCOLA gasps] Yes, of course!
Just a moment, please!
Maple! Come help Chocola out
and take her order meow!
[MAPLE]
Sorry! I'm too busy over here!
Aw, man.
Hey, uh...
We'll be with you
in just a moment!
Go ahead.
Well... okay.
[AZUKI grunts]
We worked our tails off today.
I know, right?
We took a day off at the beach
and somehow still
wound up working.
Well, the important thing
is we all had fun together!
Thank you guys again
for helping us out today.
[SHIGURE] No, we were
glad to be of service.
We inherited this place from our
parents and now we're in charge.
We've never done that
much business in one day.
Well, that's Shigure for ya.
Comin' in clutch
with the great ideas.
Yeah, good work as always!
I didn't do that much really.
You girls had all of the
heavy lifting, so thank you.
You worked hard today, too,
Cacao. We're very proud!
Cacao is a good girl.
It was so fun having
a full restaurant.
[GIRL 12A grunts]
Although, I think
we were only popular
because we had the novelty
of the cats working here today.
[SHIGURE]
Yeah... about that.
[BOTH gasp]
I have a proposal that
you might be interested in.
[REPORTER 03A]
Up next, an exclusive story
about a popular
beachside snack shack
staffed entirely with cute cats!
Huh?
Well, hello there!
Next time you go swimming, come
visit Beach Clubhouse Orange!
We can't wait to serve you!
Oh, was that your proposal?
It was! Those girls seemed
like really nice people,
so I introduced them to some
cats who needed a good home.
Cats are lucky.
So you know what that means--
that beach clubhouse is
destined for lots of success.
[SHIGURE]
But business and success aside,
one thing is for certain--
there's nothing better
than a life with cats.
Oh, hey!
[COCONUT giggles]
[BOTH giggle]
Hi!
[CHOCOLA gasps]
[BOTH]
Hello and welcome!
We're pleased to
serve you at La Soleil!
[CACAO giggles]