[explosion]
‐ What was that?
‐ I think a plasma grenade.
David: Focus, guys.
Pitohui's the mission.
‐ [gunshot]
‐ Open fire on the wall!
‐ [yelling]
[shotgun blasts]
‐ [groans]
‐ Lax!
[explosion]
[photon sword hums]
‐ Now this is fun.
[yells]
[laughs]
‐ [yelling]
‐ [grunts]
‐ I'm not going down that easy!
‐ [laughs]
It's time to die, boys!
You don't know
when to quit, do you!
‐ What? Did you think
I'd be scared of a glow stick?
‐ That's right. This kind
of thing doesn't interest you.
Guns are your jam.
‐ Yeah. So what?
‐ Bet you didn't know.
This Muramasa F9,
it's got a neat feature.
‐ [grunting]
‐ [laughs]
‐ Is‐‐Is this fun for you?!
You crazy bitch!
‐ I'm loving every second
of it, actually.
And now I'll enjoy
your death, too...
bitch.
‐ Pitohui!
[yells]
‐ Yes!
You know it!
That is me!
‐ [gags]
[both screaming]
‐ Thanks for playing!
[laughs]
[laughing]
[laughter continues]
Fuka: Hello! Earth to LLENN.
Boss: What happened in there?
[brush rustling]
LLENN: Th‐The whole team's dead.
Pito killed
every last one of 'em.
Fuka: Whoa.
Boss: No way.
‐ H‐How is someone like me
supposed to beat
someone like that?
["Ryusei" by Eir Aoi playing]
‐ [singing in Japanese]
♪ ...safety ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ The darkest night ♪
‐ [gasps]
[whimpers]
[Terminal buzzing]
[buzzing stops]
Spectator: This'll be
the last scan of the tourney.
‐ Mm. There's only
four teams left.
‐ Crap.
PM4's got this in the bag.
‐ LLENN can still
pull through, man!
‐ T‐S is still
up on the rampart.
What are they waiting for?
‐ I bet they'll run out the game
up there, sniping at everyone.
‐ [groans]
God, they make me sick.
If they were real men,
they'd fight toe‐to‐toe.
Except for M, everyone
out there's a friggin' wimp.
Hang in there, ladies.
‐ How am I gonna do this?
What do I do?
What do I do? What do I do?
Oh, come on. Think.
You need a plan.
A plan, a plan,
but what kind of plan?
Boss: New plan, everyone!
Let's storm the cabin!
‐ Huh?
Wh‐Wh‐What?!
[automatic gunfire]
Wait! Don't go without me!
I'm not ready yet!
Boss: Sorry.
You're taking too long.
I'm calling the shots now.
‐ What's up?
‐ B‐Boss and her team
are just charging right in!
‐ Nice.
‐ No, it's suicide.
I can't kill Pito without them.
We need a plan,
but I can't think of any.
‐ Right.
I'm charging in with 'em.
‐ Huh?!
‐ That's as good a plan as any.
Just you watch.
We'll catch Pito,
wrap her up in a mat,
and bring her right back here
in nothing flat.
‐ [giggling]
‐ No, stop.
Would you wait a second?!
Get back here!
Whoa!
You gotta be kidding.
Of all the stupid‐‐Come on!
Fuka: Calm down,
and take your time.
You'll get loose eventually.
‐ Fuka! Didn't you
hear anything I said?!
You can't charge in
all by yourself!
‐ Whoever undoes
that Gordian knot
is destined to rule the world.
[laughs]
‐ [groans] Dang it!
[groans]
‐ Ladies, hit 'em hard and fast!
Team: Roger that!
M: We got four Amazons
heading straight for us.
They're getting closer.
Four hundred meters now.
Standing by for orders.
‐ Well, well, looky here.
I see LLENN's friend coming.
She's, uh,
skipping across the field.
The weird thing is
I don't see LLENN anywhere.
Do you have
any idea why that is?
M: No, I don't. From here,
it looks like they're
attacking out of desperation,
like they're
begging to be shot.
‐ Seems awfully fishy.
I know they're up to something.
‐ Well, until we
find out what that is,
thinning their ranks
is an option.
‐ I guess that's all we can do.
Here are your orders, then.
Kill them
with extreme prejudice.
‐ [yelps]
‐ [gasps]
‐ [laughs]
A bullet bounced off my helmet.
Talk about lucky.
‐ Fuka, stay down!
‐ [giggles] Nah, I'm good.
‐ It's really not fair
when they're so short.
Well? How are you doing?
‐ I got one so far.
‐ Ohh!
‐ Nice shot!
‐ He just got another!
‐ Whoa!
‐ [overlapping chatter]
‐ Oh, come on.
Sophie: What's up?
‐ Boss and the others
are on that suicide run.
‐ [sighs]
[single shot]
‐ Why's she smiling?
Aha.
‐ [panting]
Oh, great.
Looks like I'm
the last one of us left.
Gotta hand it to M.
If there's anyone sharp enough
to figure us out, it's him.
[crowd groaning]
Sophie: That's a shame.
Her timing
was way off at the end.
‐ I dare you to tell her that
when she gets here.
‐ Come on!
Fuka: Don't tell me
Alexander the Great's
still working on that knot.
Remember the prophecy.
It specifically states
that you cannot rule the world
unless you untie it.
‐ Yeah, I know!
[sighs] Stupid knot.
This'll do you.
‐ [Fuka screams]
‐ [gasps] Fuka?
‐ Fuka!
Fuka!
I took care of SHINC.
How are you doing?
‐ Eh, not good. Frustrated.
LLENN's not coming out.
I shot up her partner
and everything.
I can't believe
she's not coming to her rescue.
‐ God, would you
just finish her already?
[Pito chuckles] What's that?
Kindness? Mercy? Compassion?
M: Mercy and compassion
are the same thing,
and, no, it's not about that.
LLENN isn't coming to save her,
because she doesn't have to.
This isn't a real battle.
And while you mess around
with her friend there,
LLENN's figuring out
our blind spot,
and the last surviving team's
closing in.
I want to X her out ASAP so we
can be ready for everyone else.
Pito: Can't we just wait
a little longer?
‐ Fine. I'll kill her.
‐ [sighs]
Okay, jeez.
Oopsie.
Only got her hand.
Still getting
used to this rifle.
Damn, she's tough!
LLENN sure knows
how to pick a teammate.
[laughs]
She's not a threat anymore,
at least
for the next two minutes.
‐ Um, Hey, LLENN,
I got bad news for you.
It was an honor
serving on your team,
but my hands and feet are gone,
and I'm stuck.
‐ That's 'cause you
charged in by yourself!
‐ Yeah, but I don't regret it
or anything. That's for sure.
‐ You should!
‐ Hey, it's better
than sitting around like you,
all nervous and indecisive.
I did what I could,
and I'm good with that.
I bet if you asked
Boss and the others,
they'd say the same thing, too.
‐ [groaning]
[screams]
If I killed Pito at the start,
none of this
would have happened!
But they dropped us
so far away from each other,
and then people got in the way,
and my ammo supply went down.
And then,
when I finally get to her,
she's turned into
a rampaging monster.
I wanted to take a minute and
figure out a plan of attack,
but everyone just ran in
and got killed.
Instead of doing something,
I'm still
standing here, shaking.
Aah! I've had it!
I'm done worrying about Pito!
She can win this thing
for all I care!
She's so strong,
she probably will.
Why should I stress over someone
killing her before I do?!
That's her problem, not mine!
And if she kills me first,
that's fine, too.
If I die, I die!
Fuka: So what are you gonna do?
‐ I'm gonna kill!
‐ Kill who?
‐ Pito!
‐ Okay. How?
‐ I don't know!
I'll use my gun
if I have bullets left
or my knife. I don't care
what I use to do it.
I'm gonna kill Pito and win!
P‐chan: Awesome!
[LLENN gasps]
‐ I'm with you all the way.
Let's do this.
‐ Sweet. It's you and me, then.
LLENN: We're gonna
murder Pito together!
‐ You go, girl. Get her.
Tanya: Just like in SJ 1.
Toma: An erratic LLENN
is the best LLENN.
‐ Go, you little psycho. Go.
‐ Damn it. This is
what I wanted all along.
This is the go‐for‐broke version
of LLENN I wanted to fight.
Pito: Look! There she is!
M: Yup. I see her, too.
‐ Don't forget. She's mine.
If you kill her, I'll kill you.
Wait.
She's running away?!
What the hell?! Of all the‐‐
Unh! Get back here!
Come on! We're going after her!
‐ What'll we do
about her partner?
‐ We can kill her later.
‐ You sure? She might be
fully healed by then.
‐ Who cares?!
‐ [blow lands]
‐ [M groans]
[stammering]
LLENN's too fast.
How are we gonna catch her?
‐ Oh, I already thought of that.
At top speed,
she's as fast as a car, right?
‐ So?
‐ So it should be obvious
how we'll catch her.
‐ [yelling]
[engine roaring]
Here they come.
‐ Put the pedal to the metal!
Get me in range, idiot!
‐ If I go any faster
and have to turn,
there's a chance
you'll get thrown out.
‐ I don't care! Go faster!
Hi‐yo, Silver!
‐ [gasps]
Uh‐oh!
All right! Bring it!
‐ [laughs]
Now it's on!
Go! There's a duel comin' on!
Giddy‐up, horsey!
Hyah! Hyah!
‐ [yelling]
‐ Now this is the fight
I've been dying to have.
Come on!
Fight me,
you little chickenshit!
[groans]
‐ [gasps]
‐ Hmm?
[tires squeal]
‐ [screams]
‐ [grunts]
‐ Yes! It worked!
‐ [engine roaring]
‐ What the‐‐
It was shallow.
‐ Up to now, I killed
with my fists, my guns,
some grenades, and a sword,
pretty much everything,
everything except a car,
that is.
What you gonna do now,
huh, LLENN?!
‐ [grunts]
[both gasp]
‐ [giggles]
I missed.
‐ Now let's see
how you dodge my bullets.
‐ [yelps]
‐ Did you get her?
‐ A marker hasn't popped up yet.
Oh, there she is!
How the hell
is she still alive?
[sighs] I guess
I just winged her.
I swear, it's either 'cause
she's lucky or small or both.
She's tough to kill.
LLENN: Dang it.
Looks like the end for me.
‐ Do you want me
to get a little closer?
Pito: No. I'm fine where we are.
Are you worried I'll miss her
from here or something?
‐ No. It's just that HP
decreases under water.
She'll die whether
you shoot her or not.
I guess I figured
you'd wanna get closer
so you could look her
in the eyes as she died.
‐ Whoa. About time you got
into the spirit of this.
I'm good here. I don't wanna
take any chances around her.
I'm scared she might kill me
if I drop my guard.
‐ Wait. You're scared? Really?
‐ Of course. What do you
think I am, an idiot?
Sure, I'm scared,
scared of dying.
That's what makes this
so much fun.
‐ What's Pito waiting for?
Why doesn't she finish me?
Oh, well.
Either way, it's over.
P‐chan: Get up, LLENN!
Don't quit now!
‐ Oh, leave me alone.
‐ Come on! You're not dead yet!
‐ It's not at zero,
but it's getting close.
Fuka: Hang on, LLENN!
I'm almost there!
LLENN: Don't bother.
[gasps]
Fuka: Get ready!
I'm comin' in hot!
‐ Eh, I guess I'll put her
out of her misery now.
Don't want her
to drown to death.
M: I'll pull up
a little closer, then.
["Independence"
by Elza Kanzaki playing]
[Pito laughs]
What's she doing that for?
M: I don't know.
‐ Maybe it's some kind
of shrimpy pre‐death ritual.
[chuckles]
Now what?!
‐ Hang on!
Pito: Charge!
Don't just sit here!
Go after it!
‐ ♪ Don't discard... ♪
[singing in Japanese]
Fuka: 'Sup, girl!
Damn, you look so fine.
Wanna go for a ride
in my new whip?
‐ Okay.
‐ ♪ Meant to be... ♪
‐ Mm, someone's gonna
get lucky tonight. [giggles]
LLENN: Hurry!
Get us out of here!
‐ You got it, sugar.
Know if there's
any love hotels around here?
Pito: Get back here!
[gunfire]
LLENN: Wait.
I didn't know you could drive.
‐ I don't, but I do play driving
games every now and then.
‐ How you find the time to play
all these games is beyond me.
‐ Like they say, be prepared.
‐ Y‐Yeah.
Pito: Take this!
LLENN: Do your grenades explode
if you throw 'em?
‐ Nah. You have to fire 'em.
‐ Oh, crap.
[Pito grunts]
‐ ♪ Are you satisfied
with the way you are living? ♪
♪ Don't silence the true voice
from inside ♪
♪ I must try,
it's do or die... ♪
Ohh! God!
LLENN: I did it!
Fuka: LLENN, look!
‐ [gasps]
What in the heck is that?!
Fuka: What in the heck's
it look like?!
‐ No way. They got geysers here.
‐ Ah, damn it. Another second,
and they would have hit that.
They're all going off
right on time, though.
Talk about punctuality.
LLENN: Faster! Go faster!
Fuka: I can't!
‐ Why not?!
‐ We're out of gas.
M: We're almost out.
‐ Of what?!
‐ Of gas.
‐ Okay, then.
‐ Ram into 'em!
‐ ♪ Don't discard ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ Independence ♪
♪ Meant to be ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ I will never let fate
decide for me ♪
♪ Don't discard ♪
[singing in Japanese]
‐ [laughs]
‐ ♪ This is my independence ♪
♪ Meant to be... ♪
‐ [thinking]
I'm sorry, P‐chan.
‐ Not even! Do what you gotta.
[giggles]
‐ ♪ I will never
let fate decide for me ♪
‐ [yelling]
‐ Oh, yes!
This is what I've been
waiting for all day.
You're so irresistible...
I wanna kill you.
["To see the future"
by Tomori Kusunoki playing]
[singing in Japanese]
♪ You say good night ♪
♪ To see the future ♪