Pito: Happy New Year, LLENN!
LLENN: Happy New Year!
‐ So, LLENN, I was
wondering about something.
Have you heard about Squad Jam?
‐ Did you say, "Squid jam"?
‐ Ecch!
Now I'm picturing that. Gross.
‐ What's gross about it?
It's just fermented squid paste.
‐ That's not what
I'm talking about!
You thought I said, "Squid,"
but I didn't.
I said, "Squad." You know,
like a group of soldiers
on a mission?
‐ But you also said, "Jam."
‐ Not the kind
you spread on bread.
I meant "jam" like, jamming
a bunch of things together.
‐ Oh, like bullets
jammed in a gun.
So then, Squad Jam is
just a bunch of squads.
‐ That's right. Squad Jam's
this tournament coming up,
where a bunch of teams
get to fight it out
in a battle royale.
[billiard balls clatter]
["Ryusei" by Eir Aoi playing]
‐ [singing in Japanese]
♪ ...safety ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ The darkest night ♪
Pito: Squad Jam's
also called "SJ."
‐ And it's
literally a battle royale,
where everyone fights
each other to the death?
‐ Yup. You ever hear
about something
called Bullet of Bullets, LLENN?
It also goes by the name B. o. B.
‐ I only know
the basics about it.
There's a one‐on‐one prelim
to find the top 30 players.
Then they fight
'til only one's left.
The survivor gets the title
of strongest player in "GGO."
That's it, though.
‐ The third one was held
not too long ago,
and I was in it.
‐ Whoa! So how'd you do?
‐ I only made it
to the second round of prelims.
‐ Oh. That sucks.
‐ Yeah, a sniper got me.
Chalk it up to bad luck.
Anyway, something really cool
happened in the finals.
Two players worked together as
a team right up until the end.
You should have seen it.
God, what a blast!
Talk about intense.
The whole time,
I was on the edge of my seat.
So this guy from Japan
was watching the last B. o. B.,
and he thought it was so cool,
he got this crazy idea.
He thought,
"How 'bout a battle royale,
but with teams
going at it instead?"
‐ Hmm.
‐ He DMed ZASKAR,
the folks that created
and operate "GGO,"
about it, and here we are.
‐ Wait. they granted
the request of some rando?
‐ Well, that's what happened.
He even offered to sponsor it,
so ZASKAR had nothing to lose
at the end of the day.
Aw, man. Setting this up must
have cost him a pretty penny.
The guy's a writer in his 50s
who's got
this insane fixation for guns.
He loves 'em so much,
he's got shooting
going on in all his books.
[writer chuckles]
‐ Huh. Sounds like
an eccentric guy.
‐ Hah! He's both a writer
and a gun nut.
He's way beyond eccentric.
I say, if we see him
out in public,
we scream bloody murder 'til
the cops show up and nail him.
‐ It sounds like you got
a grudge against him, Pito.
‐ No, not really.
Anyway, the folks at ZASKAR
liked his idea, and since
he was gonna be the one
bankrolling the whole thing,
they said, "What the heck?"
and agreed to go ahead
and do it as a mini‐tourney
on the Japanese server.
They called it Squad Jam,
SJ, for short.
The sign‐ups for teams
are going on right this minute.
It's gonna happen next Sunday,
February the first.
‐ Hopefully they get
enough players for it.
‐ Want one?
‐ No, thanks.
It's a quick turnaround,
but a bunch of teams
already signed up.
Pretty sure
none of the B. o. B. finalists
are gonna be
in the mix for this one.
I have a feeling
they all prefer playing solo.
‐ [crunching] Hmm.
Their loss, I guess.
‐ What's up?
You're not into this?
‐ Sorry, but I'm
not really cut out
for these player‐versus‐player
tournaments.
‐ That's hilarious,
considering you're one
of the most ruthless assassins
in this game.
‐ I‐I'm not ruthless!
‐ Yeah, right. Whatever.
Sign up.
You'd be so awesome at it.
‐ Who, me?! For real?
You like, wanna team up?
‐ No. As much as I'd like
to take part in the bloodbath,
I'll have to sit this one out.
My best friend
since middle school's
getting married
the same day as the tourney.
If I skipped her wedding
to go blast a bunch of people
in a game,
she'd never forgive me.
It wouldn't matter
if I survived and won.
‐ She'd kill you for sure
in real life.
‐ You know it.
But you're not
doing anything that day,
nothing important,
like a friend's wedding,
or your wedding, right?
‐ Maybe?
I'd have to check my calendar.
‐ I so knew it!
I'll take care
of signing you up.
‐ H‐Hold on!
I didn't say I would.
Besides, I have to be on a team.
Who can I team up with
besides you?
‐ Hah! I knew you were into it.
‐ I was just asking.
‐ I happen to know a player
who'd be perfect for you. Unh.
He's super talented,
but a little on the weird side.
Actually,
he's pretty much a criminal,
if you wanna
get right down to it.
I wouldn't call him
a bad guy, though.
He's not exactly good, either.
You guys are gonna make
an awesome team together.
‐ Wait. Just him and me?
‐ Yup, just you guys.
I had others in mind,
but they're all busy, too.
‐ Honestly...
after hearing you say all that,
do you think I'd be okay
teaming up with him?!
‐ New experiences
are good for you.
‐ You're right,
but I don't know.
‐ LLENN, be honest with me
for a sec here.
I get the feeling
something's bugging you.
‐ Huh?
‐ If I were to guess,
I'd say something in your
real life's got you down.
That's why you play "GGO,"
to blow off a little steam.
Am I right?
You're here,
'cause you wanna escape.
‐ [gasps]
‐ I know what you're thinking,
how'd I know?
It's simple, really.
I'm here for the same reason.
There's all kinds of stuff
in my real life that I hate
or can't do anything about,
but here in "GGO,"
I get to unload
on monsters and people
and kill the hell out of them
with no regrets.
‐ "No regrets."
‐ Mm.
‐ [boom]
[gasps]
‐ [running footsteps]
‐ All I'm saying is,
this game lets us take out
all our frustrations
in ways we can't
in the real world.
[monster roars]
So let's cut loose
and kick some ass!
[monster roars]
If I don't hear from you
by Wednesday morning,
I'm signing you up!
‐ I didn't say I would!
‐ Sorry! I can't hear you!
‐ 'Cause you don't want to!
‐ Blow its rotten face off!
‐ [gunfire]
Miyu: No way. This Squad Jam
thing's a PvP with teams?!
That sounds awesome!
‐ Mm, yeah, well...
I'm not sure about
picking fights with people.
That's kind of scary.
And I don't know about
teaming up with some stranger,
even if Pito vouches for him.
Part of me worries
I'll just be in his way.
Anyhoo, that's why
I'm calling you.
Since you're
the big VR expert,
what would you do
if you were in my shoes?
‐ I think if you think
it'd be fun,
you should totally do it.
‐ Uh, that's the problem.
I don't know.
‐ Whoa! Hang on a sec.
I just looked it up,
and Squad Jam's
happening February 1!
‐ Yeah. So?
‐ Elza Kanzaki's concert's
that day. Remember?
I told you I'd try
to get tickets for us.
‐ [gasps] I totally forgot.
I'm sorry.
If we can still get tickets
to it, I'd rather go to that.
And you can stay over
and stuff, too.
‐ Cool! But what if we
can't get tickets to it?
Mm, this point,
our chances are fifty‐fifty.
‐ When will you know
you got 'em?
‐ 4:00 Tuesday.
‐ If you can get 'em, I'm not
gonna do the tournament.
Let me know
as soon as you find out.
"The rules for Squad Jam
are basically the same
as B. o. B.'s battle royale.
The match begins when the teams
are teleported
to the playing field.
The team that survives
to the end wins.
The setting is a special map.
Teleportation is random,
so where teams start
depends on luck.
Players may use any weapon
they please during battle.
They may also use
any vehicle they find.
Corpses usually disappear
right away,
but in SJ, they will remain
on the map for ten minutes.
The Satellite Scan.
Each player
will receive a terminal,
which will periodically display
their opponents' locations
for a short time."
Huh.
[groans]
[clock chiming]
‐ Please let me get
a ticket to see Elza.
Please, please, please.
‐ [girls chattering]
‐ [groans]
Girl: You see her?
‐ Yeah, how could I not?
‐ She's so tall.
[cell phone rings]
Miyu: I'm sorry, Kohi.
I couldn't get tickets
to Elza's concert.
‐ That's okay.
Guess I can play now.
Thanks for trying
to get them. Bye.
‐ So let's cut loose
and kick some ass!
‐ [gasps]
[thinking]
I'll kick ass, all right.
[country western music playing]
[dog barking]
[glasses clinking]
Pito: Yoo‐hoo! LLENN!
I got us a private room up here!
I knew I could count on you.
You're gonna slay out there,
literally!
Ow! Take it easy, Pito! [groans]
‐ So, about your partner
in this thing,
I asked him to run some errands
for me in real life,
and he'll be a little late.
‐ She knows him in real life,
too. Interesting.
Is he her boyfriend, lover,
husband, maybe her dad?
Heck, he could even be her son.
‐ Did you bone up
on the rules of SJ last night?
Knowing you, I bet
you stayed up super late
going over every word.
‐ Y‐Yeah.
‐ Then how 'bout you and I
go over
the most important points of SJ?
Teams can have
from two to six players,
no more, no less.
If you shoot
your teammate by mistake
or they get hit
by friendly fire,
their HP will take damage.
Unlike in B. o. B.,
you can communicate
with your team here.
You can't communicate
with other teams.
Corpses stay on the map
for ten minutes
and then return
to the saloon.
At the start of the game,
all teams are dropped
at least one kilometer apart,
but they can
close in on you quick,
so always be on guard.
Snipers can pop your bubble
from 800 meters,
and a machine gun can
ventilate you from 600 meters.
There's one thing about SJ
to always keep in mind.
Get ready to answer this one.
The Sat Scan only shows
where the team leader is,
which means...
‐ Um...
‐ Yes. LLENN.
‐ There's no way to tell where
a team's members really are
unless you have
a visual on them,
which means you can use
your team leader's position
to set a trap?
‐ That's my LLENN,
as sneaky as an ant lion
in the Sahara!
You ruthless little bug.
‐ Please don't tease me
like that.
‐ Who's teasing?
The way you pop out at players,
spraying bullets,
God, you're vicious!
‐ It gives me the chills.
‐ Question!
‐ Yes! LLENN!
‐ What happens if a team's
leader dies? Do they lose?
‐ That wouldn't be fun
for the others, now, would it?
During registration, you give
each team member a rank.
If the leader dies,
the next rank takes their place.
‐ That's perfect.
It's one less thing
for everyone on the team
to worry about
during all the shooting.
‐ Yup, you said it.
Focus on the fight.
It'd be so cool if
the two of you win this thing.
‐ [sighs] I can't believe
I'm doing this.
‐ There's one last rule
to keep in mind.
The leader's
the only one who can resign,
and if that happens,
the whole team's out, too.
But I'm pretty sure
that's not going to be an option
either of you are gonna go for.
‐ Hmm.
‐ Well, that's everything.
‐ Good luck, squad leader!
‐ [gasps]
What do you mean
I'm the leader?
I‐I can't be the leader.
What's up?
Is the person you're
sticking me with weaker than me?
‐ You're so cute
when you get all frazzled.
He's not weaker than you.
Seriously, he's
the strongest player I know.
‐ Then why me?
‐ Trust me girl, okay?
‐ It's all part of the plan.
‐ [door opens]
‐ M: I'm here.
‐ [gasps]
‐ Sorry I'm late.
Pito: Yeah,
you'd better be sorry.
‐ The traffic was bad.
I did get everything
you wanted done, though.
‐ Meet your new partner.
As you can see,
he's big as a house
and has
poor time‐management skills,
but he's one hell of a fighter.
Go on, doofus.
Introduce yourself.
‐ How's it going?
Name's M, like the letter.
Nice to meet you.
‐ Nice to meet you, too.
You can call me LLENN. [gasps]
‐ Sorry to duck out on you kids.
Have fun, and don't
do anything I wouldn't do.
‐ Uh...
‐ Bye!
‐ [door closes]
‐ [sighs]
‐ So, uh...
‐ [yelps]
it's obvious we're both
nervous about this,
but, like, let's not be.
You know, nervous.
I don't want
Pito kicking my ass
'cause I made you
so nervous that we lost.
‐ You're kidding.
I‐I mean, mm‐hmm!
I totally get it.
But you don't have
to worry about me,
'cause I'm going to give it
my all and then some!
I'm rarin' to go, M.
‐ Me, too. Let's do our best
out there, LLENN.
Is it okay I call you that,
instead of, you know, "Captain"?
It'll help me relax.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ Thanks for understanding.
So what were you talking about?
‐ She went over
the rules with me
and said I was the leader,
but wouldn't tell me why.
‐ And did she tell you why
she wanted us to meet today?
‐ No, she didn't.
‐ [sighs] That figures.
Let's go.
‐ What do you mean? Go where?
‐ The training grounds.
I want to check out
your combat skills.
We'll start with you
in stand‐up firing position.
Now fire ten rounds
on semi‐auto.
Now fire ten more,
fast as you can,
the rest on full‐auto.
[LLENN panting]
‐ Sprint full speed
to the truck.
Touch it. Then run back
at full speed.
Aim for the target
while you're running,
and fire on full auto.
When you're down to
eight rounds, reload and fire.
[gunfire fades]
Now walk with your eyes closed,
straight ahead,
steady pace, even steps.
Stop, turn to your right,
and find your target.
On my command, get up, and run.
Go!
When I signal, hit the dirt!
Now walk backwards
as fast as you can.
‐ [yelps]
‐ If you trip and fall,
get in the prone position.
Scrunch up into a ball, and roll
straight down the slope.
‐ [groans]
‐ I have a good idea
of your skills now.
‐ Whoa, that's what you use?
I've never seen a rifle
like that before.
‐ It's the M14‐EBR.
The EBR stands
for Enhanced Battle Rifle.
It's a souped‐up version
of the standard M14,
7.62 caliber.
‐ I guess that means
your combat style's
what they call midrange,
semi‐auto?
‐ You got it.
I like to keep as much distance
between me and the enemy
as possible.
I'll use the EBR
up close if I have to,
but if I'm in a room,
I use this.
This is the HK45.
It's German made, .45 caliber.
It holds ten rounds in the mag.
Push this up,
and the safety's on.
Remember that, in case
you need to use it someday.
‐ I got it.
Lever up, safety's on.
‐ You have any questions?
‐ Um, why do you want me
to be team leader?
‐ It's a strategy.
During play, I'll be
the one giving the orders.
‐ That backpack's huge.
Wonder what's in there.
["Pilgrim" by Elza Kanzaki
playing]
‐ ♪ Goodbye... ♪
Karen: Dear Elza Kanzaki,
this is my first time
writing a fan letter.
I love all your songs
and think you have
one of the most soothing voices
I have ever heard.
It helps me forget
what a drag my life can be.
I'm unusually tall for a girl.
I've had
sort of a complex about it
ever since I was a little kid.
‐ ♪ Tomorrow
will be yesterday... ♪
‐ I didn't have
many friends growing up.
I'd always picture myself
towering over the other kids
and that made me
keep to myself.
I started playing VR games
as a sort of therapy
for my self‐consciousness.
The thinking was,
if I could be
someone totally different,
maybe that would help me
be more sociable.
After some trial and error,
I finally found a game I liked,
one that let me play
as a short, cute character,
one dressed all in pink,
so super cute.
In case you were wondering,
the game is called
"Gun Gale Online."
It takes place
on a ravaged Earth
where players shoot each other
with all kinds of guns.
It's pretty brutal, but because
of the character I get to be
and listening to your music
while playing, I don't mind.
Hopefully my experiences
in the game
will give me the courage
I lack in real life.
I'm sorry
for the rambling letter,
but if you're
still reading this,
I'd like to ask you
for a favor.
If it's possible,
could you please
hold your next concert
in a larger venue?
I'm sure there were
lots of folks like me
who couldn't get
a ticket for your last one.
Thank you for reading this
and for all
the wonderful songs.
From a huge fan,
Karen Kohiruimaki.
Announcer:
"Gun Gale Online" players,
stand by for an announcement!
We're hosting
a battle royale at 1400.
Get ready for Squad Jam!
‐ You don't know how excited
I am to be sponsoring this.
I hope everyone has a blast,
both literally
and figuratively.
‐ Try your luck,
and guess how many shots
will be fired
during the tournament!
‐ Ready, M? 'Cause I sure am!
‐ Oh, almost forgot.
‐ Pito gave me a message.
‐ What?
She said we'd better
win today, or else.
‐ Yeah, that sounds
like her all right.
‐ I told her I'd do the best
I could, both of us would.
I also told her if you
get killed, I might resign.
Hope you don't mind.
‐ No, that's fine.
‐ Then let's see how far
we get today and have some fun.
‐ Roger that!
Announcer: Okay, Squad Jammers,
it's almost time to start,
but first are all teams present
and ready to teleport?
Players: Yeah!
M: All right. Gear up.
‐ Right.
‐ Don't forget to pack
your Satellite Scan Terminal.
‐ Mm‐hmm.
‐ And pack this, too.
‐ [gasps]
[gasps] Really?
Like, you think I'll need it?
‐ It's good to have
in case you run out of ammo.
‐ But I'm bringing along
a ton of mags.
‐ What if you
get caught in a room?
Sometimes in close quarters,
a knife's better than a gun,
especially for someone like you
with a high level of agility.
Strap it to your lower back,
horizontal.
When you use it, draw it
with your right, backhanded.
Your enemy
will be bigger than you,
but you can dash
between their legs
and slash at their inner thigh.
That's where
the femoral artery is,
and if you hit it,
you'll do a lot of damage.
If the enemy's
drawing down on you,
dash forward, and aim for
the inner part of their bicep.
Then slash upward, like this!
And if you can get behind them,
slash through their boot
into their Achilles tendon.
Once your enemy's down,
draw the blade
across their neck,
and make a long cut.
‐ Where'd he learn all this?
‐ Go for the eyes
when attacking the head.
Make sure to stab
straight and hard,
and you'll damage the brain.
If you wanna score
an instant kill with a knife,
you either go
for the enemy's throat
or their eyes.
‐ Roger that.
‐ All right. Hope you're ready.
‐ Yep, you know it!
‐ Glad you're fired up
about this.
‐ To be honest,
if I got a ticket
to Elza Kanzaki's concert first,
I wouldn't have signed up.
‐ That sucks
you couldn't get a ticket.
‐ It's okay. I'm glad I'm here.
[thinking] Let's do our best
out there, P‐chan.
[buzzer sounds]
‐ Get ready, players!
The Squad Jam's about to start!
Karen: We called ourselves
Team LM
because of our initials.
In a few seconds,
we'd be going into battle.
["To see the future"
by Tomori Kusunoki playing]
[singing in Japanese]
♪ You say good night ♪
♪ To see the future ♪