Narrator: If you
died in a game,
you didn't die in real life.
That was before
"Sword Art Online."
The incident claimed
many lives, and, as a result,
almost ended the development
of all VR games.
But when the admin package
called "the Seed"
became available, guaranteeing
the player's safety,
development not only continued,
it skyrocketed.
One such game became popular,
thanks to its
post‐apocalyptic environments
and player‐versus‐player duels,
where guns are used
instead of swords
and the roar of gunfire
blows across the terrain
like a hellish wind.
It's appropriately called...
Announcer:
"Gun Gale Online" players,
please stand by
for an announcement!
Today, at 1400 hours,
we're hosting Squad Jam,
a battle royale tournament
for teams!
[players cheering]
Announcer: Each team
can have a max of six players,
and there are 23 teams
gunning for first place,
so pick your fave,
and cheer them on to victory!
‐ It's good to see
you're fired up about this.
‐ To be honest,
if I got a ticket
to Elza Kanzaki's concert first,
I wouldn't have signed up.
‐ That sucks
you couldn't get a ticket.
‐ It's okay. I'm glad I'm here.
[thinking] Let's do our best
out there, P‐chan.
Announcer: Get ready!
The Squad Jam's about to start!
[players cheer]
["Ryusei" by Eir Aoi playing]
‐ [singing in Japanese]
♪ ...safety ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ The darkest night ♪
Announcer: Squad Jam is on!
[buzzer sounds]
[whooshing]
[girl sighs]
Whoa. They're starting us
in a big forest.
‐ This isn't good.
‐ Why? Because the trees
block your shots
and my outfit stands out?
‐ Yup. Wear this
'til we get out of here.
‐ Uh...
‐ You can shoot through
the poncho if you want.
‐ I'll get another one.
‐ [device beeps]
Time to get oriented.
‐ Looks like
we're the only ones here.
‐ No enemies
within a klick of us.
We'll skip going north and east.
‐ So where to?
Have a preference?
‐ We should head due south.
That's the urban area.
Try to stay
ten meters behind me.
‐ Roger that. Lead the way.
‐ [on radio] Stop. Get down.
‐ [automatic gunfire]
That's the sound
of a 556 assault rifle.
And that's the sound
of a submachine gun.
‐ You can tell?
‐ Yeah.
Two teams are
after the same position.
They probably
surprised each other.
They're in the forest
to the west of us.
‐ They sound so close.
‐ I got an idea.
LLENN, you take point.
Head in that direction.
I'll let you know
if you go off course.
‐ Sure. Roger that.
[groans] Please don't let me
run into any enemies.
Hey, M,
I can't hear any shooting.
Do you think they
might be headed this way?
‐ Don't stand there
wondering about it.
‐ [groans]
‐ Move.
‐ The enemy could be anywhere,
behind a tree,
waiting to snipe at me.
[yelps]
[groaning]
That does it!
What the heck am I afraid of?!
Even if they kill me,
P‐chan'll tear 'em up first.
[gasps]
M: Stop!
Down.
Stay alert.
Eyes front!
‐ [gasps]
‐ I'm 300 meters behind you.
It's the nine‐minute mark.
When the sat‐scan finishes,
the enemy will only see
your position.
That's why I'm hanging back.
‐ Got it. Only the team leader's
position is revealed.
‐ Hmm. You're catching on.
If we're lucky
and the enemy's close,
they'll attack you
when the scan's done.
‐ But then what do I do?
‐ Start spraying bullets,
fall back, and use
the trees for cover.
I'll circle around to the left
and pick off
whoever's chasing you.
‐ [thinking] Great.
I'm a decoy now? Awesome.
‐ Don't bother
watching the scan.
Just stay alert.
‐ Roger that. [gasps]
Uh, M, I spotted them.
‐ Thirty seconds
'til the scan starts.
Tell me what you see,
and hurry.
‐ [gasps] U‐Um...
they're on the other side
of the highway,
i‐in the city.
They're about 200 meters away.
‐ Calm down.
How many are there?
What kind of guns?
‐ I see five.
I can't tell
what kind of guns they have,
but they're not small.
They're behind a blown‐up wall.
They're just standing around.
Wh‐What do I do?
Should I open fire on 'em,
or what?
‐ You can't hit them
with a P90 from there,
so relax. The scan's up.
‐ [thinking] I can't believe
I have to sit here and wait.
Should I wait,
or should I attack?
‐ Got 'em.
There's one team on the border
between the city
and the highway,
about 200 meters from you.
‐ Should I start falling back?
‐ Not yet.
I doubt they'll attack you
right away from that distance.
‐ [sighs]
[gasps]
[squeals]
[on radio]
M! They're targeting me!
[screams]
They got me pinned down
over here, M!
Help! Do something!
‐ You know what
they're shooting?
General‐purpose machine guns,
7.62 millimeter,
probably MAGs, judging
by the sound of the rapid fire.
There's more than two of them.
If you listen,
you can just make out
the hum of another gun
firing even faster.
Sounds like a 556.
That's a Minimi.
‐ Could you skip the lesson
and help me?!
‐ As long as you're
behind that tree, you're safe,
so stay put.
‐ Oh, my gosh!
[panting]
Damn it!
[automatic gunfire]
‐ It shouldn't
be much longer now.
LLENN: What shouldn't?
What are you talking about?!
‐ Nothing.
Just stay where you are.
‐ We're a rapid‐fire nightmare,
yo! Boo‐yah!
‐ We won't stop firing
'til we run out of bullets!
‐ The Japan Machine Gun Lovers
are here to get it on!
Whoo‐hoo!
‐ Uh...
‐ Yo, we got bogies on ou‐‐
‐ It's a sniper!
[gasps] They're behind‐‐
‐ Take cover!
‐ Oh, crap!
‐ [gasps] The shooting stopped.
M: Another team
snuck up behind them
and started picking them off.
Perfect timing.
I'm heading over to you now,
so don't shoot me.
‐ [sighs] That was too close.
I almost died
without firing a single shot.
[bush rustling]
Hey, M.
‐ You can borrow my scope.
I didn't tell you before, but I
saw that other team on the scan.
They were close enough that I
figured they'd move on 'em.
‐ How come the machine gunners
didn't notice them?
‐ Don't know. Maybe when
they checked the scan,
they didn't realize
they were as close as they were.
Or maybe they saw how close you
were and didn't check their six.
Either way,
those guys were sloppy.
‐ Wait! This whole time,
you were using me as a decoy
to get
the machine gunners killed?!
‐ Yup.
‐ Glad I could help out.
‐ Let's watch the action
from here.
There were five machine gunners.
Three are dead. That leaves two.
‐ They're totally distracted
by the sniper team.
Wanna take 'em out?
‐ No way.
We're gonna sit here
nice and quiet for now.
‐ [groans]
‐ Movement to the left of them
on the wide street.
Behind that torn‐up bus.
You see how they're advancing?
Nice and tactical.
‐ Just the four?
‐ No, that's not the whole team.
‐ How do you know?
‐ Where are the others?
You see 'em?
‐ No, but they're out there.
Those four are taking
the shortest route
to the machine gunners.
They're using cover and moving
like they know
where they're going.
That means there's probably
two snipers up in a building
telling them which way to go.
They're the ones that took out
the machine gunners.
Wherever they are,
they had nice, clean shots.
‐ I don't see 'em.
‐ That's the point.
A sniper that reveals
their position
by letting their barrel hang out
in the open's a dead sniper.
I gotta hand it to 'em,
splitting up a team of six
the way they're doing's
a heck of a strategy.
Whoever they are,
they definitely know
what they're doing.
Those two are goners for sure.
‐ Huh?
‐ Eh?
‐ Run!
‐ [yelps]
‐ They're out in the open now.
You gonna shoot 'em, or what?
‐ Hell, no.
I could take one of 'em out,
but the others would scatter
by the time I reset.
Better to let 'em go.
Besides, they won't
bother with us.
They probably think
we retreated into the forest.
‐ They're on the move now!
‐ Got snipers.
‐ Where?
‐ The building with the arch,
coming down the side.
‐ What the heck? No way.
‐ They're rappelling. Way faster
than taking the stairs.
I didn't know you could get
a skill like that here.
I want it.
‐ That's not
just the "GGO" skill.
Trust me. I have it.
The version
you can get in‐game
doesn't let you descend as fast
as those guys are doing it.
‐ Then how?
‐ Like I said,
they didn't pick up
moves like that in here.
Those guys know
how to rappel for real,
and they're good at it.
‐ Who are they?
Mountain climbers, maybe?
‐ Not the way they handle guns.
‐ If you know what they do
in the real world,
why don't you just come
right out and tell me already?
‐ It's a guess, but seeing
how they move as a unit,
have tactical skills,
and rappel as fast as they do,
I have a feeling they all
have serious combat training.
‐ For real?
‐ Those guys are pros.
Handling weapons
is part of their job.
They might be cops or soldiers,
maybe even special forces.
Take your pick.
‐ [gasping]
What?! Isn't that the same
as cheating, then?!
They can't play if they're
professional soldiers!
‐ Last time I checked the rules,
they didn't say they couldn't.
‐ [groans]
‐ "GGO" is perfect
for folks like them.
They can play it to train,
and now with Squad Jam,
they can test their skills
against others.
‐ So now what?
If we don't take them out,
we can't get in the city,
and we're stuck.
Can't we just charge in,
guns blazing?
‐ Nope.
‐ Can't we at least try it?!
Fine. Have it your way.
Okay, now what do we do?
‐ You consider yourself lucky?
‐ Excuse me?
‐ Up to this point,
would you say your life's
been blessed with good luck?
‐ Hmm, never thought about it.
You know, yeah!
My life has been lucky.
I'm a lucky girl.
[thinking]
I think.
‐ Good enough.
We're gonna bet
on that luck of yours.
We'll wait here
'til the next scan.
If luck's on our side,
we'll make our move.
‐ What are you thinking?
‐ I'm betting
the machine gunners
made so much noise it attracts
the other teams to the area.
While the pro team's
dealing with them,
we'll hop onto the highway and
make a beeline to the end of it.
Then, we'll head
into the residential area
and hide there
'til the next scan.
‐ Sounds like a plan.
‐ If there's another team
within three klicks of us,
there's a chance
we'll run into them.
‐ Seven teams gone.
That leaves 16 in play.
[gasps] See that?
There's three teams closing
on the pros and one straggler.
‐ Guess you were right
about your luck. Good for us.
Bad for those
other teams, though.
‐ Well?
‐ Looks good.
We'll wait
'til the fireworks start
and then get
the hell out of here.
‐ [giggles]
[insects chirping]
‐ [automatic gunfire]
‐ [gasps]
They found each other.
‐ Time to move! Go! Go!
‐ Is it okay I'm leaving you
behind like this?
‐ [on radio] If I need you
to stop, I'll tell you.
‐ [thinking] Wait. Is he
using me as a decoy again?
I'm supposed to be
the team leader,
and he's treating me
like a grunt.
[shuffling]
‐ [grunting]
I can't believe
I made it out alive.
Yo, dudes!
Anyone still alive out there?
Man: Yeah! I'm still here.
‐ Where?! Come on out!
Where you at? Let's get
the hell out of here already!
‐ I think there's been
some confusion.
I'm on the other team, dude.
That was too easy.
What a jackass.
Should've checked his team stat
before calling out.
Ah, looks like I'm
the only one left on‐‐
‐ Like shooting fish
in a barrel.
‐ Hanging back and letting
these bozos off each other
is the only way to play!
‐ Best part about battle royales
is killing fools like him.
‐ Aw, man!
‐ Damn.
‐ [radio]
Bravo, Charlie, this is Delta.
Kitchen's clean.
‐ Roger that, Delta.
We'll check
the next scan from here.
Stand by, and stay sharp. Over.
‐ Yo, Chief, what do you want me
to do about that pink chick
and Bigfoot hauling ass
down the highway. Take 'em?
LLENN: Man, what a run!
‐ Surprised we
didn't see anyone.
‐ Or get shot.
‐ Yeah.
‐ When's the next scan?
‐ It's coming up. Get ready.
‐ Eight teams were killed
in the desert this time.
‐ Probably fighting
for the central ruins there.
It's a prime spot.
‐ Amazing.
‐ You talking about
the pro team's skill?
‐ And your predictions.
‐ Here we go. We're next.
‐ No one.
Thank goodness.
‐ And that does it for the scan.
It looks like 15 teams
have been killed off so far.
That leaves eight, including us.
Luck's definitely
on our side today.
‐ Which of the other teams do
you think's gonna come after us?
‐ There's two in the forest
that are close,
but we can ignore them.
Looks like they're having
a bit of a standoff.
‐ If each one's waiting
for the other to make a move,
they'll be there a long time.
‐ I have a feeling this team'll
sneak up on them from behind.
That'll shake things up.
The team at the spaceship
in the marsh
has the upper hand,
tactically speaking.
If they're smart,
they'll stay put.
‐ Hmm.
‐ As for the team in the desert
and the one in the prairie,
I don't know what
their next move's gonna be,
especially the one
near the ruins.
It's weird
they haven't entered them.
It's a good place to dig in.
‐ Mm‐hmm. I was just thinking
the same thing.
‐ Let's not worry about them
'til the next scan.
We got bigger fish to fry
right here.
‐ Yeah you're right,
the pro team.
‐ If they're not in this to win,
but for combat experience,
they won't wait
for others to come to them.
They'll go after
the closest team, us.
‐ Well, now what're we gonna do?
We can't beat pro soldiers.
‐ Well, if we play
our cards right,
there's a good chance we can.
‐ Really?!
‐ Your size, speed and agility
might give us the advantage,
if you're up for it.
‐ [laughs] Sure!
I'm up for anything!
Come on!
Tell me the plan already!
‐ All right.
You got it.
‐ If we're gonna beat
the next scan,
we need to hustle.
New orders, people.
We got ten minutes
to get our asses
to the residential district.
[radio] Spotted a team of two
on the highway headed there,
a pink munchkin
and some big guy,
types of weapons unknown.
Scan in 40.
Everybody hold.
Stay alert.
[timer beeping]
Scan starting.
Huh.
Damn. They're close,
due north, 80 meters!
‐ I don't see anyone.
‐ I got nothing
on my end, either.
‐ Same here. No vehicles
in the intersection.
‐ Move up.
Team: Roger that.
‐ Scan doesn't show elevation.
They could be hiding
down a manhole in front of you.
Watch your six.
‐ We're there.
I'm looking, Chief.
I don't see any manholes.
‐ Facing northwest on my end.
No manholes here.
Zero movement, sir.
Clear to the northeast.
No enemies,
no manholes, nothing.
‐ I'm clear to the north,
too, Chief.
There's no enemies in sight.
Yo, Chief,
these scans ever make mistakes?
‐ That's a negative.
The scans are always solid.
Call out everything you guys
see in the intersection.
‐ Some cracks in the road,
a rusty bike on the ground.
‐ I see a civvy car tire
lying on its side,
two broken branches
in the street,
a dirty suitcase, an empty can.
Scratch that. Three cans.
‐ I got a shopping cart
over here, nothing in it.
No holes in the ground.
‐ There's nothing out here
but us, Chief.
‐ [groans]
Son of a‐‐
The suitcase! Light it up!
M: Forty‐five degrees right,
Seven meters ahead.
‐ [yells]
M: If you take someone down,
use their corpse for a shield.
In Squad Jam, a dead body
becomes an "Immortal Object,"
so you can use it for cover
under fire.
‐ Crap! She's so small!
‐ Little runt!
[gasps, growls]
[gasps] Aw, come on!
‐ We're done. No need to engage.
‐ It's probably for the better.
‐ That's not real‐world speed.
It's the game.
It's no good to us.
Eh, training's over for today.
Pulling the plug.
‐ Awesome!
‐ Talk about fast.
‐ She took out all those pros.
‐ No wonder she's so famous.
‐ I still can't believe
she did it.
‐ And we know who LLENN is
in real life.
You rock, Karen!
‐ [chuckles] Come on, guys.
You're embarrassing me.
["To see the future"
by Tomori Kusunoki playing]
‐ [singing in Japanese]
♪ You say good night ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ To see the future ♪