‐ [squeals]
‐ [chuckles]
‐ [thinking] No more doubts.
I got this.
Watch out, Pito. I'm coming.
[buzzer sounds]
Announcer: Squad Jam 2 is on!
[whoosh]
‐ Suburbs.
‐ Hey, LLENN,
look at that big old wall.
‐ Eh?
It must be the boundary.
‐ Oh, right.
No one's getting over that,
well, not unless
they're 100 feet tall, anyway.
‐ I wonder if it goes
all the way around the map.
‐ Let's see. Where are we?
Oh! There we are,
way up in the corner.
Look. Railroad tracks.
That's right.
You can use vehicles here.
Let's fire up the train
and take it somewhere.
‐ Where do you wanna take it?
‐ I don't know.
The city, I guess.
Yeah, and go shop for clothes.
‐ We'll go shopping
after I kill Pito.
‐ Roger that.
‐ So we're here.
‐ Yup, so now what?
Which way do you wanna go?
‐ That hilly area
looks dangerous.
It's perfect for snipers
'cause of all
the vantage points it has.
We should stay clear of it.
‐ Yes, ma'am!
‐ Uh...
‐ What's the big round thing?
A baseball stadium?
‐ Are they as big as that?
‐ Since "GGO" takes place in
the future, maybe they will be.
‐ Oh, look.
Some kind of building.
It could either be a factory
or a school. I don't know.
And right below that,
there's a rocky mountain range.
Well? Did you memorize
the terrain?
‐ Wait! I have
to remember all that?!
I didn't have to memorize maps
back in "ALO."
If I wanted to go anywhere,
I flew.
I don't wanna get lost.
‐ No, no worries.
‐ Huh?
‐ I think I got it all.
‐ Really?
‐ You can look at the map
anytime during the game,
but we'll be going fast,
so try to keep track
of where you are
as best you can.
If we get separated,
call and stay put.
‐ Uh...
roger that.
‐ [thinking]
It's been four minutes.
We'll wait here
until the first scan happens.
I want to make sure
there are no enemies nearby.
Once we know it's clear,
we'll head out,
avoid the other teams
as much as possible,
and make our way to Pito.
And as soon as I find her,
I'll kill her.
["Ryusei" by Eir Aoi playing]
‐ [singing in Japanese]
♪ ...safety ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ The darkest night ♪
LLENN: It's clear where I'm at.
‐ [radio] Same. God, I'm bored.
‐ Scan's coming up, so check
your Terminal for enemies.
If they're close,
get ready to run.
‐ You got it.
I'll tap some of the dots, too,
and I'll let you know
if I find your friend.
Leave it to me.
[Terminal beeping]
‐ No enemies on this block,
thank God.
Pito could be any of these dots.
I wonder which one.
[gasps] Don't tell me.
‐ Well, that sucks.
LLENN and her partner
are the farthest away.
Boss: LLENN got dropped
on the northwest edge,
eight klicks north of us.
‐ What should we do?
‐ [sighs]
We'll hit the closest team to us
and make our way up to her.
[wind blowing]
‐ They stuck the favorites
in opposite corners.
‐ That's such B. S.
Of all the teams, why'd they
drop hers the farthest away?
[wails]
‐ [deeper voice] Young lady,
life doesn't always work out
the way you want it to.
All you can do is rise
to the challenge and carry on,
just like you've been doing.
Or was that just luck?
‐ Okay, okay.
You made your point.
We're gonna head
for the southeast,
and if anyone gets in our way,
we're gonna crush 'em.
[running footsteps]
I'm clear on this end.
‐ [radio] Heading over.
‐ Come on, come on.
Where are they?
They gotta be
around here somewhere.
[thinking] There.
I'll circle around
and hit them from behind.
‐ Got it.
‐ Distract 'em for me.
‐ This is gonna be great.
Those fools won't know
what hit 'em.
The Ambush Fairy and
Grenade Fairy are gonna
blast 'em to kingdom‐‐Uh‐oh.
‐ Fuka!
‐ [wails] I blew it!
[scraping]
[sobs] I'm sorry!
‐ No, I'm sorry.
I forgot to tell you to
watch out for traps out there.
Man: No bodies. Nothing.
Man #2: Where'd they go?
‐ [thinking]
It's going to take two minutes
before her legs grow back.
Man #3: ...couldn't
have gotten far.
‐ Leave me. Get out of here
before they find you.
‐ I'll go when you're dead.
‐ Dang, you're cold.
‐ Stay clear of the window.
Get down as low as you can.
I'm the champion
of SJ, remember?
I can handle these guys.
‐ That's one.
Two.
There's three.
[man panting]
[shrieks]
‐ [thinking] Two more to go.
[gasps]
[launcher pops]
Nice shot, Fuka.
‐ You know me.
I'm the kind of girl
who loves payback,
the more brutal, the better.
‐ [crowd cheering]
‐ Holy crap!
No wonder
that team's top‐ranked!
‐ She hit him right in the face
with a friggin' grenade!
I think I'm in love.
‐ That knife to the nuts
was a little overboard, though.
‐ Agreed.
‐ That was amazing, wasn't it?
Yes, sirree, that's what you get
when you go head‐to‐head
against my LLENN.
‐ She is rad, but just so we're
clear here, she ain't yours.
‐ Aw, yeah!
Bullets for days, yo!
God damn, I love my machine gun.
Lax: Six bodies confirmed.
They're out.
Man: No other enemies
in the area.
‐ Roger that.
We'll wait for the next scan.
If it's clear,
let's get off this mountain.
Reload, and stay sharp.
No one moves
'til I give the word.
[automatic weapons firing]
Boss: We got this! Keep on
pounding 'em! Don't let up!
Eat lead, you bastards!
‐ They got three of ours.
Fall back, and regroup!
Big ugly one's sniping at us.
[yelps]
‐ [chuckles]
Should have ducked.
Man: What the hell?
I can't see it.
There's no Bullet Line.
How the hell
am I supposed to know
which direct‐‐
‐ Yeah I did it! I got him!
‐ You got the hang of it now.
‐ Shirley, why didn't you
take a shot? You missed out.
‐ No, that's okay.
Maybe next time.
Pito: This is so boring.
What are we doing, M?
We can't just stay here
picking our butts
while everyone
blasts away down there.
Come on. Let's get off
this mountain already.
‐ Not yet.
‐ Why's that?
No, wait. Let me guess.
It's 'cause you don't
wanna fight, isn't it?
Yeah, you just wanna
chicken out like last time.
‐ I have a plan.
‐ [sighs]
What do you guys wanna do?
‐ Contract says
we follow orders.
The leader says stay, we stay.
‐ Ecch. You party‐poopers.
‐ We don't need to engage
in random battles.
There's a chance
you might get picked off.
Do you wanna die like that?
‐ No. But I don't wanna die
of boredom, either.
[grunts] I'm getting antsy.
‐ I know, but be patient.
Like I said before,
I do have a plan, okay?
You wanted me
to be the leader here,
so follow my lead.
‐ All right, "sir."
Whatever you say.
But the second you die,
I'm going on a killing spree.
‐ Have fun with that.
You'll be taking on the most
vicious player by yourself.
‐ And who might that be?
‐ You know who.
Your friend, LLENN.
That pink bunny's fangs
are sharper now,
and she's hungry
for your blood.
‐ [laughs]
[whoosh]
[Fuka yelling]
[laughs]
Yes! My legs grew back!
Thank God!
My HP's topped off, too,
thanks to my handy‐dandy medkit.
Whoo‐hoo! Welcome back, legs!
♪ I got my legs back,
I got my legs back ♪
I won't screw up
like that again! No, sir!
I'm gonna watch
my step from now on!
Hear that, boys? I'm back,
so set all
the tripwires you want.
I'll just hop right over 'em.
‐ Yeah, well, be careful
where you're hopping,
'cause tripwires
can be at waist level
and head height, too.
There are even traps
that you're supposed to find,
just to make you step
into another one nearby.
‐ A trap for a trap, huh?
That's like
beyond playing dirty.
‐ That's how you survive "GGO."
You'll get used to it,
eventually. I got used to it,
and now I'm checking doorways
for wires in real life, too.
‐ My best friend's
turned into a commando,
and I couldn't be happier.
‐ Get ready.
The scan's about to start.
‐ Ready.
‐ Here we go.
‐ There's PM4.
‐ I'm glad they're still alive,
but it doesn't look
like they moved.
‐ All right, what's the plan?
‐ Let's go after the team
at the train station,
right there.
It's the middle of town,
so we can find
a good vantage point.
They're on the tracks
between platforms.
Good cover for them,
since the platforms
are concrete and bulletproof.
It's like a little fortress.
‐ They're just gonna
sit there and wait?
Those chickens.
I know.
Let's run 'em over with a train.
‐ We don't know
how to drive one.
Look, we'll sneak up
using the houses for cover.
‐ I was thinking. I still
feel bad about the last team,
so to make up for it,
how 'bout you let me
deal with these guys?
‐ I don't know.
Do you have a plan or something?
‐ Yeah. This time,
I'll do the shooting,
and you do the relaxing.
[laughs]
Boss: Ten minutes
'til the next scan,
and not one team's in range.
Not one. Damn!
[groans]
[echoing]
You assholes!
Doesn't anyone have
the balls to face us?!
[echo] ...to face us?!
...to face us?!
...to face us?
‐ What a potty mouth.
I never heard you
swear like that before.
‐ So what? It's a game.
I'm not hurting anyone.
It is called role‐playing,
after all.
‐ Actually, if you
get used to swearing here,
there's a chance you'll do it
in the real world, too.
I'd be embarrassed
if you did that on the subway.
‐ [gasps]
Yeah, you're right.
‐ I know.
Sophie: You could still
taunt the others.
Just try to be
more elegant about it.
‐ Okay.
[clears throat]
[echoing] You cowards!
Does no one have
the testicles to face us?!
[echo] ...to face us?!
...to face us?!
...to face us? ...to face us?
[wind blowing]
‐ SHINC and PM4's
a ways away.
LF's even farther out.
That settles it.
We're heading west.
[Pito groans] This sucks.
I wish she'd come
and kill me already.
[groans]
Hurry up, LLENN.
‐ Good. It's clear.
‐ All right. I am so ready.
Which way do I point?
‐ Um...
that way,
about 300 meters, give or take.
‐ [chuckles]
This is gonna be hot.
Let's do this.
Okay, LLENN, get to it.
‐ Yup. See ya.
Talk to you in a bit.
[launcher pops]
‐ What was that?
‐ Sounded like someone farted.
Holy crap, that was a grenade!
‐ Would you chill?
That wasn't even close.
They're just firing
in this direction, is all.
[team gasps]
Close. Aim five meters
to the north of that last shot.
‐ Roger that.
[launcher pops]
‐ Two down.
‐ I'll launch grenades at 'em
from a safe distance.
They won't see me,
'cause of the houses,
but I won't see them, either.
That's where you come in.
Find someplace high,
and spot for me.
Every time I shoot,
tell me how far off I was,
and I'll adjust my aim.
‐ Okay, but can you
hit 'em like that?
‐ Hah! Can I hit 'em?
Do you know how many hours
I spent practicing?
‐ I don't know.
‐ A lot.
Look, who says you
have to fight eye to eye?
These kind of weapons
are all about getting 'em
when they least expect it.
I practiced
by setting up targets,
measuring distances,
and shooting by feel.
I got pretty darn good
at it, too.
Just give me a distance,
and I can hit anything
with my eyes closed.
All I need is a person
giving me accurate info.
‐ Get down.
I'll do it,
but you'll be a sitting duck,
and if someone spots you,
you're dead.
‐ I was pretty much dead
a little while ago,
but I bounced right back
like a zombie.
‐ I see one guy 18 meters up
from your last shot.
‐ 18 up.
[explosions]
‐ Got him.
Two are up and running
along the track,
five meters down from the last.
‐ Oh, those guys are toast.
LLENN: They're out.
One more to go.
He's over the platform,
heading due east.
He's fast, so if you
can't hit him, no worries.
‐ Huh! I'll waste him
with a six‐pack attack!
Here I go.
‐ Yes, Fuka!
You got him! You got 'em all!
You're a genius with
those guns! That was amazing.
That was beautiful!
Yeah, I know!
Hmm. See what
a little grinding can do?
‐ Let's get to the station
for the next scan.
Check your map.
We'll head for the dome next.
[crowd cheering]
‐ She took out that whole team
with just her grenades.
‐ She's a beast
with those hand cannons.
‐ You see that?
There's not a team out there
that can match
the little blonde and my LLENN.
Both: Dude, she ain't yours!
‐ [Terminal beeping]
‐ [thinking] Don't be dead!
Yes.
Huh? Oh, my gosh.
‐ What are those seven teams
all doing there?
I mean, they can't
not see each other.
What do you think they're up to?
‐ Something bad.
‐ [chuckles]
Pito, check this out.
You'll love it.
[running footsteps]
Fuka: Are you gonna tell me
‐ what's going on?
‐ Those teams near Pito,
that's what.
They're working together now.
‐ Huh? Why would they do that?
‐ There's only one reason
I can think of!
I bet someone called
for a cease‐fire.
Whoever it is must be
a good negotiator,
'cause they convinced
all those teams to join forces.
Now they're in command
of an army of dozens of people,
and I bet you anything
they're on their way
to attack M and Pito.
‐ Ohh! Yeah,
that's pretty clever!
Anna: That is so lame.
I mean, really?
Boss: They're a pathetic bunch.
That's for sure.
Roza: Do they actually think
throwing bodies at that team
will help 'em?
Boss: You never know.
There's strength in numbers,
and right now,
they have the numbers.
Sure, M's an amazing player,
and he does have that shield,
but if he gets surrounded,
it's not gonna do him any good.
Maybe he'll survive.
We won't know
'til the shooting stops.
David: Well, that's some
kind of strategy.
I'm a little disappointed
they didn't ask us
to join them, though.
‐ Wait. You'd be cool trooping
with those goons? Seriously?
‐ Not even. We'd play along
until the time was right
and then slaughter everyone.
It's a battle royale, after all,
and there's no such thing
as allies here.
‐ They all teamed up.
That sucks. Why didn't they
ask us to join 'em?
‐ So what's the plan now?
‐ I wanna see what happens
to those saps they're after.
We'll stay out of sight until
they're done killing each other.
‐ [running footsteps]
‐ [panting]
[thinking] Seven teams,
that's 42 people max.
Pito's in some real trouble.
What do I do?
What do I do? What do I do?
[yelps]
[grunting]
‐ Would you calm down?
You wanna break your neck
and kill yourself
out of the tourney?
‐ [groans]
‐ Freaking out
won't help anyone.
‐ I know! But no matter
how good Pito and M are,
they're way outnumbered.
‐ Okay, what's the chance
of you getting there
if you ran like crazy?
‐ Even if I ran full speed,
I wouldn't make it in time.
‐ If they're as sharp
as you say,
I bet you they'll bail
once they see
it's a no‐win situation.
They'll be fine. You'll see.
‐ [groans] I sure
hope you're right.
Pito, you better not die yet.
I'm supposed to kill you.
[Pito laughing wildly]
[laughing continues]
Oh, they're so clever!
[laughs]
This is the best thing ever.
‐ Man: Uh, shouldn't we retreat?
‐ Huh?
‐ There's a hell
of a lot more of those guys
than there are of us.
I mean, the odds
ain't in our favor.
What should we do?
‐ Are you kidding me?
That's obvious.
We'll set up an ambush and
wipe out every last one of 'em.
[laughing]
[laughter echoing]
["To see the future"
by Tomori Kusunoki playing]
[singing in Japanese]
♪ You say good night ♪
♪ To see the future ♪