Fuka: Are you gonna tell me
what's going on?
‐ Those teams near Pito,
that's what.
They're working together now.
‐ Huh? Why would they do that?
‐ There's only one reason
I can think of.
I bet someone called
for a cease‐fire.
Whoever it is must be
a good negotiator,
'cause they convinced
all those teams to join forces.
Now they're in command
of an army of dozens of people,
and I bet you anything
they're on their way
to attack M and Pito.
Pito, you better not die yet.
I'm supposed to kill you.
‐ [crowd murmuring]
‐ This is no good.
‐ Twenty‐nine against six.
‐ I know. But, hey, at least
this battle won't be boring.
‐ I bet the princess
is crapping her black cat‐suit
right about now.
‐ True that. That chick's
a liability if I ever saw one.
‐ Women! Every time
there's a fight,
you can count on them going,
"Eee! Get me out of here!
This is too scary!" They can
be such a drag, am I right?
[Pito laughs]
They're so clever. [laughs]
Some genius got seven teams
together to gang up on us.
This is the best thing ever.
Man: There's a hell
of a lot more of them
than there are of us.
The odds ain't in our favor.
What are we gonna do?
‐ Simple. We're gonna
set up an ambush
and wipe out
every last one of 'em.
‐ You're kidding.
‐ Nope. Talk to M.
He'll explain exactly
how to set this massacre up.
["Ryusei" by Eir Aoi playing]
‐ [singing in Japanese]
♪ ...safety ♪
[singing in Japanese]
♪ The darkest night ♪
‐ They're in range,
150 to 200 hundred meters.
‐ It's go time.
All teams, converge.
‐ Are they sure this is it?
‐ B Team, you guys see anything?
‐ No. No movement.
‐ They might have bailed.
‐ Wait. See that?
‐ [scoffs] They think
they're safe in there.
‐ All teams,
we have reason to believe
target's behind the falls.
Make things hot in there
for 'em. Fire at will!
‐ Fire!
[Pito laughs]
Now that is what I call
a hail of bullets.
So how you doing in there?
‐ I got shot.
Pito: Are you gonna die?!
‐ I'm sorry to say this, but no.
Pito: Darn it! And I was
all set to go avenge you.
‐ Thanks. Anyway, the others
are in place and standing by.
When I give the sign,
do what you do.
Pito: You don't
have to tell me twice.
Let's get this show
on the road.
‐ Uh‐huh.
‐ ♪ The world gets infected
with a disease ♪
♪ Sick, makes me forget
how to breathe ♪
♪ Bleed it out,
bleed it out... ♪
‐ [screaming]
‐ They're alive!
Open fire! Go! Go!
‐ ["Disorder"
by Elza Kanzaki continues]
Pito: I'm moving in.
I won't be needing backup.
‐ Roger that.
‐ ♪ We're all faceless
and anonymous... ♪
‐ Holy crap!
‐ [chuckles]
‐ [crack]
‐ [laughs]
‐ What'd she do that for?
‐ Hi!
‐ [groans] Ow.
[groans]
‐ Huh?
‐ [both scream]
[Pito laughs]
‐ ♪ In disorder ♪
[singing in Japanese]
‐ Jesus! She killed 'em all.
What in the goddamn hell is she?
‐ ♪ No need ruler ♪
[singing in Japanese]
Man: Thought your shield
was bulletproof.
‐ Couple slugs bounced
off the rocks and hit me.
Long as it's not my head,
I'm good.
Man: I told you this was gonna
be dangerous. No one listens.
‐ Where's Pito?
Man #2: She's down there
fartin' around
with the last two guys.
‐ [grumbles]
‐ ♪ Raise your flag ♪
‐ [singing in Japanese]
‐ ♪ White or black... ♪
‐ Get it over with already.
‐ I'd like to.
He still has his gun, though,
so I'm just standing here,
waiting for him to draw it.
It's not right to shoot
a defenseless person.
I couldn't live with myself
if I did.
‐ But you don't have a problem
watching that poor guy suffer.
We don't have time for this.
Do him already.
‐ Fine, whatever. There.
‐ Gah! [grunting]
‐ Uh‐oh. He's still holding on.
‐ [grunts]
‐ Oh, my God,
would you let go already?
‐ Is this fun for you,
torturing another player?
Psycho!
‐ Is it fun being on a team
of thirty ganging up on six?
Hell, yes! It's hard
to pick which is more fun,
and I know
that if we switched places,
you'd do the same to me, buddy.
‐ Let go! This is
the one chance you got, man!
Drop me, and kill that bitch!
‐ No way.
Until these guys are dead,
we're in this thing together.
Besides, our leaders
are listening in,
and I bet they're
on their way to save us.
‐ Let me go.
‐ Right. Back to it.
Why won't you die?
[sighs] This is why
I hate using pistols.
And now I'm out of ammo. Hmph.
‐ You had a solid strategy.
You fought well,
but you have to face reality.
Even if your leaders come,
they don't stand
a chance against us.
‐ [growls]
M: Tell 'em this.
Resign now, or else.
‐ No, you idiot!
Where's the fun in that?!
New idea.
Tell your leaders this instead.
"We totally got our asses
kicked by those guys.
They were so tough,
but you're tougher,
so please come on up,
and avenge us." Hee hee.
‐ Can you do that?
‐ Uh‐huh.
And when they find you,
they're gonna butcher you all.
‐ You're all gonna pay for this!
‐ Look at your faces.
That's the kind of hate
I've been waiting for.
Later, boys.
[both stammer]
‐ You're all bastards!
‐ Rot in hell!
[Pito chuckles]
Seemed like those two
got to be good friends
at the end there.
In ten minutes, they'll be
buying drinks for each other.
How cool is that?
‐ God damn it! What the hell
happened up there?!
‐ Every last one of 'em's dead.
‐ I'll make 'em pay
for what they did to‐‐
‐ [screams]
‐ [leaders gasp]
Pito: One more to go, and‐‐
No. Wait. [groans]
Bummer.
I really wanted to kill him.
‐ Damn, dude.
How many did she kill?
‐ I stopped counting
when she got to 20.
‐ She went full‐on berserk.
She even used her hands, man.
‐ I know that gun.
It's an M107A1. There's, like,
only supposed to be one
of those on the Japanese server.
‐ Anti‐materiel rifles like that
are popping up more and more.
In the last B. o. B., this girl
named Sinon had a Hecate Two,
and she kicked all the ass.
‐ Picking those dudes off
was easy with that rifle,
even at her distance.
Man: I wonder what other
surprises she's got.
‐ Now we know
one thing for sure.
That team's gonna
destroy everyone and win.
M's got that shield,
and those tactical‐looking mofos
are nothing
to sneeze at, either,
but with that woman, too,
they're unstoppable.
The other teams are dead.
They just don't know it ye‐‐
‐ Who cares about them?!
check out how LLENN's doing!
Don't count her out just yet.
As long as she's alive,
there's still
a chance she can win.
LLENN: Okay, Fuka,
I'm at 100 meters.
No enemies in sight.
‐ [radio] Roger that.
Light the way,
and I'll catch up to you.
‐ Here you go.
‐ There's your Bullet Line.
Heading over to you now.
[spits] Whose idea was it
to stick a grassy field
in this dome?
[groans]
I'm like a Hokkaido cockroach
scuttling across
the kitchen floor,
if Hokkaido had roaches.
Well, Mom?
Are we there yet, or what?
‐ We're about halfway now.
‐ [groans]
That's as far as we got?
‐ Sorry. We're going
as fast as we can
using the Bullet Line trick.
Besides, it's safer in here.
If we'd gone
around the north side,
we would have bumped into MMTM,
and South,
it would have been SHINC.
Going through the dome is
the fastest way to get to Pito
and the safest.
‐ So what about the three teams
in here with us?
‐ Yeah, them. I guess
this is where we find out
how lucky I am or not.
Are you sure your wings
didn't transfer over
from the other game?
I could hang underneath you
and shoot while you fly.
‐ Nope, sorry.
I gave up all my fairy skills
to come help you out here.
[automatic gunfire]
‐ Hmm.
That's ahead and to the left,
mm, about 200 meters from us.
I don't see Bullet Lines,
though.
‐ Then they're fighting
each other.
That could
totally work out for us.
Keep up the good work, guys.
Wipe each other out.
‐ No. It's weird, real weird.
Something's not right
about the way they're shooting.
‐ Like what?
‐ Like this is a trap.
You see those three teams?
I bet you anything
they're working together,
just like the ones
going after Pito.
They must have seen us
on the last scan
and figured we'd
cut through the dome.
‐ Ooh, you're so popular!
This is getting exciting.
So how do you know
it's a trap?
‐ You saw where the three
team leaders were on the map,
so it's kinda weird
all that gunfire
is coming from the same
direction and distance.
The only explanation
is they're all shooting
from the same position.
‐ Wow, you sure have sharp ears.
So what do you wanna do?
Sneak up from behind and
blast 'em back to the saloon?
‐ No. I don't want to waste
my ammo on these guys.
If we keep moving
and be careful,
we can avoid them.
‐ Roger‐dodger.
Lead the way, girl.
‐ I'm gonna take
a little detour to the right.
Could you please give me a Line?
‐ Okay! I'll aim
another 100 meters ahead.
[insects chirping]
‐ [gasps]
Fuka, enemy sighted, 70 meters.
‐ There she is!
[launcher pops]
‐ [gunfire continues]
‐ You okay, LLENN?
‐ Yeah, but they know
where I'm at!
Your shot saved me,
but I used a whole mag
taking four of 'em down.
I only have 700 bullets left.
‐ Uh, how can I help?
‐ Come to me.
‐ Coming!
Eh?
‐ [gunfire]
‐ [screams]
They're shooting at me!
‐ Come on! Hurry!
‐ I can't! I can't!
If I get up to run,
they'll blow my head off!
There's Lines all over,
and bullets are whizzing by!
‐ Fuka.
‐ I'm a goner.
Get out while you can. Survive.
‐ Fuka, we'll do that plan
we were saving.
‐ Okay! I'm ready!
‐ [grunts] Let her rip,
twelve o'clock!
‐ What the‐‐Hold your fire!
You might hit
one of ours by mistake.
‐ Yo, why is the smoke pink?
‐ It's her, the Pink‐‐
‐ Did you see where that came‐‐
‐ Keep your head down, Fuka.
I can barely see
what I'm shooting at.
‐ I'm low, so fire away.
‐ [thinking]
I was saving this plan
‐ for when I got to Pito.
‐ [gunfire]
I hate to have to waste it
on these morons.
I'm gonna kill
every last one of you!
‐ More smoke, comin' up!
Man: That pink girl's
in the smoke with us!
I'm hit.
[smoke grenade booms]
Don't shoot if you can't‐‐
‐ Tell your friends,
"I killed the pink girl.
It's all good. Stop shooting."
Tell 'em yourself, you little‐‐
[crowd groans, laughs]
‐ Another one down!
Spectator: Damn!
‐ My God. How does LLENN
know where they are?
‐ She follows
their Bullet Lines.
Even in all that smoke,
they're visible.
‐ [thinking]
I'm wasting too much ammo.
Fuka: LLENN! I only
got six cans left!
‐ No worries.
There's only two or three
of these guys left, anyway.
I'll holler
if I need some help.
Fuka: Gotcha.
Rest in peace, losers.
LLENN: Dang it,
I used 200 rounds so far!
I can't keep‐‐There you are.
Suck on this!
[gunfire]
‐ Oh, boy.
Note to self,
never piss Kohi off IRL.
‐ [grunts]
‐ [gasps]
‐ [laughs]
[both yelp]
‐ Heh! You want some of this?
‐ Wait. Don't shoot!
‐ [laughs] Say your prayers,
you scumbag!
Heh! Boo‐yah.
[insects chirping]
‐ You missed.
‐ What the‐‐
How could I miss you
when I'm standing this close?
‐ I think I know.
Young lady, you never
shot one of those before.
‐ [growls]
‐ [laughs]
You know how in SJ,
after a player gets killed,
their corpse
stays on the field
as an Immortal Object
for ten minutes?
That means, after I kill you,
I can grope your avatar,
and I won't get flagged
for harassment.
‐ You lousy, rotten, sleazy,
perverted bald‐ass creep!
I smite thee
in the name of all women!
[yells]
‐ [groans]
‐ Don't mess with a fairy
swinging a broadsword!
You'll regret it.
[crowd gasping]
‐ Damn straight.
Every fantasy VR gamer I know
is a bad‐ass.
‐ Sh‐She beat him to death.
‐ Dear God.
LLENN: 15, 16, 17.
‐ Huh. Not a bad body count.
‐ There were three teams,
so there should be
18 bodies total.
Wait. There is!
‐ Ow!
‐ Knew it.
‐ Clever, but not clever enough.
‐ Okay, okay. You got me.
Hold your fire. I surrender.
My hands are up,
I got nothing in 'em,
and my side arm's holstered.
I promise I won't go for it.
You'd blast me
before I could draw anyway.
‐ I would,
but I wanna save bullets,
so I'll let you resign instead.
‐ Okay.
That's way better than dying.
But first, I was wondering
if we could chat for a bit.
I have a small confession.
If there's one thing
that gets me going,
it's cute, kick‐ass girls
like you two.
‐ [groans]
‐ Oh, great.
We found another creep.
If you don't wanna shoot him,
I will.
LLENN: What kinda mags
are in those pouches?
‐ Hmm?
Permission to move my hand
and show you?
Don't worry. I'll go slow.
‐ [gunshot]
‐ Ow! Ow! God!
LLENN: Try that again,
and lose an ear.
Now show me
what's in those pouches.
‐ Dang, you're scary.
Here.
‐ I knew it!
Do you use a P90, too?
‐ Nah, I use an AR‐57.
Do you know it?
It's a pretty nifty
piece of hardware!
It's a specially designed
upper receiver
that fits on the lower receiver
of an M16.
It uses P90 mags‐‐
‐ Gimme all your mags now,
the ones in your pouches
and the ones you got
in storage, chop‐chop!
‐ Whoa now! Wait a second!
That's all the ammo
I have in the game.
Why do you wanna bone
a fellow player like that?
‐ I'm gonna win this! And I
need your mags to, so gimme!
‐ Ha! Looks like
I got you over a barrel!
[laughing]
‐ Fuka, I'm gonna blow off
his arms and legs.
Could you please go behind
and loot his storage?
‐ Okey‐dokey!
‐ You guys might be cute,
but you're as ruthless
as a bunch of pirates.
Uh, news flash.
This is being broadcast.
They can't hear
what we're saying,
but it's obvious
what you're doing.
Robbing a defenseless player's
pretty low.
It's even worse,
'cause you're ladies.
This moment'll go down
in "GGO" history.
‐ You gonna give me
all your mags, or what?
‐ [sighs] Okay, okay,
I'll give 'em to you.
I'll just have to grind away
'til the end of time
to get 'em back, but whatever.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
Before I do, maybe you
could give me something
as thanks for my generosity?
LLENN: Like what.
‐ Oh, I was thinking
about something small,
something like a kiss?
‐ Say what?!
‐ Huh?!
‐ It's just a kiss, a smooch,
a little peck.
I'd love it if I got one
from both of you,
but I'll settle for you, Pinky.
One teeny kiss,
and my mags are yours.
Right here.
One little kiss on the cheek.
‐ [groans]
‐ Oh, my God. This game
is chock‐full of lechers.
LLENN, who cares
about the mags?
I'm gonna blow
his skeezy head off.
‐ I'll do it.
‐ Uh...
‐ It's not a big deal.
‐ For real?
Are you crazy?!
‐ This kid's got some issues,
for sure,
but if all I have to do is
kiss him to get at those mags,
it's way better
than robbing him.
‐ Yes! [laughs] I get a kiss!
‐ I get a kiss!
‐ Well, as long as...
‐ you're cool with it, have fun.
‐ I said I'd do it,
but I want the mags first!
‐ You got it.
Just do like you promised,
you cutie.
‐ Cha‐ching!
You just hit the jackpot.
Now let me kill this goon.
‐ Stop it.
‐ You look so scary.
‐ I hate giving you
the satisfaction,
but I did promise you.
[stammering]
[kiss]
‐ Oh! Clever!
Even if this is live,
folks'll think you're
just whispering in his ear.
‐ All right. Are you happy now?
‐ You don't even know.
[laughs] My heart's pounding!
[laughs] Love it.
Nothing in the world
compares to how a girl kisses.
It's not all rough and crude
like how guys always kiss.
‐ Uh, I'm sorry. What?
‐ He said he kissed guys.
Do you, like, force them
to kiss you like you do girls?
‐ No! Not even.
Might as well tell you.
You see, I'm a girl IRL.
Both: You are?!
‐ My avatar's female, too,
but it's androgynous,
so I have a guyish voice.
I wish she were chestier.
Wait. It's easier
just to show you.
See? Female.
And in real life, I'm bi.
‐ Hold it. We're in a game.
Don't talk about real life here.
‐ It's cool.
I don't care if you know.
And now that you do,
let's have drinks sometime,
just us virtual girls.
Come on. There's hardly
any girls in "GGO."
Let's be friends.
It'll be great.
But, like, you have no idea
who we are in real life.
I‐I could be
a 50‐year‐old woman!
‐ Who cares if you are?
I don't. I love everybody.
Look, since we
know each other now,
we should form
an all‐girl squad. Come on!
‐ Would you just resign already
and let us get back to the game?
‐ Well, um, thanks again
for handing over your mags.
‐ My pleasure.
[beeping]
‐ What the‐‐
‐ Get down!
‐ LLENN!
‐ Go on. Win this thing!
‐ [gasps]
‐ [groans]
[both yelp]
Crap!
All that talking distracted us.
It gave another team
the chance to move in.
Wonder who.
It's MMTM.
["To see the future"
by Tomori Kusunoki playing]
[singing in Japanese]
♪ You say good night ♪
♪ To see the future ♪