[KATSUKI]
Hey!
Do you really think
Deku has a Quirk?
You saw how he threw that ball.
[KATSUKI] Was he seriously just
tricking me all these years?
I'm gonna roast that
damn nerd today!
[IZUKU]
He can be a real pain, sure.
But his strength, and
confidence, and his ambition...
Not to mention his Quirk.
They're all so much
greater than mine.
But that just means
that I have to do better.
I refuse to lose today.
[ALL MIGHT]
All right.
Let's begin the
indoor combat training!
Team A and Team D.
Your time starts now!
[grunting]
What's the matter, Deku?
Afraid to stand up and fight me?
I won't hurt you so bad
they'll have to stop
the fight. Just close!
[IZUKU grunts]
[gasps]
Wow! Look at those moves!
[KATSUKI] Impossible. How'd
he know? He's not that good!
[grunting]
[yelling]
[groans]
You can call me Deku,
but I'm not the same helpless,
defenseless kid anymore!
You hear me? I've changed!
From now on, Deku is
the name of a hero!
[IZUKU] Kacchan and I grew up
in the same neighborhood,
so we've known each other
since we were little kids.
Uh...
Come on! Let's fight bad guys!
[BOYS]
Yeah!
Oh! Yeah!
[IZUKU]
All the other neighborhood kids
followed him around.
It seemed like he
could do anything.
And no matter what
he decided to do,
he was always so confident.
I thought he was the
coolest person I'd ever met.
[IZUKU]
However...
After his Quirk manifested,
he started to change.
[KATSUKI] You're shaking in
your boots, you're so scared.
But you wanna fight me anyway.
That's why I hate you!
[IZUKU]
Here's the sad truth.
All men are not created equal.
When I was four years old,
I learned that some kids
have more power than others.
[TENYA]
Bakugo! Come in!
Give me a status report.
Where are you?
Just shut up and
defend the weapon.
I've got more important
things to worry about.
[TENYA] Are you forgetting
what our mission is?
Hello? He hung up on me!
This isn't the time
for radio silence.
We're supposed to
be partners. Argh!
[KIRISHIMA]
Hey, who's Bakugo talking to?
I'm not hearing anything.
Can we get any sound
with this video?
He's got a radio in
his ear so he can
talk to his partner.
I gave it to him before
the match started.
Along with a map
of the building.
Also, this. A roll
of capture tape!
Wrapping this around
your opponent
means you've apprehended them,
and they're out for
the rest of the game.
[ASHIDO] So, there's a
15-minute time limit,
and the good guys have
no idea what floor
the nuclear weapon
is hidden on, right?
[ALL MIGHT]
Correct!
Then the heroes are clearly
at a disadvantage here.
A big one!
Real Pros have
to outwit villains
on a daily basis.
That's life.
Even when the odds aren't
in our favor, we fight!
--[JIRO gasps]
--[KIRISHIMA laughs]
All together!
[ALL MIGHT, STUDENTS]
Let's hear a Plus Ultra!
Monsieur. He's on the move.
[ALL MIGHT]
Hm?
[KATSUKI grunts]
Ah! Uraraka! Go!
[OCHACO grunts]
[IZUKU grunts]
Ballsy move. Think you
can take me alone?
[KATSUKI]
He's using the capture tape!
[IZUKU] Hero notebook
number ten, page 18!
Luckily, I got to see
Eraser Head's moves in action!
What'll Kacchan do now?
Knowing him, he'll be impatient
and try another big punch!
[gasps]
[IZUKU]
I was right!
The little guy's really good!
[SERO] He's holding his own
and he hasn't even
used his Quirk yet!
[ALL MIGHT]
Not surprising.
He's always been pretty
good at taking action
in crisis situations.
[ALL MIGHT] Plus, he spent
years taking notes
on different heroes.
He internalized
everything he learned.
Those lessons are
in his blood now.
That fanboy knowledge
is paying off!
And driving him forward!
[IZUKU]
He kicked first this time.
He's switching things up so
I can't predict his moves.
Does that mean he's worried?
[KATSUKI grunts]
Get back here, Deku!
[KATSUKI growls]
[IZUKU] I'm not gonna be able
to fight him at close range now.
I need some kinda plan!
Dammit!
You were tricking me
for years by acting weak.
Bet you've been laughing
behind my back, huh?
[gasps]
[KATSUKI growls] So where's that
flashy power a' yours now?
[growls]
Let's see how it
compares to mine.
Quirk or no, you'll
never beat me, Deku!
[KAMINARI] That guy has
some real anger issues.
Kinda scary...
[ALL MIGHT] Midoriya told
me that Young Bakugo
thinks very highly of himself.
But this level of pride
is something else.
It may end up being his demise.
[IZUKU panting]
[IZUKU] Good, he's completely
forgotten about my partner.
Just like I thought.
If they wanted to
send someone out
to stop us here,
it should've been Iida.
He's way faster, after all.
[IZUKU] That probably means
Kacchan's gone rogue.
The two of them aren't
working together as a team.
If we had to take those
two on head-to-head,
our chances of winning
would be pretty low.
They've got such strong Quirks.
I can't go after the
weapon right now
or Kacchan will follow me.
And if we both tried
to take him down,
we'd probably run out of time.
[IZUKU]
So we stay split up for now.
I have to trust Uraraka.
She'll find the weapon and Iida,
and then I'll join her
for a two-on-one fight.
That's how we'll win.
I'll just have to capture
Kacchan down here.
On my own.
I can do it.
As long as I don't get
too close to his hands.
[KATSUKI]
Stop hiding!
[gasps]
Come out and
face me, you coward!
[IZUKU]
By the way.
I've been meaning
to tell you, Kacchan.
You're even worse than
the rest of these rejects.
You really think they'd
let someone like you in
when they could have me?
No, wait!
I'm not trying to
compete against you.
You gotta believe me!
[IZUKU]
I take back everything I said.
Like it or not,
you can't stop me!
From now on, Deku is
the name of a hero!
[KATSUKI]
He's just a little bug.
[IZUKU]
Wow, you're so awesome!
Whatever, this is nothin'.
[IZUKU]
Ow!
Jeez, Izuku.
You really can't do
anything right, can you?
Look!
You can read the last part
of Izuku's name as "Deku."
Whoa, so you can read that?
Well, obviously.
Deku. That must be what
you call a helpless loser
who's completely useless.
[BOYS laugh]
Why are you being
so mean, Kacchan?
[KATSUKI]
Why don't you understand?
[BOYS]
Whoa!
Dude, that has to
be a new record.
I bet it is.
Wow!
Heh, cool!
Where's yours?
Well, uh, it sank.
[BOYS laugh]
[KATSUKI] Why can't you
do anything right?
[PRESCHOOLERS]
Whoa!
Awesome!
You're so lucky!
Yeah!
Impressive.
I bet you that's gonna
grow into an amazing Quirk!
Definitely.
A flashy Quirk
for a future hero.
It's perfect!
[KATSUKI] Yeah, you're
right! I am amazing!
In fact, I bet there's
no one as great as I am.
Wow, you're so lucky!
Your Quirk is
amazing, Kacchan!
When I get mine, I hope
it's just as cool!
Whatever, Deku.
No matter what power
you end up with, you'll
never be able to beat me.
[KATSUKI]
A worthless bug for me to smash.
[BOY 1C]
Hey, did you hear?
Deku doesn't have
a Quirk. Like, none.
[BOY 7A]
What? Really?
[BOY 1C] Yeah, it's called
being "Quirkless."
[BOY 1B]
That's dumb.
[BOY 7B]
What a loser.
[BOY 7C]
He's so lame.
[PRESCHOOL TEACHER 7B] Don't
worry about it, okay, Izuku?
[KATSUKI]
You're a total failure, Deku.
Forward march and here we go,
members of the Agency
Bakugo. Sound o--
Kacchan!
Hey. You okay down there?
Oh, don't worry.
Kacchan is super tough! See?
[KATSUKI grunts]
[KATSUKI]
I was just fine on my own, Deku.
[BOY 1C]
Hurry and get back up here!
Sure! Just gimme one second.
[KATSUKI]
I didn't need your stupid help!
Are you all right? Are you hurt?
I was worried you might'a
hit your head or something.
[KATSUKI] But you looked at me
like I was some kinda weakling.
Kacchan!
I couldn't just stand there
and watch you die!
[KATSUKI]
Like you! But I'm not!
I'm so much better than you are!
[OCHACO] Found it. Now I
just have to tell Deku.
And try my best to stay outta
sight until he gets up here.
[gasps]
[TENYA] Bakugo definitely
has a villainous side.
And that's exactly what we need
to succeed in this mission.
I need to temporarily devote
myself to criminal intent.
Yes. I won't fail this trial
and risk bringing shame down
on the Iida family name.
That means...
I must now embrace evil...
...to become a hero!
Behold! I am the
personification of villainy!
[TENYA cackles]
[OCHACO]
He's so serious.
[TENYA]
Hm? Uraraka, is that you?
[OCHACO gasps]
Uh...
[TENYA] I knew you would
come here alone the instant
that Bakugo ran off by himself
and engaged with Midoriya.
Your Quirk allows you to
float anything that you touch,
but I've prepared for that.
By hiding every object
in this room so you have
nothing to use
against me, do-gooder!
My dastardly tricks have
rendered you helpless!
You've blundered, hero!
[evil laughter]
He really is...
playing the part.
[OCHACO]
Um, Deku?
[IZUKU]
I'm here. How's it going?
[OCHACO]
Iida knows that I'm here. Sorry.
Right now he's monologuing.
[IZUKU]
Where are you?
[OCHACO] Near the middle
of the fifth floor.
[gasps] Right above me!
[IZUKU] We probably don't
have much time left, now.
We have to finish this
fast or they win!
I won't give up yet.
I can capture Kacchan.
I won't lose!
[gasps]
I'm all loaded up.
What does that mean?
[KATSUKI] Why aren't you
using your fancy Quirk?
Don't tell me you're
underestimating me, Deku.
Get over here and show me
what you're really made of.
[IZUKU] I have no choice.
I have to face him.
Right now!
Kacchan. I'm not
scared of you anymore.
[growls]
Heh.
Since you're such a stalker,
by now you probably
know how my Quirk,
Explosion, works. I secrete
nitroglycerin-like sweat
from my hands and
make it blow up.
Imagine what I could do
if I had a lot of it.
That's right, these gauntlets
aren't just for show.
They've been storing up my sweat
inside for one monster blast.
[ALL MIGHT]
No, he's going too far!
Young Bakugo!
Don't do it! You'll kill him!
He'll be fine as
long as he dodges!
[IZUKU yelps]
[TENYA, OCHACO yelp]
--[STUDENTS gasping]
--Whoa, whoa! This's nuts!
Come in! Come in, Midoriya!
[IZUKU grunts, pants]
Is that even allowed?
[KATSUKI laughs]
These are awesome.
The more nitro sweat that's
stored in these gauntlets,
the stronger the explosion is.
[KATSUKI]
Go ahead.
Use your stupid
Quirk on me, Deku.
Even if you give me
everything you've got,
you'll never beat me.
[TENYA]
Bakugo. Answer me!
What is going on down there?
Did you cause that blast?
[OCHACO]
Now's my chance!
If I can claim the weapon,
that means we win!
[TENYA gasps]
[TENYA]
Not so fast, Hero!
[OCHACO grunts]
[TENYA gasps]
[OCHACO]
I just have to touch the weapon.
In one move,
this'll all be over.
[TENYA] Since when can
she make herself float?
Release!
[OCHACO] This special move
is hard, but it's worth it!
[yells]
[OCHACO yelps]
[groans]
[TENYA] Admirable attempt,
but your Quirk's no threat
if you can't touch anything.
I can easily keep this
weapon out of your reach
until time runs out.
[evil laughter]
[OCHACO grunts] It's not over,
I won't let Deku down.
[KATSUKI] What's the matter?
You look scared.
You dodged the attack, so you
can still fight, can't you?
Come and get me.
[IZUKU] The gauntlets make
it so he can use his powers
at long range. I'm not safe,
even if I stay away from him.
So what do I do?
Come in, what's the situation?
[OCHACO]
It's not good!
Are you ignoring me again?
I'll get your attention.
[KIRISHIMA] Sir, isn't
this getting outta hand?
That Bakugo is
acting real crazy.
He's gonna kill 'im!
Not so.
I won't hurt you so bad
they'll have to stop
the fight, just close!
Oh, he'll be fine
as long as he dodges!
[ALL MIGHT]
Despite his fierce posturing,
he's not actually trying to
kill Midoriya. But still...
[ALL MIGHT]
Bakugo.
Use that stored-up power again
and I'll stop this fight.
Your team will lose.
Huh?
[ALL MIGHT] To employ such
a strong attack indoors
is inviting the destruction
of the stronghold
you should be protecting.
That's a poor strategy, whether
you're a hero or a villain.
The penalty would be
a massive loss of points.
[ALL MIGHT]
I know that as a teacher,
I should stop this
fight now. But...
[growling]
The pillar by the window.
Get there now! [gasps]
[KATSUKI]
We'll fight hand-to-hand!
[IZUKU] It's no good.
I can't dodge this!
I'll have to
counterattack! Like this!
[KATSUKI grunts]
[yells]
[STUDENTS gasp]
What was that move?
He doesn't come off as
a guy with a strategy.
But he's actually
quite intelligent.
[ASHIDO]
Huh?
What're you talkin' about?
[TODOROKI] He changed his
trajectory while in midair
using a blast that doubled
as a smokescreen.
Very clever.
A feint attack
like that requires
an extreme amount of precision.
He had to calculate
the physics and demonstrate
control over his Quirk.
Ugh, Bakugo is uber
talented. I hate it.
[IZUKU grunts]
[KATSUKI]
Here it comes, nerd!
The famous right hook
you were whining about!
[IZUKU screams]
[KATSUKI]
Deku!
Don't you ever
forget what you are!
You're a weakling!
[groans]
[IZUKU] He's not giving me
any time to form a strategy.
I can't beat him without
a Quirk after all.
He's too good.
[IZUKU] I have no choice.
I have to use it.
[ASHIDO]
This is hard to watch!
All he has to do is wrap tape
around him, not kill him.
Bakugo's certainly
acting like a villain.
I thought Midoriya
was pretty amazing
at the start of the fight,
but he's completely
outmatched in terms
of combat power.
Not to mention, Bakugo
seems like a natural
at all this stuff.
[ALL MIGHT]
I should end this. But--
[pants]
[ALL MIGHT] For his sake,
I'll let it go on.
[ASHIDO]
He's running away!
Not very manly, but he
doesn't have a choice.
He's outgunned. Unless he's
got some kinda plan.
It's possible...
[IZUKU panting]
Why won't you use your
damn Quirk against me?
Still think you can
stop me without it?
That's not it.
You've been hiding your
true power for years.
What's the deal, Deku?
Did you think you were better
than me this entire time?
That's what you think?
[IZUKU]
You idiot.
You've always been
stronger, Kacchan.
I know that you're
better than me.
[grunts]
[IZUKU]
Can't you see?
That's why I wanna beat you.
Because you're amazing!
[KATSUKI] You're even more
of an idiot than I realized.
Come at me!
[ALL MIGHT] The only other time
I hear that much passion
in his voice is when he
talks about being a hero.
In order to achieve his dream,
he has to do this.
Not for me, but for himself!
[IZUKU]
Detroit...
[yelling]
They're gonna kill
each other! Sir!
[yelling]
Both of you, stop--!
Uraraka, now!
[ALL MIGHT]
Hm?
Right!
[TENYA gasps]
[IZUKU]
I can't beat you.
Not in a one-on-one
fight like this.
But I can win!
Smash!
[KATSUKI gasps]
[TENYA gasps]
What's happening?
This is it! Sorry, Iida!
Improvised special move:
the Comet Home Run!
[TENYA] In the name of villainy,
I demand that you stop this!
Release!
[TENYA gasps]
I got it!
[TENYA]
No! The weapon!
This was your big plan...
...from the very
beginning, wasn't it?
You were playing me this
entire time, you bastard.
[IZUKU]
I wasn't... going to use it.
[grunts]
[IZUKU whimpers]
Because I can't control it.
My body just can't handle...
the backlash of my power yet.
Mr. Aizawa said I'd be useless.
But this was all...
that I... could think of.
[KATSUKI gasps]
This is the only way...
I had any chance at winning.
[KATSUKI grunts]
You did it.
[ALL MIGHT]
The hero team...
...wins!
[ALL MIGHT] You kids still
have a lot to learn,
but I'll help you hero up!
[IZUKU] Next time:
"Bakugo's Start Line"!
[ALL MIGHT]
Young Bakugo's going to get
all teary-eyed on us!
[IZUKU]
Go beyond!
[IZUKU, ALL MIGHT]
Plus Ultra!