[TEACHER A] Check out the
results from the exam.
[TEACHER B] Wow, the first
place student didn't even
have Rescue points.
[TEACHER C] He took down those
faux villains like an ace.
When most of the other examinees
were running from
the big obstacle,
he stayed focused on letting
the smaller targets get in close
and then counterattacking.
That kid is tough.
[TEACHER B] On the opposite end,
the seventh place student
had zero villain points.
[TEACHER C]
He's not the first UA hopeful
to take out that giant robot.
Though, it's been a while
since I saw someone
blow it away with one attack.
[TEACHER D]
But at what cost?
Did you see how badly
he injured himself?
If you ask me, it's like his
body isn't used to his Quirk.
Hm...
[IZUKU]
The night after I opened my
UA acceptance letter, he finally
got in touch with me again.
[ALL MIGHT]
Huh?
[IZUKU panting]
Hi, All Might!
Too loud, kid!
[MAN 5A]
All Might's here?
[WOMAN 5A]
No way! Where?
[ALL MIGHT]
Way to blow my cover.
Say it was a mistake.
I was just kidding!
Nothing to see here!
[MAN 5A]
Lame.
[WOMAN 5A]
I wanted an autograph.
[ALL MIGHT, IZUKU sigh]
[ALL MIGHT]
Congrats on getting in.
I couldn't have done it
without your help!
[ALL MIGHT]
Oh, speaking of which.
I didn't tell anyone
at UA that I've been
training you or anything.
[IZUKU]
Hm?
Really. I wasn't
one of the judges,
and I didn't pull
any strings for ya.
You earned your spot
all on your own.
[IZUKU]
Wow, thanks for telling me.
I'm glad to hear that!
[gasps] Oh, yeah!
I was really surprised
to hear you're gonna be
a teacher at UA this year!
I was wondering what brought
you here all of a sudden.
After all, your agency
is in Minato, Tokyo,
--and everyone knows--
--[ALL MIGHT] Gettin' creepy.
[ALL MIGHT] The school didn't
want me telling anyone
about the job until they made
an official announcement.
It seemed like
fortuitous timing.
An easy way to find someone
new to inherit One For All.
I was on a long hunt
for a successor.
[IZUKU]
So that's it.
He was originally planning
to give it to a UA student.
Someone who was strong.
Who already had a Quirk.
[IZUKU] Your power
completely wrecked my body.
And all I did was jump
and throw one punch.
I can't control it.
What do I do?
You'll learn to manage in time.
Hoping to master it right
away is like asking a baby
to run a marathon. You still
have to go through the process
of learning how to walk.
[IZUKU]
Yeah... Wait!
You knew I was gonna
get hurt that badly?
Well... We were
in a time crunch.
But it turned out all right.
Plus, now you know what
you're dealing with.
[IZUKU gasps]
[ALL MIGHT] Right now, your
Quirk is either all or nothing.
One day, you'll learn how
to control your output.
Then you'll be able to adjust
exactly how much
power you're using.
[gasps] I just need control?
[ALL MIGHT] You're overflowing
with energy at the moment.
With training, your
body'll hold it better.
Then it's yours to command.
[gasps]
[MAN 5A]
Look, it really is All Might!
[WOMAN 5A]
No way! Where'd he come from?
Right. Now we run!
[IZUKU]
Huh? Okay!
[ALL MIGHT]
The torch I passed on to you
is but a small flame right now.
In time, it will be kindled,
until you wield
a raging inferno.
The more powerful you become,
the more you'll outshine me.
Eventually, I'll retire.
My job complete.
Hoo! Deep stuff, All Might.
[IZUKU'S MOM]
Izuku. You're all set?
[IZUKU]
Yeah.
[IZUKU'S MOM]
Are ya sure?
You didn't just pack
action figures, right?
I have everything.
Now I gotta go.
I don't wanna be late.
[IZUKU'S MOM]
Izuku!
[IZUKU groans]
What?
I'm really proud of you, son.
[gasps]
[IZUKU] That day, I began
my high school career.
I'll see you soon.
[IZUKU] The acceptance rate
that year was just as small
as it always had been.
One in 300.
Four people got in because
of recommendations,
and 36 through
the regular exams.
We were split into two
classes of 20 students each.
Class 1-A... 1-A...
C'mon, where is it? Ah! There!
[IZUKU] Man, this thing is huge.
Are there giants here?
The most promising
students in the country
are waiting behind this door.
[gasps]
Maybe we're in
different classes.
Maybe everyone in here is nice.
Take your feet off
of that desk now!
Huh?
It's the first day and you're
already disrespecting
this academy by scuffing
school property, you cretin!
You're kidding me, right?
Your old school put
a stick up your ass?
Or were you born with it?
[IZUKU]
Just my luck.
Uh--
Let's start over.
I'm Tenya Iida from the
Somei Private Academy.
Somei, huh?
So you must think
you're better than me.
I'm gonna have fun
tearin' you a new one.
[gasps] You would threaten me?
Your own classmate?
Are you sure you're
in the right place?
Ha!
[TENYA]
Huh? It's him.
--[STUDENTS murmur]
--[IZUKU gasps]
Uh, hi.
[TENYA]
Good morning!
My name is Tenya Iida fro--
[IZUKU]
Yeah, I-I know.
I'm Izuku Midoriya.
It's super nice to meet you.
[TENYA]
Midoriya. You realized that
there was something more to the
practical exam, didn't you?
Huh?
You must be very perceptive.
And I completely
misjudged you, I admit.
As a student, you're
far superior to me.
[IZUKU]
Um.
I find that hard to believe.
Hey! I recognize
that messed-up hair!
--Falling boy!
--[gasps]
[IZUKU] Oh my gosh, it's that
nice girl who talked to me!
She looks good in that uniform.
[OCHACO]
That punch was amazing!
Oh, hey, hi! Oh my gosh!
So, uh, I should
probably be thanking you
for going in and talking to him.
[OCHACO]
Huh? How'd you know about that?
[IZUKU]
Oh, I-- Um-- What?
[TEACHER 1A]
I can't believe we have not one,
but two students from our
school heading off to UA!
And to think, you're
one of them, Midoriya.
It's a miracle.
[KATSUKI, IZUKU grunt]
[KATSUKI]
What'd you do to pass the exam?
You must've cheated
somehow, right?
I'm supposed to be the
first and only student
from this crappy school
to get into UA,
but you had to go and
screw that all up.
I warned you not to apply!
[IZUKU]
Kacchan.
[grunts]
[IZUKU]
Someone I look up to told me
that I can become a hero.
That's why I applied.
That's why I'm going.
Huh?
Like it or not,
you can't stop me.
[KATSUKI] I'm gonna ruin
that little bastard.
Right after I figure
out how he got in.
What do you think
we're doing today
besides orientation? I wonder
what our teachers are like.
I can't wait to meet everybody!
If you're just here
to make friends
then you can pack up
your stuff now.
Ah!
U-Uh--
[OCHACO whimpers]
Welcome to UA's hero course.
[ALL gasp]
What is that thing?
[AIZAWA] It took eight seconds
before you all shut up.
That's not gonna work.
Time is precious.
Rational students would
understand that.
[IZUKU]
Who is this guy?
If he's here, then he
must be some kinda pro.
But he looks so worn out.
What's his deal?
Hello, I'm Shota Aizawa.
Your teacher.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[IZUKU]
Our teacher?
Right, let's get to it.
Put these on and head outside.
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[ALL MIGHT] UA's course doesn't
follow the normal academic path.
[sighs]
[ALL MIGHT]
Get the wrong homeroom teacher,
and life is hell.
[STUDENTS]
What? A Quirk assessment test?
But orientation!
We're gonna miss it!
[AIZAWA] If you really wanna
make the big leagues,
you can't waste time on
pointless ceremonies.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[AIZAWA] Here at UA, we're
not tethered to traditions.
That means that I get to run
my class however I see fit.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[AIZAWA] You've been taking
standardized tests
most of your lives. But you
never got to use your Quirks
in physical exams before.
The country's still
trying to pretend
we're all created equal
by not letting those
with the most power excel.
It's not rational.
One day, the Ministry of
Education will learn.
Bakugo, you managed
to get the most points
on the entrance exam.
What was your farthest distance
throw with a softball
when you were in Junior High?
Sixty-seven meters, I think.
[AIZAWA] Right. Try doing
it with your Quirk.
Anything goes, just
stay in the circle.
Go on. You're wasting our time.
All right, man,
you asked for it.
[KATSUKI] I'll add a little heat
to my pitch and drop their jaws.
[growls] Die!
Oh, whoa.
[AIZAWA] All of you need to know
your maximum capabilities.
It's the most rational
way of figuring out
your potential as a pro hero.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Whoa, 705 meters,
are you kidding me?
I wanna go! That looks like fun!
This is what I'm talkin'
about, usin' our Quirks
as much as we want!
So this looks fun, huh?
[gasps]
[AIZAWA] You have three years
here to become a hero.
You think it's all gonna
be games and play time?
Idiots.
Today you'll compete
in eight physical tests
to gauge your potential.
Whoever comes in last has none,
and will be
expelled immediately.
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
Aw crap, he got Aizawa.
Midoriya's gonna be
singled-out from the start.
[IZUKU]
Immediate expulsion?
Eight tests? Oh, crap. Not good.
[pants]
[IZUKU] I can only use
One For All at either
zero or 100 percent right now.
I don't have any control yet.
[AIZAWA] Like I said, I get
to decide how this class runs.
Understand?
If that's a problem, you
can head home right now.
[IZUKU] A huge test on
the first day of school?
What the crap am I gonna do?
You can't send one of us home!
I mean, we just got here!
Even if it wasn't the
first day, that isn't fair!
[AIZAWA] Oh, and you think
natural disasters are?
[STUDENTS gasp]
[AIZAWA]
Or power-hungry villains? Hm?
Or catastrophic accidents
that wipe out whole cities?
No, the world is
full of unfairness.
It's a hero's job to try
to combat that unfairness.
If you wanna be
a pro, you're gonna
have to push yourself
to the brink.
For the next three years, UA
will throw one terrible hardship
after another at you.
So, go beyond. Plus Ultra-style.
Show me it's no mistake
that you're here.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[TENYA] I don't approve
of this kind of hazing,
but UA's the top hero
program. I have no choice.
[KATSUKI]
Time to blow these nerds away.
[AIZAWA]
Now then.
We're just wasting
time by talking.
Let the games begin.
[whistle blows]
[MEASURING DEVICE 5A]
Runners, on your marks. Ready--
[gunshot]
[MEASURING DEVICE 5A]
3.04 seconds.
[grunts]
[TENYA] At 50 meters, I can
only get up to third gear.
[PRESENT MIC]
Tenya Iida, his Quirk: Engine!
As you can see his legs
are pretty dang fast!
Well, he's definitely
in his element,
but speed won't help
him in every test.
[OCHACO]
I'll lighten up my clothes.
Oh, and my shoes, too!
[PRESENT MIC] Ochaco Uraraka,
her Quirk: Zero Gravity!
[MEASURING DEVICE 5A]
Get set--
[gunshot]
[PRESENT MIC]
She can nullify
the gravitational pull of
anything she touches.
But if she uses her power
too much, she totally hurls!
[MEASURING DEVICE 5A]
Five point four nine seconds.
Seven point one five seconds.
[OCHACO] Well, at least that's
faster than junior high!
[AOYAMA]
Nice attempts, mon amis.
[MEASURING DEVICE 5A]
Runners, on your marks.
But you're just not
showing enought panache!
[gunshot]
[AOYAMA]
Let your powers shine!
[PRESENT MIC] Yuga Aoyama,
his Quirk: Navel Laser!
That's right, a
bellybutton laser.
[PRESENT MIC]
But he can't shoot it forever.
[MEASURING DEVICE 5A]
Five point five one seconds.
[AOYAMA] Hm. Shooting my
beautiful beam for more
than a second hurts my tummy.
[SERO, KIRISHIMA, KAMINARI,
ASHIDO, AIZAWA] What a tool.
[AIZAWA] Testing the upper
limits of their powers
helps me assess their
room for growth.
It becomes clear what
they can and can't do.
Their true potential.
[MEASURING DEVICE 5A]
Runners, on your marks.
Ready--
[gunshot]
[AIZAWA] Sometimes,
pros have to be creative
in order to succeed.
Burst speed!
[MEASURING DEVICE 5A]
Four point one three seconds.
[PRESENT MIC] Katsuki Bakugo,
his Quirk: Explosion!
[MEASURING DEVICE 5A]
Seven point zero two seconds.
My power has more uses
than anyone else's
in this school.
[KATSUKI]
Pathetic.
[IZUKU]
There are still seven tests.
Everyone's gonna be using
their Quirks on all of 'em
and getting awesome results.
[IZUKU]
So what do I do?
I've got a ton of power,
but I can only use it once.
And it'll break me.
Control! That's what I need.
Maybe I can focus like
All Might suggested.
[ALL MIGHT] You can harness
One For All. It's simple.
You have to feel it!
Can you be a little
more specific?
So you already
know what it's like
to fire on all cylinders.
[IZUKU] Yeah, like
a lot of broken bones.
No, I'm talking about
the rush inside.
You must have felt it
coursing through you.
What was it like?
Mm... A bzzt, or no, like,
whoosh or maybe kapow, or--
Um... Ooh, I know!
Like an egg about to
explode in a microwave!
That's pretty boring, but okay!
If that's the metaphor
you wanna go with,
then lower the wattage, or
decrease the cooking time.
Whichever one works.
Keep focusing on that
image and keeping the egg
from exploding, all right?
[IZUKU]
I can do that.
You've got three
weeks until school.
The more you concentrate,
the faster you'll learn.
Control over One For All
isn't gonna happen overnight.
But you'll nail it one day.
You just gotta keep trying.
[whistle blows]
[IZUKU] Okay. Keep the
egg from blowing up.
[beeping]
[SERO]
Wow!
Uh?
[SERO] You hit 540 kilograms?
You're such a beast!
[MINETA]
Yeah, like a muscle-y octopus.
Ah...
[whistle blows]
[AOYAMA giggles]
[KATSUKI grunts]
[IZUKU grunts]
[IZUKU]
Focus.
[whistle blows]
[MINETA yelping]
[gasping]
[whistle blows]
[STUDENTS]
Infinity?!
That's insane!
How's that possible?
[IZUKU]
This is bad.
I've gotta come up with
some kind of a game plan.
Everyone's had at least one
crazy-good score already.
[IZUKU] All that's left
is this, the distance run,
sit-ups, and the seated
toe touch. It's now or never.
This is my best chance
to use One For All.
If Midoriya doesn't
shape up soon,
he's the one going home.
Huh? Of course he is.
He's a Quirkless loser.
He has a Quirk.
Did you not hear about what
he did in the entrance exam?
[KATSUKI]
Huh?
[AIZAWA]
Here it comes.
[IZUKU'S MOM]
Izuku!
I'm really proud of you, son.
[ALL MIGHT] Young man.
You, too, can become a hero.
[IZUKU]
I won't let them down!
[yells]
[MEASURING DEVICE 5A]
Fourty-six meters.
[gasps]
Uh... What gives? I was
trying to use it just now.
[AIZAWA]
I erased your Quirk.
[gasps]
The judges for this exam
were not rational enough.
Someone like you should
never be allowed
to enroll at this school.
Wait, you did what to my--
Ah! Those goggles. I know you!
[IZUKU] You can look at someone
and cancel out their powers.
The Erasure Hero. Eraser Head!
--[STUDENTS] Uh...
--[SERO] Eraser? Who's that?
[TSUYU]
Oh, I've heard of him.
I think he works
on the down-low.
[ALL MIGHT] Aizawa's one of
those guys who doesn't like
the media because he thinks
they interfere with our work.
And he judges celebrity
heroes like me
because I look good
in the spotlight.
You're not ready.
You don't have control
over your power.
[gasps]
[AIZAWA] Were you planning
to break your bones again?
Counting on someone else
to save your useless body?
No! That's not what
I was trying to do!
No matter what
your intentions are,
you would be nothing more
than a liability in battle.
[gasps]
[AIZAWA] You have the
same reckless passion
as another overzealous
hero I know.
One who saved 1,000 people by
himself and became a legend.
But even with that drive,
you're worthless
if you can only throw a single
punch before breaking down.
Sorry, Midoriya.
With your power, there's no
way you can become a hero.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[AIZAWA] I've returned
your impractical Quirk.
Take your final throw.
Hurry and get it over with.
[worriedly] Mm...
I wonder if our teacher
gave him some advice.
[KATSUKI] Probably told
him to start packing.
I'm here, cheri.
Wait, who are you, again?
I've only got one
shot at nailing this,
so what am I gonna do?
[AIZAWA]
Is he going to use his Quirk
and have to forfeit the rest
of the events like a fool?
Or admit defeat and
settle into last place?
Either way, he
doesn't belong here.
[IZUKU]
I still can't control my power.
But I can't just
give up, either.
Do I let the egg explode?
It might be my only
shot at staying at UA.
I have to try something.
No matter what the consequences.
[AIZAWA]
A waste of a Quirk.
[IZUKU] Mr. Aizawa was
right about what he said.
[IZUKU] If I can't control
my Quirk, there's no way
I'll ever become a hero.
Hey, hey, is he for real?
[IZUKU] I have to work way
harder than everyone else here
if I wanna succeed.
[IZUKU]
Even if I have a lot to learn,
I'll focus on what
I can do right now.
Smash!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[IZUKU] It hurts...
But not as bad as before.
[AIZAWA] Were you planning
to break your bones again?
Counting on someone else
to save your useless body?
[IZUKU]
Mr. Aizawa.
You see? I'm still standing.
This kid...
[ALL MIGHT] I was worried
about you, young man,
but you're doin' a great job.
You knew you had to
use One For All,
but not at full power
or else you'd be KO'd.
So, you propelled the ball
at the last possible
point of contact--
by sending the
power of your Quirk
shooting through your fingertip.
Minimizing the injury
to your body
while maximizing the throw.
[ALL MIGHT]
What the heck, young Midoriya?
How did you go
and get so cool?
[IZUKU] Hero Basic Training,
a class only available
in the UA hero course.
[OCHACO] Deku, let's do our best
in this combat exercise, okay?
[IZUKU] Oh my gosh, I talked
to a girl again! [squeals]
[OCHACO] Looks like we're up
against Team Iida and Bakugo.
[IZUKU gasps] You mean, I'm
going to have to fight Kacchan?
Next time:
"Rage, You Damn Nerd"!
[OCHACO]
Look at Deku's bunny ears!
Oh my goodness! They're so cute!
[IZUKU]
Go beyond!
[IZUKU, OCHACO]
Plus Ultra!