[STUDENTS gasping]
[THIRTEEN]
I'm sorry. He got me.
Thirteen!
[screams]
[AIZAWA]
I'm positive I erased his Quirk.
That means he's super strong
even without powers.
[AIZAWA groans]
[AIZAWA] I think he's
as strong as All Might.
[AIZAWA groans]
[IZUKU]
You! Let her go! Now! Smash!
[IZUKU yelps]
Ribbit!
[IZUKU] All of us, even
our teachers, were scared.
The evil we faced clouded
our hearts with fear.
[IZUKU] But the deeper
the darkness around you...
[ASHIDO, OCHACO gasp]
[IZUKU]
...the brighter the light shines
when a ray of hope appears.
[STUDENTS]
It's All Might!
[ALL MIGHT] I couldn't
shake the feeling that
something had gone
wrong here when
Aizawa and Thirteen
didn't answer my calls.
So I hurried over,
running into Young Iida
along the way.
He told me of the
villainy at work here.
[ALL MIGHT] I can't believe
all of this went down
while I was resting.
I hate to think of
how frightened
these children must be.
And how hard my
colleagues had to fight
in order to protect them.
The only thing I can do
now is reassure them
that things will be okay.
That's my duty as
the Symbol of Peace.
[ALL MIGHT]
Have no fear, students...
Because I am here!
Look, we're saved!
Ribbit.
He's here...
All Might!
[IZUKU]
And he's not smiling.
[SHIGARAKI]
After all this waiting...
The heroic piece
of trash shows up.
[VILLAIN A]
Holy crap. It's All Might.
I've never seen the
guy in person before.
I didn't expect
him to be so huge.
[VILLAIN D] Heh. This is no
time to talk, you idiots.
If we strike now,
we can kill him--
[VILLAINS gasp, groan]
[ALL MIGHT] I'm sorry, Aizawa.
I should've been here.
--[yelps]
--[TSUYU, MINETA grunt]
Uh... What the heck?
Everybody, back to the entrance.
And take Aizawa with you.
He doesn't have much time
[MINETA]
Yes, sir!
[TSUYU]
Ribbit.
You saved us, All Might.
[SHIGARAKI panting]
[SHIGARAKI]
No, no, no.
It wasn't supposed
to go this way.
He's still fast, Father.
Somehow he managed to hit me.
[SHIGARAKI sighs]
[SHIGARAKI]
Of course a government hero
relies on violence.
I wasn't prepared.
I couldn't even see
him when he moved.
But he's not as fast as
I thought he would be.
Not as fast as he used to be.
I guess it's true, after all.
All Might really
is getting weaker.
[gasps]
All Might, you can't!
That brain villain
took One For--
I-I smashed him and didn't
break my arm this time,
but he wasn't fazed at all.
He's too strong!
[ALL MIGHT]
Young Midoriya!
[IZUKU]
Uh--
I got this.
[IZUKU sighs]
[ALL MIGHT]
Carolina...
[SHIGARAKI]
Nomu.
[ALL MIGHT]
Smash!
Huh?
[NOMU growls]
Guess he wasn't
wrong when he said
it had no effect on you.
Let's try this!
[screeches]
[ALL MIGHT grunts]
Doesn't even matter where
I punch you, does it?
[SHIGARAKI]
That's because Nomu here
has shock absorption, All Might.
The only way you're
going to hurt him
is to slowly gouge
out his flesh.
Of course, I don't think he'll
sit back and let you do that.
You've finally met your match.
[ALL MIGHT] Ha! Thanks for
telling me how to beat him!
All I have to do
is wear him down,
and then it's on to you!
[SHIGARAKI]
Hey, hey now.
[SATO] All right!
Take that, bird brain!
[SERO]
Whoa...
That's what you villains get
for underestimating him.
[OCHACO, ASHIDO gasp, giggle]
Are you guys seeing
this? That suplex
looked like a huge explosion!
All Might's on a
whole 'nother level!
And yet he still has
to look at his notes
when he's teaching us.
[IZUKU] It's possible they
have a way to kill him.
But even if they do,
there's not really anything
we can do to help him now.
If we tried to, we'd risk
getting taken hostage,
which is so much worse than
just getting in his way.
I have to put my
faith in All Might,
and stop worrying about
the villains' plans.
Get that guy!
Punch him right in the balls!
Maybe we were worried about
these bad guys for nothing.
All Might's unstoppable.
[IZUKU]
Seems that way. But...
I know the truth.
I read the hero news this
morning on my way to school,
and saw the headlines
about All Might.
Then, when they
were talking about
why he wasn't at training,
Thirteen held up three fingers,
probably to indicate
that All Might
was already at his limit today.
He must've been absent because
he'd used too much of his power!
He shouldn't be using
One For All now!
I'm the only one in
my class who knows.
Pretty gross, right?
I got this in a big fight
five years back.
My respiratory system
was basically destroyed,
and I lost my whole stomach.
All the surgeries have
pretty much worn me out.
And it can't be fixed.
Right now, I can
only do hero work
for about three hours a day.
The rest of the time,
this is what I look like.
I'm supposed to be the guy
who's always smiling, right?
I'm the Symbol of Peace.
People everywhere have to
think that I'm never afraid.
But honestly, kid, I smile
to hide the fear inside.
It's just a brave face I put on
when the pressure is high.
This job isn't easy.
[IZUKU] He's saving us,
but at what cost?
They're cheering him on,
but they don't know what kind of
trouble he's actually in.
[ALL MIGHT]
Oh, c'mon.
What kinda cheap
move was that?
[GROUP gasps]
[ALL MIGHT grunting]
[SHIGARAKI]
Nice.
You were trying to
bury him in the concrete
so he couldn't
move around anymore.
Sorry, that won't work.
Nomu's as strong as you are.
That won't stop him.
[ALL MIGHT grunting]
[SHIGARAKI giggles]
Nice work, Kurogiri.
We've got him just
where we want him now.
[ALL MIGHT grunting]
[ALL MIGHT] Crap! This monster
found my weak spot.
[ALL MIGHT] Damn. Gotta stop
him, despite his power.
If this is your best,
then you picked
the wrong place to attack.
You should just give up now.
[SHIGARAKI pants]
[SHIGARAKI]
Kurogiri.
[KUROGIRI] Normally I wouldn't
want blood and viscera
flooding the insides
of my warp gates,
but I'll make an exception
for a hero as great as you.
[ALL MIGHT grunts, growls]
[KUROGIRI] Since you're too fast
to see with the human eye,
Nomu had to restrain you.
And once he's pulled your
body halfway through.
I'll squeeze the gate shut.
[KUROGIRI] I'm going to enjoy
tearing you to pieces.
[groans]
[IZUKU]
Asui.
Yeah, what is it, Midoriya?
[IZUKU] Will you carry
Mr. Aizawa for me?
Ribbit? Sure, but
what're you gonna do?
[IZUKU] All Might...
I won't let them kill you!
[TSUYU, MINETA gasp]
[MINETA]
Are you crazy?!
[IZUKU] There's still so much
I want you to teach me!
This can't be how it
all ends. It just can't!
[IZUKU]
I'm coming!
[ALL MIGHT]
Midoriya, no.
What do you think you're doing?
[yells]
[KUROGIRI]
How foolish.
Get the hell outta my way, Deku!
[gasps]
[KATSUKI yells]
[ALL MIGHT] He's frozen! That
means Todoroki must be here!
One of your poorly
trained thugs told me
you're here because you think
you can kill All Might.
[ALL MIGHT]
He controlled his Quirk
so that the ice stopped just
before it reached my body.
I think I can loosen
this villain's grip now.
[ALL MIGHT grunts]
[gasps] Are you okay?
[yells]
Damn! That was gonna be cool!
Guess I found your
body that time,
ya smoky bastard!
The Symbol of Peace
will not be defeated
by delinquents like you.
Kacchan! Everyone!
Todoroki... and Bakugo.
And Kirishima, too.
[AIZAWA groans]
Let them handle it,
we need to hurry.
Yeah, okay!
They're helping.
Wait, Is that Tsu down there?
Hey! We're all up here!
It's Ochaco!
Hey!
Can you come help us out?
He's super heavy
and bleeding all over the place!
[OCHACO, SATO gasp]
Mr. Aizawa!
Come on.
[OCHACO grunts]
[THIRTEEN]
Don't worry.
All Might will
take care of this.
When the other teachers
get here, it'll get dangerous,
so find someplace to hide.
[ASHIDO]
Uh, okay!
[SHIGARAKI]
Kurogiri.
How could you let this
brat get the best of you?
You've gotten us into
a real jam here.
[KATSUKI] Heh. You got
careless, you dumb villain.
It wasn't hard to
figure you out.
Only certain parts
of you turn into
that smoking warp gate.
You used that mist to
hide your actual body,
as a kind of distraction.
Thinking that made you safe!
That's why we missed.
[KUROGIRI] You live up to
your school's reputation.
But if you didn't have a body,
you wouldn't be wearing
this neck armor, right?
You're not immune to physical
attacks if they're well aimed.
[KUROGIRI grunts, groans]
[KATSUKI]
Don't move!
You try anything funny, and
I'll blow your ass up right now,
you got it?
They'll be cleanin'
you up for weeks.
Oh, that doesn't
sound very heroic.
[SHIGARAKI] They escaped
uninjured and captured
my two strongest men.
Kids these days
really are amazing.
They make the League of
Villains look like amateurs.
Can't have that.
Nomu.
[NOMU screeches]
[gasps]
How is that thing still moving?
He's all messed up.
Stay back, everybody!
What is this?
I thought you said his power
was shock absorption.
[SHIGARAKI] I didn't say
that was his only Quirk.
He also has super-regeneration.
[SHIGARAKI] Nomu has been
modified to take you on
even at 100% of your power.
He's basically a highly
efficient punching bag
that hits back.
[SHIGARAKI] First, we need
to free our method of escape.
[IZUKU, TODOROKI gasp]
--[KIRISHIMA] Huh?
--[KATSUKI gasps]
[SHIGARAKI]
Get him, Nomu.
[ALL MIGHT]
He's fast!
[IZUKU yelps]
[TODOROKI, KIRISHIMA yelp]
[groans] Such force.
[gasps]
[IZUKU gasps]
Kacchan!
[KATSUKI grunts]
Kacchan? Whoa, that's
awesome, you dodged him!
Shut up, no I didn't,
you damn nerd.
[KATSUKI] That speed... I
couldn't even see him coming.
Then how'd you get over here?
[gasps] Isn't it obvious?
[ALL MIGHT pants, coughs]
[gasps] All Might!
[SHIGARAKI]
So, he protected the child, huh?
[panting] These are kids,
and you didn't hold back?
[SHIGARAKI]
I didn't have much choice.
He was threatening my companion.
Besides, these kids
are no angels.
The plain-looking one?
[gasps]
[SHIGARAKI] He tried to kill
me with a maxed-out punch.
What kind of "hero" does
something like that?
You think you can get away with
being as violent as you want
if you say it's for
the sake of others.
[ALL MIGHT growls]
[SHIGARAKI]
Well, you know what, All Might?
That pisses me off.
Why do people get to decide
that some violent acts
are heroic and others
are villainous?
Casting judgment as to what's
"good" and what's "evil."
You think you're
the Symbol of Peace?
Ha. You're just another
government-sponsored
instrument of violence.
And violence always
breeds more violence.
I'll make sure the
world understands that
once you're dead.
You're nothing but a lunatic.
Criminals like you;
you always try
and make your
actions sound noble.
But admit it; you're only
doing this because you like it.
Isn't that right?
[SHIGARAKI]
He's got me figured out.
We've got them outnumbered.
And Kacchan found the
mist guy's weakness.
These dudes may
act really tough,
but we can take 'em down
now with All Might's help.
Let's do this.
Don't attack.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Get out of here.
You would've been
in trouble earlier
if it weren't for me,
remember? You need our help.
[ALL MIGHT] I thank you
for your assistance,
but this is different.
It's gonna be all right.
Just sit back and
watch a pro at work.
But you're too hurt.
You're bleeding.
And you're almost out of ti--
[IZUKU]
All Might...
[SHIGARAKI]
Nomu. Kurogiri. Kill him.
I'll deal with the children.
[ALL MIGHT] I'm afraid that
I barely have a minute left
in this form.
My power's declining
faster than I thought it would.
[SHIGARAKI] Let's clear
this level and go home.
[ALL MIGHT] Even so, I have
to stop these villains.
Heads up, we're
fightin' after all.
[ALL MIGHT]
Because I am...
[ALL MIGHT] ...the world's
Symbol of Peace and Justice!
[SHIGARAKI gasps]
[IZUKU gasps]
[screeches]
[ALL MIGHT yells]
[SHIGARAKI grunts]
Weren't you listening?
One of his powers
is shock absorption.
Yeah? What about it?
[ALL MIGHT grunting]
[IZUKU grunting]
He's gonna fight that
brain guy head on?
Whoa, they're... so fast!
[KUROGIRI]
No! I can't get near them!
[ALL MIGHT] He said your Quirk
was only shock absorption,
not nullification.
That means there's a limit
to what you can take, right?
[ALL MIGHT groans]
[ALL MIGHT] So, you were
made to fight me, big guy.
If you can really
withstand me firing
at 100% of my power...
[SHIGARAKI gasps]
...then I'll have to go beyond
that and force you to surrender.
[ALL MIGHT grunting]
[IZUKU] He's giving it his all
even though he's injured!
[IZUKU] Those aren't just
random punches, either.
They're targeted, and every
single one of them...
[IZUKU] ...is more than
100% of his power.
[yells]
[SHIGARAKI growls]
[ALL MIGHT]
A real hero...
[ALL MIGHT] ...will always find
a way for justice to be served!
[ALL MIGHT]
Ha!
[ALL MIGHT yells]
[gasps]
[ALL MIGHT]
Now for a lesson.
You may have heard
these words before,
but I'll teach you
what they really mean.
Go beyond! Plus Ultra!
[TOKOYAMI gasps]
What's happening?
Everything is shaking.
[VILLAIN I groans]
What was that?
Um, did a villain just fly by?
Or am I goin' crazy?
It was that brain dude.
[SHOJI]
Such power.
Ah... That's All Might for you.
That's why he's the most amazing
hero in the entire world!
Ribbit, ribbit.
[MINETA]
Yes!
[KIRISHIMA] That was like the
finishing move in a video game.
He beat the shock absorption
right out of him.
I've never seen that
kind of brute strength!
Imagine having power like that.
He must've been punching
that monster so fast,
he couldn't regenerate.
[TODOROKI]
He really is the best.
[KATSUKI]
That's how you get to be a pro.
[IZUKU]
He did it...
[ALL MIGHT]
I really have gotten weaker.
Back in my heyday, five
hits woulda been enough
to knock that guy out.
But today, it took more
than 300 mighty blows.
[whimpers]
[ALL MIGHT]
Time's up. Gotta end this fast.
[ALL MIGHT grunts]
[IZUKU gasps]
You've been bested, villains.
Surrender.
We all want to get
this over with quickly.
[SHIGARAKI]
He cheated.
[crunch]
[ALL MIGHT]
I know the members of Class 1-A
will become valiant heroes!
[IZUKU] Next time:
"In Each of Our Hearts!"
[ALL MIGHT] Now, yell it,
from the depths of your soul!
[IZUKU]
Go beyond!
[IZUKU, ALL MIGHT]
Plus Ultra!