[REPORTERS clammoring]
[REPORTER A] Hey, you!
Can you tell us what it's like
to work so closely
with All Might?
[IZUKU] U-Um, sorry, I
have to go to the, uh,
the nurse's office!
Yeah, right away!
Are you one of
All Might's students?
Tell us-- what's the Symbol
of Peace like in person?
Um... What's he like?
Well... Uh--
He's super muscle-y. Yeah!
How is he faring as a teacher;
what are you learning?
His leadership and
wisdom remind me
on a daily basis that
I attend the world's
most prestigious
educational institution.
Of course, he's the
personification of honor
and integrity that one
would expect, but he's also
not afraid to show his
students a more humorous side.
It's truly a unique
opportunity to be under
the direct tutelage of
the pro we all admire.
Excuse me, kid!
Are you in All Might's
class? Oh, hold on.
Aren't you that
Sludge Villain kid?
Walk away.
Please, sir. Can you
get All Might for us?
Also, you look like a
mess, what's your deal?
All Might's not on campus today.
Now get outta here,
you've disturbed my
students enough already.
[REPORTER A gasps]
But my viewers wanna know
how he's adjusting
to life as a teacher!
[REPORTER B] I feel like I've
seen that guy somewhere before.
But where?
[REPORTER A] I don't know, but
he's a bit scruffy for a hero...
[AIZAWA] How does All Might
ever get anything done
with this media circus
stepping on his cape?
All right.
If you won't bring
All Might out, I'll--
No, hold on!
[alarm blares]
[REPORTER A shrieks]
Hey! What's happening?
Don't you know about
the school's defenses?
This gate is the UA Barrier.
Defenses? It
practically killed me!
[REPORTER B] Yeah, well,
it's designed to stop anyone
who doesn't have a
student ID or special pass
from entering the campus.
Guess it works.
[REPORTER A grunts]
[REPORTER B] Apparently,
there are security sensors
like this all over the place.
[REPORTER A]
Keeping the public out.
This school thinks
it's untouchable!
The least they could do
is grant me one interview.
[REPORTER B]
I know, right?
We've been here for two
days and I don't have
a single comment
on the record yet.
[IZUKU] The news that
All Might had been hired
as a faculty member at UA
took the entire
nation by surprise.
Naturally, the media
swarmed the school
in search of a story.
Everyone wanted to get
their hands on All Might.
Yeah. Everyone.
[AIZAWA]
Decent work on yesterday's
combat training, you guys.
I saw the video
feeds and went over
each of your team's
results. Bakugo.
You're talented.
So don't sulk like a child
about your loss, okay?
Yeah, whatever.
[AIZAWA]
And Midoriya.
I see the only way
you won the match
was by messing up
your arm again.
Work harder.
And don't give me
the excuse that
you don't have control
over your Quirk.
That line's already getting old.
You can't keep
breaking your body
while training here.
But your Quirk will
be really useful
if you can get a handle on it.
[gasps]
[AIZAWA]
So show a little urgency, huh?
Right.
Let's get down to business.
Our first task will
decide your future.
[STUDENTS]
Is it another Quirk test?
You all need to pick
a class representative.
[STUDENTS] Oh, good.
Just normal school stuff!
Pick me, guys!
I wanna be class rep!
I'll take it!
Yeah, you're gonna need me.
Someone with style
would be best.
I'm, like, totally
the right pick!
[IZUKU] In a normal classroom,
a representative's duties
would just be a
bunch of extra work.
But here in the hero course,
there's more to it.
It's a way to get noticed
by agencies and prove
you can lead a team
like a real pro.
Silence, everyone, please!
[TENYA]
The class representative's duty
is to lead others.
That's not something
just anyone can do.
You must first have the trust of
every student in the classroom.
Therefore, the most logical way
to fill this position
is democratically.
We will hold an election
to choose our leader!
[STUDENTS] It's pretty obvious
you want us to vote for you.
Is this really the best idea?
We've only known
each other a few days,
how do we know who we can trust?
Besides, everyone'll just
vote for themselves.
Most people will.
But that means
whoever does receive
multiple votes must truly be
the most suitable
person for the job.
It's the best way, right, sir?
Do what you want, just decide
before my nap's over.
[TENYA]
Thank you for your trust!
How did I get three votes?
Okay, you idiots,
who voted for him?
What, did you
honestly think anyone
was gonna vote for you?
[KATSUKI]
What did you just say?!
[OCHACO] Maybe I'll just
keep my vote to myself.
Zero votes...
I feared this might happen,
but I can't argue with
the system I chose!
So you voted for
someone else, huh?
But you knew it was best
to vote for yourself, right?
What were you tryin'
to prove here, Iida?
[AIZAWA] All right,
the class rep is Midoriya,
and our deputy is Yaoyorozu.
Really? Uh. It's not a mistake?
[sighs] How'd this happen?
This might not be so bad.
Yeah, I can get behind
Midoriya I guess.
[KAMINARI] Yaoyorozu was
totally on top of it
when it came to our
training results!
[OCHACO sighs]
It's always so crowded in here!
[TENYA] That's because students
in the support, management,
and hero courses all share
the same cafeteria.
This rice is delicious!
[sighs] Guys, I'm kinda worried
about the class rep thing,
I don't think I'm qualified.
Sure you are.
You'll be great.
[IZUKU]
Hm?
Your courage and quick
thinking under stress
will help make you
a worthy leader.
Not to mention the strength
you've demonstrated.
Those are the reasons I
voted for you, at least.
[IZUKU]
You were one of the three?
Didn't you wanna be
rep really badly,
I mean you do look the part.
'Cause of the glasses!
[IZUKU] That's not
exactly how we should be
choosing our rep.
Wanting a job and
being suited to it
are quite different things.
Observing the Iida family's hero
agency has taught me that much.
[OCHACO, IZUKU]
"Agency"?
Hold on, what does
your family do?
[TENYA]
Uh-- Oh, it's nothing.
Y'know, I've been wondering
something about you.
Admit it, Iida.
You're filthy rich!
Uh-- I was afraid people
would treat me differently
if they knew about my family.
[OCHACO, IZUKU]
Oooh...
[sighs] You see, the Iidas have
been pro heroes for generations.
It runs in our blood.
[IZUKU, OCHACO]
What? That's awesome!
Are the two of you familiar
with the Turbo Hero, Ingenium?
I know all about him!
He's a super-popular
pro with 65 sidekicks
working alongside him
at his Tokyo agency!
Don't tell me...
He's my elder brother!
[OCHACO]
Your family's famous!
[IZUKU]
I can't believe it!
[TENYA] Ingenium is an
unmatched commander
who honors the hero code.
As the second oldest Iida son,
I strive to be just like him.
However, I think it
might be a bit soon
for me to be in a
real leadership role.
You, for example.
You figured out what the
judges were looking for
in the practical exam.
A rep needs that
sort of insight.
[IZUKU, OCHACO gasp]
That's the first time I've
seen you smile, Tenya!
You should do it more.
[TENYA] What're you talking
about? I smile all the time!
[IZUKU] Iida wants to be like
Ingenium in the same way
I wanna be like All Might.
But he shouldn't be
so hard on himself.
I was clueless in that test.
Hey, yeah, so about
that practical exam--
[bell rings]
--[TENYA, OCHACO gasp]
--What is that?
[ANNOUNCER A] Warning.
Level Three security breach.
No way!
[ANNOUNCER A] All students
please evacuate the building
in an orderly fashion.
What's a "Level Three
security breach?"
It means that someone's managed
to get past the
school's barriers!
This hasn't happened
in my three years here.
We should get going!
[STUDENTS yelling]
Stop shovin' so hard!
[STUDENT B]
Wait, I'm getting trampled!
[STUDENT A]
I said, stop pushin' me!
Ow. This is a total mob!
Everyone was quick to react.
As I'd expect from UA students.
Sure. But they're also
causing a huge panic.
Crap! I can't stop!
--[TENYA] Godspeed, Midoriya!
--[OCHACO] Oh no, Deku!
Who in the world
could've trespassed
onto campus grounds?
It's... the press
that was outside!
All you have to do
is give us All Might!
He's here somewhere!
We said it's his day off.
[REPORTER B] Just give us
one good comment on record
and then we'll leave.
I know how you people work,
give you an inch and
you'll want a mile.
They are trespassing.
That means they're
kinda like villains.
Why don't we just beat 'em up?
Don't you even think about it.
Unless you want your name
dragged through the mud.
Let's wait for the cops.
[PRESENT MIC groans]
I was afraid it was some
kind of attack on the school,
but there's no need
to worry, everyone!
[STUDENT C]
Ow!
[STUDENT D]
Sorry, I think I...
[STUDENT E]
Back off!
[TENYA]
Where're the teachers?
Why aren't they taking control?
[KIRISHIMA]
Everyone! Stop freakin' out!
[TENYA]
Kirishima! Kaminari!
[KAMINARI]
The current's too strong!
[TENYA] Am I the only one here
who realizes everything's fine?
There's no reason for
us to be panicking!
[OCHACO yelps]
[TENYA]
Uraraka!
Tenya, help me!
[grunts]
[TENYA]
What would Midoriya do?
Or my brother? How would
they handle this?
[TENYA gasps]
[yelps]
[TENYA]
I have an idea!
Huh?
[TENYA]
Touch my hand.
Make me float above
everyone else!
Oh.
[TENYA] I need a place where
I'll get everyone's attention!
Engine Boost, go!
[IZUKU grunts]
[TENYA yelping]
What're you doing?
[TENYA] This is it. Be concise,
clear, and confident.
Make an impact!
Listen up, everything is okay!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[gasps]
[TENYA]
It's just the media outside.
There's absolutely
nothing to worry about.
Everything's fine!
We're UA students.
We need to remain calm and prove
that we're the best of the best.
[STUDENTS sigh, mumble]
[IZUKU gasps]
[STUDENT F]
Look, the police are here!
[STUDENT G]
Thank goodness.
[PRESENT MIC]
That's a wrap.
Get these vultures
out of our station!
[police sirens blaring]
[YAOYOROZU] It's time,
class rep. Let's begin.
Um.
Okay, so we need to figure out
who the other class
officers will be.
But first, there's
something that I wanna say.
I've thought a lot about this.
And I think that Tenya Iida
should be our class rep!
[TENYA gasps]
He was able to capture
everyone's attention
and get us in line.
So I believe
that he should be the one
leading our class from now on!
[gasps]
[KIRISHIMA]
Yeah, you know what?
If Midoriya vouches
for him, I'm good.
Plus he was a big help.
He totally manned up
and took charge, right?
[KAMINARI]
Yup! Oh!
Did you notice he
looked like the dude
on the emergency exit signs
when he was on the wall earlier?
This is a waste of time.
[yelps]
I don't care who the
rep is, just hurry up.
If Midoriya is nominating
me for this job...
...then I humbly accept.
I pledge to carry out
the duties of class rep
to the best of my abilities!
Sounds good, Emergency Exit!
[KAMINARI] Emergency Exit Iida!
Don't let us down, man!
Hello, I got two more
votes than him.
[PRINCIPAL] How were ordinary
members of the press
able to bypass our
security systems?
Someone else must
have been behind this.
Some villain actually managed
to infiltrate our school.
But was this purely a show of
power or a declaration of war?
[panting]
[HEADGEAR]
Don't move.
One step closer, and I'll
kill this whole family.
You don't want the blood
of these damned yuppies
on your hands,
now, do ya, heroes?
[ALL MIGHT]
Never fear, dear citizens!
Missouri Smash!
[HEADGEAR groans]
[ALL MIGHT]
I'm here to keep you safe
even on my morning commute!
[WOMAN A shrieks]
A hit-and-run!
I shouldn't be late for school,
but I can't ignore
someone in need!
[ALL MIGHT]
I've clearly gotten slower.
My powers have been
weakening even faster
since I gave One For All
to Young Midoriya.
I'm pushing my hero form
too far past the limits.
Fighting that Sludge
Villain even though
I was exhausted shortened
the time I can spend
as the Symbol of Peace.
[ALL MIGHT sighs]
[ALL MIGHT]
Wait. You told Bakugo, what?
[IZUKU]
I'm so sorry.
[ALL MIGHT grunts]
[IZUKU] I didn't even tell
my mom about any of this,
but for some reason, I felt like
I had to explain it to him.
Like it was only
fair that he knew.
[ALL MIGHT] Midoriya isn't
the type of person
who wants to show off.
That's not the reason
he shared our secret,
so I didn't lecture
him too much.
Don't look so sad.
He didn't take you seriously,
so I don't think
he'll say anything.
This time I'll let things slide.
Just make sure this
doesn't happen again.
You need to think
carefully about
the responsibility that
comes with this power.
If word got out
that One For All
could be passed on,
villains across the globe
would come for you,
trying to take it.
You must keep this
secret to ensure
your own wellbeing, true.
But also for the
safety of the world.
[gasps]
[ALL MIGHT]
Understand?
[ALL MIGHT] Even if he is
a more suitable vessel now,
he's still a 15-year-old boy.
I have to make sure
I guide him well.
[TOWNSPERSON A] There's a
hostage situation across town!
[ALL MIGHT growls]
[AIZAWA] Today's training
will be a little different.
You'll have three instructors.
Me, All Might, and
another faculty member
will be keeping tabs on you.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[IZUKU] Three pros? Is that
because of the break in?
Sir! What kinda
training is this?
[AIZAWA]
Rescue.
You'll be dealing with
natural disasters,
shipwrecks, stuff like that.
--[STUDENTS chatter]
--Disasters, huh?
Sounds like we're
in for a big workout.
[ASHIDO]
Totally!
Real hero stuff.
This is what separates
the men from the boys.
I'm shakin' with excitement.
Finally, I'll get to show off
how good I am in water. Ribbit.
[AIZAWA]
Guys, I'm not finished yet.
[STUDENTS gasp]
What you wear in this
exercise is up to you.
I know you're excited
about costumes...
[AIZAWA] ...but keep in mind
that you haven't gotten
used to them yet, and they
might limit your abilities.
This special training's
at an off-campus facility,
so we'll be taking
a bus to get there.
That's all. Start getting ready.
[IZUKU] Rescue training.
I've been waiting for this.
It'll bring me one step closer
to being the kind of hero
he is. I'll do my best.
[OCHACO] Deku? Why are you
wearing your PE clothes?
Where's your costume at?
You saw it after
the combat training.
It was kinda trashed.
I'm still waiting on the
support company to fix it up.
[whistle blows]
Gather around, Class 1-A!
Using your student numbers,
form two neat lines
so we can load the
bus efficiently.
[IZUKU] Iida's kicking it into
high gear as our class rep, huh?
[TENYA] The bus's open layout
ruined my boarding strategy.
Iida, you really need to chill.
If we're pointing
out the obvious,
then there's something I wanna
say... about you, actually.
About me? What is it, Asui?
I told you to call me "Tsu."
Oh. Yeah, right.
That power of yours. Isn't it
a lot like All Might's?
[IZUKU yelps]
What? Really? You think so, huh?
I never really
thought about that.
I guess it's kinda similar...
Wait, hold on, Tsu.
You're forgetting All Might
doesn't hurt himself.
That makes a huge difference.
[sighs]
Still, I bet it's cool to have
a simple augmenting-type
a' Quirk.
You can do lots of
flashy stuff with it.
My Hardening's super
strong and can destroy
bad guys in a fight,
but it doesn't look
all that impressive.
Oh, no way, I think it's
really awesome looking.
You're definitely pro material
with a Quirk like that.
You really think so?
Seems like it'd be easier
to be a popular hero
if I had somethin' flashier.
My Navel Laser's got
the perfect combination
of panache and strength.
But it's way lame
if it gives you
a stomachache, sweetie.
Well, if any of our
classmates have
pro Quirks, it's
Todoroki and Bakugo.
Sure, but Bakugo's always angry,
so he'll never be that popular.
[KATSUKI] Uh-- What'd you
say? I'll kick your ass!
Ya see?
Y'know, we basically
just met you.
So it's kinda telling that
we all know your personality
is flaming crap
mixed with garbage.
You're gonna regret
the day you applied
to this school, you loser...!
[IZUKU] I can't believe
what I'm hearing.
Kacchan's the one in class
who's getting teased.
UA is so confusing!
[KAMINARI]
Wait, what did you say?
[YAOYOROZU] This is such
a disgusting conversation.
Yeah, but it's kind of fun
listening to them fight.
[KATSUKI]
Like hell I will.
Hey, hey, we're here.
Stop messing around.
--[STUDENTS] Yes, sir.
--[KATSUKI] Whatever.
[THIRTEEN] Hello, everyone,
I've been waiting for you!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[IZUKU]
It's the Space Hero, Thirteen!
The chivalrous pro who's
rescued a ton of people
from disasters across the world!
Woo-hoo!
Thirteen is one of
my favorite heroes!
[THIRTEEN] I can't wait
to show you what's inside!
[STUDENTS]
This is gonna be awesome!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[KIRISHIMA]
Holy crap!
It looks like some
kind of amusement park!
[THIRTEEN]
A shipwreck. A landslide.
A fire. A windstorm. Et cetera--
I created this training
facility to prepare you
to deal with different
types of disasters.
I call it the Unforeseen
Simulation Joint.
But, you can call it, USJ!
[STUDENTS] Just like
Universal Studios Japan.
Hey, shouldn't All Might
be here already?
Lemme guess, he booked
an interview instead.
[THIRTEEN]
Actually, it's something else.
[AIZAWA]
Hm?
[THIRTEEN] Apparently he
did too much hero work
on the way to
school this morning
and used up all his power.
He's resting in the
teacher's lounge.
I'm sorry.
I should be able to
catch the tail end
of the rescue exercises.
I'll be there as soon as I can.
That man is the height
of irresponsibility.
[AIZAWA] Well, we should be
okay with just the two of us.
The clock's ticking.
We should get started.
[THIRTEEN]
Excellent.
Before we begin, let me
just say one thing.
Well, maybe two things.
Possibly three, four, or five.
[STUDENTS]
We get it!
[THIRTEEN]
Listen carefully.
I'm sure you're aware that
I have a powerful Quirk.
It's called Black Hole.
I can use it to suck up anything
and turn it into dust.
Yeah, you've used
Black Hole to save people
from all kinds of disasters
before, haven't you?
[THIRTEEN] That's true,
but my Quirk could also
very easily be used to kill.
[OCHACO, TENYA, IZUKU gasp]
[THIRTEEN]
Some of you also have powers
that can be dangerous.
[TENYA, IZUKU, OCHACO]
Oh...
[THIRTEEN]
In our superhuman society,
all Quirks are certified
and stringently regulated,
so we often overlook how
unsafe they can actually be.
Please don't forget
that if you lose focus
or make the wrong move,
your powers can be deadly.
Even if you're trying
to do something virtuous
like rescue someone.
Thanks to Aizawa's
fitness tests,
you have a solid idea of
your Quirk's potential.
And because of All Might's
combat training,
you likely experienced how
dangerous your powers can be
when used against other people.
Carry those lessons
over to this class.
Today, you're going to
learn how to use your Quirks
to save people's lives.
You won't be using your powers
to attack enemies or
each other, only to help.
After all, that's what
being a hero is all about.
Ensuring the safety of others.
[IZUKU]
Thirteen is so cool!
[THIRTEEN]
That's all I have to say.
Thank you so much for listening.
[STUDENTS cheer]
Right. Now that that's over...
[STUDENTS gasp]
[AIZAWA grunts]
[grunts]
Stay together and don't move!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[AIZAWA]
Thirteen. Protect the students!
Whoa, what is that thing?
[IZUKU gasps]
Wait, has the training
started already?
I thought we were
rescuing people.
[AIZAWA]
Stay back!
[gasps]
[AIZAWA] This is real.
Those are villains.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[IZUKU] We thought we were
going to be practicing
saving other people's lives that
day, but when they appeared,
we realized we were
the ones in danger.
[IZUKU] Asui. The villains
are attacking us!
[TSUYU]
I told you, call me "Tsu."
[IZUKU] Is this really the
time to be correcting me?
Next time: "Encounter
with the Unknown."
[TSUYU] Oh, so that's why
Mineta's hair is like that.
Now I get it.
[IZUKU]
Let's Go beyond!
[TSUYU, IZUKU]
Plus Ultra!