[IZUKU]
Heroes. I've admired them
since I was just a little kid.
And I dream of being
one in the future.
[IZUKU] It all started
with a video online.
[ALL MIGHT laughs]
[MAN ON VIDEO 1A]
Look! He's got more!
[ALL MIGHT laughs]
[gasping]
Fear not, citizens.
Hope has arrived.
Because I am here.
[yells]
[IZUKU]
After seeing that grinning pro
save so many people,
I started learning everything
I could about heros.
[IZUKU]
I studied because I wanted to be
just like him when I grew up.
[IZUKU] Eighty percent of the
population of this world
has some kind of
uncanny superpower.
Those abilities
are called Quirks.
Since people started
manifesting them,
there's been one profession
that's dominated
all of our minds.
[IZUKU] With the explosion
of crime and disasters
brought about by Quirks,
humanity needed people
to protect the innocent.
We gave the name to those
brave enough to take action:
Heroes.
They're the ones who put
thier lives on the line,
who defend us from evil.
Without them,
diabolical villians
would destroy our
cities, our lives--
maybe even the planet.
Then there's him.
Now that I am here, that is!
[IZUKU]
The greatest among them...
All Might!
The Symbol of Peace and Justice.
He lives up to his title
of "Number One Hero."
No matter the situation,
he always save people with
a huge smile on his face.
I admit, I'm kind of
obsessed with him.
I admire All Might with
every ounce of my being.
[IZUKU]
Oh, yeah.
I'm Izuku Midoriya.
[IZUKU] Right now, I'm
working hard every day,
putting my all into
trying to become a hero.
[IZUKU] That's why, despite
what I'm about to tell you,
this isn't actually a sad story.
[IZUKU]
Back then...
Sorry, kid, it's
not gonna happen.
[DOCTOR 1A] Based on the
research that's available,
it's safe to say your son
isn't going to develop a Quirk.
[IZUKU] This was the harsh
reality I had to face
when I was only four years old.
My goals of becoming
a hero were dashed.
I was Quirkless.
[BOY 1C]
Deku doesn't have a Quirk.
It's called being "Quirkless."
[BOY 1A]
He's so lame!
Jeez, Izuku.
You really can't do
anything right, can you?
Look! You can read the last part
of Izuku's name as "Deku."
Deku...
That must be what you
call a helpless loser
who's completely useless.
Why are you being
so mean, Kacchan?
[STUDENTS cheer]
[TEACHER 1A] Yes, yes, you've
got some very impressive Quirks.
I know you all want to
go into the hero track!
Oh, yeah, Midoriya, don't
you wanna go to UA, too?
[STUDENTS laugh]
[STUDENT 1C] Midoriya?
You're kidding, right?!
[STUDENT 1B] There's no
way you're getting into
the hero course
without a Quirk!
[KATSUKI growls]
[KATSUKI]
Listen up, Deku!
You're even worse
than the rest of these
damn rejects,
you Quirkless wannabe.
You really think they'd let
someone like you in
when they could have me?
[screams]
That's so mean.
[IZUKU screams]
[IZUKU] Even though
I didn't have a Quirk,
I couldn't just
give up on my goal.
[IZUKU]
Which is a good thing.
Because, sometimes in this
world, unexpected things happen.
[grunts]
[IZUKU]
Is that... All... Might?
[ALL MIGHT]
Sorry about that back there.
I didn't mean to get you
caught up in my justicing.
[IZUKU] The real thing...
Standing right in front of me!
He looks so much
cooler in person!
One second!
Is it possible to become a hero,
even if I don't have a Quirk?
[IZUKU] I'm a normal kid
without any powers.
Could I ever hope to
be someone like you?
[IZUKU whimpers]
[IZUKU screams]
[IZUKU]
I-- Wait. Who--?
What happened, you deflated!
I assure you that I am All M--
[screams]
Impossible!
Pretty gross, right?
I got this in a big
fight five years back.
Right now I can
only do hero work
for about three hours a day.
The rest of the time,
this is what I look like.
Pro heroes are always
having to risk their lives.
It's not bad to have
a dream, young man.
Just make sure your
dreams are attainable.
Realistic. Understand?
[CROWD screaming]
[WOMAN]
It's a monster!
[ONLOOKER 2D] Why aren't the
heroes doing anything?
[ONLOOKER 2E] It looks like
they've met their match.
Plus the villain captured a kid.
Things aren't lookin'
good for him.
[ALL MIGHT]
So pathetic.
[KATSUKI grunting]
[IZUKU gasps]
[ALL gasping]
[IZUKU panting]
[DEATH ARMS]
No, you idiot! Stop!
You're gonna get
yourself killed!
[IZUKU]
What am I doing?
Why am I running?
Why can't I stop?
[SLUDGE VILLAIN 1A]
You're toast, kid!
[IZUKU]
What do I do?
What would a hero do right now?
Page 25! Right!
[IZUKU]
Take this!
[SLUDGE VILLIAN 1A groans]
[gasping, coughing]
Kacchan!
What the hell?
Why are you here?
I dunno. My legs...
They just started... moving!
[IZUKU] I'm not sure
exactly why I acted.
[DOCTOR 1A] Sorry, kid,
it's not gonna happen.
--[IZUKU] I'm the one to blame.
--[KATSUKI] You really think
they'd let someone
like you in...
[IZUKU] I've wanted to be
a hero since I was little...
There's always a
smile on his face...
[ALL MIGHT] I honestly don't
think you can become a hero
without a Quirk.
[IZUKU] All I could think
in that moment was...
Kacchan!
I couldn't just stand there
and watch you die!
[ALL MIGHT gasps]
[KATSUKI]
Get the hell off me!
[ALL MIGHT] I have to do
something. No matter the cost.
[SLUDGE VILLAIN 1A]
Just a little bit longer, kid.
And I'm done playing with you!
[DEATH ARMS] Save the boy!
This thing'll kill him!
[ALL MIGHT]
I really am pathetic.
[gasps]
[IZUKU]
All Might. But...
I told you the traits that
make a great champion,
but I see now I wasn't
living up to my own ideal.
Pros are always
risking their lives!
That's the true test of a hero!
[SLUDGE VILLAIN 1A]
Damn you, All Might!
Detroit... Smash!
[CROWD cheering]
[CROWD cheers]
[IZUKU]
Is it possible to become a hero,
even if I don't have a Quirk?
Could I ever hope to be
someone like you?
[ALL MIGHT] There are
stories about every hero.
How they became great.
Most have one thing in common.
[ALL MIGHT]
Their bodies moved
before they had
a chance to think.
Almost on their own.
[IZUKU whimpers]
And today, that's
what happened to you.
[sobbing]
Young man, you, too,
can become a hero.
[sobbing]
[IZUKU]
Like I said,
unexpected things happen.
The impossible can
become achievable.
[ALL MIGHT] Young man,
you, too, can become a hero.
I deem you worthy of my power.
My Quirk is yours to inherit.
Huh?
I wasn't born with this power.
It's a sacred torch
that was passed onto me
from someone else.
Someone gave you this Quirk?
No way.
[ALL MIGHT]
Yes way.
And you're next.
I can give you my abilities.
Okay, I'll do it.
Yes!
[IZUKU] And so began my
ten months of total hell.
[ALL MIGHT]
Put your back into it
and drag it all the way
to the park's entrance.
Get that tire into the truck!
This is what it takes
to be a hero, kid.
Hustle! Go!
[IZUKU yelling]
[ALL MIGHT]
Only a few minutes to spare.
But you exceeded
my expectations!
Holy...
...stinkin'...
...supercrap!
Take that to heart, young man.
This gift:
You earned it with your
own valiant efforts.
[IZUKU]
My dream was becoming reality.
It was almost like I was living
in a comic book or something.
Eat this.
Huh?
[IZUKU] The hero I admired most
trusted me with his power,
and with his secret,
and, unbelievably,
before I knew it,
I was taking the entrance
exam to get into UA High,
the most pretigious
training school for heros.
Are you ready?
[gasps]
[IZUKU]
Smash!
I wish I could go back in time
and tell four-year-old me
that everything
was gonna be okay.
You both passed the exam.
[IZUKU] That, if you work
hard and don't give up,
wonderful, life-altering
things can happen to you.
Even if you are just
a Quirkless nobody.
Welcome, Izuku.
You have made it.
You're now part of
the hero academia!
[IZUKU] After that, my high
school career at UA began.
And things got nuts...
Show me it's no mistake
that you're here.
[IZUKU] You see, my classmates
and I all want to be pro heros.
The teachers can be
a little hard on us...
We have to go all-out.
[OCHACO panting]
[IZUKU]
I have to work way harder
than everyone else here
if I wanna succeed.
Smash!
[STUDENTS gasp]
This kid...
[KATSUKI growls] I'm getting
to the bottom of this.
Hey!
[IZUKU]
Kacchan has it in for me,
but that's nothing new.
and since I was
Quirkless until recently,
I have to work twice
as hard as him.
That's the only way I can
keep up with anyone.
[growls]
[gasps]
[screams]
[KATSUKI]
Deku!
Don't you ever forget
what you are!
You're a weakling!
Smash!
[IZUKU]
Well...
I guess none of us came
to UA to make friends.
Still...
I found some great ones.
[KIRISHIMA] Man, I don't
know what you were saying
during that match,
but you were all fired up!
[IZUKU] The students
here range from weird
to downright irriplaceable.
I like "Deku."
It could make a great hero name!
Plus, I think it
sounds kinda cute.
[IZUKU]
I've got friends,
and friendly rivals.
[IZUKU] And I'm still
doing my research, too.
I take plenty of notes about
everyone in my hero notebooks.
[IZUKU] First off, my
childhood friend: Kacchan.
He can secrete
nitroglycerin-like sweat
from his hands and
make it explode.
He really excells when
it comes to combat--
he even took first place
in the entrance exam.
[IZUKU] Uraraka can make
anything she touches
totally weightless.
Plus, she can
make herself float!
The only thing is, if she
uses her Quirk too much...
It can get messy.
So she has to be careful.
Simply put, Iida can
run really fast.
Apparently, he can increase
his speed in stages.
His accelerated kick
is crazy powerful.
Then there's Todoroki.
His Quirk lets him freeze
with his right hand
and burn with his left.
At least, that's what I hear.
He only ever shows us
what his ice powers can do.
Asui's abilities allow her to
swim super fast under water,
jump really high,
and even cling to walls.
So, basically,
whatever a frog can do.
The balls on Mineta's head
will stick like glue
to anything they touch.
He can't pick off
too many though,
or he'll start bleeding.
[IZUKU]
That's not everyone.
All my classmates
have incredible Quirks.
We're constantly training
and trying to figure out
how we can use our powers
to their fullest potential.
Not just when we're fighting.
There might be lots of other
ways for us to use our Quriks
that we haven't even
begun to think of yet.
[IZUKU]
The teachers that guide us at UA
are all impressive, too.
They're pro heros.
[IZUKU] Mr. Aizawa can erase the
Quirks of anyone he looks at.
He's also an agile fighter,
particularly when he uses
the special cloth
wrapped around his neck
to snare a bunch of
villians at the same time.
And then, of course,
the greatest pro ever is
a teacher at UA this year.
The Number One hero:
All Might.
His Quirk can be used to channel
overwhelming amounts of power.
It's known as "One For All."
[ALL MIGHT]
Texas... Smash!
[IZUKU] He's got a bunch
of different Smash attacks
in his arsenal.
And his ability to
jump long distances
definitely comes in handy.
I've inherited
All Might's power.
Though I can't really
control it yet...
[IZUKU] It looks like it's
going to take some time
for me to make his Quirk my own.
But that just means I have
to keep pushing myself.
I won't stop.
I'm positive I'll become
a legendary superhero
like him one day.
[RECOVERY GIRL] Do you have
to be the "Symbol of Peace"?
Is it that important?
If they knew I wasn't,
the temptation of this power
could corrupt our society.
This Quirk...
Those who wield it
are responsible for
mankind's safety.
[IZUKU] So, yeah. Everyone
at UA is pretty incredible.
But what's the point
of having these Quirks?
What should we be
doing with them?
And why did we all fight
so hard to get into UA?
Why are we trying to be heros?
At the heart of the matter,
there's only one motivation.
We want to help people.
And to do that, we have to be
able to take on villians.
That's a lesson we
learned the hard way--
far earlier than any
of us expected to.
The day that we were
attacked while training.
When we met pure evil.
[SHIGARAKI]
Hey.
What do you think'll happen...
...when the mighty
Symbol of Peace...
...is finally killed
by the villains?
[IZUKU]
Tomura Shigaraki.
The boss of a group
calling themselves
the League of Villains.
He has a fearsome Quirk
that lets him disintegrate
anything or anyone he
touches in an instant.
[SHIGARAKI] You think you're
the Symbol of Peace?
Ha.
You're just another
government-sponsored
instrument of violence.
[SHIGARAKI]
Nomu. Kurogiri.
Kill him.
[ALL MIGHT]
I'm afraid that I barely
have a minute left in this form.
My power's declining faster
than I thought it would.
[SHIGARAKI] Let's clear
this level and go home.
[ALL MIGHT] Even so, I have
to stop these villains.
Because I am...
[ALL MIGHT] ...the world's
Symbol of Peace and Justice!
[ALL MIGHT yells]
[ALL MIGHT yelling]
He's gonna fight that
brain guy head on?
Whoa, they're... so fast!
[KUROGIRI]
No! I can't get near them!
[ALL MIGHT] He said your Quirk
was only shock absorption
not nullification.
That means there's a limit
to what you can take, right?
[ALL MIGHT groans, growls]
[ALL MIGHT] So, you were
made to fight me, big guy.
If you can really
withstand me firing
at 100 percent of my power...
...then I'll have to go beyond
that and force you to surrender.
[IZUKU] He's giving it his all
even though he's injured!
Those aren't just
random punches, either.
They're targeted, and every
single one of them...
...is more than 100
percent of his power.
[yells]
[ALL MIGHT]
A real hero...
[ALL MIGHT] ...will always find
a way for justice to be served!
[ALL MIGHT yelling]
[ALL MIGHT]
Now for a lesson.
You may have heard
these words before,
but I'll teach you
what they really mean.
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!
[IZUKU]
Thanks to All Might's help,
and the bravery of my
teachers and classmates,
we were able to escape.
The whole experience made us
more resolved than ever
to become powerful,
fearless heros,
so we can stop evil.
So we can protect the world.
Those villains made
a mistake attacking them.
This class is strong.
They're filled with
courage and drive.
Mark my words.
They'll become great heroes.
[IZUKU] And now, a life-changing
event is about to take place--
the UA Sports Festival.
After surviving a fight
with real villains,
I'm sure everyone will be
even more focused than before.
I know I will be.
I'm going to give
everything I've got.
[IZUKU]
What is justice?
What does it mean to be a hero?
I'm still figuring all that out,
but I have learned some things.
It's okay to fall.
It's okay to cry.
You just have to
keep moving forward.
You have to go beyond!
Plus Ultra!
[IZUKU] The new season
of My Hero Academia
is finally about to begin!
Don't miss the UA Sports
Festival that everyone's
going to be watching.
The student who
wins the competition
will basically have their future
as a pro hero in the bag.
Everyone'll be
fighting for the top.
We're all enrolled
in this school
to become pros, after all.
So you bet I'm
gonna give it my all!
Next time:
"That's the Idea, Ochaco"!
Uraraka finally tells
us why she's here.
Go beyond!
Plus Ultra!