[MAN] Well, skit.
What the cripes?
We don't get hardly
any tourists anymore.
I don't care what it takes;
I gotta get popular again
like real quick.
Hi. Nice to meet
you--I'm Iceland.
A new character.
[ICELAND] Hetalia!
Hetalia! Hetalia!
[hurried footsteps]
[WOMAN pants]
[breathless]
[WOMAN sobs] Please!
Somebody help me!
[gasps]
[high-pitched pop]
[bloopy footsteps]
[WOMAN yells]
[multiple bloopy footsteps]
[bloopy footsteps]
[WOMAN groans]
[whimpers]
[AMERICA] Dudes,
this is an emergency!
As the paper thing in front of
you with those crazy drawings
that are supposedly words says,
a majority of humanity has been
turned into NOPPERA ghostie
blobs by the freaky beam
of light that shoots out
of the other NOPPERA-BOU
or bow or bah, I don't
really know how to say it.
Tony, my righteous
alien dude friend,
told me they're Pictonians
from the planet Picto!
For real dudes; Picto's in
like way far outer space.
Your brain's in way
far outer space!
Dude, they're born
looking like NOPPERA,
--and they want everyone else...
--[ITALY] A little smile for ya!
...hello?!
Listen up! We can't
let these NOPPERA dudes
make Earth all freaky and
boringly white, right?
This is whack! We gotta stop
those dudes! Who's with me?
Also, what's a NOPPERA?
[JAPAN] Oh, yes.
I know what they are.
Huh?
[JAPAN] It is a Japanese
monster without a nose, eyes,
or a mouth. It's proper name
is the NOPPERA-BOU. Okay?
Wait a tic. Are you
trying to say this
is all your fault, Japan?
No! I was simply explaining
what NOPPERA means.
No more, no less.
Why the hell do I have
to be turned into NOPPERA
because of stupid
Japan and scary stories?
[JAPAN] It's not my fault!
Focus countries! Japan may
have screwed things up,
but we still have
time to fix it!
Now, your ideas will all
suck, so listen to me!
We'll combine all of
our military strength!
I'll be in command, so you can
all wear the colors of my flag!
All heroes wear red,
white and blue!
[ITALY] I think we should gather
under the white flag! Flap!
Why in God's name would
we put you in charge?
Duh. I'm the hero.
Everybody knows that.
I beg to differ.
Everybody knows
I've got the biggest~
No one asked you,
cheesy monkey!
Shut up, Black
Sheep of Europe!
I've told you not
to call me that!
[sighs] They never
stop fighting.
White flags! Come on! I made
a whole lot of them! See?
We can each wave
our very own!
[gasp]
So you think
I'm right, right?
Uh. Well. This is
why I sense the mood
and refrain
from speaking.
Russia! What are
you gonna do, dude?
I'm going to
do fighting.
Rock out, my dog! I've
got the perfect job
for you to have then!
Back up sidekick!
What?
Yeah. Every superhero
needs a sidekick.
I should know; I am the
hero! They even make
big budget Hollywood crazy
good movies about it.
We also have top-notch
productions in the UK!
Um, time traveling phone
booths can only go so far.
Shut it, Pepe Le Pew!
Just because you invented
movie making doesn't mean
you're any good at it!
All your films are good
for is putting me to sleep!
I'll have you know,
my movies have been
very popular lately!
Dude, you
can't compete
with Michael Bay sequels!
[CHINA] That attitude is
why I restrict your films!
Mine are more
quietly artistic
with cultural
storytelling.
My movies are the most fun
ones if you want to ask me!
[COUNTRIES bicker]
[GERMANY growls]
That is enough!
While you sit here arguing
about nothing, more of mankind
are being turned into those
NOPPERA or Pictonians or
whatever they're called!
Now listen, if we are
turned into those things,
that will mean we lose our
faces, so we won't be able
to recognize any one
of us from the other.
Think about it, you dummkopfs!
[FRANCE] I will never accept
your opinion...
[BRITAIN] ...beautiful
like a horse's arse!
[laughs] No need to
argue, 'cause I'm right.
I know my ideas are
best because otherwise
I'd kill them.
I'm only allowed to
hear my own thoughts;
and those are the ones I like.
[COUNTRIES chatter]
[breathes tensely]
[exasperated sigh]
All right, then.
I'm done here.
[BRITAIN and FRANCE gasp]
[GERMANY] I don't know why
I even thought we could have
a simple discussion.
That's not how we work, is it?
What a waste. This entire
meeting has been pointless.
I will do what I have to do,
and you do what you have to.
[door slams]
That's exactly what
I was going to say.
There's too much fighting
together to figure out
if we should fight
together anyway.
I am far too gorgeous
to have been in such
a stuffy room for so long.
"I am far too gorgeous
to--" shut up, France.
I was just trying to help.
I don't need you guys;
I'm the hero!
Oh. My belly. It hurts.
[gasp]
Hey, wait up you guys;
c'mon, don't leave me
in here by myself!
I'm still here. And,
I hate to complain,
but no one even bothered
to ask my opinion.
Who are you?
I'm Canada.
♪
Hey! Hey! Hey! It's
"Dancetime I'm Awesome"!
The popular singing show
made for me and also by me,
because I am Awesome Prussia!
Now let's get us started,
shall we? Today, we've
got Ukraine and Belarus!
They're singing
"Carrot and A Stick"!
"Carrot and A Stick".
[A.D.] Sorry, sir. They
cancelled last minute.
They did what?! Who do
they think they are,
the White Stripes?
I am sorry! My big
boobies make my back hurt,
so I didn't think
I could perform well.
Brother Russia?
Where are you?
Why did you leave me here with
Double D Means Double Dumb?
[BELARUS] Hurry up and
come out, or I'll find you!
[PRUSSIA] Hetalia!
[UKRAINE] Hetalia!
[BELARUS] Hetalia!
♪
[bloopy sounds]
[PEOPLE gasp]
Okay, dudes!
It's time to kick ass!
As the heroes, we'll
intercept their lame attack
with mad skills!
[AMERICAN PILOT] Roger!
Oh crap!
[RUSSIA laughs]
Now you can see
what happens when you play
with big unstable guns.
Or maybe not.
[CHINA] We will stop
them at Red Cliffs!
[CHINA gasps]
Suck ball!
I knew fortune cookie
this morning was
full of bad lie!
Bastards! You're
dealing with
a former pirate, now!
[shocked grunt]
[FRANCE] What kind
of name is NOPPERA,
and why do you not express
any kind of individuality?
Unfortunately trying to
make me bland is unforgivable,
so consider yourself punished.
No!!
[GERMANY] Do not allow them
to come anywhere close to us!
Understood?
[GERMAN SOLDIER] Jawohl.
[rumbling]
Here they come.
[gasps]
Germany! Germany!
I know I say this a lot,
but this time
I really mean it!
Please, Germany, help me!
Help me! Help me! Help me!
[ITALIANS scream]
Germany, we've
got trouble.
The enemy is
attacking!
[yells]
[GERMANY] Nein!
[JAPAN BOSS A sighs] It sounds
like those Mujina pranksters
in Hawaii.
[JAPAN BOSS B] Oh, yeah.
I heard of them before.
Some sort of faceless
ghost mumbo jumbo.
[JAPAN BOSS C] Either way.
We can't just leave things
how they are, can we?
[ALL THREE BOSSES] Mmmm.
[ALL THREE BOSSES] Can we?
Maybe we should continue
this matter on another day.
No! We haven't yet
decided what to do!
Whaaa?!
[ROMANO] What the
crapola happened here?
And where is my stupid
brother anyway, eh?
[ROMANO as PICTONIAN] Assholes!
[PONY neighs]
[gasps]
Pony! I'm so
glad to finding you!
I looked like everywhere!
Why you look at me like that
with the no eyes?
[PONY as PICTONIAN]
Ahhh...
I can't wait!
Christmas is coming!
[FINLAND as PICTONIAN]
Ho. Ho. Ho.
[GREECE] I love cats. Is there
something wrong with that?
[gasp]
[concerned sound]
[shocked sound]
[gasp]
[sad moan]
[LIECHTENSTEIN]
Hey, Big Brother? I'm happy.
I thought you should know.
Okay. Yeah, whatever.
[electric hissing]
[ITALY] Hetalia!
Okay, brainstorm on
bringing down the Axis--
I'll start off,
so listen carefully--
I think it's all Mr. Schnitzel's
fault, personally. I bet he's
secretly in love with Italy. How
can he not see how wrong it is?
Eh, get it? 'Not see.'
I can't understand a
single word you're saying.
Would you please
just stop eating?
My vocabulary
can be intimidating.
I'll stop eating this
absurd pile of hamburgers
so you can focus better.
[sucks through straw]
Axis [sucks] bad guys [sucks].
Allies [sucks] good guys
[sucks]. And the hero is me!
Oh shut it!
[AMERICA] Hetalia!
[typewriter sound]
[RUSSIA] Okay.
So all I have to do is
jump out of this plane
and attack them, right?
[CHINA] That's right.
Put on your parachute now.
Don't be silly, there's
plenty of snow on the ground.
It'll break my fall
because it's soft.
What? I don't
think that's right.
I'm Russian, I know
everything about snow.
Well, see ya around.
[RUSSIA] Vodkaaa!
Hey, see this? It says
Russia broke his back
jumping from a plane
without a parachute.
Oh yeah? Hey. Why
don't you go surrender
to the maid or invent
some new cheese?
Why are you here?
Because, I like to mess
with your needlework.
[RUSSIA] Hetalia.
Count off!
Just me.
It's time to start
our training.
We'll begin with the proper way
to treat your subordinates.
Sig heil. I
mean, yes sir!
Sehr gut. First,
remember that
other people are humans.
You have to treat them
both with
kindness and respect.
With kindness,
right, pookie?
Sometimes
with discipline!
Discipline! Got it!
Naughty pookie.
Naughty naughty naughty naughty
pookie sweetie naughty---
Ow that really hurts.
Help me, Germany!
It's attacking me. Make it
stop! Oh it hurts so bad...
What is your
problem, Italy?
[ITALY] Hetalia.
Count off!
Uno!
Ni!
All right! You've
made it halfway,
so its time to test
your the training and see
what you're made of.
[ITALY and JAPAN] Yes, sir!
[GERMANY paced breaths]
[ITALY weak breaths]
[ITALY whines]
[GERMANY paced breaths]
[ITALY cries]
Italy! That pace is
never going to cut it.
We are not going to lunch
until you finish your laps.
[ITALY whines breathlessly]
[GERMANY] Amazing. It's as
if he is solely motivated
by food or the
prospect of women.
[ITALY cries]
Where're you going?
It's no time to skip out
on training!
[ITALY] Britain is
going to get me!
[GERMANY] Italy?
For crying out loud,
you need to learn to run this
fast when you're not in retreat!
So it was proven true
that Italian tank advance
60 mile a week, but are somehow
able to retreat at 60 mile
a day when they see
the British coming.
Meow.
[GERMANY] We're done with our
training for today! Come back!
[JAPAN] Hetalia!
[GERMANY] Scheiße. It looks like
being turned into Pictonians
is a fate we will
all share, now.
I refuse to accept
being as ugly
as the rest of you!
Look on the bright side,
at least you won't smell
like drunk cheese anymore.
Are you guys
hungry at all?
[AMERICA] Chill out! We're not
gonna let this get us down!
Dude, we're gonna
stand together
whether we like it
or not! I don't.
[RUSSIA] I agree!
I don't like it.
[CHINA] That's right! We should
fight together against them
even if we hate it! I hate it.
I hate it more.
Oui. Je déteste.
[JAPAN] No likey, but
we might as well listen
to each others' opinions.
[GERMANY] All right!
Raise your hand if you want
to work together. Now!
[ALL but ITALY mumble]
[ITALY] Pasta!
Meow!
Check this out.
A dose of originality!
We get a huge hero.
He repels attacks with
his deflector shield and beats
the crap outta those lameoes.
In that case, I think
Japan should do it.
I mean he's got
Evan[beep], right?
And don't forget
about Gun[beep]!
But those are
just anime!
If you talking anime,
I can totally handle that.
[CHINA'S HERO] Hame Kame Ha!
You know, I feel like
I've heard that before,
but better.
[ALL but ITALY and CHINA]
Yeah. I do, too.
It original Chinese idea!
[GERMANY] Idioten.
[ALL] Huh?
Why don't we,
oh, I don't know,
try coming up with
something realistic?
I was thinking
the same thing!
My idea's perfectly realistic.
Ta-da!
[ALL] Yeah.
We need something realistic.
You wankers!
Don't ignore me!
[TONY] Fucking. Fucking.
Fucking. Fucking. Fucking...
Oh. What a
charming alien.
He's no alien! Tony
is my best friend!
That doesn't mean
he's not an alien!
[AMERICA] Dude, Tony!
What's the scoop, brah?
[TONY] Fucking bitch. Bitch...
[AMERICA] That's a trip!
Here's the deal.
Tony said he got a totally
top secret picture from
the Bureau of
Space Development!
[BRITAIN and FRANCE]
How'd he understand that?
All I heard was 'fucking'.
[TONY] Bitchy!
[BRITAIN] Oh, come on, now.
That is obviously photoshopped!
[laughs] Sorry, man,
that's just Tony's style.
Tony, quit busting our balls.
Dude, we're trying to be
serious here!
[TONY] Bitch fuck.
Seriously? You
better be telling me
the truth, dude!
[TONY] Bitchy.
Rock out! Thanks
a butt load, Tony!
What is it? What did
your weird friend say?
[AMERICA] Well, luckily
he wastes a lot of time on
the most popular porn and
intergalactic message boards,
so he was able to track down
the Pictonian's research sight.
Then he hacked into it.
Apparently their password
is just "password".
[BRITAIN] Oh. Bravo for
him being an alien, then.
[AMERICA] Hey! He's my friend!
[FRANCE] Again.
All I heard was "bitchy".
[GERMANY] I can't read
what it says at all!
[AMERICA] Calm
down, dude! Tony!
Start that translation
software thingie!
[TONY] Fucking.
[FEMALE NARRATOR] This pure
white planet is known as Picto.
Achieving what they believe
to be the ultimate form,
they've decided to pursue
galaxy-wide perfection through
a process that uses light
to transform other beings into
their uniform image, referred to
as assimilation. Sound familiar?
[FEMALE NARRATOR coughs]
That's unforgivable!
[FEMALE NARRATOR] According
to nasty, nasty rumors,
the kind known to almost always
be accurate, the Pictonians
decided upon Earth as their very
first target due to its lack
of technological advancement as
well as general intelligence.
IE, they thought
it would be easy.
And truthfully,
the Earth could use
a remedial class in
pretty much everything.
It's famous for social
anxiety, violent outbursts,
intolerance, self-mutilation,
and pouting, which is the worst.
There are other additional
issues, but I'd rather not
get into them. I don't
want to bum you out.
[FRANCE] Apparently
our planet is passé.
[ITALY] Boo.
[RUSSIA] The boo is right.
[TONY] Fucking?
What does he say now?
[AMERICA] The more evolved a
species, the more their faces
look NOPPERA-like.
[RUSSIA] Oh. I have
collection of evolving faces
I'd like to show them.
[GERMANY] Where are they weak?
They have to have weaknesses!
[TONY] They do!
[ALL scream]
[FRANCE] Why haven't you
been speaking English
this whole time?
[TONY] Because
I don't do dubs. Okay.
Their weaknesses are...
[typing on keypad]
[TONY] Let's see. Huh.
[SPAIN] Bueno! This is el
commercial for Café Espana!
We're around the corner from the
cinema, so come have a coffee
at my café, okay? It's
just instant, but still.
For a limited time, I can give
you a tee shirt for cheap.
Special price just for you!
[SPAIN] Hetalia! Hetalia!
[TONY] Hold on. I spelled
weaknesses wrong.
[typing on keypad]
[interference]
[static]
[AMERICA] Tony!
[frantic running]
[AMERICA gasps]
[AMERICA] What on Earth?
[CHINA] It not on Earth.
That is the point.
Damn. The
light's enormous!
I think it's
their mother ship!
[explosion]
[ITALY screams] This is
where I fly backwards!
[FRANCE] Well,
I guess I was right.
[BRITAIN] Yes. That has
to be their mother ship.
[AMERICA laughs]
[AMERICA] Those space
dorks are so predictable.
Oh!
Everybody, take a look!
[ALL gasp]
[bloopy footsteps]
[FRANCE] They are all
going inside of the ship!
[RUSSIA] Well, that's sort of
making the sense. I'd fly
NOPPERA humans back to Picto
for slave labor if I were them.
Unacceptable! We shall not
allow such atrocities!
Let the torture begin.
Germany, I'm sorry
I touched you.
But if we fight sporadically,
we will only end up defeated.
Must kill!
[AMERICA] Hey dudes!
I have an idea. We could
infiltrate their ship
and find their weaknesses!
[CHINA] Yes! I like
the way you thinking!
[BRITAIN] Right. You can
leave the spying to me.
[JAPAN] Nothing ventured,
nothing gained, as they say.
[FRANCE] Exactly
who are "they"?
[ITALY] I have a way
we can all get inside!
[ALL] Huh?
Ta-da!
What the hell?
What is that?
It's my Pictonian costume!
Don't you like it?
I made it from all the
white flag material I have.
Oh! Good news! I made
one for everybody!
[shocked gasps]
[GERMANY] Attack!
[AMERICA laughs]
[AMERICA] Hail the
conquering hero!
[BRITAIN] Double O Ninja!
[FRANCE] What a relief!
I look amazing in white!
[CHINA] Hang on tight, Panda!
[RUSSIA] Hooray death.
[JAPAN] I run into battle!
I'll wait for
you guys here!
Italy! You are coming
inside with us.
What? But I would rather
not. Willingly walking
onto an enemy space ship
seems kinda reckless to me.
Plus I don't want to get
my costume all dirty.
Fine, you can
stay here alone.
[scared gasp]
Being alone is worse
than anything! Wait!
[ITALY] Hetalia!
So, England. I have
something important
to say to you.
I would like for
you to marry me.
[horrified gasp]
That's very
funny, France.
I don't believe it's
April Fools day yet.
What's the
matter Old Chap?
You can't even afford to
buy a calendar anymore?
[nervous laugh]
You are wrong,
mon ami.
And this is
not so funny.
Right. What the hell
is wrong with you?
[FRANCE] Here; take this.
[BRITAIN] That's a marriage
registration form, you idiot!
[BRITAIN gasps, struggles]
No, it's not. Can't you
see? It is a calendar.
It's for you!
It is a calendar!
What's come over you?
Unhand me you foppish twit.
[FRANCE] Just sign it!
[BRITAIN] I will
do no such thing!
[FRANCE] I said sign it!
[BRITAIN] No! Stop it!
[BRITAIN] No! I don't
know what you're up to,
but I don't like it!
[FRANCE] Look, I don't want
any part of this either,
but we don't have
much of a choice!
Come on! Blame the Suez Canal.
That thing's put me
close to bankruptcy!
If I don't get married to you
right away, I overheard my boss
saying that he would
kill me! That would suck!
I will kill you!
[BRITAIN grunts]
That's still not a
satisfactory reason to be wed!
Have at you! Here's what
I think of your damn form!
[FRANCE] No!
What are you doing?
Now you see! That's what
happens when you try
to force people
to marry you, Frog!
[laughs]
You brute! Devil! Don't
you even care if I die?
Please, I'm begging here,
you have to listen.
I can become England's
quaint little French Village
if you want me to.
Come on! Help me!
I will not, fool. Why on
Earth would I ever want
to marry you?
First of all. you
need to learn to deal
with and accept
your failures--
[BRITAIN gasps]
[crazed laugh]
Unhand me this instant
you foul smelling mime lover.
Release me! Let me go!
Turn me loose!
Are you not listening
to me, France?
Lessen that grasp! I said
let me go this minute!
This is rather undignified!
[typewriter sound]
[bell rings]
No. I will be fine.
You will see.
Just you watch me.
I'll be fine. Just fine!
[crazed laugh]
[FRANCE] Hetalia.
Hey Italy. What is that
you're looking at?
Oh. This! My
combat record.
[camera snap]
[old-timey music]
[book slams shut]
[CANADA] Hetalia.
[NEWSCASTER] In
today's news. The entire
world is in crisis.
Luckily, Canada and Cuba
have joined forces.
They've dedicated their time
to assisting the injured.
I'm sure they are a lot
of help, too.
[MAN A] My legs! My legs!
[MAN B] My arms!
It's only half of you;
it could be worse.
You still
have your legs.
Yes. I find that helping
people gives me a warm,
fulfilled feeling.
Who are you?
I'm Canadia.
[CANADA] Hetalia!
[CUBA] Hetalia!
Okay, now do
exactly as I say.
Russia, you can
back me up, dude.
China, you should
back me up, too.
France and Britain, you guys
back me up, and Germany--
Huh?
Pick a lot, find your group,
and start searching.
Don't ignore me!
Damn it. The last
person I'd want
to work with is you.
Pardon moi? Stop
stealing my lines, fool!
Shh!
Quick, Follow me!
[bloopy footsteps]
[FRANCE sighs]
That was a close one.
True, but we
won't allow them
to capture us so easily!
Now, let's go find their
information
room, shall we?
Hey! Don't tell me
what to do, bossy pants!
[AMERICA] Okay, my dudes.
Let's find this ship's cockpit
like pronto, yo!
[CHINA] Then we can
destroy the switch for
the Pictonian's light beam.
[bloopy footsteps]
[AMERICA gasps]
[CHINA gasps]
[PANDA squeals]
[RUSSIA] Never show
enemy the fear.
[bloopy footsteps]
--[AMERICA gasps]
--[CHINA] Ai ya.
[bloopy footsteps]
[BOTH sigh]
So I guess they can't
tell we're different.
[GERMANY and JAPAN pant]
[ITALY] Hey guys!
Where are we going?
We're going to rescue
the earthlings
that were turned
into Pictonians!
We're looking for housing
facility they must
have in here somewhere.
[bloopy footsteps]
[ITALY] Hey!
[ITALY] Oh...
Those guys creep me out!
[gasps]
Germany! Over there!
[GERMANY gasps]
[FRANCE] They have files. Maybe
that's the information room.
Yeah. C'mon!
[BOTH gasp]
[FRANCE] What a gorgeous,
swollen blue ball!
[BRITAIN] It's the Earth, you
idiot. They're probably using it
for their battle plans.
[FRANCE] It looks like the
white areas are the ones
that have already attacked,
and the red dots are where
they're currently attacking.
[BRITAIN] I
can't read it.
[FRANCE] It's not
human, remember?
No worries. I have
a translator app.
[FEMALE NARRATOR] Britain. A
former pirate, but now a rather
effeminate yet gentlemanly
empire with a plethora of rain.
France is a longtime
acquaintance he's often
found bickering with
for bickering's sake.
However, in their heart of
hearts, they love each other.
Sexually.
[BOTH] Uh. Where the
hell did they get that?
[BOTH bicker]
[door slides open]
[BRITAIN] Perhaps this
isn't the best time
to bicker for bickering's sake.
[FRANCE] Oui. I agree.
Fear not, my friend!
In cases like this,
there's always a hidden
door somewhere nearby!
See? Like that!
Yoink!
[BOTH scream]
[FRANCE] You idiot!
We're falling!
[BRITAIN] Yes,
I know; thank you!
[CHINA] No one's in here.
[RUSSIA] I bet it's
their break time.
Perfect! Now,
let's go find that
white blob maker
beam shooting lever!
[CHINA] I don't know.
There are so many switches,
any of them could be it.
[AMERICA] Dude.
Seriously, right?
[RUSSIA] I think it
must be this one here.
[BOTH] Hmm?
You see?
Yeah. It does look like
it could be the one, but--
[CHINA] It's too easy!
It has to be trap!
Oh, relax. It's not
like the floor is gonna
spontaneously fall
if we pull it! Ha ha h--
Ah--
Uh--
[high-pitched tone]
[deafening alarm]
[bloopy stampede]
That's loud!
Let's go!
[bloopy stampede]
[distant alarm]
That's bad. One of
the others must have
tripped the alarm.
[JAPAN] Sounds that way. I hope
that everyone is still safe.
[CAT] Meow!
That's nice.
Italy, you nincompoop!
Why did you bring
a cat with you?
What? He's therapeutic
and relaxing!
Relaxing?!
Dude, what's up?
These guys do not wanna
let us get away!
I thought they couldn't
tell that we looked different!
I starting to get
bad side cramp.
[ALL THREE pant]
[BRITAIN and FRANCE yell]
[ALL yell]
[ALL scream]
Ugh!
Ahh! Ai!
Ugh.
[screams]
Way to go! We'd almost
totally lost them until
you guys decided to fall out of
the wall and ruin everything,
so thanks a lot for
getting us all cornered!
[BRITAIN] Oh, shut up!
You can't make this
whole thing our fault!
He's right. And I hate
you for putting me
in the position to say that.
I think we have
different position
to worry about.
[CHINA] What do we do now?
[BRITAIN] Those green light
things are getting brighter,
aren't they?
[FRANCE] Oh mon dieu.
They're going to turn us
into one of them!
[RUSSIA] Don't worry so much.
I'm sure those Axis power guys
will be here any second.
[gasps]
Uh!
[FRANCE whimpers]
[gasps]
[angry CAT howling noise]
Huh?
Uh?
Ah?
[angry CAT howling noise]
[GERMANY grunting, screaming]
[GERMANY] Stop it
with the scratching!
[JAPAN] Please. Calm down.
This is not going to
end up well for us.
[explosion]
[GERMANY screams]
[JAPAN screams]
[ITALY screams]
[GERMANY groans]
Meow!
[JAPAN gasps]
[ITALY whimpers]
[BRITAIN] Welcome to the
party. Thanks for nothing.
[CHINA] You could have
not picked worse place
to fall at moment.
[AMERICA laughs]
[AMERICA] At least they
stopped them for a sec!
Now we can all die together!
[electric hissing]
[LIECHTENSTEIN]
What do you think?
I think...
it tastes like sandwich.
Thank you, I'm
glad you like it.
[LIECHTENSTEIN] Hetalia!
Hey, Germany. Come
listen. I wrote a song
especially for you.
What? Even though
I'm your enemy?
Okay. Let me hear it.
[ITALY] ♪ Germany. Germany.
Germany is a really really ♪
♪ nice place! Even though
I'm your prisoner, ♪
♪ you give me food! ♪
♪ And it doesn't suck
like English food! ♪
♪ Sausages with cheeses
always taste so good! ♪
♪ It'd be heaven for a dog.
Yeah, that's Germany! ♪
♪ Tell me, how is it
you Germans are so robust? ♪
♪ You're crushing me
with your intimidation. ♪
♪ My fragility causes me
to openly weep out of fear. ♪
♪ Your women terrify me. ♪
♪ Is it the norm
to drink a barrel of beer ♪
♪ and then bust it on
somebody's head? ♪
♪ Please don't come
to my place in large mobs. ♪
♪ German tourists are scary! ♪
♪ Even the girls
that are from Germany are ♪
♪ more rugged
than I am. Yahoo! ♪
[HOLY ROMAN EMPIRE]
Welcome home, Italy.
[GERMANY] Hetalia!
[ITALY laughs]
[ITALY] That was great Germany.
Damn them both! If
I wasn't bested by
that fucking German
blitzkrieg again!
I let them beat me
without much of
a fight this time, but
next time won't be so easy.
They don't know it but I still
have a top secret weapon left.
More powerful than
conventional bombs even.
Gentlemen, it is time
to attack with black magic.
[CROWD Ohs and Ahs]
[chuckles] Germany will learn
the power of the dark side
which fears no man--
Britain! What're
you doing?
I say. Haven't you
ever heard of knocking?
[MAN] Where did you
put the 'Eye of Newt'?
[BRITAIN] Hetalia!
[BRITAIN] Damn it! Since
I was interrupted before,
I'll do it at my
place this time.
Our family's magic
is No. 1 in the world.
You're no match for me,
you stupid America!
[chants] Santa ritahh-meter
maidahh-Ringo johnnahh-tito
marlon jackla toya janet
Michaeldumble dorahh
-theex-plorahh. Santa
ritahh-meter maidahh-Ringo
johnnahh-tito marlon jackla
toya janet Michaeldumble
dorahh-theex-plorahh.
I have summoned you
from the depths of hell.
Show yourself!
You called?
[BRITAIN] I wasn't calling you!
[RUSSIA] Hetalia!
[ITALY] Hey, hey Germany?
What are you doing?
Can we go play
football, can we?
Nein, I am reading.
But it's so pretty outside;
let's go play football!
[exasperated sigh]
Hey, Germany, play
football Germany.
Hey, football Germany,
Germany football!
Are you wanting
me to gas you?
[shocked gasp]
[ITALY] Hetalia!
[JAPANESE BOSS] Hey,
Japan. What are you making
for dinner tonight?
I'm cooking potatoes
in broth along with
fresh mountain vegetable.
[JAPANESE BOSS]
I had some beef stew
at Britain's house once.
Can we have that instead?
What? You want me
to make British food?
But it is--
[JAPANESE BOSS]
Thanks! I knew you'd do it!
What kind of fool
want food from Britain
when they could have
something delicious I make?
I can make better
stew than Britain.
I have the finest
palate in the world.
I am not certain how to make,
but it will be better than
anything from that tasteless
island. Let me see.
I will need beef, potato,
a carrot, and what else?
A noodle. Soy sauce
to make brown.
Wait, this doesn't look right!
Sir, stew is complete.
[JAPANESE BOSS]
See? I knew you could do it!
[JAPAN] I apologize
if it is not correct.
[MALE NARRATOR] This is the
dish later known as Nikujaga.
[JAPANESE BOSS chews happily]
I love it!
[JAPANESE BOSS] Delicious!
[JAPAN] Hetalia!
We are left with no
other choice at this point.
Please listen, Pictonians!
We have come here today
to show you our hospitality.
[ALL] Huh?
Calm down. Just
think about it for
a moment really careful.
It may be true they have come
to Earth to invade it.
But on the other hand,
they are still our
guests, are they not?
It's Japanese custom
to be hospitable.
No, it is humanity
custom to be hospitable!
Now then.
I think we should hold
reception for Pictonians!
Hold what?
He's kidding?
He has to be.
No way.
Cool?
Okay?
I do not think
this is best idea.
You know, nothing
else is working,
so we might as well
give 'er a shot!
[AMERICA laughs]
If you want to have
big reception,
just leave it
all to me!
[CHINA] Ta-da!
You go ahead and eat
as much as you want to!
How did you manage
to build a Chinatown
on a spaceship
in five seconds?
[CHINA] Well? Do you love it?
There is plenty to go round,
so keep eating. No worry!
Si!
That is not for you!
♪
[bloopy claps]
Aw, thanks! I hope this
is a fun time for you.
So, you Pictonians
enjoying youselves?
[PICTONIANS]
We don't know.
[CHINA] That is wonderful!
I had feeling you would!
[ALL] Uh?!
Wait. You
don't know?
But, um. You are liking
the food, aren't you?
[PICTONIANS]
We don't know.
[CHINA] Ai yah.
[FRANCE] Hello!
It is my turn to show you what
true hospitality means! I never
leave a guest unsatisfied!
Now enjoy!
[muah]
[FRANCE] I have for you a full
course dinner from a five-star
restaurant, and served with
the finest French wines!
Si!
Nein! That is not
for you, either!
[FRANCE] Tell me the truth.
S'il vous plait. You love it.
Am I right?
[PICTONIANS]
We don't know.
[FRANCE] Pourquoi.
Yes. I would like
to be going now.
Don't let me down!
[ESTONIA, LATVIA, and LITHUANIA]
Yes, sir.
We'll...
[ESTONIA, LATVIA, and LITHUANIA]
try,...
sir.
[sobbing]
[ESTONIA, LATVIA, and LITHUANIA]
Honestly, we're not finding
this very entertaining
for anybody.
You like it, da?
[ALL gasp]
[awkward mumbling]
[PICTONIANS]
We don't know.
[ESTONIA, LATVIA, and LITHUANIA]
Time for twirling away.
[RUSSIA] Pochemu! Pochemu!
Pochemu! Pochemu!
All right. You can have a taste
of my hospitality then!
[GERMANY shaky laugh]
Well, hello. This is an
especially good German beer
we like to drink where I am from
so, I hope that you like it.
[shaky laugh]
[GERMANY] I don't like this.
[GERMANY shaky laugh]
Yo dude. You look
nervous, bro.
Hello ladies and gentleman!
And hello to you
Pictonian dudes, too!
When humans hear the word
hospitality, they all think
about me because I know how to
have a good time! Check it out!
♪
[BUNNIES giggle]
[PICTONIANS murmur excitedly]
We don't know!
We don't know! We don't know!
[muah]
[PICTONIAN A] I'm not sure!
[PICTONIANS, excitedly]
We don't know!
[ITALY] Hey! I want to say it,
too! I'm not sure, either!
I'm not sure! I'm not sure!
[AMERICA] Rad! Things
are like totally starting
to get exciting for realz!
Now all I gotta do is allow them
into the VIP room and
let them win like crazy,
give them tickets to the shows
--then, before they know it,
I'll trick 'em into signing
this rockin' peace treaty!
Not yet. It's still
far too early for that.
We have not yet successfully
buttered them up enough.
A treaty is premature.
Let me give it a try.
Because, I am known
throughout the world
for incredible festivals.
Sure. Go for it dude.
♪
Kon'nichiwa, Pictonians!
This is BON
dancing festival. This is
where we all dance together!
♪
[ITALY] Cool!
I want to dance, too!
[sings along with music]
This is fun, huh?
[PICTONIANS]
We don't know. We don't know.
Now's the time,
dude. Make those blobs
sign, sign, sign!
No, it's still too early.
First we must pacify
them with gifts and make sure
they are feeling relaxed and
happy before they leave. We can
talk the treaty on another day.
That is secret
to good reception.
What? You can't be serious.
I've taken the liberty
of preparing the gifts.
[AMERICA laughs]
Dude, your sense of
timing is incredible.
Thank you
very much.
[ITALY, PICTONIANS]
We don't know! We don't know!
Check it out! Those
dudes look like
they're like
totally happy!
I am curious, Britain. What
did you put into gift bags?
Isn't it obvious?
I put scones in there
I made from scratch.
[ALL but BRITAIN] Huh? Uh...
[PICTONIANS] Seriously?
[PICTONIANS]
Seriously? Seriously? Seriously?
[ALL but BRITAIN gasp]
[BRITAIN] What's wrong?
[PICTONIANS]
Seriously? Seriously? Seriously?
Fail. Dude, I
think your scones
pissed off the Pictos.
Why? Scones
are so yummy.
Hey, what's wrong? Come
on all you Pictonians!
What happened to all the
happy? Have another scone
and let's keep having fun!
Eh?
[PICTONIAN B] No way.
[PICTONIAN C] No way.
[PICTONIANS]
No way. No way. No way.
[AMERICA] Yeah. I don't think
they like that plan, dude.
[RUSSIA] No.
[GERMANY] I'm not sure
what's happening,
but we should retreat!
[ALL] Run away!
[PICTONIANS] No way!
No way! Now way!...
[ITALY] Hey you guys!
Wait for me!
[bloopy stampede]
[GERMANY grunts]
[AMERICA] Ahh!
[BRITAIN screams]
[FRANCE yells]
[RUSSIA] Ahh!
[JAPAN grunts]
[PANDA cries]
[ITALY cries and screams]
[AUSTRIA] Hetalia!
Ahh!
I knew I wouldn't
be able to do this.
[HUNGARY] No, Austria,
don't say things like that.
You can create any
kind of music; I know it!
But I've never heard
Japanese dance music before--
how am I supposed to write it?
You know, I didn't even know
they had such things.
[dejected sigh]
[AUSTRIA] Why would Japan ask me
to compose this Bon-Bon Dancing?
[HUNGARY] It's just one BON.
[HUNGARY] Hetalia!
Okay. I'm going
to invade Russia.
Take care of things
while I'm off killing.
[ITALY] Please don't.
My medication's wearing off.
[DEMONS laugh]
It's scary to be alone
and I can see their faces
laughing at me. Britain and
France are on the march
and are going to swallow me up
like the tasty morsel that I am.
Please don't go!
[ITALY growls]
I can't be dependent
on scary mister Germany
for the rest of my life.
I'll show them the true Italy!
[ITALY gasps]
[ITALY] Over here!
I surrender! Look at me!
Quitting is hard work.
My arms are tired.
Italia Forever!
[BRITAIN] Hetalia!
We finally invented
a machine that will make
perfectly boiled eggs! As you
can see, it's a state of the art
machine that we,
the British Empire,
marshaled our
intelligence to create.
We spent several years
on the concept.
And now, after all
those years of testing,
we have the unique capability
to make delicious boiled eggs
by using technologies no
other country can replicate.
[AMERICA] Mmm mmm.
[exasperated sigh]
[AMERICA] Hetalia!
Look, a machine that
will get you beer from a tap.
--[BRITAIN] We--
--[FRANCE] Clink!
[laughs]
[BRITAIN] You bastard!
Only the French would hit
a person with beer!
[FRANCE] What is that
supposed to mean?
Another peaceful
day for the Allies.
[FRANCE] Hetalia.
Hey there Hasselhoff--
I've got a little surprise
for you.
Great. What is
it? Another Jew?
[ROMANO] I have created
a secret weapon for such
singular purpose and
stealthiness that you will be
helpless to its powers.
Mustache!
[laughs]
Woohoo! You look
so very stupid with your
big bushy mustache like some
hipster at an art school party.
Uh...
You do know it
looks like you have
the mustache
from where I stand.
Turn your head. No!
Don't look. I'm so ugly.
[ROMANO] Hetalia!
[GERMANY] Due to my merger
with Austria, he started living
at my house. Now, I have
no desire to go home.
I'm not even married.
Hey! Why do you
throw your underwear
on the floor when you've
only worn it the one time?
If Franz Joseph the First
saw this, he'd die in a fit
of fury at your
unadulterated wastefulness!
Yes, but they kind
of have a big hole in them.
This tiny hole?
F. J. One would not care
about such things, he would
have patched it up first.
[GERMANY] And so, I was forced
to continue wearing dirty
underwear he patched
with his bare hands.
[AUSTRIA] Hetalia!
[page turn sound]
[GERMANY] Dear Diary.
That darn Italy slacked off
from his training again.
Lazy bastard.
[ITALY] Oh... I wonder why
Germany is being such a big fat
meany-pants today.
[CAT] Meow.
Huh?
[ITALY] Kitty, Kitty, Kitty!
I found her here so that
must mean she's Germany's cat.
Germany could learn
about niceness and purring
and tongue baths from you.
[ITALY] Who wants a
super kitty spin this way?
How about one more
back the other way?
Argh--
We need to get that
cat back to the lab.
I love her!
Meow.
[GERMANY] Hetalia!
[GERMANY gasps]
[pants]
[GERMANY] I wonder how
long I've been here now.
When I awoke, I had washed
ashore onto the beach.
I've been wandering around
in this jungle without
any knowledge of where
I am or where I am headed.
Nor do I know what I'm
looking for. I haven't seen
the others since we
jumped ship. Literally.
I don't even know
if they're still alive.
But what's worse, I have no
idea what is happening
across the Earth. What if it's
been completely transformed
into a Picto planet? It is
this case, this island must be
the last stronghold.
I could be the last, too.
[GERMANY hitches a breath]
[GERMANY] Of course, I should
have expected as much.
My physical strength seems
to have reached its limit.
I won't ask for water.
If only I could have
some beer to moisten my throat.
I won't ask for food either.
If only I had some wurst
to satisfy my hunger.
[GERMANY struggles to breathe]
Wait. What light
is that I am seeing?
Maybe somebody's over there.
[pants]
[gasps]
[ITALY sings]
[CAT meows]
Is that Italy? But, how?
[JAPAN] I think it's
the soft glow of hope.
[BRITAIN] Criminy.
I've never been so hungry.
You're all here!
Ist gut.
[gasps]
Huh?
Hey! I've been
waiting for you guys!
The pasta will be done
in just a minute, okay?
[laughs]
[YOUNG VOICE]
Cheerio, everybody!
Huh?
[ALL] Huh?
Hey, you remember me?
I'm Sealand!
I found you by
using the interwebs!
I'm wicked good at
that kind of thing!
I brought my entire country
here to rescue you!
You don't have an entire
country to take anywhere.
Now go away you
little pipsqueek!
[SEALAND] Once I rescue all
these big important countries,
they'll have no choice
but to recognize me as
my very own sovereign nation!
[electric hissing]
[LIECHTENSTEIN]
Um. Big Brother?
[nervous gasp]
[LIECHTENSTEIN]
I was wondering. Um.
If maybe you wanted to go
on another picnic with me?
I'd like that very much.
[SWITZERLAND grunts]
[happy gasp]
[LIECHTENSTEIN] Wonderful!
I'm so happy! Thank you.
Well then, have a good night!
Yes. You have a
good night, too.
[SWITZERLAND] Hetalia!
[LIECHTENSTEIN] Hetalia!
[GIRL giggles]
Uh?
[BRITAIN] Hey, Japan. Have
you heard that child making
so much noise?
[JAPAN] I have not. I'm sorry.
How odd. I live alone you know.
[JAPAN] Strange. I'm sure
it's just the long trip.
He must be hallucinating
out of exhaustion.
Sir Britain. Perhaps
you should take a bath and
go get some rest.
[sighs]
Japan has been acting
more than a bit unusual
this evening. I'm sure it's
simply a cultural difference.
I hope I didn't do
anything offensive, though.
[BOTH gasp]
Look, a human has come
here to take a bath.
Sorry. We'll
leave now sir.
[sighs]
[scared gasps]
[BRITAIN] To be honest,
I don't mind you being in
the bath with me.
Oh... Well thank
you very much, gov'ner.
I hate to ask this,
we've only just met,
and we are naked, but
could you fill me in a bit
about Japanese culture?
Sure! No one
could inform you
more about that particular
topic than us, right?
Right!
[KAPPA] First of all,
the sushi you are familiar
with was only recently
created. Did you know that?
[BRITAIN] Really?
No--I had no idea.
[GOBLIN] You could
always just check out Wiki.
I'm sure they've nailed it.
[ALL laugh]
[JAPAN] Sir Britain. You were
in the bath quite a long time.
Yes, well, I was a bit
distracted while chatting
with the two blokes that
were already in there.
[JAPAN] What?
Well, I'm off
to bed now.
Okay. Goodnight, then.
I live alone. Who on
Earth is he talking about?
[JAPAN] Hetalia
[KAPPA]
Excuse me, Gov'ner?
Um. I just wanted
to thank you
for a wonderful evening.
Oh, hello fellows.
[BRITAIN] It was
rather fun, wasn't it?
We should take a bath
together again tomorrow.
[laughs] Oh, we would love
to, but we were just about
to leave this area
for the mountains.
[gasps]
[KAPPA] You see.
We were taking a bath
to celebrate our last day here.
Arigato!
[KAPPA] Long ago, although
humans were afraid of us,
they still believed
we were real. In a way,
I guess you could say we had a
mutual respect for each other.
But then something changed.
Before we knew it, our very
existence became nothing more
than a silly superstition
to people.
[KAPPA] We used to be able
to talk to Mister Japan, too.
[GOBLIN] Nowadays, he
won't even look at us.
But still, that
doesn't mean you both
have to leave, does it?
[KAPPA] Yes. I guess
you could say we feel
as if we've overstayed our
welcome. But, it was a pleasure
for us to spend our last
hours here with you.
I see.
[KAPPA] Take care,
Gov'ner. Nice to meet you!
[BRITAIN] Hey! We
should still get together
for a bath again someday.
[GOBLIN and KAPPA]
Yes! That would be wonderful!
[GIRL giggles]
[BRITAIN yells]
[GIRL
giggles]
Aha! You were the one
making the noise!
Stop right there!
[BRITAIN] Hey! What
are you? Damn, you're fast!
Come back here you little--
wait, you're not one of those...
Sir Britain is insane.
How many times
do I have to tell
him I live alone?
[BRITAIN screams]
[BRITAIN] Hetalia!
[CHINA sighs]
I am so full
at moment.
Who would have
guessed you'd have
a vacation Chinatown
on this random island?
I completely
forgot about it.
Wow, this seafood
pasta is pretty rockin',
am I right?
Yes, I like it!
Why don't you
go home already?
Pasta!
[ALL] Mmm...
Good grief. I will
never understand how
he can sleep so easily.
He's tired. After all he
did make us all dinner,
which was very
delectable if you ask me.
Hey I helped make
it, too, ass!
I am wondering
about Pictonian.
Why did they stop the
attacking of us when Italy
started talking to them?
[BRITAIN and FRANCE] Huh?
[AMERICA and CHINA] Uh...
Oh?
Uh.
[ALL] Yeah...
[FRANCE] They probably were
fascinated by his facial
expressions since
they don't have any.
[BRITAIN] They are extreme.
[ALL but GERMANY
and JAPAN laugh]
Uh...
[distant rumbling]
[GERMANY]
They're here!
[JAPAN] It would
appear so.
[AMERICA] Damn it!
[GERMANY] It's headed for us!
Hmmm.
Don't worry
everybody! I promise,
you can just leave
this whole thing to me!
No! You imbecile!
It's dangerous!
[SEALAND] Maybe for you,
but I'll be fine!
Hmm.
[laughs]
All systems go!
[massive rumbling]
[deafening mechanical sound]
[SEALAND] I modified every bit
of my land just for this moment!
Well, what did I
tell you? Idiot.
[massive collision]
[waves break]
[ALL tremble]
[BRITAIN] It just... stopped.
Okay! I was wrong!
What the hell
are they up to?
[BRITAIN] What's
the point in this?
[FRANCE] It's ruined!
The Eiffel Tower is atrocious!
[CHINA] It's like they
brought them to show us.
Wait! This looks
like bad news!
I think they're making their
own city with this island
as their base!
They can't!
[bloopy stampede]
Italy! Wake up now!
Why? Is something
about to happen?
[screams]
This is too scary for me!
[GERMANY] Snap out of it!
I haven't been this
scared since I pretended
to be the box
of tomatoes fairy!
Stop crying! If you don't,
I swear I will give you
something to cry about!
[screams]
There's no crying
in alien warfare!
[CAT] Meow!
[ITALY] Wait! Pookie!
Italy, come back!
[BRITAIN] Germany! Just let
him go. We have even more
pressing matters to be
concerned about at the moment.
Yes, indeed we do.
[GERMANY] Hetalia!
Hetalia! Hetalia!
Now, Japan, do you think
you could make U-boats
using those blueprints
we had from the other day?
Well, I think your
design is much too big
to do in my home. But
please do not worry.
We succeeded in miniaturizing
it using technology.
[GERMANY] No way!
[JAPAN] We have twelve
color random assortment.
And we shall release
new, additional colors
to match each season.
A popular voice actress will
advertise it for us, too.
[GERMANY] Cool!
Ahh!
[JAPAN] And that is its
ultimate final form.
[GERMANY] This is
wunderbar, Japan!
[MAN] Uh!
[JAPAN] Hetalia!
You. Italians.
You're on lookout.
[ITALIAN SOLDIERS] Tired.
Oh c'mon, you guys were
just sleeping. Move it.
[ITALIAN SOLDIER A]
The Germans have gone to bed.
Good! Let's carry
out our plan!
[ITALIAN SOLDIERS scream]
[GERMANY] How did they
all defect so quickly?
[GERMAN SOLDIER A] Well, they
are professionals, aren't they?
[ITALY] Hetalia!
[ITALY] Hello!
Good morning, Japan!
[ITALY] Hug!
[JAPAN] No, please. I don't
understand what's happening.
You've invaded
my personal space.
Not that I need
a lot to begin with.
[ITALY scared murmuring]
I do hope you
realize how awkward
that whole thing
was for me.
[ITALY scared murmuring]
[CHIBI ITALY] Hetalia!
[HOLY ROMAN EMPIRE] Oh, Italy!
[CHIBI ITALY] Oh, Holy Rome!
[HOLY ROMAN EMPIRE]
Oh, Italy, Italy!
[HOLY ROMAN EMPIRE] Hetalia!
[bloopy stampede]
One for you. One for you.
Ai ya!
[yells]
I'm hit! Oh no!
China!
Argh!
Uh!
America!
[RUSSIA] Uh!
[FRANCE] Uh!
[JAPAN] Ugh!
[growls] Bring it on!
I'll kill all of you
with my bare hands!
[muffled grunts]
[GERMANY screams]
Oh, no! Germany!
[CHINA] No! I'm rapidly becoming
one of those Pictonian bastard!
[AMERICA] Dude, me too, bro!
[BRITAIN] I hate it here.
[JAPAN gasps]
[FRANCE] No! I've
become hideously bland!
You guys!
[whines] But I don't want them
to be turned into
faceless white ghost blobs!
[groans]
Italy. Try smiling!
[ITALY] But I can't.
Those scary NOPPERA
meanies are everywhere!
[GERMANY] I don't care,
you just have to smile.
Please Italy, just
smile! Do it! Italy!
No! It's way too
scary for smiling!
[grunts]
[GERMANY] Italy!
[GERMANY] Ita...ly.
[ITALY] Please stop
walking like that.
You're really
freaking me out, guys.
But I don't want to
turn into a NOPPERA!
Why won't you listen?
I can't stop screaming--
[ROME]
♪ Listen up as I tell you. ♪
♪ What Heaven on
Earth would be. ♪
♪ All the cooks
would be the French. ♪
♪ Policemen would be British.
Engineers would be German. ♪
♪ The bankers
would be the Swiss. ♪
♪ Your lover --of course--
would be from I--ta--ly! ♪
[electric guitar]
[band and electric guitar]
♪ Let me tell you
something about hell! ♪
♪ The cooks are all
boringly British. ♪
♪ Policemen are all
grossly German. ♪
♪ Engineers are all
foppishly French. ♪
♪ Your lover is sadly a Swiss.
And the bankers are ♪
♪ frighteningly from Italy! ♪
[electric guitar]
[ROME] Thank you!
[final note reverberates]
[PICTONIANS]
We don't know. We don't know.
Hey there, Grandpa Rome!
Why is there a marker
on the ground?
I wonder if Grandpa Rome
maybe left it here.
Oh. Yeah!
[laughs]
Hey, look I drew a face!
[PICTONIAN J] Seriously?
Seriously!
[PICTONIAN K] A face?
[ITALY sings joyfully]
[PICTONIANS laugh, cheer]
[laughs]
Oh!
[ITALY] I found Germany!
[ITALY] All done! Yay!
It looks exactly like you!
You know what? I can
draw everyone's face!
[ITALY sings joyfully]
Nice.
[ITALY] Ha!
Ha ha!
Heeee!
Ah ha ha ha!
Ah ho ho ho!
Ahhh...
Heeey!
[AMERICA] Dude, what's the deal
with all your weirdo faces?
[BRITAIN] Look in the mirror;
your face is weird, too.
[FRANCE] What about me?
Do I look weird, as well?
I'd rather be--
[JAPAN] Everyone.
What is happening to Germany?
[ALL] Huh?
[ITALY] Hey!
Germany turned back!
[CHINA] Me too! My
body is changing back
to the normal China,
just like Germany.
[AMERICA] I'm happy
to see you hands!
[FRANCE] I'm gorgeous
again. All is well!
[AMERICA] We're gonna
have so much fun!
[JAPAN] I think
I might be smiling.
[GERMANY] Italy.
You did wunderbar.
Ha ha!
[ITALY] Hetalia! Hetalia!
Ciao Japan.
Guess what I heard.
Germany said you were
good at miniaturizing.
Do you think you
could shrink me, too?
Apologies, but no.
We are not currently
accepting orders to
miniaturize Ita--
You shrank it!
Your thing.
Japanese people
grower, not show-er.
[ITALY] Whoa! What is this?
Stupendo! Amazing! Whoa!
[JAPAN] Hetalia!
[GERMANY] Why the heck
is this guy such a putz?
I ate some really weird
British pizza the other day.
It kinda tasted like
fish and vinegar.
[GERMANY] He's supposed to
be a descendant of mighty Rome
so it's not a problem
with his genetics.
Look, Germany. Someone's
teaching a lesson.
[MAN] The flavonids
in tomatoes cause those
who ingest too much to become
unnaturally good humored
but pathetically weak.
However our latest research
has but cracked the
surface of this phenomena.
It's funny. That professor
guy doesn't know it
but he just said
'butt crack."
[laughs]
Now I see.
[GERMANY] Hetalia!
Dude, rock out. I am
awesomely the first one here!
Now I can say:
[AMERICA] Say, aren't you
running a little late?
Those losers are
totally going to feel like
completely stupid, yo.
[AMERICA] It's Britain!
All right. That
should do the trick.
[AMERICA] The portraits!
Britain was drawing them
the whole time?
[AMERICA] Hetalia.
[CHINA] What's up with
these weird drawings?
[FRANCE] They're even worse
than our actual animation.
Who drew this crap?
It does not capture the
essence of my natural beauty!
Yes, and I have a
unibrow for some reason.
[CHINA] I think the ones
at the bottom are best.
[RUSSIA] If that one
is supposed to be of me.
I'll hack it out
with my pickaxe.
[ALL THREE] You what?
[AMERICA] Uhh...
Well, that's just annoying!
Why would someone choose
to draw us in such a fashion?
It's unforgiveable really--
How dare that mysterious
person flexibly express all of
our individual characteristics
with skilled sketches using
boldly formed, innovative and
cutesy American pop art styles
he probably learned
in New York City!
So it was you.
You an ass.
[AMERICA] Hetalia.
That's unacceptable.
I will draw all the portraits
from now on.
[ALL]
China! You're a chick?
[CHINA] Hetalia! Hetalia!
Thank you! I guess
that means they're
back to normal, too!
[gasp]
Wait? Who the
hell is that?
Oh, what? Now you
have a spokesperson?
[PICTONIAN GIRL] I would like to
apologize for all the trouble
we have caused you
and your people.
Our initial goal was to conquer
this planet and assimilate you
to our image. But,
after seeing how much fun
this world can be,
we've decided we do not wish
to change anything about it.
Instead, we would like to
thank you for changing us
and for giving us faces.
To show our gratitude,
we will turn all humans
back to their original form
and transport them to their
individual countries. Also...
Would you mind
giving that to me?
[GERMANY and ITALY] Huh?
[PICTONIAN GIRL] We do not
have any of those on my planet.
No problemo!
Here you go!
[PICTONIAN GIRL]
Thank you very much.
I will treasure it forever.
[bloopy footsteps]
[PICTONIAN GIRL]
We're gonna go now.
If you don't need
anything else.
[GERMANY and ITALY gasp]
Goodbye! Have a
safe trip back!
[ITALY laughs]
You can come back and
visit whenever you want!
[BRITAIN] What are you
saying? We don't want them
coming back here!
[ITALY sings happily]
[LIECHTENSTEIN] Big Brother?
[LIECHTENSTEIN]
Another beautiful morning,
don't you think?
[SWITZERLAND] I guess.
So is anybody having
idea how we will
return to our homes?
Sonofabitch! We should
have asked them
to give us a lift
before they flew away!
Italy! This is
your fault.
If you hadn't told them goodbye,
they would not have left!
[ITALY cries]
[SEALAND] No need to fear!
Sealand is here!
Please, don't worry!
I'll be able to take you home
on my country!
[SEALAND] This is perfect!
Those jerks will have to accept
me now as my own nation!
They'll owe me!
Dude, who's up
for a world conference
when we get back!
Stop. I think before
we get carried away
we should celebrate
with BON dancing.
[ALL] Huh?
[BRITAIN] Why do we
have to do BON dancing?
[FRANCE] How the
hell should I know?
[ITALY] Cool! I want
to dance! I like to dance!
[SEALAND] I can do it, too!
[PICTONIAN language]
[ICELAND] So, I don't know what
the deal is with these guys,
but thanks to them we can see
auroras anytime of the year now,
which means we have
more tourists. Lucky us.
[KIDS] The end!