- Aniplex.
- We pray for help,
embrace curses,
and protect you from the dark.
We're magical girls.
[distant voice speaking]
We traded our souls
for our powers
and a destiny of battle.
A destiny which ends
in oblivion,
for the only way to escape
our despair
is to vanish from this world.
- [distant voice]
Soon girls from all over
the world were having
their wishes granted
which really the creature
very happy.
They fought the monsters
till they could fight no more,
which made the creature
even happier.
- The end will come
for all of us
so we continue our fight
and wait for the law
of cycles to lead us away.
- [distant voice]
It was said that at the moment
they cease to exist,
a being would suddenly appear
and lead them to a land...
- In this broken world,
doomed to repeat its tragedies
and hatred,
I dreamt of someone I knew
and saw
her familiar smile again.
[dramatic music]
♪
[water drips]
[toy squeaking]
[rockets whistling]
[booming]
- [giggles]
[grunts]
♪
- [whimpers]
- Awesome job, Madoka.
- We got this thing right where
we want it!
[both grunting]
[blows landing]
[door creaks]
[toy squeaks]
[FictionJunction ASUKA's
"Mada Dame Yo"]
- [singing in Japanese]
♪
♪ Nightmare
- [gasps]
[distant birds chirping]
[groans]
[exhales sharply]
It's morning already?
[peaceful music]
Good morning, Kyubey.
- Kyu?
Kyu.
Good morning, Dad.
- Hey, Madoka.
Mornin'.
- Mom up yet?
- Tatsuya's wakin' her up.
He might need some help, though.
- Okay!
[giggles]
- [chuckles]
- Mama, Mama!
Wake up, wake up!
Come on, Mama!
Mama!
- [grunts]
Rise and shine!
- [screams]
Huh?
What's new in your world?
- Hitomi's not doin' so well.
Kyousuke's been so busy
it's hard for her to see him.
- Oh, that's gonna be
a big problem
if they're serious
about going steady.
Tell her don't get discouraged,
don't obsess,
and don't give up.
- [gasps]
Ah.
- Here.
- I think Miss Saotome's
in the dumps, too.
She talks about the end
of the world
in class all the time.
- Oh, boy.
Well, maybe I can set her up
on a blind date or something.
- I wonder why she isn't
more popular with the guys?
There's a lot of really
cute things about her.
- When it comes to men,
she sets her standards
really high.
- [whimpers]
- She doesn't wanna compromise.
That's just how she is.
- Oh.
- Here we go.
[chuckles]
- Oh, I almost forgot.
We have a new student
transferring in today.
- That's weird.
Isn't it kinda late
in the year for that?
- I wonder what they're like?
Whoever it is,
I hope we can be friends.
- Kyu.
Kyu, kyu.
- [gurgling]
- [shouts]
Ah.
Yay, safe.
Now, be good
and eat it all up, okay?
- Okay!
- Hey, Honey.
Some more coffee?
- Ooh, I better not.
[gulps]
[kisses]
- [giggles]
- [kisses]
All right.
I'm off to work.
all: Have a great day!
- Hey, you.
- [chomps]
- You'll be late
if you don't hurry.
- Huh?
Oh, yeah.
[chomps]
See you later!
- Have a great day!
- [panting]
[panting and chewing]
- Kyu!
- [giggles]
[Claris' "Colorful"]
- [singing in Japanese]
♪
[cheerful music]
- [panting]
[both giggling]
- Good morning!
[exhales]
- [giggles]
- Glad you could make it today,
Madoka.
- Nice job last night, killa.
- [giggles]
- Dude, I totally saw you
walking home with her!
[both laughing]
- You get any sleep after
you got back?
- Yeah, a little.
I didn't have time to do
the reading assignment, though,
so I'm toast if I
get called on today.
- Oh, don't even sweat it.
Hell, I didn't even bother doing
my homework last night.
I'm in way more trouble.
[laughs]
- [groans]
- [chuckles nervously]
- Hey, Madoka,
you'll hook me up
with your homework later, right?
- [groans]
Hold it!
Don't you dare mix Madoka up
in your shady schemin'
- It's only 'cause you won't
let me see yours.
Besides, if anyone's shady,
it's you,
all sneaking off by yourself
and getting head start
on your homework.
- I offered to help you with it
when we got home!
- [groans]
- It's your own fault
for bailing
to go watch TV!
- [giggling]
- Come on, you guys.
Take it easy.
- I knew it was gonna be
too hard to go to school
and be a magical girl.
- [whimpers]
- There's never any time
to have fun!
[giggles]
- Oh, yeah?
Well, no one ever said
having fun
was gonna be part of the deal!
- [whimpers]
- Kyu.
- [giggles]
Come on, Sayaka.
- Stop running around like that!
[school bell rings]
- [clears throat]
Okay, class.
Just because the date
of the Mayan apocalypse
has passed,
don't you dare think
you're safe.
This is the beginning
of the end times, kiddos!
[all gasping]
We'll have a solar
and lunar eclipse
on the holy days
of a certain religion,
totaling six!
Isn't that scary?
You better believe it.
[chuckles menacingly]
What's it all mean?
It means that by 2050
our planet will experience--
what's it called, Nakazawa?
- Uh, I don't know what
you're talking about, Ma'am.
- That's not an answer.
Statistics show 41% of a certain
country's population believes
the second coming
of Christ will happen
in the next 40 years!
The seven trumpets
of "Revelations"
may blow any minute.
- Uh...
all: Huh?
- In my humble opinion,
the end of the world might
not be such a bad thing.
I've had my fill of men
and love for one lifetime.
If the only thing I have
to look forward to
is hitting 40,
I'd rather it all ended
in one big explosion.
- Um, Ma'am?
Are you--
- Huh?
Oh, I almost forgot.
We're going to have
a new student joining us
for the rest of the semester!
all: Uh...
- [laughs]
What a space cadet!
- Miss Akemi?
You can come in.
[all gasping]
[indistinct chatter]
- [gasps]
- Hmm?
- Huh?
- It's nice to meet you.
My name is Homura Akemi.
- Miss Akemi was in the hospital
for a while due
to a heart condition.
Since she's been away
from school for so long,
she might need
some help adjusting,
so let's all help her out, okay?
all: Yes, Ma'am!
- [giggles]
- Huh?
- A soul gem?
- No way!
She's one of us!
- There's an open desk next
to Nakazawa.
Have a seat and we'll begin.
- I--If you knew about her,
how come you didn't
say anything to us?
- I'm sorry I didn't.
I kept it a secret because
I thought it would be
a fun surprise.
- Oh, I knew it.
I should have introduced myself
to you last night.
- Wait, last night when we
were huntin' the nightmare?
You mean you were waiting
at the rendezvous point
with Mami?
How come you didn't help us?
- She did.
As a matter of fact,
she helped us out a lot.
She has the most amazing power.
- [gasps]
- She's so strong,
if she works with us,
she'll boost our strength
100-fold.
- Uh, I"m not really
that strong,
but I can back you up.
I'm not very good
at attacks, though.
- Well, you seem pretty cool
to me,
and with all
the big-shot nightmares
we've been fighting lately,
we need the extra help.
I guess after last night
you proved you got what it takes
to roll with us.
If you wanna join our team,
I'm cool with it.
- Thank you for the chance
to prove myself.
I'll do my best
to help you fight the nightmares
and keep everyone safe.
I won't let you down.
[grunts]
[both giggling]
- [gasps]
- We'll all do
our best together, Homura.
[giggles]
- Oh.
[dramatic music]
♪
- Isn't it pretty?
- Mm-hmm.
♪
Can you believe
it's already been a month
since you showed up here?
- No, I can't.
It's like the time
has just flown by.
It feels like I've known you
forever, though.
- [giggles]
It'd be nice if the nightmares
stayed away tonight.
Then everyone could get
a good night's sleep.
- Kyu.
Kyu.
- If I tell you something,
promise not to laugh.
With you hearin' us talking
like this
it feels like something I wanted
for a long time,
which is weird,
'cause we're just talking.
I mean, we're gonna see
each other
at school tomorrow anyway.
- It's not weird.
I mean,
I feel that way, too.
2Sitting here with you,
it seems like something
I've wanted for a long,
long time.
[engine whirring]
- [grunts]
[beeps]
[phone trilling]
[phone clicks]
- Hello, who is this?
- [gasps]
Uh, hi, Kyousuke.
It's just me.
Are you free to talk now?
- Um, sure, Hitomi.
What's up?
- Sorry to call you so late,
but, well...
I was wondering if you
were doing anything this Sunday.
Do you have any plans?
- Yeah, I do.
There's not much time until
my next recital,
so I have to practice on Sunday.
Sorry.
- No, I understand.
- Our schedules never match up,
do they?
- It's okay.
There's nothing you can do
about it.
Besides, I know how dedicated
you are to your music.
That's what I love about you.
- [chuckles nervously]
Right.
I'll see you tomorrow
at school, then.
- Okay.
Goodnight.
[phone clicks]
[exhales sharply]
I understand.
His music means more
than anything to him,
and that is what
I love about him.
His drive,
his passion.
Whatever!
Would it kill him to use some
of that drive
and passion on me for a change?
Whoa!
[whimpers]
[crying]
Oh, I've had it!
I don't need Sundays anymore!
I wish his stupid recital
would disappear.
If I had my way,
it would all just...
[booming]
- [humming]
- [chirping]
[indistinct chatter]
- Bebe, hand me a hairpin,
please.
- [chattering]
[chatters]
- Oh.
- [chattering]
- Oh, no.
Not again.
- [chattering]
- [sighs]
- Goodness me.
I always say,
late nights are the enemy
of beauty.
[both grunting]
[film reel clicking]
- Hey, ain't that
Hitomi Shizuku's nightmare?
- I guess she's havin'
a hard time.
- [scoffs]
With a boyfriend
like Captain Oblivious,
it doesn't surprise me.
- Ooh, sounds like
someone's done some movin' on.
- [chuckles]
Yeah.
Maybe.
I chalk it up
to life experience.
[booming]
[both gasping]
[both shouting]
- Look sharp.
You''re putting yourselves
in danger
if you don't
take this seriously.
- [giggles]
Yes, ma'am.
- Where's Madoka and Homura?
- We're so sorry to
make you wait!
[all panting]
- Glad you decided to show up.
- [giggles]
Sorry, Sayaka.
- Kyu, kyu.
- [chattering]
[chattering]
- [giggles]
All right.
Let's go to work, ladies.
all: Okay.
[classical music]
♪
[exciting music]
all: Puella Magi Holy Quintet!
♪
[screeching]
[booming]
- Madoka!
Mami!
- Okay!
[grunts]
- Go for it, Homura!
- [gasps]
[clicking]
[uplifting music]
♪
both: Hero Duet!
- Release!
- I get how you feel, Hitomi,
but you gotta calm down!
Five Lillian!
[grunting]
Now, Kyouko!
- [scoffs]
Latticework Barrier!
♪
- Look, you guys!
It stopped moving!
- Nicely done.
Now, let's finish this.
♪
[booming]
["Cake Song"]
- ♪ Big cake round cake
right in front of me ♪
♪ Who do you think
- [gasps]
- ♪ This cake could be
- [chattering]
- ♪ No it's not me
♪ I'm just
a little old raspberry ♪
♪ That big round cake's
too red ♪
♪ Don't you know
♪ Could the cake be Kyouko
- ♪ No not me
♪ I'm the juicy apple
in this story ♪
♪ That big round cake loves Bebe
can't you see ♪
♪ Is the cake Mami
♪
- ♪ No it's not me
♪ I am the cheese
♪ This big round cake
is tumbling you see ♪
♪ Could the cake be Homura
♪ Ah not me
♪ I--I'm the pumpkin full
of seeds ♪
♪ This big round cake
looks sweeter than sweet ♪
♪ Could the cake be Madoka
- ♪ No it's not me
♪ I'm the melon don't you see
♪ When you slice the melon
it will bring you sweet dreams ♪
all: ♪ So why is the dream
so bitter of late ♪
♪ 'Cause the kitty's dream
is the one on the plate ♪
♪ It's so plump
♪ It's gonna taste great
[booming]
- [chattering]
- [grunts]
[classical music]
♪
[giggles]
- [chattering]
both: We did it!
- Kyu!
- With us combining
our powers like that,
taking that sucker down
was a breeze.
- There was a moment
when I thought
we were in trouble,
though.
- [giggles]
- [grunts]
- It's best not to
get too overconfident.
- Why do you gotta be such
a wet blanket?
Instead of preachin'
you should invite us over
for tea and cake.
- Now, that's
what I'm talkin' about.
Way to use your brain, Kyouko!
- [grunts]
[all giggling]
- Now, that's a great idea.
Who wants to come over
for refreshments?
all: I do!
[all giggling]
[dramatic music]
♪
- [gasps]
[birds chirping]
- [giggles]
Come on, Sayaka!
- [grunts]
- Ha ha, too slow!
[laughs]
- I'm running a little low
on chamomile tea
but I think I might have
just enough for one more pot.
- Goodie!
I love your chamomile tea.
- Or I could make some
of the echinacea tea
I got the other day.
- Whoa.
That stuff's all sour
and I don't do sour.
- [laughs]
Your taste buds haven't
developed past
the first grade.
- Yeah, but my fists have!
- [chattering]
[both giggling]
- I know, Bebe.
I didn't forget.
You'll get a special treat, too.
- [chatter]
- [giggles]
[birds chirping]
- What's wrong, Homura?
Why so quiet?
- Huh?
Oh, it's nothing.
I'm okay.
- [giggles]
- Is that how battles are?
And have they always been
like that?
[dramatic music]
[birds chirping]
♪
- Homura!
Do you wanna try some
of my fried chicken?
- Sure.
Thanks.
It looks delicious.
- [giggles]
- [grunts]
[groans]
[unsettling music]
♪
- Okay, what'd you wanna
talk about?
- Oh, um...
I was wondering,
have things seemed a little odd
to you lately?
- Huh?
I dunno what you mean.
Odd like how?
- Well, that's the thing.
I don't know.
Everything just seems off.
- I got no idea
what you're sayin'.
You feelin' okay?
- [groans]
I guess the reason I wanted
to speak to you
before anyone else was you're
the one who seems
the most odd to me.
- What?
- What I mean is,
compared to the impression
I have of you,
something about you
seems different.
It's like you're not
the same person you used to be.
- Okay, what are you tryin'
to do here?
Are you tryin' to pick a fight
with me?
Is that what this is?
- No, not at all.
Look, where are you living now?
- What do you mean?
I'm crashin' at Sayaka's place.
You lose your memory all
of a sudden?
- And how long have you been
at Mitakihara?
- I transferred in
a little while before you did.
- And when was that?
- Hmm?
I guess it
was last year around...
hmm.
♪
When did I transfer in?
Oh, whatever.
Why's it matter?
- Where did you live before
you moved here?
- Kazamino, the next city over.
Things had got
pretty quiet there for me,
so when Mami told me stuff
was getting out of hand here,
I came over.
- Have you gone back
to visit Kazamino lately?
- No, thank you.
I don't got no reason
to go back there.
[chewing]
- Mm.
- [exhales sharply]
- Hey, Kyouko,
would you do me a favor?
Come to Kazamino with me.
- Huh?
What the hell for?
- I just wanna go see it.
That's all.
If the city's the same
as you remember,
I promise we'll turn around
and come back.
Then I'll know it's just me
and not something else.
- I got no idea what
your trip is, girl,
but whatever it is,
I don't think you're pullin'
my leg here.
Not you.
You're on the level.
- I am.
- [exhales sharply]
[chair scrapes across ground]
[chomps]
[grunts]
Well, the trip won't be
for nothin'.
I know a good ramen shop there.
Buy me dinner and we're even.
We got a deal or what?
- [giggles]
Dinner's on me, then.
[dramatic music]
♪
- At the next stop we'll be
in Kazamino City.
[bus engine revving]
- Next stop,
Mitakihara City Third Street.
Passengers for Shinonome--
- [gasps]
Wait, that ain't right!
- We're supposed
to turn left up here!
Huh?
[bus brakes hissing]
[bus engine revving]
- [grunts]
- [gasps]
- Maybe we got on the wrong bus.
- No way.
I'm sure we got on the one
for Kazamino Station.
- Let's catch the next bus
and go back,
and let's make sure
it's the right one.
[tense music]
[both gasping]
♪
- That's the right one.
No mistakin'.
[brakes squeaking]
[brakes hissing]
[bus engine revving]
[beeps]
- Next stop,
Mitakihara City Second Street.
- Uh?
- Passengers bound
for the elementary school
should disembark at this stop.
Stop requested.
♪
[both gasping]
- [grunts]
What's your problem?
Stop the bus!
[both grunting]
[grunts]
Damn.
[bus engine revving]
What the hell's going on?
- We should try walking next.
If we go back to that crossroad
and take the left fork,
it should take us
to Kazamino City, right?
- Yeah.
[unsettling music]
♪
- Hey, was that crossroad
really this far back?
- No.
It's odd we haven't reached it
by now.
[gasping]
No way!
- Something's definitely wrong.
- [gasps]
- Either we missed the crossroad
which I highly doubt
or something else
is going on here.
- Yeah, but what?
Why's this happening?
Is it some kind
of trick to keep us
from leaving Mitakihara City?
[grunts]
- I don't think the answer
is as simple as that.
My theory is that nothing exists
beyond the city.
- What?
Really?
- Kyouko,
I'm sorry,
but could you not tell
the others for a little while?
There's something
I wanna check first
just to be sure.
- Are you crazy?
We have to tell the others!
- Please.
I think it will be safer
if we pretend
we haven't discovered anything.
- Huh?
[gasps]
- If we draw attention
to ourselves now,
we'll be hunted down.
This is a trap.
Make no mistake.
- Got any idea what's goin' on?
- Yes, which is why
I don't want you to do anything.
For now,
let me handle this.
- [gasps]
- As far as I can tell,
the one who's trapped us
is only playing
with our perceptions for now,
so as long as we play along,
we won't be in any danger.
- [exhales sharply]
Fine.
Whatever you say.
♪
- [gasping]
- Maybe my memories
are screwed up,
but I think I get where you
were comin' from before.
- How so?
- It's weird.
Like,
I don't remember you bein'
as tough
as you're actin' right now.
But it doesn't surprise me,
either.
This you--the tougher you--
feels right.
[scoffs]
- [gasps]
[grunts]
[giggles]
Am I the only one who remembers?
[grunts]
♪
I have seen this kind
of trap before.
A self-contained illusion.
A maze with no exit where prey
is lured and led astray.
There's no doubt about it.
This is a labyrinth.
[clanging and creaking]
Witches: the ones
who spread despair and disaster.
It's the final form
a magical girl takes
when she's lost hope
and given into despair.
I remember how hard I fought
to change our cruel destiny
by repeating time over
and over again.
It all ended, finally,
thanks to one girl.
Her sacrifice broke the cycle
of hope and despair.
With that, the world should
have been led
to a new order of things.
However, it seems we've all
forgotten what happened.
Or rather,
we were made to.
Someone is trying to replace
our memories of what happened
with false ones...
And trapped us here
in this false Mitakihara City.
- [chewing]
[plate crashing]
[chattering]
- [laughs]
Oh, you silly thing.
Mind your manners at the table
or you're going
to turn into cheese.
- [chatters]
[chattering]
[grunts]
all: Hmm?
- [chatters]
[all laughing]
- You guys are so cute together.
You're like best friends.
I remember the day I met you
and there was Bebe
tagging along along
and being adorable.
- [giggles]
Bebe and I have been friends
for a long time.
- [chatters]
- I met her before anyone else.
We've had lots of adventures.
Far too many to count.
- Do you remember how Bebe came
to stay with you,
or when you met her?
both: Hmm?
- [chatters]
[chattering]
- [giggles]
I was just curious,
is all.
- [chuckles]
I'm not sure of the exact date,
but it seems like ages ago.
Back in those days,
I was all alone.
The only magical girl
in Mitakihara City.
The only one who comforted me
and cheered me on was Bebe.
[grunts]
[chuckles]
Without Bebe in my life,
I would have given up
the fight long ago.
- Come on.
Don't say that.
- She's right, Mami.
You're much braver
and stronger than that.
- Not really.
I just act confident because
that's what's expected
of a senior magical girl.
The thing is,
Madoka and Sayaka have come into
their own now.
We even have you and Kyouko
to back us up, too.
I never dreamed I'd have
so many friends I could rely on.
I don't have to push myself
so hard anymore because now
I have help.
[gasps]
- [chattering]
- Now, now.
[both giggling]
- The nightmares have
gotten stronger recently,
but I feel way safer fighting
them now than I did before
'cause now I've got
more girls on the team.
Plus I get to work
with my friends
and that's always fun.
- Whoa.
Fighting nightmares
is not supposed to be fun.
Don't forget that.
- [giggles nervously]
- [grunts]
I know what you mean, though.
Things are better now.
It's the kind of life I used
to dream about back before
I met all of you.
We're bound by a destiny
of constant battling.
To find any happiness in a life
like this is incredible.
I never imagined
it would be this way.
- Mami, may I trouble you
for some more tea?
- Sure.
[grunts]
Back in a bit.
- [grunts]
- I have to boil
some more water first.
[whooshing]
- [gasps]
What are you doing?
Is something wrong?
- I'm sorry, Madoka.
[clicking]
- [chatters]
- You can stop the charade now.
- [chattering]
- I remember what you used
to be.
You hear that?
I know what you really are.
- [chattering]
- You've altered our memories
and trapped us
in this fake Mitakihara City.
You can deny it all you want,
Bebe,
but this is your doing.
- [chattering]
[squealing]
- What do you want with us?
Is this some kind
of game to you?
Is this how you have fun?
- [chatters]
[whimpers]
- Memories are so annoying.
As soon as I get one back,
others come flooding in one
after the other.
Yes, I remember Mami Tomoe now.
She always troubled me.
She would put on a strong front
and go all out,
but she had the softest heart
of any of us.
Revealing the truth
was always hard with her there.
Shattering her optimism,
it felt cruel.
And it hurt me.
I remember now,
and I wish I could erase
the memory of all
the hearts I broke.
- [chattering]
[grunts]
- Let's have it.
Why are you doing this to us?
Tell me right now
or I'll end you!
- [chattering]
- [gasps]
[gasps, shouts]
[grunting]
- I was going to wait until
I understood the situation,
but you were hurting Bebe
and I will not stand by
and let that happen.
- You knew what I was up to.
- Yes.
Now explain yourself.
Why do you want to hurt Bebe?
- [gasps]
You're being deceived by her.
This is not the real
Mitakihara City.
Our memories are false.
None of this is real.
- [gasps]
Really now, Homura.
How can you say such things?
- [grunts]
[clicking]
[grunts]
- [chattering]
- [grunts]
Hurry, Bebe.
Run!
- [chattering]
- [grunts]
- I suppose this means
you're going
to protect that creature.
- I'm giving you the chance
to walk away.
If you choose not to...
You'll have to fight me.
- [gasps]
[rock music]
♪
- [shouting]
- [gasps]
[gasps]
We know each other's moves
too well,
but at this rate,
do you think you can beat me?
- I can outlast you.
That's for sure.
[both grunting]
- [grunts]
[gasps]
- [gasps]
[both panting]
[booming]
♪
Well,
we aren't getting anywhere.
- [grunts]
[grunts]
[whooshing]
- [grunts]
[gasps]
- [gasps]
- No, stop!
- [grunts]
[gunshot]
- Homura!
[gasps]
[booming]
- [grunts]
[gasping]
[grunts]
[shudders]
[gasps]
[groaning]
- Your magic is quite fearsome
but in a fight
you're a fool if you think
you'll always have
the upper hand.
- [grunts]
Please, Mami.
Can't you tell
something's wrong?
Don't you feel anything strange
about yourself?
- You could've killed me
but you didn't.
That must mean you still have
some regard for my well-being,
but still,
you were trying to kill Bebe.
- Please try to remember!
She's a witch--
the enemy of magical girls!
- I don't know
what you're saying.
Witches are not our enemies.
The wraiths are.
- [gasping]
- [gasps]
That's right.
Wraiths.
That's what I've been fighting.
But then what
are these nightmares?
[both gasping]
[clanging]
[whooshing]
- [grunting]
What is this?
What's going on?
- Please don't be mad!
- [gasps]
- I can explain!
- [whimpers]
- Wait, who are you?
- Bebe?
- I'm sorry I didn't
say anything till now.
Mami, promise you won't get mad
about what I'm going
to tell you?
- [grunts]
[blow lands]
- [gasps]
What are you doing here?
- Honestly, what the heck
were you thinkin',
takin' on Mami when she's
in top form?
Either you got a lot of guts
or you're super dumb.
- [grunts]
I couldn't help getting into
a fight with her.
I was defending myself.
I was really after--
- Bebe, right?
Lemme guess.
You thought 'cause she used
to be a witch,
she's still that way?
Jump to conclusions much?
- Then you remember?
- 'Course I do.
That's why I'm here.
Think about it, though.
Nothin' about this makes sense.
I mean, why would a witch go
to all the trouble
of makin' a labyrinth big enough
to hold a city
if all she's gonna do
is keep us here?
She isn't tryin' to hurt us,
and she's not luring
new victims in, either, right?
The sweets witch you remember
wouldn't do that.
She'd snuff us out
the first chance she got,
wouldn't she?
You would've realized that
if you stopped to think.
It's pretty obvious
this labyrinth wasn't designed
to lure people in.
The witch who made it wants
to maintain a status quo
in here.
That's all that's goin' on.
Question is,
who would want things
to keep goin' on like this,
and why?
Start there,
work backwards, and--
[blow lands]
Runnin' back into your own
little time again, huh?
That's a bad habit of yours.
You count on that trick
too much.
- [grunts]
You think the person
who trapped us in here
might actually be one of us,
right?
- Would it really be all
that surprising if it was?
Remember what Mami said
about her life now?
She said it's the happiest
she's ever been.
So do you think she
could be the witch?
- Well, a witch
is the final form
of a magical girl.
I don't know.
Maybe she is,
maybe she isn't.
- [scoffs]
That sounds like something
you'd say.
While I gotcha here,
mind if I ask you somethin'?
When you find the witch
who made this labyrinth,
what'cha gonna do with her,
Homura?
- Well, obviously, I'll--
- You'll what?
Kill her?
- [gasps]
- Why?
'Cause she's a witch?
- What are you getting at?
- [chuckles]
Is this really so bad?
I mean, really.
We don't have to kill anyone.
We just keep working together
and having fun.
Is the person who wished
for a life like that so evil
that she deserves to die?
- [gasps]
Hold on.
Are you siding with a witch?
- Like you said,
they're what we become.
Go figure I'd sympathize
with her.
- I just realized something.
A sort of crucial point
in all this.
The creatures Mami
remembered fighting
were wraiths,
not witches.
And Kyouko didn't understand
the concept of labyrinths
when I mentioned it,
not because they'd forgotten
about witches
but because neither of them knew
about them in the first place.
Which makes sense since witches
don't exist in this universe.
A magical girl's soul
is supposed to be taken
by the law of cycles before
she becomes a witch.
That's a concept she created
when she remade the world.
What she sacrificed herself for.
- I knew it.
You remember her, too,
don't ya?
- Yes, I do,
and that's what bothers me.
I should be the only one.
There are three people
in this world
who don't belong in it.
The first one is the witch
who made the labyrinth.
The second one is Bebe who looks
just like a witch.
And the third one is you,
who remembers witches.
Who are you?
Are you really Sayaka Miki?
- Oh, come on.
[giggles]
I'm the same old Sayaka
you've always known,
transfer student.
- [gasps]
[gasps]
- [grunts]
[both grunting]
- [gasping]
Your reflexes are impressive.
You certainly weren't
this agile before.
- Whatever you do next,
ask yourself this one question.
Would you be okay destroying
this version of Mitakihara City?
Think hard about that before
you do anything.
Just so you don't
regret it later.
- This city is fake.
An idealized world
someone dreamed up.
[unsettling chanting]
[high-pitched laughing]
[unsettling music]
♪
- Mami needed help guarding
the city so I came over.
- It's the life I used
to dream about
before I met all of you.
Is this really so bad?
I mean, really.
- Someone dragged us into
this dream world.
A coward who's turned her back
on her responsibility
to fight the wraiths.
I can't forgive anyone
who'd do something like that.
Magical girls must
keep fighting always.
It's the price we've paid
for our wishes.
Our fate was tragic once,
but she gave up everything
to change it.
This farce is wasting
the sacrifice Madoka made
for us.
And I won't allow it.
[all shouting]
- Hey!
Homura!
- [gasps]
[grunting]
[gasps]
- [grunts]
[grunts]
- [gasps]
[both shouting]
[thuds]
- Kyu.
- [gasps]
- [laughs]
- Ah, thank goodness.
I've been looking for you.
Mami's worried about you.
You know that?
What happened?
You okay?
- [gasps]
[grunts]
I'm okay.
[gasps]
- Hey, Homura,
you really shouldn't go off
by yourself like that.
If something's ever bugging you,
you can always come talk
to me if you want.
I might not be able to help
you much with your problems,
but it's way better than having
to worry about them
all by yourself,
isn't it?
It hurts me to see you suffering
so much when all I wanna do
is help.
I wish you would talk to me.
[grunts]
- I had a dream
and it scared me.
- Why?
- In my dream,
you went someplace far away.
[inhales sharply]
And it was so far,
I wasn't gonna be able
to see you again,
and everyone forgot about you.
[engine rumbling]
No one remembered you
except for me!
I was the only one
in the world who could!
[crying]
I was so lonely and sad
and no one understood
how I felt!
I started to think
all my memories of you
were just things I made up!
I thought I was going crazy!
[crying]
[gasps]
- You're right.
That dream does sound awful.
- [gasps]
- But it's okay now, really.
I'm not going anywhere,
especially if it's so far away
I couldn't see you again.
I'd never do something like
that.
- [gasps]
You wouldn't?
But how?
How can you be so sure?
- [giggles]
You know how wimpy I am.
If I did anything
that makes someone as strong
as you cry like this,
it would break my heart.
- [gasps]
It would break your heart?
Leaving us behind would hurt you
that much?
- Of course it would.
I'd hate to leave you
and Sayaka.
Or Mami and Kyouko.
Or my mom, dad, and Tatsuya.
Even Hitomi and all our friends
from class, too.
I wouldn't go if I couldn't see
you guys again.
I know I don't have the courage
to do something like that,
even if I didn't have a choice.
- [gasping]
You're right.
I know you wouldn't.
I knew it would hurt you more
than anything,
but still,
how could I have been so stupid?
I should have stopped you
back then.
no matter what I had to do.
I shouldn't have let it happen.
Madoka.
- Huh?
- I want you to know that when
the time comes
and you have to make
a hard decision,
you will have the courage
to make it.
One day you'll find out there
are things only you can do,
and then you'll know just
how strong
and how kind you really are.
Believe me.
It's the truth.
- [gasping]
Homura?
- Sorry.
You probably don't
remember anything, either.
I know there's a chance
you might just be an illusion
or a fake version
of you someone created.
How else could we see
each other again like this?
Does it even matter?
- [whimpers]
Huh?
- It does to me.
I can tell you're
the real Madoka.
You're here and I can talk
to you again
and feel your kindness
one more time.
And I'm so happy.
Thank you.
I couldn't have asked
for anything that would make
me happier than I am right now.
I have to go now.
Sorry, but there's something
I have to do.
- But where are you going?
- [chuckles]
[grunts]
- I wonder what's going on
with Homura?
- Kyu?
[cell phone ringing]
[techno music playing]
- Hey, Homura.
What's goin' on?
- I was wondering.
Do you remember the witches?
- Hold up.
Witches?
If I said I don't,
is that something
I should be worried about?
- No.
You shouldn't remember them.
- [groans]
The hell's that mean?
Are you messin' with me?
- What about Madoka Kaname?
- Huh?
- Madoka.
Do you remember her?
- Of course I remember her.
Shouldn't I?
[gasps]
Wait, I shouldn't?
- No.
If things were in order,
you shouldn't remember her.
Those memories are false.
- [gasps]
This is like some kinda
bad joke.
For real.
- If I'd stopped and thought
about it from the start,
it would have been obvious.
To create a world
where Madoka exists,
someone would have to know
about Madoka to begin with.
[bus horn honks]
I figured it out.
I know who rewrote our memories
and trapped us
in this false Mitakihara City.
I know who it is.
- What's wrong, Homura?
Tell me where you are!
Let me know
and I'll come get you!
[grunts, gasps]
[dramatic music]
♪
- There's one last thing I have
to confirm to be sure.
Don't worry.
I can do this by myself,
and if I'm right,
I'll end everything.
- Wait.
What?
- I'm sorry I got you involved
in this.
[phone beeps]
There's a limit to the distance
my body can be away
from my soul gem.
At most it should be 100 meters.
[owls hooting]
[clocks gonging]
[booming]
[chanting in foreign language]
[beeping]
- Next stop,
Mitakihara City Second Street.
Passengers bound
for the elementary school
should disembark at this stop.
Stop requested.
[booming]
- It's true.
[gasps]
I'm not a magical girl anymore.
How could this happen?
How?
Why?
Why would I end up as this?
When did it even happen?
When did I become a witch?
[all speaking foreign language]
- I'm sure you didn't
really want
to know the truth,
and yet you couldn't bear it
if you didn't seek it out.
Human curiosity
is quite fascinating.
And illogical.
- [grunts]
- Considering you were
the one searching,
I was certain you'd uncover
the truth eventually...
Homura Akemi.
- Incubator.
I should have known.
This could only be your doing.
- Naturally.
Now,
correct me if I'm wrong,
but you're probably wondering
where your body and soul are.
Would you like to know?
Permit me to show you.
[hissing]
- This is outside
the false Mitakihara City.
This is the real you
in the real world.
- How?
- Simple.
We developed an isolation field
to completely contain
your soul gem.
We were curious
to see what happened
to a tainted soul gem
in a closed environment.
It had to be free from all
external influences
or the experiment wouldn't work.
- Really?
- What is it that cleanses
magical girls
and makes them vanish?
It's something you called
a law of cycles.
Well, we wanted to know
what happened to a soul gem
when it's cut off
from this phenomenon.
Thanks to you,
we witnessed
some very interesting results.
We observed
a peculiar closed space,
one that could shape
its own reality
as well as lure
and trap victims.
Now,
correct me if I'm wrong,
but I believe this is the power
of that witch concept
you explained to us before.
Your soul gem remains intact,
preserved by
the isolation field.
It's the only thing keeping you
from completing
your transformation into
a witch.
Excuse the metaphor,
but you're like a chick
that wasn't able
to break out of its shell
and matured inside it.
That's the reason
you wound up creating
a labyrinth internally
as opposed to externally.
Under these conditions,
you managed to recreate
a whole city
inside your
quote-unquote "shell."
In other words,
this is the world inside
your soul gem.
- Interesting theory.
But if this labyrinth
is isolated from the world,
how could anyone
be lured into it?
It's not possible.
- True.
all: But we made
a little adjustment.
The isolation field's barrier
only works in one direction.
Even though
it repels interference
from the outside,
we can allow victims
to pass through.
[camera shutter clicks]
- But only if they're invited
from within,
and you did the inviting.
You unconsciously chose
your targets.
[camera shutter clicks]
Once you let them enter,
they were trapped.
[camera shutter clicks]
Even under these
limited conditions,
we surmised that
if the entity you refer to
as the law of cycles ever wanted
to reach you, it could.
All that had to happen
was for you to invite it
into your labyrinth.
Then it would materialize
in the form of one
of your targets.
Once trapped,
we incubators would finally
be able to identify
and observe it.
Then we could find out what
this karmic force is
that makes
magical girls disappear.
There are several people
within your labyrinth
who don't exist
in the real world,
and yet they seem
to have existed
at some point in time.
The most interesting of these
is a girl who isn't recorded
in any past memory
and who isn't
a future possibility, either.
Even though she doesn't exist
within the karmic cycles
of our universe,
she was able to slip
into your world
without causing any disturbance.
We were fortunate we didn't have
to spend too much time
or energy searching for it.
Who knows how long that
would have taken?
But you saved us the trouble,
Homura Akemi.
Thanks to you referring
to the law of cycles
as Madoka Kaname,
we were able to identify it
rather quickly.
- Then that is her.
- If we were disappointed
in anything,
it would be that Madoka Kaname
never displayed any sign
of having unusual powers.
It seems the memory rewriting
performed by you--
the master of the labyrinth--
affected her as well.
She not only forgot
the reason she entered--
to save you--
she also lost sight of who
she really was
and her capabilities.
So we couldn't do anything
to her.
[Yuki Kajiura's "Noi!"]
♪
On one hand,
Madoka Kaname forgot
she was a god,
and on the other,
you forgot you were a witch.
Because of that,
we incubators could only watch
as this pointless
endeavor unfolded.
We were fine waiting patiently
and observing
but since you discovered
the truth,
the delicate balance
within your world
has started to crumble.
Now,
Homura Akemi,
reach out to Madoka Kaname
for help.
If you do that,
it will make her remember who
she really is
and what she came here to do.
- Tell me what your
real goal is, incubator.
- Of course.
The law of cycles
has been a hypothesis
up to this point.
Now we can observe it.
[glass cracking]
- For what purpose?
Satisfying curiosity
is illogical.
You said so yourself,
so I can't believe you'd go
to such lengths just
to confirm Madoka exists.
You wanna control Madoka,
don't you?
[exciting music]
♪
- I won't deny it
was our end goal
in this whole affair.
It would have been a long
and difficult endeavor, though.
After all,
this phenomenon has been
a complete mystery to us.
We can't very well interfere
with something
when we can't confirm
its existence.
[booming]
- I seriously doubt you'd
give up trying, though.
- True.
If we could observe it,
we could interfere with it,
and if we can interfere with it,
we can control it.
The information we'd collect
from that would allow us
to conquer the law
of cycles completely.
Then we could make magical girls
turn into witches
and collect vast amounts
of energy all in one go.
Your hope and despair
are the keys.
The phase change between
those emotions
creates huge amounts
of energy.
More than we ever imagined.
You magical girls
are the gateway
to limitless possibilities.
In our humble opinion,
you should all conclude
your existence
by transforming into witches.
- [grunts]
- Why are you angry?
This has nothing to do
with you anymore.
Your existence has reached
its completion,
and now at the end of your life,
you've attained your wish
to meet the one person
you've waited so long for.
I should think you'd be happy
about that.
- Hardly.
I am anything but happy.
- Wait.
You can't be serious.
You're creating a curse?
What are you thinking?
It's spreading too fast
to purify.
- As you are now,
you won't know this,
but you see,
the reason I chose
to become a magical girl
was to save Madoka.
I stand by that choice.
You want me to betray her.
But I'd rather turn into
a witch before I do.
And I will never let
you incubators touch her again.
- You're willing to give up
your salvation for her?
If you do,
you'll spend the rest
of eternity living among
all these curses.
- Not at all.
In fact,
I'll make sure this labyrinth
will be my grave.
Mami Tomoe
and Kyouko Sakura are both here.
I have faith in them.
- That's ridiculous.
Do you have any idea what
it would mean
if you died inside
the isolation field?
You won't be able to break out
of the shell.
You'll transform into a witch
inside its egg.
If you're trapped in there,
the law of cycles
won't sense you.
You'll be destroyed.
And your soul,
no one will be able
to save it from despair.
You'll lose your chance
to see Madoka Kaname
again forever.
You can't want that.
- Would you shut up already?
[indistinct chatter]
- [squeaks]
[chanting in foreign language]
[booming]
I can't believe you'd prefer
the worst possible fate.
[squeaks]
[chanting in foreign language]
Honestly, I can't comprehend why
human thought is so illogical.
[booming]
[chanting in foreign language]
- [gasps]
[dramatic music]
[gasps]
Madoka.
♪
[gasps]
[gasping]
♪
[shudders]
[shouting]
So this is being a witch.
My emotions have all come back
to haunt me again.
[rumbling]
I can't remember
anything anymore.
Just glimmers of light
and regret.
[birds squawking]
[booming]
Yes.
This is it.
My despair.
Madoka.
I just want to say thank you
for coming here
to this god-awful place.
I can't even say goodbye
to you in the end.
I'm sorry.
[buzzing]
[clocks ticking]
[unsettling accordion music]
♪
- That's a witch?
- You don't have
to be scared of her.
She looks horrible but she's
the one who's suffering here.
- It's like a bad joke.
- Wait a moment!
That's Homura Akemi!
You're not really going
to fight your friend, are you?
- Kyubey?
- Huh.
I had no idea you could talk.
- It's unfortunate, Kyubey,
but we have to trust
what Bebe's told us.
- Madoka, listen!
You have the power to save her.
All you have to do
is acknowledge
the real power inside you.
- Huh?
- Don't listen to him, Madoka.
It'll be fine.
You'll see.
Just do it how
I told you earlier.
- Uh, okay.
- [chattering]
[horn blowing]
[uplifting music]
♪
- It's okay, Homura.
We're not gonna let you
go on like this.
Promise.
♪
[applause]
- [gasps]
W--What are you?
- Sayaka and I once brought hope
to the world
but we succumbed to despair
and spread our curses.
- Thanks to the law of cycles,
me and her are working
to free the world
from that destiny once
and for all.
♪
You were so focused on Madoka,
you never noticed us,
did you, incubator?
Keeping you in the dark
was the only way
we could work
without you interfering.
- So the two of you
are actually part
of the law of cycles?
- No, not exactly.
We're more like
her private secretaries.
Our job was to hang on
to all of Madoka's memories
and powers till the time came
to give 'em back to her.
- I'm Sayaka's backup,
and she's mine.
If things went bad
and one of us didn't make it,
there'd always be someone
to return Madoka's memories
to her.
♪
- Sending the three of us
in here to save Homura
seems like overkill to me.
♪
She's keeping us on our toes,
that's for sure.
- Yeah, but it's
for her own good.
So it's worth the trip.
Besides, she fought hard to keep
the world safe,
so savin' her's the least
we can do.
- Sayaka?
[shouts]
- Come on, Madoka.
It's time we got to work.
- [gasps]
Right.
[Kalafina's "Misterioso"]
- [singing in Japanese]
- [shouts]
♪
- What are you doing?
Stop!
You don't understand!
I have to die here!
♪
[both gasping]
- Jeez, Homura.
[grunts]
Quit bein' so stubborn.
We're here to help
so chill out already.
♪
- Man, what the hell have
you guys gotten me into?
There you go.
- [grunts]
Thanks a lot.
Uh--
- I had a horrible dream
about you last night.
You were dead.
[birds chirping]
But it wasn't a dream.
It was real, wasn't it?
This right here,
us fighting side by side,
this is the dream,
ain't it?
- It'd be sad if it were,
but it's not like that.
Not really.
I thought I didn't have
any regrets when I died.
But the truth is,
when I found out about
this assignment,
I jumped at the chance
to come back.
'Cause in the end,
I did have one regret.
You.
I missed you.
- Seriously?
I came back 'cause I wanted
to each cheese one more time.
- [groans]
Thanks a lot.
Way to kill the mood.
- [chuckles]
- [grunting]
- You dummy.
- [giggles]
- [grunting]
- [grunts]
- [scoffs]
[both grunting]
♪
- Tiro Finale!
[booming]
♪
- Homura!
- No, Madoka!
Stop!
♪
- There it is!
The incubators' seal!
- [grunts]
Homura,
once we bust that seal open,
you'll be free!
If the incubators don't have
a hold on you,
you can reach the outside world
and see the real Madoka again.
[film reel clicking]
- [gasps]
[rain pattering]
- Please, Homura.
Stop.
I told you.
You shouldn't go off
by yourself.
- Madoka.
- Whatever happens to you,
good or bad,
you're still you
and I would never abandon you.
So don't give up.
Have faith.
- [crying]
I'm sorry!
[crying]
I'm so weak!
I just wanted you back with me!
I didn't care what
I had to do.
I'd commit the worst sins
for one more chance,
even if it'd turn me into
a monster.
It wouldn't matter.
As long as I could have
you back.
- Let's end this together.
You ready?
- Uh-huh.
[dramatic music]
♪
- You're not scared,
are you?
- Mm-mmm, I'm fine.
I'm not afraid.
I'm ready.
[whooshing]
[booming]
- This is so illogical!
♪
- [grunts]
[dramatic music]
♪
- Sayaka and Bebe,
they're gone just like that?
- Not yet.
- Huh?
- They're helping Madoka
take Homura away.
- Is that Madoka Kaname?
- Yes.
She's the law of cycles
and one day she'll take us, too.
- I remember.
The reason I'm here
was to get Homura back.
I can't believe I'd forget
something so important.
- Well, you did have some
unnecessary interference.
What a trip.
Talk about spinnin' our wheels.
- That was kind of annoying.
- You waited
for me all this time.
I'm sorry it took so long
but I'm here now.
- Madoka.
- Come on.
Let's go.
From now on,
we'll be together.
- You don't know
how long I've waited...
For this.
- [gasps]
Homura?
- Now...
[chuckles]
I've got you.
- What's goin' on?
- What does she think
she's doing?
Homura?
- Look at her soul gem!
What are all those horrible
colors?
- It's not a curse.
What is that?
Obsession?
Desire?
Homura, what's happening to you?
- [gasps]
I don't expect you
to understand.
No one in the world
could possibly understand.
[all grunting]
This emotion is mine
and mine alone.
And I've been saving it for her.
[glass shattering]
[elephant trumpeting]
- [gasps]
- Homura.
- Don't!
You'll rip me apart!
[gasps]
- It has to be this way.
[glass shattering]
I'm never going
to let you go again, Madoka.
[glass shatters]
[all gasping]
[glass crunches and shatters]
- The world is being rewritten.
Does this mean
a new principle has been born
into this universe?
- You don't remember
the last time this happened,
do you?
Well, this is the second time
I've seen this.
- What's happening?
Homura Akemi,
what are you meddling in?
You're changing something,
but what?
- [scoffs]
- I don't believe it.
Your tainted soul gem should
have disappeared with your soul,
but it hasn't.
Why?
- Because I remember why
I repeated time
and suffered over
and over again.
My feelings for Madoka,
they run so deep,
even pain has become precious
to me.
And as for my soul gem,
a curse isn't
what's tainting it.
- Then what is?
- Something you
can't understand, incubator.
It is the pinnacle
of all human emotion.
More passionate than hope.
Much deeper than despair.
Love.
- Then what are you?
You're not a magical
girl anymore
but you're not transforming into
a witch, either.
- You're right.
I'm not a magical girl
or a witch.
Madoka is as sacred as a god
and I pulled her from Heaven.
So if you want to know
what I've become,
I suppose if anything,
you could call me a demon now.
- There's no doubt now.
Trying to put human emotions
to use
is just too dangerous for us.
We could never hope
to control something
whose final form
is so irrational.
- Is that so?
- [grunts]
- The curses that have spread
across our world still have
to be dealt with.
And you incubators have
become necessary for that task.
You're going to stay and help.
Incubator!
[static hissing]
[explosive pop]
[glass shatters]
- [gasps]
[birds chirping]
[dramatic music]
- [chewing]
Hmm?
[chuckles]
♪
[gasps]
[birds crowing]
- Hey, do you have any idea
what you've done?
- I do,
but if you'd like
to share your thoughts,
please enlighten me.
- Okay, you broke off a piece
of the law of cycles.
It's the only salvation
us magical girls had.
- I only took
a tiny sliver of it.
That's all.
The piece that used
to be Madoka
before she ceased to exist.
For some reason you were all
pulled in with her.
And you you can't return
to where you came from, either.
- You have no right to screw
everything up like this!
- I'm an existence
called evil now.
And if evil is supposed
to disrupt the divine
and be a force of chaos,
it's only natural for me
to upset the laws of a god.
- Oh, yeah?
What'll you do next?
Destroy everything?
- After all the wraiths
have been wiped out,
perhaps I will.
When that day comes,
I suppose I can be
your enemy then.
The question is,
will you be able
to stand up against me?
[claps]
- [gasp]
- You're having a hard time
remembering things, aren't you?
- [panting]
[giggling]
- [winces]
- [giggles]
- I...
I think I remember being part
of something.
Some kind of being or power
bigger than this world.
But I--I can't remember what
it was anymore.
- [giggling]
- All I know is I'm not supposed
to be here.
- You're getting another chance
at being human again.
If anything you should be happy
about that.
Eventually life here
will seem natural to you
and you'll forget all about
the past.
- Even if I do,
there's one thing
I won't forget.
You, Homura Akemi,
are a demon!
- We should pretend
to be on good terms.
If you're always attacking me,
Madoka might end up hating you.
- [giggling]
Hi!
- Hey, Sayaka.
- [gasps]
- How you doing?
- Good morning, Sayaka.
Sleep well?
- Uh, yeah.
[gasps]
Sorry.
Hey, guys.
How's it goin'?
What's up?
- Are you okay, Sayaka?
- [laughs]
Yeah, I'm fine.
It's just, I don't know.
I guess when I saw you guys
and heard you both say
good morning again,
I guess I got super happy,
that's all.
- Oh, Sayaka.
Sometimes you say
the most mysterious things.
- Yep, that's me.
The original international girl
of mystery.
[laughing]
[school bell rings]
- Remember, girls.
Do not associate with men
who refuse to eat eggs
unless they've been half boiled,
and you boys better make sure
you don't grow up to be men
who complain about how
the darn eggs are cooked!
Understand?
Now that that's out of the way,
let's give a big welcome
to our new classmate.
Miss Kaname,
come on in.
[uplifting music]
[all gasping]
♪
- Um, my name is Madoka Kaname.
It's nice to meet you.
M--um, I--I'm sorry.
I mean my mother,
she was transferred to the US
so we had to move there.
We lived there for three years
and just moved back,
and now that we're back,
I'll be starting school
here today.
And, uh, it's--
it's nice to meet you.
[clapping]
- Since she's been out
of the country for so long,
she might need
some help adjusting,
so let's all pitch in
and help her out, okay?
- Hey, I was wonderin',
what was goin' to school like
in America?
- Was it cool over there?
I bet it was, huh?
I wish I could go.
- You're so teeny and cute.
You look like a grade schooler.
- [laughs]
Gee, thanks,
but I'm not that teeny.
- You guys?
Can't you see you're making
her nervous bombarding her
with questions?
Why don't you give her a moment?
- Oh, yeah.
Uh, sorry about that.
- [gasps]
- I'm Homura Akemi.
Nice to meet you,
Miss Kaname.
May I call you Madoka instead?
- [gasps]
Uh, sure.
- If you don't mind,
I'd like to show you
the campus now.
Follow me, please.
Um, Miss Akemi?
I, uh--
- Call me Homura.
- [gasps]
Homura, I, uh,--
how, I mean,
why are you showing me around?
- How does it feel
to be back again?
- Oh, well, I guess
everything feels familiar
and at the same time
it's different.
It feels strange.
- I'm not surprised.
It's been three years.
- No, it feels like
nothing's changed at all.
In fact,
if anything's changed
around here...
It's me.
- [gasping]
- Yeah.
It is me.
I should have a different form.
A different purpose here.
- [gasps]
[gasps]
- So, why?
- [whimpers]
[gasps]
- Homura?
Hey, let go!
- [breathing heavily]
It's okay.
You're exactly what
you should be.
What you've always been.
- Huh?
[gasps]
- Madoka Kaname,
do you treasure
the world you live in,
or would you break its laws
to follow your heart?
- [gasps]
Well, I--I, uh, I don't--
I--I mean, yes!
I do treasure this world.
But I don't think a person
should go and break the rules
just because they feel like it.
- Oh, I see.
Well then,
I suppose one day you
will also be my enemy.
- [gasps]
- It's fine.
I don't care.
- [gasps]
- I'll keep wishing for a world
where you can be happy.
- [gasping]
Homura?
Um...
- [grunts]
I knew it.
They always did
look better on you.
- [gasps]
[church bells ringing]
[dramatic music]
♪
[Kalafina's "Kimino Ginno Niwa"]
- [singing in Japanese]
♪
[dramatic music]
[rustling]
- [gasps]
♪
[gasps]
[film reel clicking]