Marvelous Entertainment.
♪
Well, that was good.
I'm going out for a bit,
so I'll see you later.
Rika, I'm getting sick
of you ignoring me.
I want you to give
me one good reason
why I can't ride
ATs with my friends!
You can't expect me
to just accept this.
Whether you
accept it or not,
you still can't ride.
(door closing)
♪
‐Ikki?
‐Huh?
Don't be upset.
Rika's just
worried about you.
Tell me the truth.
I think I deserve to know
about this whole
Sleeping Forest thing.
I mean, what kind
of team was it anyway?
I'm the only one here
who doesn't know
what's going on.
Sorry, Ikki, but
I promised the others
I wouldn't talk about it.
(door rattling)
♪
Sora, are you there?
Sora?
(footsteps clicking)
Hey, Cold; hey, Stone,
have you two been good?
I haven't seen
you in a while,
I'm surprised you
still remember me.
Nice weather
we're having today,
don't you think?
♪
Having you here with
the wind blowing like this
feels like old times.
(dogs barking)
So you said you
needed to talk.
I'm guessing it must have
something to do with Ikki.
What makes you say that?
Well, that's the way
it's always been.
For as long as
I can remember,
whenever you needed
to have a talk,
it's because Ikki
was giving you trouble.
I guess I never
really noticed.
And you know
I don't even think
you're aware
you're doing it.
♪
I was only
eight years old
when we took in Ikki
from Uncle Minami.
It was tough on me
because I had to help
take care of
my sisters, too.
Back then, we were
still getting money
to take care of him
and pay the rent,
so at least we didn't have
to worry about the bills.
Still, he was quite a handful.
It was really
frustrating sometimes.
Do you know
about Demon Rock?
Ha, I've heard that
story a million times.
I'm sorry, but the whole
thing still blows my mind.
When I saw Ikki
jump off that rock,
it sent a shiver
up my spine.
Even after all these years,
I've never forgotten
that feeling.
♪
That boy is
loved by the wind.
In a way, it's exciting,
but I'm afraid
of what might happen.
He's so much like you.
It's almost scary.
There's no telling
how far he'll go.
He has the power
to ride the wind
all the way to the
ends of the Earth.
To fly so far
that I won't be able
to reach him anymore.
I fear the god of wind
will carry him away.
I don't blame you
for feeling that way.
After all, the god of wind
can be pretty cruel sometimes.
I think I know that
better than anyone.
I don't care if
Ikki hates me for this.
In the end, I'd rather
have him resent me
than see him get hurt.
After all, he's the only
little brother I've got.
(crying)
I'm sorry, Rika,
I never knew.
I mean, just the
other day he had a fall
that probably
would have killed him
if he hadn't
landed in water.
(crashing)
(dog whining)
(panting)
Yeah, that's great,
but what do you
want me to do?
I just want you
to talk to him.
I think this is something
only you can talk about.
(barking)
(yelling)
Ikki, what the hell?
(screams)
♪
(growls)
(scream)
♪
Whoa!
Looks like we meet again.
You've got to mind
your manners, kid,
it ain't nice to eavesdrop.
So, I hear
you're next in line
to be the Sky King.
The Sky King?
I didn't know that.
I think it's about time
you spill the beans, Rika.
Or maybe I should
call you Queen of Thorns
like they used to in
your Sleeping Forest days.
Why don't you tell him
about your Sonia Road?
♪
All right,
I get it, I get it.
Back when you were
in Sleeping Forest
you used to be
some kind of AT queen
with your own road
and everything.
I bet you led your team
in lots of Parts Wars
and won all
kinds of emblems.
You used to fly high and do
whatever you wanted to, right?
So come on, why can't
I do the same thing?
Sorry, Sora, I shouldn't
have bothered you with this.
Wait, Rika, you can't
turn your back on this now.
Like you said,
the god of the wind
will carry him away.
♪
I think you
should tell him, too.
Ikki's already
started to fly.
He's gone too far
to just give up.
If you don't
talk to him now,
the situation is only
going to get worse, Rika.
Sorry, Rika,
but I agree.
You what?
♪
Come on, Rika,
you ought to know
he's not the type of guy
who's gonna
follow your rules
unless you've got
a damn good explanation.
No kidding.
Rika, let's just
talk about this
so I don't have
to worry you anymore.
Ikki...
♪
After all this, I guess
he deserves to know.
♪
What's this, a soda?
Yeah, use it
on your ankle.
Oh, thanks,
I'll pay you back.
Nah, don't worry,
it's on me.
Just consider it
my admission fee
for watching that
battle of yours.
It's worth it for
a chance to meet
the famous Queen of Thorns.
I'm actually a
pretty big fan of yours.
(chuckling)
♪
Well, later.
Hey wait, your money!
I promise I'll pay you back
next time I see you, okay?
I think the
reason I said that
was to convince myself
that we'd see
each other again.
I warned you, didn't I?
Roses have thorns, you know.
If you don't
watch yourself,
you might just
end up getting pricked.
(clapping)
Wow, bravo, good show.
You don't disappoint.
I was wondering when
I'd see you again.
Here, I've got your cash.
Cash, why do
I need cash?
For the soda you
gave me, of course.
That's funny, I just
had it right here,
where'd it go?
(chuckling)
My name's Sora,
it means sky.
Big open kind
with lots of clouds.
That's a pretty flashy
name for a guy like you.
But now that
you mention it,
that flighty
attitude of yours
does kind of
remind me of a cloud.
Wow, so you've been
carrying that money around
ever since we met?
I‐‐I just don't like being
in anyone's debt, okay?
Really, it's just a soda.
Anyway, is there
a reason why
you're always riding
alone like that?
Wha‐‐what do you mean?
Usually people
who are into ATs
belong to some kind of
team or something, right?
You don't get
to have much fun
if you ride alone.
That's what it's come down to
since they started
this Parts War.
You're right.
You know,
I used to ride my ATs
to have a good time.
But now it seems
like everywhere I go,
someone is always trying
to pick a fight with me.
That's too bad‐‐
well, see you next time,
whenever that is.
‐Later.
‐Hey, hold on!
I haven't paid you yet!
From then on, I started
running into Sora
at more and more AT battles.
I guess I was too busy
with my own
fights to notice,
but I never
saw him get involved
in a Parts War.
Good evening,
your majesty.
Getting bored
now that you've
conquered all
the teams around here?
Actually, I head some team
called Sleeping something
is taking control
of this area.
Really?
It's no ordinary
team, either,
there's some really
tough Storm Riders
that got together and totally
dominated the Parts Wars.
They're even calling
themselves kings.
Heard of 'em?
I think I heard
about it somewhere.
I'm trying to remember
the name of the guy
who runs the team.
I can't say for sure,
but I think his last name
is something like Takeuchi.
So what do you say
we do this together?
Do what?
Kick their ass.
I hate it when
arrogant jerks like that
gang up and think they
can push people around.
Come on, we can take
those losers, right?
♪
This is where the
Sleeping Forest hangs out.
So that's how you've been
beating all these teams.
No stickers, no emblems,
just a good old
fashioned ass‐whipping.
Hey, can I ask you something?
As long as
I've know you,
you've always ridden alone.
Why'd you invite
me this time?
I don't know I just‐‐
Uh!
♪
Hold on, Sora, I'll
finish these guys in no time.
♪
What's going on?
Sora?
♪
I know it looks bad,
but I wasn't trying
to hide anything from you.
Maybe I ought to introduce
myself again, huh?
♪
I'm the original leader
of the Sleeping Forest,
Sora...Takeuchi.
Nice to meet ya.
♪
But you can call
me Sky King, baby,
'cause my wings
are big, strong,
and last all night long.
I didn't care about
teams or Parts Wars
or anything like that.
But when Sora asked me
to join the Sleeping Forest,
I couldn't say no.
I became one
of their kings,
but at the time
I didn't know
what I was getting into.
I just wanted
to be with Sora.
I got a dream, you know.
There's something I want
to accomplish with this team.
It's gonna be big.
It's gonna change the world.
He always had this
twinkle in his eye,
like a little boy.
And when he spoke,
he sounded more
like a politician.
But I need help.
That's why I
had to gather
all these different kings.
Of course,
I need your help, too.
So, are we gonna
do this or what?
Sure, after all,
I still owe you.
Oh, yeah.
Well, if you really
want to pay me back,
I can think of a way.
Hey, hold on,
it was just a soda,
don't push
your luck, all right?
Here, close your eyes.
Sora.
For the longest time,
I never knew what
I was fighting for.
But when I was with him,
I thought I'd finally
found a reason.
♪
(evil laughter)
(scream)
♪
Sora, Sora!
Sora!
Say something, Sora!
I guess it was
too high after all.
It looks like
I won't be able
to fly with you anymore.
Nooo!
Our wings had been
drenched in the blood
of his lofty dreams.
In the end, they collapsed
under their own weight.
Sora, here.
I don't want it anymore.
You can throw it away,
for all I care.
Don't be ridiculous.
This emblem is
the symbol of your dream.
I can't just
throw it away.
My dream, huh?
Don't give me that crap.
You don't know a
damn thing about my dream.
Don't get the
wrong idea, all right?
The only reason
we were together
is 'cause I needed
the Queen of Thorns
to rise to the top.
Girls like you
are nothing but
a royal pain in the ass.
You think you're special
just 'cause we got together?
‐Stop it!
‐(slap)
(distant dog barking)
I'm sorry.
That dream of mine
is dead now.
All my hopes and
feelings fell apart
like some fake wings
made out of wax.
I can't fly anymore,
understand?
Go find the real Sky King.
We're through.
♪
(sobbing)
It was then that I realized
that all along,
he had been my wings.
And although I had
thought we were reaching
for the sky together,
in the end, I was
nothing but a burden.
♪
It doesn't matter how
much the wind loves you,
there's always someplace
beyond your reach.
I can't stand
that Storm Riders
are willing to
risk their lives
over some silly Parts War.
You can understand
that, can't you?
So you'll stop,
you'll stop riding for me?
Ikki?
♪
Uh‐uh.
Huh?
I don't wanna,
I don't wanna!
No means no,
I'm gonna fly!
I don't have
to listen to you!
I'm asking nicely.
All right, Rika, you
want me to quit that bad?
Then bet your emblem.
How 'bout that?
♪
If I lose, I'll
hand over my ATs
and quit riding,
no questions asked.
But if I win,
then I do what I want
and you promise to butt
out of my business forever.
♪
(laughing)
Good call!
That's how a
Storm Rider does it.
Sora, don't encourage him!
Who the hell's side
are you on, anyway?
Sorry, hate to say it,
but I'm afraid
I'm gonna have to
side with him on this one.
Listen, Rika, even
after all that's happened,
I ain't got no regrets.
I'd do it all again.
'Cause if you take a
man's dream away from him,
then what the hell's he
supposed to do with himself?
Might as well have
never been born, you know?
♪
I see that I was mistaken
about this after all.
♪
I was mistaken to
think I could trust you
to help me to
convince Ikki to quit!
And since you won't
listen to reason,
I'll have to beat
some sense into you!
This is bad!
She's really pissed off.
(screams)
That's okay,
'cause I know you guys
are still
on my side, right?
Well, we, uh...
Of course we are, huh?
Yeah, of course.
Because if you betray me,
you know what
you're gonna get!
Don't know, but I'm
guessing it won't feel good!
Whatever it is,
I know I don't want it!
All right, that settles it.
We'll have a
B‐Class Parts War.
That's disk,
if you didn't know.
We'll have to bend
the rules a little,
but I think
it'll work out.
Check it out, Rika and Ikki
will be disk holders.
Everyone else
will play defense.
Now if the
holders get the disk
into the opposing
team's end zone,
they get a point.
First team to score
ten points is the winner.
This is really weird.
How did we get dragged
into this anyway?
This is starting
to get interesting.
In this corner,
we've got the new and
old Sky King candidates
along with three dogs.
Our opponent is the new
and old Sleeping Forest.
Show 'em who's boss, kid.
Like I say,
if you're a real man,
sometimes you got to let
your fists do the talkin'.
Right.
(panting)
(barking)
I traded one team
of bitches for another.
You know,
you should be grateful
for a chance like this.
It's not every day you get
to have a high‐ranked battle
with the legendary
Sleeping Forest.
Don't hold back.
You got it!
(electricity humming)
(bell ringing)
♪
Rika, you sure you want
to do this in your sneakers?
I still got some old
ATs back at my place
if you want to borrow 'em.
No thanks.
I can beat you just
fine without them.
You really better give it
all you got, kid.
'Cause it looks
like you've awakened
the Queen of Thorns
from her slumber.
I'm telling you, if she's
anything like she used to be,
you're in for one
hell of a fight.
♪
All right, way to go
white dog!
♪
This is a pain in the ass.
Let's just get it over with.
Watch it, fleabag!
What are you doing,
Mikan, they're just dogs.
(barking)
(scream)
Really scary dogs!
♪
Don't underestimate
my partners.
Not bad for fleabags.
♪
I never thought
I'd face off
with the old leader
of Sleeping Forest.
I've always wanted to
have a battle with him.
Even in a wheelchair,
he's hard to keep up with.
Not too shabby,
but let me show you
why I'm still king.
(scream)
Divine wind attack,
Sora Takeuchi's version two!
All right,
now it's your turn!
♪
Dammit, she's fast.
Hey, dumbass, what are
you doin' back there?
I told you we don't
score any points
unless you make
the touchdown!
♪
Mikan!
Come on, kid, defense!
Knock her down
if you have to!
Huh?
(yells)
♪
(yelling)
You call yourself
the Sky King
and this is
all you've got?
You're lucky I'm
going easy on you.
Back in my day,
you'd be lying
in a puddle of
your own blood by now.
You're wasting my time.
I don't believe it.
I'm telling you,
that girl's as hot
as the day I met her.
Take a look at that ass.
Is that a fine
piece of work or what?
Huh?
Ugh, come on, man.
Don't you know
it's bad form
to tell someone
his sister's ass is hot?
'Cause if I say
no then I'm lying
and if I say yes,
then I'm just a perv.
That's not the point,
all right?
Listen, normally
when you're riding ATs,
you use your knee joints
as the core of your movement.
But for the Queen of Thorns,
the core is higher.
Her attacks have
a wider range of motion
because they
originate from her hips
instead of her knees.
Ergo, nice ass.
(bell ringing)
That technique
of hers blocks your path
like a wall of thorns.
If you ain't the real Sky King,
there's no way you're
gonna make it through.
Got it!
I can do this!
I'm not gonna
give up my ATs!
Uh?
(screams)
♪
I can do this,
I'm not giving up.
No matter what,
I'm not giving up my ATs.
The Sonia Road pushes a rider
to their absolute limit.
If Rika keeps this up,
she's gonna tear
her legs to pieces.
Don't worry,
I'll chop down
her wall of thorns
in no time.
I know Rika's doing
this to protect Ikki,
but I don't know who
to believe in anymore.
Next time on Air Gear,
I'll break free
from this cage
and reach for the sky!
♪