♪
Glad you could
make it, Kogarasumaru!
Welcome to
Behemoth's Battlefield,
the underground coliseum!
♪
(yelling)
These are the remains of the
beasts who've challenged us
only to be
slaughtered by our fangs.
Now all that's left of their
teams is a graveyard of parts.
Kogarasumaru!
♪
Looks like he's
going in‐‐come on!
Hey, wait for me!
Let's go!
‐Kill 'em dead!
Yeah, baby, plug
me in, plug me in,
and turn it on!
No, no, not like that!
You're gonna fry my circuits!
Too many plugs
in one outlet, man!
(laughing)
Glad you could
make it out tonight.
Gotta give props to
all you violence junkies
sitting in on the big fight.
As always, your MC for
the night is me, DJ Plugman.
You better recognize, biotch!
♪
(cheering)
We've got ten wild
animals in the cage
for the D‐Class cube battle!
Our matchup for tonight is
the newbie team Kogarasumaru
and the Great Beast Behemoth!
If you're new to the scene,
the rules are simple!
The last man standing wins.
Now, if sickos
wanna see some blood,
then you came to
the right place!
So let's get medieval!
They need three wins,
and they're at a
pretty big disadvantage.
I'm sure Agito's
counting on Swimsuit‐‐
I mean, Croissant Mask
to win one of these fights.
What should I do?
Who should I switch with?
Man, this place is nuts!
Used to be a sewage plant
before they took it over
and turned it into an arena.
Up ahead, the pipe
is gonna branch off
in different directions.
After that, you can
go wherever you want.
Each path leads
to a different cube
where your opponent
is waiting for you.
The battle has already begun,
so put your game face on!
‐Is that it?
‐Well,
it looks like we've
got three choices,
so what's it gonna be?
I'm taking this one!
Good luck!
All right, then I
guess this one's mine.
Hope you're making
the right choice!
(sniffing)
‐Ew!
‐Yeah.
Gross‐‐why do I
always get stuck
fighting disgusting,
pig‐faced losers?
Now, now, I'll have you know
that out of all the
people in Kogarasumaru,
no one understands the
mysteries of a woman's heart
quite like me.
Whatever, a battle
is still a battle.
I'm Ryo Mimasaka, otherwise
known as the Gorgon Shell.
In five seconds, I'll
give you a taste of heaven.
♪
There's someone
here‐‐I can feel it!
♪
But I don't know
where the hell they are!
I am the Aeon Clock,
Yasuyoshi Sano.
You've got a cute face, boy.
It's a pity I
have to destroy it.
Time, heed my command.
(grunting)
It's too tight!
This is discrimination!
Ah, who am I kidding,
it's my fat ass.
(hissing)
Now I get it‐‐this is what Agito
was trying to warn Ikki about!
I'm the Hecatonchires
Bomb, Fuumei Goshogawara!
The battle's already
started, fat ass!
(laughing)
You've been here
before, haven't you?
It looks like you took
this passage on purpose.
So which one of these
leads to Akira's cube?
That one.
Oh, yeah?
‐So it's that one.
‐What?
Bastard!
I'm just kidding, don't worry.
I don't care about
that Akira guy,
so I'm not gonna snatch
away your prey or whatever.
If we want this brilliant
plan of mine to work out,
then both of us have to win
these matches no matter what.
So don't lose,
even if it kills you!
Ha‐‐who the hell do you
think you're talking to?
♪
‐Yo.
‐I'm the Cyclops Hammer,
Mitsuru Bando.
You're going down!
Oh, yeah, bug eyes?
Bet your pride on it‐‐
let's see what you've got!
♪
Akira Udo.
It's time to settle this.
You've had something of
mine for the last two years,
and now I've come
to take it back.
You know what
I'm talking about‐‐
I've come to claim
my place among the kings.
The Fang King Regalia
will be mine!
(cheering)
♪
Whoa, that's Burning
Heaven, no way!
Oh, my God, it's really them!
(shrieking)
I'm gonna puke.
Hey, what's up, you guys?
You ready to rock?
We came out to show
Behemoth some love tonight!
But before we get started,
I have an announcement to make.
We've been bugging him
about this for a long time,
but we finally got
Akira to make us a deal!
If he wins tonight's
battle, he'll join the band!
Yeah!
Wahoo‐‐you hear that?
That's the sound of
the bomb being dropped!
Now that we've got
the music pumping,
why don't we take a
look at the monitors
and see how the
fight's coming along?
Huh?
This is Hecatonchires's cube,
but there's nobody in there!
What's going on?
Huh?
What the hell is that?
It's a meatball‐‐
a pork meatball!
I wonder what just
happened in there!
It looks like Fuumei gave
the meatball a one‐way ticket
down the River Styx.
All right, this
should be interesting!
Let's rewind the tape
to see what went down.
Yeah, the Digger Wasp Rock!
What, you never heard
of a digger wasp?
They live in the South America,
and they're famous
for shaking their ass
and building a nice little
bedroom in the ground.
Once they sting their prey,
they drag 'em
into their tunnels
and start rockin' and rollin'.
Then when their
prey gets worked up
into a nice little
meatball, they eat him!
Hecatonchires's Digger Wasp
Rock uses the same concept
except the eatin' part.
(cheering)
Buccha, no.
Man, talk about an
instant kill technique!
That meat was deep‐fried
before he even
landed in the skillet.
Now let's switch to Camera Two
to have a word with the winner!
Uh, wait, that ain't right!
♪
I can't believe it!
The meatball was able
to stop his spinning
with brute force!
His world has been
turned upside down!
The Hecatonchires Bomb
has self‐destructed!
(grunting)
♪
All right, you
coffee‐colored pig.
You better pray to God
that you end up
fighting the wasp guy.
You're probably the
only fat ass in Japan
who can reverse this technique!
Now listen up, and
I'll tell you what to do!
♪
What's wrong with
you, you freak?
I paid good money for this!
‐Come on!
‐Ooh‐‐oh, yeah,
that's right, he said
something about that!
It may not look like it,
but Buccha's actually
only got ten percent body fat!
Then how do you explain
his big fat belly?
That's not fat, it's blood!
Since he's always overeating,
blood pools up in his stomach
and makes it look
like he's overweight!
But when it's time to fight,
he redistributes the blood
to his muscles, giving
him superhuman strength!
(indistinct yelling)
♪
Wow, keep up the
good work, guys.
I'm pulling for you.
Hmm‐‐I thought I was
gonna die back there.
That guy can really spin.
Good thing it's over.
My arms are already
at their limit.
Well, that's it, boys and girls.
In Cube number
three, the winner is‐‐
No way.
Don't get too cocky,
you Berkshire pig,
'cause the fight's
just getting started.
I‐‐I didn't want
an easy win anyway.
♪
(grunting)
How the hell is he doing that?
Hecatonchires has
dislocated his arms
and is using them like whips!
Now he's got a huge reach
advantage over the meatball!
Since each wall of the cube
is less than 18 feet wide,
there's no place in
the room he can't reach!
I hate to use this move
on a bloated pig like you,
‐but you leave me no choice!
‐This is it!
The Killer Bee Hundred!
How do you like it, huh?
Aren't you gonna
pump yourself up?
You can't do it, can you?
Your body can't take it anymore,
especially not
after this, porky!
(groaning)
That is sick‐‐the friction
from all those punches
is burning the meatball's skin!
(cheering)
You hear that?
Sounds like one of the
battles has ended already.
You've changed over
the last two years.
You didn't used to wear
those stupid chains.
If animals don't
evolve, they die out.
But while my fangs have
been growing stronger,
it looks like yours have dulled.
Face it, Agito,
you've become obsolete.
♪
Oh, the meatball stopped movin'!
Looks like he's out cold.
So weak, so pathetic.
Looks like I was wrong.
This is it.
Yeah, you're right.
It's obvious that your fangs
are longer than anyone else's.
♪
Huh?
After all this hype,
that's all you got?
Never thought you'd be
so weak and pathetic!
I expected more
from a Holy Beast!
Did you really think that
you were gonna take me down
with those puny little
bee stings, you punk?
I'll swallow you in
one bite and top you off
with lots of royal jelly!
(growling)
♪
But you know, the woolly
mammoth, saber‐toothed tiger,
and dire wolf all became
extinct because of long fangs.
♪
I can't believe it!
The meatball is taking command!
Hecatonchires is
totally screwed!
(cheering)
Well, this has been
quite a surprise.
I bet even Agito didn't think
it would turn out this well.
You think?
Actually, this is working
out exactly how I imagined.
I've always thought that
Buccha had impressive potential,
even when he first
started the Yao.
It's someone else
I'm worried about.
You mean the Little Crow?
No, I mean the one who has to
face the man who controls time.
(panting)
(squeaking)
♪
(yelling)
He did it again!
Where is he coming from?
I have to admit, your
reflexes are pretty good!
But it's no use.
To one such as I who
controls time itself,
you're nothing but a block
of marble frozen in place.
‐An hourglass.
‐Three minutes.
In just three minutes, these
fingers will carve your flesh
into a beautiful sculpture.
(yelling)
I can't see him.
Agito!
This is Aeon Clock.
For the record, he controls time
and has a thing
for underage boys.
That's all you need to know,
and if you end up fighting him,
try to die
gracefully, all right?
‐Good.
‐Hey, hold on a second!
There's gotta be something!
Can't we stop time, too?
Well, even if you could find
a way to counter his technique,
you still wouldn't
be able to win.
Time control or no time
control, his battle level is 82.
But it is a trick, right?
I mean, there's no way somebody
can actually stop
time, is there?
I'm telling you it's pointless
either way, all right?
Next, ready?
Agito.
What's that supposed to mean?
Hell if I know.
Even flies and ants
can show their wrath.
It means you shouldn't
write something off
just 'cause it's small.
'Kay.
Agito, I think there's something
you need to learn, too.
Everyone always thinks that
the strong prey on the weak,
but you know, when the
situation calls for it,
the weak can prey
on the strong, too.
Whatever, I guess you
wouldn't understand.
Wake me up when
the meeting's over.
If the predator
attacks with his fangs,
what does an animal
with no fangs do, run?
That can be a road, too.
I may run, but that doesn't
mean I'm running away!
Whoa, what's going on?
The dude in the
beanie just disappeared.
Now what the hell are
we supposed to watch?
Man, I bet we are the dumbest
audience in the world right now,
sitting here
stretching out our necks
and squinting our eyes to look
at a little gray room
with nobody in it!
I hate to say it, but this
battle's getting kinda boring!
We wanna see some blood!
♪
I remember when I used to
just stare up at the sky
like an idiot.
Back then, I really
thought I was free
to go anywhere I wanted,
but I never realized
that there was an iron
fence holding me back.
And by the time I finally
noticed, my dream had died,
and the world
belonged to someone else.
Every day, my share of space
got smaller and smaller,
and the fences surrounding
me climbed higher and higher.
It seemed like before I
even learned how to crawl,
I knew I'd never have
the strength to fly.
I knew I'd only see the sky
through the links in the fence.
♪
That's why I'll keep running.
Even if I can't reach the sky,
I'll keep running
in this shitty cage
until I can't run anymore!
Man, screw this.
Let's take a look through
our super high‐speed camera.
There he‐‐there he is!
Holy crap, beanie boy
is really tearing it up!
It looks like you're going
to get your ass handed to you
if you think this is just
another team of F‐Class newbies!
Be careful, Kazu.
♪
I'll see through your
trick, just watch me!
♪
(ticking)
‐What the hell?
‐Now, time.
Heed my command.
♪
That's no good!
I want to hear a
scream that blossoms
from the depths of your soul!
(screaming)
Good‐‐a canary's
voice is most beautiful
when it has lost all hope
and sings a final song
filled with despair.
Holy crap, that poor
bastard's getting nailed
by the Great Wheel of Time!
One of Aeon's certain
kill techniques!
♪
I was afraid this would happen.
Kazu.
Kazu, sweetie!
Huh‐‐there you are!
I made a whole pot of
my special garlic stew!
Why don't you come
eat with everyone else?
Oh, sorry, I'll
be done in a sec.
I just wanna sit here
a little bit longer.
Hmm?
Why don't you come
over here and sit down?
I...
I can't believe we're
finally alone together.
He's so close.
This is my chance to
tell him how I feel.
But I didn't have time to
prepare‐‐what am I gonna say?
♪
Um, I, uh...
Look at the sky.
♪
Normally, it feels
so big and far away,
but from here, look.
It almost seems like you can
reach out and grab it, right?
♪
Sorry, time's up.
Au revoir.
♪
What the hell?
Where did those
red lines come from?
♪
Blood?
I see‐‐damn.
That's why he
was running around.
If I look at the lines,
then the answer's obvious.
You're right there!
I've got you now‐‐
you can't hide!
Take that!
Yes, yes, kick his ass, Kazu!
I see him, but I
don't believe him!
It looks like Aeon was using
some trick with
light to disappear,
but there's no way he coulda
set that up in a room like that!
It's the heat.
I know because I was the
one who taught him that trick
back when he used to
ride the Flame Road.
A mirage, like your friendship.
Don't get smart with
me, you little punk ass!
From now on, I won't
give you enough time
to move a single finger!
Time stop‐‐now!
(whooshing)
I can't move.
What's going on?
Did time really stop?
I'm afraid it did, for you.
You see, I've put your brain
into a state of extreme tension
causing it to allocate
all of its resources
to visual input.
Your body can't keep
up with the stimuli!
One second feels like ten.
You might say I've stopped
the clock in your brain!
Damn, I thought I had him.
I should've known.
Agito was right,
he's too strong.
Wait, what just happened?
The battle ended
all of a sudden!
It's like frames were
cut out of the film!
(panting)
What am I doing?
I should be ashamed of myself!
Getting carried away like that.
(gasping)
♪
Maybe not.
Whatever happened, it looks
like Aeon is the winner!
Guess I couldn't stop you from
moving that finger after all.
It's okay‐‐he put
up a good fight!
Holy crap, check it out!
I thought the fight in
the third cube was over,
but it looks like something
crazy's going down.
♪
Man, these Behemoth guys are
a lot stronger than I thought!
If this keeps up,
we're gonna lose
before we can
even score a point!
This really is bad.
It's time for me to get serious!
This looks like a job for Swim‐‐
Croissant Mask!
Wait, who the hell are you?
In the face of perversity,
hope springs eternal!
I may look funny,
but it's really me!
Next time on Air Gear,
we finally score one!
Wait, if you're the
real Croissant Mask,
then who the hell's that?