♪
(shouting)
This is it.
Whoever can get ahead
for even one step,
for even one second
is the winner.
Simple, just how I like it.
(shouting)
(chuckles)
I'm gonna blind
you with the power
of my awesomeness, bug eyes!
Bullshit.
I call upon the wind,
the power of a raging storm!
Super ultimate invincible!
Oh, no!
No, not even close!
And it looks
like his momentum
has made him spin
out of c‐‐c‐‐control!
No, he's accelerating.
This was all
part of his plan.
He's using centrifugal force
to power his fight!
This is where the
real technique starts.
God of the Wind, AT typhoon!
Bring it on, bitch.
(shouting)
♪
Do you think you
can blow me away
with a little
breeze like that?
I'll tear you to pieces!
How you like me now?
(grunting)
That stupid‐looking
technique worked!
Their punches are
really kicking up dust.
Woo, and here comes the Shark!
You better watch it, Akira!
You're leaving
yourself wide open!
Ah!
Come on, you can do it.
This is my game now.
You're finished!
(grunting)
(shouting)
(roaring)
Fuck, two waves
at the same time?
You did it, Akira.
It's just like you said.
Your fangs have evolved.
♪
Akito, please.
I need your help.
Just one step, please.
Just take one step
out of the cage.
If we do it together,
we can make it.
For just one blow,
lend me your strength!
He's using the Leviathan's
Fang with our Regalia.
How the hell is
that possible?
(grunting)
Hey, who's winning?
I can't see anything!
Just use the read!
Check their power levels!
Oh, right.
(beep)
It all comes down to the
strength of their fang.
Whoever loses
gets blown away.
(beeping)
Oh, no.
I've had to use every
trick in the book
to make it this far,
and for a second there,
I actually thought
I could beat you.
I hate to admit it,
but you win.
Agito, I know you're
always bossing people around,
and you're still an annoying,
antisocial son of a bitch,
but the truth is,
well, I mean,
you really are a pain
in the ass, but, I mean‐‐
Run for your life!
God, shut the hell up.
Why are you such a
whiny little bitch?
But, damn, it's like my
feet are glued in place.
I can't move an inch.
♪
I'm sorry, Akito.
It looks like I'm
useless after all.
It's been fun, but I
guess this is goodbye.
(whooshing)
We're not finished yet, Agito.
Can you feel it?
The wind's still blowing.
(whooshing)
(shouting)
Crow?
Wait, what
happened to Mitsuru?
♪
Ha, I'll be damned.
Even in a place
like this dump,
I can still find a
nice tailwind to ride.
He‐‐he's riding on my Fang.
No way.
He did it.
The little crow
found a way to fly.
♪
I can see it.
The Wing Road!
What the hell?
You've been in this
cage for too long.
You don't even realize that
your wings are rotting off.
I'm gonna pick up
this whole damn cage
and break through
and grab the sky!
(whooshing)
(swooshing)
I may have been
afraid to admit it,
but I think deep down
I've always known.
No matter how hard it may be,
there's no such
thing as a bird
that would rather stay
on the ground than fly.
(whooshing)
♪
(shouting)
(clanging)
They did it, those
Kogarasumaru bastards
actually pulled it off!
With a final mighty roar,
the Beast King came
tumbling down the mountain!
(cheering)
They did it, Ringo!
I can't believe it!
(chuckles)
(cheering)
They really are
something else.
I think that punching contest
was probably the turning
point of the match.
Yeah, you're right.
Ikki let Mitsuru
punch him in the stomach
on purpose, right?
Ugh, that crazy kid.
I didn't make him
wear that thing
so he could use it
to block punches.
Ha‐ha, would you
rather he get hurt?
You know, I haven't
seen him in a while,
but the Agito I know
sure as hell never smiled
and laughed like that.
(laughing)
(gasping)
(roaring)
The battle may have ended,
but this isn't over.
Akira!
(grunting)
(gasping)
I still have my
mission as a king.
Don't forget that.
You punk!
(shouting)
(gasping)
Listen, Crow, or maybe
I should say Ikki,
it was a good battle.
I'm impressed.
♪
But don't get cocky.
You aren't ready
to be king yet.
Ha, look who's talking,
you pointy‐haired asshole.
But still I have to admit
you're pretty strong.
And this is gonna hurt.
(slamming)
(gasping)
(grunting)
Where'd he go?
(gasping)
Akira.
♪
It's okay.
It's over.
You kept your promise.
You can finally rest now.
♪
Dude, that's crazy.
I think he just
passed out standing up.
(crying)
It is over!
(shouting)
♪
This is just what I'd expect
from an old sewage plant.
Filthy, smelly,
and packed full of shit.
But that's all right
'cause it's about to get
one hell of a cleaning.
♪
Come on.
All right, and, now,
for the grand finale...
...Kogarasumaru!
Please, I'm way too
tired to do this.
Victory pose!
(whooshing)
Hey, I'm not trying to rain
on your parade or anything,
but I think you're getting
a little ahead of yourselves.
We haven't decided
a winner yet.
Let's see, the last one
standing was Agito
and the Crow knocked
out the Hammer,
but then the King
knocked out the Crow.
That means‐‐hell,
I don't know.
This has never
happened before.
Even I'm confused.
The match is the least
of our concerns.
Someone could die if
this mob gets uglier.
Uh, I'm getting scared.
Yeah, the mood in here is
starting to get kind of sucky.
Are we gonna be okay?
I've never seen so many
rioters in one place before,
and they're all
Behemoth fans too.
Maybe we should get going.
The Fang of the great
beast has been broken.
Huh?
Everyone here has seen
it with their own eyes.
There is no room for debate.
Behemoth has lost.
(booing)
♪
Yeah, they're getting
uglier, all right.
All right, everyone, let's
just proceed to the exit
in an orderly fashion.
Just don't hurt me.
(booing)
♪
What's going on?
‐Huh?
‐What?
Huh?
♪
It's the Shinjuku
Crocodile and his G‐Men.
♪
(clicking)
(coughing)
♪
(groaning and shouting)
Come on!
Ah!
Oh, my God!
Bastards sure took
their time getting here.
Come on, let's go!
We better get out of here
while we still
have the chance!
Buccha, take the Crow with
you while you're at it.
He's like a frigging
monkey on my back.
Agito, you did this,
didn't you?
You tipped them off
because you knew
this would happen if we won.
(grunting)
Two years, ha.
I guess we've both changed,
haven't we, Akira?
Yeah, look at us, surrounded
by all these noisy morons.
With punk‐ass shits
like that hanging around,
it's hard to get
any rest, you know?
You can rest all you want
when you're back in your cage.
Don't worry, all your
noisy punk‐ass friends
are getting locked up, too.
Now let's go home,
you little piece of shit.
‐Ah!
‐No!
My shoulder can't hold out.
Akira!
You haven't even
been gone a month,
but I've been so lonely.
It felt like a
thousand years.
Why do you have to make
your brother sad, Agito?
Well, what do you have to say?
You're a son of a bitch.
You want me to wash your
mouth out with soap, huh?
That's not fucking soap.
Taking it a little far,
don't you think?
It looks bad, but that's
just the boss's way
of expressing love
for his brother.
(grunting)
Ah!
(heavy breathing)
Now who's next?
(clicking)
You're in my way, little girl.
Rubber bullets
still hurt like hell
and leave a nasty bruise.
♪
Someone like you
wouldn't understand.
Akira didn't make a cage
to lock himself up.
He did it to protect
riders who can't fly
and to protect me too.
He surrounded us with a
cage made from his own body.
He took us in.
He let himself suffer
so we could be free.
He's always there for us
to protect us against enemies,
against people like you.
You're pissing me off, bitch.
Now shut the hell up!
Akira isn't in a cage
because he can't fly.
With the wounds that
he suffered for us
and his heavy Regalia,
this is the only way he
can protect his friends.
Talk is cheap,
but I ain't buying.
Huh?
♪
It's all right, Ren,
we all understand.
You don't have to waste
your breath on scum like him.
Uh.
Hm, little punks.
How the hell they get
past our barricade?
Heed my message,
souls of steel,
rise, come together as one!
(zapping)
What the hell's going on?
(clanging)
(zapping)
Without your guns, you
bastards are about as useful
as a sack of dog shit.
That guy must be the
King of the Rising Road.
He's really strong.
Well, we got a real knack
for meeting like this,
don't we, Kaito?
Anyway, I ain't
gonna try and stop you
if you want to fight
this angry mob
with your bare hands.
But if it was me,
I'd hit the road
while I had the chance.
We don't take kindly to
strangers in these parts.
This is no good.
I'm sorry, Sora,
but you're wrong.
This is my battle.
This is my team.
I have to end it.
I'm willing to take
responsibility.
(clicking)
If you can arrest
the leader of all this,
then that should be
enough, right, Kaito?
I'm pretty sure all the guys
here are underage anyway.
It's not like
it'd be hard for us
to take out all these cops,
but on the other hand,
if we did something like that,
I'm sure it'd come back
to bite us in the ass.
We'd probably end up
starting an even bigger war
between police
and Storm Riders.
If we don't want the
whole AT scene to suffer,
then I guess this is the
only solution we've got.
‐It's not fair.
‐We're gonna miss you, Akira.
♪
I did it, Simca.
I finally
fulfilled my promise,
just like you asked.
♪
(helicopter droning)
As of this moment,
Behemoth has been disbanded.
♪
It's time for you
to leave the cage.
Mm.
It's all right now.
We've grown stronger
in these past two years...
..all of your teammates...
...and me too.
♪
(droning)
What did he mean when he said
he'd fulfilled his promise?
If a bird flies alone,
no one will feel the
strength of its wings,
but when a flock of
birds beat their wings
as hard as they can, they
can create a powerful gale.
I knew that someday
a rider who could lead
that gale would appear.
I needed Akira to take care
of the flock until then.
That was the promise.
♪
Akira.
I know we've gotten sort
of a bad rap lately,
but when it comes down to it,
we Marufu G‐Men are
just trying to protect
innocent people from the bad
guys who misuse their ATs,
just like when you
were with the force.
If we get involved
in this thing,
Behemoth is gonna
get wiped out.
That okay?
While he's in Behemoth
the only people Akira can
protect are his teammates.
But his cage is
much bigger than that.
You could fit all
of Japan in it.
Everyone on our team
feels the same way.
We're all waiting
for you to come back.
Well, at least think
about it, all right?
♪
(fluttering)
Is something the matter?
It's nothing.
♪
It's been so long.
I guess I forgot how
bright the sky was.
(birds chirping)
(traffic honking)
♪
Check out my armpit hair.
How long before you
think he'll hurl?
Want some, you
like kale juice?
Are you listening?
That isn't his
homework, is it?
They totally screwed me over.
This is so not fair!
He's so cute!
Okay, pull your pants down.
Hey, I thought you
told me he was dying.
He looks already dead to me.
Oh, she's acting all cool,
but she spent three hours
picking out these
pajamas for you.
Ah, what the hell
is your problem?
Shut up, you noisy
little shits!
Get out!
Don't you have anything
else better to do
with your miserable
little lives?
Dude, you look just fine.
We'll be back tomorrow
to eat some more bananas.
And make you drink kale juice!
And touch nurses'
asses, woo‐woo!
Go touch yourself.
Man, our team is
kicking major butt.
These apples are good.
Thanks to my Stink Road,
we just took out the biggest
Storm Rider team in Japan.
We won.
I still can't believe we
beat those guys, you know?
Yeah.
We kicked their ass.
You guys have come
so far already...
(squawking)
...but you still have
a long way to climb,
and there's a tower
of demons ahead of you
that stretches
far into the sky.
(heels clicking)
Huh?
What the hell am I gonna
do with all this crap?
eBay maybe or Carl's list,
or whatever the
fuck his name is.
I hope you get
well soon, Agito.
(indistinct chattering)
We're all gonna miss you,
so you have to come back
as quick as you
can, all right?
Get well, huh?
Yeah, right.
As long as I'm sharing
this body with Akito,
he'll never get better.
His leg will never heal.
(whooshing)
In a way, I'm regretting
this whole thing,
regretting the
fight with Akira...
♪
...regretting getting
the Regalia back...
...and regretting making
friends with everyone.
I don't want to fade away.
(gasping)
♪
(slurping)
(sighing)
Shit.
♪
♪ The truth ♪
♪ The truth shall
set you free ♪
♪
♪ Truth ♪
♪ The truth ♪
♪ The truth, the truth
shall set you free ♪
♪
I don't care who you are.
If you mess with
Kogarasumaru's area,
you're as good as dead!
Wait, the school clock tower
is your secret base?
Don't get carried
away, you guys!
That lightning.
It's the sign of
the Rising Road.
That's the Thunder King, Nue!
What, Genesis?
You want me to be the leader
of the strongest
AT team in Japan?
No, Ikki, don't do it.
You can't accept their offer!
Next time on Air Gear,
the mega storm is
set into motion!
♪