♪
(indistinct arguing)
Take that!
Kyoto.
Now stopping in Kyoto.
♪
What, I don't have time
for that kinda stuff.
I have entrance exams
to worry about.
You still don't get it, do you?
The end of the year field trip
could be your last chance
to hook up with
someone from school.
Yeah, 'cause after
this year everyone
goes to different high schools.
You gotta take this
stuff more seriously.
All right, Kyoto, here I come!
This is it.
Check out all these stairs!
I'm gonna jump 'em!
Settle down, and
get back in line!
We'll be getting on a
bus as soon as we exit
‐the train station.
‐But I wanna jump!
(engine whirring)
(birds chirping)
A long, long time ago,
some super important
dead guy lived here.
Hey, what kinda half‐assed
explanation is that?
Okay, listen up everyone,
it's like this.
In order to reduce the
power of the feudal lords
in Western Japan, Tokugawa...
♪
What‐‐oh.
What's going on here?
Told you, this is the
power of the class trip.
It's like I said, everyone's
starting to hook up.
‐Everyone's hooking up?
‐Yes!
Ikki, Ikki!
♪
Oh, there he is.
What's he doing walking
around all the way up there?
(heartbeat pounding)
Miss Noyamano.
Miss Noyamano,
is something wrong?
Oh, it's nothing, I was just
zoning out for a sec there.
What the heck was he just doing?
No, forget it,
it doesn't matter.
Ikki and I are more like
brother and sister anyway.
Yeah, it's none of my business.
He can do whatever he wants.
None of my business,
none of my business.
Ringo, stop, that tree
is a national landmark!
(indistinct chatter)
Ikki, who the hell
was that girl?
She was hot, did you two kiss?
What would your
mother think, huh?
We didn't kiss, she just came up
and started
whispering in my ear.
Something about being my
number one fan or whatever.
I actually get
that a lot lately,
ever since the battle
with Behemoth.
I don't think it's very
smart to let strangers
come up to you like that, Crow.
I mean, have you forgotten
we're on their turf?
If they're the big Buddha
in Kyoto right now,
that means we're
standing smack dab
in the middle of
the palm of his hand.
The team is the core
of Genesis Kansai region.
They may only
have three members,
but they're the strongest.
Team Trident!
Genesis, huh?
Guess that explains why Aeon
wanted to introduce us to them.
‐Genius.
‐Shut up, bird brain.
Smoker.
(indistinct conversations)
♪
(grunting)
(yelling)
That's the mother of all walls!
I gotta take a spin!
Back spin 1,000!
He really likes his
walls, doesn't he?
Aha, there you are,
you little turds!
Hey, Buccha, get
down from there!
Don't make me come up
there and kick your ass!
Wait, come back here!
All right, everyone,
it's lights out.
Hurry up and go to bed.
(sighing)
Those brats are gonna
give me an ulcer.
Thanks for looking
out for all the kids.
I brought you a drink
to help you relax.
Wow, thanks a lot, that's
just what the doctor ordered.
(groaning)
What the hell do you
think you're wearing?
Huh, what do you mean?
I always wear this
when I go to bed.
You can't go outside looking
like that, back to your room!
I wasn't expecting that.
(snoring)
Well, I guess I
shouldn't be surprised.
With all the hell
they were raising today,
they must have
worn themselves out.
Yeah right, you can't fool me!
Now fess up, who
the hell are ya?
I'm Yamada from
the class next‐door.
I'm Murata, sir.
Ikki told us to lay down here.
Just don't tell him
you found us out, please.
(grunting and laughing)
♪
Oh man, this is too
good to be true.
I'm guessing they're gonna
realize soon that we're gone.
Yeah, but what's it gonna do?
♪
Wow, these side streets
are really great.
We should break out our ATs
and go racing around here.
Sure the hell beats
staying in bed.
♪
(camera shutters clicking)
What's with the pictures, and
where are those jerks going to?
Yeah, well, wherever they're
going, they're in a hurry.
I wonder if there's a place
where you can ride your ATs.
♪
(indistinct chatter)
Almost naked chicks.
(giggling)
Come on.
Please!
So, you think we should
go join him or what?
This is all right, but I
wish I'd brought my ATs.
Hey, I think those are
the guys from earlier.
♪
(camera shutters clicking)
But I wanna jump!
Hey, Buccha, get
down from there!
♪
(horns honking)
I had a feeling you'd
show up sooner or later.
It's been a while, Yoshitsune.
So is the Rumble King
of the Over Road
a pro at video games as well?
What the hell man,
that's creepy!
I don't think I
like Kyoto anymore.
I don't know what their deal is,
but they've been
stalking us all night.
That can't be helped, the story
about Genesis being under us
is all over the place,
it's everywhere.
Yeah, you're right,
I feel like this thing
is really starting to
get serious, you know?
(whooshing noise)
Whoa!
(shouting)
Oh shit.
I don't see what the big
deal is with this Ikki kid.
He's supposed to follow
the Wing Road,
but he doesn't even
have the Regalia yet.
I'm not gonna call him king
just because Simca tells me to.
Sure doesn't take much to be the
leader of Genesis these days.
I don't know how you
expect all the members
to bow down to someone like him.
You know, if this is supposed
to be some kind of joke,
I'm not laughing.
Ah, what the hell is going on?
If you wanna go to the top,
you gotta think ahead.
Victory favors the rider
with the best strategy.
Crap, I can't believe
these jerk wads
are attacking us in
the middle of the city!
Oh man, this is bad, without
our ATs we're really screwed!
Die, punk!
(groaning)
Listen, Sunao, this is an
order from the boss himself.
Don't let them leave here alive.
Do you have any idea who
you're dealing with here?
You candy ass samurai
need to learn some manners!
They're the members
of Samurai Spirits,
a B Class team affiliated
with Team Trident!
I don't think we can
hold out much longer.
Let's split up
and get outta here.
There's no way, we can't outrun
Storm Riders without our ATs!
Check this out, I learned this
one watching ultimate fighting!
Megaton Suplex!
This is your chance, Sunao,
rip that bastard a new asshole.
(speaking gibberish)
Yoshitsune, are you
responsible for this?
Oh, so you have 'em wired, huh?
Well, looks like you
caught me red handed,
but you can't blame
me for trying.
I don't understand, why?
'Cause that kid's a pain
in my ass, that's why.
We were running the Kansai
branch no problem,
just minding our own business
before he came along.
Now that little shit
comes waltzing in,
acting like some
kinda celebrity,
and we're supposed to
bow down and take it?
The bottom line is
this place is my turf.
I don't care who the hell
he is, I'm not letting anyone
barge in here and do
whatever they like.
(grunting)
(thudding)
♪
Wait a sec, isn't she‐‐
I think that's enough.
You boys are having
way too much fun.
‐No we're not.
‐No, I swear.
Hold on, it's not
what you think!
(screaming)
(rumbling)
‐We're all gonna die, aren't we?
‐You can't be serious.
In case you didn't know, I'm
one of the heads of Trident,
the Kansai branch of Genesis.
You can call me Benkei,
it's nice to meet you.
This is a misunderstanding,
it's not our fault.
We were just acting under
orders from Takei and‐‐
(groaning)
That's gotta hurt.
Sorry if these guys have
caused you any trouble,
but the fact is, the riders
here aren't too happy
about you becoming
the leader of Genesis.
I'm surprised you
weren't expecting
something like this to happen.
Don't get me wrong though.
I'm not trying to excuse
what those punks did.
You're still our guest,
and if we send you home
in a body bag then that
reflects poorly on us.
Well, that's what the
boss would say at least.
Then I have a message for you
to take back to your boss.
If he doesn't want
his dogs to bite,
he should learn to
keep them on leashes.
If that's how you feel maybe you
should follow your own advice.
If you're serious about
becoming the leader of Genesis,
then before you know it, all
of Japan will be your backyard.
But if you can't even deal
with the dogs in Kansai,
how will you handle the rest?
You need to step up and
show them who's in charge.
There's something
else you should know.
When it comes to our boss,
no matter what road you ride,
none of you stand a chance in
hell of defeating him in battle.
You may be proud of
that wind of yours,
but once it faces
our boss's power,
it's no different than feeding
a breeze through a turbine.
It's the windmill theory, I
know that might not make sense
to you now, but you'll
understand soon enough.
See ya.
I knew there was something
fishy about that woman
the first moment
I laid eyes on her.
Still, I wasn't expecting this.
(birds chirping)
The windmill theory, huh?
Good morning everyone, I hope
you're enjoying the trip so far,
but let me say, if you don't
wanna end up like these punks,
then you better not cause
any trouble, get it?
All right, now eat
your breakfast!
Were they up all night fighting?
They came back with
a lot of bruises.
It's the second day, we
really gotta turn up the juice.
‐Got it?
‐Juice, what do you mean?
Oh, come on, don't
be such a prude.
We're going to
Uzamasa Movie Land!
This your chance to spend
some quality time with Ikki.
‐Just the two of you.
‐Just the two of us, huh?
Now that I think about it,
even though Ikki and I live
in the same house,
it's been a long time
since we've gotten to spend
time alone with each other.
All right everyone,
it's time to go!
Let's enjoy the tour, okay?
What does she mean
by windmill theory?
I don't get it.
(background chatter)
Even after all these
years, I still feel like
there's a gap
between me and Ikki.
(indistinct conversations)
I mean, I really like Ikki,
I have for a long time,
and I'm sure he doesn't
hate me or anything.
But when it comes down to it,
I don't think he likes me
nearly as much as I like him.
We're just not
on the same level.
Is a little trip like this
really going to be enough
to make up for that?
Is it okay for me to have hope?
Even just a little?
♪
Well, if I let Ringo
and Ikki get together,
that's kinda like helping
the enemy, but whatever!
I'll do it, it sounds like
it might be fun anyway.
(together)
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
It was a lot more
expensive than we thought.
♪
(together)
Well, hey there.
You're looking pretty good.
Huh, where's Ringo?
‐It's show time, baby!
♪
So, what do you guys all think?
Does it look weird?
If by weird you
mean totally hot.
Then yeah, it
looks pretty weird!
(giggling)
All right, Ringo, now's
your chance, he's all yours.
What?
‐Um, Ikki.
‐Uh, yeah?
Do you wanna maybe take
a little walk together?
Uh, sure, actually
there was something
I wanted to talk to you about.
Huh?
Listen, Ringo, you have
to be bold like a devil,
but you also have to be
delicate like an angel.
♪
What's with that look?
This is a bad idea, I feel
like my heart's gonna explode.
It's beating so loud
I bet Ikki can hear it too.
Let's go around this corner,
that way no one can see.
(stammering)
♪
Ringo.
I have a question, it's
something really important.
Okay.
No way, is this for real?
What a pain in the ass.
How the hell does Takei
expect us to pull this off?
Finishing off that
punk is one thing,
but kidnapping the girl
is too much trouble.
(speaking gibberish)
Would you tell your
pet to shut up?
Don't you realize that
the whole world hangs
in the balance of what
happens between them?
Ohh.
Hey, can you guys see
anything from up here?
I see you!
I‐‐well,
it's not like I really
mind or anything.
But I feel like this is kind of
sudden, and what if, what if‐‐
oh my God, his face
is like right there!
(heartbeat pounding)
Ringo, listen.
Do you know what the
windmill theory is about?
‐Say what?
‐It looks like I'm gonna end up
battling against some
king from Team Trident.
The problem is I don't know
anything about his technique.
Hm, what's with that face?
Sorry about this, but
you said you didn't want
people to know
that you ride ATs.
That's why I had to make
sure we were all alone.
Ohhh.
I should've known,
who was I kidding?
Really, you'd think
I'd know better by now.
Ikki's always had
a one‐track mind,
and right now his brain
is so occupied with ATs
he doesn't have room
for anything else.
Hey, Ikki, look, come on.
Don't you think
this kimono is cute?
You haven't said if
you liked it or not.
Huh, I don't know.
You look like one of those weird
haunted dolls or something.
It's really starting
to creep me out.
You're really starting
to piss me off.
♪
There he is, hey Ikki, your
friends are in big trouble!
(tires screeching)
♪
You bastards, what the hell
do you think you're doing?
♪
Tonight at 8 PM sharp,
Takei wants to have you
over for a special dinner.
Till then, how
about a little buzz?
A stun gun, is that how
they got everyone else?
♪
(screaming)
‐Who did that?
‐Over here, you fool.
Ninja?
Allow us to take care
of these lowly thugs.
There is no need
to be suspicious.
All right, but you guys
are pretty suspicious.
Why am I doing this again?
♪
Damn it, those samurai
ass wipes are too fast.
They're getting away!
I can't catch up!
What, Ringo?
It doesn't matter
who loves who more,
or how big the
gap between us is,
on the road that we ride
we don't have time
to worry about things like that.
Right now all I can
do is keep running.
That's one thing
we both understand.
You're slow!
Where'd that come from?
So that's our new leader.
Let's tag along and see what
this kid's really made of.
What do you say, Aeon?
You've gotta go all out, Ikki!
Stay with me and don't
fall behind, all right?
Uh, sure.
♪
Me and Yoshitsune are gonna
settle this with Kyoto's
famous AT challenge,
the Devil's 30‐30.
Ikki, do you realize
what you're getting into?
33.3 meters is a really
long way to jump,
and you'll be putting your
teammates' lives at risk.
It's all right, I'm gonna
fly to Wing Road again.
Next time on Air Gear
it's the final battle!
Kogarasumaru versus Trident!
Me versus Yoshitsune!
Get ready for the Devil's 30‐30!
I'm serious, get ready.