♪
(yelling)
Bring it on, baldy!
I'm the one who calls
the shots around here!
♪
Later, boys!
Little bitch is all talk.
♪
I think I'm starting
to get the hang of this,
shifting my weight,
timing my acceleration.
Everything's so precise!
These things react almost
as fast as I can think!
‐Huh?
‐Take that!
(laughing)
Better watch where
you're going, piss boy!
Dammit.
♪
If I don't do something,
I'm gonna end up
looking pretty pathetic.
My legs don't wanna move,
but my heart is telling me
to get my ass in gear!
We'll take care of the scrubs.
You've gotta win this thing!
Those who wander into our forest
shall fall into
an eternal slumber!
Sleeping Forest, let's go!
(grunting)
♪
This is what you get
for being naughty!
Take 'em out!
♪
How could you use
your AT as a weapon?
You have no right to ride!
Go, hurry!
Yeah!
♪
(chuckling)
I always wanted a
shot at that emblem,
and now it's in
the palm of my hands.
♪
(zapping)
No way‐‐when did he
learn a trick like that?
♪
(alarm dinging)
Huh?
What's going on?
This is not right‐‐there
shouldn't be any trains coming.
Looks like this is
gonna be a real hoot!
If it's not train,
then what is it?
You can bet your bottom
dollar it's a punk‐ass kid!
(yelling)
‐Ow!
‐Definitely a rookie.
Well, that was one hell
of a smooth move, Hollywood!
Ow, my head.
This is bullshit!
What the hell are you
trying to pull here?
Are you out of
your freakin' mind?
But you said the person
who shuts off the sign wins.
I won't accept it.
This battle never happened!
Hey, that's cheating‐‐
get back here!
Listen, jerk, I'm gonna get that
emblem from you no matter what!
‐You hear me?
‐What's the big deal?
It's just a stupid pin.
Well, stupid or not,
it's only natural
for him to bet his life
on an emblem like that.
‐Simca?
‐That's what it means
to be a Storm Rider.
Wait, you wanna have
dinner or something?
You go nowhere.
Aw, crap, you are
gonna eat me, aren't you?
No one eats rookie.
Does that mean you're
gonna have your way with me?
You're gonna pull my
pants down and‐‐oh, God!
So what are you gonna
do about neon sign
you shatter all over place, huh?
I'll pay you back once
I make it big, I swear!
Maybe I'll take
out of your hide.
No!
I was blind.
I never knew there
was another world,
a world above the ground I've
been bound to all of my life!
Now the door's been opened.
I've seen the road in the sky.
I've ridden it, but
only for a moment.
Now it just feels like a dream.
Ow!
(grunting)
‐Get off me!
‐Don't just stand there
trying to look all dramatic.
That toilet ain't
gonna clean itself!
Then move your foot
and let me work!
Actually I kinda like you there.
Perv‐‐that's what you get
for practically
losing our emblem!
Small price to pay
for jacking Rika's ATs
and screwing 'em up!
I oughta kick your teeth in
and flush 'em down the toilet!
And if you tell anyone
about Sleeping Forest,
I'll rip your tongue out
and shove it up your‐‐
Ikki, so tell us, what happened
after the meeting last night?
Yeah, dude, you got in a fight
with the Skull Saders again!
But you're still okay!
You're still talking about that?
Those stupid jerks are so lame,
I already forgot about 'em.
Let's just say they're
probably too humiliated
to flash their ugly
mugs around here.
But enough of that.
I'm starting an Air Trek team.
You're gonna be a Storm Rider?
With who?
You...
♪
...and you.
‐You're nuts.
‐(unintelligible) nuts.
I want both of you to go out
and get you a pair of ATs.
But now that I think about it,
I guess we're gonna
need five people
if we wanna battle.
I wonder who we should get
for the other two members.
‐Huh?
♪
All right, let's
start your training
with the basics of the basics.
Walk forward.
‐So stupid.
‐Walk, walk, walk.
Ikki!
What's your problem?
You said you wanted
me to teach you
so that's what I'm doing.
If you're not gonna
take this seriously,
then you can just
teach yourself!
Okay, sorry, sorry.
Here goes.
Geez, Ringo, this is a
lot harder than it looks.
You're doing fine‐‐keep it up!
It's just tough at first
because you're using muscles
you don't normally use!
Good‐‐stop right there!
Ow.
‐Oh, man, I'm spent.
‐That's normal.
You'll get used to
it sooner or later.
So you guys‐‐I mean,
the Sleeping Forest.
Sorry, Ikki, but I'm really
not supposed to talk about that.
Right, I forgot about that.
Oh, by the way, I decided to
start my own Storm Rider team.
With who?
Well, actually, right now,
it's just Kazu and Onigiri.
But I was thinking about
asking Simca the Swallow.
You think she'd go for it?
Yeah, right, huh?
What was I thinking?
Hey, Ringo?
Hey!
Ow!
(birds chirping)
Prickle, prickle, pull, pull.
Stuff you with cotton
till your belly is full.
Pull, pull, snip, snip.
Cut out your flesh
from the head to the hip.
Snip, snip, sweep, sweep.
Pick up the needle
and drive it in deep!
Take all the pieces,
weathered and torn,
sew them all up and
then you are born.
♪
Come on, Ringo!
Teach me some more!
‐Pretty please?
‐Yeah, I'm busy.
Get Simca to do it.
Well, well, a lovers quarrel.
‐Shut up!
And by the way, Ume,
I've told you before
to stop filling up the house
with those creepy dolls!
I'm not creepy, just different!
If you're not busy, do you think
you could teach me some AT‐‐
Never!
Tonight, we're going to
be celebrating the birth
of our 100th gorgon offspring.
♪
You know, cute little Ume
was able to master
her ATs in only two days,
but it looks like
ugly old, icky Ikki
‐just isn't as talented as her!
‐That's creepy, stop it!
♪
(buzzing)
It's gone‐‐what's up with that?
I thought she wanted
me to work off my debt!
I guess the shop
isn't here every night.
♪
What the hell's
going on over there?
♪
(groaning)
(grunting and clattering)
You'll pay for that, you punk!
Are you okay?
Hey, jerkwads!
If you don't wanna
get your asses stomped,
you'd better hit the road!
You won't get away with this!
Looks like I already did.
Hey, you!
♪
Pretty good.
(laughing)
He takes mushy to
a whole new level.
‐Dumbass.
‐He looks like a bean bag.
Hey, Ringo?
Don't worry about him.
Boy are just stupid at that age.
Whatever‐‐that's fine!
I'm not really interested
in Ikki's business‐‐really!
He and I are like brother
and sister, you know?
I mean, why should I care
if he wants to hang
out with some skank?
(laughing)
♪
Rez‐Boa‐Dogs!
Formation lineup!
♪
‐Dokun!
Numbers 19 and 22, come forward.
‐Yes, sir.
Dokun!
I'm sorry, but for
acting out on your own
and embarrassing
the Rez‐Boa‐Dogs,
that was a
well‐deserved punishment.
But I want you to
understand that this hurts me
as much as it hurts you!
It pains my soul!
Forgive us...
‐Inuyama.
‐I'm sorry we're such pussies.
It's all right, it's all right,
let it out, my little pups.
Listen up, we ain't just
rollin' over and playing dead.
Tell that bitch Simca
that I'm the big dog!
Okay, you two, the first lesson
is the basics of the basics.
I'll break it down for
you, so watch and learn.
This is the walk‐‐walk, walk‐‐
(giggling and growling)
That was my head!
It's not our fault you
look like a retard, Ikki.
Can it, fat ass!
Laugh at the basics,
and I'll make you cry!
Huh?
Oh, crap, sorry, guys,
there's someplace
I gotta be right now.
Hey, Ikki!
He better come back.
I almost went broke
buying these things.
Guess we'd better
keep practicing.
(train horn blowing)
I thought I could find you here.
♪
We've gotta stop
meeting like this.
Yeah, well, how long have
you known that I've been here?
Long enough.
I don't know if I like that.
Makes me feel like a stalker.
You're not like
a stalker at all!
Stalkers are weirdos
that peep on girls
when they're in the bath
and eat meat off the floor,
but I know you never do
creepy stuff like that,
'cause you're all
cool and muscley.
So no problem‐‐you can
stalk me all you want.
Well, I am pretty cool.
I guess I should give
you another present, huh?
Huh?
(wind blowing)
All right, close your eyes.
All right.
(whimpering)
Here!
Huh?
♪
Um, wait, what‐‐
It's your lucky charm.
♪
Now it's like we're
together all the time.
(laughing)
♪
Dokun!
(grunting)
♪
(wind hissing)
I've come here to retrieve
the Rez‐Boa‐Dogs emblem
you stole from us.
I'd like to do
this without a fight,
but if you refuse
to turn it over,
then a 270 percent
stronger Dokun awaits you!
What does he mean "stole"?
Don't tell me these
guys are after me
because of your present!
Don't lose it‐‐it's
your lucky charm.
There's nothing lucky
about this thing at all!
If you survive this, I'll give
you your real present, 'kay?
What do you mean "real present"?
Don't let me down, Little Crow!
♪
Welcome home, Master!
I've been waiting for you!
Get you head outta your ass!
♪
(grunting)
What the hell was
that for, punk?
Oh, sorry, I thought
we were gonna fight!
Actually, I don't really know
how this whole emblem
battle thing works.
You guys were looking all
serious and making demands,
so I wanted to show you
that I wasn't gonna back down,
but that's not the point.
I don't like how
you're talking crap
and acting like you're all
better than me or something.
‐It's pissing me off!
‐I see.
♪
You think I'm all
bark and no bite, huh?
You see that water
tower over there?
If you can beat me to the top,
then you can keep the emblem.
Take it or leave it.
I'll even give you a
five‐second head start.
I don't need five
seconds to beat you!
Three is just fine.
You're gonna want those
two seconds back, punk.
Three...
(whirring)
...two...
one!
Ready?
Go!
Simca!
Well, now, what could
Sleeping Forest want with me?
♪
Ohh, yeah, that's right.
Run while you still can.
It'll all be over soon.
♪
Tell me, Simca, what kind of
mess did you get Ikki into?
Right now, he's just
like a baby chick.
You might say I threw
him out of the nest
to teach him how to fly!
I don't see what's
wrong with that.
♪
If I had known it
was gonna be this easy,
I would've given him
the three‐second lead.
Almost there!
♪
Ikki's so young,
he doesn't have his wings yet.
But if he reaches the sky,
he'll soar like an eagle.
But someday, he'll
be able to fly with me,
his heart reaching
for the heavens,
never looking back.
Only then will
he truly be alive.
♪
Damn, they caught up.
That little crow
is mine, understand?
I don't want you
getting in my way
of trying to clip his wings.
♪
Bitch!
(grunting)
Wasn't that a
little uncalled for?
Don't treat Ikki
like some kind of fool.
He isn't your toy, and
he sure isn't your pet.
He doesn't need you.
He could've flown by
himself from the start!
♪
‐Hold still!
‐Dammit!
Let me go, you punks, now!
Rez‐Boa‐Dogs,
formation Hunting Bay!
(howling)
♪
Think I'm going down that easy?
Think again!
(yelling)
♪
(all exclaiming)
I'd rather die than
hunt one of my own dogs.
I'll be fine‐‐let's go!
♪
What a beautiful moon tonight.
Do you see it, Little Crow?
It's almost as red as my cheek.
♪
Hmm.
I did it‐‐eat that, losers!
♪
(yelling)
Come on, somebody give me
some wheels for my AT, please?
If you want parts that bad,
then get 'em yourself!
I'm asking because I
don't have any money!
Well, then, I guess you'll
just have to have a parts war.
‐What's that?
‐It's where you have
an AT battle
for parts or emblems,
but you might lose your
Air Treks if you get beat.
Don't worry, I won't lose.
Let's see, my opponent
is Issa Mihotoke?
He's nothing!
Next time on Air Gear,
Emerge, the Warrior
of the Night.
♪