♪
You're the punk
who had the match
against the Yao
the other day.
Oh, then you saw it, did you?
Well then, you'd have to admit,
I was pretty amazing,
wouldn't you agree?
Fuck!
Pretty arrogant for
a low‐class piece of shit.
Where the hell do you
get off talking crap to me,
you little freak;
do you have any idea who I am?
♪
If it's off balance,
come back, I'll fix for you.
Still, I don't know why you need
a motor with such crazy torque.
Ha!
If I were you, I'd give up ATs
before you hurt yourself.
A wuss like you will
be torn to pieces.
You're better off crawling
on the ground like a worm
instead of flying in
the sky like a bird.
♪
Does it bother you?
Does what bother me?
You mean that cocky
little punkass?
♪
Well, I mean, does it bother
you that he saw the Wing Road?
♪
Why should I care?
I tear wings to
pieces with my fangs
and yank them from the sky.
♪
Get back in the car.
You've seen enough.
♪
(chatter)
(yelling)
♪
Don't give me that crap!
What the hell's
your problem, huh?
It's time to pay your tab, sir.
That'll be $36,620.
Will you be paying cash?
Or do you have food stamps?
What are you talking
about, bitch, I don't pay!
Drinks, service repairs,
entertainment, and VIP seating.
We offer these services
free of charge
to the leader of
the Skull Saders,
but seeing as you're
just Magaki Kouji now,
I'm afraid the tab stands.
‐'Kay?
‐Don't pull that crap with me.
You're coming with us, punk.
Let's go.
♪
(groaning)
(punching, grunting)
I ain't paying shit,
you got that?
This is what I think
about your tab.
You bastards think you can
treat me like crap, huh?
Just 'cause I lost a fight?
Just 'cause I lost
to that middle school punk?
♪
No way!
This cannot be happening to me!
That son of a bitch
got a lucky break last time
but now the little
bastard's riding my ass
like he's been racing for years!
No fucking way!
♪
(yelling)
I don't think so.
Let's make a deal.
If you fuck over the emblem,
I'll let you live, all right?
♪
What?
(yelling)
♪
Damnit.
I'll kill him,
I'll kill him, damnit.
I'll kill that stupid
son of a bitch!
♪
‐Boo!
‐(whimpers)
♪
I'll get my revenge, damnit.
Just you wait, Ikki Minami.
I'll make you
suffer for this.
(panting, grunting)
What?
♪
Who the hell are you?
I bet you're starving.
Go ahead and eat up.
♪
(yelling)
(screaming)
♪
You got another one coming.
‐Do it, Ikki.
‐Mm‐hm.
(giggling)
Hey, wait!
You're the one who
was coming onto me!
Why are you running
away, baby cakes?
‐Come back!
‐Why don't you catch me
and find out?
Get back here!
Come on!
Come on, I said wait!
(giggling)
♪
Oh, there, hey!
Hey, where'd you
go, sweet cheeks?
Right here!
(groaning)
Looks like this
one's another loser.
I'm tired of being
the horny guy bait.
Huh?
♪
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
Ever seen "Seven Samurai"?
I'm looking for new recruits.
Is this some kind of joke?
Listen, Ikki,
you're supposed to be
putting together a team
of riders, not perverts!
Oh my!
What's going on?
Ms. Tomita, would you please
tell them to stop this?
They're taking a nap, how cute!
Do you think they'd mind
if I laid down and joined them?
The afternoon classes
are totally boring!
Just great.
Here, read it when you get tired
of hitting people on the head.
A love letter, huh?
I never knew you felt
that way about me.
Never knew I‐‐
what a jerkwad,
but I do love him.
Whoa, an A‐class Parts War?
♪
Ume found out about it
when she was looking
online the other day.
It's the Kintetsu Buls
versus Agito.
Agito?
Huh.
Hey, check it out,
it's going down today.
Yeah, where's it at?
If you're gonna
make your own team,
you should watch other
people's battles too.
It's an A‐class match,
so it should be good.
Besides, I‐‐huh?
♪
‐Come on, ride up!
‐Let's go!
Huh?
♪
All right, let's
check this thing out.
Hell yeah.
Hey, you little shit stains!
Don't ride your ATs
inside the school!
I'll confiscate 'em, damnit!
I ain't playin'!
Um, you guys... get out!
I have to go shopping,
get out of my car!
♪
Which one of you's
touching my ass?!
That's gross, stop it!
♪
Cut it out,
you're gonna mess up
the inside of my car
if you don't stop!
I'm really sorry.
No, they're getting
man juice all over my car!
Man juice!
Chill, it's just sweat, okay?
You know, this place
is kinda far away.
I don't care, just
start the car, please!
(loud rumbling)
Huh?
♪
(wailing)
Go!
(engine struggling)
The whole Parts War thing
started as a webpage
where you could trade AT
parts with other riders.
It was a good way
to make new friends
and pick up things you couldn't
find in normal AT shops.
Yeah, but that's so boring.
I think it's better this way
because now teams have a chance
to meet up
and have a big battle.
Ah, the sweet smell of Kazu.
I mean, that sounds more
like what a Storm Rider
should be doing in
the first place, right?
You think so, huh?
Riding means different
things to different people.
There's all kinds of teams.
I know there are teams
that just like to fight
but they really aren't
the majority at all.
Most people just like to ride.
I think AT is just
something you should relax
and have fun with.
All those silly battles,
areas, and emblems,
that stuff doesn't have
anything to do with AT.
Every time you jump,
every time you turn
and twist in the air,
you do it just a little
bit better than before,
and suddenly, your moves
start to look closer and closer
to how you imagined them.
That's what matters to me.
Knowing that every time I ride,
I'm a little better than before.
♪
I think when you
build up your strength,
when you push yourself
harder and harder,
when you accomplish
something with your own power,
well, that's true freedom.
♪
Hi, just forget it.
Sorry, I guess I was
talking all weird, huh?
(giggles)
Damn.
I wish she wasn't
in love with Ikki.
(growling)
♪
♪ Come, come, come on ♪
Look out!
♪
Hey, stop the car, asshole!
You're about to go
into Buls territory!
We're having an important
battle today, so‐‐
(yelling)
Did you see that?
Oh crap, I think she killed him.
Oh my God, we're all gonna die.
Geez, women drivers.
♪
Huh, wait, that's Buccha.
Then that kid must be...
No freakin' way.
Hey, call the boss.
He's gonna have a cow.
From East Side Middle School,
are you serious?
He must have found out
about the match online.
Wait, so who's coming?
It's that rookie
everyone's talking about,
you know, the middle school kid
they say has a shot
at becoming the Sky King?
It's crazy, even
Simca and Spitfire
have been watching him.
You hear that?
Looks like we better
put on a good show.
Ha, I don't wanna see you
slacking off, all right, Agito?
What does he think?
Agito; he actually
seems pretty happy.
He said that guy is at
the top of his list,
so he wants to try
and scare him.
Yeah, that sounds like him.
(chatter)
What's that?
(yelling)
Tom‐Tom, your driving sucks.
♪
So that's the
Sky King guy, huh?
Just looks like some stupid
middle school kid to me.
No way, take a closer look.
He's checking out
the battlefield,
sizing things up with
those piercing eagle eyes.
It's like he can stare
right into your soul!
♪
Oh man, I gotta take a crap.
Where the hell
is the bathroom?
Every time I go on a field
trip, I gotta take a dump!
Glad you decided to
show up, babyface.
Who the hell are you?
My pal Inuyama from the
Rez‐Boa‐Dogs told me about you.
♪
I'm Gonzo Tokudawara,
the head of the Kintetsu Buls
and king of this area.
You can call me T‐Gonzo.
Oh, I get it, since you
have a reindeer head,
you're friends
with the dog head guy.
I knew you reminded
me of someone.
You old dudes sure are weird.
Easy, kid, or I
might not be gentle
when I change your diapers.
Anyway, me and Inuyama
have been friends
since we were your age.
I can't believe a
little squirt like you
beat a monster like Inuyama.
‐How'd you survive his headbutt?
‐Dude, what the hell?
It's the first time they met
and they're, like, best friends?
‐Boss, it's almost time.
‐All right.
♪
Damn, now that's what
I call a six pack.
‐Hold this, kid.
‐Hm?
(yelling)
Ow.
Careful, the floors
around here are kinda flimsy.
If you wanna climb to
the top, remember this.
Even if you're
just a street punk,
you gotta start somewhere.
For me, even this battle's
just another stepping stone
before going pro.
Sooner or later, T‐Gonzo
will be a household name
and riders all over the
world will look up to us.
It's what me and the
Buls are fighting for.
♪
Four years.
It's taken us four
years to get here.
Just a little bit longer.
One more step and our
dream will come true.
We can't lose now.
Man.
Hey, old dude!
‐Kick ass.
Hm.
♪
Parts War A‐class, Balloon.
The goal is to
retrieve an emblem
that's floating
inside a balloon.
The chosen team members
all play at once
and the playing field extends
to wherever the balloon flies.
The rules are simple
but the battle isn't.
A team of five
players is selected
and each of them
plays a different role.
The Panther chases
after the balloon,
the Decoy plays as bait,
the Ultimate handles
the main offense,
the Middle acts as backup,
and the Keeper blocks
the enemy's attacks.
Offense, defense,
speed, and strength
are all essential
but it's not just
the individual skill
that decides the winner.
If there's no teamwork
or a poor game plan
or just weak formation,
even a team full
of powerful riders
won't be successful.
Wait, but why
is it five to two?
Yeah, this is
an official battle,
shouldn't both sides have
the same number of players?
I guess they're just really
confident they can win.
Huh?
It's that kid.
♪
Agito, now.
Agito, tear them to pieces.
♪
Kintetsu Buls, disperse!
All right, here they go.
(yelling)
♪
Just watch and
see what it means
to be an A‐class Storm Rider.
♪
Each move is executed with
speed, strength, and precision.
The attacks are powerful
but there's also a graceful
flow to each of their motions.
♪
They're not just showing off,
every trick and every
move within that trick
has a purpose.
They're taking in
their surroundings,
their opponent's motions,
and the intricacies
of their ATs
and focusing all those
elements on a single point:
victory.
You see, that's why A‐class...
Hm?
(screaming)
Ikki, what the hell
are you doing?
He's taking a dump!
Every time we take a
field trip, he takes a dump!
But why's he have
to dump right there?
Because if I waste time
looking for the can,
I might miss out
on the match.
♪
(sighs)
Huh?
That's weird,
he's not even wearing ATs.
And why's he leaving
in the middle of a battle?
What about his teammate?
♪
♪ Check it out ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪
♪ Now ♪
Hold up, hold up!
♪
(laughing maniacally)
Damn, he's good.
He's not even using his hands.
Who is that kid?
Even for an A‐class rider,
he's too strong.
His style of fighting
is really strange
and there's something up
with his partner too.
This just doesn't make sense.
You'd think people'd be
talking about a rider this good
but I'm in Sleeping Forest
and even I didn't find out
about him until today.
♪
(yelling)
Little shit!
♪
I feel like my
blood is on fire!
My heart's pounding so fast,
it's about to burst
out of my chest!
This really gets me off!
No way.
This is what I live for.
Walking the line
between life and death.
One wrong move
and it's all over!
♪
You're nothing to me.
I turn gravity upside down
and tear through my enemies
from the inside out!
Emblems, teams, friends?
Ha, that all means nothing
but a bunch of shit to me!
This kid's a monster.
♪
This is my road, the Fang!
He's screwed.
♪
(giggling maniacally)
Gonzo!
♪
Did you know that Agito's
personality changes
when he switches his eye
patch to the other eye?
If you're gonna talk nonsense,
at least put some pants on.
You better do it fast, too,
we're surrounded
by Marufu G‐Men.
They're gonna charge you
with public indecency.
First, Tom‐Tom needs
to get Gonzo to a hospital.
Everyone else, follow me
to the top of the plant.
Hold on tight 'cause
we're about to fly!
Ikki, watch out, shark!
Next time on Air Gear,
I'll pull you out
of that well, Agito,
and show you the sky.
♪