♪
Modern technology has
allowed for the advent
of a four‐kilowatt
miniaturized motor
no bigger than a tiny gear,
and it's become
especially popular
among extreme sports fans
who use it to modify
their roller blades.
♪
These daredevils push
themselves to go even faster,
to fly even higher.
With these high‐tech devices,
they enter a world of their own,
racing down the streets,
writing their own rules.
For Air Trek riders,
there are no boundaries.
The world is their road,
and the sky is the limit,
climbing higher and higher
to the heavens themselves.
(static crackling)
Air Trek‐‐fucking bullshit.
Watch your mouth!
(yelling)
What do you think you're doing?
I didn't give you permission
to watch my videos, punk!
♪
Don't you have any manners?
Have respect for
people's privacy.
♪
You'd think that by now
you'd have figured out
the rules around here, Ikki.
♪
How about you give
me a warning next time
before you try to kill me?
Geez, and I'm the hero, too.
Ikki, did you
lose another fight?
Well, you're lucky you didn't
go and get yourself killed!
(yelling)
No way!
‐Huh?
I haven't lost
the fight yet, okay?
Ikki?
♪
Are you kidding me?
You're the leader of
the East Side Gunz?
Ha‐‐you're just a little shit!
I'm gonna kick your ass!
♪
(grunting)
Son of a‐‐
(yelling)
♪
Got ya.
Listen, runt.
You know what'll happen if
I drop you from way up here?
It won't be pretty!
(whimpering)
You get it now?
This is what happens when
you screw around with me.
I can't believe it!
This little bastard
pissed his pants!
(laughing)
I want a picture!
Hey, while he's here,
why don't we stuff
some firecrackers up his ass?
Yeah, make him go boom!
Ikki.
Ikki!
Hey, man, you still alive?
What were you thinking?
Weren't you listening when
I told you the Skull Saders
are the toughest Storm
Riders around here?
Yeah, yeah‐‐where's
my fucking bike?
Forget the bike, dude,
you're lucky to be alive.
Hey, Ikki, wait!
Where are you‐‐
(clanking)
(squeaking)
(birds chirping)
I thought so‐‐he's
always easy to find.
Ikki!
Kazu told me what
happened‐‐I can't believe
you tried to take a
team of Storm Riders on!
You're not still pouting
about getting beat, are you?
‐Shh.
‐Huh?
♪
What the hell is she?
That girl practices
around here every day.
♪
Not bad, huh?
Looks just like Gamachi
from the Air Trek commercial.
So do you always
come here to watch her?
Don't get the wrong
idea or anything.
I don't know her name,
and she doesn't
even know I'm here.
♪
(sizzling)
Don't grab that one,
it isn't cooked yet!
All right, but I call
dibs on the big piece!
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
Oh, uh, well, I
can't eat it all so‐‐
Sorry, sis, no mercy.
He has to face his punishment.
But he's so hungry‐‐
just look at him!
That's a face only
a mother could love.
(panting)
Well, it's not like you
have any dignity left!
Go ahead, eat!
(growling)
(yelling)
♪
Bad dog!
You really have a
death wish, don't you?
Noooo!
Gross!
I smell like barbecue sauce!
That dirty animal
ruined our meat night.
It doesn't matter
if it's meat night
or any other night,
that little bastard
is always finding news ways
to piss me off, you know?
But on the bright side,
we all get to take
a bath together!
Hey, what are you doing?
Well, Ringo, no fair!
Since when did your
boobs get so frickin' big?
Hold on, let me grab 'em!
‐No way!
‐Calm down, you two!
You're gonna slip
and bust your heads.
Honestly, they're so immature!
I'll let you touch mine!
‐You pervert‐‐I said no!
‐Don't be so shy!
Come on!
(grunting)
You owe me a peek for
treating me like crap!
(yelling)
Oww!
It's not fair.
They treat me
like a freakin' dog,
but they're the real bitches.
I have feelings too, you know.
I oughta call social services
on those jerks for this.
Huh?
♪
Why not?
(chuckling)
What the‐‐
♪
Air Treks‐‐no way.
Are these all theirs?
♪
How come they never
told me about this?
♪
Sleeping Forest.
Huh.
Is that some kind of group name?
Just lock the left buckle in,
and I should be ready to go.
All right.
(alarm beeping, yelling)
♪
Huh‐‐it's really moving.
It's just like on TV!
"Acceleration‐‐applying
pressure with your feet
will increase the speed."
Like this?
Wait, that's too
much, slow down!
♪
That was close.
It looks like the
brake is at the bottom,
but it's hard to stop.
I guess I'll need to
turn or make a powerslide
if I wanna slow down.
But man, this rocks.
Hell yeah!
I should've figured he
would do this sooner or later.
Rika's gonna be pissed
he took her Air Treks.
Yeah, and knowing Rika,
she's probably gonna
take it out on us, too!
Let's just pretend like
we don't know anything.
Ikki.
(wind howling)
Damn, I can't believe
that girl was able
to grind on the fence like that.
Should I try it?
Well, maybe I should wait
till I've practiced
a little more.
Birds can spread their
wings and fly to the heavens,
but you're stuck
here on the ground.
Why is that?
(whirring)
♪
I can fly.
You hear that, birds?
You can suck it!
(yelling)
♪
This is awesome!
It's like I've got
wings on my feet!
♪
Uh, wait a sec.
How the hell am I
supposed to land?
Landing, landing!
What the hell was I thinking?
Crap!
♪
Please, I just wanna stop!
(electricity buzzing)
(yelling)
Ow!
What, is meeting over already?
(screaming)
Typical reaction from rookie.
Obviously, you've not
been riding very long.
‐Please don't eat me!
‐You're not worth eating!
I run top class
AT shop for pros,
not little boys
who piss their pants.
Hey, don't diss me!
You're talking to Babyface
of the East Side Gunz!
(crying)
Oh, God, please don't eat me!
You are new recruit
from Sleeping Forest?
Well, sorry I was so rude.
You must've gotten lost
on way to meeting.
‐Korojii!
‐Eh?
This Sleeping Forest kid
needs to go to meeting, okay?
Yeah, okay!
Move it or lose it, Hollywood!
‐Wait for me!
‐So.
He's from Sleeping Forest.
I wonder how he
managed that one.
♪
Try to keep up!
Hey, slow down, old man!
Who you callin' "old man"?
(laughing)
I said wait!
Hey, where the hell is this
old geezer taking me, anyway?
(grunting)
Crap.
Damn, old man!
Why the hell did you stop?
Huh?
'Cause we're here.
The big meeting.
(indistinct whispering)
(water rushing)
Hey, check this out, I'm cool!
No you're not!
(indistinct conversations)
Oh, so it's like a
big Storm Rider party.
‐Huh?
‐Hi!
Simca!
Whoo!
♪
So her name's Simca, huh?
Cool.
Good thing I
brought that sticker!
Uh, excuse me, can
I stick one on, too?
Yeah, sure, if you can catch me!
Hey, no fair!
Get back here!
Huh, Ikki?
What's he doing
at the big meeting?
When did he get into ATs?
(laughing)
Close!
Almost!
Don't give up!
Hell yeah!
No way.
(chuckling)
‐Huh?
‐You see that?
That guy put up a challenge!
Yeah, he put his sticker
on top of the Skull Saders!
Guess he's looking for a fight.
♪
This is Team B,
we're ready to move.
This is Team D‐‐we've
secured the eastern entrance.
All Teams ready to go, sir.
♪
Leave the north entrance free.
We'll get the
bystanders out that way.
I can handle the front alone.
Team A can back
up the east side.
Roger.
It's been a while
since the last hunt.
I'll be disappointed if there
isn't anyone worth fighting.
(indistinct conversations)
Did I do something wrong?
Not bad, rookie.
You've got a lot of guts
taking on the Skull Saders
without any
teammates to back you.
Yeah.
Wait, you mean I'm
gonna have to fight?
‐Yeah!
‐You again.
I guess one ass‐beating
wasn't enough for ya, huh?
Fine with me‐‐bring it on.
I won't hold back this time.
I just hope you
brought some diapers
if you're gonna
piss your pants again.
Son of a bitch.
No, not this again!
‐Ikki, why?
‐You're not even a Storm Rider!
Just say you
didn't know the rules
‐and apologize, okay?
‐Oh, hell, no.
Simca‐‐I told you
this isn't a game,
‐so stop screwing around.
‐Yeah, whatever.
I'm not the one who
started all this mess.
Why don't you mind your
own damn business, Spitfire?
You think you can
tell us what to do
just 'cause you're one
of the eight kings?
The punk
disrespected our symbol.
We're not gonna sit here
and take that crap, got it?
Listen, you ass, we're
not here to talk about‐‐
Freeze‐‐this
meeting's over, punks.
I'm the Chief
of the Countermeasure
Against Reckless Use of
Aviation Footwear Department,
Kaito Wanijima.
Under the authority
of article four
of the 12th Division law,
you're all under arrest!
Damn‐‐I should've
known they'd show up.
Meeting adjourned.
(indistinct shouting)
♪
(chuckling)
Those little delinquents
think they can get away from us.
Well, stop standing
there like idiots
and bust them then.
That's it, come on!
Hurry up and take out
the trash, I'm bored!
Well, then, I'll
be sure to leave you
some scraps to play with, Agito.
♪
‐What's going on?
‐Hey, piss boy!
You're not getting off easy
just 'cause the cops showed up.
You asked for a fight, and
that's what you're gonna get.
I'll scrub the road
with your face
till it's as
smooth as your head!
That's what I like to hear!
You ever heard of the Glum Slum?
The Glum Slum‐‐that
old bag's AT shop?
The first one who makes it there
and shuts off their neon sign
takes the other team's emblem.
I've been waiting for this.
Not every day you get a shot
at a legendary emblem like that.
Uh‐oh, he looks serious!
Hang in there, rookie.
If you win, I'll give you
a special reward, okay?
♪
(yelling)
Bring it on, baldy!
I'm the one who calls
the shots around here!
Later, boys!
♪
Little bitch is all talk.
(whirring)
I think I'm starting
to get the hang of this.
Shifting my weight,
timing my acceleration,
everything's so precise!
These things react almost
as fast as I can think!
Take that!
(laughing)
Better watch where
you're going, piss boy!
Dammit.
If I don't do something,
I'm gonna end up
looking pretty pathetic.
My legs don't wanna move.
My heart is telling me
to get my ass in gear!
♪
Huh‐‐Ringo?
I'm impressed,
Ikki, you look like
you're doing pretty
good for your first time!
‐Thanks, I guess.
‐You've got some nerve
betting our emblem on a
fight with a bunch of thugs.
And now we have to
come clean up your mess!
Your arrogant stupidity
could've cost us our emblem!
You too?
We'll take care of the scrubs.
You've gotta win this thing!
I really hate
this kind of thing.
ATs shouldn't be
used for fighting,
But now that I see you
getting excited about 'em,
I'm glad!
Watch and learn, rookie!
♪
I have a feeling these
punks might not fight fair!
We'd better be extra careful.
Those who wander into our forest
shall fall into
an eternal slumber!
Sleeping Forest, let's go!
(grunting)
♪
This is what you
get for being naughty!
Looks like he had
teammates with him after all.
Damn, I can't let him slow me
down if I wanna win this thing.
Take 'em out!
♪
How could you use
your AT as a weapon?
You have no right to ride!
Go, hurry!
Yeah!
♪
That's it‐‐it's
all his battle now.
But if he's racing
at this level‐‐
Our emblem is as good as gone.
Don't worry.
Even if he does lose it,
I'll kick their ass
and take it back.
(chuckling)
I always wanted a
shot at that emblem,
and now it's in
the palm of my hands.
The Skull Saders
can finally rank up.
We won't be stuck
in E‐class anymore.
What?
(electricity zapping)
(whirring)
♪
No way‐‐when did he
learn a trick like that?
(zapping)
♪
What the‐‐
The wind, it's splitting.
♪
No, this is like a road!
I can see it!
A road of wings!
♪
(grunting)
That's not funny, Ikki!
If you don't take
the basics seriously,
then you'll never
master your ATs!
All right, all right, sorry!
Oh, by the way, I'm forming
my own Storm Rider team.
‐Huh‐‐with who?
‐Well, right now,
it's just Kazu and Onigiri.
Do you think we could get
Simca the Swallow to join?
I really don't think
that's a good idea!
But I wanna ride with Simca!
Next time on Air Gear,
listen to the Screams
of the Rez‐Boa‐Dogs.
♪