♪
(engine running)
Kaito!
♪
What the hell do
you want from us now?
♪
I was so worried, you bad boy.
You really scared your big
brother disappearing like that
without calling home.
Anyway, I'm not mad, I know‐‐
If you ever try
that crap again,
I'll make you wish
you were never born.
That smile is totally
freaking me out.
♪
But‐‐but I...
(laughs)
♪
It's good to have you back.
(whimpering)
I really missed you.
♪
Now get in your cage.
Good, let's get home.
Ultimate technique.
Raging Fist!
(grunts)
That really hurt!
You little shit!
♪
Ikki.
Who the hell do you think
you are, you piece of crap?
I'm with the police, remember?
I'll throw your ass in jail.
Think you can scare me
with some puny stick, twerp?
Oh, this thing, I just
found it lying on the ground.
Do you know what it belongs to?
♪
♪ Oh yeah ♪
(gasps)
My emergency break.
How did you get that?
(laughs)
Huh?
♪
My car!
I'll get you for this.
Just wait!
I'll get you,
you asshole punk!
Now's our chance,
let's get out of here.
You're really gonna help me?
You mean you don't hate me?
Hm.
I can't let you
go back to the well
after you finally
learned how to fly.
Kaito!
I don't care if
you're my brother!
I‐‐I mean we, we won't
be your tool anymore!
(clanging sounds)
(sighs)
I'll kill him.
♪
Crap.
Come on, Kazu, you've been
doing that all morning.
You're gonna be
late for school.
I know, sis, I'm about to leave.
See you later!
All right, I only
knocked over one can today.
I'm getting good at this.
♪
I don't have any
money, I swear!
Yeah, right,
you wanna prove it?
Yeah, jump up and down,
let's see if you jingle.
Come on, man, I said jump!
Jump, dammit, come on!
I said jump, you stupid chode!
You guys are pathetic.
Huh?
You learn to act that
way watching cartoons?
Got a problem, pipsqueak?
Oh, I get it, you're from
the East Side too, huh?
Bring it, bitch.
Yeah, if you wanna talk shit,
come say it to our faces.
Agh!
Morning, Kazu,
what's up?
‐Oh, Buccha.
‐That guy's gonna hate us!
We're gonna make you
pay for this, you punk!
We're gonna get you.
(distant shouting)
Huh, what was up
with those guys?
Just forget about it.
Kazuma Mikura, tough, heroic,
and great at street fighting.
Second in command to the
infamous East Side Gunz.
Sounds badass.
But somehow I feel like I
have a kind of dim shadow.
Rah‐hah, loser!
Class, this is Agito Wanijima.
He's a psychopathic killer‐‐
I mean, a nice young boy.
Everybody please be
careful around him.
He's very dangerous‐‐
I mean, different.
He's just a little different,
so try to be nice, okay?
Nice to meet you, everyone.
(girl classmates squeal)
No, not another character
that stands out more than me.
Dude, snot bubble.
So, there you go.
For now he's staying with me,
or maybe I should say
he's renting out a room
at Ringo's house.
So you two are
cohabitating already, huh?
That's so soon.
At this rate, you'll
be married in no time.
What a fag.
I mean, you're the man.
So how was your first time?
Did you dumbasses listen
to a single word I just said?
So, um, is it okay
if I start class now?
Squawk, oh, God,
gonna die, squawk.
♪
(giggles)
Well, anyway, now that we
finally have five members,
it's time to form
the Ikki Empire‐‐
I mean, our Storm Rider team.
Right!
Let's start with
Akito and Agito.
You're the supreme commanders
of all offensive operations.
Your job is to totally
kick everyone's ass.
Roger.
I'll kill 'em all, captain.
Buccha, you're
the culinary commander
of the commando food unit.
You'll beat the crap out
of people and eat stuff.
Sounds like the job for me.
I won't let you down.
Finally, Kazu and Onigiri.
Yeah.
You know that you guys have
been two of my best friends
for over ten years now.
So your positions are...
Well, let's see here.
How about Private Fatass
and Errand Boy Number Five.
Huh?
Hey, wait a minute!
Just why the hell
am I number five?
All right, keep your pants on.
I'll make you
the head secretary
of going to get us
drinks and snacks
from the vending machine.
We're gonna throw you off
the roof, you bastard.
Yeah!
Squawk, beat it, squawk.
Dammit, this is bullshit.
Ikki's really starting
to piss me off.
He barely even knows
Buccha and Agito
and he's already treating them
better than his best friends.
‐What the hell?
‐Hey, Kazu!
What's up, Kitsune?
Someone wants to talk to you.
Would you come
here for a sec?
Huh?
(screams)
Holy crap, these guys used
to run the East Side Gunz.
Long time no see, Kazu.
What's up?
Nothing much,
sir, how are you?
We're fine, now shut up.
We missed you, kid.
Word on the street is that
you and the rest of the Gunz
made an AT team,
is that true?
Well, what do you want to hear?
You know, the legacy of
the Gunz has been passed down
to East Side seniors
for 27 years.
You're not gonna let that
go to waste, are ya?
I mean, listen, Kazu, why
don't you be the next leader
‐of the Gunz?
‐What?
Me, leader?
I...
That punk Ikki's
no good anymore.
He's lost his head
over this AT shit.
(laughs nervously)
Yeah, I know what you
mean, I was thinking...
You're wasting your time
playing Ikki's lap dog.
You deserve a lot better.
You think so?
If you're gonna
take on responsibility,
you gotta make sacrifices.
We can't just hand over our
legacy to anyone, you know.
So here's the deal.
You gotta bring
us Ikki's head.
♪
Then you can forget it.
Huh?
(clamoring)
We make you a good offer
and you blow us
off like that?
What the hell?
If you want to side with Ikki,
we'll take you out too, man.
Just admit it, you guys are
afraid of Ikki, aren't you?
You just crossed the line, kid.
(grunts)
♪
You piece of shit.
Errand Boy Number Five
of the Ikki Empire,
Kazuma Mikura.
If you want to get to Ikki,
you gotta go through me first.
♪
I never noticed, but the reason
the cherry trees look so nice
is 'cause they have
all these little flowers
blooming around them.
♪
Man, Kazu, what
happened to your face?
Your beautiful face!
If you suck that
much at fighting,
just let me handle it.
Shut up, give me a break.
♪
Seriously, if we're
really gonna do this thing,
then I say we
gotta make it big.
I'm gonna be the best
damn errand boy in Japan,
so you better not let me
down, we got a deal, boss?
♪
In ancient times
when Greek city‐states
battled one another
for supremacy,
their armies built
massive altars
by piling up their defeated
enemies' weapons and corpses.
The strong were decided by
whose altar reached the highest.
These altars were
called Towers of Victory
or Tropeaum.
The Parts War is the same.
There are eight kings
who wield their regalia
and rule the eight roads
that lead to the summit
of the Tropeaum.
Climbing atop the corpses
of their fallen opponents
and facing
countless struggles,
they ride the waves of victory
and crush anyone
in their path.
Then, when
everything becomes one,
the legendary Sky
King shall appear
and ascend to the heavens with‐‐
What the hell is
she talking about?
They didn't really have
ATs back in Ancient Greece.
You better not be looking
at porn sites again.
Your lunch break was
over a long time ago.
Get your asses back to work,
stupid clock timers.
You're lucky
I don't dock you.
Hey, check it out.
What do you
think about this one?
It's cute, huh?
I want something
that sticks out,
something really flashy.
Hey, guys, remember,
one each, okay?
There's nothing
here in XXXXL,
no wonder nobody shops here.
If they can't meet
their customers' needs,
I don't know how they're
gonna stay in business.
Hey, it's free,
don't complain!
The problem is you're too fat.
You wanna shop here,
lose some weight.
Hey, shut your hole.
Well?
Ooh, I like it,
I like it!
I really appreciate this, Gonzo.
No biggie, I owe you
guys from last time.
Here we go.
Agh!
(angry overlapping shouting)
Man, I hate
affirmative action.
There are a lot
of things you need
before you start a team.
You have to get an emblem
design, make stickers,
get a memory card to hold
the data from your battles,
you need to keep
buying AT cards,
oh, and get safety gear.
It's too much!
How are middle school kids
supposed to afford all that?
Well, you have to go through
so much trouble to make it,
people develop real emotional
attachments to their team.
Storm Rider
battles mean so much
'cause you're putting
your pride on the line.
Ah‐ha, there you are!
Hey, Ringo!
This way, this way!
Hey, Ume!
Sorry, I hope we
didn't take too long.
So what is this place?
It's Ms. Michita's house.
She's gonna make your
team emblem for you.
She happens to be
a friend of Ume.
I buy all of her stuff
and she owes me a favor,
‐so it all works out.
‐Awesome!
You mean this lady's
like a real designer?
So, uh, who's this again?
Huh?
(whispering)
♪
Hm, mm‐hm.
She said she needs
as much information
about the team as possible.
It could be like the number
of members or anything.
Just something to give
her a better picture.
Wow, it's really an honor
to have someone like you
working on this for our team.
If you don't mind me
asking, when do you think
you'll have it all ready for us?
(whispering)
Mm‐hm, mm‐hm.
If she can make contact
with Decral aliens,
it'll be ready by tomorrow.
Aliens?
You sure this is okay?
She's weird.
Well, just nod
your head and smile.
You know how artists
can be sometimes.
‐Look out.
‐Huh?
(groaning)
She said that
amateurs like you
shouldn't interfere
with an artist's work.
Okay then.
So I guess I'll leave it to you.
Now that the design
is taken care of,
you just have to find
someone to make the emblem.
I had a silversmith
make mine last time.
I'll get him to do it.
Awesome.
So now all we need
are helmets.
(phone ringing)
Hello!
What's up, Emily?
I found some helmets
for you guys.
I got them from this
senior at Northside High.
His team got disbanded
so he can't use them.
Nice.
(phone ringing)
Dude, we just got off work.
We made like 60 bucks.
Maybe you guys should
come work here too.
It's really not too bad.
Yeah, sure.
All right, I'll see
you guys in a sec.
♪
So this is what making
a team is like, huh?
You know what,
it's a lot of fun.
But wait, Ikki, what's
your team going to do?
Hm.
Blah.
Well, that's a funny face.
But yeah, I mean,
there's all kinds
of different things you can do
with an AT team
these days, Ikki.
Some people race, some people
enter professional sports,
some form gangs,
and others just want to
get in shape or have fun.
♪
I never even
thought about that.
Huh?
What do I want to do?
What do I want to
accomplish with ATs?
♪
What's our team's purpose?
Well, if you don't
have a purpose,
then the reason
you're starting your team
can be to find a purpose.
Once you start riding,
I'm sure you'll see
a lot of things
in a new light.
♪
You think?
Maybe you're right.
♪
Well, boss, I have to say,
it's a pretty awesome name.
Way to go.
Of course!
Kogarasumaru was the name
of a legendary sword.
The maru part is something
people used to add
to the names of stuff
like boats and castles
back in the old days.
It means something like,
"We all share a common fate."
Kogarasumaru.
Team Kogarasumaru, take off!
(chatter)
What's up?
Uh, what's up?
You guys.
Man, I have to admit,
after all this time,
I never thought you guys would
make it out of this place alive.
Yeah, well, we did, jerk face.
Mm‐hm.
Listen up, delinquents!
Don't try anything stupid.
I'll have you know I'm
third degree black belt
in karate and Judo too.
If you turds are looking
for revenge on the school,
you've gotta go through me.
So who wants the
first black eye?
I think I'll pass, holmes.
Come on, teach,
we're over that now.
In fact, what do you say we
all go for a couple of drinks?
I already bailed high school,
so starting today
I'm a working man.
Nonsense!
Even if you're working,
you're still underage.
If you want to drink,
drink some juice,
but screw you if you
think I'm buying.
Yeah, whatever.
I almost forgot.
Hey, Baby Face.
Huh; What?
Say cheese.
Shit!
Ikki!
Yi!
Ow!
That's what you get for
turning your back on the Gunz
to make some shitty AT team.
Because of you punks,
the 26 year legacy
of the East Side Gunz
ends with our generation.
Ha.
So starting now, if you
want to be part of a legend,
make your own.
So, looks like you
got some work to do.
Better not let me
down, Baby Face.
♪
Hey, Maki, wait.
‐Thanks.
♪
Now it's our time.
Right here, look.
Another team
claimed the school?
This is the first time
this area's been claimed
since the Yaooo was
defeated and broke up.
♪
This is our turf.
The seniors entrusted us
with protecting our school.
We won't let anyone
take it away.
Ringo, are you
bringing the food?
Wow, you're really
getting into this.
Well, yeah, I mean, all they
used to do is get into fights,
so I'm kind of
excited to see them
get so serious
about their team.
Can you blame me?
(grunting)
(groaning)
Kazu, sweetie?
♪
What do you think you're doing?
Hey, Ringo, we're
just beating some sense
into these punks that tried to
make our school their own turf.
‐You wanna help?
‐You idiot!
Huh?
(sniffling)
I thought you
were a Rider, Ikki.
I was so happy
you finally decided
to make something
of yourself,
but now I find out you're no
better than the Skull Saders.
You're just using AT as an
excuse to get into fights.
♪
Uh, numbskulls,
she was so excited
she made dinner for you guys.
♪
Dammit, what the hell
was I thinking?
Doesn't mean anything
if you take an area by force.
Even I know that.
Now look at what you've done.
You better tell Ringo
you're sorry, asshole!
And it better come from
the bottom of your heart.
You buttheads were kicking
their ass as much as I was!
‐Hey, kid.
‐Huh?
You're either a
rookie or an idiot
if you think you can pull
crap like that around here.
Well, let's see.
♪
AT operating time 165 hours.
I guess you've only been
riding about two months, huh?
Yeah, they haven't
even registered
for the Parts War yet.
♪
Average ground speed,
42 kilometers per hour.
Minimum turning
radius, 2.2 meters.
Reflectives ration, 5.5.
And only five successfully
executed tricks above E‐Class.
This guy's a joke.
What, are they
psychic or something?
It's just a read.
They're little cell phone
programs that analyze
the data stored inside
the heel of your AT.
So they know how
much Kazu sucks?
No way, that's not fair!
Hey, hey, they're using
pretty decent parts.
This might be a good
battle after all.
All right, here's the deal.
We'll challenge
you to a Parts War.
If you win, you take
the area, but if we win,
you leave all of your equipment
here and go home naked.
Hmm.
Does that mean the girls
have to strip too?
If we're lucky.
In your dreams, boys.
Chop chop, let's get this show
on the road, you bastards!
He's sold out!
‐Pervert!
‐And now he's flying!
Crap!
So, are you up
for it or not?
We can totally school
these jerks in a fight.
We don't have to
play their game.
Kazu, things are
different now.
Huh?
♪
(gasping)
We're Riders.
We fight with ATs.
Come on!
Let's bet our emblems.
♪
Kazu just slid off the track
and Onigiri got a
face full of fence!
Somehow this didn't
work out how I imagined.
At this rate,
you're gonna end up
losing your emblem
to the Sabeltigers,
not to mention your clothes!
I know, I've been
getting naked a lot lately.
But this time it's different.
Fear not, in the
face of perversity,
hope springs eternal!
Carried by the wind,
your savior has arrived.
Next time on Air Gear,
with brilliant style
and blinding speed,
I come to the aid
of those in need.
Croissant Mask has arrived!
♪