♪
Are all of them‐‐
Should you see fit,
they are yours to command.
♪
You have said that your wings
have the strength to carry
our dreams to the
heavens themselves.
I believe in those
words of yours.
Now I ask that you
lend us those wings,
and pave the road to a new era.
A new era
of Genesis.
You are our Sky King.
(rumbling)
♪
(bells ringing)
Your wish is my
command, my lord.
Ask and you shall receive.
You'll really do anything,
no matter what?
Yes, anything, you have my word.
I see.
Then get me an espresso
and dozen chocolate donuts.
(chuckling)
You said anything, right?
All of a sudden I've got a team
of 350 riders to order around.
That's wack.
(footsteps approaching)
What's up, Ume?
Ikki, are you sure you wanna
be the leader of Genesis?
Well, I don't know
for sure yet, but‐‐
Do you have any
idea what it means
to take on a job like that?
Did anyone even
tell you why Genesis
was formed in the first place?
Do you know what
their objective is?
Hm, they're gonna tear down
the Tower of Trophaeum, right?
‐Ume, stop.
‐But someone has to tell him!
I know how you feel, but
no matter what you say,
you can't get through
to a bird brain like him.
But I, I still like Ikki!
I don't want us
to have to fight.
I mean, Ikki's like part
of the family, I want him
to stay with us
forever, don't you?
Whoa, wait, hold on a sec.
Why did you say we're
gonna have to fight, huh?
You need to stop
taking orders from Simca,
especially when you don't even
know what you're agreeing to.
I don't get it,
why do you all have
a bug up your ass about Genesis?
♪
I'm sorry, Ikki, but
we can't talk about that.
♪
Okay everyone, here are
the handouts to fill you in
about this year's class trip.
(bells ringing)
(indistinct conversations)
I guess I'd better
take him one too.
♪
Hey, Crow, what you
gonna do about Genesis?
If you go along with this, then
we'll have the strongest team
in all of Japan
under our control.
‐Would that be awesome or what?
‐Yeah, but don't you think
this whole thing is
too good to be true?
Do you even realize that you
have to be at least B class
before you even think
about challenging
the summon of the
Tower of Trophaeum.
Since we're still E Class
that means we have to win
nine battles in
a row to advance.
Nine wins in a row?
Not only that, but our
team possesses Regalia.
So we need to understand
just what kinda
danger we're up against.
‐So what do you think, Ikki?
‐It's obvious, isn't it?
We kill every team
that gets in our way.
Come on, what don't
you cut the crap, Crow?
I mean, you're pretty good,
but me and Akito aside,
you guys are still beginners.
Yeah, well maybe it would
be a good idea to see
how Akito feels about this too.
That's how you roll, Kazu.
Wow, they're letting
you out already?
Well, I still have to
take it easy for a while,
but they said I can
go home at least.
(water flowing)
Akito said he doesn't really
care what you guys do.
He did?
He can't ride with
the rest of the team
until our injuries
heal, so he says
if Ikki's serious about
taking over Genesis,
then there's no reason
not to go for it.
Well, you haven't convinced me.
Hmph!
‐Aw, come on, Buccha!
‐Let him go.
Oh yeah.
Is that a Kyoto tour guide?
Yeah, we're going
on a field trip.
What, is there something wrong?
Well, that sounds like fun
and all, but you can't go
unless you have money
saved up, right?
Money, oh, yeah right.
I guess you kinda just
ran away from home, huh?
I'll talk to Tom‐Tom tomorrow
and see what she can do.
Okay.
(dog barking)
(wind blowing)
♪
What up?
I wanted to ask you something.
Did all these teams
aim for the Trophaeum?
Most of them, by the way,
I heard your team was going
to take control over Genesis.
We haven't decided yet.
Really we don't even know
how this whole thing works.
At this point,
we couldn't challenge
the Trophaeum if we wanted to.
I mean, how are
we supposed to know
what the teams on
the top are like?
You'll know, actually
you've known for long time.
Say what, what's that
supposed to mean?
It means exactly what I said.
Remember first night
you came here?
Which team's emblem were
you wearing on your jacket?
Wait.
You mean, Sleeping Forest?
♪
So, Ringo's team is
at the top of the tower?
Now you're finally
starting to get it.
Ringo Noyamano is successor
to Sleeping Forest.
You see, after the Kilik
incident, their team fell apart.
Now as far as most riders know,
they're nothing but a legend.
But ones at the top
know the truth.
Kilik?
It happened before
Ringo was on the team.
Someone betrayed others
and took out the boss.
That must've been the guy
Rika was talking about.
That means Genesis is‐‐
It's a megastorm
created to bring down
the Tower of Trophaeum
and crush Ringo Noyamano's
Sleeping Forest.
Now, do you understand?
This is really starting to
get fun now, don't you think?
I don't see what's
so fun about it.
Well, maybe not for you I guess.
So what're you gonna do?
Are you gonna slap me
like you did last time?
I told you, Ikki
is not your toy.
I never said he was, did I?
He's much more
important than that,
'cause I believe that Little
Crow is the one whose wings
will carry me higher
than I've ever flown before.
Mm‐mm, you're wrong.
But he said he'd
accept, didn't he?
That's why you're so mad, right?
You can't stand to lose
your little toy, can you?
I'm sorry, but he's free now.
It's all up to him.
Just sit back and
enjoy the show.
See you around!
♪
Hey, Aeon, got my donuts?
No, but I heard
you're going to Kyoto.
‐Yeah, it's for our class trip.
‐Perfect timing.
Now that you've been elected
the new leader of Genesis,
there's a king in Kyoto
I'd like you to meet.
‐I trust you don't mind.
‐If it's okay with you,
could we talk about this
leader stuff some other time?
I've kinda got a lot of things
on my mind and my head hurts.
Sure, that's fine.
Whenever you feel up to
it just give me a call.
Yeah, later!
(whooshing noise)
Hey, Ringo.
I see, you're not supposed
to be able to go on the trip
if you don't have the money.
I'm sorry, Akito, but
it looks like you might
have to stay behind
and have study hall.
Come on, there's gotta
be something you can do.
I'm sure as a teacher
you make enough money
‐to pay for him, right?
‐What?
Well, why don't you
just ask Mr. Orihara?
(clearing throat)
Well, you know, I'd love
to help you guys out,
but I just spent all my savings
on a new punching bag, so...
♪
I'm sorry about this, it's not
that I don't have any money.
I actually saved up plenty
when I used to work
for the Marufu G‐Men.
Then what the hell
is the problem?
Well, it's not a matter
of having money,
it's a matter of getting to it.
♪
Ringo!
Gonna have a
Kogarasumaru meeting
at our hideout after class.
But Ikki, I‐‐
I want you to be there too.
All right?
♪
(birds chirping)
I found it.
So you sure that's where
your bankbook's at, Akito?
(beeping)
That's it, I'm positive.
My brother and I lived in
that trailer all our lives.
♪
Great, we're totally screwed.
I don't know about you,
but I'd rather stay home
than risk getting shot at.
♪
Well, not me, I never
got to go on field trips
when I was in grade school.
I didn't want Rika
to have to pay,
so every year I stayed at home.
♪
Of course I was
really frustrated,
but it wasn't because I
wanted to go on a field trip.
In fact, it didn't really hit
me until the class came back.
When I saw everyone
laughing and talking,
then I realized that they
were all sharing memories
that I could never be a part of.
♪
I've made my decision,
all right?
Kogarasumaru,
prepare to move out.
♪
‐Ikki.
‐You can't be serious.
I mean, what're we
gonna do about Akito?
Even if we could sneak into
the trailer we'd still need him
to show us where
the bankbook is.
Don't worry, even if Akito can't
ride, he's still coming with us.
Whether we're going to Kyoto
or the top of the Trophaeum,
we do everything as a team.
This isn't just about
some class trip.
It's about our dream.
This time I want all of us
to share our memories,
because now we're on
our way to the top,
and we have to believe that
what we're doing is right.
We have to believe, 'cause
we'll be crushing the dreams
of all the other riders
on the way to the top,
‐and that's fine by me!
‐Ikki.
Right now we have control over
all the riders in Genesis,
but in one month, I say,
we declare war and show them
what we're really made of!
If we can bring them
down with our own power,
then they'll know we're serious.
If we're gonna rule them,
we're gonna make them
bow down ourselves.
I think you landed on your
head one too many times.
However...
Count on me to fill
in as Akito's leg.
Now, come on, let's go
get the savings passbook!
Oh, by the way, it just
so happens that Aeon said
we're supposed to meet
a new king in Kyoto.
That means this is our big
chance to conquer Kyoto,
but before that, we gotta
get back Akito's bankbook!
We'll call it
Operation City Hunter
Wriggling in the
Darkness, let's go!
What kind of stupid ass name
for an operation is that?
Stop complaining, go!
Kogarasumaru!
(together)
Kill 'em dead!
♪
I'm sorry, sir,
this road is closed.
If you wait, we'll
be done in a minute.
All right, but hurry up,
if you take too long
I'll put a cap in your ass.
Good thing our boss is stupid,
and doesn't lock up
the equipment at night.
Yeah, guess we're lucky
we work for a stupid boss.
♪
Open up!
(growling)
♪
So, uh, where'd you get
this sweet looking ride?
Hands off, jerkwad,
hey, don't I know you?
What, who, me, no.
All right, just like we planned.
You've got 30 seconds
to find that book.
Right.
♪
I imagined this
place looking like
a torture chamber or something.
But actually,
now that I'm here,
it kinda reminds me of my place.
♪
‐That bastard!
‐This isn't right.
I'm sure I left it in here,
I know I didn't take it out.
Kaito must have moved it,
I don't understand.
Why would he have taken it?
I'm sick of this, I'll
take a back street.
No, just wait a little longer!
Crap, what the hell
are those idiots doing?
‐Ahhhh!
‐That's not good!
Well, that's gonna
suck for Ikki.
I think I'll go home and pack.
(engine whirring)
Well, this sucks.
So have you found it yet, Akito?
I can't figure out where
he could've moved it.
What're we gonna do now?
Don't move, ya filthy
little thief.
I gotta tell you, you picked
the wrong car to rob.
(shouting)
(thudding)
Akira!
What in the hell
are you doing here?
What, what am I‐‐how about you?
If Kaito finds out you're here,
you two are gonna be road kill.
(whooshing noise)
Kaito, wait, who's driving?
‐You are.
‐Ahh!
(tires skidding)
(grumbling)
‐Big brother.
‐Looks like I must have had
a little too much
to drink last night.
I'm having some kind
of weird hallucination.
That must be it,
no other explanation,
'cause I remember kicking
Akito out of the unit
when Akira came back.
Kicking me out?
And there's no way that
piece of shit traitor
would've had the
nerve to come back,
especially not with
a damn crow with him,
'cause he knows if he did
come back, I'd kick his ass.
Actually, that reminds me,
that useless little brat
left his bankbook behind.
I think I put it in
that bag under my bed
with the rest of his crap.
I don't need it, so I guess
I might as well throw it away.
Now I'm sure when I open
my eyes and turn around,
that hallucination will be gone,
if it knows what's good for it.
♪
Thank you, Kaito.
Wow, you can actually be nice,
I'm pretty impressed.
You're too naive, Akira,
you should know better.
It's all part of the plan.
Now that Akito's a part of
Genesis, we have an inside man.
♪
(engine whirring)
Guess you guys are still
brothers after all, huh?
‐I'm glad everything worked out.
‐Yeah, me too.
I was afraid I wouldn't get to
go on vacation with everyone.
♪
The king of Kyoto is one of the
three leaders of Team Trident.
They're the most powerful
team in the Kansai region
with over 200 riders under them.
This could get ugly, looks like
they'll definitely need my‐‐
I mean, Akito's help.
Hey, something wrong, Akito?
Huh, oh, nothing.
You know, Ume's been
crying for a long time.
You should probably talk
to her when we get back.
Way ahead of you.
(whooshing noise)
(train buzzing)
I hope you're ready, Kyoto,
'cause here we come!
♪
Nijo Castle and
Kiyomizu Temple, huh?
Japan has such a rich heritage.
Why are you talking
like a tourist?
Don't you know that class trips
are the perfect
romantic getaway?
Well, that's what I was hoping
until that weird girl showed up.
‐Who is she anyway?
‐I don't know.
‐I think she's a fan of me.
‐You have to keep your guard up.
You never know when
someone might attack.
Got it, next time on Air Gear:
Genesis, Kansai Branch, here
come Benkei and Yoshitsune!
♪