♪
I think you're worrying
about this too much, Ringo.
No, something is
definitely up.
That blonde doctor
was wearing high heels.
I don't think she's
with the hospital.
What's going on?
I can't move.
Who the hell are you, anyway?
I was sent here by
a certain someone.
I'm afraid that's
all I can tell you.
Mm.
Fuck, get away!
That's gross, don't touch
me with your cow tongue!
Damn, it's locked!
Hurry, give me your ATs.
(whooshing)
‐That's it!
‐Huh?
(gasping)
Um, uh, hi.
Oh, hello, are you
a friend of his?
‐Uh, yes, ma'am.
‐Good.
Make sure he takes it
easy for a while, okay?
Normal doctors can't heal
injuries caused by Regalia.
But wait a second,
you mean I wasn't the one
who caused this injury?
But I thought it happened
because I was
using Akito's body.
Uh, I don't know
what you mean.
You've just got a bad
case of rider's fatigue
from pushing
yourself too hard.
The shot I gave you earlier
is designed to gradually
melt away the toxins
that have accumulated
in your legs.
You mean it's gonna heal?
Of course it's going to heal.
You just leave it to me.
I'll fix you right up.
It's not my fault.
Akito will get better.
You made me miss
Deco King for this?
You were trying
to freak me out,
and it ends up he was
just getting a foot massage
from some slutty doctor!
Oh, I‐‐uh, sorry.
Come on, let's
get out of here.
Sorry for disturbing you.
‐Crow, wait.
‐Huh?
Take the Regalia with you
'cause sooner or later
you're gonna need it
if you want to be
the Sky King.
I don't want it anyway.
♪
Sorry, but right now I still
don't feel comfortable
leaving Akito with you,
but if you hurry up
and become the Sky King,
then I might change my mind.
But until then, I still
have to look after him,
so I'll stay on the team.
♪
That's right you
will, dumbass.
You better get well soon
'cause we're about to take
this all the way to the top.
I don't want you to
miss your ride, got it?
Hm.
♪
The moon's so beautiful.
And yet...
You know, don't you
think it's kind of funny
that we've never
seen the principal?
No one even knows
where his office is.
They call it
the Mirage Room.
What is going on there?
Praise me, worship me!
Give me all your money!
(indistinct chattering)
Wow, you turn
away for a second
and he starts
acting like a god.
♪
Hey.
Keep your panties
on, sweetheart.
Huh, what's wrong, Buccha?
What do you mean?
I mean the battle we
fought against Behemoth
was broadcast all
over the world.
Team Behemoth led by
the Beast King, Akira Udo,
was taken out by a rookie
team named Kogarasumaru.
In case you were wondering,
this is their area.
They took out
the Fang Regalia,
but you could
find it there too.
So now that you know
where to find 'em,
who's up for a little match?
Hey, you guys are famous now.
Yeah, well, cool or not,
it means every other AT team
will be gunning for us.
♪
So what, I don't
care who you are.
If you want to
mess with our area,
then you're as good as dead.
♪
You've got some major
cojones there, Crow.
Come on, let's do this!
Starting tonight, we're
gonna guard our area
until the sun comes up!
Be there at 11:00 sharp!
Kogarasumaru!
Kill 'em dead!
(horn blaring)
(squeaking)
No enemies in sight yet, over.
Good, continue your
surveillance, out.
Okay, I think we
have confirmation.
You guys are pathetic.
Hey, are you sure
you want to make
this train track
our secret hideout?
Well, major streets have a lot
of traffic even at night,
so we could be easily spotted.
Our enemies would most
likely come after us
crossing this train bridge.
Who cares if it's practical?
I just wanted to
build a secret base.
Are these guys coming or not?
Hm, huh?
Look, there they are!
Yeah, you're right!
Those are the punks
I saw on the interweb!
Holy crap, these
guys are serious.
(shouting)
(grunting)
♪
I'll kick your ass!
(laughing)
♪
Ah, the sunrise
after a battle
is even more dazzling than
usual, don't you think?
I'm a lover, not a fighter.
Chill out, Crow, all this
fighting's killing us.
Hell, Agito is still
in the hospital.
We need to slow down.
Our turf is getting
to be too frigging big
for us to even manage.
Yeah, Buccha's
got a good point.
What are we supposed to do
with all this space anyway?
Let's just give up
what we don't use
and keep the good parts.
I don't wanna.
What's wrong with you?
I thought you guys wanted to
aim for the top of the tower.
If you guys are
whining so much
after a battle with a
bunch of crappy thugs,
what are you gonna do
when we have to face
some real competition, huh?
Hm.
Sorry, I guess
you were right.
We just got a
little discouraged.
Yeah.
Hm, long as you understand.
Okay, let's get it
on again tonight!
Yeah, kill 'em dead!
(honking)
♪
(sighing)
What do you think?
Did it turn out
like you wanted?
Oh, yes.
I'm moved.
It's perfect.
'Course it is,
glad you like it.
(sighing)
Ah, I'm sorry,
but I'm afraid we're
all booked up for today.
Excuse me, ma'am?
♪
Sorry, but I'm gonna
have to close up early.
Here, why don't I
reschedule you for tomorrow?
(clock ticking)
Well, now, are you going
to just sit there and mope,
or do you want to
tell me what's wrong?
I don't know.
I've never felt like this.
(clock ticking)
It's strange, but ever
since that fight...
(whooshing)
...it's like I've grown
closer to the sky,
like a wind is
blowing inside me.
It was small at first,
but it's growing stronger.
All right, let's go!
Hold on.
What are you doing?
I know, more and more winds
are shooting through me,
twirling inside me,
building up into storms
and tearing me up.
Before, these winds were
nothing but a whisper,
a little buzzing in my ears.
When I'd sit and
watch the sunset,
it would dance on
the tip of my tongue
like a quiet melody, but,
now, it's grown into a roar,
and I can't rest
my wings any longer.
That wind is commanding me
to destroy my enemies
and conquer the
tower in the sky.
Let me finish this up then.
All right.
You care about
the Crow that much?
More than you know.
♪
Holy shit.
There's a lot more
than yesterday.
Yeah, and they're like
really butt‐ugly too.
Don't wuss out on me now!
I don't care who they are!
If they want to mess
with our area‐‐oh!
No!
No way, he pounded him
like a little bitch!
You bastard!
You're the bastard, bitch.
If you want to
go to the shop,
you gotta wait in line
like everyone else.
What shop?
That shop.
(honking)
♪
(indistinct chattering)
Whoa, so that's the
legendary Glum Slum, huh?
I never thought I'd see this.
Ha‐ho!
Long time no see, Hollywood.
Hey, Koro.
Glad to hear
about your big win,
but you're out of your
cotton‐picking minds
making a hideout in
a place like this.
Heads up.
(clinking)
A key?
I've got a vacant room you
can borrow for a while.
‐Take good care of it.
‐Wait, Koro,
are you sure about this?
It's little much,
don't you think?
Don't push yourself
too hard, Hollywood.
The sky ain't going nowhere.
♪
Come on.
(siren wailing)
All right, let's see.
Turn it five
times to the left
and three times to the right.
You really think
this is gonna work?
Uh, something just clicked.
(gasping)
(clanging)
(slamming)
(laughing)
(gulping)
(clicking)
♪
Whoa.
(gasping)
♪
No fucking way!
Oh, check it out.
I can't believe that guy
is our school principal.
That old man's getting
all up in our business.
At any rate, this sure beats
our last secret hideout.
♪ Beyond the sky ♪
♪ I stretch out my hands ♪
♪ Even if the sun setting
beyond the skyline
colors my hands crimson ♪
♪ The days I've
spent with you ♪
♪ The corpses
of the soldiers
that I have piled up ♪
♪ Before I knew it ♪
♪ It had gotten
higher than the tower
I was aiming for ♪
♪ Even the winter
that had been hiding
between the buildings ♪
♪ Gets pushed by
the wind and sway ♪
I'm opposed to this.
Now is not the time to
get involved in a battle.
Behemoth has been disbanded.
We've lost over 70
percent of our members
along with the Regalia.
If this goes poorly,
we'll lose the rest
of the team as well.
We're at a huge disadvantage.
It's too risky.
♪ The corpses of the soldiers
that I have piled up ♪
♪ Before I knew it ♪
♪ It had gotten
higher than the tower
I was aiming for ♪
♪ Even the winter
that had been hiding
between the buildings ♪
♪ Gets pushed by
the wind and sway ♪
It must be the wind.
Maybe it swayed my heart
so much it's broken now,
but, you know, broken wings
can still dance in the sky
if the wind is strong enough.
Of course I'm scared too,
but the thing is, it's
not losing I'm afraid of.
I'm afraid that if
I keep doing nothing,
then before I know it,
my wings won't work anymore.
This doesn't sound like you.
I've never seen you
act this way before.
(thudding)
Everyone, listen!
Team Spitfire,
Nine‐Tailed Fox, Coca Fire,
all members must assemble
at precisely 3:00 a. m.
Don't be late, not
even by a second.
Convey this message to Iron
Hammer and Loop as well.
In case of any injuries
and malfunctions,
ask Kulto Team
for their assistance.
Route 5462.0.
Now ride!
I'm not sure if
this is right
or if the Simca I know
would make this decision,
but in a way, I think it
may be our only choice.
Word on the street is that
all the little boys and girls
out there with
wings on their feet
have gotten a secret
love letter from Spitfire.
Sounds to me like a big
party is about to go down.
I can't believe they
made a secret hideout
in a place like this.
Yeah, but I can't figure out
why the school would need
a hidden room like this
in the first place.
It looks like a whole
bunch of Storm Riders
are having a big meeting.
‐I wonder why.
‐That's great.
I bet they're all
forming some big mob
so they can come
kick our asses.
Well, at least that
saves us the trouble
of going after them.
They can come and get it.
(laughing)
Hey, what's going on?
I bet Buccha just
bumped into some button
he wasn't supposed to.
Always blame the fat guy.
That lightning.
(clanging)
♪
Mm‐mm.
‐Hey, it's that kid.
‐Should I know him?
Oh, yeah, Ikki's never seen
him because he passed out.
That's Nue, the Black Crow,
the Thunder King
of the Rising Road.
Hm.
Oh, great, now we got
kings coming after us.
So what's this about, huh?
♪
(shouting)
Well, just as you requested,
the entire mega storm
has gathered here
for your meeting.
There's no doubt in my mind.
The strength of his
wings will carry us all.
I have a message from
the Swallow to the Crow.
I guess you could call it
a love letter really.
From Simca, huh?
Now might be a good
time to announce
that we're planning
to incorporate
Kogarasumaru into the team.
You've got it wrong.
This isn't about making
Ikki part of our team.
Actually...
It's the other way around.
His team isn't joining us.
We're joining them.
What?
♪
I was against it, but there
wasn't much I could do.
Our team consists of 360
of the best riders in Japan
including four kings.
Simca's taken all these
riders and their teams
under her wing for
only one purpose:
Bring down Trophaeum.
Mega storm is the
strongest team in the world,
so be honored, Ikki Minami.
Tonight...
...we bow to you.
Bow to me?
No!
(cheering)
Fly high, Genesis!
Our time has come!
(wind whooshing)
(panting)
Hey, Ringo, what's going on?
What do I do?
There has to be some
way to stop this.
(dog barking)
Oh, excuse me.
Please forgive the
sudden intrusion,
but I am the Aeon Clock,
Yasuyoshi Sano.
Ah, you need not worry.
I have no interest in
gazing upon your shapely ass.
So if you don't mind,
I'll be coming in.
And you'll die!
Bastard!
My, you're a violent
gorilla woman.
I'm home!
♪
Welcome home, Master Ikki,
it's good to see you.
As was requested
by the Swallow,
I will serve as your
personal assistant
from this day forth.
What?
You've been chosen.
You're our new king.
I never agreed
to any of this.
‐I still...
‐Hey!
It's been a while, kid.
I heard you
really hit it big.
Huh?
Who are these people?
What's going on here?
What makes these
assholes think
they can just barge
in here without asking?
(indistinct chattering)
♪
‐Mitsuru.
‐Oh, Ikki.
So, what are you doing now?
We should ride
together sometime.
Sounds good.
Thing is I'm kind of busy
building my own
team right now.
I know I'm not good enough
to fill Akira's shoes yet,
but, someday, I'd like to
form a Storm Rider team
strong enough to have
the same kind of impact
that Behemoth used to.
I hear ya.
Hey, do you think this
Genesis thing is for real?
I mean, seriously, what the
hell are we supposed to do
with, like, 350 new members?
If Simca's really put
Genesis into motion,
then I guess that'll
probably happen.
Geez, I need a drink.
Hm?
Hey, that's funny.
Where the hell did Ringo go?
♪
What should I do?
I feel like everything is
slipping through my fingers.
I can't ask Ikki
to stop riding,
but if he teams up
with Genesis,
then he and I will be...
(whooshing)
All you have to do is say
yes and it will be done.
Just one word,
and the greatest power
in the world of ATs will be
in the palm of your hand.
I don't know,
that's nice and all,
but I just can't see myself
riding with a bunch of
people I've never met.
I mean...
You know, I'm glad Simca
thinks I'm up to this, but I‐‐
How's this?
If I gather everyone
for you to meet,
would you feel better
about riding with them?
(yawning)
Yeah, sure, gather whatever.
Hm.
I call for an
emergency assembly!
The new leader of
Genesis, Ikki Minami,
demands all members
report to his residence.
Huh?
No, it can't be.
Our flesh, our blood,
our bones, and our souls
shall come
together in harmony.
Brave soldiers
who rain death
upon the tower of
dreams, come forth!
The enemy's corpses shall pile
to the gates of
heaven itself!
(gasping)
♪
Uh, are all of them‐‐
Should you see fit,
they are yours to command.
You have said that your
wings have the strength
to carry our dreams to
the heavens themselves.
I believe in those
words of yours.
Now I ask that you
lend us those wings,
and pave the road
to a new era,
a new era of Genesis.
You are our Sky King.
(clattering)
(heart beating)
♪
(whimpering)
♪ The truth ♪
♪ The truth shall
set you free ♪
♪
♪ Truth ♪
♪ The truth ♪
♪ The truth, the truth
shall set you free ♪
♪
Is that some kind of trick
or are there
really eight of you?
Those guys win their battles
by sacrificing
their teammates.
But you have a
better plan, right?
‐Ikki!
‐Of course.
I'll just jump off of Kazu's
head and win the match.
He can't swim, but
I'm sure his body
will wash up somewhere.
Are you nuts?
How is that better?
Next time on Air Gear,
a war of sacrifice,
rivals in battle.
And rivals in love.
Huh?
Shit.