♪
The East Side Gunz
are a big, fat joke.
During the day's the only
time you can act tough.
Am I right or what?
What the hell are
you saying, huh?
She's saying you guys
only rule this place
during the day.
There's another gang
that takes control at night.
Four wheel drive
Storm Riders.
They're known as the Yaooo.
Kings of the Night.
Kings of the Night?
♪
Wh‐‐what the hell is it?
Construction?
(rumbling)
♪
(whimper)
Uh, a tank?
Oh, crap.
♪
(growling)
That's him.
(groans)
♪
Buccha.
Run!
♪
This school
is my territory.
If you cocky little turds
have the balls to wear
ATs here at night,
then you're begging
for a fight!
(laughs)
♪
Damn it.
I had no idea Fatty
was the Yaooo leader.
Wait, I can't run
with these things on.
I'm too slow!
This way.
(shouts)
♪
What are we gonna do?
I think I gotta call Ikki.
No way.
We can do this.
We have to show Ikki
that we can handle
things on our own.
Five, six, seven, eight.
Show time!
♪
(whimper)
(punch)
♪
(shouting)
(cackling)
♪
(groans)
Let me go!
All right, you little
shit‐for‐brains.
Who's the real ruler
of this school?
Don't make me laugh.
Because everyone
knows the Gunz‐‐
Gunz, you're a bunch of wusses.
I let you play your
games during the day,
but you wear
your ATs at night,
then you better know
who rules the school.
You're a lightweight.
Huh?
You can't hurt me.
You're nothing
but a bunch of hot air.
Bloated piece of crap.
Just wait.
I'm gonna stomp that
overblown belly of yours
and bust it wide open.
(sighs)
(grunts)
AT attack, Hell Strike.
Sorry, but the only
thing getting stomped
around here is your throat.
♪
Ikki, I'm sorry.
I guess I really can't
be like you after all.
Wait.
♪
(panting)
Even if I can't...
Even if I can't!
♪
(shouting)
Ikki!
(dialing)
(phone ringing)
(snoring)
Wake up, Ikki.
Your cell phone's ringing.
Huh?
♪
(munching)
This isn't like you.
‐Huh?
‐The way you're eating
is sloppy.
Almost desperate.
Oh, it's you, Spitfire.
You startled me.
My jaw's a little
sore, that's all.
Not really your
style, Buccha.
I thought you let
the Gunz take the heat
from the cops while
you ran things
from the shadows.
Yeah, well...
Does that Little Crow
put a fright in you?
Is that it?
Are you kidding?
Ikki's nothing
but a rookie.
Really?
That's not what
a swallow I know told me.
She said he has
powerful wings.
I'm the one who's gonna fly.
I'm the one who's
gonna rise to the top!
Just look at all these
emblems I've earned!
Brag all you want, mate,
but no matter how many
F‐Class emblems you get,
you'll never rise
above E rank.
I can't wait to see
Ikki in action.
I think it should be
quite a good show.
Ta‐ta.
♪
(growls)
I'm the one
going to the top.
(panting)
(door squeaks)
Oh, Ikki!
Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
Thanks for calling me.
How are they?
Uh, well, they
just fell asleep.
Gotcha.
Ikki!
I need to talk to you.
All right?
All right, later.
Are you sure
that telling Ikki
about the Yaooo
is a good idea?
I want to.
But what if he ends
up like the others
and the Yaooo just get worse?
I don't know!
(sirens wail)
After seeing them
fight like that,
protecting the school,
I don't...
know what to do.
Kazu, Onigiri.
I'm sorry, Ikki.
We should've told you
guys about the Yaooo sooner.
The problem is,
they're always
threatening students
like us that stay late
after school.
They're nothing but trash.
Every last one of them.
They're nothing but trash!
All right!
Listen up, guys.
Today we're gonna talk about
Fleming's Left Hand Rule!
Don't you think
I look like a rapper?
Don't ya?
♪
(shrieks)
He didn't like the joke.
I was afraid they
wouldn't like the joke.
I'm such a terrible teacher.
I'm going to get
fired, aren't I?
I know, I know
I'm a stupid hoe
and I deserve to be slapped.
Just do it.
Slap me, come on!
Well, let's move on, shall we?
♪
Ikki, are you all right?
You're still working
on that, huh?
Why don't you get
Ume to help you.
She can probably finish
it in two or three hours.
Sorry, I can't.
I have to finish this
thing by myself, all right?
Otherwise there's no point.
I see.
Guess you're right.
‐Hey, look.
‐Hmm?
This should
help you out.
It's called
a Trick Pass.
♪
Trick Pass?
Yeah, it's like a map.
Parts Wars are official
competitions, you know?
If you look, you can find
records of past battles.
This Trick Pass is
of the Yaooo's territory.
Check it out.
Looks familiar, right?
♪
Oh, I see,
this is our school.
Depending on what
class you're in,
you have different
kinds of Parts Wars.
The event for F‐Class is Dash.
It's just like a race.
That's the level you're at.
Buccha's E‐Class,
so he does Hurdles.
Hurdles, huh?
♪
Just think of it like
an obstacle course.
In this case,
the school buildings
are the hurdles,
and you're racing
from one end to the other.
Since the challenger
is forced to fight
on their opponent's territory,
they're usually
at a disadvantage
in Parts Wars.
Even if you know your
way around the school,
you probably don't
know the exact locations
of all the handrails,
pipes, and other things
you can grind on.
It might be hard for you
to find a road to take.
So, are you still
gonna go for it?
♪
I can see the way.
So, you came?
Yeah.
I saw you put that
crap on our emblem,
but I thought you
were gonna wuss out.
So, what you gonna
bet, Little Crow?
Not those
busted up ATs, I hope.
I'm gonna make you
eat those words!
These ATs carry the pride
of the East Side Gunz.
Kazu's and Onigiri and mine.
♪
Let's do this, Fatty Buccha.
(growls)
Screw the AT parts.
I want your emblem.
♪
All right.
This is an E‐Class Parts War.
Hurdles, the course
is our school
in case you didn't
already know.
It's from here to
the Nanomi Akindro
statue behind
the north building.
(military stepping)
♪
I'm gonna make pork rinds
out of that fat ass of yours.
Bon appetite.
And maybe I'll turn
that crow of yours
into a late night snack.
(crow squawks)
‐Five.
‐Six.
‐Seven.
‐Eight.
Go!
♪
So the Little Crow's
trying to make his way
to the top, aye?
How far do you
think he'll go?
The road of
Tropaeum is a long one.
♪
All right, first hurdle.
The South Hall.
This is a rare treat.
I didn't think you'd
grace us with your presence.
I'm not here
to watch the match.
I was hoping to take
you on a midnight stroll.
Not that again!
Yo, yo, yo.
Backspin Wall Ride 360.
Do that grab,
add a fake spin.
Accelerator,
Buccha Special 1440.
Don't tell me Simca
put you up to the this
to keep an eye on Ikki.
It's my own reconnaissance.
I'm curious to see if
he can actually turn
a one percent chance
into a victory.
That's not something you
get to see every day.
(groans)
Ha‐ha!
Where the hell is he?
(glass breaks)
(groans)
You punk!
What the hell kind
of move was that?
Ikki's not experienced
enough to climb
a building yet.
At this point,
he can only go
in a straight line.
(groans)
♪
Damn it.
He's too fast!
Don't tell me you've
underestimated me.
Stop screwing around
and show me what you
can really do!
No, he's not fast.
I'm just too slow!
I'm so freakin' slow
that I'm getting beat
by a fat ass!
So, he's bad at running,
and he can't jump at all.
At this point,
the only way
he can win is if he
outsmarts his opponent.
Now it's just a matter
of how well he memorized
the map of the school.
Take this!
(alarm bell rings)
(groans)
See you later, piggy.
(shrieks)
♪
That was cool, man.
So, tell me, Rookie,
just what have you
got cooked up next?
One full course of
ass whooping on the way.
Shit!
He really is
clueless, isn't he?
I'm sure he's blissfully
ignorant of the fact
that an F‐ranked
rookie like himself
has less than a one
percent chance of taking out
an advanced class
racer in a Parts War.
Yeah, you're right.
Ikki still doesn't
really know anything.
But because of that,
he'll keep fighting.
Let's see how you like
my super floor wax
danger fake technique.
(shouts)
(liquid splashes)
(growls)
Ahh!
It's all over then.
♪
You don't have
to do this anymore.
Just give up, punk.
I know what you can do,
and it's not
enough to win.
Yeah?
That's a load of crap.
It's not over till
the fat man sings!
(growls)
Not this again!
I may not beat
you with ATs,
but I can still
kick your ass,
even if I have
to resort to this.
I can't lose!
(growls)
Spinning Wallride
Overbank 1800 degree
Buccha Special!
Clever.
He's using the rotational
power of his arms to propel
himself up the side
of the building.
I'd wager he's the only
rider in E‐Class who can
pull off a technique like that.
Now it looks like he's
intentionally taking
the long way
around the building.
He knows that even
with the extra time,
he'll still be able
to maintain a lead.
(gasps)
Hey, wait a second.
Don't ignore me, fatty,
'cause we're not through.
♪
What the hell?
It's like he
feels sorry for me.
Like he's looking down on me.
It‐‐it's just
like back then.
♪
It's the same thing.
This isn't over.
I haven't lost yet.
♪
Don't underestimate me!
Ikki, don't do it!
♪
There's no way.
He won't make it.
Crap!
♪
Ikki, no!
(wind blowing)
(chuckling)
You two?
♪
An Upper Soul.
How can he do
something like that?
(shouts)
♪
These ATs carry
the pride of
the East Side Gunz.
Kazu's and Onigiri's and mine.
♪
Huh?
(groans)
♪
All right!
Impossible.
Planning that from
the start is one thing,
but to be able
to pull it off
last minute is just...
♪
Mighty wings, aye?
Now I get what you mean.
Ikki?
(groans)
That was just
beginner's luck!
No.
I could see it in my head.
The Trick Pass told me
that there was a pole there.
Huh?
♪
He knows the pass.
Is he using all‐around
traction wheels to stick
to the wall?
His ATs were made
by combining parts
from Kazu's
and Onigiri's.
As a result,
the front and rear wheels
are slightly different.
I'm sure he wasn't
thinking of this
when he made them,
but since each of the wheels
has a different rotation,
it ends up having
the same effect
as all‐around
traction wheels.
(groaning)
♪
Kazu, Onigiri...
I really owe you one.
If you didn't lend
me a hand back there,
this battle
would've been over.
When we get back...
I'll treat you to
some ramen, all right?!
♪
That's it.
I can see the goal.
Let me show you why
I picked this as the goal.
I outsmarted you, Crow Boy.
You fell right
into my trap.
Huh?
Take a look at the
opening of the goal.
It's exactly my size.
As long as I get
in there first,
you won't be able
to get around me.
It's called strategy, punk!
Take a look at it yourself.
You can't even squeeze
one ass cheek in there.
(chuckles)
Huh?
(laughing)
(groans)
♪
You've gotta be kidding me!
I guess you didn't know
that I could redistribute
my body mass?
Too bad, bird brain.
♪
It's not over yet!
Watch out, Spitfire.
What do you think
you're doing
showing up out of nowhere
and torching the place?
You're gonna hurt someone!
It's because he has
the power of the Flame Road.
He's ranked A‐Class in
the Parts War, you know.
Huh, A‐Class?
Flame Road?
What do you mean?
C'mon, Ikki,
you mean you don't
know about the eight
roads and the eight kings?
Wait, what's going on?
It's like my body
is moving on its own.
Next time on Air Gear,
my blazing instinct
and my blazing heart.
♪