♪
(helicopter droning)
All right, fill me in.
The main unit's
assembled at point zero.
All personnel
are standing by.
(droning)
Behemoth, huh?
This'll be our first
big catch in a while.
(droning)
♪
(grunting)
Don't fuck with me,
you piece of shit!
♪
Ultimate technique.
Tornado hammer!
Look, they're holding hands.
I mean, that punch
can shatter concrete
and he blocked it
with one hand!
Calm down, Mitsuro, all right?
That's enough.
Have you forgotten
what I taught you?
The first to lose his cool is
the first to lose the fight.
Akira.
Was that some kind of
trick with your hand?
The gloves, maybe?
Hm.
You know, it's funny,
but I guess we've never met
face to face before,
but I've heard all
about you from Simca.
Simca, huh?
Oh, that's cool.
So I guess you two
are friends, huh?
(zapping)
(grunting)
You cocky punk.
Ah!
Hm.
(shouts)
I don't care how many
of you there are.
I'll send you all back to the
garbage heap you came from.
(shouting)
Ikki!
No, this is too
terrible to watch,
and yet I can't
tear my eyes away.
(laughing)
I can't believe
he fell for that.
You dumbass, do you even
know what you're doing?
Hey, guys, shh, shh.
Damn, if they hadn't
blown my cover,
I would've drop‐kicked you
in the back of the head.
So how do you like
my new technique?
I call it "body double."
♪
(shouting)
Now you're gonna pay!
(grunting)
No way.
(chuckles)
You may have blocked
his punch with one hand,
but I did it without
using a single finger.
I'd say that
makes me the winner.
(rumbling)
Cut the bullshit and
use your ATs, dammit!
This is about to get serious.
(roaring)
His aura is so strong
you can almost feel it.
I see why they
call him Behemoth.
In the age of gods, humans,
beasts, fish, and plants
all lived together
in the same place.
But that world couldn't last.
The fish ate the plants,
the birds ate the fish,
the beasts ate the birds.
So the gods said
to the beasts,
"Scatter to the fields.
The birds will
take to the sky
and the fish to the sea."
Mayan legend.
Akira told me that story
just after we met.
I remember that day in the
park as if it were yesterday.
Hold on a second,
is this story gonna be long?
'Cause I kind of need to
change clothes right now.
That was before
he formed Behemoth
and became the
King of Beasts.
Not a flashback.
(birds chirping)
(birds cooing)
So you like birds, huh?
You must be Simca.
Well, Spitfire already
told me about the plan.
(gasping)
I like coming to this park
when the doves are molting.
Their new feathers
are easy to break
and have thick
veins inside them.
Take a look.
If they try to fly
with broken wings,
then they force
out the blood
and it rains from the sky.
I'll take the job.
It's the duty of
beasts like me
to break the wings
of the little birds
that think they can
soar into C‐class.
You know something?
I really hate birds.
(engine revving)
They're always looking down
on me from up in the sky.
But once I break their wings,
they just writhe
on the ground
like pathetic little worms.
This is his stage.
This is where the gods have
willed him to do battle.
But no matter how
long his Fangs are,
they still can't
reach the sky.
(grunting)
♪
Wow, our spur‐of‐the‐moment
combo attack actually
worked pretty well.
I guess that proves
once and for all
that I'm the greatest genius
the world has ever known.
Well, I have to admit
that wasn't bad.
♪
(heavy breathing)
You don't have
to take that crap!
Show him what the
Fang King is made of.
Now he has to face his
greatest weakness, the sky.
♪
(exploding)
Now, that's more like it!
Watch out, Akira!
It's a trap!
Ah!
Wonder how many times
he'll fall for that.
(smacking)
Looks like this is turning
into a pretty one‐sided match.
Oh!
Ohh!
Oh, man, this is for real?
Are we really gonna
win this thing?
Now that the Crow has
brought the sky to the Cube,
his combination
attack is making
minced meat out of Akira!
I hate to say it, but it
looks like these rookies
are roasting up some
Behemoth for dinner.
Come on, Crow!
We've got the edge now!
Let's finish him in one shot.
(gasping)
♪
(grunting)
What the hell do you think
you're doing, Akira?
You have our pride
on your back!
The emblems of over
a thousand Behemoths
are riding on you.
Don't cower on the ground
like some kind of
pathetic rodent!
♪
(gasping)
(yells)
Crow, attack from
the right side!
Who said you could
tell me what to do?
Whoa!
‐That's bull‐‐
‐Shit, brilliant.
They don't call him
the King of Beasts
for nothing, after all.
(whooshing)
Spank me silly!
What the hell's
going on in there?
Ah!
(whirring)
(whooshing)
Fuck.
You were right.
This is turning into
a one‐sided match.
Told ya.
I am the Fang,
the king of destruction
who tears through
everything in his path.
Bloody armor, come forth!
(groaning)
♪
(gasping)
Can you hear it?
The Regalia is howling.
♪
(screaming)
Come on.
Ohh!
‐Ahh!
‐Ohh!
Ahh!
The great beast
has descended!
And I gotta tell ya,
this is the first time
I've ever seen Akira
break out the Fang Regalia!
Ah!
Son of a bitch!
Hey, Crow, you all right?
Hell yeah!
That's great.
That's so cool that
he, like, transformed!
Mine don't do that!
I want a pair like yours!
Come on, man,
hook a brother up.
♪
Ha, but I guess you won't
hand 'em over for free, right?
That's fine.
I'll just take them.
I guess you
haven't noticed yet,
but your sky is gone
and your wings
are broken, Crow.
The cage is
closed once again.
From now on, you're
trapped in a world of beasts.
♪
It's hard to say exactly
what Ikki's up against.
Even though I inherited
Rika's position
as one of the eight kings,
I still don't
know all that much
about all the different
Regalia out there.
Judging by Akira's attacks,
it's probably
not a single part,
but an entire
system of operation.
It seems to collect inertia
from braking and landing,
then retransmit it as
a kind of energy wave.
If you look at it that way,
it makes sense that
Akira can't fly very well.
Considering that he's got
such a complex mechanism
in such a tiny wheel space,
it's no wonder that he has
to sacrifice other functions.
He's thrown them away.
In exchange for Fangs,
he's given up his wings.
(shouting)
This is starting to get ugly.
I should be all right,
but at this rate,
I'm afraid shark boy
isn't gonna be able
to hold out much longer.
♪
Could it be‐‐above us?
(grunting)
Didn't I tell you?
♪
You're trapped in my cage.
You can't escape.
This is my world now.
There is no sky.
Oh, you got told!
Now all that's left is
for these birdbrains
to have their
heads chopped off
like my grandma's chickens.
Son of a bitch.
What do we have to do
to beat that thing?
Look, he always speeds up
before he uses his
technique, right?
Yeah, so what?
Those giant Fang
attacks are created
from the energy
made when he brakes,
meaning the longer
and faster he rides,
the bigger and more
powerful his attacks become.
So if we stick to him,
we can stop him
from picking up speed
and he won't be able to
use his Fang technique.
Well, why the hell didn't
you tell me that sooner,
friggin' dumb‐‐oh!
You're the dumbass, dumbass!
They make a good team.
You get the Fang
from far away,
but if you move in close,
you get the hammer.
The fight turned out just
how Spitfire said it would.
It looks like I can't let
my guard down around him.
Welcome back.
You don't look very cheery.
It's not a bad match, I guess,
considering Ikki made Akira
break out the Fang Regalia.
♪
But maybe that's the problem.
Akira just doesn't seem to be
enjoying himself tonight.
If he's not having fun,
it's just boring.
The stronger the opponent,
the more interesting that
makes the battle, right?
Normally, when a rider goes
all out, he's so excited
it's like he has lightning
coursing through his veins.
At least that's how
it's supposed to be.
♪
Akira's strength is
different than Ikki's.
(beep)
He had to sacrifice a lot
more than just his wings
to get those Fangs.
(beep)
♪
He didn't just lose
his love of fighting.
He lost the only
friend he's ever had.
These bastards are
illegal immigrants
and AT smugglers.
Fire on sight.
(honking)
(guns firing)
Damn.
Don't let them
get away, Akira.
You hear that,
don't fuck this up.
Who the hell do you
think you're talking to?
(beeping)
(whooshing)
Agh!
Looks like they're
wrapping up down there.
(gasping)
Huh?
Not good!
He's gonna try to take
that girl hostage.
Ah!
♪
(heavy breathing)
Are you all right?
I'm sorry you
had to see that,
but I was afraid he
was going to hurt you.
Big brother!
Please, hold on!
Don't die.
I‐‐I thought he was
going to take you hostage.
He looked like
he was smuggling
something in that box.
(chirping)
(gasping)
Why, my brother didn't
want to hurt anyone.
That was just a present!
Today is my birthday.
My leg doesn't work,
so he got me
something that could fly.
♪
I'm sorry.
I really am.
It's all right.
He managed to pull through,
and even though
he was my brother,
he's still a criminal.
Now, he's been
sent back home,
but that's all behind me.
I'm not mad.
Actually, I want to
thank you for what you did.
Thank me?
But why, I just‐‐
Because with my
leg the way it is,
I've always dreamt of flying.
I think it's
wonderful that ATs
can make that
dream come true.
You're able to use your
ATs to help fight crime.
Really, I think that's great.
It's, uh, nothing really.
♪
Fuck.
(engine puttering)
♪
(bird chirping)
Here you go, it's dinnertime.
Open wide.
What happened?
Where are its wings?
Oh, I chopped them off.
If it had wings,
it would fly away.
Now I don't have to worry
about it leaving me behind.
♪
(engine puttering)
(cheering)
♪
Believe it or not,
someone has challenged
Agito for his Regalia!
Will this be the end of
the Fang King's reign?
Let's see who he's up against.
♪
Ren!
Just what the
hell's going on?
I don't understand.
Don't you try to stop me.
I am the one who set this up.
Agito just accepted
my challenge.
Dumbass, why don't you try
thinking with your brain
instead of your
balls for once?
Don't you see,
she's been using you
just to get at
the Fang Regalia.
(gasping)
When my brother came here,
he was an underground
AT parts broker.
Before he got deported,
he was trying to steal
the Fang Regalia for
one of his clients.
Now he's receiving threats
from other smugglers.
I'm afraid he's
in over his head.
That's why I'm here.
I need the Fang Regalia
to save my brother's life.
I'm sorry.
I was using you to find
out Agito's weak point.
Please forgive me,
I had no choice.
Straight from
the horse's mouth.
I bet you feel pretty
stupid right now.
I'm going to fly!
You'll see!
I'll win, and I'll
fly all the way home.
Just wait.
♪
Sometimes,
on days like these,
I feel like even I can fly,
even if only for a moment.
♪
Yeah.
(swooshing)
It hurts when I
get sand in there.
I can't run fast enough to
keep up with you anymore.
(sighing)
They say anyone can fly
if they try hard enough,
but that's not true.
Birds that fly
with broken wings
will fall to their deaths.
But if I can pretend to
fly for a little while,
at least I won't
be left behind.
I'm sorry.
♪
You don't have to fly.
Akira.
If you have to cry until
there are no more tears,
if you have to carry
feathers drenched in blood,
if you have to sacrifice
yourself to reach the sky,
then you don't have to fly,
not in a sky like that.
I promise I'll never fly
away and leave you behind.
I'll stay with you
inside this cage.
Is this really what you want?
Is this what it's come to?
♪
Akira!
I'm taking the Regalia.
You hear me?
(grunting)
(clinking)
(cheering)
♪
If I were her, I would've
done the same thing.
After what he's been through,
I'm sure Akira is
quite proud of the fact
that he can't fly.
But, now, that pride
has turned to hate.
All he cares about
is clipping the wings
of those who fly above him.
(cheering)
That was amazing, Akira.
You really are the king.
(gasping)
♪
The strain from
using the Fang attack
is tearing apart the
muscles on his legs.
Akira?
I'll finish this soon.
Don't worry.
Agito?
I'm starting to get
sick of these guys.
Let's finish this.
This is the final trick.
(shouting)
♪
♪ The truth ♪
♪ The truth shall
set you free ♪
♪
♪ Truth ♪
♪ The truth ♪
♪ The truth, the truth
shall set you free ♪
♪
Akira and Agito are really
starting to let loose.
Their two Fangs are colliding.
But in the midst of
all these attacks,
I feel like their hearts
are being wounded too.
Agito, the wind
is still blowing.
The God of Wind hasn't turned
his back on us just yet.
Let me ride your Fang!
This is the Wing Road.
Ikki's spreading his wings!
Next time on Air Gear,
the Behemoth and
the Great White Shark
face off one last time,
and there can only be
one King of the Beasts!
♪