Marvelous Entertainment.
♪
All right,
now it's your turn.
Got it!
I can do this.
I'm not gonna
give up my ATs!
(yells)
(screams)
♪
What the hell am I
doing on the ground?
I gotta focus.
Otherwise she'll kick my ass
before I can even fight.
♪
From now on, I'm
doing this for real.
♪
(bell ringing)
I'll show you
what I'm made of!
♪
(smacking)
This is pathetic.
I wanted to believe
this kid was something.
It looks like
those rumors about him
were all lies.
I can do this!
He's just a punk
who's barely average,
let alone Sky King material.
Dammit.
Just wait.
I expected more from you.
♪
I'm not gonna
give up ATs.
You hear me, Rika?
This isn't over.
I can still fight,
I can do this!
Well, I hate to say it,
but it looks like
this is about over.
You're right, I don't
think Rika's Sonia Road
is gonna hold out much longer.
Huh?
I doubt he planned
this from the start,
but Ikki's actually
playing to his strengths.
I know it's not pretty,
but this might
be the only way
to beat the Sonia Road.
(bell ringing)
♪
(yells)
What?
I see, that's the
Sonia Road, all right.
It may be powerful,
but it takes a toll
on the rider.
Since she ain't
got ATs or Regalia,
it's even worse.
If she keeps
using it like this,
her body's gonna
start to break down.
Kid looked like
he was screwing up,
but bit by bit
he's cutting his way
through her defense.
He may be taking
a beating out there,
but it looks like
his persistence
is finally starting
to pay off.
♪
Hi‐ya!
Oh, man, that's bad.
Ugh!
(scream)
You know, in the
language of flowers,
the rose symbolizes
love and devotion.
And when that
love is strong
when it has
something to protect,
there's no limit
to the strength
of the Sonia Road.
Why...why can't you
understand, Ikki?
Why can't you understand
that these thorns
are here to protect you?
♪
I'm doing this for you, Ikki.
I'm fighting to protect you.
♪
Don't do this.
He's no match for her.
No matter how much
ATs mean to him,
he can't understand her pain.
♪
(lightning cracking)
Yeah, whatever.
That's just like you.
I've heard all that before.
In a way it's nice
staying in a cage.
There's nothing
to worry about.
There's food to eat and
you're safe from the world.
♪
But you know what?
I'm not gonna let you
lock me away, Rika.
Because I'd rather
be free then safe.
(wings flapping)
♪
I don't give a damn
what anyone says.
I won't stop riding
no matter what.
(thunder booming)
I'm gonna take
that cage of yours
and tear it down,
along with your road.
You're gonna tear
down my road, huh?
Those are big words, Crow.
But even if you broke
free of your cage,
how far do you think those
overblown wings of yours
are gonna take you?
(thunder booming)
♪
(exclaims)
She can't keep
this up much longer.
She's being eaten alive
by her own road.
I guess in a way
it's the opposite
of the Fang Road.
Instead of carving its mark
on other people's bodies,
it poisons the rider
with their own thorns.
That's how far
she's willing to go.
♪
The rain's picking up.
Yeah, no kidding.
If I had known
this was gonna happen,
I would have brought some
wheels with better grips.
(wind howling)
Look at that, the wind's
starting to change.
It's too early
to give up now.
All right, kid, get ready
to ride the storm.
♪
Catch!
It's mine, bitch!
♪
Nice interception, wow!
Ikki, you little punk,
that hurt.
Hey, dog, catch!
(barking)
♪
(yells)
(laughing)
♪
This is it, you're mine,
I've got you now!
Even I can't predict
where the disk is going
in a storm like this.
♪
He says he doesn't like
being kept in a cage, huh?
What does he expect me to do?
I'm his guardian,
that's my job.
Back then, all I did
was sit back and watch.
I let Sora do
whatever he wanted
without thinking
of the consequences.
If only I had
held on tighter.
If only I had chained
him down with my thorns.
Even a little, then none
of that would have happened.
I won't let that
happen again!
♪
That's enough, Rika,
it's time for you to let go.
This isn't like before.
His dream isn't like the
nightmare from back then!
Can't you feel it?
There's a new wind blowing,
and it's already
building into a storm.
Ha!
♪
No, Ikki,
I won't let you go!
(thunder crashing)
(gasp)
It's like he
can't even see me.
(thunder crashing)
(wind howling)
This is it.
After all this, I'm
going to lose to a kid
who only started
riding two months ago.
He really is
loved by the wind.
♪
But I've known that
from the beginning.
I've been hiding
from the truth.
But deep down, I know that
we're all born with wings.
If only I had
a little courage.
spread my own wings.
I would have been able
to fly back then, too.
But I didn't.
I never flew.
Not even once.
Because back then,
I didn't have a wind
like this to carry me.
♪
What'd I tell you?
If only I were
wearing the Regalia
or at least my ATs.
♪
No, I can't say that.
It was my choice.
I was the one who decided
never to wear ATs again.
Looks like her legs
are giving out on her
and she's gonna bet it all
on one last faceoff.
♪
All right, Ikki,
you want to play rough?
If you won't give up,
then I'm not gonna
give up either.
This is it.
(water splashing)
♪
(thunder booming)
God, I always wondered
why you were so unfair.
I never could understand
why let us suffer so much.
While I sat there
on the ground
watching people around me
sail beyond my reach,
I wondered why some
of us were given wings
and others were forced
to stay behind.
But now I know
I was wrong.
I see that we're all
born with wings to fly.
Some of us just don't
think to use them.
Or worse, believe
we can do it.
But now, Ikki's freed
me from that cage.
While I was in the
darkness I never noticed,
but he was already
soaring above the clouds.
♪
Ringo, I haven't had meat
in almost three years!
Let me eat, let me eat,
let me eat my victory meat!
Why hello there, Mr. Meat.
What's that?
You want me to eat you?
Great‐‐and it looks
like Agito's missing, too.
So we can't let his dinner
go to waste, now can we?
Try showing some
self control for once.
First he wastes our time
with that stupid fight
and now he eats
all our smoked meat.
Children can be
such a burden.
Oh, this meat is so good.
Don't talk with
your mouth full, Ikki.
Anyway, I lost,
so I'll keep my word.
From now on,
I won't say anything
about you riding ATs.
But I have to admit,
I didn't think a
snot‐nosed brat like you
could actually beat me.
I'll be cheering
for you from now on,
so you better
not let me down.
(sinister laugh)
You finally
recognize my genius.
It was only
a matter of time.
I guess I should
give you a reward
as a token
of my admiration.
After all, since
you won a Parts War,
you should get
some parts, right?
I have some old
equipment I used to wear
back when I
was still riding.
Would you like to use it?
What, parts?
Gimme, gimme, gimme.
♪
Uh, what's this?
They're weights and
you can't take them off
no matter what.
'Cause if you do,
then I'll kill you dead!
Don't give me that crap,
you freakin' cow!
How do you like it
when I grab your boobs?
(yells)
Too slow, too slow.
‐Oops.
‐These things are heavy!
They're not that bad,
it's only 60 pounds, moron.
And this here
is the only key.
Meow...mm!
(yells)
You've got to be kidding me.
This isn't funny.
Hey, cat, come back here!
Come on, kitty, please!
Oh, Ikki.
(wind blowing)
Nice breeze we got today.
(bell chiming)
Listen, Stone,
Cold, Stunner,
you guys wait here
while I pick up
some dinner, all right?
(barking)
They always put the
good ones on the top shelf.
Thank you.
♪
You know, it ain't like
I couldn't reach it
if I wanted to.
I just don't
like jumping
in the middle
of the store.
It freaks people out,
that's all.
♪
I know, but I'm
sure it must be
pretty hard
on you sometimes.
I always worry
you're not eating right.
So if you don't mind,
maybe sometime I can
come by and cook for you.
I mean, if...
♪
Do whatever you want.
(wings flapping)
Don't worry, from now on
I'll be your wings, okay?
♪
You're silly.
The sky feels so close,
I could almost
reach out and kiss it.
(engine roaring)
♪
Ikki, what do you think,
did we get it right?
Dude, you guys
can't spell for crap!
You should go
back to grade school.
Why do I even bother?
♪
Ginger ale,
coffee with milk.
Plum flavored seaweed tea.
Chestnut juice.
All right, that should be
good for starters, anyway.
Kazu.
Raw egg.
(evil laughter)
Spicy barbecue sauce.
Holy crap, that one
crosses the line.
He's gonna kill us dead!
He's enjoying this, too.
Chipotle mayonnaise.
Oyster sauce.
Fish sauce.
Habanero pepper sauce!
I think I'm gonna puke.
Yeah, me too.
I thought they were
gonna be training today
so what the hell
is this crap?
(shouting)
You guys know
the deal, right?
Last one to the finish line
has to guzzle down
the Kogarasumaru
suicide sauce in one gulp!
No turning back!
Yeah, that's cool, but
I think it's pretty obvious
who's gonna be drinking it.
What's going on?
How the hell is
Onigiri faster than me?
Huh, silly fool,
I'm not slow,
I just need
the right motivation.
Here I come.
♪
This is great, their times
are getting better and better
with every race.
Look at that,
Kazu's on fire.
Must be because he's
thinking of his sweetie.
I think they're afraid
of drinking that juice,
but that's just me.
No!
♪
(laughing)
Drink it down!
Well, it's
definitely working.
In no time flat,
Kazu's taken his speed
way beyond death class.
That's nice and all,
but what are you gonna do
with Captain Craptastic?
(moaning)
He's got zero technique
and his style
looks like shit.
And you know,
if he's the leader
then why the hell's
his ass dragging
like a dog with worms?
But what really
pisses me off
is that some
moron out there
decided that that
punk has what it takes
to be the next Sky King.
Oh, I guess
you didn't hear.
Ikki's at a big disadvantage
because Rika's
forcing him to wear
these 60‐pound
handicap weights.
I'm sure he'd be much better
if he took them off.
All right, now
for the second round
we can add a little
smoked meat for flavor.
Man, he's hard core.
Hey, Agito, I didn't
know you were up.
Don't just stand there,
come over here
and join us.
Are you kidding me?
You really think
I want to screw around
with worms like you?
Why not, this
stuff is only fun
if you have
a lot of friends.
Yeah, we're a team.
You can take
your team and suck it.
Uh, come on, man,
we're buddies, right?
Come play with us.
Rawk, boytoy, rawk!
Dammit, cut that out, get
your finger out of there!
♪
Damn, little bastard ran away.
Hey, Ikki, I've been
hearing some weird rumors
about the riders
around here.
Seems like all the
teams of the east side
have been totally disbanding
without any kind of
explanation or anything.
(evil laughter)
I don't blame them, I mean
with a genius like me around,
they must have all gotten
scared and given up.
Yeah, that's it.
Wait, what do you mean?
Did they get wiped out
by some other team or what?
If it was a team,
I don't know who.
They haven't been
reporting their wins
for the Parts War webpage.
♪
(bird cawing)
I'm home.
Ugh, man, I got
to take a bath,
I'm sweating like a pig.
Ikki, pick up your
stinkin' dirty clothes!
♪
Hey wait, what the hell
are you doing here?
Oh, you know
I just thought...
maybe we can get in the tub
together and splash around?
Don't worry about us,
we'll turn up the TV
so you two can make
all the noise you want.
Have fun.
Who said you could watch?
I mean, now who's the perv?
Good gosh, I go away
for a few weeks
and now Ikki's batting
for the other team.
(growls)
Her head's inflating!
Hold on, stay back, Ume.
Ringo's head is
extremely volatile.
Get out of here,
this isn't funny!
♪
Too slow.
No, no!
♪
Ooh, yes...no, wait!
You know, Ikki, I'm
really glad me and Agito
were able to
come live with you.
♪
I never thought
I'd say this,
but right now, I'm just
really happy to be alive.
♪
You know,
if I had one wish,
I'd wish we could
stay like this forever.
No matter what.
Until the end of time.
♪
All right, Behemoth,
you want to fight?
bring it on!
Wait, Akira Udou
and the Holy Beasts
are even stronger than
most A‐ranked riders.
It's too risky
to take them on now.
I don't care what
you or Agito think,
I'm not missing
out on this!
The strongest
D‐Class team
and the strongest
F‐Class team.
I wonder what will happen
when Agito and
Akira face off?
Next time on Air Gear,
we'll show those bastards
what Kogarasumaru
is made of.
Kill 'em dead!
♪