♪
Oh, this feels good.
There are eight different roads
and eight kings to rule them.
♪
The eight kings, huh?
(chuckling)
♪
(echoing splash)
Right now, I think
I'd rather just ride
than get into
something like that.
♪
Hey, hold on, what do
you think you're doing?
You need someone to wash
your back for you, Little Crow?
No way!
(gasping)
(screaming)
Ah, Ikki, don't die!
That looks bad.
Oh, by the way, Ringo...
Huh?
I needed to ask you something,
and I want an honest answer.
What is Ikki to you?
W‐well, he's, uh...
Because I'm serious.
Dead serious.
‐Huh?
‐If you don't want him, I do.
You're only serious about
collecting the eight kings.
The riders who are
destined to become king
will be forced into battle
over and over again,
whether they like it or not.
Ikki's not ready for that.
He needs a partner who's
willing to support his growth.
And you're saying
that person is you?
Listen, Ringo, I'm saying
if it weren't you,
I wouldn't even be
telling you this.
Once, all eight kings
were gathered together
and formed a legendary team,
the Sleeping Forest.
But I'm sure you
know that already,
seeing as you're the legitimate
successor to that team.
That's why this is an issue.
♪
This is where I saw it.
There it is.
♪
The Wing Road.
I swear,
I'm gonna ride it again.
♪
What up?
Well, well, well.
I haven't seen you
around here lately.
Uh...
Wow, there's that many teams?
So many teams pop up recently,
not to mention teams
that lost in Parts War
and have to break up.
What a freakin' waste.
It's so stupid that
people stop riding
just because they
lose a Parts War.
Geez, I didn't know they
made AT motors that small.
This particular motor
is much smaller
than ones put in most ATs.
It's actually top secret one
used in military robots.
I don't really get it,
but it sounds cool.
You're the punk who had
the match against the Yaooo
the other day.
Oh, then you saw it, did you?
Well, then you'd have to admit,
I was pretty amazing,
wouldn't you agree?
Fuck, pretty arrogant for
a low‐class piece of shit.
Where the hell do you get off
talking crap to me,
you little freak?
Do you have any idea who I am?
(laughing deviously)
♪
Not what I'm used
to working with,
but I managed to
install motor for you.
♪
If it's off‐balanced,
come back, I'll fix for you.
Still, I don't know why you need
a motor with such crazy torque.
Ha.
What's up with that eye?
And why would he wear
a straightjacket?
If I were you, I'd give up ATs
before you hurt yourself.
A wuss like you will
be torn to pieces.
You're better off crawling
on the ground like a worm
instead of flying in
the sky like a bird.
♪
Who the hell is that kid anyway?
Ah, that's Agito,
A‐Class, Storm Rider.
Agito.
♪
All right, see ya later.
Strange.
Now one of emblem
stickers is missing.
‐I'm home!
‐Spinning Rika Hold!
(screaming)
Uncle, uncle, uncle, I give!
Zero minutes and twelve seconds.
The winner is Rika!
I just got here.
What the hell was that for?
That's just Rika's way
of saying, "Welcome home."
Right, big sister?
I thought we'd wait
till Rika got back
before we punished
you for stealing
the Sleeping Forest emblem.
You're lucky
'cause if it was me,
I probably would've
busted your face in.
So, how have you been?
Heard you got a pair of ATs.
Have you been practicing
while I was out on my road tr‐‐
I mean, my business trip?
Damn straight.
Although a genius like me
doesn't really need to practice
to be good.
I'm in my own class.
I fly so high,
I crap on the birds.
Hey, that's rude!
Don't just cut me off when
I'm saying something important.
Listen to me when I'm
talking to you, damn it!
I know, Ikki.
Even if nobody's listening,
I know you've been
practicing every night.
You have a lot to be proud of.
Wait, maybe I should get Rika
to try some more wrestling moves
on me so I can cop a feel
of her soft, round...
ahh‐hh‐ss!
You girls are in
middle school, right?
Isn't it a little dangerous
to be out this late?
Which school do
you go to anyway?
Wait, before you say
anything, let me warn you.
If I don't like your answer,
I might play a little rough.
(laughing)
Shino‐‐Shinonome Eastside.
Well, what do you know?
Shinonome Eastside.
That's too bad for
you, little bitches,
'cause I fuckin'
hate that place.
Now, I think I know just
the game to play with you.
Huh?
Who did that?
(girls screaming)
Look, Magaki.
It can't be.
Those who wander
into our forest
shall fall into
an eternal slumber.
(groaning)
♪
I once heard of an urban legend
that says whoever
hears that voice
and gets a challenge
from the Sleeping Forest
will disappear and
never be heard from again.
But it can't be real.
♪
(chatter)
What's that?
Hey, guys, what's goin' on?
Hi, sweetie.
Did you call me "sweetie"?
Oh, no, what I meant to say‐‐
Yeah, whatever.
What are you guys looking at?
(gasping)
♪
What the hell is that?
That's gross.
♪
Who would do that?
Guess the Skull Saders
want a rematch.
Better tell Ikki about this.
♪
(squawking)
(shoveling)
Those bastards want to fight
that bad, I'll give it to them.
(footsteps approaching)
Mikan, what should we do?
Nothing, why should I care
if that dumbass wants
to get himself killed?
Just means one less
mouth to feed, right?
Better watch what you're saying,
or Rika will hear you.
Hey, I saw Ikki tuning his ATs.
I think he's serious about this.
What's gonna happen
if the Skull Saders
bring their whole team?
Ringo, Sleeping Forest as we
know it is a thing of the past.
To most of the Storm
Riders out there,
it's nothing more than a legend.
‐Yeah, but‐‐
‐Let it go.
Right, Rika?
We used to have our stickers
plastered all over town.
Someone probably
just grabbed an old one
off some monument to
play a prank on him.
I bet that Swallow girl
put him up to this.
That's just like her.
(rumbling)
Ikki!
♪
Hang on, if this is a set‐up,
then maybe we
better help him out.
Unless...tonight's
meat night, right, Rika?
Meat night, oh yeah.
♪
What are you guys doing here?
Look, we might not have
an emblem or a name yet,
but that doesn't mean
we aren't a team, right?
We're not gonna let
you go alone, Ikki.
If the Skull Saders want
to pick a fight with you,
then they get us, too.
♪
(groaning)
Buccha?
Don't get the wrong idea, Crow.
I'm not coming to help,
I just want to see
how the match turns out.
Whatever.
You don't have to come up
with some lame‐ass excuse.
Just follow us, all right?
Let's go.
♪
This is the West District.
No sign of the enemy, over.
Roger, over.
This is bullshit.
Who gives a rat's ass
about Sleeping Forest anyway?
I can't believe Magaki is
puttin' us through this crap.
I hear you, man.
I was supposed to
have a date tonight.
I mean, what kind of dumbass
pretends to be Sleeping Forest
just to pick a fight with us?
‐Hold on.
‐What is it?
Something's not right.
Where'd that breeze come from?
(screaming)
(clanking)
(wind howling)
They're nothing but fools,
lying to the eyes and
fangs of the beasts,
creeping in the
shadows of the city.
Tonight, the hunters
will become the prey.
♪
I knew you were behind this.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Don't play dumb.
Why are you always putting
Ikki up to this stuff?
He could die!
Wow, sounds like things
are getting interesting.
♪
(giggling)
(banging, chain rattling)
Son of a bitch!
(grunting)
Those bastards are useless.
Can't they even keep watch?
How the hell did we lose the
north, east, and west sides
all at once?
You guys stay here and
guard the base, all right?
Do what?
Oh, okay.
Uh, hey, boss,
what are you gonna do?
I...was going home
to do my homework.
Are you kiddin' me?
That's bullshit.
Look, boss!
Holy crap!
Don't tell me that's
Sleeping Forest.
Sorry to keep you
waiting, baldie.
♪
(chuckling)
So it's just the little bitches
from the East Side Gunz.
Why the hell are you trying
to pass yourselves off
as Sleeping Forest?
You think you're hot shit
just 'cause you beat the Yaooo?
You can talk all
you want, cue ball.
You still don't stand
a chance in hell.
How did you even make it
here in the first place?
There's no way in hell
you took out all my guards.
What guards, what are
you talking about?
Are you punks trying
to piss me off?
'Cause I got some news for ya.
I'm taking Sleeping Forest's
emblem and going all the way
to the top of the Tropaeum.
♪
Parts War, F‐Class, Dash!
Holy crap!
That's high!
Grinding up vertical
walls isn't something
you really mastered
yet, is it, Ikki?
Hey, shut your pie hole.
I did just fine in
the match against you.
This building's so old,
it might just fall
and crush your baby face.
All right, but if it wasn't you,
then who did it?
Beats the heck out of me.
But it goes to show
how much attention
Little Crow is getting.
Look, quite an audience,
wouldn't you say?
♪
Is that who I think it is?
It can't be.
♪
Is it really okay to let
Ikki handle this by himself?
I mean, they challenged
Sleeping Forest.
‐Maybe I should...
‐That's strange.
The Skull Saders usually
bring their whole team
to outnumber their opponents,
but not tonight.
Don't tell me your teammates
have been backing him up
from behind the scenes.
You mean my sisters?
I'm sorry, Ikki,
but it looks like
you're gonna have
to ride alone again.
Heh, yeah, it does,
but you guys keep practicing so
you can ride with me next time.
Finish these guys
off for good, okay?
♪
It's 33 meters to the
giant pin on the roof.
Fall from that height,
your head'll smash
open like a watermelon.
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
It's time to get it on.
♪
Do you think Ikki
can beat that guy?
He'd better, or he's
not getting any dinner.
♪
Hey, Ikki?
Shut up, we're about to start.
Five and six and
seven and eight.
♪
What the?
I don't care how good
you think you are.
You're in my house now, punk.
This wall belongs to me.
♪
Spinning Wallride Overbank
1800 Degree Buccha Special!
♪
Hey, that's...
No way!
Did he learn to do
that trick from Buccha?
What did I tell you?
It's his destiny to
become king of the sky.
(gasping)
♪
No way!
This cannot be
happening to me!
That son of a bitch got
a lucky break last time,
but now the little
bastard's riding my ass
like he's been racing for years!
No fuckin' way!
♪
(bellowing)
Man, this is incredible!
I'm not just racing anymore,
I'm flying like a bird.
♪
I have wings.
I'm really flying!
♪
I don't think so.
(shouting)
(screaming)
Oh, shit, he's falling!
Ikki!
Fly, Crow.
I really screwed up.
There's nowhere to grind.
It's over, I'm‐‐I'm gonna die.
Ikki, no!
(footsteps approaching)
♪
I think playtime's over.
Now it's time to go home.
It's not over,
he hasn't lost yet!
♪
Face it, your plan was a bust.
You know that, right, Agito?
♪
Let's make a deal.
If you fork over the emblem,
I'll let you live, all right?
♪
(screaming)
(all gasping)
♪
Damn it.
(shouting)
What the hell, Ikki?
You always gotta
show off, don't you?
(groaning)
You better hurry
and do something
before you fall.
I don't think I can hold
onto this chain much longer.
(railing creaking)
♪
(chain rattling)
Yeah, you did it,
Ikki, way to go!
All right, yeah!
Uh, that was just wrong.
Ditch your ATs and
hit the road, Jack.
Your Storm Riding days
are over, you hear?
♪
(laughing)
Hey, hold on!
I didn't say you could go home!
Don't just leave me here!
Wait a sec, come back!
Hey, look at me when
I'm talkin' to you!
Oh, wow, now I
want him even more.
Don't treat Ikki
like he's your toy.
You're one to talk.
Well, anyway, see ya.
♪
You are such a...hmm?
Man, I'm starving!
(whimpering)
I can't believe it.
You guys had
barbecue without me?
Don't give me that look.
Why don't you just heat up
some instant ramen or something?
That's not fair!
Where's my reward for
taking out the Skull Saders?
Where'd you get that?
Stop stealing our emblem,
you dirty son of a bitch!
I'm gonna fry your ass
on the hot plate, punk.
It burns, it burns!
♪
Man, this is awesome!
ATs really are the best.
I think I'm getting
the hang of this, too.
That's great, Ikki.
You're starting to
ride like a real pro.
I still can't do
it quite like you,
but at least I've got some
real‐life battle experience.
Ikki, listen.
Why don't you join Simca's team?
I thought about it at first,
but now that I'm getting better,
I'd rather make my own team.
She can join if
she wants, though.
Next time on Air Gear,
to hell with lost love.
We're partners, right, Onigiri?
♪