Here, I poured you a cup, too.
Oh. Great, thank you.
This has been so nice.
I haven't been to a
hot spring in a long time.
[KYON] Yeah, the baths were
awesome. So was dinner.
I guess we have
Miss Tsuruya to thank.
We do, don't we?
I mean, the
accommodations alone.
This inn is run by one
of her relatives, right?
And that store we stopped
by on the way here.
Yeah.
She may not act it, but she's
from a pretty wealthy family.
[KOIZUMI]
I didn't know that.
[KYON] Nice to have some
peace and quiet, huh?
Yeah, it is.
I like how tranquil the
whole world seems at night.
It's so relaxing, you know?
Absolutely. Being someplace
--calm like this is really--
--[door slams, footsteps]
Hey guys, I'm here!
Couldn't you have
maybe locked the door?
Now I know for next time.
You ready? The night is
just getting started!
Hey, you guys! We're comin' in!
Um. Sorry about this.
No problem.
What about the other
two? They coming?
No. I think it's
just us for now.
Miss Asahina was tired, so she
decided to stay in her room.
Miss Tsuruya is
staying with her.
You can't blame her
for being worn out
after what those two
did in the bath!
Her exhaustion was well earned.
[HARUHI]
Come on! Hurry up! Hurry up!
Okay, I found it.
[laughs]
[KOIZUMI]
Here you go.
[HARUHI]
Yay! Koizumi to the rescue!
All right, guys!
Now that we've got a deck
'o cards, it's time to play!
I now hereby
declare the opening
of The Late-Night
Card Game Contest!
People are trying to sleep.
It's nighttime, you know?
Keep it down, 'kay?
[HARUHI]
Yeah, yeah, fine.
[ASAKURA]
Don't "yeah" me.
Okay, what do you think
we should play first?
[KOIZUMI]
Well, how 'bout we play a game
that we all know the rules to?
That could be fun.
[KYON]
Yeah, that sounds good.
Let's do it this way:
do you know how to
play crazy eights?
[ALL but ASAKURA]
Yeah!
All right: poker?
--[ASAKURA] Yep!
--[HARUHI] Yeah, yeah, yeah!
What about Go Fish?
Yep, yes, yes, yes!
Uh. Gin rummy?
[NAGATO grunts]
There's always solitaire.
Yes!
[KOIZUMI, HARUHI, ASAKURA]
Hm?
[gasps]
It was a joke.
[KYON] I didn't think anyone
would raise a hand.
Let me see. How
about Concentration?
There we go.
Concentration it i--
[HARUHI] Great! So we're
playing old maid?
Yes, of course we are, Haruhi.
And I'll be the dealer!
[giggling]
[HARUHI]
Done!
Your performance in
Old Maid is a reflection
of the way you live your life.
You're gonna have to
explain that one to me.
[KOIZUMI] If you start out with
the joker, that's just bad luck.
But if you still have it at
the end, then it's probably
because of something
you're doing.
Huh?
[HARUHI giggles]
[NAGATO]
Oh...
See, Kyon.
Card games are
microcosms of human life.
Oh, I hope that's
not really the case.
[NAGATO]
Huh...
[NAGATO gasps]
[ASAKURA, HARUHI cackle]
Um, don't. Please don't.
All right, Koizumi,
you're first.
Okay.
So, what's the
loser have to do?
Huh? Aw...
Jeez, you love your penalties.
No kidding.
Why don't we just skip the
penalty this time around?
[KOIZUMI] I don't know,
I think it sounds fun.
Yeah! What's the point
of playing a game
if you aren't gonna
risk anything?
What do you think, Yuki?
About doing a penalty? Hm...
I think it can be fun when
there are stakes to a game.
[yelps]
Within reason.
If the penalty's not crazy,
then I think it's fine.
Oh? "Not Crazy," huh?
Well then, let me ask you,
what exactly would qualify
as "crazy" by your standards?
I'd like to hear
the answer to this.
I think it could be helpful.
For future reference, you know.
[gasps]
[KYON] Okay, both of
you. That's enough.
Lay off. Quit giving
her a hard time.
If we are gonna have a
penalty, let's make it easy.
The loser can go out
and buy some snacks
and drinks for everybody.
How boring! A snack
run's not a penalty!
I think it should be
something a lot tougher.
[NAGATO whimpers]
Uh... Actually,
on second thought,
I'll allow it as
a warm-up this time,
since it's only the first
round for us and all.
[sighs]
[KYON]
Hm...
[NAGATO]
Thanks for that.
[KYON]
Hm? Uh--
Oh-- Ah!
[ASAKURA] Hm... Things are
starting to get a little more
natural between them.
He casually helped her,
and she casually thanked him.
Oh my, it seems
they're growing
closer and closer by the minute.
They're so comfortable
in front of other people.
I wonder what would happen
if they were alone?
Things could get
out of hand, fast!
--[HARUHI] Yes!
--[gasps]
[HARUHI]
Game over!
[NAGATO]
Looks like I lose.
You had the joker from
the beginning, didn't you?
Yeah, how did you know?
Your poker face is the worst.
[NAGATO]
Oh!
Looks like you're off
to buy us some snacks.
All right. I'll be
back in a bit.
[KYON]
Wait.
I'm going with you.
Really? You're coming?
Yep.
[growls]
[HARUHI]
Hold on a sec!
If you go, too, then it's
not much of a penalty.
Well, what do you
want me to do?
She can't go out in a strange
area by herself at night.
[gasps]
Okay, then I'll go with you.
No, that's all right.
If we all go, then
it really won't be
much of a penalty anymore.
I think the two of
us can handle it.
I mean, we're just
getting snacks.
Well, I don't care what
he says, I'm going.
[gasps]
In other words--
[ASAKURA]
I'll tail them!
[yelps]
[KYON]
Are you okay?
I am. Thanks.
That was a good catch.
There aren't very many
streetlights around here.
We should really watch
where we're going.
[NAGATO]
Yeah, probably.
Hey, I know. Here.
Oh--
This should help keep
us both from falling.
[ASAKURA, HARUHI gasping]
[ASAKURA, HARUHI yelp]
--[ASAKURA gasping]
--[HARUHI laughing]
Nooooo!
Ahhh! What's wrong?
You scared me!
Huh?
Uh. Oh. I'm really sorry.
I-- [pants]
Give me some water?
Here. Have it all.
[ASAKURA]
Great, thanks.
Whoa! That was a shock!
What was? No one
here did anything.
Yeah, that's Ryoko.
She can make any
situation a tense one.
[ASAKURA]
I can't believe I scared myself
with my own daydream.
How embarrassing.
That's not the point, though!
If Nagato loses,
that's the kind of thing
that could actually happen!
Yeah!
[ASAKURA]
Get a hold of yourself, Ryoko.
[NAGATO]
That's it. I'm out of cards.
[ASAKURA] Any way you look
at it, I'm worrying too much.
[KYON]
Me, too. All done!
Huh?
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
[gasps]
[ASAKURA]
Ah...
Well, guess we
know who's buyin'
our snacks, don't we?
Now, on to the next game!
[KYON]
Yeah! Let's do it. What's next?
Hello, hello!
Mikuru's all rested up now,
so we thought we'd drop by.
Better late than never.
Hey there. Glad you're
feeling better.
It's just the two
of you here, then?
[KYON] Koizumi lost a round
and had to do some squats
as a penalty, so he's
off taking another bath.
As for the other two,
see for yourself.
[whimpering]
[HARUHI snoring]
[KYON]
They're getting some shut-eye.
It's not surprising.
Asakura is a creature of habit.
She's usually already in
bed by this time of night.
And I'll bet just being
Haru must get exhausting.
So that's her excuse.
You two have just
been having a cozy
game of concentration, then?
[KYON]
Heh, It feels a bit more like
a boring game of not-real-cards.
Well, in that case,
I guess I'll just have to let
you in on a little secret.
You'll find it if you go a bit
further up on the mountain.
There's this little observatory
that's perfect for stargazing.
Why not check it out?
Stargazing?
That's part of the reason
I suggested this inn:
so we could all go up there.
But, someone's gotta keep
an eye on those two
sleeping beauties, eh?
But there's nothing to
stop you from going.
[KYON, NAGATO panting]
Ow.
How you doin'? Are you
holding up okay?
Yeah. I think so.
I'm getting really
sweaty, though.
But that's all right. I can
always take another bath.
Is your ankle hurt?
[NAGATO]
No, it's okay.
This is a steep hill, and
we've covered a lot more
ground than I thought
we were going to.
[NAGATO]
Yeah.
[KYON]
Well...
I guess that's what we
get for taking anything
Tsuruya says at face value.
[KYON] I can't say I'm
super comfortable wandering
around here in
the dead of night.
[NAGATO]
Yeah.
[KYON]
Maybe we should hold hands.
Just to keep from falling.
What?
[KYON] Or maybe it would be
a better idea to just give up
and go back to the inn.
No, it's all right.
I mean, it shouldn't be a
big deal if we try going
a little bit further on, right?
But if you wanna
go back, that's okay.
No, you're right.
Let's keep going.
We've come this far, haven't we?
So! Onward and upward, it is!
Take it.
[gasps]
Thank you, but,
I'm sleepy, so, my hands are
kind of sweaty and you know.
Don't worry. I'm not
afraid of a little sweat.
Hm? Since when does getting
sleepy make your hands sweat?
[NAGATO]
Uh-- Um...
How pathetic!
Are those two idiots
ever going to hold hands?
You just woke up, you
sure got a lot of energy!
Well, we're on an
important mission!
We are the only ones
standing between those two
and romantic disaster.
There's no time for
us to be sleepy!
I'm not just here to help
you with your crazy plan.
The reason I'm here
is for the stargazing.
I was also considering that
you might end up getting lonely
out here all by yourself.
So you should thank me, really.
Come on. They're on the move.
[groans]
Dinosaurs?
[HARUHI]
Wa-hoo!
[laughs]
Hey, quit messing
around, would you?
Stop being so grumpy.
We're here, so let's
have a little fun!
Go on, you slide, too!
[sighs]
[HARUHI]
Come on.
What's it gonna take to get
you to chill out a little?
Huh?
[HARUHI] You were waiting
for them to hold hands,
weren't you? So why wouldn't
them dating be okay?
But at the same time,
you don't want them
to end up crossing the line.
[ASAKURA]
Hm...
Do I want them to start dating?
Yeah, that would make me happy.
Except...
I feel like the closer
Nagato and Kyon get,
the more time she
spends with him,
the further she
and I drift apart.
It makes me sorta lonely.
Maybe I shouldn't feel
that way, but I do.
The truth is out now.
[ASAKURA]
It's not concern I'm feeling.
I'm just jealous,
that's what it is.
[HARUHI]
Ryoko...
[ASAKURA]
Hm?
That's the stupidest
thing I ever heard.
[ASAKURA]
Stop it!
Would it kill you to be
nice to me, just this once?
I'm a little
fragile here, Haruhi!
Yeah.
[HARUHI]
I mean, come on.
It's just that you and
Yuki are so close,
I can't understand what you
have to be worried about.
What happens between those
two is beside the point.
That is not gonna change your
friendship with Yuki at all.
In fact, I'll even give you
my personal guarantee!
You guaranteeing it only
makes me more worried.
I don't see why.
Even so, I can tell
you were trying
to be nice to me for
a change. So, thanks.
[HARUHI]
I was mocking you, Ryoko.
I didn't do anything
to deserve your thanks.
Ahhh! That's Archaeopteryx!
It's, like, the coolest
dinosaur ever!
[ASAKURA]
Uh, can you hold on a second?
Huh?
[ASAKURA]
It's my butt. It got stuck.
Take a look at this guy.
He's got a hole right
through his middle.
No wonder he's extinct.
[HARUHI grunting]
Up!
[ASAKURA, HARUHI grunting]
[HARUHI]
Come on!
[ASAKURA]
Pull!
My finger.
Huh?
[KYON]
It's a girl!
[ASAKURA, HARUHI panting]
[BOTH scream]
Did ya have a nice nap?
[HARUHI]
People think Dilophosauruses
had big neck frills
and spewed venom,
but there's really no proof
that they were
actually like that.
Really? No! I won't
get distracted!
[TSURUYA] Oh, hey!
You guys takin' a break?
[ASAKURA, NAGATO, HARUHI]
Huh?
[TSURUYA] Mikuru got tired
again. Big surprise, huh?
[TSURUYA] Well, come on.
We're almost there.
[KYON]
She climbed that whole hill
with Miss Asahina on her back?
Scary. Amazing! But scary.
[ALL gasping]
[NAGATO]
Beautiful.
[KYON] This really is
an incredible view.
[ASAKURA]
Yeah, it is.
[HARUHI]
Good job, Miss Tsuruya!
[TSURUYA] I'm glad you all
like it. I do what I can.
By the way, I
stopped by the baths
and asked Koizumi to join us.
He said he'd come up
later with snacks.
He was in the bath, huh?
All right. No further
details needed.
Wow. You can see the
stars so clearly.
I wouldn't be surprised if
we saw a spaceship or a UFO!
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Are you interested
in aliens, too?
[NAGATO]
Huh?
[HARUHI] Let's make some
astronomical observations!
Oh, yeah, the message!
This might be a
good place for it.
A message?
[HARUHI] I gotta find
something to write with,
like a stick or something.
Uh...
[HARUHI]
anything will do,
I just need something
to write with!
[NAGATO]
Uh, I, uh.
Hey, you two!
Don't just stand there,
help us with our observations!
Is that an order?
Hey, you too, Mikuru
and Miss Tsuruy.
Huh?
[HARUHI]
On second thought, never mind.
You can just stay
there and rest.
[sighs]
[HARUHI]
Get ready to find something!
[KOIZUMI]
Hello, everybody.
Phew. Sorry if you
were waiting long.
Yay!
Snacks for everybody,
thanks Koizumi! Yummy!
Ooh, look!
[ASAKURA] Oh good, there
are drinks. I'm so thirsty!
That wasn't exactly
a leisurely stroll.
Yeah, no kidding.
You're drenched in sweat.
[KOIZUMI]
Yeah. Guess I'll have to take
another bath when we
get back to the inn, huh?
Hey, man. Personal
space, remember?
Hey, look!
We're all up here,
just like I was hoping.
Yeah, it's nice, huh?
[HARUHI]
All right, guys.
Now that we're all here,
we can decide
what our next activity is
going to be for the night!
Anyone have any ideas?
[KYON]
We should conserve energy,
or we're gonna need
a rescue party.
Got it! Does anyone
wanna play tag with me?
Nope. Overruled.
How 'bout doing something calm,
like looking at the stars?
Overruled!
[KYON]
Oh, come on!
--[HARUHI] But it's boring!
--[TSURUYA] You guys!
[distant bickering]
You wanna play tag
with me, don't you?
[laughs] That does sound fun.
[HARUHI] All right,
Mikuru! Start running!
[TSURUYA]
Mikuru, go on!
[MIKURU]
Huh? Wha--? No!
[HARUHI]
Whoa! She's it!
Mind if I ask what you're doing?
Oh, it's just...
They seem close enough to touch,
but then you try to
grab them, and, nothing.
[KYON]
Hm.
[KYON] I'm kinda hungry.
Wanna go grab some snacks?
[NAGATO]
Sure.
Let's go, then.
'Kay.
[train horn blares]
[NAGATO]
It's time to head home.
[sighs] I really hate it
when it rains every day
like this, don't you?
[NAGATO]
Mm.
[ASAKURA]
And summer break will start
as soon as the rainy
season is over.
Have you come up
with a plan yet?
[NAGATO] What do you mean?
A plan for what?
[ASAKURA]
Well, summer means no school,
which means no Literary
Club meetings, right?
And that means you
won't have any excuse
to spend time with Kyon
like you usually do.
So, you may have to get creative
if you want the
chance to see him.
[NAGATO]
Oh, yeah? Hm. Like what?
[ASAKURA]
It could be anything, really.
"It's hot outside.
Let's go swimming!"
"I'm bored. Let's
go to a museum!"
[NAGATO]
I think I get it.
You've only known him for what,
half a year now? I'm sure you
can think of lots of things
you haven't done together yet.
[ASAKURA]
I'll go get the shopping done.
Don't wanna miss
the good sales.
[NAGATO]
Okay. See ya later.
[ASAKURA]
See ya.
[car horn beeping]
[tires screech]
[NAGATO] Next episode:
"Someday in the Rain."