[KYON]
I felt pretty confident
that I'd gotten decent
scores on the exams.
But that didn't stop me
from being relieved to
find out that I'd passed.
And, as a reward for my
valiant academic efforts,
it arrived at last:
Summer break!
The sun felt almost
impossibly hot,
but, temporarily freed
from the rigors of school,
the Literary Club was gearing up
for its first summer vacation.
[KYON]
Led, of course, by Haruhi,
we started thinking of
ways to fill our time.
But fortunately,
Miss Tsuruya joined us,
and instead of making
theoretical plans,
we were able to
make actual ones.
And for our first activity,
we're heading to--
[ALL gasping]
[HARUHI giggles]
[KYON]
The beach!
[HARUHI]
Ahh!
The beach is the
best in the summer!
Thanks a lot for inviting us.
It's so cool that your family
has a summer home here.
Aw, it's no big deal.
I mean, there'd be no point
in letting it sit empty.
I say we worry about
settling in later.
For now, let's just dump our
bags and get down to the beach.
[KYON]
Yes! Like now!
[KYON] Man, what is
this place? Paradise?
How are we the only ones here?
I wonder if this is
their private beach.
There's no way. Those don't
exist in Japan, do they?
It's totally possible.
I've got this distant relative.
He bought an uninhabited island.
[KYON]
Well, that's impressive.
To be honest, I thought that
sort of thing only existed
in mystery novels.
[KOIZUMI] Actually, he did
take advantage of the location
to stage a little
murder mystery prank.
The police wound up
getting involved, though.
[KYON]
That's not surprising.
It sounds like something
only Haruhi would enjoy.
[KOIZUMI] Yeah. Like a
locked room murder mystery.
A reality sealed within itself.
That's something Miss Suzumiya
would probably like.
[TSURUYA]
Stare at this, instead!
[TSURUYA giggles]
--[HARUHI] What are you guys
--[KYON] One!
--standing around for?
--Two!
--The ocean awaits!
--Three!
[KYON] She may be nuts,
but she's got a great body!
[chuckles]
You know how to choose a suit.
Not everybody can
pull off a bikini
with that much personality,
but you sure can.
You look perfect!
[HARUHI]
Of course I do!
What, aren't you going
to say something about me?
You look great
in your suit, too.
We're finally here.
Nagato got a new suit.
I think it looks good
on her, don't you, Kyon?
[KYON]
Mmm.
Yeah. Looks good.
You could've been
more enthusiastic,
but I guess it'll do.
Glad you like it.
Let's go already!
But Miss Asahina isn't here yet.
Don't tell me that brat
is causing her trouble.
What? No. I don't think
she's done anything wrong.
Take it easy! Mikuru's just
helping her change, that's all.
Really? No way!
Isn't she old enough to be doing
that sort of thing herself?
Hey, everybody!
I'm sorry it took us while.
[KYON'S SISTER giggling]
[KYON]
Hey.
Don't tell me you're annoying
my friends already.
We just got here.
[giggles]
Nu-uh! I'm not annoying
anybody! Right, Mikuru?
Right.
[KYON]
I'm really sorry.
I'll try to keep her from
bugging you anymore.
It's okay, we're having fun.
I think you're little
sister's adorable.
She was pretty insistent
on coming along.
What the--?
[KYON]
Hm? Uh!
[KYON'S SISTER yells]
I don't ever get to
have fun! It's not fair!
[groaning]
Anyway, sorry again.
The little stowaway
is welcome to join us,
Aw, thank you!
[KYON'S SISTER giggles]
[KYON'S SISTER]
Tee-hee.
[KYON]
Evil little brat!
[HARUHI]
Now that we're at the beach,
it's time to do some
cool beachy stuff!
We've got a whole list to cover!
First, we'll race to that
island over there! See?
[ASAKURA]
We're going to swim there?
[HARUHI] Yeah!
It'll be an adventure!
Fighting against the waves is
the real challenge of the sea!
Come on, Mikuru! Let's go!
--[HARUHI laughing]
--[MIKURU screaming]
[HARUHI] Aw. Come on,
you guys, that was pathetic.
Let's do somethin' else.
Okay, next!
[HARUHI]
A little to your left.
You can do it! Keep going!
Just a little further!
[HARUHI] There's more than
watermelon out there,
so careful where you strike!
I really, really, really hope
she hits the right thing.
At least we're on the beach.
We might as well just sit
back and relax and enjoy.
How exactly?
[yelps]
I missed.
[KYON]
Which one?
[BOTH giggling]
[HARUHI]
Gotcha!
All right!
[HARUHI]
Yeah!
[screaming]
Yep, this is a classic
day at the beach.
[clicking]
Huh?
[KYON]
Well, she's consistent.
Everyone's got their own
version of fun, don't they?
Uh.
[KYON]
Um, can I help you?
Koizumi has a point.
Different people have different
hobbies, and that's just fine.
[KYON]
Uhhh...
[ASAKURA] But we did come all
the way to the beach, so--
[NAGATO]
Huh?
[ASAKURA] I know you're busy,
but do you have a second?
The ball flew all
the way down there.
Maybe you could go and get it?
[NAGATO]
Huh?
And while you're there,
you might as well play with it.
Uh. Okay. In a minute.
I'm about to get a rare item--
[ASAKURA] No, you're not.
You're going to play.
[NAGATO]
Yes, ma'am! Right away, ma'am!
What're you waiting for?
You... mean me?
[ASAKURA] Do you see anyone
else I could be talking to?
[KYON]
Mm.
Are you going to go
down and join her,
or are you going to make
Nagato play all by herself?
[KYON] Do you have to
look so proud of yourself?
Go on. She awaits.
[KYON]
Who are you supposed to be now?
Looks like I've been assigned
as your beach ball partner.
[NAGATO]
Oh.
Um, okay. Here I go. Ready?
Yeah, ready.
[NAGATO]
There!
Got it?
[KYON]
Uh-huh!
Uh!
Ah!
Sorry, that was my fault!
It's ok. I don't
mind getting it.
Okay, thanks.
[KYON] Nothing like
some awkward silence
to round out a day at the beach.
How did I talk to Nagato before?
I've been so nervous
around her lately.
Uhh. This isn't
gonna work at all.
The way I'm acting,
it must look like I'd rather
be anywhere but here.
I have to act normal.
Act normal. Act normal.
[NAGATO]
I can't believe the two of us
are playing together on
the beach! It's incredible!
Ah! No! If I smile like that,
he'll think I'm weird.
I should act normal. Act normal.
Act normal.
--[NAGATO] Act normal.
--[KYON] Act normal.
--Act normal. Act normal.
[KYON] Act normal.
Act norm-- I can't do it.
[KYON]
Hey, Nagato!
[NAGATO]
Hm?
Let's just head back
to the others.
[KYON'S SISTER]
Kyon! I wanna play!
Let! Me! Play!
[BOTH gasp]
[thud]
[KYON]
I... didn't... mean to--
To what?
[KYON'S SISTER]
Uhh...
[NAGATO, KYON gasp]
[yelps]
Are you gonna kiss?
N-N-N-N-N-N-No!
You're the one who kicked me!
This is your fault!
[KYON'S SISTER giggling]
[KYON'S SISTER]
You're a naughty boy, Kyon!
[KYON]
Act Two.
[KYON] We're headed
into the mountains now,
which might require
some explanation.
It was the second night
we spent at the beach house.
We were having
dinner and talking.
[KYON]
A test of courage?
[TSURUYA]
The beach is getting kind of old
and we're still only in
the middle of the break.
So why go there next?
Besides, I know the
perfect place for it.
We can pack up and head there.
Huh? What, like right now?
[TSURUYA]
Hmm.
It's a bit far,
so maybe tomorrow.
[KYON]
Okay.
A test of courage.
Can you handle it?
Yay! Fun! I wanna
test my courage!
[KYON]
Yeah, you'll be fine.
I can't wait!
Boogey men. Goblins. Demons.
Ghosts and ghouls.
Rabid squirrels.
It's gonna be so cool!
I'm especially worried
about those rabid squirrels.
[HARUHI] What's the matter?
You look a little pale.
Are you getting scared?
[ASAKURA]
Of course not! W-Why would I be?
Your hand's trembling.
What's the matter?
Have you heard of this place
we're going to? Is it that bad?
[ASAKURA] What happens at this
place that's so terrifying?
[MIKURU]
They just... appear.
I knew it?!
There really are boogey men!
[MIKURU]
No...
[HARUHI]
Ghosts? Ghouls? Demons?
[MIKURU]
Well, actually.
Goblins, yes!
I knew it all along!
[KYON] Haruhi, give her
a chance to finish.
[ASAKURA] Calm down, Miss
Asahina. Here, have some water.
I'm sorry for getting
so freaked out about it.
I was thinking 'bout what
happened last year, and I just--
It'll be okay. I really doubt
there will be any ghosts.
[HARUHI grunts]
But, so you know, Miss Tsuruya
has done everything she can
to make the test scary, so
I hope you're ready for it.
Yeah. Poor Mikuru actually
fainted last year.
It's that bad?
[TSURUYA giggles]
I don't think it's very funny.
You really scared
me, Miss Tsuruya.
[KYON]
What did she do?
Miss Asahina seems traumatized.
[KOIZUMI] She can probably set
up something pretty extravagant
with the money she's got.
[ASAKURA]
I don't wanna be scared.
That's not my idea of fun.
Is that so weird?
[HARUHI]
It's the goblins.
She's pretending it's
not, but I know it is.
Good curry. You mind
if I have some more?
[KYON] She's the only one
still focused on the food.
Well, despite what
Mikuru says, I'm innocent.
I didn't do anything.
[MIKURU] That's not true,
and you know it!
[TSURUYA] Say what
you want. I'm not lying!
[KYON]
Something here's not adding up.
So now, we're headed
to the mountains.
And at the end of this bus ride,
we get to face a
"test of courage".
Whatever that means.
[KOIZUMI]
Wow.
Look at this place.
It's so big.
Yeah, well, doesn't
surprise me much anymore.
The mountains are totally
the best in the summer!
Who wants watermelon?
This is nice,
but I'm kind of starting
to feel like a freeloader.
It seems like we're
always staying
at somebody else's house.
It's not like they're using it.
You really worry too much.
[HARUHI] See, she says it's
fine, so, that means, it's fine!
Kyon! Can we go bug hunting?
[KYON]
Huh?
I wanna go!
[grunting]
Okay, fine. I give, already.
Oh, no! We don't have
bug nets. What a shame.
Never mind.
I wanna live here!
This house has everything!
Including insect cages!
We'll do the test
of courage at night
so there's still time to spare!
Bug hunting sounds fun, too!
Sometimes I think you
can find fun in anything.
We should have a
cicada-catching contest next.
That's totally summery!
[KYON]
So, one word from Haruhi,
and here we are having
a cicada-catching contest.
Aw!
What're you doing?
You have to think like
a cicada to catch 'em!
[KYON]
Seriously?
There!
Hold still, I've almost got you.
Ha, ha! He got away!
I got one!
[TSURUYA]
You're good at this!
[whimpering]
--[TSURUYA laughing]
--[MIKURU screaming]
[HARUHI]
It's huge!
Is that a Hercules beetle?
That's not a cicada
so it doesn't count.
[KYON] We all met back up
to compare bug counts.
And, sure enough, to
absolutely nobody's surprise,
Haruhi was the big winner.
And in last place...
[KYON]
Also to no one's surprise.
Okay! We're splitting
up into pairs.
On a side note,
while no one can question her
enthusiasm about the test,
Kyon's sister fell asleep,
so she won't be participating.
And we can't go off and
leave a little kid alone,
so Ryoko offered to skip
the test and stay with her.
Someone had to do it.
[HARUHI]
Nice evade.
All right, we have teams of two.
First up, Koizumi and Haru.
Mikuru and I will be
the all-girl pair.
And, then there's the couple
we've all been waiting for:
Yuki and Kyon.
We're not a couple.
Now then, as for the
route we'll be taking.
You just go straight along
this path and that's it.
There are no lamps or anything,
so we'll have to make
do with moonlight.
Keep going until you
reach the meeting point.
It's gonna be a deep, dark pond.
That's everything. You
know all you need to know.
When we come back,
we'll walk together.
So, first up--
We volunteer to be the first!
If there's supernatural
stuff out there,
I wanna get to it first!
That's fine. Mikuru and I
don't mind going second.
You can soften up whatever
might be waiting for us.
They're out there waiting.
And obviously that leaves
the two of you going last.
[KYON]
All right. Fine by us.
All right, Koizumi you
gotta keep up with me, 'kay?
Get ready to catch at least
two or three ghosts!
[KOIZUMI]
I'll do my best.
It's not all that far
from here, actually.
At that pace,
they'll have some time to
kill when they get there.
That could be dangerous.
When Haruhi's bored, she's
always at her craziest.
Ha. Yeah, she is.
[NAGATO] Just looking
at her is scaring me.
[TSURUYA] That should be enough
of a head start for them.
We'll go ahead and leave now.
Stay here, and then take off
in another five minutes or so,
okay?
[KYON]
Uh-huh.
[TSURUYA]
Here we go!
[MIKURU whimpering]
[KYON] Huh, here we go.
More awkward silence.
[KYON] This is like
the beach all over again.
[NAGATO] We're alone again.
Just like at the beach.
[KYON]
Nagato?
[NAGATO]
Huh? Yes?
What Miss Tsuruya did with her
flashlight was kinda scary.
Do you think-- Should
I have said something?
[NAGATO]
Huh?
You know what, never mind.
Forget about it.
[NAGATO]
Maybe you should've.
[KYON]
Yeah, I guess I should've.
[NAGATO]
Yeah.
[KYON] Way to keep the
conversation going, Kyon.
Are you okay? With this
kind of stuff, I mean.
What, like ghosts and
goblins and stuff?
Yeah. You're totally calm,
like it's not fazing you at all.
[NAGATO]
Huh?
Hmm. I'm not really
a fan of scary stuff,
but I guess... it's not
bothering me right now because--
[KYON]
Uh.
Because, I've got you here
to protect me. You know?
[gasps]
[NAGATO]
Because--
[KYON]
Uh...
A lot of the horror games I play
are scarier than anything that
exists in real life. You know?
[chuckles] Yeah.
[KYON sighs]
[KYON] What the hell
is wrong with me?
[NAGATO]
Let's go.
[KYON]
Uh, yeah.
[MIKURU screaming]
[KYON]
Huh?
Why are you stopping?
Wait a sec. I thought
I heard something.
[MIKURU screaming]
[BOTH gasp]
That sounds like--
Yeah. Sounds like Miss Asahina.
Something might've happened
to them. Let's hurry!
Are you two okay?
[NAGATO]
Are those?
They... just appeared.
But aren't they...?
[HARUHI]
Fireflies.
Yeah. And a lot of 'em, too.
This pond is actually
famous for its fireflies.
[NAGATO]
How beautiful.
[KYON]
Yeah.
[HARUHI] Aw, I thought we were
gonna have a test of courage.
Ghosts, goblins,
boogey men, and demons.
But all we got to see
was a buncha fireflies.
Yeah. Disappointing.
Hold on a sec.
Before, when Miss Asahina
said "they just appear"?
[TSURUYA]
Mh-hm. This is what she meant.
She assumed the fireflies
were some kind of mean
spirits or something.
[KYON] That was last
year, though, right?
Why did she faint again
when she saw them this time?
[TSURUYA giggles]
[TSURUYA]
The thing is,
she still doesn't know
they're only fireflies.
I'm waiting for her to
figure it out on her own.
[KYON] So you were just messing
with us this whole time?
Yeah, a little.
Although, I wasn't the
one acting terrified.
So, how much longer
are you going to wait
before you say something
to her about it?
[TSURUYA]
Hm.
[KYON]
What? Why are you smirking?
Forget about it.
I'll let you figure this
out on your own, too.
[KYON]
Huh?
[NAGATO]
Next episode: "Fireworks."