[NAGATO]
I can't tell.
What is this?
Is this a dream?
Or are these her memories?
[NAGATO, KYON chattering]
[NAGATO] It's like the
world is disappearing.
And soon, I'll disappear, too.
[NAGATO]
No! I don't want to!
[KYON]
Nagato.
Nagato!
Okay, there we go! Man,
you're a heavy sleeper.
Here.
[KYON]
Hm?
--[NAGATO gasps]
--Whoa!
What?
[KYON]
You're still half-asleep.
Exams are finally over.
Come on. There's no
reason to stick around.
[NAGATO] I remember
the feel of his hand.
Every time I go to sleep,
my memories get more
and more mixed up.
At this rate, it won't
be long before--
[KYON]
Come on, sleepy-head.
[NAGATO]
Okay.
[KYON sighs]
Done and done!
[ASAKURA]
You look awfully relaxed.
I guess the exams
went all right?
[KYON]
Yeah.
All in all, I think
I did pretty well.
And I've got Nagato
to thank for it.
Oh, that's right.
You guys logged a lot of hours
studying at the library.
[KYON]
Yeah we did.
And since she was
such a big help,
I'm sure you'll find a good way
to show her your appreciation.
What sounds fun?
You could take her
to an amusement park.
What do you say, Nagato?
[KYON] Is there someplace
you'd like to go?
An amusement park, right?
[KYON] How about we see
what Nagato thinks?
[NAGATO] Well, if it's someplace
we're all going to go together.
[KYON] You sure this is where
you really wanted to go?
[NAGATO]
Uh-huh.
[ASAKURA] It's your call,
but I still think
an amusement park
would've been better.
[NAGATO gasps]
Huh.
[ASAKURA] I don't think I've
ever been to a used book fair.
[KYON]
Yeah. It's my first time, too.
How does it work?
[ASAKURA]
It looks like different stalls
carry different kinds of books.
[NAGATO]
Yeah. It's well organized.
[KYON]
I just realized something.
For a Literary Club,
we sure don't read much.
[ASAKURA] It's like we're doing
real club activities today.
[NAGATO]
Yeah.
Wow, that's bright.
Phew! Summer is
definitely on its way.
[KYON] What'll we do with our
summer break, President?
Huh?
[KYON] Just wondering what the
Literary Club's big plans are
for summer vacation.
[NAGATO] I haven't really
thought about it yet.
Oh, okay.
[ASAKURA] Well, we need
to make some kind of plan.
I'm sure we can
think of something.
Any ideas, Kyon?
Well, let me think a sec.
Hm.
[ASAKURA, KYON]
Hm?
[KYON]
Oh! The summer festival!
That sounds good!
[ASAKURA]
Yeah! We can all go together!
[KYON]
I'm in. So, what do ya say?
[NAGATO]
Sure.
[KYON]
Whoa! Impressive spread!
Are they all homemade?
Absolutely! With the help of
my lovely assistant here.
Not much help.
I just dipped the
shrimp in some batter.
That's more than I can do!
Here goes. I'll start
with the shrimp.
The batter's delicious.
[ASAKURA giggles]
Ah-- Thank you.
[KYON]
You're lookin' a little tired.
[ASAKURA] We have been
walking around a lot.
I'm okay.
I could probably keep this up
for a few more hours.
Uh... That makes one of us.
I'm kidding.
[KYON]
Okay, good.
Although, after seeing
you at the library,
I wouldn't have
been too surprised.
[NAGATO]
Really?
Saw you blink.
I surprised you
just now, didn't I?
[NAGATO]
No. Definitely not.
How 'bout that! They look
like a happy couple.
Kyon deserves serious credit.
He's been great.
It hardly took any time
for him to start treating
this Nagato just
like the other one.
What d'you know?
[ASAKURA sighs]
Today was surprisingly fun.
[NAGATO]
Yes.
[ASAKURA] I'm excited about
the cookbook I found!
We should go again sometime,
and bring the other
club members along.
We can invite Miss Asahina
and Miss Tsuruya.
Make it a real party!
Sure.
Maybe not Miss Suzumiya.
She tends to get
bored very easily.
True.
And, of course,
you might prefer to have
some alone time with him.
Just you and Kyon.
Would you like that?
[NAGATO yelps]
[NAGATO]
Why would I?
[ASAKURA chuckles]
[NAGATO] I think you've
got the wrong idea.
Do I? About what?
It's the other Yuki that
likes him. It isn't me.
[ASAKURA chuckles]
Oh, please elaborate!
Miss Asakura wants to hear more.
Tell her all about
how you don't like him.
Go on. She's listening.
[NAGATO] I know her feelings,
and I even understand them.
But the other Yuki and I
aren't the same person.
Her emotions aren't my emotions.
[ASAKURA chuckles]
[NAGATO]
What?
You seem to understand
her very well.
Are you so sure that she's
the only one who likes him?
[NAGATO] A dream. The
same one I always have.
In it, I'm an observer.
A fly on the wall,
peering into her memories.
It's a simple dream, really.
[KYON]
Nagato.
Come on. Let's go back.
[NAGATO] Today, I realized
that I'm in love.
[NAGATO]
How beautiful.
[KYON] Mind if I ask
what you're doing?
[NAGATO]
Oh, it's just...
They seem close enough to touch,
but then you try to
grab them, and, nothing.
[NAGATO]
No!
Come on. Let's go back.
[NAGATO]
No!
[KYON]
Let's go, then.
[NAGATO]
No!
[NAGATO] It's not mine!
This isn't my memory!
[NAGATO] Today, I realized
that I'm in love.
[NAGATO] And I also know
I'm about to disappear.
[NAGATO] When you sleep,
your body rests,
but your mind doesn't.
It uses the time to
organize your memories.
More and more of her memories
are starting to become clear.
[NAGATO]
I'm not sure how I know this,
but the next time I fall asleep,
when I wake up, everything will
return to the way it was.
She'll be back. And I
won't be me anymore.
I'm certain that's
what's going to happen.
[NAGATO]
Today is Sunday.
I don't have much time left,
so what I do have is precious.
I'm going to make
the most of it.
[ASAKURA sighs]
What a nice day!
This was a good idea.
So? Are you going to sit down?
[ASAKURA]
I have to say,
I was surprised that
you suggested this.
Dining al fresco isn't
really your thing.
Well, like you said,
it's a nice day.
So, are you becoming
an outdoorswoman on us?
I know what happened.
You got a taste of
sunshine at the book fair,
and now you're hooked!
[NAGATO]
Mm.
In honor of our first picnic,
I made a special lunch.
I thought the occasion deserved
a little something extra.
Right.
[NAGATO]
I think it's for the best
if I act like
everything is normal.
Wow, that's a lot.
It may be possible that
I got a little carried away.
[NAGATO]
Delicious.
Glad you like it.
In that case...
[NAGATO] Even if I did
decide to tell her,
what would it really change?
Would she care?
Probably.
I bet she'd be a
little sad, at least.
But, at the same time,
me going back to my old self...
That's something she wants.
So how could she not be happy?
Here! You should
try a bite of this.
[NAGATO] She'd be sad and
happy at the same time.
She'd be speechless.
It'd be awkward for both of us.
Oh, no. What's wrong,
do you not like it?
[NAGATO]
It's great.
Eating outside makes the food
you cook taste even better.
Stop that! You're going
to make me blush.
I'm just kidding!
Please tell me more!
[NAGATO] I want these
last moments together
to be happy ones.
[ASAKURA]
Is something the matter?
[NAGATO]
Mm-mm.
If I have to go,
I wanna leave
seeing my friend smile.
[chuckles]
Hey, sleepyhead.
You can barely
keep your eyes open.
Did you stay up
late reading again?
At first, I thought you were
a totally different person.
But it seems like you're
becoming more like
the old Nagato as time goes by.
The way you smile, when you
act startled, your shyness,
and the fact that
you're in love.
I know you're going to say
it's because the memories
are flooding back, and I do
think that's part of it.
[ASAKURA]
But not all.
I think there's more to it.
If you ask me, just
living is changing you.
Being with your
friends is making you
more like your old self.
Enough of that!
That's more introspection
than we need right now!
[NAGATO]
I get it.
It's not a straightforward
healing process.
I'm not just going back
to who I used to be.
Being with them is changing me.
It's helping me to become... me.
[ASAKURA]
Uh, what are you doing?
I'm gonna stop by
the library for a bit.
You go head home without me.
Then I can get
started on dinner.
See ya later!
[NAGATO]
Thanks for everything.
And good-bye.
[NAGATO sighs]
[NAGATO] At least I was
able to finish the book.
Now I just need to return it.
[NAGATO]
And that's that.
If I had a regret in all this,
it would be that
I never got the chance
to tell him how
I feel about him.
[NAGATO]
I can't.
[NAGATO gasps]
[NAGATO]
Hello?
Nagato! Hey, it's me.
Do you have a second?
Yeah. I've got some time.
[NAGATO]
It's nothing important really,
but I realized the book you
checked out from the library
is due back soon.
Did you ever finish it?
[NAGATO]
Yeah, just now.
[KYON]
Okay, good deal.
It was a science-fiction
book, right?
[NAGATO]
Yes.
[KYON]
So, what was the story about?
[NAGATO] That's a difficult
question to answer briefly.
Then I guess I'll have
to change my question.
Did you find it an enjoyable
read, Professor Nagato?
[NAGATO]
It was intriguing.
"It was intriguing," you say!
So you like it, then!
[NAGATO]
Yeah.
[NAGATO] This is beginning
to feel like a scene
from a bad romance novel.
[KYON] Honestly, I was
asking you about it
so I could pretend I'd read it,
but you make it sound
interesting enough that
maybe I actually will.
[NAGATO]
You'll be glad you did.
[NAGATO] Should I take this
as some kind of sign?
Him calling out of
the blue like this?
[KYON] If it has the Professor
Nagato seal of approval,
it must be good.
[NAGATO]
Yep.
[KYON] Anyway, don't
forget to return it.
[NAGATO]
Mm-hm.
[KYON]
And, ya know,
I could always go with you
to return it if you want.
Between going to the book fair
and our library trips,
it's like I'm always
surrounded by books lately.
It's starting to feel sort of
like my natural habitat.
Hm? Are you there?
Nagato?
[NAGATO]
I like you.
No, actually.
It's more than that.
I love you.
[KYON panting]
[KYON]
Err. What?
Are you messing
with me or something?
I mean, what are you saying?
[NAGATO] And, I won't actually
be able to return the book.
Would you mind doing it for me?
[KYON panting]
[KYON]
Sure, I can return it.
But why do you need me to?
You know what, never mind that.
Can we talk about what you
just said for a minute?
[NAGATO]
Don't worry about that.
You don't need to say anything.
Either response would
just leave me with regrets.
[KYON]
Where are you?
Are you home? Please tell me.
I'm gonna head your
way right now. Okay?
Don't talk like I'll
never see you again!
[NAGATO] You should know
the next time you see me,
I'll be back to my old self.
[KYON]
What're you saying?
[NAGATO]
Anyway, I wanted to tell you
how I feel about you
before that happens.
I'm glad I got the chance.
[KYON panting]
[NAGATO] Oh, and, I have
another favor to ask.
I'm really tired, so by
the time you get here,
I'll probably be asleep.
I'm sure my other self will
be panicked and confused
when she wakes up.
I think it'd be best
if you took her home.
[KYON]
Hey... Hey!
[screams]
[NAGATO] I did it.
I told him how I felt.
It wasn't so
difficult after all.
And now, well, there's
nothing for me to regret.
Almost.
[NAGATO]
Ahh. Close enough to touch.
[KYON panting]
[KYON]
I shouldn't be surprised.
I knew this was gonna
happen someday.
But it was so hard
to talk to her,
compared to the other Nagato.
So I never asked her
what was going on--
if she felt herself changing,
returning to normal.
But still, this
doesn't seem fair.
[KYON gasps]
[KYON]
Nagato!
Nagato, I'm here, okay?
And we need to talk.
You can't just--
[NAGATO]
You should know.
The next time you see me,
I'll be back to my old self.
That's all.
She said everything
she wanted to say.
And then she just disappeared.
It's not fair.
You're an idiot for letting
things end this way,
you know that?
[KYON]
Goodbye then, Nagato.
Hey.
Wake up!
[NAGATO grunts]
[yawns]
[NAGATO]
Hm?! Ah--
Hey! How'd I get here?
And why am I alone in a park at
this time of night with you?
Now that's the Nagato I know.
[chuckles]
Good morning. It's been awhile.
Ah, yeah.
Wait! "Good morning"?
It's--It's been awhile?
Huh? What?
[NAGATO]
Next episode: "Her Confusion."