[NAGATO]
Huh? Whoa! I got a rare item!
What am I doing?
Tomorrow is important.
I shouldn't stay up late.
Time to get some sleep.
Christmas is already here.
Don't worry. The
party'll be great.
[gasps]
[doorbell rings]
[ASAKURA]
To review:
you laid down, but you were
so excited about today
that you couldn't fall asleep.
[NAGATO]
Yeah, that's right.
[ASAKURA] So you thought
you'd play a video game
to take your mind off of things,
and before you knew it,
it was morning, just like that.
[NAGATO]
Yes, ma'am.
[ASAKURA giggles]
You're like a child
the day before a field trip!
It's so freakin' cold!
Hey, Kyon. You're
earlier than usual.
Yeah.
[ASAKURA grunts]
[ASAKURA]
You guys wait here.
I'll just go get
the clubroom key.
Great, thank you.
[KYON sniffs]
[KYON] Is that cake
you've got in there?
[NAGATO]
Mm-hm. Sure is.
[KYON] So you really baked
a two-tiered one? Wow.
Yeah, I pulled it off somehow.
[KYON] That's cool.
I can't wait to try it.
[KYON]
Whew. Let's get the heater on.
[NAGATO, KYON sigh]
[ASAKURA]
Once you thaw out a bit,
can you get started in here?
I'll be in the home ec.
room working on the turkey.
It'll probably take
a little while.
So decorating's up to you guys.
[KYON, NAGATO]
Leave it to us.
Good luck with the turkey.
Somehow I'm not reassured.
[KYON, NAGATO sigh]
I'm actually starting
to get kinda hot.
Yeah, I think I'm
sweating a little bit.
Well. Let's get started, then.
[NAGATO]
Yeah.
Oh, hey. I've got a surprise.
Here, take a look.
Hey! This looks like...
[KYON chuckles]
Asakura was against it until
the last minute, but...
[NAGATO]
It's snow!
[KYON]
The cotton kind.
With the heater, it's
probably a fire hazard
to spread it all over the floor,
but the corners
should be fair game.
Sounds good to me.
That's strange. Doesn't
look much like snow.
[gasps] We have
to pull it apart!
Oh, I get it!
[ASAKURA]
I didn't realize
turkeys were so
high maintenance.
[TSURUYA] Well, then,
let that be a lesson to you.
She who mocks the turkey
will be mocked by the turkey.
Right, Mikuru?
Oh, uh, sure, I guess.
We were able to get
the Christmas tree
as far as the
school gate via car.
[ASAKURA] Then I'd say
it's time to have Kyon
show off his muscles, right?
Knock, knock! How's it going?
Whoops! Missed me!
--Oh, yeah?
--[KYON] Take that!
[KYON, NAGATO laughing]
[KYON, NAGATO]
Oh, hi.
[KYON]
A-Asakura!
[KYON, NAGATO whimper]
Anger!
[KYON]
Aah!
[KYON, NAGATO]
We're very sorry.
[KYON]
Hey, get the door, will ya?
[ASAKURA]
Hold on a second, okay?
Come on, Nagato. Hurry up!
[KYON]
Not like this is heavy.
[TSURUYA]
This is no time to be shy.
You can show a little
more than that.
[MIKURU] I don't know!
This is really short.
[gasps]
Ta-dah!
[KYON]
Whoa! Santa cosplay!
What do you think?
Pretty cool, huh?
[KYON]
Yeah. It's awesome!
You can thank Miss Tsuruya.
She brought them for us.
I've never been
one for half measures.
I really think
this is too short.
Great idea. You all
look wonderful.
[TSURUYA]
Aww, do we?
You can't hide behind me
like that all day, you know.
Just go up to him and say:
"So, how do I look?"
[TSURUYA]
You should know something, Kyon.
Members of Mikuru's fan club
haven't even gotten
to see her dressed in a
Santa costume like this.
You are one seriously lucky guy.
[KYON]
Yes. Yes, I am.
Please. Is this
really necessary?
I'm sorry about this, Kyon.
Huh?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Is it okay to call
you Kyon? Do you mind?
Yeah, I don't mind.
Go right ahead.
That really is a nice
outfit. You look great.
Well thank you.
She does look great.
Much better than me.
What did I expect?
It's not exactly
my normal style.
[ASAKURA]
Don't look so sad, Nagato.
You're cute in your own way.
You just have to
find the confidence
to let it shine through.
[ASAKURA]
Unless you have more members,
the Literary Club...
will be terminated?
Well, it does
sorta make sense.
One member isn't
really much of a club
when you think about it.
But, if you get the number up
to five, you're good, right?
[sighs] Are you even
listening to me?
Sulking's not going to
help anything, you know.
[NAGATO]
I'm not sulking.
Oh, you are listening.
[ASAKURA] So, it's time to
start recruiting more members.
[NAGATO]
That's definitely impossible.
[ASAKURA]
Oh. You've given up, then.
[NAGATO]
Yeah. Of course. It's hopeless.
[ASAKURA] Hopeless? You sound
so certain. All right.
Well, maybe I can figure
something out. You never know.
You just had a moment
of hope, didn't you?
I thought it was hopeless.
Isn't that what you said?
[gasps]
[ASAKURA]
Ah-ha!
It looks like you haven't
given up after all!
Considering how you jumped
at my offer to help.
It's impossible for
me to do anything.
But maybe you could.
Well, there's nothing
I can do that you can't.
You just don't wanna risk
putting yourself out there
because you're too afraid.
Am I afraid of asking
people to join?
Of course.
What reason am I
supposed to give them?
"Please join my club
because otherwise
I'll be the only
one in it. Thanks."
And besides...
"Besides" what?
[NAGATO]
Well, it's just...
I don't think I can
do it all by myself.
Actually, I take that
back. I know I can't.
[ASAKURA]
All right, then!
[gasps]
If you feel unsure,
ask me for help.
There's no reason you
have to do it alone.
I'm your friend.
I'm not your mother
or your big sister.
I can't tell you what to do.
I can't take your hand and lead
you in the right direction.
I can't protect you from these
fears that always haunt you.
I can work with you.
But I can't solve
your problems. I can't!
[ASAKURA] I won't do anything
until you make up your mind.
So think, and think hard
before you answer this.
What do you want?
What are you willing to fight
for, because you know what?
To save the club,
you'll have to fight.
[ASAKURA]
I wonder if that really sank in.
You have to fight for yourself.
--[pop]
--[KYON yelps]
[MIKURU] Ah! Oh, dear!
I'm really sorry!
[TSURUYA laughs]
You didn't lose an eye, did you?
[NAGATO]
Asakura. Here.
Thank you.
[ASAKURA sighs]
What will be will be, I guess.
What's wrong?
[KYON] All right!
Does everyone have a glass?
We're good over here!
Well, in that case. Cheers!
[ASAKURA, MIKURU,
NAGATO, TSURUYA] Cheers!
[ASAKURA]
Here you are, the wait is over.
--My turkey!
--[TSURUYA] Hey, Asa.
--[ASAKURA] Coming!
--I want some, too!
So, I bet you're excited, huh?
[NAGATO]
Mm-hm!
So good!
Looks like it's a hit, huh?
Well, I guess I'll
give it a try, then.
[KYON] How exactly are
you supposed to eat it?
A little on the chewy side, huh?
[KYON]
You could say that again!
But it's still delicious!
[TSURUYA] You see the beauty
of turkey now, don't you?
[TSURUYA] Ha, ha, ha!
That's a great look!
No, really! You should
grow a mustache, Kyon!
[ASAKURA] You'll have to beat
the girls away with a stick!
[MIKURU]
You guys...
I think it looks
really good on him!
You're the ones who
made me wear this get-up.
I don't think it's very
fair to make fun of me.
[KYON] Man, where's the
hard stuff when you need it?
Oh, Mr. Santa! Can I
have my present now?
You mock me and then ask
for presents? That's cruel.
Here ya go. That's all
I've got to offer.
Wow. Thanks so much!
[ASAKURA]
Hey, Kyon.
That's really all
I have, I'm sorry.
[BOTH]
You're such a good boy!
Thanks, Mister Santa!
[KYON]
Oh. Sure thing.
So... What do ya say?
Is it time to cut the cake?
[MIKURU]
It looks delicious!
[ASAKURA]
Impressive, huh?
The work of our very
own club president!
Way to go, Nagato!
Wait a sec. Where is she?
Strange. Where'd she go?
[TSURUYA]
The restroom, maybe?
Do me a favor, Kyon.
Will you go out and see
if you can find her?
Oh, sure.
I'll track her down,
wherever she ran off to.
[ASAKURA]
Out with it.
[TSURUYA giggles] You'll make
a good mother someday, Asa.
So nurturing!
She is, isn't she?
Hello! Nagato!
[KYON]
Miss Nagato!
President Nagato!
[yawns]
[NAGATO]
A good party.
I'm glad the club
is still around,
and it's all thanks to her.
I wonder if I'll see her again.
Time to find food.
[NAGATO]
Ah. Forgot my glasses.
Well, it's just my usual route.
[ASAKURA]
What do you want?
What are you willing to fight
for, because you know what?
To save the club,
you'll have to fight.
[NAGATO sighs]
[HARUHI]
Hey, you!
[NAGATO gasps]
Come over here
a second, will you?
[NAGATO]
Huh?
Come on! Hurry up!
Uh... I'm sorry,
are you talking to--
[HARUHI]
Do you see anyone else around?
Now, come on! Move those legs!
[NAGATO]
But I-I don't. Please.
Just tell me what we're doing.
First things first.
You hold onto this.
And what is this?
[HARUHI] I'm going write what
that note says. Right here.
[NAGATO]
Like, on the ground?
Yeah, obviously.
And I gotta do it real big.
So I need you to watch and
make sure I'm not screwin' up.
Okay. Wait! Do you
have permission?
[HARUHI] Of course
I don't have permission!
Hence the sneaky,
cloak-and-dagger type operation.
Don't worry.
This is just a rehearsal,
so there's no pressure.
I'll move fast, and we'll
be done before you know it!
I don't know...
Now, get your butt
up on that bench
and check out what I'm doing.
[HARUHI]
Okay! Here I go!
[NAGATO]
This is crazy.
Even without my glasses,
I'm pretty sure she's way off.
Should I tell the lunatic
she's doing it wrong?
I should tell her, shouldn't I?
What's our status?
Is this about halfway through?
[NAGATO]
Uh... Well... I don't know.
Pretty close, huh?
What do ya think of that?
You gotta be kidding!
Whoa, hold on!
You normally wear glasses?
[NAGATO]
Yes, yes, yes.
Then it's obvious.
We're switching
responsibilities.
Huh?
[HARUHI]
Walk five steps south
and then turn 135 degrees.
[HARUHI] From there,
eight steps northeast.
A little further! No, stop!
Head west exactly six steps!
Good. Now draw a
circle. A big one!
Keep up the good work,
you've got it!
[HARUHI]
Thanks for helping!
Is it done?
Ah, it's just a
rehearsal, so this'll do
well enough for now, I'd say.
Do ya have any idea what it is?
No.
[HARUHI]
This is a message to Santa.
[NAGATO]
What?
[HARUHI]
The idea is to lure him in
without making him suspicious.
When he appears, I'll grab him!
[NAGATO]
I'm sorry. Just to be clear.
You believe Santa Claus exists?
[HARUHI]
It's okay if he doesn't.
I won't be crushed or anything.
But that's not the point.
The way I figure it,
the worst situation
would be if he did exist
and I didn't know it.
So what else am I gonna do
but verify it personally?
[NAGATO] This girl's not afraid
to go after what she wants.
Seems she can't stand
not to know things.
She's perfectly fine asking
a total stranger for help.
That fearlessness.
That's the kind of thing
that I need right now.
[HARUHI]
I'm wiped. Time to head home.
See ya later.
[HARUHI]
Oh!
If you can, you should
stop by on Christmas day.
I'll show you Santa Claus
when I catch him. You'll see!
[NAGATO]
What do you say?
Will you join the Literary Club?
Of course!
So you've made up
your mind, I take it?
[NAGATO]
Mm-hm.
[ASAKURA] Then I'll help you
however I can, Club President!
Great, thank you.
But for now, at least,
I think joining the club
should be all I need you to do.
For now... I'll see what
I can do on my own.
[inaudible]
[NAGATO chuckles]
[KYON]
Hey. What's so funny?
Why're you out here?
[KYON] I was gonna ask
you the same thing.
You pulled a disappearing act,
so I've been looking for you.
Oh. Whoops. I'm really sorry.
[KYON] So what brought
you out here, anyway?
The view.
I wanted to see the
clubroom from down here.
[NAGATO]
It's a relief.
[KYON]
A relief?
[NAGATO]
Yeah. I'm relieved.
The clubroom.
It's become very precious to me,
so it's a relief to know
that it's not going anywhere.
It's just a really nice feeling.
So there you have it.
That's why I'm relieved,
and I have you guys
to thank for it.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Sounds like you've
got it all wrong.
Huh?
[KYON] Who did what needed
to be done in order
to keep the Literary Club
from being shut down?
And who persuaded me and Asakura
to join the club
in the first place?
That would be you.
Don't thank me.
Be proud of yourself and the
work that you did, instead.
[NAGATO]
That's nice of you.
I'm so happy I could explode!
Seriously. Like, bang!
Uh-oh. I can't get my
face back to normal!
[KYON] Oh, hey. You're kinda
shaking. Are you cold?
[NAGATO]
No. I'm okay. I'm actually warm.
[KYON]
Um. Okay.
[NAGATO]
I need to calm down.
This is getting ridiculous.
[KYON]
Nagato.
[NAGATO]
What is it?
[KYON]
Look up.
[NAGATO]
Up?
It's snowing!
Ah--
Open your hand.
I've got a surprise for you.
No, not like that! Like this.
Here you go.
[gasps]
Merry Christmas!
U-Uh...
[inhales]
Merry Christmas to you!
Thanks.
[NAGATO gasps]
[NAGATO]
He gave me a Christmas present.
And we're alone out here.
There's pretty snow,
and I feel really good.
I think...
...I might be able to
tell him. I have to!
So, while we're here.
[KYON]
Hm?
I, uh, well, I wanted to...
I mean, there's something
I thought I would tell you.
[inhales]
Whoa! I can't believe
it! It's snowing!
Come here! You have to
take a look at this!
White Christmases are rare!
I don't know if I've ever--
[whimpers]
Ah...
[KYON]
What was that about? Weird.
Gah! What's wrong?
Are you doin'
all right down there?
You don't look so good.
[NAGATO]
Oh, I'm fine.
Just a little very
tired, that's all.
[KYON]
"A little very tired"?
So, how tired is that, exactly?
Well, tell me if
you need something.
[NAGATO]
Okay.
[KYON grunts]
We'll go back and join the party
after you rest up a little.
If we stay here too long,
we'll catch cold.
[NAGATO]
Um, don't you need your coat?
No, you can hang
onto it. I'll be fine.
I've got a strong
immu-- Ah-choo!
[shivers]
Maybe you should take it back.
It would be very
ungentlemanly of me,
I couldn't do that to you.
Well, okay then.
[KYON]
Uh, um. You know?
What is it?
Is it just me,
or does this feel
more than a little awkward?
Um, yeah. It's pretty awkward.
[NAGATO, KYON shiver]
[KYON]
Ah-choo!
[NAGATO] It is pretty
awkward. But, you know,
I've never been warmer.
[KYON] Cleaning up is the
worst part of the party.
Asakura says the
party's not over
till everything's tidy again.
[KYON] Oh, yeah?
And where is she, then?
She's already there.
[KYON]
Such a responsible young lady.
[NAGATO]
Got what I wanted.
The Literary Club
is still around,
and we had a Christmas party.
Things would've been different
if I hadn't met that girl.
She helped me find confidence
to fight for what I wanted.
Someday, I'll have to thank her.
[HARUHI] I'll show you
Santa Claus when I catch him!
You'll see!
[NAGATO] It's too bad I wasn't
able to make it back there.
[leaves rustling]
[KYON]
Hm?
[KYON, NAGATO gasp]
[BOTH]
Wha--?
[NAGATO] Next episode:
"Haruhi Suzumiya!"