[NAGATO]
It's like I can't tell who I am.
I don't mean that
I lost my memory.
[TAXI DRIVER]
There's a hospital nearby.
Get in my cab.
I'll take you to--
I'm fine, thank you.
The fall wasn't bad.
It probably looked a lot
worse than it felt.
[NAGATO]
I know my name.
I know that I am Yuki Nagato.
But...
[NAGATO]
At the same time, I'm not.
I don't recognize
my memories as my own.
[doorbell rings]
[ASAKURA]
The rain just won't stop.
[ASAKURA] We've got
curry for dinner today.
[NAGATO]
I know her.
Her name is Ryoko Asakura.
She's my friend.
Yuki Nagato's friend.
[ASAKURA]
You know,
this curry would be good
with a pickle relish.
I could whip one up now,
if we have any pickles.
Hm? Is something wrong?
[ASAKURA] What? You almost
got hit by a car?
[NAGATO]
She's a little like a mother,
helping Yuki out
with everyday things.
[ASAKURA]
You're hurt!
I'm okay.
No! I can see your injuries.
You should undress.
Are there more?
[NAGATO]
She can be pushy.
You're overreacting.
[ASAKURA]
"Overreacting"?
I am not overreacting!
Yeah, okay, the car
didn't actually hit you,
and you're just a
little banged up.
[NAGATO]
Whatever her flaws,
she's genuinely
concerned for me.
You're right. I'm sorry.
[NAGATO] Or rather, she's
genuinely concerned for Yuki.
[NAGATO]
But that... isn't me.
[doorbell rings]
[KYON]
Morning!
[ASAKURA]
Good morning!
[inaudible]
[NAGATO]
I know him.
I know that boy.
[KYON]
What book are you reading?
Le M-Me-Mys-Mystere de la--
Right. Looks good.
[NAGATO] I don't really
know how to talk to him.
It feels sort of awkward.
I know how Yuki
feels about him,
but I'm not sure what
to do about that.
You know, I heard
about yesterday.
Sounds rough.
[gasps]
[NAGATO]
Did Asakura tell you?
[KYON]
Hm? Well, yeah.
[NAGATO] While I'm aware
of Yuki's feelings for him,
my current self cannot
actually feel them.
[NAGATO]
Oh.
So, how are you feeling?
[NAGATO] Although,
from the way he behaves,
I can tell that he
cares about me, too.
[KYON]
Uh, what's the matter?
[NAGATO]
Just to be sure.
Are you worried about me?
What kind of question is that?
Of course I am!
[NAGATO]
He's just a nice person.
There's no special
meaning behind this.
But, I think...
Uh--
[NAGATO] It's this side
of his personality
that Yuki is the
most attracted to.
[NAGATO] Nothing around me is
any different than before.
Well, what do you think of it?
Should we add a
little more cheese?
No, this is fine.
Yeah?
[NAGATO] We're eating dinner
just like we always do.
But...
[NAGATO]
I don't think it's silly.
It's nice of you
to worry about me.
[ASAKURA] Well, that's
what friends are for.
[NAGATO] But I'm not her.
I'm not the same Yuki as before.
[ASAKURA]
Actually...
There is just one more thing.
Who are you?
And where's Nagato?
[NAGATO]
Another thing about her.
She's very perceptive.
In a way, you're still Nagato.
But in a way, not.
I can feel you're
a different person.
Can you explain what's going on?
Because I don't understand.
I'm very sorry. I wish I could
make sense of it. Truly.
But I don't know
who I am, either.
From what I can tell,
it doesn't seem like the
same thing as memory loss.
It feels like I'm reading
someone else's diary.
While I have the memories,
they don't feel like
my own experiences.
But, since I remember all
the same things Yuki does,
I can pretend to be
her easily enough.
Just because you can pretend
doesn't mean you should.
Why didn't you explain
this to me earlier?
I'm sure it isn't too late
to get you some help.
Let's go to the hospital.
I don't want to.
But why not?
You see me as abnormal.
I'm not the version of Yuki
Nagato that you've come to know.
[gasps]
To you, I'm
essentially a stranger.
But, what about me?
Am I just supposed to accept
that I'm abnormal somehow?
If I do that, I'm lost.
If I do that, I'm totally alone.
And that scares me.
So I'll just be normal.
You're right, I'm sorry.
I didn't think about how this
must be making you feel.
Well, anyway.
I think it's better that
we talked about it.
The longer we let it go on,
the more complicated
it would have become.
I guess I'll just treat you
like I always have, then.
Right, Nagato?
Yes, if that's okay.
Well, it is true that I'd like
to have the old Nagato back.
She is my friend, after all.
But that doesn't mean I should
reject the person you are now.
You're having a hard time.
I understand that you're
confused and scared.
So, you're the person
I should be helping.
The current version of Nagato.
Thank you for that.
But, even so.
Maybe... we can
skip school tomorrow
and go to the hospital instead?
You might feel okay now,
but I still think you should get
checked out, just to be sure.
I'm not rejecting you.
I just wanna know
you're healthy.
That's okay. I'll go.
I'm not scared now.
[DOCTOR] I see some light
abrasions on your head,
but no abnormality
in your brain.
Certainly nothing that
seems life-threatening.
Well, that's good to hear!
[DOCTOR] I think the
symptoms you described are
a temporary dysmnesia
caused by having received
a substantial shock,
but I can't be sure
without further observation.
We'll hospitalize you
for the week and--
Excuse me.
Do you think you could treat
her without hospitalization?
She's been able to live
her normal life just fine,
and I can stay nearby
in case something happens
or she needs me for anything.
I think that'll be better,
if we act like things
are still normal.
[DOCTOR sighs]
All right, we can keep an
eye on her at home, then.
We appreciate it, thanks!
[DOCTOR] It's not like being
hospitalized is a cure-all.
And she'll probably
feel more comfortable
being close to a friend.
[DOCTOR]
Here's the plan:
Your brain organizes
your memories
while you're asleep at night.
So make sure you sleep well.
Eat well, too.
Try to be patient
and take it easy.
[ASAKURA sighs]
That was nerve-wracking!
How are you? Did you
hold up all right?
It helped having
you with me.
That's sweet of you!
Well, time to tell him.
[KYON]
What?
Her personality just changed?
I understand this might be
difficult for you to accept.
But... Hey, what're you doing?
Hey, Nagato, think I
could borrow your game?
[NAGATO]
I don't have it with me.
You're not kidding!
She's totally different!
You didn't need
much convincing!
Well, honestly.
I've been feeling like there was
something wrong since yesterday.
Didn't expect this, though.
[ASAKURA] It might be sort of
inconvenient for a little while.
Nah, I think it'll be fine.
But are you sure you're
okay to come to school?
I mean, it seems like it
might be kind of difficult.
[ASAKURA]
Huh?
[KYON]
Well...
I'm thinking about this from the
current Nagato's perspective.
If she's coming to school,
that means she has to keep
pretending to be
the old Nagato, right?
And pretending to
be someone else
sounds like it could
get pretty exhausting.
Do you think you can do it?
[NAGATO]
I've been thinking about this.
And even if I'm not
the Yuki I was before,
that doesn't change the
fact that I'm still Yuki.
I wanna be normal.
Fair enough!
Well, now we have to tell
Miss Suzumiya and Koizumi.
But I don't think
they'll be here today.
[KYON]
Oh, yeah.
They said they wouldn't be
coming for a while, actually.
Something about refresher
classes before finals.
[ASAKURA]
Ah, yes.
The pressures of being
in a prep school.
[KYON] She said we'd better
be ready for when they're done,
though, because she's got lots
of "fun" plans for the summer.
Let's not forget, we've
got exams to take, too.
A little quiet time is probably
exactly what we need.
Oh! I didn't think to ask
you about your classes.
Have you been able
to follow them so far?
It's been fine.
I may not feel like the personal
memories that I have are mine,
but knowledge is knowledge,
so classes aren't a problem.
I shouldn't be too much
trouble for you.
[sighs]
And I won't do anything
to embarrass the old Yuki
or ruin her academic standing,
if that's what
you're worried about.
[ASAKURA]
Oh, um, I--
[ASAKURA] Is that really
what she thought
I was trying to get at?
Oh, no! That's not
what I was saying.
I'm not worried!
[KYON]
It was just a misunderstanding.
Don't worry about it.
Thanks for saying so.
And even more,
thanks for Nagato.
[KYON]
Hm?
For accepting the fact
that she's changed.
She was afraid to
say anything at first.
I guess she was worried she
might end up alone if she did.
What do you mean "alone"?
She probably figured we would
get all distant from her
if we knew.
We are a little thrown off, but
how could we not be, you know?
[sighs]
You should stop getting
so worked up, though.
Now, I'm not saying that's
going to be easy for you to do.
But you should try.
You're too worried about her.
I bet she can sense that,
and it's making her even more
nervous than she already was.
Stop acting like it's only me.
You're every bit
as worried as I am.
You might as well admit it.
[KYON]
Pot, kettle. Kettle, pot.
Nice to meet you.
[ASAKURA] Stop it, what do
you think we should do?
More than anything,
I want her to go back
to being her old self,
but I don't wanna just
abandon the current Nagato.
Well, we'll keep being
her friends, then.
Was it even a question?
Of course we're going to!
[door clicks]
[KYON]
You want something to drink?
I'll even let you choose.
I've got tea or, uh...
Huh.
[NAGATO]
Huh?
Uh, sorry to interrupt.
Maybe you're not thirsty.
You don't mind if I have one?
[KYON]
Of course not!
[NAGATO]
Then, I'll take the tea.
[KYON]
You really like books, huh?
[NAGATO]
Yes. I enjoy reading.
[KYON]
Yeah, I noticed.
Maybe you'd like to go
to the library sometime.
[KYON]
Hmm? You okay?
[NAGATO]
That sounds nice.
Great!
We'll have a library
day. It's a promise.
[alarm beeps]
[NAGATO]
I had a dream.
But I don't remember it.
I have no idea
what it was about.
[doorbell rings]
Good morning. How are
you, sleepy-head?
I stayed up really
late last night.
I guess it's books
now instead of games.
Maybe you're just meant
to be a night owl.
I'll get a nice
breakfast ready for us.
You go wash your face.
[NAGATO]
Okay, thanks.
[ASAKURA] How many pieces
of toast would you like?
[NAGATO]
Just one, please.
[ASAKURA]
I'll take care of the dishes.
You can go change.
Okay.
[stomach growls]
[ASAKURA]
Mm?
[ASAKURA] I'll take care of the
dishes and make some more toast.
You can go change.
[NAGATO]
'Kay.
[ASAKURA chuckles]
Well, I guess her
appetite's the same.
[KYON]
Well, I made it.
[ASAKURA]
Hm? You were almost late.
That's been happening
a lot lately.
I've been working really
hard for the exams.
[ASAKURA]
Oh?
You don't seem worried,
though, honor student.
Must be nice.
Well, I have to work really
hard to look this confident,
so I've got a lot
of stress stored up
that you may not see at first.
But, I do have my limits,
and when I get there,
it's not too pretty.
Oh, yeah? What's gonna happen?
[ASAKURA]
No way to know.
One day the pressure
will make me snap.
Maybe I'll come up and
stab you from behind.
Okay, you're starting
to freak me out.
But listen, should we
be worried about Nagato?
With classes? You
heard her yesterday.
She says she's doing fine.
We're just going to
have to trust her.
It's just that we have PE today.
[ASAKURA] Hm. That could
present a problem.
We'll have to keep an
extra-close eye on her!
[chuckles nervously]
[TEACHER] So, who would
like to solve this for us?
Nagato, come on up.
Okay.
[ASAKURA, KYON]
Uh-oh!
[ASAKURA] I was worried about
whether she could follow
what the teachers were saying.
[KYON] But I didn't think
about this possibility!
It becomes "boingy"
then "tight-ish"!
--Get ready.
--Right.
So what's our plan
if this goes south?
[NAGATO]
There, I'm finished.
[TEACHER]
Yep, that's right.
[ASAKURA, KYON]
Huh?
What's wrong with
you two? Sit back down.
Impressive! That
was a good time.
Huh. I always thought of Nagato
as a slower-moving sorta girl,
but that looked pretty fast.
Oh. She's a speed demon.
I did something wrong?
[ASAKURA]
Huh? What're you talking about?
[NAGATO] You're giving me
that worried look again.
[chuckles] Am I
really that obvious?
I am, aren't I?
[NAGATO]
Yes, a little.
I'm sorry. I'm trying
not to worry, I promise,
but it's pretty
difficult for me.
You ran really well,
though, so good job!
[NAGATO]
Thank you.
I guess we didn't have anything
to worry about after all.
That's good.
Yeah, it is.
And I don't think anybody's
noticed the difference.
Even so.
I could probably stand
to be more authentic.
--[ASAKURA] Huh?
--[KYON] Hm?
Ahhh!
Um, are you okay?
[KYON]
What the heck was that?
[NAGATO] That's something
Yuki says a lot.
It's one of the memories
of hers that I have.
Ahhh!
[chuckles]
Um, you did a good job answering
that math question, too.
Clear and concise.
I knew I could do math, easily.
But I didn't think I could
explain well if I was called on,
so I read the textbook and
reviewed some of the problems.
That was a good idea.
[ASAKURA]
A textbook.
Was that what she was
up so late reading?
She's really trying
not to let it show,
but she's doing her best to
play the part of Yuki Nagato.
That was a delicious lunch.
[stomach growls]
[ASAKURA, KYON]
Huh?
Here. If you want,
you can have some of mine.
I'll make some more next time.
And the same goes for breakfast.
I'm happy to do it.
I like cooking, so don't
ever hesitate to ask.
Oh, um, it's not like that.
Oh?
I was too embarrassed
to ask you.
That's understandable.
Asakura can be very
judgmental sometimes.
[ASAKURA]
What? Really?
Oh, I'm sorry.
[KYON]
Hm... Huh? Huh?!
Argh! I'll never
understand this!
Studying?
Yeah, exams and all.
[NAGATO]
Can I see?
Sure.
[NAGATO] You just have to bring
this number over here. See?
That's amazing! Thank you!
So, how about this one?
[NAGATO] You just need to solve
this part, then this one.
[KYON]
Nice!
Okay, okay! Do this one next!
[NAGATO]
Like this.
[KYON]
Oooohhh!
Heh, heh, heh.
This is excellent.
I can just have Nagato
teach me everything.
I won't have to endure
Asakura's dirty looks anymore
whenever I ask her for
help with my homework.
[NAGATO]
He's up to something.
Still. It's nice
that he wants my help.
It feels good.
Oh. I didn't know
you guys were still here.
With exams coming up,
club activities are
cancelled, starting today.
[KYON]
Huh?
The teacher should've told
you about it in homeroom.
What are you waiting
for? Get goin'.
You didn't know?
I didn't.
I was actually reading
a book during homeroom.
[KYON] And I was just
sort of spacing out.
Guess that explains
why Asakura didn't come.
Weird that she didn't
mention it, though.
[NAGATO]
Grocery shopping usually takes
all of her attention
after school.
[KYON]
Yeah, that's true.
Not sure what to do now.
There are more problems
I wanted to ask about.
It would be easier if we
could just use the clubroom.
[NAGATO]
There's your promise.
[KYON]
My promise?
You said we'd
go to the library.
We could go now.
Yeah, that sounds
like a good idea.
Now's the perfect time.
Okay, let's go!
[NAGATO]
Next episode:
"The Disappearance of
Nagato Yuki Part II."