[NAGATO breathes heavily]
[breathing continues]
[ASAKURA]
Hello there!
Hmm.
Looks like she's taking
a nap. We can't have that!
Sleeping Beauty's in
for a rude awakening.
[KYON] Or you could, you know,
wake her up nicely.
[ASAKURA]
Rise and shine!
[NAGATO]
Ow!
Good morning, Princess!
It's about time for
the club meeting.
[NAGATO]
That hurt.
If my growth is stunted,
I'm blaming you.
[ASAKURA] Yeah, I think
I'm all right with that.
You'll be cuter if you
stay pint-size, anyway.
That's not nice.
[KYON]
Hey, Nagato. Are you okay? Here.
Come on.
Uh-- Ah!
Th-Thank you, Kyon.
[KYON]
Hm?
[ASAKURA] Hm... You know you're
still holding his hand, right?
[gasps]
--[NAGATO gasps] Uh, sorry.
--[KYON yelps]
[ASAKURA] Well then, I'll just
be heading out now. Bye!
[NAGATO]
Ah...
But aren't you coming
to the clubroom?
[ASAKURA]
Sorry, I have to miss today.
There are some errands
I need to run.
But don't worry,
I'll still come over
to your place to cook dinner.
Great!
Oh, and, Kyon?
When club activities
are all wrapped up,
maybe you could
walk her home, 'kay?
And you're welcome to stay
for dinner, of course.
I'm off! Market, here
I come! Woo-hoo!
Hm. Sale days get her excited.
Uh-huh.
Well, off to the
clubroom, huh?
Oh!
[KYON]
Well, it's official.
[NAGATO]
What is?
Just that I've been a member
of the Literary Club
for a full week now.
So, do I get a
cake or something?
You like it so far?
Hm... Well, I'm not really sure
why I joined, honestly.
I basically just read
or do my homework, so.
It's pretty much the same stuff
I'd be doing if I wasn't in it.
[NAGATO gasps]
[music plays]
[NAGATO grunts]
--[school bell rings]
--[gasps]
[yawns] And thus ends another
productive club meeting.
I guess Literary Clubs aren't
much on variety, are they?
I don't think that's fair.
[KYON]
U-Uh--! Sorry!
I'm sure real Literary Clubs
are quite different.
Hold on, are you telling
me I joined a fake club?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[NAGATO]
Maybe this is boring to you.
We don't do much in the way of
traditional club activities.
But I'd rather read here,
where I can listen
to the noise and laughter
of the other clubs,
than sitting alone
at home with my book.
I find it sort of comforting.
That's why I started the club.
What I'm getting at is that
you joining wasn't pointless.
[KYON]
Uh--
[NAGATO] You're the whole reason
the Literary Club still exists.
I'd be alone without you.
You're an important part
of the club, you know?
So, thank you.
I mean it. I, um...
[gasps]
This last week...
It's been really great!
[KYON] Yeah. So, anyway,
we should get going!
[NAGATO]
Mm-hm!
[NAGATO gasps]
What is it?
It's almost Christmas!
Which means we need
to start planning
for the club Christmas party.
[KYON] Fake clubs still
have parties? That's cool.
[NAGATO]
Can we?
You're the one running the show.
You are the club
president, right?
Yep!
[gasps]
Was that someone you know?
Just imagining things.
[NAGATO] This is the story of
a somewhat shy, bookish girl.
[KYON]
The light is changing! Let's go!
[NAGATO]
Whoops.
[NAGATO] Oh! We'll need
a turkey, for sure.
[KYON]
Turkey?
Oh, are we still talking
about the Christmas party?
[NAGATO]
Yeah.
You can't have a party
without a turkey, you know?
Oh, is that a thing?
[NAGATO]
Yeah!
[shrieks]
[KYON]
Wow...
I didn't think my
hand was that cold.
I'm sorr--
I'm sorry for interrupting
this little romantic
comedy moment.
So, Asakura, how'd
you do at the sale?
A good haul.
I may have gone overboard.
My hands hurt.
Will you carry these for me?
Hand 'em over.
[ASAKURA]
Thanks!
Watch this part carefully.
[NAGATO]
What?
Here.
These are heavy!
You did buy a lot!
Ow, ow, ow! So cold and sore.
My poor hands.
I hate this time
of year, don't you?
[KYON gasps]
--[KYON] They're like ice cubes!
--There! Much warmer!
Now, now, stop thrashing.
You don't wanna
break the eggs.
[KYON]
You tricked me! I call foul!
[ASAKURA]
Let's review.
You see an opening
and you make your move.
Aggressively. Got it?
[NAGATO gasps] Incredible!
That's some high-level flirting.
Well, are you guys
coming or not?
Yes, Wise Master!
[ASAKURA]
Oh, don't call me that.
Hey.
[ASAKURA humming]
I gotta say, that freaks me out.
There's something about the
way you wield that knife...
Hey, Nagato?
[NAGATO]
Just a sec. What is it?
Well, I heard a rumor.
About a certain club
Christmas party.
Yeah! What do you think?
I hate to burst your bubble,
but I don't think
it's going to work.
Not in the clubroom, anyway.
The school won't let us.
If you're so set on a party,
why don't we just have
it at home, instead?
That way we have
everything we need.
I wanna have it
in the clubroom, okay?
Can we please just
leave it at that?
[ASAKURA]
Hm?
[KYON] I admit it: this
looks pretty darn good,
even the vegetables.
[ASAKURA giggles] With veggies,
it's all in how you cut them.
[KYON]
Mm!
[ASAKURA chuckles]
Have an egg, Nagato.
Go on, I bet you'll like it.
Oh. Thanks.
So. Back to the party idea.
Why do you wanna hold
it in the clubroom?
[gaggs]
[gasps]
Are you all right?
Oh, no! Your cute
sweater got all stained!
Come on, hurry!
We need to get it
in the wash quickly.
Um. I can undress myself.
But it's easier without
stuff in my hands.
[laughs] You two are
really close, aren't you?
[ASAKURA]
This stuff is dangerous.
One clumsy move
with a chopstick,
and you're covered
in boiling broth.
Nagato is always--
Huh?
[screams]
[KYON]
S-Sorry! Sorry!
[ASAKURA shrieks] I forgot
that Kyon was here, too!
[KYON]
You think she's okay?
Get in there! Go!
[yelps]
Hey, how ya doin'?
Is this seat taken?
Okay, great!
--[NAGATO] Uh...
--[KYON] I...
--Oh!
--Uh!
No, you first. Go on.
Oh! I was just...
I wanted to know...
How much did you see?
[KYON]
Strike one!
Some pitchers begin with
a couple of warm-up throws,
but not this one! Nope, it's
straight to the curve ball!
I guess beating around
the bush isn't her style.
Well, I saw... Uh... Your belly!
Just your waist, I mean!
That's really all?
Totally! I didn't see
anything else, I promise!
[KYON]
Let's see if she bought it.
[NAGATO]
Okay. That's good, then.
[KYON]
Hook, line, and sinker!
[sighs]
Um. I do have just one
more question, though.
Yeah, shoot.
The toughest one's
out of the way.
So you saw my stomach.
What'd you think?
[KYON] That question's
a conversational landmine!
And I'm about to get
blown to pieces.
[NAGATO]
What's he gonna say?
I think boys like
a little more... meat.
[KYON] If I say I liked it,
then I'm the creepy guy
who likes her stomach.
But if I say I didn't, then
I'm the jerk who insulted her.
I can't do this on my own!
[KYON]
I can't say that!
Calm down!
You're blowing this
way out of proportion.
It's not like you're a bad guy.
You've got nothing to hide.
Just tell her the truth,
and it'll be fine.
[KYON]
Your stomach's nice.
I-I mean, I don't think there's
anything wrong with it.
It's not like I have
a stomach fetish.
[NAGATO]
Hm? Stomach fetish? What's that?
[KYON]
Mm...
Nothing! I'm an idiot
who talks too much.
Forget I said anything,
okay? I'm begging you!
Uh. Yeah. Sure.
[KYON sighs]
There's gotta be something else
we can talk about.
New subject. New subject.
So, why's it so important
that we have the party
in the actual clubroom?
Wouldn't it make more
sense to have it here,
like Asakura said?
[gasps]
[NAGATO]
It wouldn't be the same.
The party isn't really
about Christmas.
It's about celebrating
the club itself.
With a party?
Yeah. That's right.
To celebrate the fact
that there is a club.
That you guys joined.
That we're all
doing this together.
[ASAKURA] And you think the
best place to have a party
for the club is in
the clubroom, huh?
That's right.
Having it there would
mean a lot to me.
If that's the case,
I guess it can't be helped.
Okay, then. Let's do it!
Really?
[ASAKURA] Yes! I'm a member
of the Literary Club.
If you're serious about this,
I'll do whatever I can
to help you make
it happen, President!
[ASAKURA]
Where should we start?
What's the most important
part of the party?
A turkey!
[ASAKURA]
There's a lot of oden left!
Come on, we can't
let it go to waste.
[KYON]
Subject change!
[NAGATO]
Right!
[KYON]
Hey, it worked!
[NAGATO] No, wait. I was
talking about turkey.
We need to get a turkey!
[SHOP OWNER A]
Nope, you're outta luck.
We don't carry turkeys here.
No room for that
kinda thing, y'know?
Yeah, I sorta figured that.
Sorry. I can give
you a great deal
on chicken wings, though!
Really? I love a good bargain!
[SHOP OWNER A] Sure! And I'll
throw in something extra.
Thanks so much!
That's wonderful!
Hey! I got a really
good deal, you guys.
[KYON]
Chicken wings? Really?
If you've got your heart
set on a whole bird,
we're gonna have to go
to a bigger store.
It's a little far away,
but I'm game.
[gasps]
I had no idea that
something like a turkey
could complicate things so much.
[sighs]
[ASAKURA] I'm sure you
thought things through
pretty carefully when
you were coming up with
this whole Christmas party idea.
Except...
...I think this turkey
obsession has more
to do with appetite
than anything else.
Admit it! You've just got
a big, fat turkey craving!
Nuh-uh! I--
I thought it would be
festive and memorable.
Plenty of people have turkey
for the holidays, you know.
It's not that weird.
Oh, look, I've got a piece
of fried mincemeat cake,
courtesy of my friend
the butcher over there.
[gasps] Okay, I admit it!
I just wanted turkey!
[ASAKURA] Mm-hm! I will
reward you for your honesty.
[NAGATO]
Thank you! Thank you!
That didn't take much.
[TSURUYA laughs]
That's a classic tactic.
[gasps]
[TSURUYA] The old
carrot-and-stick approach.
And it worked like a charm, too!
[MIKURU]
She's such a good friend!
[KYON] I-I didn't see you
lovely ladies standing there!
Miss Tsuruya. Miss Asahina.
Nice to see you!
Kyon.
Surely you aren't suggesting
that we aren't allowed
to come shopping here, are you?
[KYON]
No! I wouldn't dare.
Well, I think I can guess why
seeing us has shaken
your composure so much.
Huh?
[TSURUYA] Just look at the
company you're keeping!
Who are these little cuties?
I take my eyes off
you for a second,
and this is what you do?
That's not very loyal
for a card-carrying
member of the Mikuru Fan Club!
Huh?!
[KYON]
Since when did I join that club?
Wow, that's a terrible picture.
Although your initial approach
left a lot to be desired,
your fervor was such that
I hoped you might one day
become a leader within the club.
[NAGATO]
Stop it!
[GROUP gasps]
[NAGATO]
I mean, please.
What's the matter?
[ASAKURA]
Aww.
Nagato's really
fighting for her man!
But...
[NAGATO muffled]
[ASAKURA]
How many times have I told you
not to talk with your mouth
full? It's just unattractive!
You have to decide! Eat or talk!
What was that?
[ASAKURA]
Agreed!
You understood her?
[panting]
[CROWD]
Please, can you just go now?
Oh? You're ready to
talk now, Glasses?
It takes some chops to lure away
our fan club member like that.
I didn't lure anybody anywhere.
No? Then what are you doing?
Literary Club stuff, okay?
We're having a Christmas party,
and there are a lot of
things we need to do.
Like finding a whole turkey.
Which means going to a
bigger store, and, you know.
Lots of other places to
do some other things, so.
[KYON]
Uh--
[NAGATO]
So, we're going now!
You need a turkey?
[NAGATO]
We're in a hurry, so goodbye.
[TSURUYA]
My family ordered extra.
We could give you one.
[NAGATO grunting]
[KYON] Hm... She wants
to give in so badly,
I think it's
actually hurting her.
[NAGATO gasps]
[KYON]
She's basically a nice person.
Go on, take the turkey.
You know you want to.
Miss Tsuruya's family
throws a Christmas party
every year, and they
always have extra.
[NAGATO] Oh, well, if it's
really no trouble, then--
[ASAKURA]
No! Stop right there!
You poor, gullible child!
She may be acting nice now,
but she is the enemy!
Don't forget it! Ever!
You wanna take
the easy way out?
Well, tough turkey!
See what I did there? Turkey!
She wants the bird.
Just let her have it!
I like how you think!
[NAGATO]
Huh?
[TSURUYA] I mean, life's not
all kittens and rainbows!
Things are tough.
Obviously, I wasn't
going to hand over
a turkey to you for free!
There, you see?
There's no such thing as a
free lunch, not in this world!
[KYON]
If it wasn't for you,
we'd be heading home
with a turkey right now.
[ASAKURA]
So. What do we have to do?
I have the perfect idea.
I hope you're ready
for this, Glasses.
I'm gonna see what
kinda game you have.
[gasps]
[TSURUYA] Since Kyon's choosing
between you and Mikuru,
I need to see what you can do.
Uh, what am I
choosing for, exactly?
The best way to see
what you're capable of
is to have you
compete against Mikuru.
No thank you!
I don't wanna play!
I accept!
Huh?
[ASAKURA] If it helps, think
of this as a shoujo manga.
You're the main character's
childhood friend, right?
And another woman is trying
to snatch him away!
Only, you're not actually
Kyon's childhood friend,
so you don't even have
that going for you!
Okay. I think I got it!
Now, Nagato! Fight for
all you're worth!
Don't hold anything back!
[NAGATO]
I understand, Master!
[ASAKURA]
Quit calling me that!
[TSURUYA]
Soliciting competition!
Go get 'em, ladies!
Um. S-Scallions
are on sale today!
Good for hot pot! They're tasty!
Oh! Radishes are good
in hot pot, too!
--I know we have some.
--For the next hour only,
--Let's see.
--get a reduced price
--I thought they were--
--on napa--
[BOTH]
Wrong!
[ASAKURA] See, Nagato!
Hold the sign higher, like this!
And Mikuru, you need
to make yourself heard!
[TSURUYA, ASAKURA] Veggies
for sale! Come and get 'em!
[TSURUYA] Running competition!
Let's work those legs!
[NAGATO, MIKURU panting]
[MIKURU] Can you please
slow down a little?
[TSURUYA]
This may be the one time when
Mikuru's breasts
are a disadvantage.
[panting]
[MAN 1A]
If I never-- Ah!
[NAGATO] I-I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
[MIKURU] I can't... run...
any... further...
[MIKURU, NAGATO panting]
--[ASAKURA] That's pathetic!
--[TSURUYA] Wrong again!
[ASAKURA, TSURUYA panting]
Nagato! You have to look
where you're going!
Mikuru! Keep those breasts
nice and high when you run!
Remind me again
which two of you
were supposed to be competing?
[TSURUYA]
Cooking competition!
If you can't take the heat,
get out of the kitchen!
[TSURUYA]
All right, everybody!
Pick the person you think
would make the better owner!
[DOGS barking]
[TSURUYA]
Flower arranging competition!
Not for pansies!
[ASAKURA]
Well, it's been fun.
You put up a good
fight, Miss Tsuruya.
[TSURUYA cackles] You weren't
too bad yourself, actually.
I guess next time we'll need
to have a tie-breaking round.
Lookin' forward to
kickin' your butt!
[ASAKURA, TSURUYA laugh]
You guys are nuts.
You know that, right?
Hey, Nagato.
So what do you wanna
do with the turkey?
Hello! Nagato?
The turkey?
Oh. I'll ask Asakura.
I'm sure she'll know what to do.
[NAGATO]
A Christmas cake...
I definitely want
at least four tiers.
[KYON]
Hey! Another freezing day, huh?
So cold.
[NAGATO]
No, five tiers.
--Yes, I think...
--[KYON] Talking to yourself?
[NAGATO]
I'm working on the party plans.
[gasps] Wh-When
did you get here?
[NAGATO]
He's so close!
[KYON]
Hey, can I have a look?
Ahh! No! Go away!
Get out of here!
[NAGATO]
Or I'll die of embarrassment.
What did I do?
[NAGATO] I-I'm sorry. I'll
show you when it's done.
Please, just step back?
[KYON]
Sure. Okay.
[NAGATO] I'm the one who
insisted on this party.
I have to deliver.
It's gotta be the
best party ever.
[NAGATO]
And next time...
[KYON]
I've got a question.
Yes?
[KYON] What're we gonna
do about the tree?
Asakura's on it.
She invited those girls
we met at the mall
the other day to the party.
And the bossy one said
she'd get a tree for us.
Yeah, I remember her.
She and Asakura sure
have a lot in common.
Well, I'm happy to
help carry it here.
Oh, thanks.
I hate to ask you
to do manual labor.
[KYON]
I really don't mind helping.
I'm actually looking
forward to this party.
Really? Well, I'm glad.
[NAGATO]
Wow, I can't believe it!
He's looking forward
to my party!
Um, in that case, just
forget what I said earlier.
Would you like to
help out with the plans?
[KYON]
Sure. I'm happy to.
Hm...
Well, first of all,
no scattering snow in the
clubroom. It'll just melt.
[NAGATO sighs]
--As for the cake...
--[NAGATO] Just four tiers?
That's like a wedding cake!
Wha-- Huh?
--W-Wait! Wedding?
--Fine. Two tiers.
--But that's the absolute most.
--W-Wait! Wedding?
[KYON]
Now about this dress.
[NAGATO]
I want pure white!
It's a wedding dress!
It's not!
Maybe we should just table
the dress for now, okay?
[NAGATO]
Mm-hm.
Hey, you guys!
Hey, Asakura.
[KYON]
You're late. Where've you been?
[ASAKURA giggles]
How do you like them apples?
[KYON]
No way!
[ASAKURA] It says we can use
the clubroom on Christmas.
I just kept bugging
them until they caved.
I thought we were just gonna
have to sneak in here
after hours. Good job!
Well, being an honor student
does open some doors.
Now that it's official,
I think that we can go all-out.
So, what have you guys
been up to today?
We're trying to hash
out party decorations.
Yeah? What do you have so far?
[ASAKURA]
Oh?
So, what do you think?
[ASAKURA] Hm... I think
these look pretty good.
Seriously?
Well, there might be one or two
suggestions I would make.
But I know Nagato's been
working really hard on this,
and I wouldn't wanna
seem too controlling.
Huh?
Hey!
If you have something to say,
I think now's the time.
[ASAKURA]
Oh yeah? Well...
A cake with four tiers?
[KYON] I was able to
get it down to two.
[ASAKURA]
And the snow in the clubroom?
[KYON]
"Yuki" means snow, right?
[ASAKURA]
Huh?
[KYON] That's why she's
always so chilly!
[ASAKURA] Do you know
how bad that joke was?
[KYON]
It wasn't that bad.
[ASAKURA]
Awful.
[NAGATO] It'll be fun.
I'll make it a good party.
And when I do, maybe...
[KYON]
Hey there. Let me help you.
Here, gimme that book.
You want a library card, right?
I'll go take care of it for you.
[NAGATO]
Ah--
[KYON]
Hey. Nagato.
Huh?
Don't worry. The
party'll be great.
[gasps] Yep!
[NAGATO]
And maybe... I'll tell him...
...how I feel about him.
[NAGATO] Next episode:
"Joy to the World."