[ASAKURA grumbles]
[HARUHI]
Attention!
The club's going
to a hot spring!
That's where our
training camp is gonna be.
[KYON]
Wait, what's going on?
[HARUHI]
Here!
[KYON]
And this is...?
"The North High Literary Club
and Kouyouen Academy
Joint Training Camp."
This says it's a trip journal?
What is this? Like a guidebook?
[KYON] Man, look at this.
It's really elaborate.
[KOIZUMI] Looks like it's
even got a step-by-step
description of our route.
A hot spring sounds nice!
Look at that price, though.
Not sure I trust
someplace so inexpensive.
Oh yeah, I know.
[cackles]
Miss Tsuruya's family
has rooms at the inn
they rent throughout the year,
so we got 'em on the cheap.
[KYON]
I've got a question.
Now what?
[KYON] This is supposed to
be like a guidebook, right?
What's this?
Because it looks like it's a
report on how the trip went.
Well, look at that.
Yeah, it sure does.
Whoa! It's got my
thoughts in it!
Hey, What's going on here?
[chuckles] It's not my fault
you got the wrong idea.
I never said it was a guidebook.
Well, tell us what
it really is, then.
It's the report on our camp.
The one we'll submit to
our respective schools.
We can't just say,
"We went on a trip
and it was great!"
Things don't work like that.
We're the Literary Club, right?
So it's only appropriate that
we create a written report
to turn in when we're done.
It'll prove how much we've
grown as a result of our trip.
Academic growth
is the whole point
of this little
getaway, after all!
At least, that's what
I told our schools
when I was getting permission.
I thought my arm
was gonna fall off
making those for everyone.
Only you. Really. Only you.
[sighs] If we have
to submit a report,
shouldn't we all work
together to write it
after the training camp?
You don't get it, do you?
All right, let me see if
I can make this clearer.
Take summer homework
for example.
You end up dreading it
over your whole vacation,
which totally ruins your fun.
However, take care of it first,
and the problem's solved!
So that's precisely what I did!
So now this trip can be
all about having fun.
Ya got that? F-U-N!
You have so much energy.
Have you ever
thought about doing
something productive with it?
[laughs] That's Miss Suzumiya.
It's all part of what makes
her so charming, ya know?
I feel bad.
You did everything.
Planned the whole trip,
wrote reports for everybody...
I'm supposed to
be the president.
And what did I do?
[HARUHI]
Seriously.
Why do you always have
to be such a downer?
I did this because I wanted to.
I mean, why else would I do it?
It's not like I had to.
So we're good now, right?
Huh?
I'd listen to her
if I were you.
If she didn't feel like
doing it, she would have
no problem dumping it
on the rest of us.
Wait a minute! That's enough!
Anyway, I figure there's
a good chance our teachers
will ask about the reports
later, so you'll wanna
be sure to read your own
so you'll know what you wrote.
Well, I'm off to give these
to Miss Tsuruya
and Miss Asahina.
Oh. Hold on,
I'll come with you.
I need to say thank
you to Miss Tsuruya.
Yeah, good idea. I'll come, too.
Well, in that case,
maybe we should all go.
[ASAKURA] She's in the
middle of club activities.
We don't need to send a
whole parade of people.
The two of us can
thank her for everyone.
It'll be fine.
Good point. We'll
wait here, then.
[ASAKURA]
Cool.
[HARUHI]
What? Whoa, you're kidding!
He was feeding Yuki?
I didn't realize they had
become that much closer!
I also saw them in
each other's arms.
No way!
Well, let's remember who
we're talking about here.
Knowing those two,
I'd say there's a pretty
decent chance that
it was an accident.
Yeah. Knowing them,
that is a possibility.
So that could be a fluke.
Just something to
think about, I guess.
What I'm really concerned
about is him feeding her.
[HARUHI] But that seems
more harmless than him
grabbing her or them
getting all snuggly.
[ASAKURA] More of a
friendly gesture, maybe.
But what if it wasn't?
I mean, it could
have been anything.
[HARUHI]
I guess.
[ASAKURA] If they announced
they were officially dating,
I wouldn't be so worried
about that, you know?
That's not true, I would!
[HARUHI]
That sounds more like you.
[ASAKURA] Ah. Maybe this trip
isn't such a good idea.
To them, it could be less
of an academic trip
and more of a chance to
spend quality time together.
[ASAKURA] What do I do
if they get caught up
and cross the line?
It'll be fine.
[ASAKURA]
Don't forget: this is them!
They could go into the
coed bath by mistake.
[HARUHI]
That's not gonna happen.
[ASAKURA]
Oh, no!
What if they get into
the same bed by mistake?
[HARUHI]
Relax!
I got separate rooms
for the guys and girls.
[ASAKURA]
What if they go out stargazing?
Would that really
even be a mistake?
It's the kind of thing
that only happens
in romantic comedies, but with
them, it could really happen!
I promise: it's serious!
[HARUHI] Just sounds like
foreshadowing to me.
[ASAKURA] Maybe I am getting
a little too worked up, here.
Now that I think
about it calmly,
the answer is actually simple.
Huh?
I'll just watch them
without them knowing
and make sure they behave.
It's as easy as that!
Isn't that called stalking?
Nagato and Kyon deserve
to have a relationship
that is pure and beautiful.
And we're gonna make sure
that happens, aren't we?
[HARUHI] Hey, hold on!
Since when am I part of it?
All right! I feel
much better now.
Hey! Come back here!
Ugh. What's with her?
So be it then.
I guess it'll be a different
sorta training camp.
[HARUHI]
Here's your ticket.
[NAGATO]
Oh, thank you.
So where's everybody else?
[ASAKURA]
I'm back! Good!
Looks like more people
have joined us.
[HARUHI]
What'd you run to the store for?
What'd you get, some snacks?
Better than that!
Anti-bacterial wipes.
Is that all? Yech.
[TSURUYA]
Heya!
[KOIZUMI] Looks like all
the ladies are here now.
I'm so sorry we're late.
Have you been waiting
for very long?
Nah! You guys are fine,
nothin' to worry about.
Kyon's still not
here, of course.
Hey!
[HARUHI]
You're late!
[KYON panting]
I'm sorry!
Pay the price!
Come on.
It took me forever to
shake off my little sister.
No excuses. You can't get
away without a penalty.
Kyon's treating us, everyone.
[gags, coughs]
Always in such a rush, Haruhi.
That's how you end up
getting burned.
I'll take care of this.
So, anyway--
[coughs]
Just take a second and breathe.
[HARUHI]
The reason why we came here--
[coughs]
[sighs] Now, what was I saying?
Oh, yeah, I remember.
Our destination is in the
middle of the mountains.
We're going to be spending
a long time on the train,
so we need to
think this through.
What's really important?
I'll tell ya what's important!
Who sits with who.
That kind of thing
can really affect
how enjoyable the trip will be.
[gasps]
So, I propose the
following: Tadah!
We'll draw sticks to
determine the seating.
She could be right.
It is a long trip.
What are you waiting
for? Start pickin'!
[KYON]
What'd you do? Color-code them?
Yeah! That should be
clear enough, right?
[KYON] Okay, I'll take
this one.
It's red.
[ASAKURA]
This may appear to be about
seating arrangements,
Nagato. But!
For a girl in love, it's so
much more! This is your chance!
[ASAKURA] You could be
sitting a few inches away
from him the whole time!
What more could you ask for?
No pressure, but the
lot that you select now
could very well determine
your entire future.
[HARUHI]
Okay, your turn, Yuki!
[gasps]
Pick one.
Whoa. I wonder what that is.
Oh, I don't know, Miss Asahina.
I wish I could tell you.
[TSURUYA] Where? What're
you talkin' about?
Show me! Show me!
[KOIZUMI] Oh. That over there?
It's an apple orchard.
[TSURUYA]
Oh, yeah?
Well, I guess the randomness
is the whole point
of drawing lots, huh?
Yeah, trying to pick a certain
one doesn't really work.
Wha--? You mean me?
No, I... I wasn't doing that.
And I'm not
thinking things like:
"I wish I was sitting
next to him," or
"We could've talked so much."
--[NAGATO] Or...
--Emotional eating?
Nope. That never even
crossed my mind at all.
Nagato. Nagato?
Looks good. Could I have some?
Yeah.
Here you go.
Cool. Thank you.
Look at that.
I guess she is sort of sitting
next to him, after all.
[TRAIN ANNOUNCEMENT]
Now boarding Nagano.
[KOIZUMI] Nice to be out
of that train, huh?
Feels good to stretch! Okay!
It's time to have fun!
Well, we're here. So now what?
Do we go straight
to the hot spring?
How far is the inn from here?
Jeez.
Did you even look
at the guidebook?
The inn is set deep in the
heart of the mountains!
So we'll switch to
a van for this leg.
Really?
More traveling?
You wrote that thing.
So, why are you surprised?
I'm not surprised. I'm just
really tired of traveling.
Well, we have some time until
the inn's shuttle gets here.
Anyone want to explore?
[KYON] What're we gonna
do with our bags
while we walk around?
Let me help you with that.
Oh, thank you.
[KYON]
I'll take yours.
Oh. Thank you so much.
[KYON]
All right. We're all set.
Looks like it.
What do you think
we should do first?
Uh, I don't know.
[stomach growls]
[ALL but NAGATO]
Huh?
[KYON]
Well, with all this traveling,
we need all the fuel we can get.
This is really good!
[NAGATO]
Yup!
So the van's coming
to pick us up
some time around dusk?
And, according to
the guidebook,
we're supposed to be visiting a
temple that's nearby until then.
It's not the most
exciting thing.
But yeah, that's what
everybody does.
Here, take a look.
This temple is one of
those places people call
"power spots."
[HARUHI]
What's that?
One of the keirakuhiko
vital points?
"How many hits in the vital
points until you die?"
Power spots are spiritual.
Supposedly, they give you
energy if you visit them.
[HARUHI] You get some
kind of mystical power
just by going there? That's
so totally ridiculous!
Who would believe
that kinda thing?
I mean really, come on!
So, Koizumi. Will
you come with me?
I can't not check out
something called a power spot.
I mean, it's not like I believe
in all that mystical stuff.
Sure. I'm happy to come along.
It's always something
with her, huh?
Okay guys, then we're off!
We'll see you up there!
[ASAKURA]
Hey! Slow down a second!
[EMPLOYEE A]
Thanks, have a nice day!
I don't think she
understands the concept
of traveling in a group.
[KYON] Just accept it.
That's how she is.
And Koizumi can't ever say
no to her, either, so.
[ASAKURA sighs]
[TSURUYA] Well, we know
where she's headed, anyway.
[KYON] Let's not worry
about her for now.
[ASAKURA]
Yeah, you're right.
We should do some sightseeing
while we're here.
Oh? Looks like that's
Zenkoji Temple.
[laughs nervously]
[MIKURU] Do those Nio statues
freak out anybody else,
or is it just me?
[HARUHI] Hmph. I guess
they're pretty impressive,
lookin' all fierce like that.
But, fierce or not, those guys
have got nothin' on me.
Yep, those statues
can not touch you.
You're competing against
statues now? For what?
Ah! What am I thinking?
We're wasting time! Power spot!
Power spot! Power spot!
[KOIZUMI]
You've already got your wish.
This entire temple is
considered to be a power spot.
So, there's--
[HARUHI
We're goin' in!
[KOIZUMI]
Right behind you!
[KYON]
Godspeed.
Wow. There are a lot
of shops around here.
So which should we visit?
Well, they've got food stalls.
We could eat something.
[ASAKURA] Hmm. I don't know
if I'm hungry again yet.
[KYON] Yeah, you're right.
We pretty much just ate. Huh?
[NAGATO] Vegetable. Azuki beans.
Pumpkin. Soba bun.
Vegetable. Azuki beans.
Excuse me! A vegetable
bun, please.
Comin' right up.
[NAGATO]
And, um, azuki beans,
pumpkin and soba
buns, too, please.
[GROUP]
All four?
Ow, that's hot! But so yummy!
[laughs]
Hm? What is it?
Nothing. Don't mind me.
[NAGATO]
Hm?
[KYON] Man. Can't tell
if it's good or not.
She always looks happy
when she's eating.
Huh. This isn't half bad.
[HARUHI]
Yeah, it's pretty good.
Unique, that's for sure.
Uh? You're back.
What happened to the power spot?
Well, it's not like
it's going anywhere.
Hey! Let's try that next!
Brain freeze!
Brain freeze! Ow!
--Ugh. Can't eat any more.
--[HARUHI] Is that a power spot?
--Hey, Kyon.
--[KOIZUMI] Wait up!
Huh?
Were you planning to buy
souvenirs for your family?
Kinda have to.
My little sister will
flip out if I don't.
How 'bout you?
Oh. I'm not sure
yet, actually.
My parents live overseas,
so I don't know.
Well, if you buy them
now, you'll have to
carry them around.
You could always pick up
something later on.
Good call.
[NAGATO]
Whoa. That's a lot.
Those bags must be heavy.
Do you know how many people
I was shopping for?
These are actually
surprisingly light.
[ASAKURA]
Impressive.
Huh.
You know, I feel like I see
those things sold everywhere.
I guess there must be a
market for them, huh?
[NAGATO]
So shiny!
t's even got a face-roller-
massager-thing, too!
You're into some
really weird stuff,
you know that?
Wow! That's so adorable!
Aw! This is really cute, too!
Ah! And look how
precious that is!
[ASAKURA]
She's special.
[TSURUYA laughs] Looks like Haru
and Koizumi wandered off again.
[KYON] Hurricane Haruhi.
She does what she wants.
[ASAKURA]
And there's no stopping her.
So, what exactly are you doing?
What does it look
like I'm doing?
I'm receiving mystical power!
So this is the power spot
you keep talking about?
[HARUHI]
Yeah, this is part of it.
Apparently when you bathe
yourself in this smoke,
your physical strength
goes up one level.
[coughs] I don't know about
increasing physical strength,
but I have heard people
say that the smoke
can heal the parts of your
body that it touches.
Except, I think it's
a bundle of incense
per body part.
Using the same one for a
long time doesn't work.
[HARUHI] Don't worry.
I've got it covered.
I set up a system where Koizumi
throws in another bundle
about every minute.
Okay, it's been a minute.
Are you ready for
the next bundle?
So it's all good.
I'm getting everything the
power spot has to offer!
Okay, that's enough!
[HARUHI]
Ow! Stop!
[ASAKURA]
Step away from the smoke!
Say goodbye to the power spot!
I've got so much
left to do, though!
I only got up to the
bicep of my right arm.
You guys are having
too much fun here!
I've got my hands full.
Please don't complicate things.
Okay, it's been a minute.
Ready for more incense?
Yeah, Koizumi! Bring it on,
[ASAKURA]
We're done with the incense.
Understand? Just give up!
Knock it off!
[ASAKURA]
Quit wiggling!
Do you think we should
go and join them?
Nope.
I think we should pretend
we've never met them before.
That's a good idea.
How about we just go and
pray the regular way?
I saw something about
this on TV one time.
They said when you're
making a wish to the gods,
you want to include as
many details as possible.
Things like, who
you're wishing about
and what you want to happen.
Wait.
Was that at a Shinto shrine
or a Buddhist temple?
Eh, it's probably the same.
[NAGATO]
Who I'm wishing about...
What I want to happen...
[NAGATO]
Who I want it to happen with...
[ASAKURA]
Think I could get some help?
[HARUHI] All right!
The quadriceps are next!
I can't deal with both of them!
[HARUHI] I haven't achieved
physical perfection yet!
Miss Tsuruya, don't
encourage her!
[TSURUYA]
If she can do it, so can I!
It looks like she
needs some backup.
If you guys will excuse
me, I should help.
Go ahead. Don't
worry about us.
I'm sorry about this, Kyon!
Take good care of Miss Tsuruya!
[sighs]
[MIKURU]
Are you done making your wish?
Yes. I'm done.
Well then, why don't we
go check out that shop?
They have some cool amulets.
[NAGATO]
Wow. There are so many!
I have college entrance
exams next year.
Maybe I'll get
something for that.
Ah! What's this?
I like how it looks.
Maybe not.
[sighs]
Uh...
Here, I think this
is the one you want!
Huh?
No thanks!
Go ahead, get it.
I don't think there's
anybody watching.
Okay, tell you what.
There you go!
Now there's really
nobody watching.
That's sweet of you.
Well, go on. Buy it.
Now or never!
[NAGATO] Excuse me. I'd
like to buy this, please.
[sighs]
Help! I'm suffocating
in all this smoke!
Too much smoke!
So now you want less smoke?
I wonder if I'm any stronger!
That's ridiculous.
Come on, aren't we there yet?
I want a bath! I want a bath!
Will you please be quiet?
[TSURUYA laughs]
It's not much further.
We can't get to the
inn soon enough.
[HARUHI] No! I want a bath
right now! Now, now, now, now!
[ASAKURA] Seriously!
You're acting like a child!
[HARUHI]
No, I am not! How dare you!
I just want a bath!
I feel so gross!
[ASAKURA]
Just shut up!
[NAGATO] Next episode:
"A Plot by Haruhi Suzumiya."