[inhales, exhales]
I'm sorry it took
me so lo-- [gasps]
[ASAKURA] She went in!
Good luck! You can do it!
--[clatter]
--Huh?
Huh? Where are you going?
Wait, come back!
[KYON]
Hey. Nagato!
What's going on?
Why did she take off?
[gasps]
Yes. I will stay strong.
U-Uh--
Give that to me!
What do you think you're
doing? This isn't yours!
How dare you!
[KOIZUMI]
Hey there, everyone.
Things seem tense.
Is something wrong?
[HARUHI]
Not at all. Everything's fine.
[growls]
If there was something
wrong. It'd be...
...just a misunderstanding.
Oh, is this chocolate for me?
Thanks. That's very sweet.
[HARUHI] Finding her is what
matters most right now.
You can yell at me later.
Let's get looking.
[sighs] Hold on, I'm coming!
Hey, wait a sec!
[KOIZUMI] I don't think
they're coming back.
I feel like I missed something.
Uh? You got some, too, huh?
Uh--
[HARUHI panting]
[HARUHI]
Hm.
[panting]
[ASAKURA] She could be anywhere.
How am I gonna find her?
[TENNIS PLAYER A]
Okay, let's see it!
[TENNIS PLAYER B]
All right, let's go!
[TENNIS PLAYER A]
And... go!
[TENNIS COACH A]
Good serve!
[ASAKURA]
Well, any luck?
[HARUHI]
Mm-mm.
[ASAKURA sighs]
[HARUHI]
I'm not going to apologize.
I gave him some chocolate,
what's the big deal?
It's Valentine's.
That's what people do.
[TENNIS PLAYER A]
Sorry 'bout that!
[TENNIS COACH A]
Focus! Focus!
[TENNIS PLAYER A]
Yes, sir!
[ASAKURA]
That's not true.
It's a lot more
complicated than that,
and you know it!
You know it's about more than
some stupid holiday
to her! Come on!
Even if it was just
a friendly gift.
why give it to him before her
when you know what
she had planned?
I really think
you're overreacting.
Mine was obviously platonic,
so why does the
timing even matter?
You really don't get it, do you?
But I guess you wouldn't, huh?!
When you want something,
you just make it happen,
regardless of other people.
How was I supposed to
know it was a big deal?
Pay attention for two seconds!
I do pay attention!
[gasps]
[ASAKURA]
I'm just so angry.
[ASAKURA] I don't know what
to do with all this anger.
[ASAKURA sobs]
I told her what to do and how,
like I was some expert.
And then when it fell apart,
I blamed somebody else.
I'm a real piece of work.
I'm so, so mad at myself.
[sighs]
Take it easy.
You're gonna cry
yourself to death. Okay?
Pull yourself together.
This isn't like you.
[HARUHI]
Hm?
[growls]
[BOTH scream]
Okay! No more wasting
time on regrets!
I just have to learn from
my mistakes, that's all!
Time to move on!
[giggles, laughs] You're
really somethin' else!
[KOIZUMI]
Sorry about this.
Guess I didn't exactly pick
the best time in the world
to show up then, huh?
[KYON] No. Don't worry.
It's not like that.
Well, obviously this is
just a courtesy gift then.
But that doesn't really matter.
Miss Suzumiya was the
one who gave it to me.
That alone is enough to
make it special in my book.
Anyhow, it's a holiday.
In keeping with the
Valentine's Day spirit,
we should really be
considerate of each other.
Mmm, this is good.
Sorry, I've got
something to do.
See ya later.
[door clicks]
[ASAKURA] Now that I'm
thinking more clearly,
I realized something.
Yeah, what's that?
This whole situation is
partially Nagato's fault.
What?
Think about it like this:
The devil is getting ready
to make off with the heroine
and the hero just runs away?
The devil?
I know she's timid,
but she's gotta realize
there are times when you
can't just head for the hills!
I thought she got past this
when the club was in danger.
Guess I was wrong.
[ASAKURA] I wonder if
I'm forcing my own ideals
on her too much. That's
not very fair of me.
[HARUHI]
There she is!
Huh?
[gasps]
Where have you been?
Sorry!
[ASAKURA]
Don't you "sorry" me!
What are you doing here?
Explain yourself!
Oh, nothing.
It's because you saw her
giving him chocolate, right?
That's what made you
lose your nerve.
What? Well...
I don't see why it
should change anything.
Of course he's going to get
chocolate from other people!
I mean, it's Valentine's Day.
That's just kinda how it works!
You can't get discouraged
by every last little thing.
That's no way to live your life!
[gasps]
[ASAKURA]
Why are you so quick to give up?
Are your feelings
for him so trivial,
you can forget about
them that easily?
Answer me already!
Uh, sorry. You've
got it all wrong.
--[ASAKURA] Say what?
--Huh?
I'm just waiting. Don't worry.
I'll give them to him.
You will?
That's the plan.
Really? But I was so frantic.
I thought for sure
you'd run off for good.
[laughs] I'm not giving up,
if that's what you thought.
In that case,
why did you leave
the chocolates behind?
[NAGATO] Hm? The chocolates?
I have them right here.
I can't find them!
[laughs]
What's so funny?
Here. Your chocolates.
[gasps]
Hold it! There's still
somethin' I wanna know.
Huh?
If you really are
giving them to him,
then why'd you run
out of the clubroom
like it was on fire?
About that...
I thought that you would
wanna be alone with him.
Leaving seemed like
the polite thing to do,
so I left in a hurry.
Huh? Sounds kinda stupid.
If someone's trying to
interfere with your love life,
why should you give
a crap how they feel?
You're not interfering.
If I were in your shoes,
I wouldn't want somebody there
when I was giving my gift.
Know what I mean?
[HARUHI]
Yeah.
Hold on.
[NAGATO] So, just, you
know, out of curiosity.
Do you have...? Are you, um...
Are you in love
with him? Kyon, I mean?
[KYON]
I dunno. They could be real.
To be honest, I can't
say I dislike him.
[HARUHI]
So. There you have it.
You know how I feel now.
What'll you do? Well?
[NAGATO]
Nothing's really changed.
Huh?
I'm still planning to
give my chocolates to him.
Well then, good luck!
Ah! Are you sure?
Do you need any help?
Ryoko, stop!
--[HARUHI] Hmph.
--[ASAKURA whines]
Oh, no! It's got a dent in it!
Hey, this is really good tim--
What took so long?
--[yelps]
--You sure like to
make an entrance, don't you?
[KYON] Sorry. Uh, so,
did you find Nagato?
[gasps]
[HARUHI] We'll just get
out of your way now.
Uh...
[HARUHI] You made the
effort to come find her.
That's something.
[KYON] Huh? What's that
supposed to mean?
Is she okay?
Stay with her, Kyon.
Do we understand each other?
Uh, sure.
--Take care of my girl!
--You got it!
[KYON]
What was all that about?
Uh...
[KYON] Well, it's good
I found her, I guess,
but what should I do now?
So, uh...
Huh?
Before, in the clubroom.
I know I took off
pretty suddenly.
I'm, um, sorry about that.
Don't worry.
It's not a big deal.
Cold out here, huh?
[grunts]
So, uh... You wanna
go back, then?
[NAGATO]
Mm-hm.
Hold on!
Huh? What is it?
Well, um. Here's this.
Something for you.
Go ahead. Take it.
[KYON]
Uh... Okay.
Um, thank you very much!
Oh, you're very welcome!
[KYON]
Here.
It smells great.
[paper rustling]
You're gonna open it here?
You don't want me to?
No. I mean, it doesn't
really matter to me.
Go ahead.
[KYON]
Okay, cool.
[KYON] Whoa! They look
like they're homemade.
Are they?
[NAGATO]
Mm-hm.
Actually, Asakura helped
me put them together.
I didn't do much, really.
Just melted some chocolate,
poured it in cups,
and put sprinkles on top.
So I don't know how "homemade"
it is, to be honest.
Oh, but don't worry.
I used good ingredients.
So they should taste okay!
Uh--
Stupid, stupid!
I've gotta learn when
to shut my mouth.
[NAGATO]
Calm down. Calm down...
I'm sold. I think
I'll have one now.
You're gonna eat it right now?
You don't want me to?
No, no, I don't care!
It doesn't matter to me!
[KYON]
Okay.
Ah! But...
--[NAGATO] Go ahead.
--[KYON] Now I'm just gonna feel
kinda weird eating it.
What?
Why does the idea of me
eating it right now
bother you so much?
Oh! I get it!
It's like Russian
roulette or something.
I bet one of them
has hot sauce in it!
Why would I do that?
Okay, then what is it?
How can I explain it? Ah!
Okay, it's like, when you're
riding a bike at night,
and everything is
quiet and empty
so you start singing a love song
real loudly and then suddenly
a pedestrian turns the
corner and you're not alone!
[KYON]
Personal experience much?
Oh, or, like when
you draw a real
lovey-dovey comic
and then later...
...somebody asks to
borrow your notebook.
[KYON]
Nope. Still don't get it.
[NAGATO]
Then...
[KYON]
You know, tell ya what.
I'm just gonna eat one.
This one here.
I'll even count down.
If you wanna stop me,
now's the time. Ten!
Oh, no. What do
I do? What do I do?
Nine!
Ah. Maybe you should
take your time
--and savor it at home.
--[KYON] Eight!
Doesn't that sound nice?
[KYON]
Seven!
[NAGATO gasps]
Six, five, four,
--three, two, one... Zero!
--No!
[NAGATO]
That was completely unfair.
I did a standard countdown.
[NAGATO]
Well? How is it?
Let's see. It wasn't
spicy at all.
[NAGATO] That's not exactly
what I was asking.
[chuckles]
[KYON]
It was good.
[KYON] Thanks again. I'm glad
I've got a whole box.
[NAGATO]
Sure. I'm glad you like it.
[ASAKURA] Hmm. She gave
them to him, at least.
Though it'd be stretching
the truth to say
things are going smoothly.
Really? I thought it
looked all right.
Well, it's not like it's going
horribly wrong or anything.
But it's possible...
She focused so much
on the chocolates,
that she forgot the
whole part about
confessing her love for him.
[HARUHI]
Is a confession even necessary?
She's blushing so hard, I'm
starting to feel embarrassed
just watching
their conversation.
You think he really
needs it spelled out?
[ASAKURA]
True.
She's red enough that
even if she wasn't
in love with him, any guy
would think she was.
But, a certain someone had
already given him chocolates,
so he may be thrown
off the scent.
It was just a friendly gift!
But because he got those,
he might think
that her chocolates
are just a friendly gift, too.
Look at him. He's oblivious.
And it's all my fault.
[ASAKURA sighs]
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's just easy to say this
stuff to you, somehow.
Seriously.
I think you may be
as bad as Kyon.
Both of you are so mean.
[ASAKURA] You say that,
but it doesn't actually
seem to bother you.
Maybe you're a masochist.
What?!
[ASAKURA] If only she had
half your self-confidence
and optimism,
she'd be set for life.
[HARUHI]
Blah, blah, blah!
Even if the guy thinks
it is a courtesy gift.
It should be enough.
Just having given it to him.
Oh. Look! They're on the move.
[HARUHI] Probably headed
back to the clubroom.
[ASAKURA] Well, we don't
know that for sure yet.
[NAGATO]
Okay. I gave him the chocolates.
And he tried them
in front of me.
And miraculously, he
said they were good.
So now, the next step is...
t-t-t-t-to tell h-h-him.
Kyon!
[KYON]
Hm?
What is it?
Looks like she remembered
the love part, after all.
Well...
[KYON]
Hm?
I wanted to tell you...
--I--
--[TSURUYA] Hey, hey, hey!
--[HARUHI] Huh?
--[ASAKURA] Why now?
[TSURUYA] You managed to
give him chocolates, Naga!
I'm so proud of you!
Ah! I've got you!
[NAGATO]
Ah...
Uh, left hand isn't
strong enough...
Oh... Well, that hurt.
[gasps]
[KYON]
Uh...
He's on my...
[screams]
[ASAKURA]
I am going to kill him!
[HARUHI] What a good
chaperone! See ya later!
Sorry, Naga. I can be
kind of intense sometimes.
--How about you, Kyon?
--[NAGATO] My chest...
Okay down there?
[KOIZUMI]
Hey there, everyone.
--[NAGATO] My chest.
--Oh, finally. There you are.
I've been looking everywhere.
What happened here?
You had something to do
with this, didn't you?
It wasn't me. You know
how handsy Kyon gets.
[ASAKURA]
I'm here, Nagato!
[yelps]
[ASAKURA]
And as for you...
[KYON screams]
Huh. Buncha loons.
What are they doing?
[HARUHI] What am I doing,
for that matter?
[HARUHI] So, do you think
aliens are real or not?
[KYON]
I dunno.
They could be real.
[HARUHI]
Hm?
Well, I'm done,
so I'm goin' home now. See ya!
[KYON]
Hey!
[KYON] John Smith wishes
you the best of luck
in making the world
more exciting!
[HARUHI]
I guess I better join 'em.
Wow.
[KYON] I thought I would
return the favor.
That's what White Day
is all about, isn't it?
Yeah! This is wonderful!
Thank you so much!
Sure thing. It's no big deal.
I'm really glad
you like it though.
That's very thoughtful
of him, don't you think?
[HARUHI]
Hm...
Hey, can I see that a sec?
Huh? Sure, here you go.
Yep. They're exactly the same.
Here, thanks.
What was that about?
Oh, I see.
You were hoping that yours
was bigger, weren't you?
Sorry, you guys got
exactly the same one.
Measure any way you want.
You'll find they're
the same size.
One for you, and one for me!
[KYON]
Uh-- What is it now?
Oh nothing.
I guess he doesn't understand
girls very well, does he?
Oh really?
Well, you gave me a game
only an 80-year-old
would like, Koizumi.
[KOIZUMI]
I guess you have a point.
Do you mind if I open it now?
[KYON]
No. Just don't expect too much.
[NAGATO]
Mm-hm. Anything's great.
I never thought I would get a
present in the first place, so.
[NAGATO giggles]
[KOIZUMI, HARUHI, ASAKURA]
This is so sad.
[HARUHI] Why the heck did
that idiot give us the same
thank-you present when
my chocolate was obviously
a courtesy gift and
hers were homemade?
[ASAKURA sighs]
Looks like I was right earlier.
He must have thought that hers
were just a courtesy gift, too.
I'm surprised you
didn't say anything
when he gave them to us.
Your face when we found out
they were the same...
I thought your head
was gonna explode.
Yeah, I know.
but I saw how happy Nagato was,
so I decided to leave it.
Don't eat 'em!
[ASAKURA]
Huh. You seem kind of upset.
Is Kyon's White Day gift
really that important to you?
[HARUHI]
It's not that.
I just like to be
appropriately thankful
when someone gives me something.
What is it?
Oh, nothing.
[HARUHI]
Hmph.
[NAGATO] Next episode:
"Over the Obento."