[KYON, NAGATO]
Huh?
[KYON, NAGATO yell]
[KYON]
Quick! Call an ambulance!
[NAGATO]
Right. On it!
[KYON grunts]
[HARUHI] Get a grip on yourself!
I don't need an ambulance!
What I need is a warm room
with a good heater, now,
find me one!
Do it right now!
[HARUHI sighs]
I feel human again!
[panting]
So who are you people, anyway?
Us?!
[HARUHI] I mean, I'm not
trying to be rude,
but that panting's kinda creepy.
You were laying in the street,
shivering like you
were about to die
and demanded to be taken
someplace warm immediately.
I carried you.
You actually carried me?
Don't you think that's
overdoing it a little?
[KYON] You didn't really
give me much choice.
What's it like
to go through life
without a sense of humor?
What?
Don't get me
wrong or anything.
I do appreciate your help.
It's gotta be
hard on you, though:
having a boyfriend with
no sense of humor.
[NAGATO]
Hm?
Huh?
Hey!
Hello? I'm talking to you!
You are his girlfriend, right?
I am not!
[gasps]
Uh-- You've got it wrong!
We're just, well, you know,
we're not, things aren't,
it isn't-- It's kind
of complicated.
Wait, no, I didn't mean that!
We're in the same club!
Two people who happen
to be in a club together,
nothing more. We're
practically strangers!
[KYON coughs]
Wow! You don't
sugarcoat much, do ya?
[NAGATO]
Huh?
"Practically strangers"?
Is knowing him really that bad?
[gasps]
Geez, Nagato.
We haven't known
each other that long,
but I thought I'd
at least earned
the rank of "friend" by now.
[NAGATO]
Oh. When did that happen?
It's okay to call him my friend?
He wants me to
call him my friend?
[giggles] Well, of
course we're friends.
[HARUHI, HARUHI]
Yeah, great save.
[HARUHI]
Well. I'll be honest with you.
If you guys aren't dating,
I think we're going
to get along a lot better.
I don't get people who waste
their time in relationships.
Yeah...
So, you know.
It's not because I had my
heart broken or anything.
[KYON, NAGATO]
What?
Don't act surprised!
I could tell that's
what you were thinkin'.
Well, we can't have that.
I think it's important to
set the record straight.
So, here we go.
There are some things
you need to know about me.
First of all, I'm not
interested in ordinary people,
and I'm certainly not
interested in relationships.
What I am interested
in is aliens!
[phone rings]
[NAGATO]
Sorry, excuse me.
Oh, looks like I got
a text from Asakura.
"Hey Kyon. Nagato.
You should be at
the clubroom. Now."
That's right!
We're supposed to
help her clean up!
[HARUHI]
I think we're done here.
The feeling has returned
to my arms and legs,
and it sounds like there's
someplace you need to be,
so let's go.
[WAITRESS A] Thanks for
coming. Have a great day!
Oh, you're headed
to North High?
We can go part of
the way together.
Yeah, sure. That sounds great.
I'm Haruhi Suzumiya.
We never did get around
to introductions before.
I find conversations
less awkward
if I know who I'm talking to.
[KYON]
Well, in that case, my name's--
[HARUHI] Kyon, isn't it?
I heard it earlier.
And I'm Yuki Nagato.
Okay, great.
So, do you wanna tell
us how you ended up
collapsed in the
street like that?
[HARUHI]
That's simple.
I was standing in the
park all night long.
[KYON]
Uh, why?
So I could capture Santa.
Oh.
Huh?
[shrieks]
--[NAGATO, KYON gasp]
--My bag and wallet!
I left them both
back in the park!
[NAGATO, KYON]
What?
Since you insisted on
picking up the tab,
I didn't notice till now!
[KYON]
Insisted?
That's not good!
We have to get back to
the park and find them,
before somebody takes them.
She's right about that.
We should hurry.
Huh? You said "we."
You'd come with me?
Aren't you guys busy?
You can't even ride a train,
not if you don't
have your wallet.
It wouldn't be
very cool of us
to just abandon you
here like this.
Fine. But I move fast.
You better keep up.
That shouldn't be a problem.
It's not like
you're gonna r--
[HARUHI]
Come on! Follow me!
[NAGATO]
Come back.
[gasps]
Ah!
I found it! Look, here
it is. Nobody took it!
[NAGATO, KYON panting]
[KYON] Good, that
would've been a nightm--
I figured that it would be gone.
It's not like it was
hidden or anything.
[KYON] People were probably
too scared to take it.
Ugh. You weren't kidding.
You-- You were really trying
to capture Santa, weren't you?
Well, I told you
I was, didn't I?
[KYON] Unbelievable.
That's the word for you.
You're just realizing it?
You wouldn't believe how
unbelievable I can be!
--[NAGATO] Uh. Excuse me.
--[KYON] Uh, you know that
--Excuse me!
--wasn't a compliment, right?
[KYON, HARUHI]
Huh?
Under the snow, this paint?
It's supposed to be a
message to Santa, right?
How'd you figure that out?
I already knew!
Huh?
I met you before.
When you were "rehearsing."
[HARUHI]
Uh-- Huh?
[NAGATO]
Hm?
You guys've met before,
but you don't remember?
Well. I remember someone,
but it was dark,
so I couldn't make out the face.
Besides, based on the body type,
I assumed it was a
junior high school boy.
You don't remember?
That's awkward.
[HARUHI] No,.. Uh...
I totally remember you!
In fact, I was actually testing
to see if you remembered!
Well,
it's funny, but I've been
hoping I would run into you.
I actually wanted the
chance to thank you.
[HARUHI]
Thank me?
That's right.
I was sort of having
an inner crisis,
but you helped me get past it.
Meeting you gave me
the strength I needed.
So, uh... So, thank--
[HARUHI]
Stop right there!
I didn't do anything for you.
Wha--?
[HARUHI]
I can't think of a single thing
I did that night to help you.
In fact, I'm pretty sure
it was the other way around.
If you found some sort
of inner strength,
that's exactly what it was:
strength from inside you.
Give yourself credit, not me!
[gasps]
That's pretty interesting.
She basically said the same
thing you told me yesterday.
Is that the same?
[NAGATO]
Mm-hm!
[HARUHI] Oooh, so your
mind works the same way
mine does, huh?
Very interesting.
Huh?
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
I only suspected it before,
but now I'm certain.
You are my nemesis.
I totally agree.
There you go, thinking
just like me again!
How can you capture
a man who's not real?
How can you say that
Santa isn't real
when you haven't even
bothered to check?
I'm just being thorough.
You don't need to check
something like that!
Oh yeah? What's your
basis for that argument?
Think about it. You can't
prove a negative,
so there's always a
reason to keep checking.
And of course, that doesn't
only apply to Santa!
My goal is to find aliens,
time travelers, espers,
and people from
parallel universes
and make the world a
cooler place to live in!
[giggles]
[NAGATO, KYON]
Uh...
[NAGATO] She does kind of
rant like a crazy person,
but there's something
to what she says.
She's really--
[KYON]
You really are unbelievable.
That's right! I am unbelievable.
[NAGATO]
Unbelievable.
You guys are a
little late, huh?
[NAGATO, KYON]
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Nagato.
Your mission is to
eliminate all decorations.
Yes, sir!
[KYON]
As for me:
I'll be tackling this
Christmas tree.
Now, let's hop to it! Move!
A good Christmas.
And a great party.
[NAGATO]
I'm glad that's done.
[KYON]
It took longer than I thought.
[ASAKURA]
It did take a while.
It would have been done
sooner if two of us
had been more punctual.
We are sorry.
When you say it like that...
How can I not forgive you?
[NAGATO]
All right, well.
Here we are.
Since I won't see you guys
till school starts again,
I guess I'd better wish you
a happy New Year now.
Yeah. Same to you.
See you guys next year.
Uh. Um, I.
[KYON]
Hm?
Just, thank you.
For everything, I'm really
glad you joined the club.
Happy New Year.
I'm glad, too.
Well, see ya later.
[ASAKURA]
So, how'd it go at the party?
I want details!
Huh? What do you mean?
You know, did you
bare your soul
and tell him how you feel?
Oh, that. Well, uh, actually...
I did.
Really? What'd you say?
I told him I was grateful
for what he did.
That he saved the club.
That's better than nothing.
But you know what?
He said it wasn't true.
Huh?
He said I should be
proud of myself instead.
And it's crazy, but
there was actually
somebody else who
said the same thing.
[ASAKURA]
Wow.
You ran into the same
girl again this morning?
[NAGATO]
Mm-hm. Ah! Yummy!
That's right.
I hope you like it.
You know, she was
pretty incredible.
Wow! You're right! This
oden smells fantastic!
[ASAKURA]
Anyway, it must have been nice.
Seeing her again, I mean.
[NAGATO]
Mm-hm.
You know, though,
you should've asked
Kyon to visit a shrine
with you for the New Year.
[NAGATO]
Ow! It's hot!
Sometimes boys just need
a little bit of a nudge.
For ourselves and
those we love,
watch over us for another year.
Please watch over us.
[ASAKURA] You were praying
quite seriously.
Did you ask for
anything in particular?
Oh, you know.
You're right about
that. I bet I do.
[NAGATO]
Yeah...
[CAPTAIN A] First things
first. Happy New Year!
[TEAMMATES]
Happy New Year!
Enough of that. Listen up!
[KYON] And that means I'm
gonna take it easy again.
[KYON, TEAMMATES]
Yeah!
[yawns]
[KYON]
Huh?
Why're you doin' that?
[KYON]
She's locked on.
[NAGATO]
Huh. What's she doing?
This is it! The end is near!
[footsteps tapping]
[KYON]
She's fast!
Hi, there! It's been awhile.
I thought I'd say hi!
I made it to North High
and then I realized
I didn't know where
to start looking.
So I figured I'd
just trust my gut,
and it led me straight
here. Crazy, huh?
Good to see you again.
So, this is the
Literary Club, huh?
Kinda sad and empty, isn't it?
[KYON] So, did you come here
for any particular reason?
[HARUHI]
Not really.
Just, you know, trespassing.
[KYON]
She makes it sound like a hobby.
Given the uniform, I'm surprised
no one stopped you on the way.
[HARUHI] Yeah, I thought that
might be a problem, too,
and a few people did
look at me kinda funny.
But I guess they assumed
I was here on official business.
[KYON]
Fair enough.
Going by looks alone,
she could pass
for the president of
Kouyouen's student council.
I don't know if
I approve of that
look on your face at all.
Thanks for coming to visit us.
I'm sure you're really busy.
You can sit down here.
Ok, sure thing. Thanks a lot.
But first, I have
a favor to ask.
What's the favor?
I'm not breaking
any laws for you.
Nothing like that.
At least, not until we
know each other better.
I need to borrow
your gym clothes.
Huh?
[HARUHI]
You can come in now!
Perfect! Now I can totally pass
for an after-school
North High student.
What's the point, though?
You're in already.
[HARUHI]
Hm. I did get in pretty easily.
But I left someone behind
at the school gate, so...
[KYON, NAGATO]
Huh?
He can wear this.
You brought a friend?
Or an enemy.
Who would make a friend wait
outside in this weather?
[HARUHI] Well, two of us would
have stood out even more!
So I told him I'd come
back after I found you
and got your gym clothes.
But you didn't even know
you'd be able to find us.
[HARUHI] Well, it still worked
out just as I planned.
Hey.
What is it?
Maybe you should put your
hair up in a ponytail.
Why, you have a
thing for ponytails?
[KYON] It was just a
thought, that's all.
[HARUHI]
Hm...
Well. Guess it is
more convincing.
Okay! I'll be right back!
What's wrong? Have you
got a headache?
No, it's nothing. I'm fine.
[HARUHI] Here, Koizumi.
Change into this, quickly!
[KOIZUMI]
Er. You want me to change here?
[sighs] Sure, no problem.
I'll just clean this up.
I dunno.
Maybe I should grow my hair out.
[KYON]
What's that?
[NAGATO gasps]
Oh. Well. Um...
Her hair's so pretty,
all long and flowy.
I was just thinking I might
like to grow mine long, too.
Really?
I don't think there's
anything wrong with it now.
Ah...
[KYON] I mean, if you wanna
grow it out, go ahead.
It's your hair.
But I think you look good
with that hairstyle.
[gasps]
[KYON] If you do grow it out,
I recommend a ponytail.
[door slams]
[HARUHI] Whew! We nearly
froze to death out there!
It's obviously your fault
for being so slow!
Sorry about that.
I didn't mean to be slow,
I'm just not used
to changing my clothes
out in public, so.
Hello, by the way.
I'm Itsuki Koizumi. It's
very nice to meet you both.
M-M-Miss Suzumiya,
do you think I could
maybe change now?
Of course not!
A teacher could come in
any second, too risky!
Now listen up and
be amazed! You see.
Koizumi is a mysterious
transfer student!
Mysterious, yeah.
That sounds like me.
[HARUHI] He transferred
over to our school
after orientation day last year.
Pretty strange, huh?
Totally suspicious!
We like to hang out,
and I don't wanna
miss it when he reveals
his true identity.
[KYON] After this long,
he's neither mysterious
nor a transfer student.
What identity are you
expecting him to reveal?
Could be a bunch of things.
Maybe...
It's nice to meet
you, by the way.
Boy, you must have it rough.
Not really.
But I understand why
you would think that.
You're okay with this?
Yeah. Really.
People at our school
do treat Miss Suzumiya
a little differently
than everybody else.
[KYON]
I bet they do.
[KOIZUMI]
But...
Since I transferred
at such a weird time,
I wound up pretty
isolated. Until--
Hey, what's your name?
[gasps]
[KOIZUMI] When everyone else
thought I was strange,
she accepted me, just like that.
[KYON]
Oh, really?
Well, she mainly hangs
out with me because
she was intrigued by the
timing of my transfer,
and that can't last.
I think it's fading already,
so I am a little
concerned about that.
[KYON] Sounds like cause
for celebration to me.
[KOIZUMI] Not for me.
You see, the thing is,
I think there's a good chance
I'm falling in love with her.
You're crazy!
I happen to find her
utterly charming.
All right, you two,
enough talk!
This is very important,
so listen up!
[KOIZUMI]
Of course! We're listening!
[KYON]
Yeah. What is it now?
Koizumi and I are now
officially members
of the North High Literary
Club's mystery section!
And furthermore, I will be
the Lit. Club's
executive president.
You don't mind just being
a figurehead, now do you?
Uh, no.
[KYON]
A takeover?
Sounds great.
[KYON]
What is with this guy?
[HARUHI]
Now that that's decided,
it's time to make some changes!
This room needs a
serious makeover.
[NAGATO]
Oh, you think so?
Newcomers, huh?
[PLAYER A]
North High.
--[PLAYER A] Fight! Fight!
--[PLAYERS] Yeah! Yeah!
So, you're the Miss Suzumiya
I've heard about.
[HARUHI]
That's right!
[ASAKURA]
You know, we're not supposed
to have outside students
in the clubroom.
That could cause some
problems if people find out.
Yeah, I know.
[ASAKURA] And you're
okay with this, Nagato?
Huh? Yeah.
But, if you don't think
it'll work, then...
As long as you're
all right with it,
then it's fine by me.
Really? It is?
[ASAKURA] At first I thought
this girl was bullying Nagato,
but now I can tell
she's all right.
I can see it in her eyes.
Besides, if they know
they're breaking the rules,
they'll probably behave
themselves well enough.
They're from a
prestigious school,
I doubt they'd wanna jeopardize
their records by being reckless.
--[cackling]
--[KYON] You may wanna
--rethink that.
She's not just reckless,
she's downright crazy.
[HARUHI, ASAKURA]
Nice to meet you!
[KYON sighs]
[KYON]
The following day.
Hello!
I brought a bunch of
cool stuff for the clubroom!
[KYON]
And the day after that.
Hi, everyone!
More stuff?
[KYON]
Her occupation of our clubroom
was progressing steadily.
Hey! Look what I found!
Isn't she adorable?
I-I don't understand
what's happening.
Will somebody please tell me
why I was brought here?
Miss Asahina, please accept
my sincere apologies.
You already know her? Darn it!
A girl like that?
Everyone knows her.
[HARUHI]
Don't fight it!
[ASAKURA] I'm surprised
you were able to get past
Miss Tsuruya to bring her here.
Oh, the rabid
guard dog, you mean?
We did sustain some losses,
but the danger was neutralized.
Losses?
It might have something
to do with the fact
that the guys haven't made it
back to the clubroom yet.
[gasps]
Sacrifices were made.
But if you had come with us,
we might have been able to
skip the random
encounter battle.
We knew that was a possibility.
That's why we let you have Kyon.
Oh. A lot of good that did.
He was basically useless.
[screaming]
I don't think so!
[cackles]
[groans]
[KYON gasps]
--[KYON gasps]
--[HARUHI] Hm.
[yelps]
[growls]
[KYON]
Wha--? Uh--
[KYON yells]
[grunts]
N-N-N-N-N-No!
Prepare yourself!
[MORI]
That's enough.
[gasps]
[MORI]
Come on!
You're gonna flash people
jumping around like that.
Is that what you want?
--[HARUHI laughs]
--[MIKURU screams]
[MORI]
You're in trouble now.
[ASAKURA]
So, it all worked out, then.
[HARUHI]
Anyway, this guy, Kyon.
What's the deal with him?
He gets more snarky
with me every day,
and I'm getting tired of it!
And he treats me totally
different than he treats Yuki!
Huh?
[ASAKURA]
How awful for you.
I mean, I'm the
executive president
of this club!
As a regular member,
he should show some respect!
I don't know.
I would think it would
be kind of awkward
if he was groveling
to you all the time.
Huh. You might
have a point there.
It's kind of nice to
have somebody talk to me
--like I'm a regular person.
--[phone vibrates]
Most people treat me like
I'm some kind of weirdo
who might end up flying off
the handle at any moment
if they say something
I don't like.
You say that like
it's no big deal.
[door slams]
[NAGATO, HARUHI]
Huh?
[TSURUYA] Did you think
you could hide forever?
I'm not leaving until
I get Mikuru back.
Eh?
[HARUHI] Well, we're not giving
her up without a fight!
You better get ready!
[KYON groans]
[gasps]
[MIKURU yelps]
Oh, no! Kyon! Are you okay?
[KYON groans]
Huh?
Oh, good. You're all right.
I'm so relieved!
[TSURUYA] Whoa! That's a
cool frog! I want it!
Um...
[HARUHI] Hey, watch it!
Wait 256 million years
and maybe then you can
look at her underwear.
[MIKURU]
What? Noooo!
[KYON] Wait! I swear
I didn't see anything!
[NAGATO] Things used to be
very quiet in this club.
[TSURUYA cackles]
[NAGATO] But something tells
me those days are over now.
[NAGATO] Next episode:
"Be My Valentine."