[KYON] So, it sounds like
Taniguchi is going to be
applying for a job
at that minimart now.
The last time he had a job,
it was at some bar-b-que place.
He only worked there because
there was this girl he liked,
and when she quit, so did he.
I bet this'll be the same thing.
He's pretty predictable.
Well, predictably
idiotic, anyway.
[KYON]
Whoa.
Sure is quiet in here.
We should be able to
do a lot of studying.
So, where should we--
[KYON]
Hm?
Ah! Hey! Come back!
Think you could keep
your voice down?
This is a library.
Oh! Of course! I'm sorry.
[KYON] She likes this place
even more than I expected.
[KYON]
Hey, Nagato!
Miss Nagato!
Professor Nagato!
She can't hear me.
I might as well not even
exist at this point.
[chuckles]
[KYON] I've never known someone
who could concentrate like that!
I wish I'd known it would
make her this happy.
I woulda brought
her here sooner.
Except,
it's actually the current
Nagato who likes books.
Uh. Looks like she's
ready to get to work.
Or maybe not.
Hey, um, Nagato?
We came here to
study, didn't we?
[gasps]
[KYON]
Um, hello?
Just a few pages.
[KYON]
She means business!
Man. When she looks that happy,
it's hard not to feel like
a jerk for interrupting her.
[sighs]
[KYON]
I'll just go wait over there.
Grab me when you're done, okay?
[NAGATO]
Ah. Right.
[KYON sighs]
All right, then.
I'll just sit down
here for a minute.
[sighs]
[yawns]
[BOY A]
Found it, Mom!
Oh yeah? Good job, honey!
Hey, check this out!
Oh, whoa! What is that?
[GIRLS giggle]
See ya later!
--[BOY B] Bye-bye!
--[BOY C] See ya!
[phone vibrates]
[KYON]
Huh?
Hm? It's Asakura.
What does she want?
[LIBRARY EMPLOYEE A]
Eh-hem.
Uh...
I'll just step outside.
[KYON]
Hey. What's up?
[ASAKURA]
Good, you answered!
I was getting worried.
Where are you? With Nagato?
Yeah, we came to
the library together.
Okay, good. If you're
with her, that's fine.
She wasn't home,
so I was wondering where
she might have gone off to.
And she didn't
answer my call, so...
So, you immediately
started worrying, huh?
So, tell me something.
Is it hard being a mom?
[gasps] What?!
[ASAKURA]
Huh?
[KYON] Ugh. I accomplished
nothing today.
[ASAKURA]
Sorry? Is everything all right?
It's nothing.
Don't worry about it.
We're heading out soon.
I'll tell Nagato to
give you a call, 'kay?
[ASAKURA] Oh, yeah, thanks.
That sounds good.
[KYON] I didn't open a
textbook this entire time!
[gasps]
[KYON] Incredible.
She hasn't even moved.
Ahem. Earth to Nagato!
The library's closing.
We should go.
[KYON] Come on. Let's
put the book back--
Hm?
Let me get to a
good stopping place.
No can do.
Ten more minutes.
Won't work.
The library'll be
closing in ten minutes.
Well, in that case...
give me nine.
I think you're being
a little ridiculous.
[gasps]
Uh! Looking at me like that
won't change anything.
Okay, you win.
I give up.
We'll get a library card
and check that book out.
Will that work for you?
[NAGATO]
Uh...
[KYON]
Hm?
Like this? Got one.
Why didn't you tell me?
The way you were acting,
I thought you didn't have one.
[gasps]
I'm sorry. I just remembered.
[KYON]
Right, I understand.
Well, it's not a big deal.
Come on. We'll check
it out and then get going.
[NAGATO]
I didn't realize it
until I remembered
about the card.
But he and the other Yuki have
been at the library before.
It's where they met.
Hey.
[gasps]
Come on, what is
it you're doing?
Um... Uh...
Gimme that. You want
a library card, right?
Hey, um, what are you
looking around for?
Who else would I be talking to?
So, do you want a card, then?
Uh... Mm-hm.
[KYON]
Cool.
[NAGATO]
Huh?
I'll go take care
of it for you.
Huh? Hey! Hold on!
[KYON]
Well, here ya go.
[NAGATO]
Oh, great.
This is, uh...
I-- Thank you for--
[KYON]
No problem.
I mean--
I was probably
a little too pushy.
I'm kinda used to looking
out for somebody, so...
I couldn't just stand by
and do nothing when I saw you.
[KYON'S SISTER]
Hey! Kyon!
[KYON, NAGATO]
Huh?
It's too high up.
I can't reach the book!
Like I said, I'm used to
looking out for someone.
Well, see ya around.
[KYON] Don't go around
shouting out my nickname
like that, squirt!
--Meow-ow-ow-ow!
--[KYON] And no meowing!
Oh, no. I missed my
chance to thank him.
[sighs]
[gasps]
I guess that was... a dream.
Ah! You're awake. Good morning!
We've still got a little while
longer until breakfast is done.
So, go on. I'll finish
this up while you get ready.
[NAGATO] It's like I was
observing her memories
while they were happening.
They were so clear.
[NAGATO]
I can feel her personality,
sleeping in a corner
of my mind somewhere.
I think it's
starting to wake up.
[NAGATO] But, if she does
wake up completely, then what?
If she comes back, then
what's going to happen...
...to me?
There's another huge sale,
so you know what that means.
Nagato's in your care.
Have fun, gotta go!
[giggles]
Enjoy the sale!
It's just us, then.
Let's hurry up and
get to the library.
We've got some serious
studying to do today.
[NAGATO]
Hold on.
[KYON]
Hm?
I have something...
I need to do.
[KYON] Okay, well,
let's do it quickly, then.
[NAGATO] I'll be fine.
You go on to the library.
I'll meet you there later.
[KYON] I can't go to
the library by myself.
I'd fall asleep.
Seriously. I wouldn't
stand a chance.
[sighs]
He's such a liar.
Here. They're good as new.
How would you like them?
Do you wanna wear them now?
[STORE OWNER]
Not a problem.
Give me a minute and I'll
put them in a case for you.
[KYON]
How are they?
Your glasses.
Are they all fixed?
I look pretty good, huh?
[gasps] Yeah.
[KYON]
Round two! Let's go.
[CAT meows]
We're gonna study like
crazy today, right?
Of course.
I noticed that you paused
a little bit before answering.
Uh--
I know, you're right.
This is all for me, not for you.
I'm the one who needs
to study so badly.
But if you could stay
and help me out, well,
I'd really appreciate it.
[NAGATO grunts]
Sure, no problem.
[KYON]
Thanks a lot.
[heart beating]
[NAGATO]
What's happening?
[KYON]
Hm?
Ah...
Okay, I'm stuck.
What do I do here?
Where?
[KYON]
This part.
[NAGATO]
Oh. If you substitute this--
[KYON]
Oh, I see. That makes sense now.
You're awesome. Thank you!
[KYON]
Hm?
Ah--
Um, something wrong?
[NAGATO] Oh, uh, there's a
question I can't figure out.
Whoa.
A question that
you can't answer?
I didn't think...
that was possible.
[KYON]
Now what?
I'll go see if there's a book
somewhere that can help.
Let me know if you have
any more questions.
I'll come back.
[KYON]
U-Uh...
[KYON sighs]
[NAGATO]
I wonder what's going on.
I'm not my usual
self today at all.
Why did I refuse
to wear her glasses?
There's nothing wrong
with them anymore.
Why do I feel nervous
around him all of a sudden?
There's no good reason for it.
Why... is my heart
beating so fast?
I don't understand.
I don't have enough data.
I'm sure that dreaming about her
memories is what triggered this.
That much seems fairly obvious.
It's also undeniable
that her personality
is starting to wake up.
So, all this
confusion inside me,
this strange feeling I'm having;
is it hers?
[NAGATO]
I don't think so.
I am me.
Her memories still
exist inside my head.
But the observations,
feelings, experiences
I'm currently registering
belong to me, not her.
There's no doubt
about that, either.
Then, why?
[gasps]
[NAGATO]
Is it possible...
That her consciousness and
mine are mixed up together?
So that the more
she continues to awaken,
the more her feelings, her
senses, and her consciousness
begin to exist alongside my own?
[NAGATO]
So, chances are good
that she will eventually
awaken completely.
There's probably
no changing that.
It's already begun.
[NAGATO] But when it
does happen-- What then?
[gasps]
[NAGATO]
Will she and I...?
Will we...?
[gasps]
Here, let me get that for you.
I'm sure I can't help you
with whatever question it is
you can't answer.
But I figured I could at least
make myself useful like this.
[gasps]
See? All yours.
You're a meddler,
you know that?
But, in a good way.
I'm glad it's in
a good way at least.
You're used to looking
out for somebody,
so you couldn't just stand by.
Well, yeah, that's it exactly.
Wait. Have I told you
that before or something?
Thanks for the help.
Uh...
It's really nice
to see you smile.
Feels like it's
been a long time.
Oh? Really?
Yeah, really.
[NAGATO]
Well, I'm extra grateful,
since I didn't get to
thank you for that other time.
What other time?
What do you mean?
[NAGATO]
It's a secret.
A secret, ah!
Ah...
But that time wasn't...
[KYON]
Hm? What's the matter?
[NAGATO]
Nothing. Forget about it.
[KYON]
I think I'll have one now.
You're gonna eat it right now?
You don't want me to?
No, I don't care!
It doesn't matter to me!
[KYON]
Okay.
Ah! But...
[NAGATO]
Go ahead.
Another dream.
[NAGATO]
Just a simple little dream.
And I'm just an idle observer.
Watching her memories.
Just a simple dream.
Mind if I ask
what you're doing?
Oh. It's just...
They seem close
enough to touch,
but then when you try
to grab them, nothing.
[gasps]
[NAGATO]
Hold on. Was that me?
What will happen?
Is it possible that when the
other Yuki returns completely,
I'll just, just... disappear?
[NAGATO]
Next episode,
"The Disappearance of
Nagato Yuki, Part Three."