[KYON]
In the last episode.
[HARUHI]
Smoky!
[ASAKURA]
What did you expect?
[MIKURU]
Good luck!
I really hope your
wish comes true.
[HARUHI]
I wanna bath, now!
[ASAKURA]
Will you please shut up?!
[KOIZUMI]
Say cheese!
Oh! That's gonna be a good one!
I'm out.
Our snack bag's empty!
I didn't even know
we had a snack bag.
Things could get ugly
if we get hungry.
She has a point, you know.
It's gonna be a
while until dinner.
Well, fortunately for us,
there's a supermarket up ahead.
Diver, pull over
at the supermarket!
I'll be happy to do
that for you, miss.
[HARUHI]
Whew! Crisis averted!
[KYON] What're you planning
to do with all this food?
Ever hear of saving
for a rainy day?
[KOIZUMI]
Cheese!
[KYON]
Put that thing away!
[car door scrapes]
We're here!
Welcome, welcome!
It's a pleasure to have you.
You must be tired
from the long trip here.
Now, please, if
you'll follow me.
[HARUHI]
♪ Bath time! Bath time! ♪
[ASAKURA] It'll be so nice
to wash that smoke off.
[TSURUYA]
That sounds amazing.
I say we just drop our
luggage in our rooms and go.
You've had a long
journey, miss.
Let me help you with those.
[KYON]
Uh, does Miss Mori have a twin?
That's some service!
If I wait long enough,
maybe one of them will
help me with these.
Talk about perfect!
It's an old-timey country inn!
You guys can go on ahead.
I'll take care of things
with the front desk.
Cool, thanks a bunch.
Don't mind if we do!
Adorable.
Come on! Let's go
hit the hot spring!
[MIKURU] Oh, look! They have
a souvenir shop here, too!
[KOIZUMI]
Want some help with those?
[KYON] You could have
offered sooner, dude.
So precious!
[ASAKURA] What are you doing?
We're going to our rooms.
Uh, nothing!
The view from here's
pretty awesome!
Room's kinda small though.
I don't know.
I think this is big enough
for the three of us.
Yeah. I agree.
Please make yourselves at home.
You'll find the bath
on the ground floor
at the end of the
hall in the new wing.
You hear that?
I can't wait to wash off
this stinky smoke. Let's go!
Oh, right away?
I thought it might be nice
to rest a little first.
[NAGATO]
Huh?
[ASAKURA]
I guess I'm outnumbered.
--Let's go, then.
--[knocking]
[MORI] Excuse me. I forgot
to tell you something.
The open-air spring
is a matchmaking bath.
We hope you enjoy it.
[HARUHI] A matchmaking bath?
Now I'm curious!
Come on you guys,
get your stuff! Hurry!
Uh-oh, I have a bad
feeling about this.
Matchmaking bath?
[TSURUYA humming]
You almost ran me over!
Headed to the bath already?
Yeah!
Grab your stuff, we'll
meet you down there!
They have something
called a matchmaking bath
we're checking out.
Hot spring time!
[ASAKURA]
Well, see ya later.
Enjoy yourselves.
[HARUHI] Ah, crap!
I forgot to bring a towel!
[ASAKURA] Well, we're gonna
go ahead without you!
We just got here
and she's already
yelling about something.
Doesn't she ever take a break?
Well, at least this
is a little exciting,
don't you think? It's vacation,
and it's the first time
we've taken a trip together.
Here you go.
[KYON]
Great, thank you.
[HARUHI] Come on! Where is
that stupid towel?
The fun's here!
You're alone. What
happened to Mikuru?
She said she'd
come down later.
[HARUHI]
Okay.
Here you go, I think
this is yours, Haru.
Great, thank you!
Well, I'm ready.
See ya in the bath!
Whoa!
[HARUHI]
Okay, you two, here I go!
All right. We'll be heading
that way soon, too.
[HARUHI grunts]
This is the life.
Tell me about it.
This is wonderful!
Oh, wow! Look at how
big this place is!
[yelps]
I've got you, okay? Don't worry.
I'll hold your hand
the entire time.
Just go slowly and carefully
and you'll be fine.
I'm sorry. I hate that
you have to do this,
but I'm blind
without my glasses.
It's okay. I don't mind, really.
Guess this is
the herbal bath.
This is some seriously
brown bathwater.
Is it supposed to
make your skin smell
like a breath mint?
[ASAKURA]
Glasses must get annoying a lot.
Ever thought of
switching to contacts?
Do they not get all foggy
the way glasses do?
Huh. I don't know
for sure, actually.
I guess I could find somebody
who wears them and ask, though.
Wha--? Mm... No, don't bother.
To be honest, the idea of
wearing them scares me.
[HARUHI]
Ooh, look, they have a sauna!
[TSURUYA]
Cool! Let's try it!
[ASAKURA] Uh, do you think
I could borrow your shampoo?
[NAGATO]
Sure.
You're cute without glasses.
It opens up your face.
[NAGATO]
Hm.
[door slams]
[HARUHI] Ugh, I can't take it,
it's too hot in there!
[TSURUYA] Another minute
and I'm gonna melt!
[TSURUYA, HARUHI sigh]
I can see how they
might not work for you.
You would probably
just fall asleep
with them in while
playing a game.
What do you two
think about,,, that?
[HARUHI, TSURUYA sigh]
It's smaller than I expected.
Maybe, but the water
feels really good.
So, what do ya think
this little gate's for?
I think this string opens it!
[TSURUYA]
It's a matchmaking shrine!
Really? Then this is
the matchmaking bath
we heard about before.
Here goes nothin'!
Matchmaking time!
[HARUHI] Hello? There's
no one over there.
And what's up with this window,
don't they make 'em any bigger?
[TSURUYA] Whatever the case,
this may be my favorite so far.
So, how do you girls like it?
This is the one
that's supposed to be
the matchmaking bath, isn't it?
Oh, so that's what she
was talking about, huh?
[sighs]
Ah!
How'd you make it
in without falling?
[ASAKURA sighs]
I have to say, ladies,
this is heavenly!
Ya kinda sound like an
old woman, ya know that?
Miss Asakura needs this.
She's always looking
after you rascals.
[NAGATO] Oh, Miss Asahina
never joined us. Where is she?
Mikuru is not the type
who likes to rush.
Even so, she'll probably
be here pretty soon.
--[door slides]
--There, see?
Sorry I'm late, it took
me a while to get ready.
We've all been here forever!
[MIKURU]
I know, I'm sorry!
[ASAKURA]
I always knew they were big,
but without clothes,
they're just--
[NAGATO, HARUHI]
Epic!
[sighs]
[HARUHI] That's my Mikuru!
They're spectacular!
[TSURUYA] Just wait until
you give 'em a squeeze!
W-W-What are you suggesting?
What do you think?
[MIKURU yelling]
I wonder if I should
try squeezing them, too.
[ASAKURA]
Oh, by the way.
[HARUHI, TSURUYA]
Hm?
What do you guys want to do
when we're finished
with the baths?
I guess we could all do our
own thing until dinner.
Well, let's see here.
I think there's a ping-pong
table in the bath lounge.
That's an idea.
Ping-pong?
Sweet!
Hey guys!
After this, we're gonna
play some ping-pong!
[ASAKURA]
Cover yourself!
As soon as we're done soakin',
we're headin' for
the the bath lounge.
We're gonna have a
full-on tournament!
[MIKURU] What?
--[TSURUYA] Yeah!
--[MIKURU] Wha--?
[ASAKURA]
Seriously! Cover up, will you?
--Ah. This feels so nice.
--[HARUHI] Whatever.
--It's gonna be so fun!
[ASAKURA] You don't even
know what the word
"modesty" means, do you?
[HARUHI laughs] What's the
problem? It's just us girls!
I guess we're playing ping-pong.
Pretend we don't know.
If they find out
we can hear them,
there's gonna be hell to pay.
Seriously. We can't tell them.
We heard it all,
including when they
were teasing Miss Asahina.
So, what do you
think of the spring?
Is it about what you expected?
Your skin's smoother
than I would've thought.
Quit touching me! And don't
sit so close, either.
[KOIZUMI] What's the matter?
Hey, we're all friends here.
There's no need to be shy.
[HARUHI]
Watch out, Mikuru!
[KYON]
Jeez. What is with these people?
Attention!
We're gathered here to take
part in The Literary Club's
extra-special, super-mega
ping-pong tournament!
First prize will be milk
from the vending machine.
[MIKURU] If anyone's wondering,
I like fruit milk.
[HARUHI]
Hope you brought change, Kyon.
This had better not be rigged!
I actually don't mind if it is.
Not as long as Miss
Suzumiya is having fun.
Shouldn't the rest
of us have fun, too?
[HARUHI]
There! Perfect!
Tadah! Here are the match-ups!
--[HARUHI] First game.
--[KYON] Why? Why? Why?
Koizumi's serves
are unstoppable!
Kyon loses, of course!
Second game. Mikuru's
hopeless, and Yuki wins!
Third game, Ryoko is defeated
by the "Dance of the Crane."
Miss Tsuruya wins!
Fourth game!
Koizumi injures his wrist
and Yuki wins by default.
How embarrassing.
[KYON]
Foul! I call foul!
Fifth game!
Miss Tsuruya offers
to be the judge,
so she's disqualified,
and I win by default!
It's important to
always play fair!
[KYON] We got by without
a judge until now!
[HARUHI]
It's time for the final game!
This one's between
you and me, Yuki!
I'll do my best!
[KYON] For the record,
I object to this!
Are you ready?
[NAGATO grunts]
Niagara... Atlantic... Serve!
[KYON]
You gotta be kidding me.
Check, check. And here we go!
I hope you had a chance
to warm up your voices
'cause we're gonna have
a Karaoke contest!
[TSURUYA]
Woo-hoo!
Ha, ha!
[KYON]
What's with this room?
I mean, what's the
point of the bathtub?
Come on in, the water's nice.
What're you doing in there?
Let's see, who will be
the first contestant...
Mikuru!
Ahhh! Oh, me? I don't know.
[MIKURU]
♪ Round and round, ♪
♪ the world is beautiful
and bright and I, for one, ♪
♪ want it to stay that way! ♪
♪ So I will do my
best every day ♪
♪ and try with
all my might! ♪
♪ So sometimes it doesn't
matter how hard I try ♪
♪ I'll get angry,
or sad, or even cry. ♪
♪ But I know I'll
see my love ♪
♪ I'll stay strong, and
I'll live a happy life! ♪
--Oh, thank you!
--[KYON sobbing] That's so true
--[TSURUYA] Great job, Mikuru!
--Isn't it?
--Bravo! Bravo!
--[KYON sobbing]
Stop crying, Kyon! You're up.
[KYON] What? You didn't
tell me I was singing!
But that's what
"you're up" means!
Are you gonna forfeit?
I'll show you.
I'm gonna crush this
Karaoke contest!
[rock music playing]
[inhales]
[door slams]
Well that got boring fast.
Should we change activities?
Wow, that didn't
last very long.
How was the Karaoke contest?
A total snooze-fest.
I can't think of
anything else to do.
How about you, Yuki?
Oh, I don't know. I've
just been drinking milk.
After three bottles,
I think I'm good.
I'm kinda starting
to get hungry.
Yeah, actually it is about time
for dinner now, isn't it?
So hungry!
Excuse me, guys.
Dinner's ready now
if you'd like to go eat.
Perfect timing! Our next
activity is dinner!
[GROUP chattering]
♪ Cling to happiness,
or it is yours to lose! ♪
♪ If you don't, then you'll
be sad and that's not fun. ♪
♪ No, that's not
fun for anyone! ♪
♪ So just remember. ♪
♪ Hold on tight ♪
♪ Or you're gonna,
gonna shake! ♪
Yeah!
Usually, we'd toast with beer,
but we'll use juice instead,
'cause I made a vow
never to touch alcohol!
There's also the fact
that we're too young.
[HARUHI]
Anyway, it's been a long trip
and we deserve a toast!
Here's to the Literary Club!
May it keep growing till
it conquers the world!
To the club!
[GROUP]
[ASAKURA]
Time for the first dish!
The nozawana, one of
the local specialties.
[ASAKURA]
Very interesting.
There are notes of some...
Yummy!
They're generous with
the portions here.
You haven't seen half of it!
There's lots more on the way.
She's right.
The list of dishes that they're
serving tonight is extensive,
and really impressive.
[ASAKURA]
This savory egg custard
is impressively executed.
Yummy!
It says "horsemeat" sashimi.
[TSURUYA] From what I've read,
that's a specialty around here.
[ASAKURA] Horsemeat sashimi is
low in fat and in calories.
It's also high in protein.
A good source of nutrition.
[HARUHI]
I didn't know that.
[ASAKURA] Ah, yes, this
is an excellent dish!
It pairs very nicely with
the garlic and ginger.
Hey, Nagato, you should
really try the--
[NAGATO]
Mm!
Oh, never mind.
You already are.
This stuff sure has
an interesting texture.
According to this,
the main dish should be
coming up pretty soon,
and it's Shinshu beef.
Oh, yeah really?
I love beef!
Beef is yummy!
[ASAKURA] Hold still,
you've got a little drool.
Wow, you guys must
really like beef, huh?
I'm not gonna turn it down!
Hello, everybody.
I hope you're enjoying
things so far.
I'm Arakawa, the
inn's master chef.
For today's main dish,
we have a Shinshu beef
roasted on ceramics.
[HARUHI]
Hm...
Wait! I've seen you before!
You have a good memory.
I also drive the
courtesy shuttle.
[TSURUYA]
Well, thank you for all you do!
I like to make sure
that all our guests
enjoy their stays
to the fullest.
Please let us know if there's
anything else we can do.
Yeah! Bring it on!
[ASAKURA] I would consider
this the epitome
of a "meat lover's meat."
[ALL]
Thank you! It was delicious!
I'm having a hard time deciding.
This nozawana stuff was good.
Soy sauce pickles can
last for a long time.
Well, I think it's
time to go back
to our rooms and relax.
You coming, Mikuru?
[yawns] Yeah.
Anything specific you
would like to do?
We could visit the gift shop.
I already picked up my
souvenirs at the temple.
Okay, that's fine.
How about some
after-dinner coffee, then?
Um. Yeah, I guess.
That sounds okay.
[KOIZUMI]
Here you go.
It's hot, so be careful
with that first sip.
Oh, thank you.
[KOIZUMI]
Sure. No problem.
[KYON]
What's up?
Can I interest you in a game?
No, thanks. Not right now.
I think I just
feel like reading.
Oh, sure, I understand.
That's fine.
The atmosphere alone
is relaxing, huh?
[TSURUYA]
Yeah, it really is.
[TV MC A]
Here's the final question!
If you answer this one
correctly, the super-duper,
extra-mega underdog
leapfrog bonus...
[HARUHI]
This inn seems ginourmous.
Yeah, from what
I've gathered so far,
they have the main
building, the annex,
and the new wing, too.
[HARUHI]
Might be fun to explore it.
Ah--
[HARUHI chuckles]
[KYON]
Ahh. Silence is golden.
Let's explore!
They added all kinds
of suspicious rooms
to this inn. C'mon,
let's check it out!
You're gonna come with
us, right, Koizumi?
Oh, yeah.
You, too, Kyon.
No, thank you. Not tonight.
I'm content to bask in
the peace and tranquility
offered by this
fine establishment.
[HARUHI]
Huh. Suit yourself.
It'll be more fun without you,
anyway. C'mon, Koizumi!
See ya later.
I guess I'll go take a bath.
[TV ANNOUNCER A]
Over to you, Mr. Aganakata!
What does tomorrow's
forecast look like?
[AGANAKATA] Well, you see,
when high and low pressure
systems collide like these two
here, they generate clouds.
Those clouds, in turn,
produce rain.
[NAGATO] I think I'm gonna
head back to the baths.
Are you?
They were really nice,
weren't they?
I may come and join you later.
Ah.
[gasps]
Huh?
[KYON]
Uh, Nagato?
[NAGATO]
Oh, sorry!
[KYON]
About what?
[NAGATO] U-Uh, opening the
window without warning.
Yeah, it's an interesting
little feature, isn't it?
We can't actually open it
from this side, you know.
Which is exactly
as it should be.
[NAGATO]
Would you mind if I opened it?
Uh-- Uh, sure.
[KYON]
Here we go.
Almost there.
[HARUHI]
This pond is very suspicious.
I think it's just
an ordinary pond.
Hey, look at that!
We can see the men's
bath from here.
[KOIZUMI] Aren't you getting
cold standing outside like this?
On second thought,
I'll leave it closed.
[KYON]
Oh. Okay.
[NAGATO giggles]
Uh--
[KYON laughs]
[door slides]
[HARUHI] Ew, gross! Now I
feel all hot and sweaty!
[ASAKURA] I told you not to,
but would you listen to me?
No!
[KOIZUMI] I didn't see you
in the room, so I figured.
Well, you know,
I thought I should
get my money's worth, so.
[KOIZUMI]
That's one way to put it.
[MIKURU]
Hi, ladies!
[KYON] Uh-- It sure is
getting lively over there.
[KOIZUMI grunts]
This is our second
time together.
What do you think so far?
Personal space.
And try to choose your
words more carefully.
[KOIZUMI]
You're so mean to me.
I suggest you get over it.
This matchmaking bath
thing is so cool!
I think it would be fun to
give it a try with Mikuru.
Huh? No, not me!
I don't wanna try
anything, thank you!
We should offer those
breasts of yours
to the god of the
matchmaking shrine.
Now that's a worthy offering
if I've ever heard of one!
Yeah, great idea!
Get 'em over here, Mikuru!
[MIKURU whimpers]
[MIKURU]
No, please don't!
[HARUHI]
You don't have a choice!
[TSURUYA]
Is this the string we pull?
[ASAKURA]
Stop it, both of you.
Can't you see how uncomfortable
you're making the poor thing?
[HARUHI] What's the big deal?
It'll just be for a second.
[TSURUYA]
Squeezy, squeezy, squeezy!
[MIKURU]
Nooo!
[ASAKURA]
You are impossible!
Nagato, quit floating around...
It sounds like they're
having fun over there.
[KYON]
A nice, relaxing bath.
There's nothing like it.
[NAGATO] Next episode:
"Give Me Your Hand."