[NAGATO (NEW)]
Time to wake up.
[sighs]
[NAGATO (NEW)]
Hair whorl.
[gasps]
Ow!
[NAGATO groaning]
[NAGATO]
Huh? Hey, where am I?
Is anyone here? Hello?
[gasping]
[NAGATO (NEW)]
Don't get worked up.
[NAGATO]
Huh?
[NAGATO (NEW)]
He'll come to get you soon.
You shouldn't be
alone for too long.
[NAGATO]
Are you me?
Yes, I am.
Oh! It's a dream!
[NAGATO (NEW)]
That's right.
[NAGATO]
It's Asakura.
I, um...
I'm glad you're here. Like I
was saying on the phone.
Yeah, it's weird.
I just woke up.
I... well, I don't know.
I guess I must've been
napping on a park bench.
Oh?
Welcome back. Good to see you.
Yeah. Good to be back.
[NAGATO (NEW)]
Something happened.
You were in an accident
on your way home.
An accident? Whoa.
That's right.
You went to sleep
for a little while
as a result of shock
from the accident.
I took your place, living as
Yuki Nagato while you slept.
[NAGATO] Jeez, that's some
pretty crazy paranormal stuff.
[NAGATO (NEW)] We're not
talking about anything crazy.
This is nothing supernatural.
It's just a dream.
Your brain is simply
taking a moment
to organize your memories.
So, we're having a little chat.
You won't remember
when you wake up.
[NAGATO]
So, we're just killing time?
Oh! Hey, I know! Maybe
you can fill me in on stuff.
What happened when I was asleep?
[NAGATO (NEW)]
Not telling.
[NAGATO]
What?
But won't I find out anyway?
Since my memories are
being organized, and all.
[NAGATO (NEW)]
True enough,
but that's the brain
doing its own thing.
I really don't wanna
talk about it...
...so I'm not going to.
Except for one thing.
I told him how I felt.
[NAGATO]
Huh?
[NAGATO (NEW)] You know,
that I had feelings for him.
[NAGATO]
What?
Whoa! This other me has
got some serious guts.
[NAGATO (NEW)]
To be clear,
I told him how I felt,
the new Yuki, not the old.
Right. You and I are
different people, I know.
But you're pretty amazing.
I did it. And you can too.
Right.
[NAGATO giggles]
[NAGATO (NEW)]
What is it?
[NAGATO] We both like the
same person. It's kinda funny.
[NAGATO (NEW)]
Well, we can't help it.
It's him.
[NAGATO] You're right.
We're totally helpless.
[ASAKURA] It's nice
how quickly clothes dry
with the rainy season over.
[ASAKURA]
Do me a favor?
[NAGATO]
Hm?
I need to bring the laundry in.
Will you grab the basket?
[NAGATO]
Sure.
[ASAKURA]
Back to your old self.
That or you've rediscovered your
obsession with gaming, anyway.
[NAGATO]
I like books, too.
I just like games
more, that's all.
[ASAKURA]
What, like comic books?
[NAGATO]
That's mean.
Ha! Hey, I'm teasing you!
[NAGATO] Would you like it
better if I liked books more?
Well, honestly,
considering that Miss Asakura
isn't much of a gamer herself,
she probably would like
it if you read more.
I understand.
[ASAKURA]
I'm just kidding.
You can think of it as payback
for asking me such
a ridiculous question.
Uh... I'm sorry.
Come on, I can tell
something's still bothering you.
[NAGATO] It's your reaction
when I came home that night.
You were happy to see me,
I could tell that,
but... you seemed
sorta sad, too.
Well, how could I not be?
It was really sudden
and confusing.
I needed to collect myself.
But, in the end,
it was actually simple.
I just had to ask myself how
I felt about the two of you.
[NAGATO]
Uh...
And do you know what I realized?
You and the other Yuki
are both my good friends,
and nothing's going
to change that.
So, just try to relax.
Be yourself and don't
think about it too much.
And before you know it,
I'll be back to
scolding you as usual.
Sound good?
[NAGATO]
Mh-hm.
It's a beautiful day outside.
Stop looking so
gloomy, would you?
[NAGATO]
Okay.
Good, that's it! See?
You're sounding more like
yourself every second.
[groans]
[ASAKURA] It is beautiful,
but it's so hot.
There's no denying
that summer's here.
Oh! We need to get you
some new bathing suits.
[NAGATO]
We do?
[ASAKURA]
Well, we'll be hanging out
with Kyon a lot over the break.
So it can't hurt, right?
[NAGATO]
Uhh...
[ASAKURA giggles]
[ASAKURA] What style do you
think we should go with?
I'm sure we can find
something that looks good.
[NAGATO]
Yep.
Ugh.
[ASAKURA]
Lovely morning, isn't it?
Not really.
Did you get your
math homework done?
For your sake, I hope so.
I don't like it when you ask
to copy mine at the last second.
[KYON]
Well, in that case,
maybe I should copy it now.
[ASAKURA]
Uh.
[NAGATO]
I've got my work done. You?
Yep. Why don't we compare
our answers, just to be safe.
I'll find mine real quick.
Hey. Good morning.
Morning. How are yo--?
[NAGATO (NEW)]
I love you.
[grunts]
[KYON] Man. It's really hot
in here, don't you think?
--I could use some air.
--What's the deal?
[ASAKURU] Hey! Did you wanna
copy down my answers or not?
[KYON]
Pathetic.
I need to get it together.
[ASAKURA]
Hm?
Great, what a mess.
Is there somethin' wrong?
Oh, uh, no.
You wanna play?
Naw. I'm good, thanks.
You go ahead.
Hello! How's it goin'?
It's been such a long time!
How's everybody doin'?
Hey, guys.
Just when I was getting
used to the peace and quiet.
[HARUHI] ...like fail your tests
or something dumb like that.
Let's get straight
to the point, Kyon.
[KYON]
Um, okay.
Do you know what day today is?
I don't know, maybe
it's your birthday?
[HARUHI]
Not even!
Well, do you want to
know when my birthday is?
[HARUHI]
That is not important.
I didn't think this
would be so difficult.
Fine. How 'bout this: Which
month and which day is today?
It's July 7th. So what?
Oh, wait. I think I might know.
You're gonna suggest we
do something for Tanabata,
aren't you?
Exactly! Yes, I am!
I've decided all club members
will begin celebrating
Tanabata starting this year!
You might've asked us first.
Did she mention anything
about Tanabata to you?
Huh? Well...
Of course we did. Me and Yuki
talked about it on the phone.
[NAGATO]
We did? Ahh...
[NAGATO whimpering]
[ASAKURA] So, you did
know about it, didn't you?
All right, boys,
you're comin' with me.
We've got a lot to do. Come on!
Can you at least tell me
where she's dragging us to?
I don't know.
Well, what are you
waiting for? Move it!
[KYON]
Okay, fine.
Good luck. Be careful.
Yeah.
Well, I'll see you
later then, I guess.
[sighs]
And what am I supposed
to do with this, exactly?
Well, it's obvious, isn't it?
We need bamboo to
hang our wishes on,
so in there and get some!
[KYON]
Wait a sec!
I'm pretty sure this
is private property.
I don't love the idea
of stealing bamboo.
[HARUHI]
Don't worry,
I came up with a good excuse
and got permission already!
[KYON] You're good at getting
people to let you do stuff.
It's a blessing.
Now, enough talk.
Go get in there!
I'm counting on you!
And one more thing.
If your bamboo isn't perfect,
you'll have to do it again!
Okay, okay.
Awesome. Back for one day
and she's already got
us doing crazy stuff.
[KOIZUMI chuckles]
[KOIZUMI]
Exams are long and grueling.
Miss Suzumiya's just
blowing off some steam.
We've been gone a long time.
You seem quiet.
How have you been?
Oh, I'm fine. It's just that--
[grunts]
[KOIZUMI]
Mm?
Well, a lot's
happened, that's all.
You can't stop there.
You've got me curious.
[gasps]
What was that?
I was tryin' to help you out.
Huh?
Ah! They're all over!
This place is swarming
with mosquitoes!
[KOIZUMI chuckling]
[KOIZUMI]
Little flying vampires.
[KYON] Let's just get the
bamboo and get out of here!
[KOIZUMI]
I'm on it.
Ugh. I don't get it.
Why is Kyon making such a big
deal over tiny little insects?
[HARUHI]
July 7th, four years ago.
I can't believe
it's been that long.
[NAGATO]
Whoa. That looks nice!
[ASAKURA] Yeah. It's an
excellent bamboo specimen.
[HARUHI]
Isn't it?
All thanks to my
precise instructions!
We would've been lost
without your guidance.
Well, I'm glad you like it.
'Cause I'll tell you what,
this bamboo didn't come cheap.
I paid for it with my blood.
Behold. My badges of honor.
Those don't look pleasant.
Yeah, well, they itch,
that's for sure.
[HARUHI]
Oh, please!
If you'd been more careful,
you wouldn't have so many bites.
Personally, I'd say they're
proof of your defeat,
not badges of honor.
[KYON]
Interesting how she hung back
and let us go in there alone.
Confess! You knew about
the mosquitoes, didn't you?
[HARUHI humming]
[KYON]
She's a real jerk.
I found it!
Scratching like that
will only make it worse.
Here, put some of
this on. It should help.
Ah. Great, thanks.
Hm?
You can go first.
That's nice of you.
[HARUHI]
Not bad so far,
but I wonder how we
should decorate it.
We want it to look
festive but appropriate.
[KYON grunting]
I've even got some back there.
Oh. Looks like you're
having a hard time.
I could help you with that.
[KYON]
Uh. No, I'm fine.
I don't think I need to put
any of that cream on my back.
It doesn't really itch that
much anymore, but thanks.
No problem.
[KYON]
Yeah.
[KOIZUMI]
All right, fearless leader.
What should we do next?
[HARUHI]
These!
Time to write out our wishes?
How fun! I don't remember
the last time I did that.
I have to think
about what to put.
Okay! You need to keep
certain parameters in mind
when you're writing
down your wishes.
Parameters?
Here's the question:
"Who are the deities
that are going to make all
your dreams come true?"
The stars Vega and Altair
represent the gods
Orihime and Hikoboshi.
They're light years away,
so we could make our wishes
for far in the future.
Is that right?
[HARUHI crying]
I don't get it.
Was it something I said?
You never let me have
any fun! This is...
Sorry! I didn't mean
to steal your thunder.
Was there a particular time
frame you had in mind?
We can go with between 16
and 25 years if you'd like.
[HARUHI]
Mm.
But that's just the distance
from here to there, isn't it?
So won't it take twice as long
for our wishes to be granted?
Ha. A little detail! The gods'll
sort it out, I'm sure.
At least, I bet that's what
Miss Suzumiya would say.
Are you channeling her now,
or something? Just what we need.
[KOIZUMI chuckling]
I have two. I hope that's okay.
[HARUHI]
Okay, guys!
Once you're done,
hang 'em all up!
[KYON] Well, Haruhi,
what'd you wish for?
[KYON groaning]
You deserved it!
I can tell you're thinking
something snarky.
Let's hear what you wished
for before I tell ya mine!
Well, I wished for...
Ugh!
Well, what's wrong with that?
Pathetic. It's obviously
a weak attempt
by an 11th grader with
limited intelligence.
Well, I think it was
pretty clever, actually.
Where do you think I should hang
these? The tree's getting full.
[chuckles] I can do it for you.
Would you mind? That'd be great!
I can tell those are yours.
They're so practical
and well thought out.
I like how
altruistic yours were.
You didn't just wish for
money like some people might.
[KYON]
No lottery winnings for her.
Hm?
Naga-- Uh.
[KYON]
Hold on.
You don't need to hang
'em so low. Let me help.
[BOTH gasp]
Higher up would be perfect.
Here, thank you.
Yeah, sure. Leave it to me.
It looks even better outside,
like we're returning it
to nature or something.
[ASAKURA]
It does look good.
It makes me feel like our
wishes really will come true.
[HARUHI]
Hmm...
Something happened to
you while we were gone.
[KYON]
Oh, it's you.
[HARUHI]
So, what was it?
[HARUHI] Did the other Yuki
tell you how she felt about you?
[gasps]
Hey! How did you know that?
Well, you just
confirmed it for me!
[KYON]
Huh?
[HARUHI] Ryoko told me earlier
about what happened to Yuki.
The rest was easy to guess
from how you've been acting.
So...
[HARUHI chuckles]
What? You get nervous
when you talk to her?
Have you ever thought
about just asking her out?
It's not that simple.
[KYON] The two Nagatos
are different people.
This has nothing to do
with the current Nagato.
Well, it'd be easier if
I could really think that.
Funny how these things work.
She doesn't even remember it,
but I still feel nervous.
Well, that's stupid.
Hey! What's taking
you guys so long?
The party's happenin' down
here if you haven't noticed.
[HARUHI]
She doesn't even remember, huh?
Something wrong?
Come on, let's get going!
Okay.
[KYON] Hey! What do
you think you're doing?
[HARUHI]
Huh?
Well, isn't it obvious?
Trespassing, of course.
[chuckling]
Well, I could use
help with something.
[KYON]
What?
Since you didn't stop me,
you're already my accomplice.
[groans]
[KYON]
So, what're we gonna do next?
[HARUHI] Do I have to explain
everything little thing to you?
[HARUHI chuckles]
We're gonna write
a note for the aliens!
[HARUHI]
Hey.
[KYON]
Hm?
So, what do you think?
Do you think aliens
are real or not?
I don't know.
[KYON]
They could be real.
[HARUHI]
Yeah?
[KYON]
Hm?
Weren't you the one in a hurry?
It doesn't even matter...
if she remembers.
What matters is that it's
important to you, right?
Just write it off.
Something significant
happened between you two.
She may not know it.
But at least somebody
does now, right?
You're right.
Although, I still have the
right to tease you mercilessly
if I choose to.
Absolutely, I would expect
no less of you, Haruhi.
I can't help it!
My motto is: "Always enjoy
yourself at every opportunity."
I guess I got a little sappy
there for a minute.
And we all know, sentiment
doesn't go with fun.
I think you're right.
We'll have to be more careful.
I'm sorry, by the way, for
inciting you to sappiness.
That's fine, but it'll cost ya.
[giggles]
Here they are!
We've got sweet dumplings,
courtesy of Miss Tsuruya.
Hey, Haru! Long time no see!
Come on, you two, we're gonna
need help eating all these.
You should really have
some. They're yummy.
Don't you know better than
to speak with your mouth full?
--Yeah.
--[MIKURU yelps]
[TSURUYA laughing]
[BOTH laughing]
[HARUHI]
I was at that awkward age
when growing up is
confusing and strange.
Common sense was
edging out imagination,
and that was depressing.
Hey, looks like
they're having fun.
[HARUHI]
And then I met you.
You helped me, even
though you didn't want to.
You helped me see that
imagination wasn't dead.
Hey, wait a minute. Aren't
those the last two pieces?
[KYON]
Huh?
You were supposed to share.
Yeah, okay.
[HARUHI] You're the one who
saved me... from my despair.
[chuckles]
[HARUHI]
So, what's your name?
[KYON]
John Smith.
[HARUHI]
That's a stupid name!
[NAGATO]
Next episode: "His Uncertainty."