[TAXI DRIVER panting]
Are you hurt anywhere?
Oh my gosh are you okay?
Can you say something? Miss?
[TAXI DRIVER]
Uh...
Oh, neat, a fireworks show!
That sounds like a good excuse
to get everyone together.
[sighs] The rain still shows
no sign of stopping.
[TAXI DRIVER]
Miss. Hey. Miss!
Are you okay?
[TAXI DRIVER]
There's a hospital nearby.
Get in my cab.
I'll take you to--
I'm fine, thanks.
The fall wasn't bad.
It probably looked a lot
worse than it felt.
[TAXI DRIVER]
But, I can see you're hurt.
We should at least have you
checked at the hospital.
A few scratches. Nothing more.
[TAXI DRIVER]
Even so.
[NAGATO]
It was my fault.
[TAXI DRIVER]
I don't know.
Are you really sure you're fine?
[NAGATO]
I'm sure. I promise I'm fine.
[TAXI DRIVER] At least let
me pay for your glasses.
And if there's anything else,
get in touch, all right?
[car engine revs]
[ASAKURA] What? You almost
got hit by a car?
[NAGATO]
Yeah.
"Yeah"? Just "yeah"?
Huh?
[gasps] You're hurt!
I'm okay.
No! I can see your injuries.
You should undress.
Are there more?
Hurry, get out
of those clothes.
Let me check.
We have to be sure you're okay!
Let me help you.
[sighs] Well, you were right,
luckily it's nothing
but scratches.
Wait, why aren't you
wearing your glasses?
[NAGATO]
They got broken.
[gasps] I didn't see that!
You've got some on
your forehead, too.
Aren't you worried about
ending up with scars?
Let's get out the first-aid kit.
You have one, right?
You're overreacting.
Huh?
"Overreacting"? I am
not overreacting!
Yeah, okay, the car
didn't actually hit you,
and you're just a
little banged up.
But it could easily
have been so much worse!
[ASAKURA]
We're talking about a car, here.
If things had gone differently,
you could have died, Nagato.
[ASAKURA cries]
You're right. I'm sorry.
[ASAKURA] I just wanted
you to take it seriously.
Anyway, it's fine. Let's clean
those cuts and get some
bandages on them, okay?
All right.
That should take
care of it for now.
It might be kind of annoying,
but it'll help you heal faster,
so try to put up
with it, if you can.
And just to be
on the safe side,
I think we should go to
the hospital tomorrow.
[NAGATO]
I'm all right.
But you never know.
[NAGATO]
I'm fine.
Okay. If you say so.
Well. Should we
have dinner, then?
[doorbell rings]
Good morning!
How are you feeling?
You're ready a lot
earlier than usual.
And your glasses...
It's a back-up pair.
Since the ones I
normally wear got broken.
Yeah, that's right.
Good thing you have
a spare pair.
So, you're fine?
Those scratches didn't bother
you too much last night?
I could sleep at
your place tonight,
just to help out if
you need anything.
You don't need to.
Really, don't be shy.
We're good friends.
I'd be more than
happy to come over.
It could even be fun!
[KYON]
What? She got hit by a car?
No, no, no. She only
almost got hit.
She said she was
lost in thought,
and the rain made
it hard to see.
So she just didn't
notice the car coming.
[KYON] She's bandaged up.
Did she get hurt?
[ASAKURA]
No, not really.
Just some scratches
here and there, is all.
That's good, then.
Coulda been a lot worse.
It's great she wasn't
seriously injured.
Yeah, I guess.
Hm? So why don't you
seem happier about it?
[ASAKURA]
Hm?
[sighs]
She says that she's fine,
but something about
her seems off to me.
She just hasn't been
acting like herself.
Well, it must have been
a pretty big shock.
I mean, she's reading, right?
Which is weird for her.
Maybe she doesn't even
have enough energy
to play her games.
You make a good point.
That must be what's
really going on!
Huh?
After what she went through,
she must have been so exhausted!
But what did I do? I just
kept nagging and nagging.
[yells]
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[KYON]
Whoa, hey! Calm down!
[sighs] I'm not the
easiest person to talk to.
It's possible she wanted
to say something to me
but couldn't bring
herself to do it.
You can be sort of intimidating
and bossy at times,
and when you're angry,
you just get
downright frightening.
[ASAKURA moans]
[gasps]
[KYON] Hey. You didn't
forbid her from going out
or anything like that, did you?
Well, I admit, I
thought about it.
But I do have some self-control.
[KYON sighs]
That's good to hear.
She'll probably respond better
if you're not too
protective of her.
[ASAKURA sighs]
I know, I know.
[bell rings]
[KYON] Not good. I don't
remember a thing.
Like everything the teacher
said leaked out of my brain.
And the next test is gonna be
super comprehensive. Man, I wish
I remembered things better, too.
[TANIGUCHI]
Jeez, what's goin' on over here?
I'm gettin' depressed
just lookin' at you guys.
Fortunately, I'm in possession
of some valuable information.
It oughta cheer you right up.
Yeah, right. Valuable
information from you?
[KUNIKIDA] Well? What is it,
then? Come on, tell us!
[TANIGUCHI]
I just heard this from the guys
in the Tennis Club.
Don't go spreading it around,
but there's a seriously
hot chick working
at the minimart by the station.
[KUNIKIDA]
Aw jeez, why am I not surprised?
The only kind of
information you ever seem
to have is about girls.
[TANIGUCHI]
Hey, what do you want from me?
I can't help what kind of
info comes my way, can I?
[KUNIKIDA]
You look pleased with yourself.
[TANIGUCHI]
Why shouldn't I?
Anyway, what do you say?
Let's carve out
some time after school
to go check her out.
Might as well lift our
spirits before the test.
[TANIGUCHI] Hey, are you
even listening? Kyon?
Huh?
Something bothering you?
What? No, I'm fine.
And I was totally
listening to you.
You're gonna play tennis
at a minimart later today,
am I right?
That's so not what I said.
[KYON grunts]
Hey, can you do me a favor?
[KYON]
Hm?
One of the teachers asked
if I could take care of
something after school today.
Could you look after
Nagato for me?
Make sure she gets home,
that sort of thing.
Sure. I got it.
Do what you need.
Great, thank you.
[ASAKURA]
See you later, Nagato.
[NAGATO]
Yeah.
Look after her. That
sounds easy enough.
[KYON]
Class is over.
Should we head to the clubroom?
[KYON sighs]
So, Nagato...
What book are you reading?
Le M-Me-Mys-Mystere de la.
Right. Looks good.
[KYON yawns]
[KYON] It sure is quiet when
Haruhi isn't around, isn't it?
I'm not gonna lie,
it's kinda relaxing.
Huh?
[book flaps]
[KYON]
Mm?
You know, I was thinking.
This reminds me of when
I first joined the club.
We didn't have
any real activities.
We just sort of did whatever
we felt like at the time.
Another book, huh?
What are you reading now?
[KYON]
Le P-Per-Parf-Parfum de la--
Yeah, okay. That
looks good, too.
[ASAKURA]
Okay, bye!
[door slides]
[sighs] Maybe those
two are still around.
I should check.
Oh yeah, I meant to tell you.
I saw you changed your glasses.
Were you just wanting to
mix things up a little?
You do seem kinda
different today.
These are my spares.
My usual pair got broken.
Oh. All right.
You know, I heard
about yesterday.
Sounded rough.
[NAGATO]
Did Asakura tell you?
[KYON]
Hm? Well, yeah.
[NAGATO]
Oh.
[KYON]
So, how are you feeling?
I mean, she told me that
you're basically okay, but--
[KYON]
Hm? What's the matter?
[NAGATO]
Are you worried about me?
What kind of question is that?
Of course I am!
Uh, what's up? I mean, um.
You're kinda staring at me.
[NAGATO]
Well...
Thank you.
Huh?
Thank you for being concerned.
That's nice of you.
Uh--
Oh--
[gasps]
[ASAKURA]
What's going on?
Uh, the bandage
was peeling off!
We wouldn't want your cuts
getting infected, would we?
No.
U-Uh...
Well. Yeah. Anyway, I'm sorry.
Sorry about what?
Huh? Well, uh...
Nagato?
[NAGATO]
Let's go.
Right. Okay.
[KYON] You're gonna go get
your glasses fixed, right?
I'll go with you. I've got
some shopping to do, so.
[sighs]
Man, it's gonna take a
long time to fix them, huh?
I guess with the frame
totally messed up
like that, it's not surprising.
[KYON]
At least they can fix them.
That's better than
buying another pair.
[KYON]
So, it looks like you're stuck
with your spares
for a while, then.
They seem to work
well enough, though.
And they look nice.
So you're okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
Oh, all right. Well,
that's good, then.
Hey, look. A taiyaki cake shop.
[KYON]
Wanna get some?
[NAGATO]
Yes.
[KYON]
Okay!
[yawns]
[KYON] The summer festival
is coming up soon.
[door clicks]
Hey there!
I thought we would try
putting some cheese
in the curry we made yesterday.
You like that, right?
Curry with cheese?
Well, what do ya
think of it?
Should we add a
little more cheese?
No, this is fine.
Yeah?
I can't believe I almost
forgot to tell you!
Daikon radish was on sale today,
so I made sure to stock up.
We'll have to use it
for oden sometime soon.
That should be good
with the rain.
And it won't be nearly as good
once summer gets here.
Sorry to interrupt.
Ah. No, not at all. What is it?
On the table.
Huh?
Oh! Whoops, I'm sorry.
I didn't even notice
I made a mess.
I should really start eating,
it's gonna get cold!
It's pretty good.
[ASAKURA]
You might wanna hold off
bathing another night.
It'll sting your cuts.
[NAGATO]
'Kay.
And I know I've
already said it,
but I want to put
it out there again.
If you need anything,
you can call me anytime.
I'll come right
over to help you.
[NAGATO]
Mm-hm.
And, as far as going
out is concerned...
"Going out"?
[gasps] Never mind.
Forget I said anything.
I'm being silly.
I don't think it's silly.
It's nice of you
to worry about me.
That's what friends are for.
[ASAKURA]
Actually...
There is just one more thing.
Who are you?
And where's Nagato?
[NAGATO]
Next episode:
"The Disappearance of
Nagato Yuki, Part One."