[COACH A]
Move it, boys!
[HARUHI] Anyway, I wanted
to teach them a lesson,
so I ordered them
to go buy some snacks.
Wow.
So you sent them out in
this weather for supplies
that we don't even need?
It's pretty cold out there.
Yep. That's kinda the idea!
[ASAKURA] Aren't you
chilly in that outfit?
It doesn't look warm.
[HARUHI laughs]
I'm just fine, thank you!
I feel bad for
Koizumi. Poor guy.
[HARUHI]
What about Kyon?
[ASAKURA giggles]
[door clicks]
Hello there, everyone!
[MIKURU]
Hi, how are you today?
Ah! Mikuru's here!
[MIKURU yelps]
[TSURUYA]
That's far enough.
Huh?
You don't think I'll just
let you play with Mikuru?
If you want to do that,
first you're gonna
have to get through me!
Ha!
You wanna piece
of me? Fine, let' go.
[HARUHI, TSURUYA]
Ha!
I don't think so!
Battles are forbidden
in the clubroom.
Isn't that right, President?
[NAGATO]
Huh?
Aw. How am I supposed to
ignore someone that cute?
I have to admit, I understand
that feeling well.
No! Not you, too!
[TSURUYA] If you saw Mikuru
sitting on the sidewalk,
how could you not take her home?
Excuse me!
You're talking about me like
a kitten or pocket change.
[ASAKURA] Let's press pause
on this for a moment.
If we're discussing cute girls,
then why don't I
hear Nagato's name?
Wait! This isn't a competition!
I'm afraid you leave
me with little choice.
I accept your challenge!
[gasps]
Okay!
Cute Fact Number One:
when Nagato's sleeping
and I try to wake her up,
she calls me "Mom."
You'll catch cold
if you're not careful!
Just five more
minutes, Mom, okay?
How is that an example
of being cute?
Hold on! Do I actually do that?
[cackles] Not good enough.
Mikuru bumps into a pole
whenever she chases a cat.
When she looks up at the sky,
she sticks her foot in a puddle.
Ah! It's not like these are
things I do every day!
They only happen sometimes.
Oh! That's nothing!
Nagato sets time aside
every single day
to stare at her tummy
in the mirror!
Why would you even
tell them about that?
It's not a "most
embarrassing story" contest!
If that's how you're gonna play,
I can do you one better:
there's a birthmark
shaped like a star
on Mikuru's chest.
Hold on, I didn't
even know that!
Are you sure? Oh my
goodness there is one!
[gasps] Oh, I see I'm
facing off against a master.
I didn't expect you to
know things about Mikuru
that she didn't even know.
What're you gonna do?
If you leave it at that,
you'll lose for sure.
Uh, let's not egg her on, okay?
Um, you're done, right?
Please say you're done.
There's nothing else
you know, is there?
Actually, there is.
There is?
Nagato went shopping.
She attempted to
do so in secret.
She purchased ingredients for
Valentine's Day chocolate.
[gasps]
[HARUHI]
Hmm.
How nice.
No shame in sharing
a holiday, is there?
Okay. Well...
So, you bought a
little chocolate.
That's not really embarrassing.
Yeah, there's no reason
to be so secretive about it.
You see, Nagato?
--[gasping]
--[GIRLS cackle]
[TEACHER 4A]
During the Heian Era, courtship
depended upon wealth,
family status, and one other
very important and
surprising factor:
the ability to
write good poetry.
[ASAKURA]
Hey!
Ow! Geez!
Did that hurt?
It wasn't very hard.
Well, I guess it was
hard enough, huh?
What do you want?
Well, here's the thing.
Hm?
[TEACHER B]
All right. Moving on.
Here is how we find the
coordinates of the intersection
of a parabola and
a straight line.
[KYON]
Hm. Huh?
Well, this is a surprise.
Spending your time
out here waiting for me?
I like the change
in your attitude!
[laughs] Hey, it looks
like you're alone.
Where's your shadow?
[HARUHI]
Couldn't make it today.
Busy or something.
Okay. That works.
Turns out Asakura and Nagato
had something to do today, too.
Huh?
I didn't wanna sit in
the clubroom by myself.
So we cancelled today's meeting
and I came out here to tell you.
I thought I would save you
the trouble of trespassing
on school grounds again.
You just cancelled
the meeting without
consulting the
executive president?
[KYON] You're not even
a real club member!
[HARUHI]
Oh. I get it!
Today is the 13th.
That must be why the
other two are busy.
[yelps] Okay, I'll just
be on my way, then.
Just a second.
We're not done here.
What is it now? I'm very busy.
Places to go. People to see.
[chuckles] Whatever!
You're comin' with me.
Like I said--
Yeah, I don't care!
[KYON]
Wait! Hey! Where are we going?
Are you listening to me?
[ASAKURA]
All right.
Now I guess we just have
to decide where to start.
[NAGATO]
Yeah!
[ASAKURA] So, were there any
ingredients you didn't buy?
[HARUHI] So, here's the deal.
You know the saying,
"Good things come
to those who wait"?
Yeah, well, I think
it's all wrong.
I'm not getting out of
here anytime soon, am I?
If you ask me, you won't
accomplish anything
sitting around and waiting
for bizarre occurrences
and mysterious
phenomena to happen.
You gotta go out there and
hunt them down yourself.
That's the key.
[KYON]
Right...
So, basically,
if we don't want
to die of boredom,
we need to get off our butts
and start lookin'
for mysterious stuff!
[KYON]
We do?
Of course!
Good things don't just
come to those who wait!
I bet they're out there waiting
for me to come to them!
[KYON] Actually, my guess
is they'd be perfectly happy
never to cross your path.
That's enough!
Time to go out and
find some mysteries!
Where, exactly?
I dunno.
[KYON]
What?
Have a little faith,
why don't you?
Look, just because we don't
know where we're going
doesn't mean we won't get there.
Doesn't that make sense?
Not even a little bit.
Ah! We'll go search this
city from top to bottom!
We'll be like the Marco Polos of
unsolved mysteries or somethin'.
Fine. I give up. You win.
There you go!
I think that should
do it. Are you ready?
[NAGATO]
Mm-hm.
Oh, you know.
We never talked about
what we're making yet.
Was there a specific
chocolate you had in mind?
Based on the ingredients
you've got here,
it doesn't look like you want
something too elaborate.
Oh! Well. Um...
The kind you melt and then
pour in a bowl and
then top with stuff,
and then put in
the refrigerator?
[ASAKURA] I dunno why,
but I get the feeling
that if I don't step in,
this is going to go very wrong
very quickly.
Hmm.
I do like the
simplicity of that idea,
but maybe we could take
it a step or two further.
Like, how about a
heart-shaped chocolate cake?
[gasps] A heart!
No, I think that's
a little too much!
Oh? All right.
If you're trying to keep it
even simpler than that,
I'm not sure how much you're
going to need my help, though.
Well, it'll be okay.
Why don't we just get started
by melting the chocolate?
[NAGATO grunting]
[BOTH yelp]
No--!
[bowl clatters]
Don't worry. You'll be okay.
[NAGATO]
All right!
[ASAKURA]
You can do it! I believe in you!
No! Stop!
Wha--?
How about we try this instead?
We'll melt it over a bowl
of simmering water.
Oh yeah?
Otherwise it won't melt right.
Chocolate is temperamental.
Oh!
Whoa! Look at that!
Look how well it's melting!
Oh, good.
So it turns out
that there's plenty
I can help you with, after all.
They gotta be hiding
here somewhere!
[KYON] Dancing around in
a river in February.
Hey! You'll freeze to death!
Maybe you should
get outta there!
I just need a little longer!
I want a water imp!
[KYON]
Come on!
Aren't you taking
this a little far?
Fall in and you're done for.
[giggling] Look, I'm dancing!
It's fine!
[KYON, HARUHI yelp]
[sighs] I almost just died!
[KYON]
Stunning coordination.
Okay, fine. I give in.
[gasps] Well?
I came to help.
Well, good! As you should.
Oh, shut up!
Now, come on, Kyon! Follow me!
[yelps]
Haruhi!
[KYON, HARUHI grunt]
Um. That was close. Thanks.
[sighs] Yeah, sure.
Don't mention it.
[HARUHI] Your feet must be
pretty cold. I'm sorry.
Oh, don't be sorry.
I'm gonna get you back for this.
I'll put an imp in your
shoe or something.
Just you wait.
[BOTH laugh]
[NAGATO] How 'bout the
sprinkles? Like this?
[ASAKURA]
Yeah, it looks super cute.
[KYON grunts]
Winter!
[HARUHI]
Be honest.
Do you think water imps
are real or not?
[KYON]
I dunno. They could be real.
[HARUHI]
Huh?
[KYON]
You ready? Haruhi!
[HARUHI gasps]
Yeah, what?
We're done here, aren't
we? Let's go home.
[HARUHI]
That's just like you!
Tryin' to leave me behind!
[KYON]
Ow! What was that for?
I just wanna go home.
[HARUHI] So, where should
we look tomorrow?
[KYON sighs]
You're kidding. Right?
[ASAKURA] Whew! Well,
the hard part is over.
Now let's get them in the
fridge so they can harden up.
[NAGATO]
Mm-hm.
[gasps] No, no, no!
That'll only keep me up later.
Well,
once again you couldn't sleep,
so you played a game,
and that's when you lost
track of time. Right?
Yes. Sorry, ma'am.
[ASAKURA laughs]
What am I going to do with you?
Get out of bed and
wash up. Let's go!
We need to get going!
Could you please hurry?
Right. Sure!
[ASAKURA]
What are you doing in there?
I'm coming!
[door clicks]
All you have to do now
is give him the chocolate,
but when?
Oh, well, uh. I don't know.
During club activities would
make the most sense.
[ASAKURA]
Hmm.
Then we'll have to find
a way for you to be alone
with him sometime
this afternoon.
Just him and me?
[ASAKURA] Why don't you ask
to speak to him one on one.
[NAGATO]
I don't know. That sounds hard.
[yelps]
[ASAKURA]
Time to suck it up!
You already worked up the nerve
to give him the
chocolate, silly!
How much harder can it be to
ask him to talk to you alone?
I bet it could be
pretty hard, actually.
Just stay strong.
No matter how
difficult it may seem,
you have to give him
those chocolates, okay?
[gasps]
Yes. I will stay strong.
[TANIGUCHI]
All right!
Time for some tasty chocolates!
Well, where are they?
Kyon, does it look like
something's missing here to you?
Oh, Taniguchi.
The higher your hopes, the
greater your disappointment.
It's chocolate time!
♪ Chocolate for me!
Chocolate for me! ♪
What, still nothing?
Kyon, does it look like
something's missing here to you?
Taniguchi. Practice acceptance.
It will help you to avoid
unnecessary suffering.
[TSURUYA]
Nagato!
Hello there! So, on your
way to lunch, huh?
Where's Asa today? Don't you
usually eat together?
P-Please don't run off
without warning like that.
I can't keep up with you!
I was actually on my
way to the clubroom
to meet up with her.
You were, were you?
It's decided, then!
We're gonna have our lunch in
the Literary Club's room, too.
That sounds good
to you, doesn't it?
Hm? Well, sure.
It's okay with me, but
maybe we should ask her.
Huh?
[MIKURU]
May we join you for lunch?
Huh? Oh, yeah. Of course.
It's no problem!
I knew that's what
you would say!
[MIKURU]
Well, thanks.
There's lots of tension
in the classroom today,
so it'll be more comfortable
eating somewhere else.
What do you mean, "tension"?
Well, you know.
It's Valentine's Day
today, right?
So the guys have got
themselves all worked up.
[NAGATO]
Oh. That does sound tense.
I don't know. I think
you're exaggerating.
They're like hungry dogs!
If we don't give 'em
something to chew on,
I don't know what'll happen.
Things could get
pretty frightening.
There are more than 100 guys
in the Mikuru fan club!
That must be an exaggeration.
[gasps] Oh, no.
Don't tell me you made
chocolate for all of them!
[laughs]
You're not denying it.
Please deny it.
[NAGATO]
Is it true?
[TSURUYA]
Hm?
Well, uh, this might
be a stupid question.
but do guys really sit
around hoping to get
Valentine's chocolate from the
girl they're interested in?
Are you kidding?
Of course they do!
They may like to play it cool,
but nobody can ignore
Valentine's Day.
They care about this stuff
as much as girls, ya know.
[NAGATO]
I didn't know that.
So, if they get chocolate
from a girl they don't like,
is it just embarrassing?
Oh, well, I don't
know about that.
Totally possible!
Don't say that!
[TSURUYA] Sorry, but it is.
I mean, guys are human, too,
and that kind of reaction
is only natural.
[TSURUYA] The point is, how
he reacts shouldn't matter!
Here's the thing.
A gift like this is about
how the one giving it feels.
It's something you do for
your own sake, not his.
So don't worry about
what he might be thinking.
Just take those chocolates.
and throw 'em at him with
everything you've got!
[MIKURU] She probably shouldn't
actually throw them.
[TSURUYA laughs]
Oh, whoops. That was dumb.
I forgot to get
something to drink!
I'm just gonna go
grab something.
Feel free to start without me.
[door clicks]
I really don't think
she'll mind at all.
I say we go ahead
and start eating.
Okay. Sounds good to me.
[MIKURU]
Great! I'm hungry.
Uh, there's something
you should know.
Yes?
It's, well, um...
You know, earlier...
Miss Tsuruya was actually
trying to be encouraging.
It's how she talks. She wasn't
being mean or anything.
That? Don't worry, I know.
[MIKURU] She's not always
the most sensitive person
in the world, but...
True. But that's okay.
[MIKURU]
And, um. If you want my opinion,
I think he'll be happy
to get them from you.
[gasps]
He might not show it, 'cause,
you know how guys
can be all tough.
But if I was a guy and
you gave me chocolate.
I would definitely be happy!
[gasps]
[laughs nervously] Wow, that
kind of made it sound like
I was confessing my love to you.
I'm not so good at
explaining things.
It's all right.
I know what you meant.
[MIKURU, NAGATO gsap]
Oh, my! Did you hear
what I just heard?
I certainly did, and
it was pretty clear.
That most definitely sounded
like a confession of love to me.
I'm so sorry. I hate
to have to tell you.
Huh?
I'm afraid Nagato's heart
is no longer hers to give.
It belongs to Kyon.
[MIKURU] What? No! This is
a big misunderstanding.
[giggles]
Why were you two eavesdropping?
I ran into Miss Tsuruya
on my way here,
so we walked back together.
When we saw you
staring at each other
like a scene from
a manga, well...
We silently agreed that
observing your conversation
could turn out to be
highly entertaining.
[NAGATO]
It's kinda creepy how similar
their thought processes are.
It was like something
out of a Broadway musical.
I never understand
what you're saying.
How are you feeling now?
Huh? About what?
You know that all three
of us are behind you.
Does that help give you courage?
Uh-huh.
When school's over--
that's when you'll
make your move.
[NAGATO]
Mm.
[TSURUYA]
Well, we have to get going.
This was fun. See you later!
[NAGATO]
Hey, wait.
[MIKURU, TSURUYA]
Huh?
I just wanted to say thank you.
Soldier! Time to discuss
our plan of attack.
So listen carefully, got it?
Hm!
[ASAKURA]
First order of business:
hand over the key
to the clubroom.
[NAGATO]
Here.
This is where it starts.
After school's over,
I'll give this key to Kyon
and instruct him to
unlock the clubroom door.
[NAGATO]
Okay.
[ASAKURA] So, Kyon uses the
key and enters the clubroom.
Shortly thereafter, you arrive.
And, oh, hey! It's
just the two of you!
Which makes it the perfect time
to hand over your gift.
Ah!
And I'll take my sweet time
heading to the clubroom,
so you lovebirds
will have plenty of privacy.
[gasps]
Hey, easy there!
If you're already like this,
how bad is it going to be later?
Maybe we shouldn't do this.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
Yeah. I can do it. Although,
do you think we could do it
and not be so sneaky about it?
I mean, couldn't I just
hurry and wait for him?
That would make
it a lot simpler.
[ASAKURA sighs]
Oh, Nagato!
Think this through
with me, okay?
You can casually enter a room
where Kyon is already waiting.
or you can desperately
rush there yourself
and wait for him to grace
you with his presence.
Now tell me which of
these two situations
sounds more stressful to you?
[gasps]
Yes, you're right.
He should be the
one waiting, not me.
I'm glad you realize that.
This way, things are more
firmly under your control.
You can take time to breathe
and collect yourself.
You'll remember
to do that, right?
Whatever happens today,
you should be proud of yourself.
You put your whole heart
into making those chocolates.
[NAGATO]
Yeah, I did.
Heh, heh? And still nothing.
That's it! The end!
I am now officially
giving in to despair.
[KUNIKIDA]
You okay?
[TANIGUCHI]
Kunikida!
If it makes you feel any better,
all I got was courtesy
chocolate. Want some?
[COACH A]
Let's fight!
[BASEBALL TEAM]
Yeah!
[sighs]
Throw those chocolates at him
with everything you've got!
I would be happy if
you gave me chocolates!
Whatever happens today, you
should be proud of yourself.
Okay? Your heart went
into those chocolates.
[NAGATO sighs]
[NAGATO inhales, exhales]
I'm sorry it took
me so lo-- [gasps]
[NAGATO] Next episode:
"Her Melancholy."