‐ [Voiceover] Attention incoming VC202.
This is Torrington Control.
State your affiliation and objective.
‐ [Voiceover] Torrington
Control, we are a transport
belonging to the Vist
Foundation on a special mission
from staff headquarters.
We are now delivering a
prototype mobile suit.
We're sending it to you on a Base Jabber.
Transmitting the operation
code from staff headquarters.
‐ [Voiceover] Operation code received.
Special mission queried and confirmed.
Approaching Base Jabber,
descend to regulation altitude.
We'll guide you into final approach.
‐ Now commencing mission.
Detaching suit and deploying.
‐ [Voiceover] Mission? What mission?
Hey, approaching Base Jabber,
follow our control instructions!
I repeat, follow our control instructions!
[ominous music]
‐ [gasps] A black...
‐ Unicorn?
‐ A friendly?
[robotic whirring]
No.
[electronic buzzing]
[ominous music]
‐ [Voiceover] Get out of there, Banagher!
[grunting]
[intense music]
[electronic whirring]
[groaning]
[gasping]
[ominous music]
‐ Sir, the hatch won't open.
‐ But I gave you the release code!
I don't care how you do it!
Drag him out of there!
‐ Hey! Care to explain
what you're doing here?
And why's there a black unicorn?
‐ [sigh] Actually, we're
calling it the Banshee.
And it's far too complicated
to explain to you.
What's the delay here?
‐ Hold on a second!
[groaning]
‐ I'm afraid this is a family matter.
And I don't think the
military has the right
to meddle in one's family affairs.
Wouldn't you agree?
‐ What do you mean family?
‐ That's rather embarrassing
if you must know.
Banagher Links is the
illegitimate son of the
previous head of the Vist Foundation,
my father, Cardeas Vist.
So, I'll thank you to
stop asking questions.
‐ Banagher is‐‐
‐ The hatch is opening.
[ominous music]
‐ [Voiceover] It's rejecting
all external commands
and the system has gone
completely dormant.
‐ So now what?
‐ Well, our guess is that
Banagher Links has managed
to lock us out of the system,
but without confirmation
from him, we won't be
able to obtain any of the
new information that was
revealed by the La+ Program.
‐ I suppose it's in his blood.
You really didn't know?
‐ [Voiceover] No, I was
away at boarding school
when he was born!
So, I never even met him!
I can't believe this boy is actually‐‐
‐ He certainly has his
father's stubbornness.
If anyone could change
his mind, she could.
Audrey Burne.
As aliases go, it has a lovely ring.
‐ I take it this means
Chairman Ronan Marcenas
is aware of my transfer?
‐ Of course.
After all, we're working
towards the same goal,
Chairman Ronan and I.
[mechanical whirring]
We will seal Laplace's box for good.
I understand you left Neo
Zeon because you desired
exactly that.
At any moment, the boxes key, the Unicorn,
will be delivered to this Garuda.
Until that time, it's
young pilot will continue
to act as it's guardian.
I believe he's no stranger to you.
Am I right, your highness?
This Banagher Links?
Unfortunately, he's locked
access to the coordinates
that were revealed during
yesterday's battle.
The bastard child inherits
the delusions of his
foolish father.
You have no idea how much
trouble he's causing us.
‐ That guard is...
Was his father?
‐ I have a proposal for you, princess.
Let's work together.
‐ You want me to convince
Banagher for you.
‐ I will make it worth your while.
I can also guarantee a
place for your ever loyal
Zeon remnants.
‐ If your offer is sincere,
you'll have no problem
releasing Marida Cruz first.
‐ Lieutenant Marida, or
should I say Ple Twelve,
is now working with us
completely of her own free will.
‐ You forced her to
undergo reconditioning.
‐ True, we reconditioned her,
just as Neo Zeon once did.
We can hardly be held
responsible for creating
that poor creature.
All I did was free what
was already within her.
I gave her the chance to
exact the revenge she desired.
‐ What revenge?
‐ Why, against the world
that created her, of course.
A world that is unfortunately ruled by the
flawed logic of men.
‐ [Voiceover] Hey! This is
rough on the captain too!
‐ If we don't have some
idea of what's going on,
how are we supposed to protect the ship?
‐ [Voiceover] I hate being
pushed around by them.
I mean, they're just civilians.
‐ Right now, we're working
under the direction
of the general staff headquarters.
So, you can think of the
foundation as part of them.
[chattering]
Londo Bell's mission remains the same.
Our job is still to stay on course
and hunt down the Neo Zeon
ship that infiltrated earth.
That said, there can be no
denying that the circumstances
under which we operate have altered.
[chattering]
We will launch the captured Gundam type
into space via shuttle.
Once that is done, the
Vist Foundation personnel
will disembark.
Despite any objections you may have,
I expect you to conduct
yourselves appropriately.
You are dismissed.
‐ Sir, from what I'm
hearing, they're saying
the supplies that were
shipped to the Garuda
were fit for royalty.
‐ So, I guess the intel from
Luio and Company was accurate.
Well, are they gonna let me speak to him?
‐ They approved it almost immediately.
Though it would be wise to assume
that these walls have ears.
‐ And here I thought this was my ship.
I'd like a quick word with you.
Is that alright?
My name's Bright Noah.
I'm the captain of this federation ship,
the Ra Cailum.
I hear you're making things difficult
for your interrogators.
And your suit isn't giving
up any information either.
Our entire technical crew
is tearing their hair out.
‐ I can't let anyone see them.
If people find out what they are,
that place will become
a battlefield again.
My people will die just like Ms. Loni.
‐ Suit yourself.
Go on keeping that secret then.
So, did you escape that
camouflage freighter to get here?
‐ I wouldn't exactly use the word escaped.
It's more like they decided
to send me on my way, I guess.
To be honest, the captain wasn't happy
about the operation.
‐ Yeah, I don't doubt that.
Based on the actions of that
ship, I figured as much.
But if you weren't being
treated as a prisoner
while in their care, does
that mean they gave you
the freedom to do as you pleased?
‐ Yeah, you could say that.
I didn't get the sense we were enemies.
Even though I know the
federation says we are.
‐ Why was that?
‐ I think it's because I'm not a soldier.
I'm not used to categorizing
people into friend or foe.
But there, while I was aboard that ship,
I didn't need to!
‐ Thank you.
I think I understand you now.
Don't give up.
You have strength, I
can see it in your eyes.
Strong eyes can feed off of adversity.
As long as you don't
give up, you'll be able
to make the most of what comes.
‐ It's not about strength.
It's about dumb luck.
Everything that's happened,
I had nothing to do with it.
Even piloting the unicorn.
‐ You really think that?
It may have been simply due to mere luck
that you stumbled across the
Gundam when you needed it,
but that's how it happened
for every single Gundam pilot
that came before you.
However, you still had
to choose whether or not
to get in that Gundam and that's a choice
you made on your own.
You, not luck.
At that moment, something
gave you the resolve
to pilot that machine.
What was it?
‐ There's someone I wanna help.
Audrey Burne.
She's the one who everyone's
calling Mineva Zabi.
‐ [Captain] Are you sure?
You're positive that General
Revil has been mobilized?
‐ It apparently received
orders from General staff
headquarters during
it's shake down cruise.
They clearly want it to carry out
some sort of covert operation.
‐ It's the Nahel Argama they're after.
Now, I see.
That's what they used
to bait Chairman Ronan.
Eliminate everyone who
knows the secret of the box.
That's the shared agenda
of the Vist Foundation
and General Staff Headquarters.
‐ [Girl] What are you planning to do?
The General Revil is the
key to the reconstruction
of Earth Fleet.
If it attacks, the Nahel
Argama wouldn't stand a chance.
If you're having trouble
making direct contact
from your end, our people
at Luio and Company
can notify them that they're in danger.
‐ Beltorchika, I wanna
get in touch with the
camouflaged Sleeves freighter.
‐ Captain?
‐ With Luio and Company's
contacts within the federation
and Neo Zeon.
It shouldn't be a problem.
‐ Are you sure about this, Captain Bright?
‐ I have the perfect
negotiator for the job.
He does hate Zeons with
a passion, however.
‐ This is in your best
interest too, don't you think?
You'd even call it a golden opportunity.
At least I would.
Once the key to Laplace's
Box is delivered,
those foundation people plan to take
both it and your princess into space.
If that happens, they'll
be out of reach for good.
‐ Give me a reason why I should trust you.
‐ We don't like the Vist
Foundation conspiring
with General Staff Headquarters
and having the military
at their beck and call.
A certain field commander
also feels that way.
And then there's Luio and
Company, which could be called
the foundation's competitor.
Whatever Laplace's Box really
is, we just don't wanna
see the ties between the
federation and the foundation
deepening as a result.
‐ And to keep that from
happening, you'll get in bed
with the Neo Zeon and her captain.
I need you to provide
us with one Base Jabber.
‐ I'll see what I can do.
So, does this mean you'll be resorting
to your own guerilla tactics then?
‐ I'm just not sure we can
pull this off by ourselves.
Even if we hit them with a sneak attack
and recapture the princess,
it won't do any good
if we can't escape.
‐ And that is why I've been
calling this a joint operation.
I'll be sending you backup.
But it'll be from a ship you've had
a nasty run in with though.
‐ In any case, the first order of business
in times such as these is to remain calm.
We've been on standby for nearly 20 days.
It's understandable that you're antsy.
However, you my comrades
are their superior officers.
So, you must present
yourself with an air of‐‐
‐ Captain!
[panting]
Emergency message.
‐ Huh?
[clearing throat]
[spitting]
[screaming]
‐ No, I'm serious.
I'm putting my money on
that boy's intuition.
‐ [Voiceover] The course is clear.
The Azon aircraft for clear launch.
‐ Why do we need that pilot onboard
to transport the whiny one to Garuda?
‐ Who can tell with the top brass?
‐ Ensign Riddhe!
Where's Audrey?
You came to Earth with her, right?
So, where is she?
What happened to her?
Answer me!
[groaning]
‐ I need to borrow him for a moment.
‐ Whoa, careful.
The Earth's gravity can be a real bitch.
‐ What's wrong with you boys?
That man over there is
the captain of this ship.
‐ Audrey's there?
‐ No doubt about it.
The Garenciere is
planning a rescue mission.
It's scheduled to take place
during the Garuda transfer.
I suggest you work with them.
Once completed, join the
Nahel Argama, which will be
out in space waiting.
It's the only way you
can keep the box's key
out of the hands of the conspirators.
It's the only way to save her.
Can you do that?
‐ I'll do it.
‐ I'm afraid this is all I can do for you.
Just like every Gundam
pilot there's ever been,
I truly believe that
you were chosen by it.
This was the only possible
outcome for any of you.
Whether that be good or bad, who knows?
‐ Captain Bright.
‐ The rest is up to you.
Don't let the situation
get the best of you.
Be brave enough to fight off despair.
If you're a Gundam pilot,
a Newtype, you can do it.
[mechanical whirring]
‐ Audrey.
I'm coming.
[intense music]
[glass breaking]
‐ [Voiceover] I will say this.
One has to admire your pride,
but your pride is about to
get a lot of people killed.
Do you understand that?
With your actions just now,
you've stolen the future from the very
Zeon survivors who worship you.
The only possible future
for them was to co‐exist
with the Vist Foundation.
A woman's pride can be fatal to a man
and you are blossoming into a fine woman.
Every blossom needs fertilizer
and that's what that boy's become to you.
‐ Banagher...
‐ What did the Captain say to that kid?
I don't wanna get caught in the middle
of any weird scandals.
‐ Hey, you think the
rookie knows what's up?
‐ Nah, I'm guessing he's also in the dark.
But Captain Bright knows what he's doing.
Whatever happens, don't panic.
‐ Ensign Riddhe, keep
an eye on the unicorn.
Remember, as long as the key is safe,
it should help you as well.
Your father's decisions are his own.
You're young.
Act according to your own judgment.
‐ Understood.
All that goes without saying.
Especially when Mineva is involved.
Taking off.
[intense whirring]
‐ All of your weapons
have been deactivated.
I suggest that you do not resist.
‐ Ms. Marida!
‐ I am Ple Twelve.
I do not respond to the name Marida.
‐ What are you talking about?
And what are you doing in
that mobile suit anyway?
The captain and the
rest of the guards here
are worried about you!
‐ Be quiet!
Don't talk to me like that.
‐ It's me.
It's Banagher Links.
Don't you remember?
I came to Earth with the captain,
your master?
‐ Ple Twelve!
‐ Do not pay attention to that boy!
‐ I understand, master.
‐ [Master] Is everything alright?
‐ The suit is perfect.
‐ [Master] I was talking about you.
If anything's wrong, however
trivial, do report it.
‐ Roger.
‐ If you're in pain, don't tough it out
and if something's bothering you,
please feel free to‐‐
‐ Is that an order?
[sighing]
‐ Ms. Marida.
[whirring]
Is that them?
[intense music]
It's the Garencieres!
The Garuda's defense
forces are engaging them.
I'm opening the combat bridge.
‐ Not yet.
Have the suits in Nigel's
team ascertain the situation.
The object of our mission
is to deliver the unicorn
to the Garuda.
There's no need to get caught
up in their little battle.
[intense zooming]
‐ [Voiceover] It's started, huh?
‐ [Voiceover] These Zeon
bastards don't know when to quit!
‐ All suits, hold your formation.
Don't let the unicorn out of your sight.
Stay out of my way.
[intense buzzing]
‐ Move the ship in closer!
‐ Are you really going through with this?
‐ If I can get aboard,
she's as good as ours.
‐ For Christ's sake, try
acting your age for a change.
[dramatic music]
[electronic whirring]
‐ What is this feeling?
‐ I can't let Ms. Marida and
the captain fight each other.
‐ [Voiceover] Watts!
‐ What the hell?
‐ Ms. Marida, listen to me.
The captain is here.
The Garenciere's rescuing Audrey.
[intense music]
[electronic whirring]
‐ So he's refusing to kill, huh?
‐ He's going to board it in mid air?
[grunting]
‐ [Voiceover] Ple Twelve,
shoot down the Base Jabber
that's latched onto the Garuda!
That's the enemy!
‐ Roger.
‐ [Banagher] Don't do it, Ms. Marida!
‐ Great, it's Banagher.
‐ [Voiceover] What happened to our escorts
from the Ra Cailum?
That little punk used me as a springboard!
‐ [Voiceover] All craft are disengaging.
They're assisting damaged consort craft.
‐ So that's what's going on.
All of them are in on this.
Not if I can help it!
‐ Banagher.
[mechanical whirring]
‐ Highness, the shuttle
launch has been pushed up.
If you'll please come with me.
[intense electronic whirring]
‐ My master's orders are to
secure you and your cockpit.
‐ Please snap out of this!
That's not your master!
He'd never ask that!
You and the Captain should
never fight each other!
Not after all you've been through!
‐ I am Ple Twelve.
My master is Alberto Vist.
‐ No you're not!
Your name's Marida!
And your Captain is Lieutenant
Zinnerman of the Garencieres!
‐ [Master] Ple Twelve!
Don't listen to him!
You'll only listen to me.
He is the enemy and he's
just saying those things
to confuse you!
‐ [Banagher] Try to remember.
Think about everything you and the Captain
have done for each
other, why you trust him!
‐ [Master] You don't need to
listen to anything he says!
You hear me?
The Gundam is your enemy!
You will capture it and bring it‐‐
‐ Shut up!
‐ Ple Twelve!
‐ [Woman] Can't you close that hatch?
‐ I came here to rescue you.
[gasping]
[gun clicking]
‐ Huh? What's that?
[dramatic music]
‐ Ms. Marida.
‐ Gundam is the enemy!
‐ No Unicorn.
Don't let it suck you in.
Fight it!
[electronic whirring]
‐ [Ensign] Hurry, board the Delta Plus.
‐ [Woman] Ensign Riddhe,
have you thought about
what you're doing in your
position in all this?
‐ I wouldn't be doing this if I didn't.
And what would happen if you
killed Ronan Marcenas' son?
Have you thought about that?
You can have Banagher and the unicorn.
However, the girl is coming with me.
‐ Why are you still standing there?
‐ After you've taken me away,
what are you planning to do after that?
‐ I can figure that out
after we get out of here.
‐ Answer this.
What is it you're trying to protect?
Do you really wanna protect just me?
Or is it the secret of Laplace's Box?
Or is it your family's‐‐
‐ I don't give a damn about them!
The explosion that destroyed
Laplace 100 years ago,
that was the start of this whole mess.
My father, myself, even
all the people here,
we're all just pawns of
it's twisted consequences.
But regardless of how twisted
this world has become,
10 billion people still live in it.
So, we have no choice.
All we can do is protect it.
I can't let everything fall into chaos
like the Zeon's once did.
‐ Exactly and that's why we must protect
the secret of the box!
Princess Mineva understands this as well!
That is why we should‐‐
‐ Shut up!
You've no right.
Your founder's the one
who's responsible for this.
It was a stroke of dumb
luck that your founder,
Syam Vist, stumbled across the box.
At first, everything went
according to his plan.
He used the assassination
of the first Prime Minister
and the resulting hard line
policies to gain power,
but then Zeon called for
space lord Independence,
the one year war broke out
and everything changed.
That's when both Syam Vist, who
came up with the conspiracy,
and the Federal Government,
which implemented it
realized what they'd done.
They understood the
significance of their actions
and the true power of
what Laplace's Box held.
‐ You know what the box is.
So please tell me!
What could it be that's been
causing you so much suffering?
This affects every one of us.
We all have the right to know.
[groaning]
Banagher!
‐ Mineva, please come with me instead.
The unicorn, it's dangerous.
With the revelation that
Newtypes actually exist,
the prayer of 100 years ago
was transformed into a curse.
So please...
‐ What do you mean?
‐ I don't have the power to
change the world on my own
even if it's an imperfect system.
If there's no way to
change it, I'll protect it
and that means, that
means also protecting you.
[guns shooting]
‐ Intruders!
‐ Is it the Neo Zeons?
[groaning]
‐ Mineva!
[intense whirring]
‐ Ms. Marida, please stop!
‐ Light...
This is the light that will save me.
No one will steal it from me!
‐ No! Something's not right with it!
The light is really dangerous!
‐ What do you think you're doing?
Go bring Mineva back here right now!
‐ It's not safe to be here.
The Unicorn and Banshee
might be resonating
which means they could be
generating a psycho field!
‐ So what you're talking
about is another access shock.
‐ And if that's the case,
not even a craft as strong as the Garuda‐‐
[guns shooting]
‐ The Garencieres arrived.
Use this to get off ship.
‐ What about you?
‐ Don't worry about me.
I'll catch up to you.
Now go!
[intense music]
[groaning]
‐ At this rate, Audrey'll‐‐
‐ It's under his complete control.
How can he pilot like that?
That boy.
[wind blowing]
‐ Don't move.
I'll be right there.
What are you doing?
Give me your hand!
‐ Riddhe, you and I are
following different paths.
‐ Now's not the time for this.
‐ I'm a member of the Zabi family.
I will find out myself
what Laplace's Box is.
Anything is preferable to war.
I've always believed that
even if it's a twisted system.
But if the only purpose of that system
is to stifle humanity‐‐
‐ Mineva.
‐ Then perhaps I will be committing crimes
as great as my father's
and my grandfather's.
But even so‐‐
‐ What are you planning to do then?
Fight the world alone?
People don't believe that
the world will ever change.
And people don't care about
a world a century from now
that they won't live to see.
You'd be willing to fight for them?
And what's the point
when you'd just end up
making enemies of them in the end?
‐ I'm not alone in this fight.
‐ Mineva, don't do it!
‐ Goodbye Riddhe.
I will always remember you.
‐ Mineva!
‐ I'm waiting for you Banagher.
Catch me.
‐ Audrey!
[intense zooming]
Unicorn, don't let me down.
[bright music]
We're gonna be fine.
[sobbing and sniffling]
‐ They're coming, more of them.
Flaste, I apologize for the trouble.
‐ Not at all.
Banagher, it's up to you to
get the captain and Marida.
Hurry!
‐ Right.
‐ [Audrey] Banagher.
‐ I heard your voice, clear as day.
And I was happy.
I felt like I finally understood
what I was doing here.
All because you called for me
‐ I felt it too.
‐ Then what I heard was real.
So that means Ms. Marida
should also be able to hear me.
I'm going to bring her back.
I'd like you to wait here for me.
Is that okay?
‐ Yes.
I'll leave it to you, Banagher Links.
[intense laser buzzing]
[screaming]
[metal crunching]
[intense music]
‐ Another cursed Gundam.
‐ You're a Gundam too!
[groaning]
[intense music]
Gundam's are the enemy.
Enemy's must be killed!
‐ Stop it, Ms. Marida!
I beg you, you must come to your senses!
‐ I can't take it.
Your damn voice won't get out of my head!
‐ [Banagher] The reason you're
in so much pain is because
your real self is fighting
the lies they've told you!
‐ Is that you, Marida?
Listen to me.
It's Zinnerman!
‐ Who's that?
Zinnerman? Master?
‐ Those Foundation bastards
reconditioned you, didn't they?
Let's go!
Come on, Marida!
If you come back, it'll
be like it used to be.
[groaning]
‐ My master is...
My master is‐‐
‐ This is my daughter.
Her name is Marie.
If she were still alive,
she'd be the same age as you.
‐ Open your hatch and come out!
We can go back to space together!
Marida, please don't leave me all alone!
[panting]
‐ You damn Gundams!
Gundam!
Gundam, gun‐‐
‐ So I am a Gundam.
Then I am the enemy.
[intense whirring]
[intense music]
‐ Marie.
‐ [Girl] T‐minus 60 to reverse thrust.
Reverse acceleration protection set.
‐ [Man] Ballute is
prepared and on standby.
‐ Target's breaking away from the Garuda
and gaining altitude.
Amending estimated contact
point by minus eight.
‐ We're eminently positioned
to the upper thermosphere.
Then we could pull up the
target by tether cable.
‐ All hands, pay close
attention to the ship's altitude
and speed.
‐ The Garencieres, but that's the Sleeve's
camouflaged freighter.
That's the very same ship
that's been shadowing us
since Industrial seven.
Are you sure about this, sir?
‐ It doesn't matter if I'm sure.
It's a direct order from Commander Bright.
Besides, it's nice to finally
have something for a change,
regardless of what it may be.
‐ [Man] Target's engine
output appears to have fallen.
It's deviating from the
planned ascent curve!
‐ It's doing what?
What's going on?
‐ [Man] We're having engine trouble.
I can't get the output up.
‐ [Man] Do you think you'll
be able to pull it off?
We don't have enough fuel
to circle the Earth again.
‐ I'm doing the best I can.
‐ And right on schedule.
Our longtime nemesis is
right there to meet us.
I guess pulling this off
was too much to hope for.
‐ No, that ship, it's not
working for the Federation
nor Neo Zeon.
If we could reach them, it
might open up a path for us.
‐ It just might but‐‐
[intense crashing]
[groaning]
[electronic whirring]
‐ [Girl] Banagher!
‐ Kwani! Ivan!
What are you doing?
It's a crazy idea, but
Flaste, will it work?
‐ We're climbing now but we
still don't have enough power
to get back on trajectory.
‐ [Man] Can we decrease
our altitude any further?
‐ [Man] We're at our limit!
‐ Alright, deploy the cable right now!
‐ Firing tether cable.
[rattling]
‐ Come on, come back to space!
Banagher!
[intense music]
‐ He caught it!
‐ Did the cable connect?
‐ Yes, but not with‐‐
[groaning]
‐ It's no good!
Your suit will be ripped apart!
‐ Banagher!
[groaning]
[soft music]
‐ That light.
What is it?
[bright music]
[panting]
[groaning]
‐ Gundam.
‐ Ah.
‐ Who is firing at us?
‐ IFF code match found!
It's one of our own, sir!
They're in our flight path.
Elevation difference, 12.
Range, 400.
Dogosse Giar class!
It's the General Revil!
‐ Are you sure about that?
‐ Positive, sir.
‐ The General Revil.
I don't believe it.
‐ Possible mobile suits incoming!
[intense whirring]
[intense music]
‐ That thing is a monster!
So this was a trap after all!
‐ It wasn't!
Look at the way they're deploying.
They're also targeting the Nahel Argama!
‐ So, they're planning on
wiping us all out at once, huh?
‐ It can't be.
No way!
We were so close.
[somber music]
[intense whirring]
‐ The Neo Zeons are here?
[beeping]
[laser guns shooting]
[intense music]
‐ Full frontal.
[electronic whirring]
[intense music]
[upbeat music]