[missiles firing]
[loud gasping]
‐ [Newscaster] A news flash has arrived
from our Dakar press center.
[loud explosions]
‐ [Fighter] They're coming!
[intense instrumental music]
Reactor shutdown confirmed,
no chain reaction.
Heat source detected, incoming!
[somber instrumental music]
‐ [Captain] Why hasn't he launched yet,
what's the hold up?
‐ [Fighter] I need a sitrep!
‐ Unbelievable.
I didn't think they'd
actually attack the capital.
‐ This is what I've been waiting for.
[loud explosion]
Father, Mother...
I'll make the Federation pay!
‐ Loni, the diversion worked.
They'll be sending reinforcements.
Head back to the ship.
We're to sit tight until we hear
from the Garencieres Team.
‐ Roger.
‐ So it has finally begun, then.
We must resolve this swiftly.
‐ Indeed.
But we still do not know the whereabouts
of the key to Laplace's box.
The Unicorn went missing
during the recent battle
that incinerated the old
prime minister's residence.
However...
Despite that, there must be a reason
Master Cardeas chose him.
‐ God is toying with us.
Or perhaps Cardeas's dream,
or rather mankind's
dream has been fulfilled.
Banagher, my very own flesh and blood.
[somber piano music]
‐ [Newscaster] Zeon remnants
have remained dormant
in the three years since Char's Rebellion.
Does this sudden act of terrorism
signal a new uprising by them?
Some pundits believe this
to be the opening salvo
of a Third Neo Zeon War.
‐ What's he thinking?
I don't have time for this,
not when those responsible for the attacks
are still out there.
‐ [Man In Suit] I reject
your implications.
Unlike the attack on
Lhasa three years ago,
this one on Dakar cost the
lives of not just civilians,
but many government workers as well.
I must say, I find this mutual mudslinging
most unproductive, to say the least.
I would prefer to have a more
constructive discussion, Ms. Martha.
‐ Okay, I'll cut to the chase then.
I'd like you to hand
over the special guest
who's currently in your care.
‐ What...
What are you talking about?
‐ It would be in the best interest
of both our parties,
especially yours, Chairman.
‐ [Chairman] Leaving aside my interest
for the moment,
what is it you stand to gain?
‐ I'll leave that to your imagination.
Just deliver her to the...
‐ I have some pressing
matters to deal with
at the moment.
Contact me again in two hours,
I'll see what I can do.
‐ As you wish.
He claims to have "pressing matters".
I'm talking about the Zabi heir,
what could be more important than that?
[loud sighing]
‐ Forgive us for the difficult situation
we've put you in.
But father‐‐
‐ You've fallen for her, haven't you?
It's obvious that's why
you deserted your post
and fled back here.
It's like when you decided
you wanted to be a pilot,
and you left home just like that.
I never dreamed in a million years
that you'd get yourself
mixed up with the Box.
You need to know the
truth about our family.
It's the only way for you to get yourself
out of this mess.
It's life or death.
Have mercy, grant us salvation.
[dramatic music]
‐ [Newscaster] At present, the military
and the fire department are
doing everything they can
to locate survivors.
‐ Banagher.
What do I do?
I don't know what to do.
Leave me!
‐ [Newscaster] Discharged
rebellion three years earlier.
‐ Riddhe?
‐ [Newscaster] As for the mobile armor
that destroyed the Assembly Hall,
it's current whereabouts are unknown.
In coordination with the...
‐ [Riddhe] I'm sorry.
‐ What's the matter?
‐ [Riddhe] It's my family, I'm so ashamed.
‐ What do you mean?
‐ [Riddhe] My family, the Marcenas family,
has just as much blood on its hands
as the Vist Foundation.
It's the way they've
maintained their power
and prominence through
the Universal Century.
I'm certain that my
family will do anything
to prevent Laplace's Box from opening,
even if that means using
you as a hostage again.
The only way to stop that from happening
is to get the Box before
either the Foundation
or Neo Zeon does.
Either that, or we destroy‐‐
‐ It's key, the Unicorn.
‐ I...
I was only trying to help you.
And this is probably
the worst possible place
for you to be.
Whatever happens, I
promise I'll protect you.
So please, stay with me.
Promise me, you won't leave me.
I don't want to be alone.
[horse galloping]
Will you...
Will you become a Marcenas?
Walk away from Zeon and the Zabi family,
and be apart of the Marcenas family.
I think you know what I'm asking.
I don't care if it's just for show.
If you did, Father would listen to us.
You could end all this
fighting and be free.
‐ [Woman] That's not free.
What kind of freedom would that be?
‐ I understand what has to be done.
[grunting]
‐ Ple Twelve.
That's your name, right?
Answer me.
You're supposed to obey
your master's orders.
Except for the fact that
you aren't my master.
So if you want me to obey you,
you're going to have to
torture or brainwash me.
‐ That's enough, watch your mouth!
‐ We've come to learn
that reconditioning you
would prove to be difficult.
They broke the mold when they created you,
but that won't stop me.
I've no interest in a doll
whose memories can be
rewritten like a hard drive.
There's something else I'm after.
The Mass Production Type Qubeley.
That's the machine you all
used to pilot, isn't it?
And by you, I mean
Artificially‐created Newtypes.
Puppets that do the
bidding of their master.
Alas, your poor soul is
still being held prisoner
within that machine.
Unfortunately, you were created by men
who only knew of spilling blood.
Since true life can only
come from a woman's womb,
don't you find all this unnatural?
Lucky for you, I'm going to
free you from that machine.
[sobbing and yelling]
‐ [Riddhe's Father] This
is a camouflaged freighter
belonging to the Sleeves
that landed on Earth
approximately 10 days ago.
‐ I did hear something about
the ruins of Laplace being destroyed.
Are you saying these
people were responsible?
‐ I want you to use your
resources to locate them.
‐ In short, you want the Ra Cailum
to run a personal errand for you?
‐ The ship in question was also involved
in the incidents in
Industrial 7 and Palau.
As commander of Londo Bell,
aren't you concerned about the safety
of the Nahel Argama?
She is presently being
detained in the Earth's orbit.
You should know, this came from the
General Staff Headquarters by
order of the Vist Foundation.
I don't want it to appear
like we're taking hostages,
so I've laid all my cards on the table.
The Foundation is after this ship as well,
but if we take it into custody first,
it will give us the upper hand.
‐ [Commander] What's so
special about this ship?
‐ It's carrying Laplace's Box.
So you must seize control of that ship.
If you're unable to do so,
you are then commanded to destroy it.
‐ You give me too much credit, sir.
Granted, my career has
been far from conventional,
however I'm not‐‐
‐ [Riddhe's Father] It's
hardly surprising for a man
who has repeatedly
captained the motherships
of Gundam types since the One Year War
to be singled out as
commander of a Newtype corps,
don't you think?
‐ I suppose that's just my luck, sir.
‐ Well, if you'll make your
talents too well known,
there are those who will find a way
to take advantage of them.
I have one last favor to ask.
It's about that prodigal son of mine.
He's a pilot in the military.
I would like you to
take him aboard your...
What is it?
‐ [Man] I beg your pardon, sir.
‐ [Riddhe's Father] What is it, Doillon?
I told you I was not to
be disturbed unless...
Hm?
‐ It seems that the
Lady Mineva has suddenly
disappeared from her room.
We're searching the grounds
for her as we speak.
‐ Sorry to break this to you.
I'm probably the last
person you want advice
from on this.
But the only way to get
the mobile suits out
is to crack the hull.
‐ We'll save that as a last resort.
Cracking the hull would
wreck the Garencieres.
‐ But sir, whether or not their
diversionary attack works,
we have to reconnect with our allies soon.
If we stay here, it's
only a matter of time
before we're discovered.
‐ I still can't believe they
hit Dakar of all places.
‐ Yeah, but they were itching for a fight.
Can't say I blame 'em.
Don't forget, the people
biding their time on Earth
missed out on two Neo Zeon Wars after all.
‐ [Man In Green] Even so,
we better make contact soon.
Who knows what kind of crazy stunt
they'll wind up pulling next?
‐ [Man In Red] There's an oasis about
60 kilometers east of here.
Let's make a quick trip
there by mobile suit,
and then we can make
contact with our allies.
At this point, wrecking the ship
is the only way we're
gonna get out of here.
‐ [Man In Green] I understand.
But without a way of
activating the Unicorn,
it's pointless.
‐ [Man In Red] We could
always tie up the kid
inside the cockpit
and have someone else pilot the thing.
The next set of the coordinates
the La+ Program gave
are in one hell of an inconvenient place.
‐ Give me the map.
‐ Hm?
This is ridiculous.
The Captain's lost it!
Why the hell is he
taking you of all people?
Hey you!
Don't be thinking you're so precious.
Who cares if you can pilot that thing,
we'll kill you just the same.
‐ You've got it wrong, I don't think that.
This is my fault, I know that.
I killed Mr. Gilboa.
‐ You bet your ass it is!
He could've landed us safely
despite your Unicorn grabbing on
during atmospheric entry.
If he had been at the helm,
we wouldn't be in this mess!
Gah!
‐ On the house, drink up.
I like the way you dig in.
It's nice to see a young lady
who isn't obsessed with manners.
‐ Thank you very much, it looks great.
‐ I haven't seen you around here before.
So, whereabouts you from?
You're a Spacenoid, huh?
No wonder I haven't seen you before.
You sightseeing?
There really isn't too much
around these parts to see.
‐ [Lady Mineva] I beg to differ.
As someone who was born
and raised in space,
I'm happy to be able to
set foot on real ground.
‐ [Restaurant Owner] Well...
Gravity hasn't exactly
been kind to folks like me.
Makes me wonder if my
back wouldn't feel better
if I were space.
‐ Does that mean you've lived
on Earth your entire life?
‐ Yeah.
I'm a bit too old to leave her now.
My generation was raised on stories
of the bad old days from our
grandfathers and grandmothers.
Things sounded pretty terrible back then.
They needed to figure out something new,
and so they founded the
Federation government
and the space settlement program.
And you probably don't know this,
most think it was only the poor
that were forced out into space, but...
The truth is, a lot of people
left Earth on their own.
They were prepared to stay away
until the Earth's environment
had fully recovered.
But then the One Year War came along
and undid most of the progress
that had been made on that front.
‐ We're hopeless, aren't we?
‐ Eh, what can you do?
It all began out of
good intentions anyway.
‐ [Lady Mineva] Good intentions?
‐ [Restaurant Owner] Both those
in the Federation and the colonists
were motivated by the hope
that they could save humanity.
It's no different than wanting
your company to succeed,
or wanting to give your
family a better life.
‐ The way you describe it,
it sounds more like self
interest than self idealism.
‐ Yeah, I hear what you're saying.
But if we denied the people
the right to be that way,
what kind of world would this be?
I suppose there are people who can work
for the greater good even
at their own expense,
but I've always been
suspicious of those types.
Like that Char guy from Neo Zeon.
He claimed he was fighting
for the good of all people,
even while he was
dropping asteroids on us.
Truth is, whether he was
fooling us or himself,
that man never learned to love humanity.
‐ So then what do we do?
‐ Hell if I know.
And we still haven't been able
to figure that one out yet.
I'd like to think we at least tried.
And we can only postpone
paying the reaper for so long.
I spent my life regretting not being able
to do anything for you people.
In the end, the best I can offer
is just make you a cup of coffee.
[somber piano music]
[loud rumbling]
‐ I see.
I suppose you're right.
Is there anything I can really do?
[helicopters flying overhead]
The coffee was delicious.
I don't have any regrets.
This alone made my coming
to Earth worthwhile.
‐ Huh?
‐ Come, Ms. Audrey Burne.
Chairman Ronan is waiting.
Follow me, please.
‐ Are you...
‐ I am Mineva Zabi.
I have no intention of running or hiding.
Stand aside now.
[somber violin music]
‐ I'm having Mineva Zabi delivered here.
I'll be using her as bait
to recapture the Unicorn.
I'm sure she'll comply.
‐ Yes.
‐ [Martha] Why don't you be the one
to give it its orders.
‐ Um, yes.
[dramatic music]
[strange ambient music]
‐ [Banagher] Why, why pick me to do it?
‐ [Captain] Because you
look like you have the most
time on your hands.
‐ [Banagher] There's no way.
Who could walk four days through a desert?
‐ [Captain] It's not impossible.
Damn it.
Didn't I tell you to take
sips at regular intervals,
even if you weren't thirsty?
‐ [Banagher] Please, just leave me.
‐ What, you want me to tell you
to hang in there or something?
‐ [Banagher] I just want to be left alone.
I'm sick of this, being
used and caught up in things
I don't understand.
‐ Well tough luck, kid.
You're a pilot now.
So stop being a victim,
and quit your sulking already.
If Bilboa saw you, he'd
roll over in his grave.
‐ I didn't mean to kill him, okay?
When Mr. Daguza died, my
head went completely blank.
But if you can't forgive me,
then just put me out of my misery!
‐ Don't lie to me.
I see it in your eyes,
you don't believe that for a minute.
You have the look of someone
who decides for himself
how he lives and dies.
So as long as you're still kicking,
you might as well put on a brave face.
A man's life is about
struggle 'til the day he dies.
‐ [Banagher's Grandfather] If
you trust in the possibility
that lies within,
the path will show itself to you.
‐ [Man] It's all up to you now, Banagher.
‐ I tried.
I did what you asked.
And now what?
Look what happened, what good was it for?
I piloted a mobile suit,
I fought and killed in it.
And now I'm stuck walking across a desert!
Tell me, what more do
you want me to do, huh?
How much more do you expect me to fight?
[heavy breathing]
[calming instrumental music]
‐ [Man In Red] We were prisoners of war
being held here in Africa.
In the camp, the treaty wasn't even worth
the paper it was printed on.
But that's okay.
Zeons are Zeons.
To the Feds, we were the devil incarnate.
The people who dropped a colony.
While the big wigs were
negotiating a peace,
frustrating was building
up in the Federation troops
who were sent to occupy our homeland.
And they were your typical thugs.
They'd been brought up with the mantra
"Slay the Zeon Devils!"
And sayings like...
"If you're looking for a good
time, find a Zeon woman."
They needed a scapegoat,
something to appease them.
Finally, there came a night when the town
was overrun by soldiers.
The elderly begged for their lives.
Crying children clung to their mothers,
and they killed every last one of them.
The official report said the troops
were trying to pacify rioting citizens,
but it was obvious to everyone
that what they were really
doing was blowing off steam.
The name of the town was Globe.
My mother and father lived there.
So did the Captain's family.
He had a wife, and a daughter too.
She had just turned five.
[fire crackling]
And in the end, the revival of Zeon
wouldn't bring any of them back.
And I don't give a rat's
ass what's inside that box.
So, what were we supposed to do then?
Die in vain while cursing the world,
or fight an endless war?
Those were our two choices.
[somber piano music]
‐ [Captain] Why are you crying?
‐ Because it's beautiful.
‐ Enough to make you think
that all those stories
about Earth being polluted were lies?
The thing is, the air around here
is even more polluted than it used to be.
And they say the desert has advanced
all the way to Dakar's doorstep.
It's all humanity's doing.
Indiscriminate development,
dropping the colonies in the asteroid.
If humanity is the product of nature,
that makes all of mankind's wasted poison
natural products too.
And even if it's rendered
unfit for human habitation,
it'll be the result of nature achieving
a new balance, I guess.
Mother Nature does not
have an ounce of mercy.
Our ancestors were able
to understand that.
As products of nature,
it was something they knew instinctively.
‐ To survive, and to protect themselves,
they created civilizations and societies.
‐ Yeah, but what they
created got too complicated.
A society is supposed to serve the people,
not the other way around.
In the end, it made life
too difficult for people.
And to escape that insane world,
they went out into space
in search of a new home.
There, they created a different system.
It was natural that one would arise,
which gave hope to the
Spacenoids that were cast out.
It gave their lives direction.
That was what Zeon was all about,
but the old system that was
still on Earth rejected it.
Because systems born of
two different philosophies
can never be compatible.
The result is always the same.
One tries to make the other submit.
‐ Before that, a unified
government like the Federation,
and a world where 10 billion people
were living in space,
must've sounded like fantasy.
So isn't it still possibly
that humanity could succeed?
That one day they will be able to merge
the two ways of thinking?
‐ The government will never
treat everyone equally.
The hatred of the beaten and
downtrodden runs so deep,
it still clings to the
Earth to this very day.
‐ The situation's sad, don't you think?
‐ Yeah, I suppose it is.
Even though we live our lives
trying to escape sadness.
I wonder why that is.
[sobbing]
[somber piano music]
Hey, Banagher...
‐ I know, I know.
You're gonna tell me
that a man doesn't cry
in front of others.
‐ No.
Crying because you care is
an entirely different matter.
I don't trust anyone who never cries.
That's my philosophy.
[sobbing]
Banagher.
‐ Huh?
‐ I owe you one.
If it weren't for you,
I think I probably would've
given up along the way.
‐ Thank you.
But all I did was slow you down.
‐ Having someone who challenges you,
sometimes makes all the difference.
‐ Does this mean the
Garencieres has a new member?
You should stop picking
up strays, Captain.
That's it, you can stop there.
‐ [Captain] Good work out there.
‐ Captain...
Well, somebody I met one time
gave me a piece of advice.
He said to find a better way to use a Box,
so that must be my...
But where is it?
Tell me where the Unicorn's
next set of coordinates are.
‐ It's Torrington this time, eh?
This Box does have a way
of keeping us on our toes.
And I can't help wonder if Cardeas Vist
is making fools out of us.
Nicely done at Dakar,
Lieutenant Commander Kirks.
Thanks to you, we
successfully distracted them
with your Earth Zeon Remnants,
and therefore were able to
protect the Garencieres.
You have my gratitude.
‐ Sir, and you ours.
The Zee Zulus proved to be
rather formidable assets, sir.
‐ Ah, you must be Ensign Loni Garvey.
I am familiar with your father.
He has done us a grave service,
perfecting Haman's legacy.
‐ Captain.
I have one goal.
It is to settle that
scores that haunt the souls
of my father, mother, and my people.
‐ Loni!
‐ I would like to request
that you assign us
to aid in the mission
to attack Torrington.
If we dispatch that
Split‐horn Gundam there,
we could probably learn the whereabouts
of Laplace's Box.
‐ Granted.
I am the leader of Neo Zeon,
and we've made our stronghold in space.
But I have no right to give orders
to those who have been
embroiled in guerrilla warfare
on Earth since the One Year War.
‐ In that case, may I take that to mean
that you have no right to stop us either?
‐ May the heavens bless
and protect the heir
to Mahdi's cause.
‐ Sieg Zeon!
‐ Captain, are you sure about this?
Dakar was bad enough, but this is‐‐
‐ I understand your misgivings.
Nevertheless, they have
been waiting all this time.
Time has stood still for them.
And people can grow accustomed to waiting.
I suspect that they could've
gone on waiting forever.
However, time has begun to flow again.
All because of Cardeas Vist.
No dam could hold back this river,
and doing nothing will
only muddy the waters.
Do you not agree, Captain?
And to ensure that does not happen,
I have yet another job for
you and the Garencieres.
‐ Can you take that?
‐ Sure thing.
‐ So you're the pilot of the Split‐horn.
The key to the Box.
‐ [Banagher] What do you mean?
‐ Don't disappoint me.
‐ [Bystander] They say she was the one
who piloted the behemoth at Dakar.
‐ Message from Kirks Team!
‐ [Officer] The ones who attacked Dakar?
‐ It's code used by the old Principality.
It's an old watchword.
It dates back to when our forces
first came down to Earth
during the One Year War.
‐ Well, what does it say?
‐ "Help our cause, let's
give the Feds a shock."
"They won't expect what's next,
Dakar was only the beginning!"
[suspenseful instrumental music]
[loud explosion]
[dog barking]
‐ Dolphin 2, signal lost!
‐ Give me a damage report!
‐ [Submarine Worker] Sir they're offline,
too much interference!
‐ [Submarine Worker 2]
Aquatic ordinance, all green!
‐ Propulsion, values nominal!
Dolphin 1, engaging two
unknown mobile suits!
‐ [Submarine Worker] Can we
launch our reserve suits?
‐ [Submarine Worker 2] Flooding underway,
three minutes 'til completion!
‐ We're supposed to have dropped this off
at the coordinate point
once our allies have captured the base,
then wait to see if it reveals any data.
Ivan's gonna be our escort there.
Something wrong, Banagher?
‐ I just think it's strange.
This is a Zeon weapon,
why does it fit a Federation mobile suit?
‐ [Man] Well, they both
use the universal standard,
so of course they're compatible.
‐ But if they can make
their machines compatible,
why can't they find a
way to stop fighting?
‐ I don't know, but it was the
one thing that got resolved
in the course of all that fighting.
It was a matter of efficiency.
‐ In other words, it
benefited Anaheim Electronics.
‐ Well, it worked better in the field too.
I mean, it's helping
us right now, isn't it?
‐ [Riddhe] Is that it?
‐ Whoa.
‐ The kid's good.
‐ New Guinea, that's our destination.
We have a missing ship in
the Coral Sea, Bonefish.
Federation forces submarine.
Given the state of those waters,
there's a strong possibility she was sunk.
If its disappearance is linked
to the ship we're hunting,
it's possible we'll have
to engage enemy forces.
Our priority is the
procurement of Laplace's Box,
but we may not have that luxury.
Stay sharp out there.
‐ Roger.
Captain Bright?
‐ What is it?
‐ Speaking freely, I
have a request of you.
Don't give me special treatment.
Regardless of my background,
I am first and foremost an E. F. S. F pilot.
I implore you not to keep
me off dangerous missions‐‐
‐ That's enough.
Listen to yourself.
The only one giving you special treatment
around here is you.
I've no reason to play favorites.
I could care less who you are.
If I need you, I'll use you.
However, if I send you
out, come back alive.
That's what makes a pilot.
If you can do that, then
I'll treat you like one.
‐ Yes sir.
‐ It's me.
Put me through.
Bright here.
Come again?
‐ [Man In Red] Why there of all places?
‐ It's where the colony was dropped.
Damn that Cardeas Vist.
What's he trying to make us do,
force us to retrace humanity's downfall?
‐ Hey, you don't have
to worry about the kid.
‐ [Captain] But if he turns on us
while in that suit,
we wouldn't be able to stop him.
‐ At least for now, he's got
total faith in you, Captain.
‐ [Banagher] Ms. Loni...
[loud explosions]
[intense instrumental music]
‐ [Fighter] Massive
mobile armor approaching
from the shore.
Torrington base, requesting assistance!
[loud explosions]
[intense instrumental music]
‐ Russet, Candor, the next
wave is coming, scatter.
Loni, avoid the city!
‐ This is the most
direct route to the base.
Have you forgotten what
the Federation did to us?
‐ [Kirks] We don't want
unnecessary casualties,
keep your cool!
‐ Roger.
‐ [Kirks] What's wrong, Loni?
‐ Father?
[intense instrumental music]
[loud explosions]
‐ A runaway Psycommu.
Could it actually be thirsty for blood?
‐ This is...
A slaughter.
Nothing but a slaughter.
‐ This doesn't strike me as something
that Char's successors would do.
How many?
‐ [Woman] There appear to
be four small transports,
and one mid‐sized VTOL
craft above the area, sir.
‐ If that thing's the
camouflaged freighter,
that would be some dumb luck.
Think it's possible?
‐ [Woman] I've intercepted
the enemy's trunk line, sir.
‐ This the group that attacked Dakar?
All hands, level two battle stations!
Put the mobile suits on standby!
Could these people be
connected to the Box too?
‐ Audrey...
You and I, we can't escape the curse
that we each were born into.
Does this mean I'm just
fighting the inevitable?
‐ Hey there, newbie!
If you slow us down, I won't hesitate
to shoot you in the back.
Don't you forget that.
‐ [Raddhe] You got a great team here,
too bad I'm not a part of it.
‐ You can join whenever you want.
You know, all you have to do
is shoot one of us in the back.
‐ That sure is enticing.
‐ [Pilot] Pilots have to
believe their orders are sound,
even if their bosses are morons.
We're rather fortunate if you ask me.
At least we get to
serve under a great C. O.
‐ The C. O. of the Gundam Corps.
The Gundam, the key to the Box.
‐ [Fighter] Finish them all off!
[gunshots firing]
[intense instrumental music]
[loud explosion]
[loud yelling]
‐ What are you doing!
I'm going out in the Unicorn.
If I can break the La+ Program's seal,
you'll have no reason to
keep up this attack, right?
‐ Settle down.
You go out there now, those
flak guns will shoot you down.
Wait 'til we've mopped up.
‐ What do you mean mopped up?
Innocent people are dying out there,
don't you care?
‐ This is an operation.
My opinions are not relevant.
Stay put.
We didn't tie you up
and force you to come.
If you didn't expect something like this,
you have a serious lack of imagination.
This is what happens when
you seize enemy territory.
‐ Attacking innocent civilians,
decimating fleeing people?
How can you even blame this on war?
This is just an act of vengeance!
That first time we met,
back at Industrial 7,
you chose not to shoot me.
I know you, it's eating you up inside.
So make them stop!
Cause if this is your idea of war,
then why did you take me
with you across the desert?
Why did you save Ms. Marida?
She doesn't call you master
because she's a cyber‐Newtype,
it's because you saved
her like you did me.
It's because you touched her heart
just like you touched mine!
‐ Shut the hell up!
I won you over because I thought
it would make my job easier.
I was concerned about your well being
because you're the key to the Box!
So you don't think this is really war?
Well open your eyes and take a good look!
This is war, there are no principles,
no dignity, no honor.
Some kill, others are killed.
It's as simple as that.
And what's wrong with vengeance?
This war of ours is a
long way from being over.
‐ Your thinking.
That's how the Federation
soldiers rationalized
burning down the Zeon town!
[intense instrumental music]
[gunshots firing]
‐ [Man] See you soon, Louise!
‐ Even though people are sad,
we live our lives trying
to escape sadness,
you told me that!
You know this is pointless!
What you're doing, none of it is
going to accomplish anything!
‐ What would a kid like you know?
My whole team, we've been
waiting for this moment
for a long time!
So long, that I'm dying
to be out there myself.
‐ You don't have the right.
Just because you've been through hell,
doesn't mean you can force
others into that hell!
‐ If you don't quit your yammering,
I swear to God I'll...
[groaning]
Alec, get this kid off of me!
Flaste!
‐ Sorry Captain, I've got
my hands full right now.
You're gonna have to take
care of the kid yourself.
‐ You son of...
‐ I don't get it.
I just, I don't understand it.
It's true, life can be sad.
It could also be filled with pain.
But even so, we can't close
our hearts off because of it!
Other's sadness, I don't
want to forget that.
It's because we have hearts
that we can feel sadness.
And that's the reason
I want to become a man
who can acknowledge that sadness!
The kind of man you are, Captain!
[dramatic instrumental music]
[gunshots firing]
[loud explosion]
‐ Banagher?
‐ Mr. Tomura, please
launch the Unicorn Gundam.
‐ Aren't you on standby?
[intense instrumental music]
[gunshots firing]
‐ [Kirks] Loni, stop!
Leave from the east side
and head for the base!
‐ [Tomura] Are you sure about this?
If I drop him now,
he'll be a sitting duck.
[groaning]
‐ [Flaste] It's all right.
You should let the kid do what he wants.
Right, Captain?
‐ [Captain] Hmph.
‐ Captain, everyone in the Garencieres,
thanks for everything.
Banagher Links, Unicorn Gundam, here I go!
‐ Launch!
‐ I'm not the key to some Box, I'm human.
And you're a machine, built
to amplify human abilities.
That's what you were built for.
For those of us who can sense
what's in other's hearts,
other people's sadness.
So please, don't let anger take control.
‐ The Split‐horn, it's too
soon for the Garencieres to...
What the?
[loud explosion]
Did that boy betray us?
‐ [Banagher] I'm gonna
break the Box's seal,
you better all fall back.
‐ Why is the Box's key getting in the way?
‐ [Loni] Kirks!
‐ [Kirks] Loni, what is it?
‐ [Loni] The Split‐horn opened fire on me!
‐ Why would it do that?
Loni, we gotta go!
‐ We've taken a long,
treacherous road to get here.
I'll crush anything in my way!
‐ I don't like this.
‐ [Fighter] What is this?
Some kind of walking war museum?
‐ [Fighter 2] They got guts attacking
in ancient suits like those.
‐ [Fighter] That's why we
can't let our guard down.
Clearly these guys are
crazier than we are.
‐ [Banagher] Stop it,
why are you doing this?
‐ [Loni] I've waited my
whole life for this moment.
‐ Banagher?
‐ I owe you all a debt of gratitude.
As a result of the Garencieres
crashing into the desert,
we've finally been able
to take our revenge.
You're a bit too late.
If you stop me now, all of this will truly
have been for nothing.
So move it!
Hurry up and activate
the Split‐horn already!
‐ Stop this.
All the dead you're
responsible for here today,
their families will be filled
with hatred for your people!
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ He's wasting his time.
‐ Stop this, now!
If you keep fighting like this,
it'll harden your heart
and you'll lose your humanity!
‐ Shut up!
My father and mother were hunted down
for being Zeon Remnants.
Nobody gave them a choice to surrender,
they were slaughtered like animals.
I devoted my life to finishing
what my father started,
that's why I'm here!
I don't care if your
precious Box opens or not,
it's not gonna give me anything back,
now get the hell out of my way!
‐ [Riddhe] Banagher!
‐ [Banagher] Ensign Riddhe,
if we don't stop that thing,
the city will‐‐
‐ I know, but nothing you can say
will change that pilot's mind.
We have to take it out.
‐ But don't you know force
won't solve anything?
That isn't her, she's being enslaved.
I can do it, I'll stop her!
‐ You're right.
She is being enslaved.
By a curse bound by blood
that can never be broken.
‐ Ms. Loni, listen to me.
Think about it, is this
what you really want?
Is this what the real you truly wants?
Ms. Loni!
‐ But this is all I have, so...
Without this, I have nothing
to live for, nothing!
‐ [Banagher] Then find something!
It's too sad to live only
for hatred and anger!
‐ [Loni] It's only human
to be angered by injustice.
People aren't perfect!
‐ [Banagher] Even so, you
still have to stop this!
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ Have you lost your mind, Banagher?
It stopped.
‐ Father, Father...
I don't know anymore.
[gunshots firing]
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ I'll cover you, fall back now!
Damn it!
‐ [Pilot] What!
‐ [Pilot 2] I said not
to let your guard down!
‐ Only one shot left.
‐ Bastard!
‐ Loni...
Listen to me!
Don't end up like the rest of us!
[loud groaning]
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ They killed Kirks...
The damn Federation killed him.
They've taken another person away from me.
He was the last of my family!
‐ Ms. Loni!
‐ There's nothing left
for me now, nowhere to go!
‐ It's a harsh reality,
you can't fight it.
‐ I must...
I must do what I can to stop her.
I have to stop her.
Gundam!
I need to borrow your power!
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ Gundam...
‐ [Man] Lieutenant, is that?
‐ Yeah.
‐ [Man] You've gotta be kidding me.
Are you serious?
[groaning]
‐ Now move!
[loud yelling]
‐ Banagher, what are you doing?
Shoot her!
‐ You'd better stay out of this!
I'll make you pay, I'll make
you pay, I'll make you pay!
‐ This dark feeling that's inside you...
Don't let it take over your heart.
It won't do any good.
[groaning]
Don't let it consume you, fight it!
‐ For children to be consumed
by their parent's wishes
is the way of the world.
I'm not wrong to feel the way I do.
‐ [Banagher] What they left you
is not a wish, it's a curse!
‐ It's the same!
Our parents gave us life.
We're bound by blood to
carry out their wishes.
Curse or not, it's our duty!
You're a hypocrite,
your power was given to
you by your parents too!
It's mine, this is my fight and my war!
‐ Get on board, Banagher!
We have to be faster
than the reaction time
of those reflectors.
How's your beam magnum?
‐ I got one shot left.
‐ [Riddhe] It's do or die then.
‐ But Ensign‐‐
‐ [Riddhe] You have to!
It's the only way to protect the city.
Let's circle around, then
charge straight at the chest.
Split up as we pass,
then break through with
a simultaneous attack.
‐ Sieg Zeon, Sieg Zeon, Sieg Zeon...
Sieg Zeon, Sieg Zeon,
Sieg Zeon, Sieg Zeon...
‐ Come back, don't do this!
‐ Give it up already!
‐ Sieg Zeon, Sieg Zeon, Sieg Zeon!
‐ Loni, it's time to go.
Our war is over.
[dramatic instrumental music]
[sobbing]
‐ Ms. Loni...
‐ Banagher, what are you waiting for?
You're willing to die for possibility?
It's meaningless, let it go!
[yelling]
‐ Banagher...
Isn't it sad?
‐ I can't do it!
[dramatic instrumental music]
‐ [Woman] The massive mobile
armors have stopped moving.
The other Zeon Remnant mobile suits
appear to have been mopped up.
Assessing the damage to Torrington Base.
‐ Get me Romeo 8, I'll give him the order.
‐ Flaste.
Take us out of this airspace.
‐ [Riddhe] Come out of there, Banagher.
I have direct orders to seize that Gundam.
Hand over that suit.
‐ [Banagher] Ensign Riddhe...
This is all because of you.
If it weren't for you,
none of this would've happened.
[loud beeping]
‐ A black...
‐ Unicorn!
[foreign language catchy theme music]