[suspenseful music]
[unicorn powering down]
[blaster firing]
‐ The General Revil...
[suspenseful music]
[alarms beeping]
[blasters firing]
‐ It would be so easy
for me to finish them.
[blasters firing]
Those Federation scum better realize
this is the only break they'll get.
Next time we shoot to kill.
[blasters firing]
[dramatic music]
[beam rifle firing]
‐ Direct beam hit!
Starboard and central structures impacted.
‐ XO, get me a damage report.
‐ [XO] Moderate damage to Romeo 104.
Appears to be out of commission.
‐ [Captain] What the hell is going on?
‐ It seem to be long range
fire from an enemy mobile suit.
‐ [Captain] Deploy beam dispersal screen!
‐ [Soldier] Enemy mobile suit
closing in on high speed!
‐ [Soldier] Dispersal
screen's still at 86%.
‐ [Soldier] Matt Team, Alan
Team, cleared to launch!
‐ 63%.
‐ No. 5, No. 6,
prepare to fire!
‐ [Soldier] 42%.
‐ [Captain] All hands and
all deployed mobile suits
prepare for barrage!
‐ 27%.
18%.
‐ On my mark.
Target the incoming enemy mobile suit.
‐ [Soldier] Dispersal screen at 12%.
‐ Now fire!
[beam blasters firing]
[missiles firing]
[dramatic music]
[explosion]
‐ [Soldier] The General
Revil is altering its course.
She appears to be leaving the sector.
[dramatic music]
‐ Now, key to the box, we'll finally
have a chance to talk, you and I.
What do you say, Banagher Links?
‐ Do you believe it's possible
that we, the people of Neo
Zeon and the Federation,
will be able to work together?
Even when Laplace's box
is within our reach?
Banagher, you know, when I was on Earth,
I saw so many new things:
things I had heard about.
But to see them for myself is different.
It's only after experiencing them
does a person realize something.
I know now how ignorant
I was about the world.
‐ It was the same for me.
I felt and saw new things, too.
Then it hit me.
It's hard to work together.
Even if people try to
understand each other,
we can't escape from
what we were born into,
and the obligations it brings.
And yet we still ...
Cardeas Vist fought it.
He wanted Laplace's Box opened anyway.
‐ I want to believe it, too.
That people are good.
‐ The final coordinates
of Laplace's Box are ...
‐ [Soldier] Object detected!
It's a ship!
Checking registry.
‐ [Soldier] That's the ship
that attacked the Garuda,
no doubt about it.
Where is it been hiding
out these past two days?
‐ Attention, camouflaged
Sleeves freighter.
Halt immediately.
I repeat, camouflaged Sleeves freighter.
Heave to immediately.
Attention, camouflaged Sleeves freighter.
I say again.
Heave to immediately.
‐ Show yourself, Unicorn!
‐ Watts!
Geez, he's still mad over being knocked
into the ocean by the Unicorn.
‐ I'll make that thing stop.
[blasters firing]
‐ It's far too quiet.
Watts!
Come back.
Get away from that thing, hurry!
Watts, Watts!
‐ This is all your fault.
You were the one who provided the Unicorn
with the means to escape.
You were lured all the way
to the opposite side of the Earth.
I'll bet the Nahel Argama
and the main Neo Zeon fleet
are probably well on their
way to the moon by now
thanks to what you've done.
‐ I admit that things did not unfold
as I had anticipated.
I didn't think Full Frontal
would act so quickly,
nor capture the Nahel Argama.
My actions backfired.
‐ How does one lose track of a force
large enough to drive
away the General Revil.
‐ Due to the clandestine nature
of the General Revil's mission,
the fleets that normally
patrol the Earth's surroundings
were conveniently
withdrawn from that area,
a decision that I'm sure
was influenced by pressure
from a civilian entity.
Miss Martha, why would Neo
Zeon resort to such measures?
And what exactly is this Laplace's Box?
‐ Do you know about the tapestry
that has been handed down for generations
in the Vist Family?
The chest in it is
guarded by a white unicorn
and a black lion.
If they can't protect
it, we'll obliterate it.
The Londo Bell's services
will no longer be required.
[loud rumbling]
‐ I've been told the
Garencieres was destroyed.
‐ I see.
‐ I was just getting used
to the controls, too.
It's a shame since I finally felt
like I could fill Gilboa's shoes.
She somehow fit in
and she was a part of the Garencieres.
How many years has it
been since you pulled her
out of that cesspool?
At this point she's probably
closer to us than our own...
[machine beeping]
[somber music]
‐ Once I got aboard the Federation ship,
my plan was to wait for
a chance to hijack it.
But now I could care less about that.
If you're alive,
if you're alive, that's all that matters.
‐ [Man] Make sure to double‐check
the coolant on the suits
on the hangar deck.
‐ [Man] Announcement for
all maintenance personnel.
Crews are to follow their
original work schedules
on our own mobile suits.
‐ The ship's interior is
newer than I expected.
‐ Our intel says she's been overhauled.
‐ Ridiculous.
They actually stand the mobile
suits upright like this?
‐ Yeah, only people whose souls
have been bound by gravity
would think to do that.
‐ [Man] Hangar control to all crews
working on the hanger deck.
The Captain has approved the supply
of shipboard power to
Neo Zeon mobile suits.
Please accommodate any request for power.
Direct such request to the
nearest applicable station.
‐ Well, the damage to the
head is pretty bad, all right.
‐ The funnels are gone.
All its attachments are too.
It's pretty much unarmed now.
I did come up with some
ideas for the Unicorn Gundam
if you're interested.
I mean the Unicorn has stored in it
all the data for the battles it fought
since Industrial 7, doesn't it?
So if I can analyze it
and work my magic then ...
Banagher?
‐ [Soldier] Hold up on any
work around the cockpit area.
‐ With all that's going on,
we have no way of knowing who the Unicorn
will be fighting after we've enhanced it.
‐ Mr. Takuya?
I was wondering how Miss Micott was doing.
I haven't seen her at all
since we've been on board the ship.
‐ She's running errands for
Mr. Gibney in the engine room.
You know, she's really been on
edge since all this started.
‐ And you?
How are you holding up?
‐ Yeah, I'm okay.
So what are you gonna do now?
I mean you already know the
coordinates to Laplace's Box.
It's gonna be impossible for you
to keep them hidden forever.
Those sleeves are playing nice for now
but who knows how long it'll last?
‐ [Man] Bridge, we have a
situation in the engine room.
It's an emergency.
‐ No way!
Over my dead body!
You're not getting past me.
‐ What's going on here?
‐ Chief Engineer Sydow.
‐ Commander Liam, I've had enough!
I want you to get these
people off our ship right now.
Ridiculous.
When did we hand our
ship over to Neo Zeon?
‐ Chief Zydow.
[guns cocking]
‐ We feel exactly the same way.
‐ Us too.
You can't possibly approve
of what's going on here,
can you, Commander?
‐ The General Revil was sent out here
with the intention to destroy us.
For now our hands are tied.
‐ That's the reason for letting Neo Zeon
occupy the ship?
The enemy of my enemy is not my friend,
and my men shouldn't
have to put up with it.
‐ Those people are strutting around
the Nahel Argama like they own the place.
They even told me I had to let them
station troops in the engine room!
[soldiers muttering]
‐ In honor of all our
comrades who have fallen
at those peoples' hands, we
simply cannot allow this.
‐ Listen up, Neo Zeon, we
want you off of our ship!
[agreeing]
‐ Who do you think you are?
This is our ship.
‐ Get out of here!
‐ What's the meaning of this?
If you are all going to go at it,
why didn't you invite any of us?
‐ Commander Conroy?
‐ Yeah, you ECOAS boys should help, too.
‐ Your commander and a lot of your men
were killed by these people, right?
‐ I think you've made your point.
But if we refuse your demands,
what are you going to do about it?
‐ Then we'll just throw you
off by force if we have too.
You shot down those
Federation mobile suits
under the pretext of defending us!
‐ What we were defending
was the box's key.
We couldn't care less about what happens
to any of the rest of you.
‐ There's no denying the fact
that you saved us in our time of need,
and we're grateful for that.
But you can't expect us to
welcome you with open arms,
not when you've killed
so many of our comrades.
‐ I assure you, the feeling is mutual.
‐ Angelo.
I won't tolerate any rash behavior.
[dramatic music]
If any offense was given, I apologize.
But for the time being we
must rely on one another
in order to survive.
I urge everyone, please calm down.
‐ Tell me, what were
you doing down on Earth?
Things have only worsened since then.
You said it was important.
You said it was something on you could do.
[suspenseful music]
[whistling]
‐ Ahem, this is the captain speaking.
I would like your undivided attention.
As you are all aware we have been caught
in the middle of a conspiracy
involving Laplace's Box
and are now fleeing from none other than
our very own Earth Federation forces.
Joining forces with Neo Zeon
was the only way to extricate ourselves
from this unfortunate
situation we were forced into.
I would like to clarify
that we have not surrendered
and the Neo Zeon have no intention
of occupying this vessel.
In order to survive we will
work together with them
for the time being.
I expect all of you to
conduct yourself respectably
and with restraint.
That is all.
‐ You heard the man.
‐ I appreciate your cooperation.
‐ You should know I have no intention
of siding with Neo Zeon,
even if it means being
fired upon by my own forces.
I'll be damned if I allow the Earth Sphere
to be thrown into chaos
again by letting you people
get your hands on Laplace's Box.
‐ That doesn't change
the fact that your ship
has no other means of survival.
Thanks to the decoy
provided by the Garencieres
the Ra Cailum is probably
nearing Luna II right now.
By the time they have turned around
and are able to rendezvous with you,
we will have reached our destination.
‐ The destination?
Smack dab in the middle of a shoal zone.
‐ This shoal zone is all that remains
of the Battle of Loum.
If the purpose is to make us retrace
the trail of mankind's conflicts
in order to convey to us
the significance of obtaining the box,
well then, it would not be surprising
if the final coordinates led us there.
‐ You've been intercepting the data
from the Unicorn, haven't you?
So you already know the exact coordinates
of the final location?
‐ All we know is that it is
somewhere in that shoal zone.
We were not able to intercept
anything beyond that.
‐ Why not?
‐ I suspected it's because
the Unicorn wouldn't let us.
Ever since it chose Banagher as its pilot,
it has been exhibiting abilities
that weren't in its
original specifications.
For the time being why
don't we simply focus
on finding Laplace's Box?
Besides, the box can serve as a trump card
that may save your lives.
This is probably something
Banagher has already considered.
Sooner‐‐
‐ What's your excuse?
What are you going to do with
the box once you find it?
For a man they call the
Second Coming of Char,
I find it hard to believe
that all you wanna do
is simply revive Zeon.
I think it's about time
you reveal what your real intentions are.
‐ I would like to hear that as well.
[suspenseful music]
Well then, Captain, what
are you really after?
We're waiting for your answer.
‐ As you wish.
‐ If you wouldn't mind?
‐ Not at all, no.
What we spacenoids desire most
is the establishment of
our right to self rule.
However, the Federation
will never consent to this.
They know that the instant they do,
the roles of master and
servant would be reversed.
It's obvious, isn't it?
At present, life in the Earth Sphere
is dependent on the
existence of the Seven Sides
and the Moon for energy production,
food production, and
economic activity itself.
The fact is that on its
own Earth is no longer
even capable of feeding the 2 billion
earthnoid mouths it has.
Spcaenoids on the other hand
will have no trouble supporting themselves
if they were to sever ties with Earth.
If I was Zeon Deikun,
I would've taken advantage
of this situation.
However, while he may have
been a great philosopher,
a great politician he was not.
Whether it's the Zabi family manipulating
the Zeon ideals in a war for independence,
or the two Neo Zeon wars,
it boils down to the same thing.
Until we abandon the goal of forcing
them to formally acknowledge us,
there will be no victory
against the Federation.
We will strengthen the ties
between the Moon and the seven Sides
and create an economic zone
without the Earth at the center.
That is to say, we shall establish
the Side Co‐Prosperity Sphere.
‐ That actually makes sense.
‐ If all the sides enter
into an economic partnership
and boycott the Earth,
with no economic value,
it will be abandoned
until it withers away into nothingness.
Subsequently, the Federation government
probably won't survive either.
The only entity capable of
acting as mediator for this
is the Republic of Zeon.
Although it may be a Federation puppet,
it has been granted a certain degree
of autonomy from the government.
However, the Federation is scheduled
to revoke the Republic's autonomy
in just four short years.
If it reverts back to being Side 3
and is no longer permitted
to act as anything more
than a local government,
we will never be able to establish
the Side Co‐Prosperity Sphere.
‐ So you are at a crucial junction.
Then the Vist Foundation came forward
and they proposed turning over
Laplace's Box to you, right?
‐ Yes, although I highly doubt
that Cardias Vist had any awareness
of what we were planning.
From the timing of it, I suspect
that he hated the idea
that the controlling
Federation order would be more entrenched
when the Republic was dissolved.
It is common knowledge that it
is the Federation's intention
to eradicate Zeon once the
Republic has been dissolved,
as is evidenced by the Unicorn Gundam,
a device designed to
destroy the Newtype myth.
‐ So then what you truly hope to gain
by obtaining the box is time?
By threatening the Federation
and postponing the
disillusion of the Republic,
you gain the time to create
this Side Co‐Prosperity Sphere of yours.
‐ That is an accurate assessment.
‐ Now that I hear it said
out loud it seems so petty.
You'll establish the
Side Co‐Prosperity Sphere
and exclude the Federation.
Instead of asking for change from those
who have resisted reform,
you choose to ostracize them.
That couldn't be further removed
from the ideals of Zeon Deikun
who trumped of reforming humanity.
And it is also world's
apart from the passion
and madness of Char who tried to render
Earth uninhabitable and move
all humanity into space.
Now are you sure that
is what you really want?
If this Side Co‐Prosperity Sphere yours
comes to past, the earthnoids will likely
accelerate the redevelopment
of their planet,
an attempt to support
an economy of their own.
It would be a return to the old AD era.
Most likely the new
generation of earthnoids
will grow up in poverty,
will even plot to retaliate
against the spacenoids.
Familiar?
It's just like when Zeon
started the One Year War.
No harmony or reform.
Only the strong and weak endlessly
trading places for eternity.
Is that what a man who
decided to reveal himself
to the world again really wants?
‐ I can imagine how you
must feel, Your Highness.
But this is not a matter
of what's right or wrong.
It is merely how the world operates.
A vessel does not think for itself.
It acts in accordance
with the collective will
that has been poured into it.
It does this to ensure
humanity's survival.
‐ You talk like it doesn't affect you.
But you're talking about
your own people's feature
and what you're saying sounds cold
and detached like you're
somehow not part of it.
The light that enveloped
the Unicorn Gundam
that last time was warm,
like it somehow held all the feelings
of everyone I know.
What if that kind of
possibility is inside humans?
‐ I've also seen that same light before.
But the light was even larger.
I suspect that it may have been the result
of gathering the
subconscious of every human
in the Earth Sphere via the psycho frame
and converting it all into energy.
It was a psycho field that
deflected the asteroid Axis.
‐ The Axis Shock?
‐ Yet even when they faced
such overwhelming possibility
people still did not change.
To maintain the status quo,
humans will sweep even
possibility under the rug.
It's what they do.
All we can do is hope to find peace
and stability given that reality.
And what's more you should be aware
that this possibility that you speak
so fondly of has been the
trigger for many a war.
‐ The Char Aznable that I knew
truly is dead.
It is at Industrial 7.
It is the colony builder, Megalonica.
That is the final set of coordinates
given by the Laplace Program.
‐ Oh.
‐ The burden was too heavy
for that boy to bear.
‐ I'd like you to kindly
confirm this, if you would?
Thank you.
I'll be going back to
the Rewloola for a bit.
I would like you to join me, Captain.
I'm leaving you in charge here, Angelo.
‐ Sir!
[engines shutting off]
[hatch opening]
‐ When it comes to prevention Neo Zeon
from getting their hands on the box,
the Vist Foundation and
Federation Government's interests
are completely aligned.
In the face of that threat,
the continued existence of the box
is no longer of vital importance.
The Banshee is a machine
that was originally created
to be manned by Cyber Newtypes.
‐ Banagher was able to master his.
I'm sure I'll do the same.
‐ There's just one more thing.
It's a favor.
I would like for you to recover Ple 12,
the Cyber Newtype abducted by the slaves.
As to why I'll keep that to myself.
Now, I went to considerable lengths
to recommend you as the
Banshee's pilots, Ensigne Riddhe.
That's because I trust you
to carry out this request
without informing my aunt or her cronies.
In the event that you and the Banshee
are unable to destroy the Unicorn,
then the Vist Foundation will be forced
to use its final option.
Should that happen
everything will be lost,
and I highly doubt that's something
you would want to transpire.
‐ What you're talking about would mean
killing your own half brother.
You would do that?
‐ The road we're headed
down is already bloodied.
It was an accident.
Well, no it wasn't really.
Truth be told, the members of my family
have a history of killing one another.
One of the reasons why my
Aunt Martha became so callous
is because her father, my grandfather,
was killed by Siam Vist,
our great grandfather.
"Revenge against a world
ruled by the logic of men."
Her words, not mine.
Nevertheless not something
a man could easily abide by.
But then again perhaps this world
ought to be given a clean slate.
[boosters firing]
Although a species that would create
demons like Unicorn and the Banshee
is probably standing on the
threshold of destruction anyway.
[beeping]
‐ Banagher.
Visitor, visitor!
‐ Miss Marida?
Should you be out of your‐‐
‐ Here.
Help me finish these off.
They taste awful.
They're supposed to help
patients with their recovery
but I can't stomach them.
‐ Banagher, help help!
They taste awful.
‐ You're right, it's disgusting.
‐ I told you.
‐ Miss Marida, what kind of
foods do you normally like?
‐ Why do you ask?
‐ I'd rather know what you
like than what you hate.
‐ I've never really thought about it.
‐ Well, what do you think taste good?
There has to be something.
Like something sweet maybe?
‐ Do you think?
Do you think?
‐ Let me think.
Ice cream.
‐ All right then.
I know a great ice cream
parlor at Industrial 7.
We can ...
Oh.
‐ Those things the Captain
said, he's right, huh?
‐ Yeah, probably but
it's always like that.
And yet it doesn't matter.
Everything ultimately still
just blows up in my face.
It doesn't matter how hard I try or fight.
However, if it weren't for your efforts
I wouldn't be sitting here
talking to you like this.
You know, the way you feel isn't wrong.
Trust in the possibility that lies within.
And try with all your might,
do what you feel is correct.
That belief isn't a curse.
The one who told you that
probably lived that way
following that tenant,
never knowing if it was true.
Simply believing it was right.
‐ But that's so irresponsible of him.
He couldn't do what he wanted on his own.
‐ That might be true.
But still, even so.
He was lucky to be able
to entrust his dream
to someone who wasn't a stranger.
This is how the world progresses
one tiny bit at a time.
If you hold on to your dreams,
if you never give up, if you
don't become close minded.
I know your chance will come.
When it does, don't hesitate.
Get into the Gundam.
Princess.
‐ Are you feeling better?
‐ Yes.
‐ Forgive me, Marida.
I ...
‐ I hope that you, Princess,
can follow your heart, too.
‐ I told Mr. Conway what we're up to
and he said to be careful.
‐ Since we don't have
the support of the ship
we'll proceed as is.
‐ Right.
IF we use as our opening
we'll be able to drive them off the ship.
‐ Hey, Micott.
What do you think of that Zeon girl?
Do you think she's planning
on doing something?
I mean she did give Full
Frontal the box's coordinates.
0 It was to throw 'em off guard.
‐ Are you sure?
‐ Whenever a woman lies,
my skin gets tingly,
and she means business.
‐ I don't understand women at all.
‐ What are you doing?
‐ That thing doesn't have legs.
‐ If it weren't for the General
Revil's surprise attack,
you would have hijacked the Nahel Argama
with or without us, am I right, Captain?
‐ That's what you
brought me down here for.
‐ Does it seem meaningless now?
For all those years you clung
on to that hatred of yours,
never being able to get rid of it.
But now you have other dreams.
Was it the boy who somehow changed you
or was it Lt. Marida?
‐ I couldn't let go of this hatred
even if I'd wanted to.
But I wouldn't exactly
call it meaningless now.
I suppose I'm tired,
tired of huddling in the darkness,
of the me who has given up on everything.
It makes me wonder.
Back then when Char Aznable chose
to create the world of Newtypes
that his father dreamed of
instead of seeking revenge
against the Zabi family,
I wonder if maybe he was in the same
state of mind as I am in right now.
‐ If by chance Char Aznable
happen to still be alive today,
I think there's a possibility that
he would no longer be entirely human.
Go ahead.
‐ [Soldier] Captain, we've detected a ship
heading this way.
It appears to be a
Federation patrol vessel.
‐ [Soldier] This is Patrol Vessel El Faro
with the L1 Patrol.
Londo Bell vessel, Nahel Argama,
we have received your distress signal.
Please respond.
‐ What are they talking about?
How did they get a distress signal?
We didn't send one.
It's just one ship and yet ...
Ensign Mihiro.
‐ Sir!
‐ Get rid of them as quickly as you can.
The Neo Zeons will not sit idly by
if you let that ship hang around.
‐ Understood.
‐ [Soldier] Londo Bell
vessel, Nahel Argama.
Respond at once.
Wait a minute.
We're detecting Neo
Zeon vessels around you.
Two Musaka class, one Rewloola class.
Both are transmitting
Federation forces IFF codes.
Requesting an explanation.
If necessary we will go to combat alert.
Please respond.
Londo Bell vessel, Nahel Argama,
state your mission and your destination.
I say again‐‐
‐ Your orders, sir?
‐ Blow them out of the sky, Captain.
‐ [Soldier] Why are you not responding?
‐ Hurry up and give the order to attack.
‐ Don't be ridiculous.
That ship is one of ours.
‐ If you don't, they will
call for reinforcements.
What will your chances be then?
You will take responsibility.
It seems some misguided
souls aboard your ship
have put our joint front at risk.
‐ You mean they sent
out a distress signal?
‐ We could easily fire
on them from our ships
but this is your mess so
you should be the ones
to clean it up.
If you refuse to attack
we'll take it to mean
that you are dissolving our joint front.
It's your decision, yours alone, Captain.
‐ [Soldier] If you continue
to maintain radio silence,
we will deal with you‐‐
‐ This can't be happening.
[suspenseful music]
‐ Make your decision quickly.
You have civilians aboard this ship!
‐ I dare you to lay a finger
on a single one of them.
If you do I'll rip your head off, boy!
You people are no soldiers.
You're nothing but a bunch of terrorists,
and I do not negotiate with terrorists.
Any arrangement we've had
with your people is now over.
‐ Yeah, you tell 'em, Captain.
[guns firing]
‐ You bastards!
[groaning]
‐ Explain our situation
to the patrol ship.
Have them get clear.
‐ Roger!
‐ How dare they while
the Captain's not here!
‐ What should we do?
‐ Why are you asking me?
To the mobile suit deck.
We'll go secure the
Garancieres team's suits.
‐ Fleet members are headed towards
the mobile suit deck.
‐ That you, Banagher?
Get down to the mobile suit deck.
‐ [Soldier] Seal off designated air locks.
‐ Get into the Gundam
and smash the cockpits
of all the Neo Zeon mobile suits.
We'll keep unnecessary
combat to a minimum.
‐ Right.
‐ And Banagher ...
Be careful.
The commander saved your life
so you better not waste it.
You got that?
‐ Got it!
[suspenseful music]
[guns firing]
‐ [Conroy] Don't let those Neo
Zeon bastards off the ship.
We can use them as hostages
against the Rewloola.
‐ [Soldier] Engine block secured!
‐ [Soldier] Two hostiles have escaped
towards the bow of the ship.
‐ [Soldier] What is the current status
of the mobile suit deck?
‐ Mobile suit deck here.
Still engaging enemy forces.
Requesting reinforcements.
‐ [Soldier] Hangar controls secured.
We're getting repaired.
‐ [Soldier] Whatever happens,
do not let the enemy pilots
reach their mobile suits!
[guns firing]
‐ This is as far as you'll get.
I suggest you not try anything foolish.
Now that we know where the box is located
we no longer have an incentive
for keeping you alive.
We could destroy the Unicorn as well.
Why do you refuse us?
If the Federation gets a hold of the box
it will ensure the continuation
of the current flawed system.
Isn't that in direct conflict
with your late father
whose last wish was to
bring about reformation?
Only Zeon has the ability to use the box
to grant the abandoned spacenoid people
their long cherished dream.
What can you do?
How are you planning to
utilize Laplace's Box?
‐ There's one thing I do know.
I would use it for everyone.
Not just Federation, not just
for Zeon, space or earth.
I'd use Laplace's Box for everyone.
‐ Captain!
‐ And what exactly do
you mean by everyone?
One man cannot be the voice
for the wishes of the entire human race,
not unless he becomes a vessel.
But to become a vessel he
must release everything
and go beyond his own madness
and emerge from the other side.
That is no simple accomplishment.
Still, you do possess talent.
If you truly wish to become a vessel,
then come with me.
You've been entrusted
with your father's dreams
and forced to undergo training
not unlike a Cyber Newtype.
Now that you have
exhibited the power of one,
you can never go back to
being a part of that everyone.
One day you will run headlong
into the same despair that I did.
‐ [Marida] Keep telling
yourself even so Banagher.
‐ Just die already!
‐ [Mineva] Withdraw your
forces, Full Frontal!
We do not choose to walk
the same path as you.
‐ Audrey!
‐ [Mineva] The second
coming of the Red Comet.
There was a time when we
clung to your strength.
We were being hounded by the Federation
and we had nothing else to hold on to.
But you are not Char.
The Char Aznable that I knew
was a man who believed
in human possibility!
‐ Why do you insist on refusing to accept
the Captain's ideas?
[groans]
Garancieres team,
officers and soldiers of
Neo Zeon, listen to me.
Whatever Laplace's Box turns out to be
it will mark a profound
turning point for us.
It may even be capable of bringing about
the future that Full Frontal speaks of.
He may be correct.
It may be the only
realistic option that exists
to ensure humanity's survival.
However, do you truly want
to make that the future?
Isn't the future supposed
to refer to a time
that is different from the present?
A world that is better
than the one we have now?
The harmony and human evolution
that Zeon Deikun dreamt of
do not exist in that future world.
As successors to those who brought about
the tragedies of the One Year War,
we have not only
inherited the name of Zeon
but we have inherited responsibility.
If we simply accept the
status quo as a fixed reality,
we cannot fulfill that responsibility.
The light the Unicorn showed us...
‐ [Zinnerman] Marida
Cruz, open your cockpit.
‐ Marida, don't!
‐ How can the last Sazabi
heir say such a thing?
‐ Audrey!
‐ That's enough.
Come out of your cockpit and
bring the Princess with you.
‐ Marida, snap out of it.
Marida!
Zinnerman, are you still
a prisoner of your past?
You have Marida now.
Take responsibility and
live in the present.
Things were different ever since that day
you rescued Marida,
weren't they Zimmerman?
‐ Reason can't make things go away.
My hatred, the regret.
I couldn't help them.
I couldn't do anything.
They must have been so scared.
It's so much pain.
And I did nothing.
Fi, Marie.
‐ Father.
Just this once, will
you let me have my way?
[calm music]
‐ All right.
This will be my final order to you.
Listen to your heart.
‐ Understood.
[dramatic music]
‐ Zinnerman, you bastard!
[guns firing]
You people!
This is how you always act!
Irresponsible.
Weak!
That is why ...
We need something more
powerful than humanity,
and the Captain has transcended humanity.
‐ It's humanity's future.
So shouldn't it be built by humans?
It's true, people are weak and flawed.
That's why we need each other.
We pass all our dreams to one another
and we can keep walking forward
no matter how painful the path might be.
‐ What's that?
What is that light?
‐ [Full Frontal] Angelo.
‐ [Angelo] Captain!
[dramatic music]
‐ Angelo!
‐ Banagher.
We will be leaving now.
‐ Wait!
‐ It will be a race from here on out.
[blaster firing]
[indistinct chatter]
‐ Pardon me for interrupting.
I have the perfect
solution for your current
predicament, Chairman Ronan.
‐ [Liam] Maximum combat speed.
All crew extinguishing shipboard fires,
brace for acceleration.
‐ Begin detaching all units.
‐ So that's the full armor, huh?
Well, what do you think we should do now?
‐ If I asked you to put
me out of my misery,
would you be willing to do it?
‐ Come on, that's not even funny, sir.
Besides, there's still a whole mess
that needs to be done
by me and you, Captain.
‐ I suppose there is.
[suspenseful music]
‐ This is your Captain speaking.
We have just set a course for Industrial 7
to carry out our mission.
That mission is to locate
and secure Laplace's Box.
Although it may seem like we have returned
to our original assignment,
this mission is not being conducted
on orders from the military.
We do it to survive.
We are conducting this operation
under our own auspices.
We cannot allow the box to
fall into Full Frontal's hands,
whether it be his Side
Co‐Prosperity Sphere
or the future Princess Mineva described.
The crux of the conflict
is humanity's potential.
Of these two I do now know
which path is correct.
But we will not be the
ones to make this decision.
Rather it will be our children,
the youth who are alive today,
and their children, the youth
that are yet to be born.
And in order to entrust
this choice to them
we must return from this alive.
We must return with the box in hand
and then let the world face the truth.
[dramatic music]
As a soldier and as a man,
I look forward to seeing
you fight bravely.
‐ Banagher Links here.
Unicorn Gundam.
Taking off!
[boosters blasting]
I've come home.
‐ Thermal signature closing
in from six o'clock.
[alarms blaring]
It's a mobile suit.
It's being carried on a Geta.
‐ If that patrol ship sent a report back,
then there's a good chance
that the General Revil
might have dispatched it
‐ That's just great.
Disperse Minovsky particles.
It's only one suit.
Let's drive it off!
[missiles firing]
‐ You're gonna need to
do better than that.
[blasters firing]
Where's the Unicorn?
Where is it?
[suspenseful music]
‐ Ensign Riddhe.
‐ Banagher!
[foreign rock music]