‐ [Narrator] It is now
23:40 Greenwich Mean Time.
We are about to witness the
end of the world as we know it
and usher in a new world
as never before imagined.
The Earth Federation government
is about to host a ceremony
at the prime minister's
residence, Laplace,
to celebrate the birth of a new era.
The ingenuity of mankind has allowed us
to move beyond Mother Earth
and build worlds of our own to inhabit.
Tonight, we'll mark the
beginning of a new epoch.
Let us come together in this joyous moment
to honor the past, the era of Anno Domini,
and greet the dawn of
the Universal Century
with open hearts and minds.
So with great enthusiasm,
let us open the door
to our future together.
Farewell, Anno Domini, and
welcome Universal Century.
‐ Greetings, citizens of Earth and space.
I am Ricardo Marcenas,
prime minister of the Earth Federation.
It is with great pride that
I stand before you tonight.
In a matter of mere moments,
the era of Anno Domini
will fade into history.
In the past, presidents
and prime ministers
addressed the citizens of
their respective countries.
Each country had its own
people, its own territories
originally created to
protect their interests,
and defend against attacks
from other countries,
but when you look at the Earth from space,
you can't see those dividing lines.
And now that we've made mankind's dream
of a unified world government a reality,
we are no longer bound by the antiquated
nation‐state system.
And just as no man is
an island unto himself,
no one being can survive without
coexisting with the others.
Now that we must face dangers
that threaten our planet as a whole,
the entirety of our people
can face them as one.
The old nations of Earth were incapable
[speaking drowned out by warbling]
to create effective solutions.
[glass shattering]
[loud rumbling]
[people screaming]
[loud blasting]
[pensive orchestral music]
[footsteps approaching]
‐ Well, then?
‐ We're going to proceed as planned,
but this has the potential to create chaos
on a level we have never before known.
‐ It's hard to believe
it's been almost 100 years.
If nothing is done, the Earth Sphere
will not be able to continue.
Those who can correct the
flaws of the Universal Century
are beginning to emerge.
I pray that we will soon find one
who can be entrusted
to carry Laplace's Box.
‐ Yes, sir.
‐ Cardeas.
Can you forgive me?
‐ What we're about to do could lead
to the destruction of the world.
If anyone were able to
give you forgiveness,
it would have to be me.
[pensive orchestral music]
[pensive orchestral music builds]
[bright beeping]
‐ [Man] Disperse Minovsky
Particles at combat density now!
‐ [Man] Enemy ship
appears to be Clop class.
Thermal energy detected.
‐ [Man] Evasive maneuvers!
[muffled blasting]
[electrical zapping]
‐ [Man] What's taking so
long with the bulkheads?
‐ Intense heat sources
emitted from the ship.
Appears to be two mobile suits.
Correction, make that three suits!
Approaching at high speed.
‐ Send Marida out.
Ignore the mothership.
The Garencieres can shake it off.
‐ Roger that.
Target has been acquired.
That's a high‐speed Jegan,
possibly a special forces version.
‐ [Captain] That means
this was no coincidence.
We hit the debris cluster in 10 minutes.
Take care of those
Jegans and get back here.
‐ [Marida] That's an affirmative, Master.
‐ And stop calling me Master.
‐ Marida Cruz, Kshatriya, launch!
[thrusters blasting]
[dramatic tense music]
[beeping]
No way you're following our ship.
Funnels!
[dramatic tense music]
[dramatic tense music builds]
[electrical zapping]
[lasers firing]
[loud blasting]
[warbling blast]
[missiles firing]
[loud blasting]
[electrical zapping]
‐ [Robotic Voice] Damn the Sleeves!
‐ [Marida] Mission
complete, returning to ship.
‐ Therefore, it was
the Battle of A Baoa Qu
which brought an end to the
One Year War 17 years ago,
one year before you were born.
Once the hostilities ceased,
over half of the human race
had been wiped out.
The war was started by
the Principality of Zeon
in the name of independence
for the space immigrants.
And even though the war's officially over,
groups claiming to be the remnants of Zeon
have started their own wars.
They claim to desire
autonomy for the Spacenoids,
but at their heart, you will
still find the same ideas
of the inherent superiority
of the chosen elite
found in the philosophy of Gihren Zabi.
The concept of Zeonism,
proposed by Zeon Deikun,
the so‐called Newtype ideology,
was a dangerous belief
that ultimately produced
these rebellious elements.
[sharp tapping]
[gasping]
You there!
You'd best give me your full attention.
You believe you can get a
job without an education?
But Anaheim won't even hire you
for a factory worker position
if you don't hold some kind of diploma!
Don't believe everything
you hear about that 100%
job placement rate.
‐ Sorry to interrupt, Mr. Bancroft.
It's the shuttle again.
[students chattering]
[sighs]
‐ [Marco] Don't you think it's time
they upgraded the shuttles?
‐ [Takuya] The chairman's such a tightwad.
He thinks that the decommissioned
Anaheim ones are enough.
‐ [Micott] So are we staying
here tonight, or what?
I didn't bring a change of clothes.
‐ [Ester] Yeah, me neither.
‐ So that means tomorrow,
we're gonna miss the field trip
to the Snail.
‐ No way!
I can't spend two days here
listening to Bancroft's special lectures!
It'll put me in a coma!
‐ I bet I could teach all the
history up to Char's Rebellion
in under two minutes, right, Banagher?
Hey, look up there, it's a Zaku!
Dammit, Bancroft, why didn't you tell us
there was something so cool here?
‐ [Ester] What is it?
What's so cool about it?
‐ It's only the granddaddy
of all mobile suits!
[Ester grunts]
Hey, wait a sec, we gotta check it out!
‐ [Marco] No, we don't.
‐ [Ester] The wars ended a long time ago.
What are those things good for?
‐ [Denis] Takuya, I'm pretty
sure you can't take pictures.
‐ If you'd listen to me, we
coulda had so much fun, but no.
‐ Hey, Banagher.
Do you realize you look out
into the distance a lot?
‐ I do?
‐ Yeah, like just now.
‐ I'm not really looking
at anything when I do that.
It's hard to explain.
I guess I'm wondering where‐‐
‐ [Micott] Where your father is?
‐ [Banagher] No, where I am.
‐ [Micott] Oh, sorry.
‐ It feels like no matter what I'm doing,
I don't actually feel like I'm there.
‐ I know what you mean!
It's like you can't put your finger on it,
but everything feels off, right?
‐ Yeah.
‐ I sometimes wonder if that feeling's
gonna keep growing stronger.
I think the only people
who don't think that way...
[sharp ringing]
[soft pensive music]
Hey, are you listening to me?
‐ A mobile suit.
[Micott grunts]
[soft tense music]
[sharp whistling]
[panting]
‐ Increase velocity.
‐ Right.
[thrusters blasting]
‐ Fly like you're going
straight into that debris field.
[man panting]
[beeping]
Keep going.
‐ [groans] Please, sir, I can't!
‐ Breakdown, 0‐6‐0.
[tense music]
[sighs]
I'm most impressed.
‐ Thank you.
‐ With the machine.
At ease.
‐ [Gael] RX‐0, final phase, all clear.
Psycho frame g‐force
within expected parameters.
Pilot's life signs stable.
‐ We're heading back now, Gael.
‐ [Man] I'm sorry, sir.
‐ What's the matter?
‐ There were still some people
at the Anaheim Electronics
Industrial College training facility.
‐ [Commander] I thought we
checked the class schedule.
‐ [Man] We did, sir, but it seems
the transit shuttle broke down.
‐ I see.
Well, even if someone
did happen to notice it,
we were moving so fast,
they couldn't have caught
more than a glimpse.
‐ I was able to get hold of
a staff officer on Luna II.
They confirmed a Londo Bell
ship ran into some Sleeves
and tried to pursue them.
‐ So there was a leak.
Did they engage in battle?
‐ Yes, sir.
Not only did they lose three mobile suits,
but they let them get away.
‐ Is there anything else?
‐ I tried Londenion, but their commander
isn't very forthcoming.
‐ That would be Bright Noa, I believe.
Try the supply fleets then.
That'll tell us how the
fleet itself is moving.
‐ [Man] Yes, sir.
‐ All right, everyone, listen up.
All operational testing of
the RX‐0 is now finished.
The testing OS must now be deleted.
Seal the NT‐D and boot up
the La+ Program immediately.
[staff applauding]
[soft pensive music]
[sighs]
Forgive, huh?
[soft whirring]
‐ Roger that, entering gate number five.
So what are we gonna do with this
Laplace's Box thing anyway?
‐ If they really have it,
we'll bring it back home.
If it's a trap, we'll fight our way out.
[soft whirring]
[muffled breathing]
[grunting]
[man speaking over speaker]
[bright music]
[gasps]
[groans]
‐ Man, I don't think I
can deal with any more
of this weightlessness.
Let me skip the Snail
field trip, it's too much!
‐ [Man] What's too much
is all the partying
you did last night.
‐ Looking at the
Construction Unit is boring!
‐ [Ester] Are you kidding?
People don't usually get
to look inside that thing!
[gasps softly]
‐ Banagher!
‐ [Takuya] Don't bother, Micott.
‐ [Haro] Banagher go to bathroom?
‐ I gotta check something out.
[wind blowing]
‐ [Audrey] [inhales] I can't die, not now!
[tense music]
‐ Hey, what are you doing?
‐ Gotta borrow this for a sec.
‐ You can't do that!
Get the hell back here! [groaning]
Get back here!
‐ This handles different than in a vacuum.
[soft tense music]
There you are, but it's
almost daybreak, not good!
[groaning]
‐ [Audrey] I have to hold on!
I still need to...
[mechanical whirring]
[soft tense music]
[grunting]
‐ [Haro] Danger, danger!
[beeping]
‐ We're gonna be fine.
[tense music]
Brace yourself!
‐ [Haro] Danger, danger!
[smoke hissing]
Banagher, wake up.
[mechanical whirring]
[grunting]
‐ Ow, hey!
‐ [Audrey] Who are you?
‐ What's your problem?
‐ [Haro] Banagher, are you okay?
Banagher!
‐ You're from this colony?
[grunts]
I'm in a hurry.
Will you be able to help me get to
the Colony Builder's entrance?
‐ You mean the Snail?
‐ [Audrey] Can we get there in this thing?
‐ It's outta gas, and the battery's shot.
‐ I don't have much time, help me!
There's someone I must speak with,
but if I don't get there in time,
I'm afraid something terrible will happen!
We must act immediately, so please!
‐ Stop something?
What is it?
‐ A war.
[tense pounding]
‐ Hey, wait!
You can't do it alone!
[mechanical whirring]
Who's this person you need to talk to?
The Snail, that's what everyone
calls the Colony Builder,
but all it is is a factory.
Although it's just a rumor, supposedly,
there's a Vist Foundation
mansion at the end of it.
‐ Have you been there?
‐ No, I've never seen it,
but one of their higher‐ups
is the chairman of my school.
‐ [Train Announcer]
Attention all passengers,
this is a security announcement.
The authorities have just
issued a security alert.
This train will be stopped
temporarily at this station
until the security alert has been lifted.
‐ Seems like this keeps happening.
‐ Well, the government has to
be extra cautious these days.
‐ [Marco] Why don't we get off here?
‐ [Ester] We can't do that, Marco!
[people chattering]
‐ We should go.
‐ [Captain] So you're thinking
she was in that Petite MS?
‐ Makes sense, given the fact
that she's nowhere to be found.
‐ [Captain] We're going
to be in a lot of trouble
if the Federation saw her,
but we have to see how
the foundation reacts
before we can know that.
‐ My apologies, sir.
It's my fault for not noticing
that she stowed away on our ship.
‐ No, it's not.
I'm the captain of this ship,
so I'm the one to blame.
Fortunately, we know where she's going.
Get her back before she has a chance
to make contact with Cardeas Vist,
and try to stay under the radar.
‐ [Audrey] So, that's a Construction Unit?
‐ Yeah, it's a factory unit
that builds foundation blocks
for the colony.
This whole place is
still under construction.
Why aren't you eating?
You got to be starving!
Let's keep on the move.
‐ You mean we're going to eat and walk?
[distant ringing]
‐ Hey, they're about to
begin a factory tour.
We can blend in with the crowd.
We'll figure out the
rest once we're inside.
‐ Marida!
‐ Let's go back.
You have your position to consider.
‐ If you understood my position,
you'd know I can't do that!
‐ I know what you're trying is futile.
‐ [Audrey] We can't handle
Laplace's Box right now,
whatever it is.
It will simply be used by Full Frontal
to start a meaningless war,
which will bring nothing
but more suffering.
You understand that, don't you?
‐ I don't.
I understand that I have orders to follow.
‐ That's a lie!
You weren't given your powers for this.
You know very well that‐‐
‐ I'm sorry.
[soft tense music]
[Haro beeping]
‐ [Haro] Danger, danger!
‐ Give me your hand.
[Haro beeping]
[grunting]
‐ Hurry!
[tense pensive music]
[grunting]
[panting]
[bones cracking]
[groaning]
‐ Why did‐‐
‐ My name.
Sorry, I was only gonna say
I never told you my name.
‐ It's Banagher.
Your pet called out your
name after we crashed.
‐ Banagher, go, Banagher, go, Banagher!
‐ Yeah, so I'm Banagher Links.
‐ And I'm,
my name's Audrey, Audrey Burne.
‐ Audrey!
This is Haro.
It's a replica of a robot mascot
built by an ace pilot back during the war.
It was the coolest thing
ever when we were kids.
‐ [Audrey] I wouldn't
know what most kids liked.
‐ [Banagher] What do you mean?
‐ [Audrey] Well, when I grew
up, we were always on the move.
I was brought up like a nomad.
‐ Yeah, that sounds a lot like me.
[soft pensive music]
‐ [Takuya] Man, look at those rails!
‐ [Ester] They go up so high!
‐ [Marco] Whoa, check out that framework!
‐ Come on, Micott, take
a look, it's really cool!
‐ Yeah, right down there!
‐ I guess Banagher never showed, huh?
‐ That Petite MS that
crashed on our school campus,
I hope that wasn't him.
‐ It didn't crash, that
was a forced landing.
And we don't know why he did it,
so we shouldn't be
spreading rumors about him.
If he gets kicked out of school,
he's gonna be living on the streets!
It's not like he has a home to go back to!
[soft pensive music]
‐ Banagher!
Who's that girl he's with?
‐ [Banagher] Those
people who are after you,
what's up with them?
‐ [Audrey] I ran away, they're
supposed to bring me back.
They're not trying to hurt us.
‐ [Banagher] You some
kind of political activist
or something?
You know, one of those anti‐Federation,
the ones seeking independence
for the Spacenoids, or whatever?
‐ [Audrey] Kinda, only scarier.
‐ You said you wanted to
prevent a war, didn't you?
[warm pensive music]
The walls of the colony grows,
more and more foundation blocks are added.
‐ Amazing!
The world itself is growing.
[warm pensive music]
‐ [Man With Mustache] Sir,
we picked something up
on lift two's surveillance camera.
‐ [gasps] What is she doing there?
‐ I don't know, sir.
I received a report that
earlier this morning,
someone snuck into the service route
to the artificial sun, but I
never would have imagined‐‐
‐ Have you heard anything
from the Sleeves?
‐ [Man With Mustache] No, sir.
‐ So she's acting on her own.
‐ This may interfere
with the Box's delivery.
I still believe that as
head of the Vist Foundation,
your meeting with the Sleeves
in person is ill‐advised.
‐ And what do you have
on this boy she's with?
‐ Ah, yes, sir, he was with her.
He looks a little young to be a bodyguard.
[tense music]
‐ That's it.
I can't believe there's
really a mansion out here.
[soft warm music]
[gentle tapping]
Maybe no one's home.
Banagher!
Excuse us, is anyone here?
Banagher, you can't just...
[soft warm music]
A unicorn.
‐ To my only desire.
‐ You can read all of that?
‐ What's going on?
I remember this.
I've seen this before.
‐ Interested in that?
The Lady and the Unicorn.
It's a tapestry believed
to have been created
in France before the Middle
Era, and it's no replica.
My predecessor went through
a great deal of trouble
to acquire it prior to the One Year War.
I'm head of the family,
Cardeas Vist, this is my home.
‐ I must apologize for
coming into your home
without permission, my name is‐‐
‐ I'm aware of who you are.
I think it would be best for everyone
if you didn't mention your name.
‐ Then we'll skip the formality.
As long as you understand my position,
that's all that really matters.
I've come here to ask you to
rethink this course of action.
I'm referring to Laplace's Box
and your plan to hand it over to us.
‐ I think you had better leave.
It's too dangerous, we
shouldn't be talking
under these circumstances.
‐ Zinnerman is a rational man.
He wouldn't cause trouble unnecessarily.
‐ Would you consider your
protection unnecessary?
‐ Tell me, why are you doing this?
I've heard that Laplace's
Box has guaranteed
the prosperity of the Vist
Foundation for decades.
Why give it to us now?
‐ Excuse me, you've been asked to leave.
‐ There are people after her!
I won't leave her alone!
‐ Do you even have the
slightest idea who they are
or what they want with
her, for that matter?
‐ I don't, I don't, but
they are scary people!
‐ Scary?
‐ [Banagher] Well, that's
just how they felt.
‐ That's something a Newtype would say.
‐ [Banagher] She said they were scary.
‐ [Cardeas] You are
putting your future at risk
by staying here.
This is not what your father intended
when he sent you to Anaheim
Electronics Industrial College.
‐ How do you‐‐
‐ I'm the chairman of your school.
As such, I can find
out who my students are
and can find out anything I need to know,
or expel them as I see fit.
‐ Go home, Banagher.
I appreciate all you've
done for me thus far.
I can take it from here.
‐ But Audrey, I can still help!
You came here to prevent
the war, didn't you?
And doesn't he have the power
to do something about that?
Hearing you talk about
the war is so different
from hearing my professors
talk about it, more grave.
You've made me see how bad it
would be, so please, let me‐‐
‐ Banagher.
‐ My heart was pounding
when I saw you fall
from the sky this morning.
Everything that felt off in
my life just slid into place.
For the first time in my life,
I knew what I was supposed to do.
I don't care who you are!
Just say that you need me
and I'll, just tell me.
‐ I don't need you.
Now, go.
The best thing you can
do is forget about me.
[soft tense music]
‐ [Cardeas] You made the right decision.
I've changed the location of the exchange
with your comrades.
Once the time seems right,
you'll be reunited with them.
‐ I urge you to rethink the consequences
of what you're about to do.
‐ I understand your concern
about this, you're not wrong.
I'm aware that Full
Frontal is being called
the second coming of Char,
and not to be taken lightly.
‐ Then why are you‐‐
‐ [Cardeas] Because it's not that simple.
Even if given the key, it will
still take someone qualified
to open Laplace's Box.
[cheering]
‐ [Audrey] The key to the box?
‐ We have taken steps to create something
that will ensure that this
is no easy horse to break.
‐ [Captain] All right, return to the ship.
We've just received a
message from the Foundation.
They want to move the
meeting from the Central Port
to the Colony Builder.
‐ So what did they say about her?
‐ They're feigning ignorance.
I can't tell what they're up to,
but we'll keep a poker face on for now.
You just head back to the ship.
I need you to be ready for anything.
[upbeat music]
[static buzzing]
‐ Huh, what's that?
‐ The head of the Vist
Foundation in person.
I'm honored.
‐ We're entrusting you with
the fate of the Foundation.
I couldn't leave this to anyone else.
This way, come.
‐ [groans angrily] You piece of crap!
[sighs]
Londo Bell?
What are they doing here?
[soft tense music]
‐ Enemy?
‐ A key?
What's this?
So it's not the box
itself you're giving us,
but rather, its key?
‐ Unsatisfied?
‐ Not unsatisfied, just confused.
We don't even know what
the box is or what it does.
Of course, nobody does, do they?
But we do know that opening Laplace's Box
would mean overthrowing the Federation,
and that your Vist
Foundation's wealth and glory
come from your secret possession of it.
We also know that your
reputation as a charity
that transports works
of art to the colonies
is nothing more than a front.
The truth, however‐‐
‐ Your leaders acknowledge the value
of what we're offering you here today,
which is why they sent a man
of your skill to receive it.
‐ What with our situation
being what it is,
we can't afford not to grab at any carrot
that's dangled before us.
And if it turns out that
carrot has been poisoned,
I guess my superiors will be disappointed.
‐ Tell me, do you believe in the existence
of Newtypes, Captain?
‐ Spend enough time on the battlefield,
and you'll encounter a sort of power
that can't be explained away easily.
‐ Power, a word that someone
with personal experience
might have chosen.
As humanity expands into space,
all of our latent abilities will blossom
in order to adapt to that great void.
We will then be able to understand
and accept one another
without misconceptions.
That's the Newtype theory
once proposed by Zeon Deikun.
It spoke of the reformation
of all of humanity,
of infinite possibilities,
of power itself.
‐ [groans] Dammit!
[gun firing]
[yelling]
[tense music]
Garencieres, enemy sighted!
Londo Bell is about to
surround the colony!
‐ [Cardeas] Since its
victory in the One Year War,
the Federation has lived in
fear of this unseen power.
The power that screams [speaks in French]
at the privileged class
that lives on Eearth,
the power that calls all the
abandoned Spacenoids to awaken.
‐ What?
[loud blasting]
[dramatic tense music]
[yelling]
[gun firing]
‐ [Cardeas] A power that could overthrow
the control of the Federation government,
whose rule has lasted nearly 100 years.
‐ Damn you to hell!
Space belongs to the Spacenoids!
[tense music]
[groaning angrily]
[groaning]
‐ [Cardeas] The Federation has
been absorbed for decades now
in a battle against this invisible power.
‐ Damn you all,
all of you dogs whose souls
are still bound to the Earth!
[dramatic tense music]
Long live Neo Zeon!
[loud blasting]
[pounding blast]
‐ Marida, what in the hell was that?
‐ Gilboa, have you heard from the captain?
‐ [Gilboa] We lost the connection.
The Minovsky Particles are getting denser.
‐ Should we engage inside the colony?
‐ [Gilboa] The enemy has
surrounded the colony.
Our only option is to
cut straight through,
find the captain, and
get the hell outta here.
‐ [Marida] Roger that.
‐ While it's true that
government research facilities
were created, they were like
laboratories of mad scientists
who deviated from the original ideologies,
and rather, chose to focus
on the military applications
of the Newtypes.
Then came the civil conflict
known as the Gryps War,
and after that, both Neo Zeon wars.
The ensuing oppression led to
the rise of military factions,
and the Federation
suffered greatly for this.
However, they did have a strong ally
that ultimately secured their victory.
Do you know what it is I'm referring to?
‐ [Captain] Would that be time?
‐ [Cardeas] Indeed.
The public grew impatient
and sought results from these Newtypes,
which, at this point, still
had no specific definition,
only potential.
The term Newtype eventually
came to be synonymous
with ace pilot, a new
definition completely removed
from Zeon Deikun's concept
of understanding without misconceptions.
‐ Hey, Tom, what do you think that is?
‐ Back there, what's that?
[soft tense music]
‐ Laplace's Box holds the
power to change our future,
or, more to the point, it has the power
to restore the future
that was meant to be.
However, not all men are
able to wield this power.
But be warned, if the
power were to be misused,
it could destroy the world.
‐ So you're giving us this
key as a test to start.
‐ If, for instance,
you're small‐minded enough
that you focus only on a single thing,
the box will never reveal
its contents to you.
‐ That one thing being?
‐ The revival of Zeon.
[loud blasting]
[soft tense music]
[lasers firing]
[loud blasting]
[booming crash]
‐ [Woman] Oh, no!
[people screaming]
‐ It's Londo Bell, combat
has already broken out
inside the colony, sir.
‐ Has the military informed us?
‐ Are you saying we've
been caught in a trap?
That's what it sounds like.
‐ Not at all.
In fact, I'd say you were followed here,
but neither of us could prove that.
‐ We'll be taking her back now.
‐ It was always my intention to return her
when the time was right.
She's safe in my mansion.
[distant blasting]
‐ It's difficult for one
man to trust another now.
It's an unfortunate state of things.
‐ I feel the same way, Captain.
[distant blasting]
[crumbling loudly]
[laser firing]
‐ Get everyone out of here!
[beeping]
[laser firing]
[electrical crackling]
‐ Get off my back!
[gun firing]
So heavy!
[soft pensive music]
I'll shut you down!
[lasers warbling]
[muffled blasting]
[groaning]
[dramatic pensive music]
[yelling]
[distant rumbling]
‐ There are holes in the colony.
‐ Guys, isn't that around
where the school is?
‐ This is war.
This is the beginning of a war.
‐ A war.
[distant crashing]
[car horns honking]
[cars crashing]
Audrey.
‐ [Micott] Where are you going?
‐ [Takuya] Hey!
[dramatic pensive music]
‐ [Boy] Come on!
‐ Sir.
‐ It's a shame.
The Federation will
break a 100‐year alliance
to take everything away from us.
Then again, we were the ones who sought
to jeopardize it first.
Gael, do not let the Federation have it!
[tense music]
[mechanical whirring]
[fingers snapping]
[lasers firing]
‐ [Boy] Hey, open the doors!
What's goin' on?
[grunts angrily]
‐ Hey, open the doors!
[laser firing]
[Micott screaming]
Hey, Banagher.
[laser warbling]
Hey, Micott, you're not hurt, are you?
What about the other [shrieks].
[loud blasting]
[missiles firing]
‐ Ester, Marco, Denis, Tom!
‐ Micott!
‐ [Micott] Where are they? [sobbing]
‐ Takuya, take care of Micott.
‐ Where are you going?
‐ There's someone I have to rescue.
Did you recognize that mobile suit
that just tore through here?
‐ It looked like a Zeta‐type
Transformable Suit.
I think it's from the Federation.
‐ Then its mothership
should be at the Snail.
You have to get there, it can protect you!
‐ Don't go, you can't leave me here!
Please don't leave me!
Banagher!
[tense music]
[gun fires]
[man groans]
[gun firing]
[guns firing]
‐ They appear to be special forces,
which means the command
module is probably‐‐
‐ In that case, we'll have to
erase the program ourselves,
and then the Unicorn.
[gun firing]
‐ You have to go ahead, sir!
[dramatic pensive music]
[gun firing]
[electrical crackling]
‐ But why?
Why this?
[elevator dings]
Alberto, you did this?
[Banagher grunts]
‐ [Captain] Don't shoot the kid.
[gun firing]
Have you been able to
get in touch with Marida?
‐ Did Martha put you up to this?
You're assuming you've used the military,
but the ones really being used...
[groaning]
[bone cracking]
[gun firing]
[grunting]
[guns firing]
[gasps]
Alberto!
‐ [Marida] Princess.
[gasps]
[tense music]
‐ Marida!
[gun firing]
‐ [Haro] Hello, Audrey.
‐ Haro!
‐ [Audrey] Banagher?
‐ A civilian?
Hey, turn back!
‐ Hey, it's you.
‐ You know her?
‐ No.
[tense music]
[loud blasting]
[lasers firing]
‐ Unreal!
We're saved, it's a
Federation mobile suit!
It's an RGZ‐95, a ReZEL, Micott.
Hey, we're students at
the Industrial College!
They blew holes in the
colony, so we escaped.
Can you help us?
[sizzling and crackling]
[loud blasting]
‐ Audrey.
What's this?
‐ Gael, you made it.
It's you.
‐ Where is she?
Where's Audrey?
‐ Don't worry about her.
This isn't her first time cheating death,
and it won't be her last.
‐ You didn't leave her behind?
You were planning on escaping
in this mobile suit, weren't you?
‐ Even if I did, I wouldn't survive.
‐ What the hell is wrong with you?
You act like you're so superior,
but you can't do anything!
Audrey came to you trying to stop this war
from breaking out,
and you had the power
to do that, didn't you?
Those people, they had plans
for tomorrow, for next week.
They had a future!
They weren't supposed to die like this!
I lost my mother, but it was different.
This isn't the way people are
supposed to die, it's wrong.
‐ Death should be treated with dignity.
We're supposed to respect
one another's lives,
but once we grow out of
childhood and we know better,
we still cause meaningless bloodshed.
We've done it to the Earth as well.
We devoured her resources,
and then sought out
new frontiers to exploit in space.
Humanity grew out of
control and must endeavor
to regain its dignity.
We must revive the hope
that was born 100 years ago.
‐ Through the potential that lies within.
We will demonstrate the true power
and compassion of humanity.
‐ To transcend what is immediate,
and realize our God‐like potential.
the greatness within us that is possible.
You've come this far,
but are you confident
that your conviction will not waver?
The weight of the burden
she has to bear is immense.
You'll need the resolve
to carry the weight
of the world on your
shoulders if you go with her.
Do you have it?
‐ I don't have that resolve, no.
All I know is I need her to need me!
‐ Very well, then you will need this.
[soft melancholic music]
[computer warbles softly]
I've programmed it to respond
to you, and you alone.
If you can prove yourself
to be a suitable pilot,
the Unicorn will grant
you powers unrivaled,
and then show you the
path to Laplace's Box.
‐ What's Laplace's Box?
‐ It's a dark curse that has
sentenced the Vist family
to serve as its guardian for 100 years,
but if used properly, it can bring light
to this Universal Century.
‐ What is it?
‐ Anna, your mother didn't want to see you
fall victim to this curse,
so she took you from me.
She must hate me, as
I'm sure you do as well,
but you must go.
Fear not, if you trust in the possibility
that lies within and
try with all your might,
the path will show itself to you.
‐ It's selfish, you can't
say all that to me now.
‐ Please forgive me.
I wanted more,
so much.
[melancholic music]
Banagher,
my wish
has finally come true,
Anna.
‐ Father!
[melancholic music]
Father.
Did I,
was he?
My...
[warm pensive music]
To my only desire,
the beast of possibility,
the symbol of hope.
Father.
Mother, I'm sorry.
I must.
[system whirring softly]
[pensive orchestral music]
I must go!
[dramatic orchestral music]
Audrey.
‐ Banagher!
‐ Princess!
[warm pensive music]
Funnels!
[electrical zapping]
‐ Go!
Get the hell out of my way!
[dramatic orchestral music]
‐ He's open.
[missiles whistling]
[dramatic orchestral music]
[yelling]
‐ Gundam.
[warm music with woman
singing in Japanese]