[dramatic music]
[yelling]
[whirring]
‐ Gundam.
[beeping]
[whirring]
‐ That thing is built with psycho‐frame
throughout the whole body?
‐ [Man] We have confirmation.
The unidentified single horn shoot
transformed or morphed.
It's a Gundam!
‐ Gundam?
‐ Micott, look at that,
it's really a Gundam.
‐ What's Gundam?
‐ It's the name of the first mobile suit
developed by the Federation.
Zeon even used to call it the White Devil.
‐ [Man] Attention bridge, the
machine currently engaging
the Sleeve's quad wing
appears to be a Gundam type!
‐ A Gundam, no way!
[whirring]
‐ Gundam.
Gundam.
Gundam is the enemy!
[whirring]
[yelling]
[dramatic music]
[whirring]
‐ [Man] Attention, unidentified machine.
If you can hear this
message, identify yourself,
your affiliation, and
your combat objective.
I repeat, unidentified machine‐‐
‐ Your performance is a
disgrace, Suberoa Zinnerman.
You failed to retrieve Laplace's Box
and weren't even able
to rescue the princess.
‐ None of these developments
could have been predicted.
For the time being, we have no choice
but to be patient and wait
to hear from the princess.
‐ Are you suggesting that we do nothing?
‐ Lieutenant Angelo.
I hear the enemy that Marida
was bested by in battle
was a Gundam, no less.
Intriguing.
I might need to come out there myself.
Have the Garencieres find out
the Federation's next move.
‐ Sir.
I will rectify this disgrace,
even if it costs me my life.
‐ You mustn't let mistakes weigh you down.
Acknowledge them and take what
you've learned to move on.
That is the privilege of being a man.
[dramatic piano music]
[whizzing]
[groaning]
‐ Mom?
‐ [Daguza] Riddhe.
You got lucky.
Don't overthink it.
Surviving doesn't mean you're a coward
any more than dying means you're brave.
The only thing that separates
life from death is luck.
‐ Sir.
I understand.
‐ [Norm] Attention, approaching vessel,
you are hereby ordered
to halt immediately.
This is the Nahel Argama of
the Federation Space Forces,
Londo Bell.
Your vessel has crossed our
ships' defensive perimeter.
‐ Those damned terrorists!
‐ [Man] Wait.
‐ [Norm] It's debris?
‐ It appears to be a derelict
vessel, Salamis class.
Our thermal sensors misidentified
its backup power supply.
‐ Stand down the alert,
return to your stations
and recall the mobile suits immediately.
‐ Are you sure?
‐ Is there a problem with that?
‐ [Daguza] It was misidentified debris?
‐ [Norm] That's right.
We're lucky it wasn't an enemy out there.
‐ But the enemy is always out there.
They must assume by now that
we've recovered Laplace's Box
and as long as that quad‐wing
mobile suit is operational,
I wouldn't expect them
to give up any time soon.
‐ So, now is not the time to sit back
and wait for reinforcements.
‐ Precisely.
Have you unlocked it yet?
‐ No, sir.
Frankly, I didn't expect the system
to be quite this resistant.
‐ So you had no knowledge
of what was going on
outside your own department?
‐ Correct.
And once development of the UC Project
was placed under the jurisdiction
of the Vist Foundation,
we were kept even more in
the dark about things‐‐
‐ Hey, what does that have to do
with the situation at hand?
‐ [Man] The com is closed.
[grumbling]
‐ What is the UC Project?
Look, ECOAS isn't officially
investigating this.
If we were, our guests from Anaheim
would keep us from getting
to the truth anyway.
‐ The UC Project.
It's a top secret program
conducted as part of the
EFSF Reorganization Plan.
This Unicorn is the flagship.
The entire body incorporates
psycho‐frame technology
which supplements the psycommu,
transmitting the pilot's psycho‐waves
directly to the drive system.
‐ Meaning the pilot can control
this entirely by thought?
But it's too much strain on
the pilot's body, am I right?
‐ Uh, right.
But, supposedly, the NT‐D has a time limit
of only five minutes once activated.
‐ This NT‐D you mentioned‐‐
‐ Commander Daguza!
I was very clear that I must be present
should you decide to interrogate my staff!
‐ Daguza to bridge.
Rather than wait for reinforcements,
I suggest we leave the sector immediately.
I have new information
suggesting that the recovered
Gundam is connected in
some way to Laplace's Box.
I recommend you set a course
for Luna II as soon as you're able.
‐ That may be, but‐‐
‐ I agree, Captain Otto!
However, why would we go to Luna II?
We should go to our Anaheim
Electronics headquarters,
at Von Braun on the moon.
‐ [Man] Attention, the ship
is entering second deployment.
‐ Please, wait here for now.
Let me know if you need anything.
‐ [Audrey] Have you
received any word about
who was piloting that Gundam?
‐ No, from what I've been told,
the hatch hasn't even been opened yet.
‐ Hey there!
Are you doing all right?
Oh, I'm the ReZEL pilot
that pulled you guys out.
My name's Riddhe Marcenas.
‐ And my name is Audrey Burne.
‐ You want to go take a look?
At the Gundam?
You are curious, aren't you?
‐ Ensign Riddhe‐‐
‐ It'll be fine, Ensign Mihiro.
I know a secret spot
where we can steal a peak.
‐ That's not what I meant!
‐ I wanna go!
This Nahel Argama was the mothership
of the Gundam team in
the first Neo Zeon War
and now it's carrying this new Gundam!
It's just too cool.
It's like destiny or something.
‐ Uh, yeah.
‐ Hey, you coming Micott?
‐ [Micott] Whatever.
‐ And I'm coming, too.
If that Gundam hadn't
shown up when it did,
you and I wouldn't be
having this discussion now.
I, for one, want to meet the
pilot who saved our lives.
‐ [Alberto] Unlike Luna II,
which is on the far side of the Earth,
the moon is
right next to it‐‐
‐ That's exactly why our enemy
will expect us to head there.
I think a detour course for
Luna II is a wiser choice.
‐ [Alberto] If you're worried
about our limited resources,
I'm sure we can make it to the moon.
Clearly, commander, you've
just become anxious.
‐ [Daguza] Send us out into
the open with no reinforcements
and I'll become even more anxious.
We're here now because
of corporate interference
with a military command structure.
‐ [Alberto] The duty of
a soldier, commander,
is to carry out orders!
‐ I've heard enough of this.
‐ Don't blame me for your‐‐
‐ Turn it off!
I know that ECOAS can do as
they please during an operation,
but I wish they'd get off our backs
while we're giving them a free ride.
To say nothing of that
primadonna from Anaheim!
‐ Complaining to us about it
won't affect the situation.
[beeping]
‐ The derelict ship we
encountered has decelerated.
Now traveling at relative speed zero.
‐ Haunted by ghosts of the One Year War?
Have the mobile suits eliminated.
They can move something
that size, no problem.
‐ But they've already returned.
‐ They what?
‐ Well, those were your orders, Captain.
Would you like to give the
order to send them back out?
‐ Just blast them with the main guns!
[whirring]
‐ Bingo, that's them.
We've confirmed the enemy's position.
‐ Transmit the coordinates
to the Rewloola.
Then we'll see what they can do.
‐ [Man] Attention all hands!
The ship is‐‐
‐ So that's Gundam?
‐ That's what they're saying.
It looks so different.
‐ I feel like I've seen
you somewhere before.
Hey.
You look like Natsume Swanson,
you know, the famous actress!
‐ I don't know much about
the entertainment industry.
‐ Oh, right.
‐ Ensign!
[muffled chattering]
‐ The hatch is opening!
[gasping]
‐ [Boy] Banagher?
Why is he‐‐
‐ How could he be the pilot?
[beeping]
‐ [Computer] Banagher.
Banagher.
‐ Doctor!
‐ Banagher.
‐ Hey, are you okay?
‐ Audrey.
‐ Banagher, can you hear me?
If you can hear me, squeeze my hand.
‐ Mihiro to the bridge.
The boy is just regaining consciousness.
Commander Daguza?
‐ I'd like to talk to the boy.
The rest of you can leave.
‐ Of course, sir, but‐‐
‐ Can you at least wait
until I've examined the boy?
He's just regained consciousness
and doesn't even know where he is.
‐ You understand that
he's hurt, don't you?
‐ I understand this minor is a civilian
who hijacked a military mobile suit,
then interfered in a combat situation,
a violation of the law severe enough
to warrant capital punishment.
[gasping]
‐ Are you serious?
‐ But, sir, he saved all of our lives,
doesn't that count for something?
‐ Not in a stolen combat machine.
‐ We're all set to launch, Captain.
All you need do is sit back and observe.
Leave the rest to us.
‐ All of this has to be
related to Laplace's Box,
am I right, Lieutenant?
A secret important enough to warrant
the deployment of ECOAS to retrieve it.
‐ There's a limit to
how much the Federation
can mobilize in secrecy.
Even as we speak, I'm sure
they're in discussions
about how to handle the situation.
All those responsible parties
trying to avoid responsibility.
‐ I hope you're right.
‐ They're here without
backup, aren't they?
I'm positive.
The captain will be going out today.
There won't be anything for us to do.
‐ And you stand by this story?
You expect us to believe that Cardeas Vist
just gave it to a boy?
So, did he say anything
when he gave you this gift?
‐ Like I said, he told me
to take the mobile suit
and use it to protect everyone.
That's all he said.
Would it be easier to
believe if he were my father?
‐ Huh?
[rumbling]
‐ All units, scramble!
Turn about, full speed!
‐ Damage report and scan the area!
‐ There's no one out there.
‐ Look harder.
[whirring]
‐ We've fallen into a trap.
‐ [Alberto] This is your fault, Captain,
you and your indecision!
If we had‐‐
‐ I've got intense heat signatures
approaching at high speed.
I count four total.
They're approaching
from directly above us.
‐ Are they missiles?
‐ No, sir, not judging
by their flight paths.
I'd say they were mobile suits.
But the way they're
navigating the debris field,
it's impossible.
[dramatic music]
The lead machine is approaching it,
three times the speed of the others.
‐ This should be interesting.
Let's test the performance
of your brand new Gundam!
‐ Are these the same guys
that attacked the colony?
‐ I can't take this anymore.
‐ Micott!
We've gotta look for normal suits.
This ship could get a hole
blasted through it any second!
‐ Everyone, you have to put these on.
What happened to the other girl?
‐ [Man] Remaining enemy mobile
suits are still in flight.
‐ You, where do you think you're going?
Put on a normal suit and get to shelter.
Huh?
[guns firing]
‐ Anti‐air, what are you doing?
‐ We can't acquire a lock.
‐ Forget the system, just shoot!
[booming]
‐ [Man] Pilots to the
mobile set deck immediately.
‐ Hey!
You dropped this!
‐ Oh, thank you.
I'm glad you found it.
This might save my life.
It's my good luck charm.
Now, you go get some rest.
There isn't anything for you to do.
We'll take care of protecting
our ship this time around.
A kid like that piloting a Gundam?
‐ Banagher!
‐ Audrey.
‐ Banagher.
Listen to me.
That machine's systems are registered
to your biometric data,
which means it can't be
operated by anyone but you.
‐ That's what I was told, but
how do you know all of this?
‐ I want you to come with me.
[booming]
[beeping]
[overlapping radio chattering]
‐ Damn amateurs!
‐ [Daguza] Don't worry, as long as
they believe we have the box,
they will try to neutralize our ship
without destroying our engines.
‐ I find it hard to believe
a single mobile suit
could neutralize the ship.
Ah, that says‐‐
‐ So, it turns out that the
ship is carrying something
that's almost as important
to them as the box.
‐ We can escape if we go now.
We could head back to Industrial 7.
You sneak onto a cargo vessel and find
some place to hide in one of the sides.
While you do that, I'll figure out
some way to dispose of that machine.
‐ Audrey.
‐ If we don't do it, that
thing is just too dangerous.
I can't let anyone get their hands on it.
‐ Now, just wait a sec!
‐ No, I will explain it to you later.
‐ If you won't tell me anything,
then how can you expect
me to agree with you?
Stop trying to convince
me by talking like this,
it isn't fair.
Audrey, what do you want to do?
Don't tell me what it
is that you should do,
your responsibility.
Tell me what it is that you want to do.
If you do, I'll‐‐
[whirring]
Wait, what are you?
‐ You know why I'm here.
‐ Audrey!
‐ [Woman] Trajectory set.
Catapult hatches one through four open.
Mobile shoot core, get
into launch position.
‐ [Homare] What's this?
Is the rich kid getting cold feet?
‐ I don't know what you're talking about.
But I'm pretty sure I
heard your voice crack,
Lieutenant Homare.
‐ [Homare] Just wait 'til we get back.
‐ Norm Basilicock.
Romeo 001, launch!
‐ [Pilot] Galom Gorga, Juliet 002, launch!
‐ Riddhe Marcenas.
Romeo 008, taking off.
[booming]
[gasping]
‐ [Homare] Severe damage,
port side catapult deck.
‐ Lieutenant Homare!
‐ Hurry up with that damage report!
‐ Get out of here and head to the moon!
‐ Mr. Alberto, it's
dangerous for you to be here.
‐ That's the Sinanju!
It's the Red Comet!
You can't defeat it!
[grunting]
Two years ago, our
experimental mobile suit
MSN‐06S was stolen by Neo Zeon
while it was being transferred
from the lunar city Granada
to a testing ground at Von Braun.
The Federation Forces that
were sent to get it back
were completely wiped out.
And they say the one
responsible is Full Frontal,
the man they call the second
coming of Char Aznable,
the Red Comet.
‐ I've heard of this story before.
The Ghost of Char, who destroyed
two Clop‐class ships with
a single mobile suit.
‐ But Char went missing during
the Second Neo Zeon War,
never to be heard from again!
‐ Be that as it may,
your men don't stand a chance out there.
Their mobile suits are useless.
The Unicorn was made based on
data collected from the Sinanju.
We've gotta get out of here, now!
‐ If we run now, then we'll
be attacked from behind.
Transfer the data to
each section of the ship.
Our enemy is not a ghost.
Send in the mobile suit corps, too!
‐ Idiot, you have no clue!
‐ That's the last time
you'll speak to me like that.
[guns firing]
[dramatic music]
‐ There it is!
[whirring]
‐ [Commander] Stay back, Ensign Riddhe.
Stay in formation.
Galom, below you!
[booming]
‐ That cannot be the real Char.
‐ Lieutenant Angelo, we
have multiple hostiles.
Shouldn't we cover the captain?
‐ Not at all.
We need only stand by
and watch, Ensign Sergi.
We'd only get in the Captain's way.
‐ At this rate, everyone will.
‐ Attention all attacking mobile suits.
You are ordered to cease fire immediately.
We are holding Mineva Zabi
captive aboard this ship.
I repeat, we are holding the
Zabi heir, Mineva Lao Zabi,
captive aboard this ship.
If you do not halt your
attacks immediately,
we cannot guarantee her safety.
‐ Hold on.
She's the Princess of Zeon?
‐ [Daguza] We are prepared
to begin negotiations.
I'm sure you'll make the right decision.
‐ I have received the image.
I'm Captain Full Frontal of Neo Zeon.
Tell me, what are your demands?
‐ That's Char's voice.
‐ This is Commander Daguza Mackle
of the Earth Federation Space Force
Special Operations Group, ECOAS.
We are requesting that
you cease your attacks
and withdraw immediately.
If you do, we can guarantee
the safety of Mineva Zabi.
‐ [Full Frontal] Can't
we just have her back?
‐ Let's take one thing at a time.
If you allow us to pass,
then we can discuss that
once our ship has arrived
in a safe location.
‐ [Full Frontal] So you're
holding her as your hostage?
However, we have no evidence
that this person is the
real Princess Mineva.
‐ That seems rather cautious for the man
that people are calling the
second coming of the Red Comet.
‐ [Full Frontal] To you,
we're nothing but terrorists.
And since we are not a
part of your military,
we cannot expect to be
protected by international law,
so you can understand our caution.
‐ [Daguza] We have the highest
regard for human rights.
‐ [Full Frontal] Oh,
that's quite a statement
coming from people who send special forces
into civilian colonies
and are now using hostages as shields.
Now it's our turn to make some demands.
I request you hand over
the materials you collected
from Industrial 7 and all data
pertaining to Laplace's Box.
‐ And in exchange?
‐ [Full Frontal] I'll
guarantee your safe passage,
unless, of course, you
object to the terms.
‐ I have no objection, however,
we are unable to comply
because we never obtained
Laplace's Box.
‐ [Full Frontal] But you did retrieve
a Gundam type mobile suit, did you not?
‐ [Daguza] That's the
property of the Federation.
It has nothing to do with Laplace's box.
‐ [Full Frontal] If you
won't accept our demands,
we'll be forced to destroy your vessel.
‐ [Daguza] You would do that
with the prisoner on board?
‐ [Full Frontal] As her
identity is unverified,
she is irrelevant.
I'll give you three minutes.
I trust you'll come to
a sensible decision.
[dramatic music]
‐ He's bluffing.
He wouldn't forsake the
guiding star of Zeon.
‐ I wouldn't be so sure.
‐ Hm?
‐ If Full Frontal is in fact Char Aznable,
he would be the son of Zeon Deikun,
which means he holds the
Zabi family responsible
for his father's death.
Why should he care about me?
‐ Interesting you should say that.
You've removed any doubt in my mind
that you are the princess.
And I'd bet that a good number
of those sleeves soldiers
out there still believe
in the Zabi family.
‐ If you believe that, then by all means,
continue this useless negotiation.
However, the soldiers of Zeon don't play
as nicely as you do.
If you were a Zeon, all
you'd be thinking about
is how to destroy anything
related to Laplace's Box.
‐ She's right!
We should destroy the
Unicorn's electronic system
while we have the chance!
That thing is the key, not the actual box,
so if we destroy it, then the safety
of the box will still be‐‐
[grunting]
‐ Let's put the resolve
of a Federation soldier
to the test, Commander Daguza Mackle.
If you have the strength,
then destroy the key and take my life.
Losing both the key and myself
will undoubtedly deal a
severe blow to Neo Zeon.
Otherwise, continue to wait for them
to storm in and take it from you.
There's not time for indecision.
‐ Audrey!
Stop talking like that.
You're only making it harder
for everyone and yourself.
‐ Banagher.
‐ Let's just go.
This isn't something you
should be involved in.
‐ My name is Mineva Zabi.
‐ No, you're Audrey.
I don't care what your name is,
to me you're still Audrey Burne!
‐ Enough.
Children shouldn't concern
themselves with adult matters.
‐ If I'm such a child,
then what about her?
‐ This girl is the princess of Neo Zeon.
‐ Well, if we're just children,
then why is she your hostage?
Is this how adults are supposed to behave?
Does being older make this right?
‐ [Full Frontal] Time's up.
What is your decision?
Understood.
Then we shall destroy your vessel.
‐ Here it comes!
Ready our defenses.
Mobile suit corps, be
prepared to intercept them.
‐ It's just a box.
Why can't you just hand the
damn thing over to them?
We don't even know what the box is.
Why do so many people have to die for it?
‐ So that no one else has to die for it.
While we don't know the secrets
hidden in Laplace's Box,
some say it could
overthrow the Federation.
What if we were to turn over the box
only to cause even more
people to lose their lives?
Could you take responsibility for that?
How would you explain
to all those families
that their loved ones had to
die because you didn't know?
Do it.
‐ Cease fire immediately,
otherwise we'll be forced
to execute Mineva Zabi.
This is your last warning.
Cease fire on us immediately.
‐ If we just take down
that red mobile suit,
then you won't need Audrey
as a hostage anymore, right?
I'll do it.
[dramatic music]
[guns firing]
[booming]
‐ Stand down, stand down!
‐ Riddhe!
‐ This is all your fault!
How could you?
Did you really think taking a hostage
would work against a bunch of terrorists?
[light music]
‐ Ensign Riddhe, control yourself!
[electrical whirring]
[yelling]
‐ Commander!
[booming]
Commander Norm.
Bastard!
What was?
The Gundam.
‐ [Woman] The Gundam is on catapult one!
‐ [Daguza] What the hell?
Don't let it launch!
‐ [Woman] Gundam pilot, identify yourself.
You are not cleared for launch.
Return to the hanger bay immediately!
‐ You did this!
‐ This is a compromise that
could work for everyone.
The Unicorn's performance is unmatched.
Even a pilot with no training
can buy us enough time to get to safety.
‐ You're practically
giving the box to them!
‐ But it's only the key!
If the key is broken now,
the box will never open.
And the Federation's
interests will be protected.
That boy is never gonna give up.
I guarantee he'll keep fighting
until the Unicorn is destroyed.
You can hear me, can't you, Banagher?
You already know how to
initiate the system, don't you?
‐ [Audrey] Banagher, don't do this.
‐ [Alberto] That pilot suit you're wearing
has a medical subsystem
designed to reduce strain
on the body from G resistance.
But don't worry about it.
Once the NT‐D is activated,
it'll kick in automatically.
‐ NT‐D?
‐ [Alberto] That's the mode in which
the Unicorn's performance
limiters are disengaged.
You handled it the last
time, you should be fine.
‐ Launch preparations complete.
Detaching from ship.
[upbeat music]
[booming]
There he is!
‐ It barely grazed him, but.
Captain!
I can't believe I fired.
It's the Captain's battlefield.
I've desecrated it!
I will make you pay!
‐ Stay calm.
[light music]
[booming]
‐ It doesn't matter how powerful you are
if you can't hit me.
[yelling]
‐ You dodged him for me.
[whirring]
‐ He has an I‐field?
[booming]
‐ Did I do it?
[groaning]
Audrey.
[dramatic music]
[booming]
[whirring]
[yelling]
[gun firing]
I got it.
This is it, Gundam.
[electricity crackling]
‐ So we battle again, Gundam.
‐ Pull back!
If you don't, they'll kill Audrey.
[grunting]
‐ We can flank him, climb!
[guns firing]
Stop!
Don't get in too close!
[whirring]
[dramatic music]
Behind you!
‐ [Banagher] The Quad‐wing?
[guns firing]
[grunting]
Audrey.
‐ Why is that boy inside the Gundam?
‐ My thanks, Lieutenant Cruz.
[grunting]
‐ [Banagher] Forgive me, Audrey.
[whirring]
‐ When I was a child, I saw
a Zabi family speech on TV.
Sieg Zeon, sieg Zeon.
I knew to be afraid even then.
A raving mob, thousands of
them, shouting in unison,
all because of your uncle, Gihren Zabi.
Neo Zeon still chant like
that, don't you, princess?
So say it for me now!
Say it!
Tell me something,
anything, to convince me
that you're the princess of Zeon,
because if you don't, why
would someone like Mineva Zabi
risk her life by slipping aboard
a Federation ship all by herself?
I guess we'll have to leave
getting the truth out of you
to the professionals.
There's just one last
thing I want you to know.
He was calling your
name until the very end.
Not Mineva Zabi.
He kept calling Audrey.
‐ You don't understand anything, do you?
And who exactly are these
professionals of which you speak?
‐ [Riddhe] We have investigators.
‐ Do you actually believe
they will conduct an official hearing?
They won't let the public
know I was ever here
no matter what happens to me.
You heard how stubborn Full Frontal was
in refusing to accept
that I am Mineva Zabi.
Why do you suppose he would do that?
‐ He was trying to, I mean,
he did it to undermine
our negotiation tactics.
‐ Take a step back and you'll see it.
How do you think I've managed
to evade being captured
for almost 10 years?
And how do you think Neo Zeon
has been able to establish military bases
within the Earth Sphere?
‐ Are you saying there've
been backroom dealings?
‐ The incident at Industrial 7
will disappear from your news reports.
It won't be easy for
the families and friends
of those who died to forgive it.
However, Spacenoids have grown accustomed
to dealing with injustice.
In turn, the Federation has
been using us a scapegoat
to channel their anger and frustration
about these outrages.
Until now.
‐ And Laplace's Box is what's
upsetting this balance?
‐ The Federation may
have begun taking steps
to resolve its relationship
with Neo Zeon once and for all.
That's why the Vist Foundation
is willing to sacrifice
the source of its prosperity.
‐ It sounds complicated.
I've always just thought
of myself as a pilot.
My job is simple.
Operate my mobile suit
and carry out any orders
I'm assigned.
That's all I have to worry about.
Even if there's been
corruption from time to time,
I've lived my life
believing the Federation
would do the right thing in the end.
But that's a lie.
Even when I was living under
the shelter of my family.
Even then, I tried not
to see what was true.
But you, what made you do
what you did, and alone?
‐ You know, I had to
deal with family issues
just like everyone else.
And my family shouldered the
blame for the One Year War.
I cannot separate myself
from all their politics
and if the same mistakes
are about to be repeated,
I must prevent them.
Even if doing so costs me my life,
I choose to take responsibility.
‐ [Man] Hey, Riddhe, there's
activity around the ship.
‐ The supply corps just came in.
They're probably restocking.
‐ [Man] And I killed the
cameras for you, too.
‐ I know.
You are still a member of Zeon.
Even if there have been backroom dealings,
you're an enemy here.
Your people killed Commander
Norm and the others.
And that is something I
won't be able to forgive.
‐ Of course not.
You said your name is
Riddhe Marcenas, didn't you?
‐ Yeah.
‐ So the family you mentioned was?
‐ I really wish we didn't
have to meet like this.
There's a lot I'd like to change.
[birds chirping]
[doors creaking]
[gentle music]
‐ They tell me there was
a room just like this
in the last fortress of the
former Principality, A Baoa Qu.
The governor general
of Palau is apparently
an ardent sympathizer of the
former Principality of Zeon.
I have to accept favors like
this location graciously,
even though the decor isn't my style.
I suppose it's a necessary
trade of a leader.
Good job, Captain Zinnerman,
and you, Lieutenant Marida.
I'll take it from here.
‐ Captain.
‐ I know.
Princess Mineva being held
hostage by the Federation
was unexpected.
We will have many
opportunities to rescue her
using both force and diplomacy.
Just be patient.
‐ Sir.
‐ Char Aznable.
‐ Come now.
Have a seat.
How are you feeling?
I've been told it was no small feat
to get you out of that Gundam safely.
‐ So, um‐‐
‐ Yes?
‐ Was that you, were you
the guy I fought with
in that red mobile suit?
‐ Do you have a problem
sitting down to tea
with a mortal enemy, Banagher Links?
You have good reflexes,
even if you're a bit reckless.
However, that's a temperament
not unbefitting a pilot.
‐ This might sound rude,
but may I ask why do you wear that mask?
Are you hiding a scar or something?
I'd like to see your face, that is,
if you have nothing to hide.
‐ You dare!
‐ It's fine, Lieutenant Angelo.
Banagher is right, it's
a matter of etiquette.
I choose to wear this
because it's my style,
but it serves as a tool of propaganda.
Most of the time I
forget I even have it on,
until someone like you makes
a point of mentioning it.
My apologies.
I've heard about how
you met Princess Mineva.
But as for how you came into
possession of that mobile suit
from the Vist Foundation,
the Unicorn Gundam,
there is much I have yet to understand.
The truth is, the decision to
turn over that machine to us
had already been arranged.
So what would make Cardeas
Vist suddenly choose you
to be the bearer of Laplace's Box?
‐ I was asked the same thing
by the two who escorted me here.
And I already told them everything I know.
‐ The prosperity of the Vist Foundation
was due to its pact with
the Federation government,
an arrangement held in place by their
secret possession of the box.
But they chose to end all
that and give it to us.
It must have taken something
significant to alter the plan,
but even if something had gone wrong,
why entrust the box to a stranger?
What makes the most sense is that
you have some relation to the Vist family.
Well?
‐ Is that a question I have to answer?
[groaning]
‐ I said that's enough, Lieutenant.
‐ You better learn respect, punk.
‐ Of course you're not
obligated to respond.
We simply want information
regarding Laplace's Box.
May I add that we're
asking you respectfully
because of your association
with Princess Mineva.
Please keep that in mind.
‐ Princess Mineva?
Audrey was very clear.
She said Neo Zeon must not get the box.
She said if they did, it would mean war.
‐ [Full Frontal] Oh?
‐ And after what happened
to our colony, Industrial 7,
anyone would feel the same way.
She's a Princess of Zeon, isn't she?
If Audrey's against it, why
are you trying to get the box?
Why won't you listen to her?
‐ Tell me, do you even believe in it?
In the existence of Laplace's Box?
Do you believe in the existence of a box
that no one has ever seen and
whose contents are unknown,
but nevertheless has the power
to completely destroy the
Federation government?
‐ Well, I...
I don't know.
But, I do believe that
even the smallest things
like knowledge have the
power to change the future
of the whole world in an instant.
‐ Such as?
‐ Well, like Zeon's first colony drop
or hitting the Earth with an asteroid
to start global cooling.
Or centuries ago, when
they made nuclear weapons
or discovered Minovsky particles
or developed mobile suits.
Even though it looks stable,
the world changes little by little,
right underneath our feet.
If an idea comes along at the right time,
it could have the power
to change everything.
‐ Absolutely right.
And you seem to know
your history well enough.
Are you aware that space immigration
was a policy of mass exile?
Even though the autonomy of the
Side settlers is recognized,
the central government retain the right
to appoint its leaders.
And since the Spacenoids
weren't allowed to vote,
they may as well have had
no suffrage whatsoever.
Not all of Neo Zeon adheres
to a single doctrine,
but what we do have in
common is the belief
that this unjust system must evolve.
In order to break from the
oppressive rule of the Federation
and realize the independence
of the Spacenoids, we've had‐‐
‐ But no one should resort to terrorism!
No matter how righteous you think you are,
you can't just go around killing people!
It's never right to take another life!
‐ You little hypocrite!
[groaning]
If it's never right to take another life,
then you're as guilty as
anyone for using the Gundam.
You killed one of our best men out there.
What do you have to say for that?
‐ I, what?
[groaning]
‐ It may have been a stray shot,
but that doesn't change the
fact that you shot him down.
‐ I don't think Banagher even knows
what you're talking about.
He was probably acting purely on instinct.
[groaning]
Ensign Sergei was just unlucky.
‐ No, did I kill him?
‐ Call for Zinnerman.
There is still so much
you have yet to learn
about who we really are.
I want you to understand us.
And it is my hope that given enough time,
we will one day work together.
‐ One more thing.
Who are you?
Are you Char Aznable or aren't you?
‐ As I am now, I consider myself
nothing more than a vessel.
A vessel for the hopes of
those abandoned in space
and for the ideals of Zeon that will
light all our paths to freedom.
So if that's what the people desire,
then Char Aznable is who I will be.
And that is the reason
why I wear this mask.
[doors creaking]
‐ [Man] Palau.
It's a civilian mining field asteroid
belonging to the citizens of Side 6.
Our intelligence agency has determined
that this is the location
where the RX‐0 was taken.
‐ You're telling me Nahel
Argama is supposed to
fight and break into that fortress alone?
Impossible.
‐ This operation is
under ECOAS jurisdiction
and reinforcements have already arrived.
Might I add, it is unprecedented
for two elite ECOAS teams
to join forces like this.
‐ [Man] And what is the
possibility of our success?
If we're supposed to recapture the RX‐0,
seizing control of one local
area's not going to cut it.
Have you even considered
all of the resources
we'll have to dedicate toward
preventing enemy pursuit?
‐ So do you agree to this plan, Captain?
‐ [Man] If we're going
to attack a stronghold,
shouldn't we be assembling
all of Londo Bell's forces?
‐ [Man] It seems like
headquarters is asking us
to die in battle.
‐ We're taking every
precaution by sending out
two teams of very
expensive special forces.
That's the best anyone can
manage for a covert operation.
‐ Nobody asked you for your opinion.
‐ The only reason the RX‐0 is lost now
is because of what you did!
[audience chattering]
‐ I realize this situation
is rather unexpected,
but if it hadn't happened,
that ship would have been‐‐
‐ I'll be back.
Damn it!
You call those reinforcements?
Covert?
Don't make me laugh!
It's just a bunch of washed up suits
spouting desperate excuses to make up
for their complete and utter failure!
‐ We've been made aware of
the orders from headquarters.
How do you intend on proceeding?
‐ Do you even have to ask?
The box is supposed to
determine the fate of the world,
so we have no choice but to go.
‐ I have no objection.
I agree with our orders.
However, if it's all the same to you,
we're choosing to look at
this as a hostage rescue.
We owe the boy that
much at the very least.
And I know how we can do it.
I believe this ship has been equipped
with a hyper mega particle
gun, hasn't it, Captain?
[birds chirping]
‐ [Full Frontal] The Federation's
movement has me concerned.
Depending on the situation,
we might need to abandon this location.
‐ You think the Federation
is going to attack?
‐ How's the analysis of
the Unicorn Gundam going?
‐ Hey, are you from the Federation?
‐ Let him eat in peace, Tikva.
‐ I'm only here because these
people forced me to come.
‐ [Woman] Sit still and
eat properly, young lady.
‐ You a prisoner?
‐ Something like that.
‐ Well, then, you're lucky
that you ended up our prisoner.
If you were a Federation prisoner,
they wouldn't give you
anything to eat or drink
and you'd be tortured.
‐ [Woman] Tikva, that's not
proper dinnertime discussion.
‐ The Federation doesn't
do things like that.
‐ They do.
My dad even says so.
He was a prisoner on Earth
and Captain Zinnerman helped him
when he was locked up in the camps.
‐ You know, many people's
friends were killed
because of Zeon, and whole families, too.
‐ Us, too, obviously.
That's war for you.
But Zeon did everything it could
to fight for the Spacenoids.
And you're a Spacenoid
like us, aren't you?
So how come you're on
the Federation's side?
‐ That's enough, young man or
you're gonna make me angry.
‐ Does it even matter?
Is war ever justified?
Even if what we're saying is correct,
that still doesn't change the facts.
Zeon dropped an entire colony
and killed a lot of people.
And all of those people who were killed,
they couldn't choose if
what they were dying for
was justified.
They weren't told anything about it.
Then one day, suddenly, they just...
It's not fair.
Not at all.
There was nothing else I could do.
I never intended to kill
anyone, but if I didn't,
I would have been killed.
I'm not.
I'm not a murderer.
‐ Come with me, now.
I don't disagree with what you're saying.
No war is ever truly justified.
However, to save human lives,
we can't always be righteous.
This was built back when Palau
was still in the asteroid belt.
When you look back at the
earliest space pioneers,
they were mostly beggars
and political criminals.
They sought to settle in space
because there was nowhere
else for them to live.
They say when the Universal Century began,
the Prime Minister stated
that we were bringing an end
to the era of God.
For the people who lived
in the asteroid belt,
the sun was indistinguishable
from any other distant star.
They needed a light to guide them.
‐ A light.
‐ Nothing can live without light.
But the people abandoned in space
eventually found a new
light to replace God.
And the new light that they
found to guide them was Zeon.
It gave them hope where there was despair,
so they could overcome the impossible
and keep living in this cruel world.
It held out the shining promise
that we could all become better.
You might find it
foolish to put your faith
in something so intangible.
There were those who would
say that ideas like this
are not essential to life.
I think that those people must be either
very lucky or very deluded.
‐ Humanity alone possesses a God.
Somebody once said that to me.
He told me about the power
to transcend the now,
the inner God called possibility.
‐ He must have been a romantic.
A person cannot believe that
without a strong faith in
humanity and the world.
Sounds like a nice person.
Ensign Sergei.
Don't worry about the lives
you take when you're in battle.
When you go into battle, you
become one with your machine,
a combat unit called a pilot.
There's no room for regrets.
That said,
you are already entangled in the situation
and it's best you remember that.
As for taking action to help
protect Princess Mineva,
I thank you.
‐ Hey, do you, I mean.
‐ Marida.
‐ Ms. Marida, do you
pilot a mobile suit, too?
‐ When we're sort on manpower, yes.
‐ [Soldier] Eat up.
You better finish before
we get into combat.
[grunting]
[beeping]
‐ It's you.
‐ We're getting out of here.
[beeping]
We're going to Earth.
‐ [Man] Sorry, man.
‐ Hey, wait!
‐ What's wrong?
‐ [Banagher] Nothing.
The third port, 14th space gate, 12 a. m.
If you are unable to do so,
we cannot guarantee the
safety of your life.
Your life?
This time,
the battlefield is going to come here?
♪ I feel you by my side ♪
♪ I know I'm not alone ♪
[singing in foreign language]
♪ I see a million stars ♪
♪ Gotta get together just for you ♪
♪ Won't ever say goodbye ♪
[singing in foreign language]
♪ I feel you by my side ♪
♪ I know I'm not alone ♪