[MAN A] Is something the matter,
Lord Hikomaro Takeshobo?
Show yourself, Pop Team Epic .
Try as you might to hide,
I would recognize your shitty
manga stench anywhere.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Bob Epic Team .
♪ Slackin', slackin',
slackin' off. ♪
♪ Slackin', slackin'.
Slackin'. ♪
[SLACKER GOD]
Ahh!
I am the God of Slackers.
You've got potential.
[POPUKO]
Uh-huh, I do!
Would you like to succeed me
and rule over all
the Slacker Kingdom?
[POPUKO]
Oh. Um. What?!
Screw that! Go back to your
realm, ya two-bit god!
♪ Slackin', slackin'.
Slackin', slackin' off. ♪
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[CHILDREN]
Pop Team Cooking!
Welcome to this week's
episode of Pop Team Cooking!
Today we've got a super-thrifty
recipe for wallet watchers!
Our main ingredient is premium
wagyu beef tenderloin. Yum!
[WOMAN A]
Oh, uh.
A less expensive, more ordinary
cut of beef would do, right?
No, it has to be this cut.
I got it for 50 yen.
What? Where on Earth did
you find such a great deal?
Listen, lady!
Do your own shopping.
Don't try to poach my steak!
You got it?
[NARRATOR]
Pop --
[NARRATOR coughing]
[POPUKO yells]
[PIPIMI]
Such force!
Special power!
[POPUKO]
Pop T.
[PIPIMI]
[POPUKO]
Pop T.
[PIPIMI]
[POPUKO]
Pop T.
[PIPIMI]
[POPUKO]
Pop T.
[PIPIMI]
[POPUKO]
Pop T.
[PIPIMI]
[POPUKO]
Pop T.
Everybody, say, "ho!"
--[PIPIMI] Pop T.
--[POPUKO] Pop T.
--Pop T.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[POPUKO]
Pass, pass!
[PIPIMI]
Okay!
Aura Cannon!
[POPUKO]
Nice pass! Okay, here I go!
[yells]
[POPUKO]
Aura Cannon!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Bob Epic Team .
Here's your water.
Press the button when
you're ready to order food.
[POPUKO]
What a jerk!
[screams]
Ding-dong.
Ding-dong. Ding-dong. Ding-dong.
Ding-dong. Ding-dong.
Excuse me! Mr. Waiter!
Bob !
Epic ! Team !
You ready to order yet?
Eh, guess not.
What a jerk!
[ICHIRO] So then, you had
something to tell me?
[POPUKO]
Ah, the food here is amazing!
[PIPIMI chuckles]
[PIPIMI] Can you guess what's
the most important thing
for a Ginza hostess to do
in order to succeed?
[POPUKO]
No, what is it?
[PIPIMI chuckles]
[PIPIMI]
Okay, I'll tell you.
It's to live life to the
fullest and enjoy it!
Mama Pipimi. So cool!
[BOTH laughing]
[PIPIMI]
Ahh. This is all quite relaxing.
[sirens wailing]
[PIPIMI] That was a glorious
soak, wasn't it, Popuko?
Yeah!
[DETECTIVE HIGURE]
Is this everyone at the inn?
Yes. Detective Higure.
What's this?
[DETECTIVE HIGURE groans]
Thank you for coming
out of your rooms
in the middle of
the night like this.
I'm here on behalf
of the city police.
Name's Detective Higure.
There's been a murder here
at the inn this evening.
At this point, every one
of you is considered
a person of interest
in the case.
I'd appreciate your
full cooperation.
You-You mean that the killer
might still be here among us?
Hurry up and catch
'em, then, copper!
I can't believe such
a horrible thing
could ever happen at our
quiet little inn, sir!
[TANAKA grunts]
Everyone, just remain calm.
I'd like to start by
taking a statement
from each of you, please.
Hm? Who do you think you are?
Well, looks like Mama be all
up in everybody's business!
Uh. I've solved it!
You're the killer!
That's the answer. I know it!
[TANAKA]
No! You've got it all wrong!
Popuko. Don't be rude
to the guests, now.
Whaddaya mean?
Did you stop in on your
way home from work?
[TANAKA]
Oh, yes.
Or were you on your way
home from a murder?
Hey, don't interfere with
my investigation, lady!
On the rocks? Splash of water?
Or a splash of murder?
You moron!
Okay, what have you got to
share with me, forensics? Huh?
[PIPIMI] So what was the
murder weapon, then, love?
Well, uh, some
kinda blunt object.
It only took one blow.
Get these two dummies
outta my crime scene!
I guess that's as far as
we amateurs are gonna get.
I'll still keep you
company, though.
After all, Mama Pipimi,
you're the number one
busybody in Ginza.
[sighs, chuckles]
Sure am. Thanks for the
compliment, Popuko.
Now, we should get to work.
There's so much to figure out!
Yes, ma'am!
[PIPIMI] The killer is
still at large in the inn.
We need to gather as much
evidence as possible.
[POPUKO]
The basic rule of detective work
is thorough data gathering!
I recall that my late
husband used to get up
so many damn times
in the middle of the night
because he had to go
pee, or so he claimed.
[PIPIMI gasps]
Popuko! Assemble all of
the guests and staff.
I've figured it out!
[PIPIMI whispering]
Oh. Oh, oh. Oh!
No kidding! I totally get
what you're saying now!
Mama! Everyone's assembled!
Popuko. Thanks for your help.
So, um, why did
you bring us here?
Don't tell me. You know
who the killer is? Tell me!
Uh, well, I didn't
do it. I swear!
Now, now, quiet down.
Nobody needs to get too excited.
I started working in Ginza
a very long time ago,
back when this floundering
nation was still full of life.
Everywhere I looked
in those days,
the world seemed so
fresh and dazzling,
a feast for my senses.
I accepted Ginza at face value,
and Ginza accepted me in return,
without question or expectation.
[WOMAN B]
Ready?
[WOMEN] Congratulations on your
25th anniversary, Mama Pipimi!
This is for you!
Oh, my.
A little something
from all of us.
Mama, go take a load
off for a change.
Everyone, thank you so much!
Mama, we're sending
Popuko to accompany you.
Huh? Me? For real?
You deserve it.
After all, you did make
top sales last month,
even as a rookie.
[WOMEN]
Have fun!
[POPUKO]
I did it!
[PIPIMI] This trip was a token
of love and appreciation
from all the girls who
are like my daughters.
And it's been spoiled by
a murderer. What a drag.
Seriously? So you're saying
that this is all my fault?
[OTHERS gasp]
But how--? How was I supposed
to know who you really were?
That we had such
a legendary guest?
[POPUKO] Well, that's as
good as a confession.
[HIROMI]
I couldn't forgive him!
Because of that man,
15 years ago, my father died.
I'm coming, Pop. I'll be
joining you very soon.
But Ginza is a mirror that
reflects the human soul.
Your death would solve nothing,
and it would appease no one.
Mama! I'm a terrible
woman who's taken a life!
I don't deserve to exist!
You fool! You know
what you are?
In Ginza, we call you
women Damned Fools!
[HIROMI]
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry!
After you've served your time,
come by my place
for a stiff drink.
Don't worry,
it'll be on the house.
We'll be waitin'
for you till then.
Come look us up in Ginza!
[HIROMI crying]
[SOSOGU]
It's me, Sosogu Hoshifuri!
Oh, no!
Daichi wants to
find his true self,
so he's planning to study
abroad for a while.
We're going to have to be apart!
Hoshiiro Girldrop ,
Episode Eleven:
"The Sudden Break-up."
Fall in love with us
again next week!
[MAN A] Is something the matter,
Lord Hikomaro Takeshobo?
Show yourself, Pop Team Epic .
Try as you might to hide,
I would recognize your shitty
manga stench anywhere.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Bob Epic Team .
♪ Slackin', slackin',
slackin' off. ♪
[SLACKER GOD]
Ahh!
I am the God of Slackers.
You've got potential.
[POPUKO]
Uh-huh, I do!
Would you like to succeed me
and rule over all
the Slacker Kingdom?
Oh. Um. What?!
Screw that! Go back to your
realm, you two-bit god!
♪ Slackin', slackin'.
Slackin, slackin' off. ♪
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[CHILDREN]
Pop Team Cooking!
Welcome to this week's
episode of Pop Team Cooking!
Today we've got a super-thrifty
recipe for wallet watchers!
Our main ingredient is premium
wagyu beef tenderloin. Yum!
[WOMAN A]
Oh. Uh.
A less expensive, more ordinary
cut of beef would do, right?
Nope, it has to be this cut.
I got it for 50 yen.
What? Where on Earth did
you find such a great deal?
Listen here, lady!
Do your own shopping!
Don't try to poach my steak!
You got it?
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[POPUKO]
Hey!
[PIPIMI]
Overwhelming!
[POPUKO]
Weakling!
[PIPIMI]
Endurance!
[POPUKO]
Pop T.
[PIPIMI]
[POPUKO]
Pop T.
[PIPIMI]
[POPUKO]
Pop T.
[PIPIMI]
[POPUKO]
Pop T.
[PIPIMI]
[POPUKO]
Pop T.
[PIPIMI]
[POPUKO]
Pop T.
[PIPIMI]
[POPUKO]
Everybody, say...
[BOTH]
..."ho"!
[POPUKO]
Pop T.
[PIPIMI]
[BOTH yelling]
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[POPUKO]
Pass, pass!
[PIPIMI]
Okay!
Satellite Cannon!
[POPUKO]
Nice pass! Okay! Here I go!
Aura Cannon!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Bob Epic Team .
Here's your water.
Press the button when
you're ready to order food.
[POPUKO]
What a jerk!
[screams]
Ding-dong.
Ding-dong. Ding-dong. Ding-dong.
Ding-dong. Ding-dong.
Excuse me! Mr. Waiter!
Bob !
Epic ! Team !
You ready to order yet?
Eh, guess not.
What a jerk!
[ICHIRO] So then, you had
something to tell me?
[POPUKO sings]
[POPUKO]
Ah, the food here's amazing!
[PIPIMI chuckles]
[PIPIMI] Can you guess what's
the most important thing
for a Ginza hostess to
do in order to succeed
above anything else?
[POPUKO]
No, what is it?
[PIPIMI chuckles]
[PIPIMI]
Okay, I'll tell you.
It's to live life to the
fullest and enjoy it.
Hah. Mama Pipi.
You're creepy.
[POPUKO, PIPIMI]
Ha-ha-ha. He-he-he.
[PIPIMI]
Wait, did you say, "creepy"?
[POPUKO]
No.
[sirens wailing]
[PIPIMI] That was a glorious
soak, wasn't it, Popuko?
Yeah!
[DETECTIVE HIGURE]
Is this everyone at the inn?
Yes, Detective Higure.
Oh, my!
[DETECTIVE HIGURE groans]
Thank you for coming
out of your rooms
in the middle of
the night like this.
I'm here on behalf
of the city police.
Name's Detective Higure.
There's been a murder here
at the inn this evening.
At this point...
Detective Higuire?
That's his name?
Yeah, it's Higuire.
Seriously?
[POPUKO, PIPIMI chuckle]
[PIPIMI] They named
the gumshoe "Higuire," man?
They've got some balls.
[POPUKO]
Oh, yeah.
I can't believe such
a horrible thing
could ever happen at our
quiet little inn, sir!
[TANAKA grunts]
Everyone just remain calm.
I'd like to start by
taking a statement
from each of you, please.
Hm? Who do you think you are?
Damn!
Looks like Mama's about to be
all up in everyone's business!
Uh. I know!
You're the killer, sir!
[TANAKA]
No! You've got it all wrong!
Popuko, don't be so
rude to the guests!
Ah!
Are you on your way
home from work?
[TANAKA]
Oh. Uh. Yes.
Or on your way home
from a murder?
Hey, don't interfere with
my investigation, lady!
On the rocks? Splash of water?
Or a splash of murder?
You moron!
Okay, what have you got to
share with me, forensics? Huh?
[PIPIMI] So tell me, what was
the murder weapon, babe?
Well, uh, some kinda
blunt object.
It only took one blow.
Get these two dummies
outta my crime scene!
I guess that's as
far as we'll get.
We're amateurs in their eyes.
I'll still tag
along and help you.
[PIPIMI]
Oh?
After all, Mama Pipi,
you are Kinshicho's
worst-nightmare busybody!
[chuckles]
Sure am. Thanks for the
compliment, Popuko.
Well, let's get to work
and solve this mother!
Roger that!
[PIPIMI] The killer is
still at large in the inn.
We've got to gather evidence.
[POPUKO] Sleuth Rule Number
One: Talk to a buncha people!
I recall that my late
husband used to get up
so many damn times in the middle
of the night because he...
You're getting killed next.
Oh!
Popuko, assemble
everyone at the inn.
I've figured it out!
I've solved the crime,
so get everyone together
so I can trick the killer
into confessing.
Ah! I totally get it!
You've solved the crime!
Hey, you coppers!
We've got an announcement!
[PIPIMI]
You look like Detective Moore.
Mama! Everyone's arrived.
Thank you. Popuko, love.
So, um, why did you
bring us here?
Don't tell me. You know who
the killer is? Tell me!
Uh, I didn't do it. I swear!
Now, now, quiet down.
Nobody needs to get too excited.
I started working in Ginza
a very long time ago,
back when this floundering
nation was still full of life.
Everywhere I looked
in those days,
the world seemed so
fresh and dazzling,
a feast for my senses.
I accepted Ginza at face value,
and Ginza accepted me in return,
without question or expectation.
[WOMAN B]
Ready?
[WOMEN] Congratulations on your
25th anniversary, Mama Pipimi!
This is for you.
Goodness gracious!
A little something
from all of us!
Mama, go take a load
off for a change.
Everyone, thank you so much!
Mama, we're sending
Popuko to accompany you.
Huh? Me? For real?
You deserve it.
After all, you did make
top sales last month,
even as a rookie.
[WOMEN]
Have fun!
This trip was a gift
from my girls,
who are all like my daughters.
It's been spoiled by
a killer. What a drag.
Seriously? So you're saying
that this is all my fault?
[OTHERS gasp]
But how--? How was I supposed
to know who you really were?
That we had such
a legendary guest?
[PIPIMI] You're the murderer,
then, aren't you?
[HITOMI]
I couldn't forgive him!
Because of that man,
15 years ago, my father died.
I'm coming, Pop.
I'll be joining you very soon.
But Ginza is a mirror that
reflects the human soul.
Your death wouldn't do
anything to appease any soul.
Mama! I'm a terrible
woman who's taken a life!
I don't deserve to exist!
[PIPIMI]
Fool!
You know what you're called?
In Ginza, women like you
are called Damned Idiots!
[HIROMI]
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry!
After you've done your time,
come by my place
for a stiff drink.
[HIROMI]
Huh?
One truth prevails, probably.
You'll find us in Kinshichou,
waiting to get drunk with you.
[HIROMI crying]
[PIPIMI]
Kinshichou Station.
Kinshichou. Doors are closing.
[POPUKO]
Damn it, I overslept!
[PIPIMI] Ha-ha! Too bad,
that was the last train!
[SOSOGU]
It's me, Sosogu Hoshifuri!
Oh, no!
Daichi wants to
find his true self,
so he's planning to
study abroad for a while.
We're going to have to be apart!
Hoshiiro Girldrop ,
Episode Eleven:
"The Sudden Break-up."
Fall in love with us
again next week!