[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Hey there!
I'm Chomp-Chomp Bacon!
And I just love to eat bacon!
[CHOMP-CHOMP BACON]
Hot!
[PRISON GUARD A]
Lunch begins now!
[beeping]
[POPUKO]
Hm?
[PRISONER A] Isn't this
the cutest stamp ever?
Oh, you like that show?
Yeah, but I've never
even read the manga, so--
[POPUKO]
Why you--! Agh!
Hey, stop that!
Number 893! No touching!
[PIPIMI]
Mr. Prison Guard.
You, uh, mind if I have a
word with that prisoner?
I don't mind, and
I've got no choice.
Appreciate that, chief.
Here, kid. I swiped
this rice bowl for you.
You're quite an
interesting character.
You got somewhere to go
when you get out of here?
I don't.
The gang'll take
care of you, then.
Ever dreamed of being Yakuza?
Bet your ass!
Right.
Well, there's no saké,
so let's suck this.
[PIPIMI]
Now we've sworn a mortal oath.
We'll be waiting for
you when you get out.
At last, the smell
of freedom. So sweet.
[horn honking]
Howdy, partner. Been
waiting for you. Hop in.
[NARRATOR A]
And so, Popu and Pipi,
who had sworn an
oath of brotherhood,
would spread their notoriety
throughout Hiroshima.
Pipi was the young boss
of the Bamboozle Gang,
whose power and influence
was growing rapidly.
Thus, under Pipi's guidance...
...Popu becomes the
gang's assassin,
taking down rivals and
adversaries ruthlessly
and with fearless abandon.
Hey, you morons.
[BAMBOOZLE A]
Wha--? It's Pipi!
Didn't I say there'd
be no more You-Tubing?!
[POPUKO growling]
Stay, stay.
[BAMBOOZLE B]
Pipi, so nice to see you.
If you came to talk,
I'm all ears.
Thanks to you guys,
the cops've been sniffing
around this operation, see?
Stop You-Tubing!
[BAMBOOZLE B]
Well, honorable young boss,
I hate to disappoint you,
but we're doing all this to take
the heat off someone else.
And if you can't guess who that
is, then you should shut up!
Don't tell me. The old man.
[PIPIMI]
No way, Boss!
We live by the code, see?
How could you stoop
as low as this?
[IIDABASHI]
Listen closely, Pipi.
Times have been tough,
and the cops have been putting
the pressure on us, hard.
YouTube, and whatever.
We do what we must.
You're wrong, Boss!
[IIDABASHI]
Shut your mouth!
We can't survive by our Yakuza
code alone, you know that!
Right?! It's time
you grew up, too.
-What did you say?
--Stay, stay!
--What did you say?
That's it?
Well, I won't sell out.
I've got my principles.
I'm quitting this gang,
and doing things on my terms.
So stay out of my way.
[BAMBOOZLE A]
Boss!
[IIDABASHI grumbles]
[MODERATOR A]
Ready?
Even!
[AUDIENCE chattering]
[BAMBOOZLE E]
See you in hell, Popu!
[PRIESTS chanting]
[BAMBOOZLE F]
Hey, Boss, it's Pipi.
[IIDABASHI]
Huh?
[BAMBOOZLES whispering]
[PIPIMI]
Hey, Popu. Where'd we...?
Where did we go wrong
to end up here?
[BOTH gasp]
She was such a poser, you know?
Said she hated subculture girls.
But she sure sucked up to 'em
like she loved 'em, didn't she?
[POPUKO grunts]
[BAMBOOZLES, PRIESTS gasping]
[BAMBOOZLE F]
What?! Popu's not--?!
[IIDABASHI]
Pipi. You wouldn't!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Bob Epic Team .
Eisai haramasukoi!
What's that you're doing?
My dance, Eisai haramasukoi.
You think it'll catch on?
Not a chance.
[POPUKO]
Forget it!
Oh, please, wait!
Wait, wait!
Wait!
It will catch on.
Eisai haramasuk--!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[PIPIMI]
Got you a present.
Whoa!
Aww.
It's just some Edgelord
keychain from a souvenir shop.
So lame.
[LORD CALAMITY]
Master.
My name is Lord Calamity.
Could you be my new master?
Whoa, a real magic
object. My bad.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
I cut my bangs too short.
I did, too.
--[MAN G] I did, too--
--[PIPIMI] Shut up.
--Shut up!
--[MAN H] I did--
[XAVIER]
My name is--
[PIPIMI]
You're--!
Uh. Uhh...
--[POPUKO whispering]
--[PIPIMI] Oh. Okay, okay...
[PIPIMI]
Oh, okay.
You may pass.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Pipimi!
Let's watch Sun and Green,
the Best of Healthy Living !
That's our favorite show!
[POPUKO gasps]
It's only a scratch.
No big deal.
Let me put a Band-Aid on it!
Aw, damn! It got
stuck to my finger!
Damn. Ah, shit. Not again!
Damn. Stupid thing. Gah!
[screaming]
Don't worry about it.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic !
Bob Epic Team .
I made a music video.
You wanna see?
Yas, you're action personified.
[POPUKO]
Yeah! Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah...
Turn it off!
Stop right now, and burn
that tape in a fire!
Okay, sure.
You're action personified.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[VIDEO GAME ANNOUNCER A]
Heaven or Hell.
Duel one: Let's pop!
[BOTH grunting]
[PIPIMI yells]
[PIPIMI]
Finger!
[VIDEO GAME ANNOUNCER A]
You win!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[NARRATOR B] Pop Team Epic
Tales of Long Ago.
I'll make that old, dead
tree burst into bloom!
Fooled ya, dumb old tree!
That's flour, not flowers!
[POPUKO laughing]
[POPUKO] Why aren't we
in the anime right now?
[PIPIMI] Before we get to that,
why do we have to sing, anyway?
[POPUKO]
Maybe the writer likes you.
[PIPIMI]
Oh, yeah. Like in [beep].
[PIPIMI, POPUKO]
So short!
[SOSOGU]
It's me, Sosogu Hoshifuri!
I'm in charge of lyrics
for our new song,
and I have no idea
what to write!
I can't think of anything!
I know! I'll write a love song
about my feelings for Daichi!
Hoshiiro Girldrop ,
Episode Nine:
"Just for You. Our New Song!"
Fall in love with us
again next week!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Hey there! My name
is Chomp-Chomp Bacon!
And I just love to
eat bacon! Nom-nom!
Today I'm going to fry
my favorite kind of bacon
and, chomp-chomp, eat it
all right up! Nommy-nom!
First, you oil up the
frying pan real good,
and then, you lay a nice, fatty
slice of bacon down to s-- Ah!
Oh! Hot! Ho--!
[PRISON GUARD A]
Lunch begins now!
[beeping]
[PRISONER A] Isn't this
the cutest stamp ever?
Oh, you like that show?
Yeah, but I've never
even read the manga, so--
[POPUKO yells]
[POPUKO]
You wanna say that to my face?!
Hey, stop that!
Number 893! No touching!
[PIPIMI]
Mr. Prison Guard.
You, uh, mind if I have a
word with that prisoner?
I don't mind, and
I've got no choice.
I appreciate that, sir.
Here, kid. I swiped this
bowl of rice for you.
You know, you're an
interesting character.
You got somewhere to
go when you get out?
I don't.
The gang'll take
care of you, then.
Ever dreamed of being Yakuza?
You bet your ass!
Right.
Well, there's no saké, so let's
both suck on this lemon.
[PIPIMI]
Now we've sworn our mortal oath.
We'll be waitin' for
you when you get out.
At last, freedom. So sweet.
[horn honking]
[POPUKO]
Hm?
[PIPIMI]
Vroom-vroom!
Howdy. Been waiting? Hop in.
[NARRATOR A]
And so, Popu and Pipi,
who had sworn an
oath of brotherhood,
would spread their notoriety
throughout Hiroshima.
Pipi was the young boss
of the Bamboozle Gang,
whose power and influence
was growing rapidly.
Thus, under Pipi's guidance...
...Popu becomes
the gang's assassin,
taking down rivals and
adversaries ruthlessly
and with fearless abandon.
Hey, you morons.
[BAMBOOZLE A]
Wha--? It's Pipi!
Didn't I say there'd be no
more You-Tubing around here?
No, no, it's okay.
Stay, stay, kid.
[BAMBOOZLE B]
Pipi, so nice to see you.
If you came to talk,
I'm all ears.
Thanks to you guys,
the cops've been sniffin'
around this operation, see?
Stop You-Tubing!
[BAMBOOZLE B]
Well, honorable young boss,
I hate to disappoint you,
but we're doing all this to take
the heat off someone else.
And if you can't
guess who that is,
then you should just shut up!
Don't tell me. The old man.
[PIPIMI]
No way, Boss!
We live by the code.
How could you? How could
you stoop as low as this?
[IIDABASHI]
Listen closely, Pipi.
Times have been tough,
and the cops have been putting
the pressure on us, hard.
YouTube, and whatever.
We do what we must.
You're wrong!
[IIDABASHI]
Shut your mouth!
We can't survive by our Yakuza
code alone, you know that!
Right?
It's time you grew up, too.
What'd you say--?!
No, stay, stay.
That's it? Well, I got
my principles, too, Boss.
I'm quittin' this gang, and
doin' things on my terms.
So stay outta my way.
[BAMBOOZLE A]
Boss!
[IIDABASHI grumbles]
[MODERATOR A]
Ready?
Even!
[AUDIENCE chattering]
[BAMBOOZLE E]
See you in hell, Popu!
[POPUKO]
This is bull[beep].
Wish I could be holding my
actual middle fingers up,
not just the ones in the photo.
But I'm dead, so
that's out, I guess...
[BAMBOOZLE F]
Hey, Boss, it's Pipi.
[IIDABASHI]
Huh?
[BAMBOOZLES whispering]
[POPUKO]
Oh, shit. Is that Pipi?
What's with the suitcase?
Maybe she's got some badass
revenge scheme planned...
[PIPIMI]
Hey, Popu.
Where'd we...? Where'd we
go wrong to end up here?
Check this out.
[IIDABASHI]
Gasp!
[PIPIMI]
Lookit.
She was such a poser, you know?
Said she hated subculture girls.
But she sure sucked up to 'em
like she loved 'em, didn't she?
[grunts]
[POPUKO]
Damn you bastards!
[BAMBOOZLE F]
What?! Popu's not--?!
[PIPIMI]
Suckas!
[IIDABASHI]
Pipi! I was wrong!
[PIPIMI]
Va-room!
The end.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[POPUKO]
Bob Epic Team .
Eisai haramasukoi!
What's that you're doing?
My dance, Eisai haramasukoi.
You think it'll catch on?
Not a chance.
[POPUKO]
Forget it!
Oh, please, wait!
Wait, wait!
Wait!
It will catch on.
Eisai haramasuk--!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[PIPIMI]
Got you a present.
[gasps]
[POPUKO]
Aww.
It's just some Edgelord
keychain from a souvenir shop.
So lame.
[LORD CALAMITY]
Master.
My name is Lord Calamity.
Could you be my new master?
I, Lord Calamity, will--
Whoa, a real magical
object. My bad.
[LORD CALAMITY] Wait. You
summoned me here. What do you--?
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
I cut my bangs too short.
I did, too.
--[MAN G] I did, too.
--[PIPIMI] Shut up.
--[MAN H] I did, too--
--[PIPIMI, POPUKO] Shut up.
[XAVIER]
I did, too!
[PIPIMI]
Wait, are you--?
--[POPUKO, PIPIMI whispering]
--[XAVIER] I did. I did, too.
--Please. Take a look. See?
[PIPIMI]
You can pass!
[XAVIER]
Phew, lucky.
Thank goodness my name's Xavier.
Thank goodness.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Pipimi!
Let's watch Sun and Green,
the Best of Healthy Living .
Our favorite show!
[POPUKO gasps]
It's just a scratch.
Don't worry about it.
Let me put a Band-Aid
on it. Here.
Aw, man! Son of a-- Got stuck on
my finger! Aw, damn! Ah, [beep]!
Oh!
[screaming]
Don't worry about it.
[POPUKO screaming]
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic !
[POPUKO]
Bob Epic Team .
I made a music video.
You wanna see?
Yas, you're action personified.
[POPUKO]
Yeah! Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah...
Turn it off!
Stop right now, and burn
that tape in a fire!
Okay, sure.
You're action personified.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[VIDEO GAME ANNOUNCER A]
Heaven or Hell.
Duel One: Let's Pop!
[PIPIMI]
You're lookin' scared.
Finger!
[VIDEO GAME ANNOUNCER A]
You win!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[NARRATOR B] Pop Team Epic
Tales of Long Ago.
Long, long ago,
before anyone remembers,
there lived a man named
Flower-Bloom Popuko.
Here's his story.
I'll make this old,
dead tree burst into bloom.
[POPUKO] Hah! I fooled
the old dead tree!
That's flour, not flowers!
Ah! Fooled the old damn tree!
Made it think it could bloom!
[PIPIMI] Everyone, please
sing your hearts out
to the song over
the closing credits.
[SOSOGU]
It's me, Sosogu Hoshifuri!
I'm in charge of lyrics
for our new song,
and I have no idea
what to write!
I can't think of anything!
I know! I'll write a love song
about my feelings for Daichi!
Hoshiiro Girldrop ,
Episode Nine:
"Just for You. Our New Song!"
Fall in love with us
again next week!