[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Eisai haramasukoi! Eisai--
What are you doing?
The Eisai Haramasukoi.
Think it'll catch on?
[PIPIMI]
Not a chance.
It will catch on.
[POPUKO] Eisai haramasukoi.
Eisai Haramasukoi.
Eisai Haramasukoi. E-E-E-E-Esai.
E-E-E-E-E-E-E-Ei--
Eisai Haramasukoi.
E-E-E-E-E--
[SHOGO]
All right!
[ALL]
Cheers!
I love the atmosphere here,
it's def going on Instagram.
Yeah, you outdid
yourself, Hayato.
This is a cool place to party.
[HAYATO chuckles]
I found it on the internet.
Some obscure site.
You wouldn't know it, bro.
Oh, damn. My nail is coming off.
Oh, that's a real
shame, isn't it?
Yeah, I'll say.
[SHOGO] Oh, hey, hey,
check out this pic.
It's from that crazy
house party last week.
Ha. Oh my God, Shogo,
you're such a party animal!
Cheese! For my Instagram story!
Oh, yeah!
[REINA]
Ugh.
Never mind.
Anyway, this is some great
atmosphere, am I right?
Yeah, I know!
Like hashtag perfect!
[SHOGO laughs]
Leave it to the ace member
of our drinking group, here.
Oh, come on! Cut that out, man!
[REINA, AYA laugh]
Yup, he's so handy! Right?
For sure.
Seriously though,
why don't the two of us
go somewhere, and, uh?
I'm ready and willing, too.
It's gotta be with you, Reina.
--Aya's been in there a while.
--Where is Aya? Huh?
Oh, that's right.
[whispering]
[gasps]
[AYA]
What was that?
This is creepy.
[whispering]
[AYA screams]
[gasps]
[SHOGO]
Hey, what's wrong?
Aya!
O-Over there!
[SHOGO]
There's nothing there, Aya.
[AYA]
But I saw them.
There were two girls at
the end of the hallway!
Aya, just calm down.
Come on. Let's get
you back to the room.
[REINA] Hey, wait. Shogo,
aren't you coming downstairs?
You okay?
[AYA]
Mh-hm.
All right, Aya.
You can drop the act.
[AYA]
Huh?
Trying to be the
damsel in distress?
It's gotten really boring,
just so you know.
[AYA]
I'm not pretending!
There really were two girls
there! I swear I'm not lying!
Hey, Reina. Stop, okay?
Shut up. I know
what you're doing.
You've got the hots for Aya,
everyone knows it.
It's totally disgusting.
Huh? No way!
Wh-Wh-What are you even
talkin' about, Reina?
Come on. Don't be shy.
I think it'd seriously be great!
You guys should hook up tonight,
and I'll hook up with Shogo!
Uh, hang on, Reina.
[AYA chuckles]
[AYA]
I feel so sorry for you, Reina.
You never could read a room.
Shogo and I have got
a little thing going.
[chuckles]
[BOTH gasp]
[SHOGO]
For now.
Then what were you doing
kissing me in the kitchen
while Aya was in
the bathroom, Shogo?
What?
Yeah, what were
you doing, Shogo?
Uh... I'm really drunk so, uh...
Huh?
[REINA, AYA scream]
You bastard.
Getting it on with
anything that moves,
and always rubbing it
in my face, too.
I'm gonna slaughter every
God[beep] one of you!
[REINA, AYA scream]
[HAYATO]
You can't get away!
[REINA]
Help!
Someone help me!
I've got to get out of here!
Oh, God! Come on, start.
For the love of God, start!
Start! Start!
It started!
[incoherent chatter]
[REINA screams]
[HAYATO laughs]
Just be a nice, good
girl for me, okay?
Damn you to hell!
No way!
[HAYATO yells]
[HAYATO]
Aya!
[AYA yelps]
[incoherent chatter]
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Bob Epic Team .
Mayor, I've come
up with an idea
for new playground equipment!
Very well done!
How 'bout a jetpack swing?
No, that simply won't do.
It's far too dangerous.
[yelps]
You will still pay
me for my work!
With your life!
[MAYOR yelping]
[MAYORS cawing]
Live long, birdies.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[NARRATOR A] Pop Team Epic
Tales of Long Ago.
Would you like to know
what I'm reading?
I'm in-tree-sted.
[POPUKO gasps]
You turned into a tree!
Oh, Pipimi!
Don't leave me like this!
[OLD MAN A] And so, that's
how the old story goes.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[thudding]
Pipimi!
How in the world
did you get so big?
[PIPIMI]
Hmm...
Science.
Oh, science.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[NARRATOR B]
Pop Team Epic Cooking!
Pop Team...
...Cooking!
Today, we've got rice omelet!
I'll draw a heart
on it with ketchup!
[POPUKO]
Ah, this is so embarrassing!
[screams]
[WOMAN A]
No!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Bob Epic Team .
[PIPIMI]
We received a letter today.
"Bob Epic Team is lame and
doesn't have enough keyframes.
Take a cue from other anime."
[POPUKO grunts]
[POPUKO] That really
cuts me to the core.
Okay, then. I'll draw
tons of keyframes!
And make 'em move!
Eisai haramasukoi!
Eisai Haramasukoi!
[PIPIMI] The Eisai Haramasukoi.
Now that's the Real McCoy!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[speaking French]
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[POPUKO laughing]
[POPUKO]
See ya later, sharky!
[sighs]
[giggles]
[POPUKO] Okay, so why
aren't we in the anime?
[PIPIMI]
There's only one episode left.
[POPUKO] No way!
It's gonna end like this?
[PIPIMI]
Hey, author...
[BOTH] ...if you like [beep],
keep making more!
[BOTH]
Too short!
[DAICHI]
As I searched for my true self,
I discovered a memory:
Five years ago, Sosogu gave
her life and died in my place,
becoming the star I
always knew she was.
But thanks to Gaia's power,
I gave up all my
memories of Sosogu,
and in return, Gaia
brought her back to life.
Now, she's about to make
the ultimate sacrifice
and give her life for me again.
This time, I want to
honor the sacred promise
I made to you.
Hoshiiro Girldrop ,
final episode:
"Sosogu and Daichi:
A Precious Promise."
We can fall in love
all over again.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Eisai haramasukoi!
[beat boxing]
Hey, what are you doin'?
The Eisai Haramasukoi Dance.
Think it'll catch on?
[PIPIMI]
Not a chance!
[POPUKO]
Hm?
It will catch on!
[POPUKO] Eisai Haramasukoi.
Eisai Haramasukoi.
[POPUKO grunting]
[POPUKO] Eisai Haramasukoi!
Eisai Haramasukoi!
[PIPIMI] Hey, c'mon now!
[PIPIMI yelling]
[SHOGO]
All right!
[ALL]
Cheers!
[REINA]
I love the atmosphere...
Oh, four of 'em.
Mm-hmm. I get it now.
I get it. I like that hefty
one on the right there.
He'll be the first one to die,
I think. Yeah. Yeah.
He just seems like he would.
See, her nail's coming off.
That must be the ghost's doing.
And when the nail comes off,
if there's no nail
underneath then...
Well, that's ghostly
stuff, too. Uh-huh.
Oh, she can't read the
situation at all, huh?
Oh... What's that?
So check out the guy
who's talking right now.
And the girl with the dark hair,
the one next to him there,
who should be in a
shampoo commercial?
Well, there's a fireball
wafting around behind them.
Between them, you see?
It's totally there.
Yeah. There's-There's
something there in the guns.
Something about them.
[gasps]
And the title is
Cursed Mansion .
And it's snowing
hard, yeah, yeah.
Mmhmm. Well, these two
sure look chummy, huh?
Hey, hey, camera man,
stop! Camera, stop!
The guy holding the [beep]--
I mean, the one
holding the beer.
He just moved his finger
in a certain way.
Didja know home run sluggers put
their fingers-their
fingers up like that.
He's gotta be a ball player.
Yeah. What now?
What now? What?
This girl, man.
Not only can she
not read a room,
but she didn't even shut the
damn bathroom door, either.
Like she was raised in
a barn or something.
I don't like that girl.
Hey, what's that? What's that
in the dark down there?
Look, look, look, look,
look, look, look, look!
I saw it, too.
Hey, I saw something!
Yeah, that's definitely
a female ghost.
Yeah, or maybe
it's a male ghost.
Nothing there? It disappeared.
Oh, there were girls,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, there were girls
there. I saw them.
[COMMENTATOR A grunting]
[COMMENTATOR A]
Huh?
Did I hear a
poltergeist noise?
I sure did. A poltergeist
noise. Yeah.
I wonder what generation
these kids are.
Like, what year they
were born and whatnot.
I don't care.
I don't really buy
into all that lazy,
precious millennial stuff.
But you know, it must've
been late last year.
Yeah, I was, uh, I was
on my way to a shoot.
And I'm just, uh,
sitting in my car.
And this guy next to me is
a young staffer guy in his 20s.
You know the type of guy.
Young guy, you know?
And we're just chatting away.
You know what I mean.
All the sudden.
[COMMENTATOR retching]
Just like that. Ugh.
Gonna puke. About to hurl.
I thought, "Oh. Oh, no! You
gotta do something, quickly!
So I grabbed my bag
and I just dumped it out
all over the place really fast,
and I handed it to him
through the window,
and he just took it and just--
[COMMENTATOR A grunting]
He vomited into the bag, and
instantly, he felt a lot better.
And then he handed
me the vomit bag.
Yeah, it was scary,
but I wonder if it was
like a generational thing.
Yeah.
What? Hey, he just took
that axe off the wall.
I was about to comment
on the weapons, and look!
Yeah.
Oh. I knew something
was suspicious.
It's the dead of
winter out there.
It's snowing outside,
the table is covered with
all kinds of snacks,
mostly junk food and stuff,
but in the middle of all that,
there's this
out-of-season watermelon,
like a sore thumb.
Oh, no, no, no, no. This is bad.
What?
There's a car. Cars and horror
films go hand-in-hand.
I bet it's an evil car, too.
I bet the car is like--
Oh, here she is.
Come on. Come on, come on,
come on. Look, look, look, look.
The car won't start.
Oh, come on, come on, start.
In American horror
films they always try
to jump start the car,
and it never works, though.
[COMMENTATOR yelps]
[COMMENTATOR A]
Uh.
It's Popuko and Pipimi, right?
Uh. That girl was wearing black
panties. I just saw them.
Huh? This--
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, all of a sud--
All that happened so fast.
[COMMENTATOR A yelps]
Ah, I see.
I figured it all out.
Figured it all out.
Yeah, you see. Do you see?
Ah. It's like the
famous horror flick.
I probably shouldn't
say the name
for legal reasons though, right?
It's an "S" word, you know?
Uh, it's The [beep],
but a parody of it.
Ah, check it,
check it. There. See?
Something weird
with that photo.
I didn't tell you earlier
because I didn't want you to get
all scared and freak
out or anything.
But it's weird. Yeah.
Oh, lookit, lookit, lookit.
They gave us the
"Dying Message."
"The End."
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Bob Epic Team .
Mayor, I've come up with an idea
for new playground equipment!
Very well done!
How 'bout a jetpack swing?
No, that simply won't do.
It's far too dangerous.
[yelps]
You will still pay
me for my work!
With your life!
[MAYOR yelping]
[MAYOR cawing]
Live long, birdies.
[NARRATOR]
Pop --
[NARRATOR coughing]
[NARRATOR C]
Yeah, nailed it, John.
[NARRATOR A] Pop Team Epic
Tales of Long Ago.
[POPUKO murmuring]
[PIPIMI]
Um-hm?
Would you like to know
what I'm reading?
I'm in-tree-sted.
[POPUKO gasps]
You turned into a tree!
Oh, Pipimi! Don't
leave me like this!
[wails]
[OLD MAN A] And so, that's
the how the old story goes.
[NARRATOR] Pop Team Epic .
Beep, boop, boop, beep.
[thudding]
Pipimi, how in the world
did you get to be so big?
[PIPIMI]
Hmm...
Ooh!
Science.
Oh, science.
Science!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[NARRATOR B]
Pop Team Epic... Cooking.
Pop Team Epic...
...Cooking!
Today we've got rice omelet!
I'll draw a heart
on it with ketchup.
Mh-hm. Drawing a little heart.
Oh, this is so embarrassing!
[screams]
[POPUKO, PIPIMI]
You saw us.
[WOMAN A]
No!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Bob Epic Team .
[PIPIMI]
We received a letter today.
"Bob Epic Team is lame and
doesn't have enough keyframes.
Take a cue from other anime."
[POPUKO grunts]
[POPUKO]
That really cuts me to the core.
Okay then, I'll draw
tons of keyframes!
And make 'em move!
Eisai haramasukoi!
Eisai Haramasukoi!
[PIPIMI] The Eisai Haramasukoi.
Now that's the Real McCoy!
[NARRATOR]
Explosion. Implosion. Beware.
[speaking French]
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[POPUKO laughing]
[POPUKO]
See you, sharky! Bye!
[POPUKO] This must be
what Heaven is like.
[giggles]
[DAICHI]
As I searched for my true self,
I discovered a memory:
Five years ago, Sosogu gave
her life and died in my place,
becoming the star I
always knew she was.
But thanks to Gaia's power,
I gave up all my
memories of Sosogu,
and in return, Gaia
brought her back to life.
Now, she's about to make
the ultimate sacrifice
and give her life for me again.
This time, I want to honor the
sacred promise I made to you.
Hoshiiro Girldrop ,
final episode:
"Sosogu and Daichi:
A Precious Promise."
We can fall in love
all over again.