[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
♪♪♪
[IYO]
Hi, Mom.
Do you remember that day
when you told me what was
most precious in life?
Well, I think I've
found it, too.
[IYO] My name is Iyo Sakuragi,
and I'm 16 years old.
I'm in my first year at
St. Culture Academy.
[sighs]
[IYO]
A new stepmom? Ugh.
[HOJO] Hey, there.
First-year, help me out!
Toss me that ball, will ya?
[IYO]
Uh! It's Hojo- senpai !
Uh, sure!
[HOJO
Thank you.
[IYO]
Ah! Senpai!
You are, like, the coolest ever!
[IYO] Hojo- senpai , captain
and star of the soccer team,
top in his class,
Student Body President,
the best at everything.
And the boy I'm
hopelessly in love with.
Oh, yeah.
I got distracted, but I wonder
what Dad's new wife is like.
[IYO sighs]
[PIPIMI chuckles]
[PIPIMI]
Here we are!
[PIPIMI chuckles]
Hey, say hello, dummy.
These jerks are your
new mom and brother.
Um, hi, nice to meet you.
I'm Iyo Sakuragi.
Hm. You're grumpier
than I expected.
Disappointing.
[IYO gasps]
What? It's Senpai?
Wha--? You're that first-year!
[BOTH laughing]
Uh. Hey, um, Senpai.
Don't call me Senpai.
C'mon, Iyo.
I'm your brother now.
What? Oh, right.
[IYO] No way! I want
you to be my boyfriend.
I don't wanna think
of you as my brother!
[IYO] And so, that's how
the story of my life
with Hojo- senpai and my
crazy new stepmom began.
Sadly, it was a life filled
with pain and hardships.
Dad and Mom couldn't
hold down jobs
and spent all of their
time and our money
at the pachinko parlor.
I couldn't study
because they insisted
on giving puppet shows
outside the window.
I couldn't sleep at night
because of their ceaseless,
Gundam motion dancing.
Who could with that racket?
My classmates, fans of Senpai's,
bullied me to tears
almost every day.
I was going out of my mind!
But in spite of all the horrors,
living with Senpai made
the suffering worthwhile.
That is, until that day.
[IYO screams]
[PIPIMI] How we spend our money
is none of your damn business!
Stop this right now!
If you spend that money,
we'll get evicted for
not paying the rent!
With all this, we can place
three times the bet on pachinko,
and win enough to take
that vacation to Hawaii!
I've had enough!
Iyo!
I can't take it!
I'll see you in Hell!
[HOJO]
Iyo, don't do it!
[thud]
[HOJO groans]
[gasps]
No! Senpai!
If only for my sake,
please don't do this, Iyo.
If they take you away,
I would just die.
Senpai, are you saying--?
Yeah, I'm saying that I...
...love you.
[IYO]
Senpai!
I'm so happy.
[HOJO] And for real,
stop calling me Senpai.
[siren blaring]
[IYO] And so, Senpai and I got
married a couple years later.
I gave birth to adorable
twins this year, too.
We went through a lot to get to
this point, but it was worth it,
and life couldn't be
better for us now.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[POPUKO] Brother's gonna
find out how quickly
he can hit a home run.
Let's see how he does.
[POPUKO] The clock starts
when the speed is set.
And it's over now.
It took 7.11 seconds.
Okay, time to assess
his performance.
Why did he have to
take it so seriously?
It's just a game.
That's all.
Thank you for watching.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[CHILDREN]
Pop Team Cooking!
Pop Team...
...Cooking!
All right, it's time for
this week's recommendation.
[POPUKO]
Yeah!
Simmering.
[POPUKO]
Yeah!
And over here, we have
the finished dish!
[POPUKO gasps]
[PIPIMI]
Tune in again next week!
[POPUKO]
Ooh. He-he!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Bob Epic Team .
Where's our next vacation?
[OWL]
Hoo-hoo. Wassap?
You must go to the outlet mall.
Oh! Look, a supporting
character's come to help!
You can take a shuttle
there from the bus station.
When you arrive, go
straight to the pet shop.
You know the one
I'm talkin' about.
After that, I think
you can figure
the rest out for yourselves.
[OWL hooting]
Do it yourself.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Can you say your
multiples of three?
Ya think I'm dumb?
Of course I can.
Three threes three.
Three threes?
Three!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
I'm the type who likes nice,
long strokes and caresses.
[giggling]
Good girl.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah. Oh, yeah.
Marilyn Monroe.
Ooh! Ha-ha.
Marilyn Monroe!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
I'm sorry.
[hiccuping]
I heard if you hiccup a
hundred times, you die.
That's 99.
Oh, they stopped.
I'll self-destruct
just to be safe.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Bob Epic Team .
Sorry, were you waiting long?
Nah, just got here, myself.
Will we be late for the movie?
Don't worry, we'll make it.
Hey, what're you
lookin' at, perv?
Huh?
Bro, what are you
even looking at?
Wanna die, you rat bastard?
I'm not lookin'.
Yes, you are!
You were. I saw you!
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are!
--No, I'm not.
--Yes, you are!
--[POPUKO] Ye--
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
And now, an impression
of [beep] [beep].
What, do you wanna die?
[POPUKO] Gosh! Whoa, [beep]!
Stop that! Hee-hee! Hey!
What? I said [beep]
stop it, now!
Oh! Hi, there! Hee-hee!
[beep] quit it!
[POPUKO laughing]
[POPUKO]
[beep]
[POPUKO laughing]
[beep] doesn't snort
when he laughs, you idiot.
[NARRATOR]
Ha-ha. Pop Team Epic .
[MR. BUNNY]
Oh, no! I'm late! I'm late!
For a very important date!
Uh! Hey! Pardon, Mr. Rabbit?
Wait for me!
Mr. Rabbit, wait for me!
Wait for me! Wait for me!
Wait! Ha-ha!
I said wait!
Hey! Bunny!
Hi. I'm Yuhi Korona!
What? Daichi and I have
gotten really close?
Does that bother you?
Hoshiiro Girldrop ,
Episode Six:
"Love Triangle? A Strong
Foe Beats Korona!"
Fall in love with us
again next week!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
♪♪♪
[IYO]
Hi, Mom.
Do you remember that day
when you told me what was
most precious in life?
Well, I think I've
found it, too.
[IYO] My name is Iyo Sakuragi,
and I'm 16 years old.
I'm in my first year at
St. Culture Academy.
[sighs]
[IYO]
A new stepmom? Ugh.
[HOJO] Hey, there.
First-year, help me out!
Toss me that ball, will ya?
[IYO]
Uh! It's Hojo- senpai !
Uh, sure!
[HOJO]
Thank you.
[IYO]
Ah! Senpai!
You are, like, the coolest ever!
[IYO] Hojo- senpai , captain
and star of the soccer team,
top in his class,
Student Body President,
the best at everything.
And the boy I'm
hopelessly in love with.
Oh, yeah.
I got distracted, but I wonder
what Dad's new wife is like.
[IYO sighs]
[PIPIMI]
Uh. Here we are. Okay, okay.
Hey, say hello, dummy.
These jerks are your
new mom and brother.
Um, hi, nice to meet you.
I'm Iyo Sakuragi.
Man. You're way
grumpier than I expected.
[IYO gasps]
What? It's Senpai?
Wha--? You're that first-year!
[PIPIMI]
That's a mackerel. Heh-heh.
[POPUKO] A damn mackerel
on his head. Heh.
Uh. Hey, um, Senpai?
Don't call me Senpai.
C'mon, Iyo.
I'm your brother now.
What? Oh, right.
[IYO] No way! I want you
to be my boyfriend.
I don't wanna think
of you as my brother!
[IYO] And so, that's how
the story of my life
with Hojo- senpai and my
crazy new stepmom began.
Sadly, it was a life filled
with pain and hardships.
Dad and Mom couldn't
hold down jobs
and spent all of their
time and our money
at the pachinko parlor.
I couldn't study
because they insisted
on giving puppet shows
outside the window.
I couldn't sleep at night
because of their ceaseless,
Gundam motion dancing.
Who could with that racket?
My classmates, fans of Senpai's,
bullied me to tears
almost every day.
I was going out of my mind!
But in spite of all the horrors,
living with Senpai made
the suffering worthwhile.
That is, until that day.
[IYO screams]
[PIPIMI] How we spend our money
is none of your damn business!
Stop this right now!
If you spend that money,
we'll get evicted for
not paying the rent!
With all this, we can place
three times the bet on pachinko,
and win enough to take
that vacation to Hawaii!
I've had enough!
Iyo!
I can't take it!
I'll see you in Hell!
[HOJO]
Iyo, don't do it!
[thud]
[HOJO groans]
[gasps]
No! Senpai!
If only for my sake,
please don't do this, Iyo.
If they take you away,
I would just die.
Senpai, are you saying--?
Yeah, I'm saying that I...
...love you.
[IYO]
Senpai!
I'm so happy.
[HOJO] And for real,
stop calling me Senpai.
[siren blaring]
[IYO] And so, Senpai and I got
married a couple years later.
I gave birth to adorable
twins this year, too.
We went through a lot to get to
this point, but it was worth it,
and life couldn't be
better for us now.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[POPUKO]
Ready, get set, go.
[PIPIMI] Brother's gonna
find out how quickly
he can hit a home run.
Let's see how he does.
[POPUKO]
Dat-da-da-dat. Ping.
Da-da-da.
[PIPIMI] The clock starts
when the speed is set.
And it's over now.
It took 7.11 seconds.
Okay, time to assess
his performance.
Why did he have to
take it so seriously?
It's just a game.
That's all. Thank
you for watching.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[CHILDREN]
Pop Team Cooking!
Pop Team...
...Cooking!
All right, it's time for
this week's recommendation.
Did I wash my hands, you ask?
Yes, like almost always,
you should, too.
[POPUKO gasps]
And here is the finished dish!
[PIPIMI]
Tune in again next week.
[POPUKO gasps]
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Bob Epic Team .
Where's our next vacation?
[OWL]
Hoo-hoo. Wassap?
You must go to the outlet mall.
Oh! Look, a supporting
character's come to help!
You can take a shuttle
there from the bus station.
When you arrive,
go straight to the pet shop.
You know the one
I'm talkin' about.
After that, I think
you can figure
the rest out for yourselves.
[OWL hooting]
Do it yourself.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Can you say your
multiples of three?
Ya think I'm dumb?
Of course I can.
Three threes three.
Three threes?
Three!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
I'm the type who longs
for sweet, long caresses.
Good girl.
Oh, yeah.
[PIPIMI]
Here's where it gets long.
[POPUKO]
Ha! That's what she said.
[PIPIMI]
Not only the neck,
but the awkward
interaction, too.
[POPUKO]
Ooh, so long.
[PIPIMI] It's like the opening
of that detective show
from the 90s.
[POPUKO] They should fill
in the blank, you know?
Like with the producer's
name or something.
[PIPIMI] Maybe they'll
add captions in post.
For when it airs.
[POPUKO]
Yeah, maybe so.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Sorry.
[hiccuping]
I hear that if you hiccup
a hundred times, you die.
That was 99.
Oh, they stopped.
I'll self-destruct
just to be safe.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[PIPIMI B]
Bob Epic Team .
Sorry, were you waiting long?
Nah, just got here, myself.
Will we be late for the movie?
Don't worry, we'll make it.
Hey, what're you
lookin' at, perv?
Huh?
Bro, what are you
even looking at?
Wanna die, you rat bastard?
I'm not lookin'.
Yes, you are!
You were. I saw you!
No, I'm not.
Yes, you are!
--No, I'm not.
--Yes, you are!
--[POPUKO] Ye--
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Here's an impression
of [beep] [beep]!
What, do you wanna die?
[POPUKO] Gosh! Whoa, [beep]!
Stop that! Hee-hee! Hey!
What? I said [beep]
stop it, now!
Ho-ho! Hi, there! Hi!
[beep] quit it!
[POPUKO laughing]
[beep] doesn't snort
when he laughs, you idiot.
Ah.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[MR. BUNNY sighs]
[MR. BUNNY] I'm late. I'm late.
For a very important date.
Oh. Mr. Rabbit!
Wait for me!
Mr. Rabbit, wait for me!
Wait for me! Wait for me!
Wait! Hey, I said wait!
Can you hear me?
Stop singing that song!
Wait! Be my friend!
Be my friend! I--
Be my friend!
[MR. BUNNY]
♪ Born to be hungry. ♪
Hi. I'm Yuhi Korona!
What? Daichi and I have
gotten really close?
Does that bother you?
Hoshiiro Girldrop ,
Episode Six:
"Love Triangle? A Strong
Foe Beats Korona!"
Fall in love with us
again next week!