[MASTER HERO] Be careful!
The Demon King approaches!
[COMPANIONS]
Yeah!
[DEMON KING laughs]
[DEMON KING]
I am impressed that you've
come this far, weaklings.
I applaud your efforts.
[COMPANION C]
Master Hero!
Let me defeat him with
my summoning magic!
[MASTER HERO]
Yes, I'm counting on you!
[COMPANION C] Oh, two-headed
dragon from beyond,
I implore you to appear
and fight on our behalf!
Messenger from across the abyss.
Twin Elemental Dragon!
What's this crap?
The animation isn't
even completed yet.
It's like they put all their
resources into episode one,
then they ran outta gas.
[DEMON KING laughs]
[DEMON KING]
I am the Demon King.
Ooh, scary!
[COMPANION D]
Do something!
You're the beast she
summoned from beyond!
Shut up. Your face
isn't even drawn in.
[COMPANION C]
Oh! I'm not worthy!
My summoning magic has failed!
Yeah, I agree. You suck!
Well, what can ya do?
Hey, you, I've heard you
do great impressions.
If I'm not impressed,
you're gonna get it!
[MASTER HERO]
Uhh...
"How you doin'?"
What?
For real, man?
Are you kidding me?
All right, lady, you're up.
[COMPANION C]
Huh?!
Do it!
Uh. Okay.
"How you doin'?" Uh.
"How you doin'?"
And you get paid
for stuff like that?
Talk about an easy job.
Yeah, I agree! You suck!
[SEIYUU A]
Hold on. Stop, stop. Stop.
What the hell is
this? This is bad.
[SEIYUU B] Uh, Mr. Producer,
can you get in here?
We need help.
[SEIYUU A]
Come here.
You said it'd be rough,
but gimme a break.
This is absurd.
What is this script?
It's just a bunch of notes:
"Ad lib here. Ad lib there."
[SEIYUU B] Nobody told me I
would have to do impressions.
[SEIYUU A]
That's not cool!
We just... we thought
it'd be funny.
[SEIYUU B]
Things seemed quiet on your end!
[SEIYUU A]
You guys weren't laughing!
All I heard was a
couple of snickers!
Rewrite this crap. An actual
script, no damn ad libs!
The work's gotten shoddy!
The whole damn industry.
Do better, for real. I expect
it to be fixed next time.
[DEMON KING]
Did you see it?
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[POPUKO]
Pop Team Epic is shit!
[PIPIMI] Constructive
criticism only. Don't--
[POPUKO] Zero percent!
Zero percent! Zero percent!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Bob Epic Team .
[BOTH]
Can't wait to see the panda!
A panda!
[POPUKO]
So cute!
A koala!
[POPUKO]
So cute!
--A panda!
--Seen it.
A koala!
Seen it.
--A Tasmanian tiger!
--[POPUKO] So cute!
A wombat.
[POPUKO]
So cute.
--A dingo.
--Don't care.
--A wallaby.
--So cute.
A wombat.
Seen it.
A Tasmanian devil!
Nuh-uh. We haven't seen
a Tasmanian devil yet.
[POPUKO]
Oops, my bad.
[BOTH laughing]
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Beach day!
Okay!
The Machu Picchu of Japan!
[PIPIMI]
Can't do that.
Set's not done, so we
can't go there yet.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
No one can compete
with my smile!
Oh? Can you compete with mine?
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[BOTH] ♪ Every day,
you turn your face from me ♪
♪ and look the other way. ♪
♪ What the fuck? What are
you so preoccupied with? ♪
♪ Look at me! ♪
♪ You act like you
just don't notice ♪
♪ that I'm so
in love with you. ♪
♪ Seriously, you're
fucking rude. ♪
♪ How do you sleep at night?! ♪
♪ Your taste is irrelevant! ♪
♪ It might be mainstream! ♪
♪ Even if you quibble about
the best subculture, ♪
♪ everyone still
thinks you're dumb! ♪
♪ Just let me show you
my Pop  Technique! ♪
♪ Feel my love through
my Pop Technique! ♪
♪ Don't let it scare you! ♪
♪ I'll give you such a thrill,
like you've never felt before! ♪
♪ Niche love stabs you
right through your heart! ♪
♪ Let it impale you! ♪
♪ You can't claim
you don't care ♪
♪ 'cause I know
you're into it! ♪
♪ Go wild! Mental! Delusional! ♪
♪ It's Pop Team Epic !
Oh, yeah! ♪
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
We've got some time.
Let's check our fortunes now!
[POPUKO squeals]
Screen shot time!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
When I see a jagged speech
bubble in manga, it kills me.
What?
[POPUKO grunts]
When I see a jagged speech
bubble in a manga, it kills me.
What?
When I see a jagged speech
bubble in a manga, it kills me.
What?!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[SERVER A]
Here you go, girls, enjoy.
I'mma Instagram this.
[POPUKO grunting]
Stop, you're ruining it.
[POPUKO squeaking]
[POPUKO]
Ha! Ha!
Boom, boom!
[POPUKO flubbing]
[NARRATOR barking]
[NARRATOR]
Bob Epic Team .
You wanna play hide-and-seek?
Okay.
And-a-one, and-a-two,
and-a-three,
and-a-four, and-a-five.
[PIPIMI]
Ahh!
--Ready or not!
--[PIPIMI] Not ready yet.
Ready or not!
[PIPIMI]
Not ready yet.
Ready or not!
[PIPIMI]
Come find me! Come find me!
Come fi--
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Here. You little
birdies want a snack?
[BIRDS]
Yeah!
♪♪♪
[BIRDS sighing]
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
♪ Little bunny Foo-foo, walkin'
through the forest. Scoop... ♪
♪ Little bunny Foo-foo,
walkin' through the-- ♪
[GIRL A gasps]
[POPUKO]
Don't sing over me!
[PIPIMI] Chill out,
she's singing in rounds!
Hurry, run away!
[GIRL A screaming]
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[BOTH laughing]
[PIPIMI]
Hold up. Think about this.
What happens if I become
a woman tomorrow,
like, before you do?
[SOSOGU]
It's me, Sosogu Hoshifuri!
The manager is really sick!
That means Daichi has to
come in and be the boss,
with just a moment's notice!
What'll I do? I'm nervous!
Hoshiiro Girldrop ,
Episode Three:
"Daichi is the New Manager?"
Fall in love with us
again next week!
[MASTER HERO] Be careful!
The Demon King approaches!
[COMPANIONS]
Yeah!
[DEMON KING laughs]
[DEMON KING]
I am impressed that you've
come this far, weaklings.
I applaud your efforts.
[COMPANION C]
Master Hero!
Allow me to use my summoning
magic to defeat him!
[MASTER HERO]
Yes, I'm counting on you!
[COMPANION C] Oh, two-headed
dragon from beyond,
I implore you to appear
and fight on our behalf!
Messenger from across the abyss.
Twin Elemental Dragon!
What's this crap?
The animation isn't
even completed yet.
It's like they put all their
resources into episode one,
then they ran outta gas.
[DEMON KING laughs]
[DEMON KING]
I am the Demon King.
Scary! Ha-ha.
[COMPANION D]
Do something!
You're the beast she
summoned from beyond!
Shut up! Your face
isn't even drawn in.
[COMPANION C] I'm not worthy!
My summoning magic has failed!
Yeah, I agree. You suck!
Well, what can you do?
Hero guy, you can
do comedy, right?
[MASTER HERO gasps]
If it's not hilarious,
you're toast.
Oh. Okay. I do a good donkey.
[yelling, grunting]
What?
What was that? For real?
Well, lady, what you got?
[COMPANION C gasps]
Do it!
Uh. Okay.
"Hey, there, Boo-boo!"
"Yabba-dabba-doo!"
"Hasta la vista, baby!"
And you get paid
for stuff like that?
Talk about an easy job.
Yeah, I agree! You suck!
[SEIYUU A]
Cut!
[SEIYUU B]
I can't take it anymore.
[SEIYUU A] Stop this!
Get in here now, please!
Hey! Mr. Producer Man!
What the hell is up with this
ridiculous anime, you dumb jerk?
This girl is traumatized.
She's never done comedic
impressions in her life!
Let's go. Time to go
home. We're done here.
Gimme those glasses,
dummy. Keep away!
[PRODUCER A]
Not my glasses!
[SEIYUU A]
Time for keep away!
Oh, look, I'm the producer now!
[DEMON KING]
Did you see it?
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[POPUKO]
Pop Team Epic is shit!
[PIPIMI] Constructive
criticism only. Don't--
[POPUKO] Zero percent!
Zero percent! Zero percent!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Bob Epic Team .
[BOTH]
Can't wait to see the panda!
A panda!
[POPUKO]
So cute!
A koala!
[POPUKO]
So cute!
--A panda!
--Seen it.
A koala!
Seen it.
--A Tasmanian tiger!
--[POPUKO] So cute!
--A wombat.
--[POPUKO] So cute.
A dingo.
Don't care.
--A wallaby.
--[POPUKO] So cute.
A wombat.
Seen it.
A Tasmanian devil!
Nuh-uh. We haven't seen
a Tasmanian devil yet.
[POPUKO]
Oops, my bad.
[BOTH laughing]
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Beach day!
Okay!
The Machu Picchu of Japan!
[PIPIMI]
Can't do that.
Set's not done, so we
can't go there yet.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
No one can compete
with my smile!
Oh? Can you
compete with mine?
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[BOTH] ♪ Every day,
you turn your face from me ♪
♪ and look the other way. ♪
♪ What the fuck? What are
you so preoccupied with? ♪
♪ Look at me! ♪
♪ You act like you
just don't notice ♪
♪ that I'm so
in love with you. ♪
♪ Seriously, you're
fucking rude. ♪
♪ How do you sleep at night?! ♪
♪ Your taste is irrelevant! ♪
♪ It might be mainstream! ♪
♪ Even if you quibble about
the best subculture, ♪
♪ everyone still
thinks you're dumb! ♪
♪ Just let me show you
my Pop Technique! ♪
♪ Feel my love through
♪ Don't let it scare you! ♪
♪ I'll give you such a thrill,
like you've never felt before! ♪
♪ Niche love stabs you
right through your heart! ♪
♪ Let it impale you! ♪
♪ You can't claim
you don't care ♪
♪ 'cause I know
you're into it! ♪
♪ Go wild! Mental! Delusional! ♪
♪ It's Pop Team Epic !
Oh, yeah! ♪
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
We've got some time left.
Let's check our fortunes now!
[POPUKO]
Mh-hm!
Screen shot time!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
When I see jagged speech
bubbles in manga, it kills me.
What?
[POPUKO mumbling]
What?!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[SERVER A]
Here you go, girls, enjoy.
I'mma Instagram this.
Shew-shew.
Stop, you're ruining it.
[POPUKO grunting]
Hyo-ho!
Hyah-hyah!
[POPUKO yelling]
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Bob Epic Team .
You wanna play hide-and-seek?
Okay.
And-a-one, and-a-two,
and-a-three,
and-a-four, and-a-five.
[PIPIMI]
Aah!
--Ready or not!
--[PIPIMI] Not ready yet.
Ready or not!
[PIPIMI]
Not ready yet.
Ready or not!
[PIPIMI]
Come find me! Come find me!
Come fi--
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Here, you little
birdies want a snack?
[BIRDS]
Yeah!
♪♪♪
[BIRDS sighing]
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
♪ Little bunny Foo-foo, walkin'
through the forest, scoop-- ♪
♪ Little bunny Foo-foo,
walkin' through the-- ♪
[POPUKO]
Don't sing over me!
[PIPIMI] Chill out,
she's singing in rounds!
Hurry, run away!
[GIRL A screaming]
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[BOTH laughing]
Hold up. Think about this.
What happens if I become
a woman tomorrow,
like, before you do?
[POPUKO]
Eh?
[SOSOGU]
It's me, Sosogu Hoshifuri!
The manager is really sick!
That means that Daichi has
to come in and be the boss,
with just a moment's notice!
What'll I do? I'm nervous!
Hoshiiro Girldrop ,
Episode Three:
"Daichi is the New Manager?"
Fall in love with
us again next week!