[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[PLATYPUS sighs]
I feel so depressed.
Sounds like you need
Pop Team Therapy!
Stupid.
Oh, I see. You're a damn hater!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
♪ Hater, you're a good boy. ♪
♪ Now, go to sleep. ♪
That hater does not
deserve your kindness!
[POPUKO]
♪ Fanboy, you're a good boy. ♪
♪ Now, go to sleep. ♪
Hater and fanboy
of what, though?
Nutria?
I got scolded at
career counseling
'cause I strive to be a paladin.
Touching documentary:
"Hellshake Yano."
Tokyo's Big Budokan.
Our antihero is about to make
his first big appearance
in this venerable arena.
[STORYBOARD ACTOR A]
How do you feel?
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B]
Move it! Heh. Okay.
Doodalie-doodalie-doodalie-doo.
Well, honestly, I'm
totally amped up. Ha-ha.
[STORYBOARD ACTOR A]
Emergency!
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B]
Manager!
[STORYBOARD ACTOR A]
The trains have stopped running!
the band won't be able to make
it to the Budokan in time!
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B]
Uh! What'll we do?
[STORYBOARD ACTOR A]
We will be forced to cancel
this epic concert.
Wait! Wait! Don't panic now!
Hold onto hope. I refuse
to give in just yet!
Click.
Right, until the others arrive,
I'll hold the audience captive
with my super-fast guitar solo!
Yeah!
[STORYBOARD ACTOR A yells]
Yano's legendary battle
against himself
in the big Budokan begins.
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B]
Time to rock!
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B grunting]
[STORYBOARD ACTOR A]
Whoa!
Check out that super-fast
guitar solo, guys!
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B] A regular
guitar solo just won't do today!
I must play faster!
I cannot slow down!
But Yano's speed-picking
reaches a fever pitch,
and he just can't
maintain the intensity.
Faster and faster!
I gotta play faster!
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B]
Toink!
Ah! My guitar string, it--!
It just snapped!
Is this the end?
Is it over for me?
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B]
No! There is hope!
Five strings left!
All hope is not yet lost!
I won't admit defeat
till I'm dead!
Tuning it to 11!
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B]
Which will snap first:
The five remaining strings,
or will it be Yano's arm?
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B yelling]
[STORYBOARD ACTOR A]
It's hell fire.
Yano is rocking with
the fiery heart of hell.
He's the man who shakes hell.
Hellshake Yano, yeah!
Hellshake! Hellshake!
Hellshake. Hellshake. Hellshake!
[BOTH]
Hell...
Hell... Shake!
[BOTH]
Hellshake. Hellshake. Hellshake.
Hey, are you listening?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was just thinking about
Hellshake Yano.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[GIRL A] Subculture bitch
on board, bitches!
[POPUKO]
Take that! And that.
And that!
[PIPIMI]
Oh, yeah!
[POPUKO] You saved me from
that bitch! Thank you!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[POPUKO]
Peek-a! You can't see me!
It's so dark in here!
I'm the one who can't see!
That was a flawlessly
cute performance.
Thank you so very much!
Now, execute him.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[POPUKO yelling]
[POPUKO]
I turned into a baby!
Baby-baby-baby, baby,
baby, baby, baby, baby,
baby, baby, ba--
[POPUKO]
But...
...I'm anxious.
What if we don't go to
the same high school?
I'll wait for you
forever if I must.
Oh, Pipimi!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[CHILDREN]
Pop Team Cooking!
Pop Team...
...Cooking!
Here we have 100%
hamburger meat!
What? It's not a blend
of pork and beef?
Of course not!
Here, everything is 100%!
We also have 100% manatee!
Here I go.
--Yeah. Go!
--You ready?
[POPUKO]
Done!
Here it is, guys!
A fully compressed
100% manatee!
[POPUKO, PIPIMI]
See you all next week!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[speaking French]
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[MAN]
Extreme Bicycle Mount!
[POPUKO]
Whoop!
[gasps]
[POPUKO]
Whoopsie!
Goosed ya!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
There, there.
There, the--
[POPUKO laughing]
[NARRATOR]
Goo, goo, goo, gah, gah, goo.
Nothing's biting.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[POPUKO]
I got a seaweed hat.
[PIPIMI yells]
I caught a big one, huh?
[POPUKO gasps]
[POPUKO] Looks just
like you, Pipimi!
[POPUKO, PIPIMI laughing]
[PIPIMI, FISH]
What'd you say?
[NARRATOR]
Pop ...!
Eff this [beep]!
I'll never play this
dumbass game again.
Ugh. My clavicle hurts.
Ugh...
Done with this [beep]!
[SOSOGU]
It's me, Sosogu Hoshifuri.
The Super Live Fest
is next month,
and I'm appearing
with Devil Volcano!
But artistic differences
cause a major clash!
Then Daichi steps in to mediate.
Will we go Torch Ballad
or Metal Core anthem?
Should the majority rule here?
Hoshiiro Girldrop ,
Episode Eight:
"Drop Stars, Disbanding Crisis?"
Fall in love with us
again next week!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Peam Ep -- Ugh! Damn it!
[PLATYPUS sighs]
I feel so depressed.
Sounds like you need
Pop Team Therapy!
Stupid.
Oh, I see.
You're a damn hater!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
♪ Hater, you're a good boy. ♪
♪ Now, go to sleep. ♪
That hater does not
deserve your kindness!
[POPUKO]
♪ Fanboy, you're a good boy. ♪
♪ Now, go to sleep. ♪
♪ Hater and fanboy of
what are they, though? ♪
Nutria!
I got scolded at
career counseling
'cause I strive to be a paladin.
Touching documentary:
"Hellshake Yano."
Tokyo's Big Budokan.
Our antihero is about to make
his first big appearance
in this venerable arena.
How do you feel? Move it.
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B]
Spinny-spinny-spinny-spinny...
Well, honestly,
I'm totally amped up!
[STORYBOARD ACTOR A]
Emergency!
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B]
Manager?
[STORYBOARD ACTOR A]
The trains have stopped running.
The band won't be able to make
it to the Budokan in time!
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B]
What'll we do?
[STORYBOARD ACTOR A]
We will be forced to cancel
this epic concert.
Wait! Wait! Don't panic now!
Hold onto hope. I refuse
to give in just yet!
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B] Right then,
until the others arrive,
I'll hold the audience captive
with my super-fast guitar solo!
[BOTH cheering]
[STORYBOARD ACTOR A yells]
Yano's legendary
battle against himself
in the big Budokan begins.
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B]
Time to rock!
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B grunting]
[STORYBOARD ACTOR A]
Whoa!
Check out that super-fast
guitar solo, guys!
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B] A regular
guitar solo just won't do today!
I must play faster!
I cannot slow down!
But Yano's speed-picking
reaches a fever pitch,
and he just can't
maintain the intensity.
Faster and faster!
I've gotta play faster!
Boing.
Uh! My guitar string, it--!
It just snapped!
Is this the end?
Is it over for me?
No! There is hope!
Five strings left!
All hope is not yet lost!
I won't admit defeat
till I'm dead!
Tuning it to 11!
[STORYBOARD ACTOR B]
Which will snap first:
The remaining five strings,
or will it be Yano's arm?
[STORYBOARD ACTOR A]
It's hell fire.
Yano's rocking with
the fiery heart of hell.
He's the man who shakes hell.
Hellshake Yano, yeah!
Hellshake, y'all.
Hellshake! Hellshake!
Hellshake. Hellshake. Hellshake!
[BOTH]
Hell...
Hell... Shake!
[BOTH] Hellshake. Hellshake.
Hellshake. Hellshake.
Hey, you listening?
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was just thinking
about Hellshake Yano.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[GIRL A] Subculture bitch
on board, bitches!
[PIPIMI]
Oh, yeah!
[POPUKO]
You saved me from that bitch!
Thank you!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[POPUKO]
Peek-a. Peek-a.
It's so dark in here!
Who turned out the lights?
Such a flawlessly
cute performance.
Thank you so very much.
Now, execute him.
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[POPUKO]
I...
...turned into a baby!
Baby, baby, baby, baby,
baby, baby, baby?!
What if we don't end up going
to the same high school?
I'll wait for you
forever if I must.
Oh, Pipimi!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[CHILDREN]
Pop Team Cooking!
Pop Team...
...Cooking!
Here we have 100%
hamburger meat!
What? It's not a blend
of pork and beef?
Of course not.
On this show, we do things 100%!
This is 100% manatee!
[POPUKO] Where there's
a will, there's a way.
[PIPIMI]
Yes, you can do it!
[POPUKO]
Yep.
[PIPIMI]
Yep!
--Here...
--...I...
--...go!
--Go!
One.
Two!
Three.
[BOTH]
Done!
Here it is! This is
a compressed Manatee!
[POPUKO, PIPIMI]
See you next week!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[speaking French]
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[MAN]
Extreme Bicycle Mount!
[POPUKO]
Hm?
[gasps]
[chuckles]
[POPUKO]
Oopsie!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
There, there.
There, the--
One, two, three!
[POPUKO]
Pop Team Epic .
[PIPIMI]
Hmm...
Nothing's biting.
[POPUKO]
Look at me go!
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
[PIPIMI]
God of the sea!
I caught a big one, huh?
[POPUKO]
Ah!
Looks just like you, Pipimi!
[ALL laughing]
[PIPIMI, FISH]
Say what now?
[NARRATOR]
Pop Team Epic .
Eff this [beep]!
I'll never play this
dumbass game again.
Tch. It's turning my world dark.
Ugh.
Done with this [beep]!
[SOSOGU]
It's me, Sosogu Hoshifuri.
The Super Live Fest
is next month,
and I'm appearing
with Devil Volcano!
But artistic differences
cause a major clash!
Then Daichi steps in to mediate.
Will we go Torch Ballad
or Metal Core anthem?
Should the majority rule here?
Hoshiiro Girldrop ,
Episode Eight:
"Drop Stars, Disbanding Crisis?"
Fall in love with us
again next week!