Franca!
How's it going over there?
Fine, I'm almost done here.
Okay.
It's opening up now!
We did it!
OK, so where are we
going now, Inspector?
To the Graceland gate of course.
Shouldn't we get
permission to do that first?
Somehow I get the feeling
that Mister isn't going
to be asking anyone
for permission.
Duh!
You finally figured that out?!
We've got the
gate open, so move it!
Boss!
Trouble here!
We've got Guild
fighters on our ass!
You've gotta be kidding me!
The rendezvous's impossible!
We're gonna get blown
to bits off if I slow down!
I'm out!
At least, I THINK so...
Bishop!
Over here!
Sons of bitches!
Deploy the Guild Skies
immediately.
Right away, Mother.
Attention!
Launch Guild Skies!
Now.
Let's bring this to
a finish, my darlings.
Yes, Mother Dear.
Holy shit!
Here they come!
Well, what do
we do now, Mister?!
Like I told ya,
you just bust through the
gate if you get noticed!
Okay, what's going on here?
My sisters are here.
Huh?
And Mister!
Wait, Angelica!
What the hell?
Hey, Katana!
Where the hell are you?
It's time to rendezvous!
Where am I?
Jeez, gimme a minute...
Hey Swamp, are you ready yet?
Keep your shirt on!
This is my first time
playin' with this damn toy!
Okay, I could use
a pickup any time now.
It's time to hunt down
the coyotes, girls.
We're going to
split into two teams.
March, June, August,
January, engage their ship.
I'll be going after Mister.
January!
After what he did
to Sep, Mister's mine!
Let's get 'em!
Careful!
Bishop!
Katana!
Do you read me?
Can't make you out, Mister!
Boss!
Where are you?!
Damn!
I KNEW it!
Hey, where are you going now?!
Dammit Coyote, answer me!
Mister!
Hey, Katana!
Mister, it's me.
It's Katana!
Yeah, we established that.
Where are you?
Well, let's have a look here...
I, uh...
WHOA!
We're headed up, Mister!
I found a way up!
Up where?
What do you mean
by "up", Katana?
Hey, it's Bishop!
You're still alive!
Obviously, now come
and get me already.
Where the hell
are you guys, anyway?
I'm a few seconds away
from the marketplace.
Okay!
We'll meet up
in the marketplace!
I'm countin' on ya.
We made it!
And we're alive!
You won't get away...
MISTER!!!
Have some of this!
Damn!
Mister's luck
is about to run out!
We're punchin' outta here!
Damn I'm good!
Attention: This is an
emergency announcement.
We ask that all customers please
evacuate as quickly as possible.
Repeat, this is an emergency...
Yo!
I could sure use some
fire support there
"mister right--hand man!"
Dammit!
It's been a while,
and I'm kinda rusty!
So get off my ass, will ya?
Pretty good!
Swamp!
We've got company!
Now where in the world
are they hiding?
What a bother...
we'll have to destroy
the buildings, too.
Huh?
Whoa...
What the hell are they doing?
Holy crap!
They're gonna
bury our asses alive!
Are they tryin'
to kill everyone?!
April!
You probably shouldn't
stand so close.
Booby trapped?
That's just Mister's
way of entertaining us.
Aw!
That didn't make 'em any
easier to find at all!
Come on, don't even act
like you didn't wanna do it.
They're persistent little
buggers, aren't they?
Coyote.
Do you read?
There you are!
Bishop, it's the Coyote!
Katana?
I'm in the marketplace's
central plaza right now.
Where are you?
Hiding between
a couple of buildings.
Damn death--girls are
still chasin' after us.
Oh, you're breaking my heart.
Now how about a lift?
Roger.
I'll see what I can do.
I've finished hacking the
surveillance system, Mother.
Coyotes detected in the central
plaza and section A--3.
En route to the marketplace.
Be sure to inform April.
Yes, Mother.
Mister, you're running
out of places to hide.
He's where?
You heard that, January?
One step ahead you,
sister--dear.
Coyote, can you read me?
Coyote!
Huh?
Damn you, Mister!
We have to go, January.
Mister, you okay down there?
Gimme a second while
I bring the Coyote down.
Man, we were sure in demand up
until a minute ago, weren't we?
Lucky for us, it looks
like the tide's going out.
Hey, what's happening, Mister?
Franca, Katana!
Get outta here!
Just get the hell out!
Fire!
February.
Get my ship ready.
We'll do it right away, Mother.
Your ship, Mother?
I want to have
a little chat with Mister.
Franca...
Franca!
Hey Mister!
Mister!
Franca!
Are you all right?
Wait for me!
I'll be right there!
Mm--hmm!
NO...!
Do you feel lucky?
Mister?
What's going on?
Who's shooting over there?
So, she's right
over there, isn't she?
And...
what if she is...?
Mister...
Papa...
I haven't seen you
since that day.
You look well, and that's
what's most important.
I have some business to attend
to with your "guardian."
Where is he?
Is that Marciano?
Right here, Mother.
Oh.
It looks like
we've found him...
Are you all right?
Say something!
Franca!
I've already
disabled him, Mother.
Quite impressive work, April.
God damn it!
Don't you lay a hand on her!
I'll make you pay, bitch!
I wouldn't dream
of touching this child.
Provided YOU tell me everything
you know about Bruce's legacy
and where it is.
If you'd like,
I can shoot him again.
May I, Mother?
No.
I doubt it would
help anything, April.
Looks like I'm out of choices.
I'd rather conduct my business
in a more tasteful fashion,
but...
MARCIANO!
Well, well, this
looks so familiar.
Mister, if this girl's
life means anything to you...
Look - just leave
Mister alone...
I'll tell you.
Oh, really?
You have to promise me!
No, Franca!
She'll betray you the
first chance she gets!
Mister!
Here it is.
The secret of my father's
legacy is inside this pendant.
Franca, no...
You better keep your promise.
Yes.
But I've decided that you're
coming with me to Graceland.
No!
Stop it!
Let me go!
Franca!
Marciano, you bitch!
I'll tear your friggin...!
Hey I thought we had a deal
you were gonna spare my life,
remember?
Guess I missed that part
of the conversation.
Well don't worry
yer pretty head.
I wasn't expectin' a BREAK!
Mister!
April.
Come back to the ship.
Yes, Mother.
Give the poor man his space.
After all, he just lost
his best friend's treasure
and that best friend's
daughter all in one day.
I wonder which is worse?
Stop right there!
I'm gonna borrow this
for a little bit.
That was just a warning.
I'm trying to stop you, damn it.
Otherwise you'll get
killed out there.
I promised her.
I told her...
that I was taking
her to Graceland!
You mind hoppin' out for me?
I'm sorry.
It's true coyotes
don't run in packs.
But even so.
They don't betray family,
no matter what.
Even if it kills 'em!
Both your heart rate and your
body temperature escalated.
That indicates a vehement
or excited mental state.
So why didn't you shoot him?
That IS the man you've been
after for the last four years,
right?
Angelica...?
Mister?
Do you read me?
Yeah, yeah I can
hear ya just fine.
You OK?
I'm peachy.
We've hit snag or two here,
but we oughta be able
to take off real soon!
OK: pressure valve...
That's not it!
Well what, then?
Marciano got
her hands on Franca.
There's no way in hell
I'm gonna leave behind!
I wonder what kind of secret
this could possibly hold.
We'll know soon enough...
Unidentified aircraft astern.
Mister!
What?!
That was pretty
damned reckless!
Perfect timing!
Catch 'em, Bishop!
Gotcha!
Bishop, Katana!
Just take us straight
to the Graceland gate!
Hell, yeah!
We're on our way!
You're not getting away!
We've got some more
company in front of us!
Damn it!
Shit!
So what do we do now, boss?
Mister, what's up?
Mister!
Katana!
Watch your heading!
Starboard, dammit!
What?
You sure that's the right gate?
Just get us in there!
Fire!
MISTER!!!