Bruce...
How does it feel, knowing
that I'm taking your legacy
while your daughter
gets nothing?
It's all your fault for
getting yourself killed!
Millennium Dug Mark Two.
An interstellar
transport shuttle built
by the Millennium Corporation.
Model year is...
G.C. 1992??!
That's crazy!
This was built the same year
my grampa was born!
Is this hunk of junk
even gonna launch?
Seems to be well--maintained.
Maybe if you're a fan
of garbage transports.
Are you sure they don't have
anything newer around here?
No, that would be a big waste...
Oh, really?
I don't get to work with
a vintage ride
like this every day.
Oh my God!
It says you can adjust the
speed of descent manually!!!
Check it out, May!
Here I was...
thinking I was malfunctioning.
Chelsea!
Got a sec?
What is it, Inspector?
Would you mind helping me
load these onto the shuttle?
All of those boxes are FOOD?!
Uh--huh.
Boy, Franca sure seemed
broken up, didn't she?
Yeah, she shoulda known that she
didn't have to worry about us,
ya know?
I imagine...
she just grew bitter living
with us grown--up Coyotes
and not having
any kids to be with.
And that's why...
when we finish this job,
I'm gonna try and give
the kid her childhood back.
Main engines optimal.
Descent point
coordinates are set.
All sections green.
All systems operating normally.
Then it seems we're ready.
Take us down.
Courier approaching Gate 7: You
are clear for docking manuvers.
I'm carrying written orders
for Admiral Malcolm
from Fleet Admiral Mill.
Outstanding.
By carrier pigeon, huh?
Yes, sir.
I take it all the cross--talk,
scuttlebutt and jamming signals
made it necessary to
deliver these orders by hand?
This mission demands an
extremely strict adherence
to the Federation
manual, Admiral.
And a leak of any portion
of this information
would be catastrophic.
Yes, I guess you're right.
Admiral Malcolm, I have
some good news for you.
General Boniek of the Graceland
Liberation Forces has agreed
to a last--minute cease--fire
to negotiate a peace treaty.
We're getting ready
for this under the table,
if you follow me...
Good.
Looks like we're not going
through with it after all.
Right.
Regardless, I'll still need
you to continue on your course
for Graceland.
I'm concerned that there might
be other factions who won't
take so kindly to our
settling the issue with Boniek
"behind the scenes,"
if you will.
So you're saying there might
be a backlash from either side,
then?
Possibly.
With that in mind, the
negotiations with Boniek
and his people
will be on your ship.
Senator Hewlett, the
Secretary for Foreign Affairs,
is already en route
to meet you.
Yes, go ahead.
Sir, we just received word
from the Graceland patrol fleet
that a single Guild battleship
is descending to the surface.
A Guild battleship?
Okay then.
So what do we do
about this, sir?
Damn.
Why now?
Are they selling weapons?
Or did Boniek's people call
them in to stir things up?
So they're engaging
in peace talks to buy time
for a counteroffensive?
Well, we can't afford to
take provocative action;
dropping a bomb or not.
Tell the patrol fleet
not to intercept them.
Yes, sir.
So you're really going to
Graceland after all, are you?
Absolutely.
And thanks a lot
for the shuttle!
It sure is cool!
Well I'm speechless.
I thought giving you that
old scrap heap would surely
make you give up.
We appreciate it.
You should also know that
a Guild battleship went down
to the surface
a little while ago.
And did the fleet fire on them?
No, the Federation
didn't engage them at all.
It's more like they just
wave at 'em going by.
That tells me...
They're still
dropping the bomb.
Otherwise they wouldn't
have let them pass.
Meaning that
they're not going
to affect the
outcome of the war.
I'd agree with that assessment.
And you're still going to
drop into the middle of that?
Yes.
I still have a man to catch.
Descent speed optimal.
60 seconds to arrival
at destination point.
Visibility good.
Landing area clear.
We have touchdown
at the destination point.
Prepare for ground operations.
All right then...
It's time to start
this treasure hunt.
Oh, man...
Marciano and her goons
are probably digging up
the whole planet by now.
Hey!
Shut up, will ya?
You're makin' me wonder
why we're even doing this
in the first place.
Damn, this is so frustrating!
Ah, those greedy bitches ain't
gonna find Bruce's legacy.
In case you've
already forgotten...
They've got Bruce's eye,
not us, Pops!
So what if they've
got Bruce's eye?
They're still not
gonna find anything.
Oh?
You seem pretty damn sure
of yourself all of a sudden.
You said it yourself, kid,
when you saw the video.
Graceland didn't seem like
the same planet at all, did it?
Yeah, I said it
"looked" different.
Yeah, well, it's more
than just looks.
Compared to what you saw in
that video, Graceland is now...
far different
than what it was before.
We can't possibly determine
from the video data where
the cave containing
the Gigabanks is now.
How can...
you possibly eat
at a time like this!
I mean...
don't you get motion--sickness?
Nah.
I'm used to eating
inside ships, ya know?
With an iron stomach like that,
you're sure to be
all right out there.
Even if...
something...
goes wrong...
We're going to miss our
designated landing point
by a few clicks.
A few clicks?
How many?
Well, to be honest, I really
don't know how far off...
Wait a minute!
How can you possibly
not know that?
Come on!
This is my first manual
descent, Inspector!!!
June's team is starting
their search of sector B--6
and January's team is
moving to sector D--4.
April's team has finished
with sector A--2
with no sign of the Gigabanks.
August's team has
gone over sector E--1,
still with no sign of the vault.
And March's team has completed
their survey of C--4
with no sign of the Gigabanks.
Next...
OK, guys, listen up...
The only way we're gonna
get a leg up on searching for
the treasure is to do something
about that bomb on our own.
One step ahead of you, boss.
You want to have a team
to board the Jupiter
and another team to start
looking for the Gigabanks.
Am I right?
That's right.
Here's the thing.
Even if we stop this bomb
from going off it won't
make any difference if
Marciano beats us there.
Thought of that, too.
We can't expose Franca to the
hazards on that ship, right?
Katana needs
to pilot the Coyote.
And the old fart here
knows all about the vault.
And that leaves me.
Which is fine,
because I can handle it.
I just need to stop the
photonic bomb, am I right?
Well, Bishop.
I'm glad ya thought this out.
But actually, I want you
on the Jupiter, too.
Him?
There's a change in plans.
You'll be goin' with Swamp.
Now wait a minute, Mister!
He'll slow me down!
I ain't bringin' that old fart!
Hey, keep your
diaper on, crybaby!
Look.
I'm gonna handle this my way.
That's what I'm worried
about, ya damn punk!
Stop sniping at me,
you shrub--headed freak!
Are you sure this is
a good idea, boss--man?
Of course it is.
Just look.
Those two are havin'
the time of their lives.
Huh?
Wha?
You are pissin' me off, you
damn Bride of Frankenstein!
Y'aint no walk
in the park either, dipshit!
I'm gonna take some sheep
shears to your skull, old man!
An' I'm gonna yank out them
two chest hairs and beat you
to death with 'em!
Hey, Angelica!
I figured out where we are!
Well?
45 degrees North
by 160 degrees East.
I guess we're at this point
on the Paralla Ocean.
Comparing that to our
intended landing site...
we're pretty far away from where
Marciano and her people landed.
Sorry.
It's all right.
As long as we get there
before Mister touches down.
Inspector.
Is he really gonna show up?
I'm counting on it.
If that's true...
this guy Mister
is way--optimistic.
That's right.
As long as he has
ANY chance, he'll take it.
He's not gonna quit.
It's his crazy side
that makes him strong.
That man is a true a Coyote!
Yep, you got it.
You see, I'm learning...
It sounds to me like
she kinda LIKES the guy...
Well, shall we get going?
Sure!
Uh, Angelica...
Those people are
evacuating, aren't they?
Yeah.
At this point, it's looking like
"get out, or get blown to bits."
So...
you think we'll find
the Jupiter in time?
You don't know who you're
talkin' to, little lady!
That's right!
They don't have a jammin' signal
out there that we can't crack!
I mean, come on--you're
talkin' to Master Katana here!
March's team has
arrived in sector C--2.
June's team has
finished up with B--3.
No sign of the Gigabanks.
January is finished with D--5.
Again, no sign
of the Gigabanks.
April's team is done with A--4.
No sign there, either.
My...
at this rate we may very well
end up having to search every
last nook and cranny on the
entire planet, don't you think?
Got somethin' on your mind,
preacher--man?
You pretend to be
all miserable.
But you're not foolin' anybody.
You enjoy
getting' on his nerves.
What?
You mean Bishop?
He's a dopey kid.
Admit it -- you're
havin' fun with him.
You're the only one
havin' fun with it.
C'mon...
You know you're
enjoying yourself.
I wasn't lookin'
for a joy ride.
This whole deal with Gigabanks.
How can you not enjoy it, man?
I'm havin' the time of my life.
Well good for you!
You know, you're really startin'
to piss me off, actin' like
you can just make decisions
for me and I'll just lay down
and do it for ya...
Yeah, but you're gonna.
Swamp, we have to stop
the bombing, all right?
That ain't easy,
and he needs help.
I can't send him alone.
Yeah, I get it.
Much as you claim
to hate all this,
it makes me wonder why you even
wanna go in the first place.
The reason I'm going is to
see for myself whether or not
you're the man who should
inherit Bruce's legacy, okay?
Guess we'll see.
Got a question for you.
Go 'head.
Shoot.
Bruce called you the
night before he pulled
the Gigabanks job.
What exactly did he tell you?
Not a thing.
Lemme ask you...
Fire away.
Tell me...
all I wanna know
is whether Bruce enjoyed
his last big heist.
Need a hand, there?
No, I'm good,
but thanks anyway.
It's pretty much done over here.
All right.
Say, Franca.
You looking forward
to the treasure?
Well...
I'm not sure.
What do you think you'd do
with 10 billion space dollars?
I never really
thought about it...
With that money,
you could buy anything
your little heart desires.
Honestly, the money doesn't
interest me that much.
I'd really like
to know more about Papa...
my family.
Everybody calls him the Pirate
King and says how amazing
and talented he was...
But I never really got
to know him as a person.
And I certainly didn't have much
experience with him as a father.
Maybe...
if I get to the treasure I
can find out for myself what
kind of person he really was.
That's another
Guild helicopter.
All that buzzing around
has got me thinking.
They haven't even come close
to finding the treasure yet.
Makes you wonder what the
treasure is, doesn't it?
I guess.
Don't you wanna
find out what it is?
Eventually.
What difference
does it make, anyway?
It might give me a motive.
It wouldn't make sense
for Mister to go through
all this just for money.
There has to be
something else at work.
And I intend to find out what.
Are you really only doing
this because it's your job?
I've been wanting
to ask you this for a while...
Is there a special reason
you started going after Mister
in the first place, Inspector?
I mean, you started
investigating him
four years ago, right...?
Look at that!
The bounty went up again!
I wouldn't be so damned
laid back about it.
You know bounty hunters
all over the place are gonna
want a piece of that action.
What about that one?
Yep!
That'll do.
Thanks for your business!
But this check is for too much!
Well now.
That depends on
what I'm buying.
I know you've got more than
spaceships for sale here.
Well, I dunno...
C'mon, you've done it before.
I can't be positive...
but the Guild is digging up
Graceland like the whole planet
was made of platinum
or somethin', you know?
Yeah...?
And there's
a rumor going around...
A group of Federation
government bigwigs
is headed over to
Graceland right now.
So tell me who's the
biggest wig on board?
That'd be Senator Hewlett...
What?
I can take it, can't I?
Sure thing.
Once I get my money's worth.
Well.
We catch anything?
Not yet.
Let's give it another minute.
Whatcha doin' there, huh?
It's an all--directions
broadcast that forces
repeater stations
to reply back to us.
And then, we look to see
exactly who's answering.
And it's juuuust
like Mister said.
There's an area right there
that isn't returning anything.
I'm guessing there's a huge
jamming net over the whole area.
That, and I just talked
to a little bird.
Says there are carrier pigeons
flying all over the place.
Wait, you can't be serious.
The Feds jam the living
crap out of everything when
they have mission like this.
So not only does the ENEMY
not hear anything,
THEY don't hear anything either.
And that means, all classified
orders get delivered by hand.
Then that means the
rumor about all of those
government officials
being on their way
to Graceland could be...
More than a rumor, it's true.
I see...
Yep.
That's what I'm sayin'.
So even if Katana and I try
to hack into the Federation's
military information network,
there won't be anything
to dig out of there because of
the information security rules.
Wow, it looks like the two
of you finally got it together
for a change.
Watch it, squirt!
Looks like it's time for us
to get this show on the road.
Here.
What is that for?
If you're comin' with me,
you're gonna need a piece'
Course an old fart
like you might not be able
to handle something new
and improved like this...
There you go again, making
up for your lack of manhood
with your mouth and your toys.
Amazing!
After all this time,
he's still got it!
I'll do what you ask...
this time.
Fine by me.
And I'm probably gonna have
to listen to one a'yer sermons
when you get back.
Bet your ass.
Just remember we're
countin' on ya so don't go
screwing this up
for us, you guys.
Yeah.
Don't go screwin' it up!
Sure thing, kid.
Count on us!
We're about to run out
of time here, people.
Let's get this
show on the road!
Did you send for us...
Mother?
I have an errand for you.
There they are...
The Twelve Sisters.
Hey, Mister.
Yeah?
What's on your mind, kid?
I was just thinking--you were
right when you said that dealing
with the bomb on his own would
have been tough for Bishop,...
but are you gonna be okay
without Swamp to help you out
at the Gigabanks?
He said so himself.
Graceland's almost a completely
different planet, now.
It's not gonna
be easy, ya know...
Ah, don't worry--we'll
probably figure something out.
"Probably"?
All right, we're ready to go.
I'm right here with ya, kid.
Lookin' good...
ya old fart.
You want me to
give you a "sermon?"
Hey, Mister...
Swamp sent this.
Is that a compass?
Yeah...
So why didn't he just
give it to you himself
instead of asking me?
What's that?
Swamp give ya a parting gift?
Yeah.
It's our map.
Straight to the Gigabanks!
All right!
They're off.
We're counting on you!
Don't screw up you guys!
Be careful!