For interfering with my plans,
I'm going to destroy
you here and now.
It's time for the two of us
to have one last party...
Mister!
Listen to me, Marciano!
Bruce's legacy of ten billion
space dollars is in here!
You let us leave in one piece,
and you can have
every penny of it!
You hear me?
And I suppose you want to
leave BEFORE the bomb goes off?
Figured that one out, did ya?
Sounds to me like you were after
something more than money,
weren't you?
With all the little dolls
you brought with you,
I'd say you have a fair bet
on getting it all outta here.
A business deal is something
that happens when each party
has something the other one
wants, but I'm not willing
to give you what you're after.
This is BRUCE'S LEGACY, honey!
I have come here
to settle a score.
Huh, why doesn't
that surprise me?
And it appears you successfully
settled one of your own.
But I'm going to kill you.
I'm going to do this
with my bare hands,
and then I'll take the money.
Ready...?
Showtime!
We only have two hours
left before that photonic bomb
goes off, gentlemen.
I need answers.
Have we evacuated all of our
troops out of Graceland yet?
Mister President, we've been
informed by our commanders
in the field that
our evacuation status
currently stands at 97 percent.
Incidentally, sir, we're
also received a report
that over 300 spacecraft from
Graceland's Liberation Forces
have evacuated
the planet as well.
Did they find out about it?
But Mister President...
Is it absolutely necessary
to take this course of action?
What choice do we have?
The GLF made their bed.
Now let them lie in it.
Mister President!
We're out of alternatives here.
It was Colonel Richard's people
who destroyed the remote
control, after all.
There should be a long--range
transmitter here somewhere.
We'll split up
and search for it!
Ok, where are you?
Transmitter...
Hands in the air!
D--Don't shoot!
What are you doing here?!
Doing my job.
I was told to delete the
data from these computers.
And you are?
I'm the director
of this facility.
And who in the hell are YOU?
I am Angelica Burns, and
I'm a Federal Investigator
I'm gonna need your assistance
getting the transmitter running.
I need to contact the Federation
President right away.
You can't use the
transmitter here for that!
I'm getting on the next
transport outta here
and you should do the same!
Stop right there!
You wanna get shot?
I need to talk to
the President now!
And I said it's impossible!
Yeah, sorry, but I
happen to know better.
All Federation bases
are required to have
a direct line to
the President's office!
If I were you I'd get that
word, "impossible" out of
your vocabulary, and fast!
You wanna try me?
Mother!
I'm sorry we didn't
make it on time!
One! Two!
This place is caving in!
Mother?
What?!
Mister!
So is this really gonna
take us to Mister?
Back when he buried
the Gigabanks...
Bruce told me all the aquifers
under Godwing were connected.
So you're say this should
eventually get us there?
I aint guaranteein'
a damn thing!
But if it gets us close, we
can fake it 'till we make it.
Well looky here.
Whattya got, old man?
I'm getting a signal from
the Gigabanks right above us.
You gotta be kidding!
This can't be right.
Is the compass
broken or something?
What the hell?!
Katana!
Huh?!
The Gigabanks!
Mister and Franca!
ah this is beautiful!
Heh...
we made it!
Damn, we're good!
Yeah!
Mister!
Get in the ship, Franca!
Yeah but...
what're you gonna do?
I'll be there in
a second, so wait up.
Fine, I will!
I'm not letting you go!
Swamp!
Do it now, man!
Say your prayers.
Mother!
Are you all right?!
Looks like the tables
have turned on ya, Marciano.
You damned miserable
filthy coyotes...
have kept me from getting
what I want long enough!
At this rate, the two of us
are gonna bite the dust here.
You know that?
As long as I get to see you die,
I could really care less,
you arrogant bastard!
Well, if you're gonna be that
way about it then I've got
no choice but
to kick your ass...
you BITCH!
You "coyotes." I hate you
and everything you stand for!
If there was only another life
for me outside of the Guild...
If I'd only had what he had,
the ability to have
my own children...!
Don't you see
that when I kill you
I'll get rid of
that pain FOREVER?!
Why give in to your hatred
like that, Marciano?
You must get awfully
damn tired draggin'
all that baggage around,
isn't that right?
How dare you...
I'm not going
to let some coyote...
an animal who can barely look
after his family INSULT ME!
What a sad story.
Completely pathetic.
Mister! Watch out!
We are not animals.
We drink together!
We share our dreams!
We trust our families and risk
our lives for our friends!
And THAT...
That's who coyotes are.
Angelica Burns?!
What in the hell are
you doing on Graceland?
Mr. President, please tell me
where they buried the bomb.
We can stop this
if you tell me now.
Now wait a minute, Angelica.
Are you telling me
you know about...?
We're running out of time,
Mister President!
Angelica, even if you get to the
bomb, how are you going to...?
The coyotes will
find a way to handle it.
What are you talking about?
Just tell me, Mister President.
NOW!
Mister President, do you
remember how I got ahold
of Super Soul on Ku--Rong?
What if he found out YOU
were in the Guild once?
No!
Now let's not get too hasty,
all right, Angelica?
All you have to do is tell me
where the bomb is buried...
Mister President.
Mother.
No...
Mister!
Don't act so surprised.
You didn't think she was
gonna kill me, did you?
No.
'Course not.
Mister!
Listen to me. You
better get up here, man!
So, what's up?
Ready for a shock?
I think you're gonna like this.
Angelica?!
I found out where
they buried the bomb.
Really?!
You've got a little more
than an hour.
Make it count.
Your call.
I mean no one could blame you
if you wanted to leave
the planet right now.
So what are you
gonna do about it...
Mister?
Well I'll be damned if
you sure didn't stick us
with one big pain
the ass legacy, Bruce.
So what now?
Looks like we got
one more party to go to!
Yeah!
All right, Angel!
Where'd they bury it?
It's under Godwing
at coordinates
E--zero--zero--eight--three,
N--zero--zero--eight--zero.
Cancellation code is
E--L--V--I--S zero eight two.
Good.
Punch those in for me, Bishop.
Already on it.
Yeah?
Ata boy.
Thanks for everything,
Angelica.
Coordinates are in
the ship's mainframe.
Sending them to you, Katana!
Why's it so damn
far down there?
So what's wrong?
Scared or something?
Don't you ever doubt...
Master Katana's Super
High Speed Express!
Sunrise!
Now that's gorgeous!
We're already past the time;
aren't we, Inspector?
Looks like it.
Then it's safe to say
Mister and his gang stopped
that photonic bomb
from going off, right?
Something's approaching
off our bow, Chief!
Huh?
Could that be...?
'Fraid it is, Bishop.
You will not defeat me...
You will NOT defeat me!!!
Katana, turn us around.
What for?!
Marciano wants to settle
this up once and for all.
But...!
This'll be a one--round fight.
All right, then.
Let's go!
Marciano!
MISTER!!!
Marciano was...
she wasa coyote,
a long time ago.
But even then...
I never shared
a drink with her...
So...
the planet's really safe, huh?
All thanks to Mister's Coyotes.
Yeah that's pretty much it.
Oh, God, this situation
is so heart--breaking!
Where the heck
did that come from?
When you think about it it's
really amazing, Angelica!
They risked their lives to
save everyone and no one's
give them any credit
for it, are they?
No one at all.
People are just gonna
see them as criminals.
Oh, don't be dramatic.
I don't know about you,
but I'm starving!
You can't be serious!
These should do for now.
Huh?
When it comes
right down to it...
Mister and his coyotes saved
Graceland and everyone on it
because that's
who coyotes are.
It's really not
that complicated.
You're right.
The "Coyotes."
Has a nice ring to it.
As your President,
I accept full criticism for
the photonic bomb scare.
However, a greater truth was
served during this crisis.
The one million plus
inhabitants of Graceland
are alive and well today.
And for that reason above all,
I take pride in, and
stand by my decision.
Recent public polls indicate a
growing public approval rating
for the President's handling
of Graceland, keeping the number
of casualties to a minimum.
Hey, Katana.
Are you up for some
gold--hunting?
I heard there was 20 tons
of it that got shipwrecked
out in the middle of...
On snowy--ass mountain?!
Too cold for me, thanks.
I also heard there was
someone smuggling a Da Vinci!
Whattya say?
Paintings are more YOUR speed.
No, thanks!
Come on!
You're gonna help
my fix my church first,
after all that trouble
you caused, right?
C'mon now, Swamp.
You're not gonna begrudge us
a couple stops along the way,
are ya?
Besides, we can probably
use some of those soggy
space dollars to fix
your church afterwards.
And I just remembered
a legendary whiskey
on a planet called Scotch!
One case left!
Aged in a barrel
just like the old days;
ya can't tell me that you
don't wanna drink some of that!
Whiskey?
So I'm left out
of this celebration?!
You could have your fill of
that famous Scotchian cheese!
Cheese, huh?
All right!
This is gettin cheesey.
Hey, we're still doing
that Aquaria trip, right?
Summer Babes!
Waitin' for ME!
You wish, poser.
We'll have to
re--open the Pirate.
I just got
some new menu ideas!
Oh, yeah!
The boys are probably
starving their asses off now!
And the LADIES are
crying themselves to sleep
waiting for me!
Humor me here!!
Just buy me drink
when we get there!
I said we're fixing
my church first, God damn it!
Relax!
We'll do all that stuff!
Hell yeah!
Let's do it!
Get a grip Katana!