You know, you might
wanna consider
sending that
docking clearance signal.
And you might wanna
shut the hell up!
I've got it covered,
all right?!
If by "covered" you mean
you're still looking through
the "Flying Federation Shuttles
for the Brain--Dead" manual,
then we're in trouble.
Requestin' clearance is
small craft operator 101
and it shouldn't be
kickin' your ass like that.
Unless you just plain
forgot how, of course.
Just get off my ass!
How am I supposed
to get this figured out
if you keep on flappin'
yer yap--trap?!
Knew you forgot!
I'm REVIEWING the
procedure, dammit!
I'm not some senile
old bastard like you!
Take a look out the
window, "genius."
You just ran out of
"review time."
What?
Holy crap!
Ok, ok....
Stay calm!
STAY CALM??!
Yeah, maybe you're right.
Where was I
in this stupid manual?
Hey Mister,
how do you suppose Swamp and
Bishop are doing right now?
Well, my guess is...
not too good at all.
I don't need to guess.
I'd even be willing
to put money on it.
Probably bitching up
a storm as we speak.
Or better yet throwing
punches already.
Hey
We oughta put out some
bandages for Bishop.
So why in the world did you
put the two of them together?
'Cuz that oughta make
things more entertaining!
Huh?
I'm having fun already.
What?!
Oh, shit!
Why didn't we think to put a
hidden camera in the cockpit
when we had the chance?
That'd been sweet.
Ah no big deal.
I mean who wants
to watch a movie when
when you already
know the ending?
Yeah, but we coulda
used the footage to
embarass them later, right?
Oh yeah!
Still feeding that
bottomless--pit, I see.
Oh, morning.
You're up early, aren't you?
Not as early as you.
Inspector...
where are you going...
wait for me...
Hey, May.
Seeing you awake too
makes me wonder.
Are all your sisters
early risers like you are?
And why would you
concern yourself with that?
Oh, it doesn't concern me
that much, really.
Only 24 hours until
til things go boom...
Hopefully we'll be able to see
another sunrise like this.
We will.
I'm counting on it.
That sounded pretty confident.
So what's your
plan of action now?
Wait.
For what?
Him.
He's definitely on the way.
After all, Mister is after the
same thing as your mother
and he doesn't like to lose,
so you can bet he'll find
a way to get here.
Gosh, Inspector.
With you it's always
Mister--this and Mister--that.
You should give it
a rest once in a...
Wha...?
You've already had breakfast?!
I'm surprised you don't get
sick from eating all the time!
As they say, you can't wait
for Mister on an empty stomach.
The proverb is you can't
WAGE WAR on an empty stomach...
Orders from the top brass, sir!
Ok, let's have a look.
Could you acknowledge them
with your signature, Ensign?
Here, right?
You've come quite a way.
Good work.
Sir!
Is there any way possible
we could get our ship
refueled before we leave?
And, we were also hoping to
have a mechanic have a look
at our portside engine.
It's been acting up
a bit lately.
Shouldn't be a problem.
I'll get the flight crew
on it right away.
In the meantime, you can wait
over there 'till we're finished.
Yes, sir.
Thank you very much.
Whew!
So I suppose you were just
"brushing up on the procedure"
on how to ask the deck officer
for gas when you started
shittin' your
britches back there?
There's a whole planet
on the line here
so give me a break, ok?!
I was just about to get to it.
Hey!
What're you up to now?
We're not gonna get anywhere
just by standin' around.
Hey!
Now wait a second!
Oh, man...
Yeah...
That's definitely it.
No way.
How are we supposed to
get up close and personal
with that big--ass
thing from here?
I mean, if it was closer,
we could slip right in, but...
Afraid sweety? Want me to hold
your hand or something?
Screw you!
I don't see you
making any moves you jerk.
Well, now.
Maybe I'll just do that.
Alright, let's see it.
You'd best shut the hell up
while I'm doin' my thinkin' boy!
Yeah right, you're one to talk.
I even had to send
your damn docking signal.
You can kiss my ass.
Yeah!
I'd bet you'd love that,
you old fruitcake.
How about I kick your ass?!
Ok. Who the hell is that?
I'll be damned
if I know what it is.
That's Malcolm!
Pardon me, gentlemen.
Now that we're all here,
let's get started.
General Boniek, I'm sure
you'll agree that how we
end this war is as important as
when we end it at this point?
Well, Senator Hewlitt, I would
dare say that your presence here
is an inspiration for all
parties to behave reasonably.
The Graceland Liberation
Forces are certainly open
for discourse.
Definitely.
I appreciate that.
After all, we certainly
do not want to leave behind
a sullied legacy as politicians
who obliterated a planet.
Simple enough, if you
don't drop the bomb.
God damn it!
What are those idiots
talking about in there?
You brought this on yourself!
You're sitting at
this table because of
your damned revolution!
I apologize.
We've already wasted effort
going down that road
so let's pull back.
Aren't we there yet?! Come on!
Yeah, April, I'm bored!
I wanna go play!
I wanna play NOW!
Yeah!
Let's play, April!
Patience, little ones.
You'll have plenty of
playtime once we get there.
Wake up, Dece!
Okay...
Aww man!
How do we get in there, huh?
Well, all right.
That makes sense.
Found my way in.
See ya!
At your service.
What the hell do you think
you're doing you idiot?!
Watch and learn, old man.
You crazy?
Pardon the interruption!
I've brought you gentlemen
something cool to drink!
We didn't request
a beverage cart!
But the galley told me to get
this over to the conference room
right away, Admiral.
All this juice is
gonna go to waste...
Fine, that's enough, soldier.
Just leave the cart here,
and let us get back to work.
I'll just leave it.
Pardon the intrusion!
What the hell were you
doin' back there?!
I've got what it takes
when it counts the most.
We're running
short on time, gentlemen.
So let's keep
this moving, shall we?
Perfect!
Well, other than
the lack of space...
You got a huge ass
Shut your mouth and listen, boy!
I'm surprised you didn't
pick the ladies room.
We'd be least likely
to get caught here.
You picked this spot in case
your bladder acts up, old man!
I aint the one who peed his
pants because he couldn't
send the signal.
Again with the signal.
You want a gold star, Pops?!
Achoo!
You want someone to hear us?!
J--Just do s--something
about that d--damn hair...
Hey, Mister.
Yeah?
Shouldn't we be using
a less--direct route
to the Gigabanks?
Yeah we should.
Heh.
But we're not.
Franca.
Hm?
Why is it a bad idea for us
to go flying straight to
the Gigabanks?
Hmmm...
Because Marciano's already
there looking to ambush us.
Is that right?
On the nose!
Their own "welcoming party." And
since we have next to no time
to get this done, we pretty much
have to roll with the punches
no matter how hard
they try to hit us.
And if I were her, I'd already
have them laying in wait for us
along our flight path.
Radar's picked up something.
Bin--GO!
Boss, I wouldn't be
so happy about that.
How many we got out there?
Hmmm...
looks like about a dozen.
Boy!
We sure are popular today!
As much as I'd like to play with
Marciano, I'd rather hang out
with a classier dame.
Heh...
Hail Queen Angelica the First!
Hey!
Stop that!
Sorry.
You keep on playing around like
that you're gonna get us killed!
Yes, ma'am!
Take it easy, kids.
Huh?
So, are you two ready
to get this party started?
The Federation's conditions
for peace are as follows...
One: Federal arbiters will
be included in the drafting
of Graceland's new constitution
after the signing of the treaty.
Two: All combat arms and
materiel used to develop same,
plus any items that could
be misappropriated for their
manufacture will be immediately
regulated by the Federation.
Three...
Hey, Katana!
Get us down on
the ground, willya?
Find us a hole in the formation
and get us through it!
No problem, I'm on it.
Katana!
Three ships
starboard underneath us!
Roger!
Time to wake up, little ones.
Our objective is making sure
the photonic bomb
never reaches Graceland.
It's aboard the
that ship, the Jupiter.
And don't hit the bomb
itself, or we're done for.
Understood?
Uh-huh. Ok.
This should buy Mother the
time she needs to seek out
this "treasure."
This proposal seems to favor the
Federation rather heavily
doesn't it?
We're all feeling our way
through these negotiations,
General.
Of course we are still
open to your concerns.
"Feeling" our way through
these negotiations?
Who do you think you're kidding?
What?
Marciano's 12 Sisters are here?
Call battlestations
to all decks.
And don't let them
get near the Jupiter!
Hooray!
Yay, yay, yay, woo!
Gentlemen, in light of
the present circumstances
I need you to consider your
safety and evacuate the ship.
So, if you please...
They can stay here
if they want, Admiral.
What?
I don't know why the Guild would
feel a need to attack the bomb.
Unless, of course...
They're intervening
on your behalf?
Ridiculous.
I'm not so certain.
We need to hurry, gentlemen!
If that photonic bomb
detonates with us here,
then all this
negotiation will be lost!
Actually, it won't
be detonating.
Mr. Hewlitt.
We'll do what we can
against the 12 Sisters,
but you should consider
evacuating in case they succeed.
And I'm telling you that even
if the Jupiter is destroyed,
we're quite safe here, Malcolm.
The press releases about
the nature of your mission
we allowed on the
news were deceptions.
There's no bomb aboard
that ship, Admiral.
There never was.
Huh?!
What?!
Are you saying
you deceived us?!
We prefer the term
"misinformation."
Federation science has never
created a weapon sturdy enough
to be dropped from outer space,
through an atmosphere and
survive long enough
to annhilate a planet.
If you light a firecracker
in the palm of your hand,
you burn your hand.
But as we all know, if you
close your fist around it,
you go to the hospital instead.
Dear God no.
The real photonic bomb is
already buried deep inside
Graceland and ready to
crack it open like an egg.
No way!
Holy shit!
Persistent little bastards, huh?
The bomb is quite real
and the timer's already set.
And you can be sure
it will explode on time.
So then.
Still think I'm
"deceiving" you, General?
You piece of filth.
My, I'm insulted.
But I'm feeling generous
so I'll tell you this.
There are two ways
to stop the underground bomb
from detonating.
You could search the
entire planet and disarm
the ignition device directly,
or enter the disarm code
into this remote control device.
Well now, look at that.
19 hours, 18 minutes,
and 36 seconds remaining.
And now that I've proven
definitively that we're
running out of time,
let's wrap this up, shall we?
So, do we bust in?
No, wait.
They could still
work it out on their own.
One, two...
three!
We're sorry, April!
No.
Huh?
The...
bomb it's...
What the hell happened?
Well, it appears that
we've settled things
to our mutual
satisfaction, General.
Your signature, if you please.
Where did you bury it?
You can drop the pretenses
and tell me that, can't you?
We're not in a position
to contact our comrades
even you did tell us.
And even if we could attempt
disarming it, you probably have
jamming signals
around the burial site.
Besides, you already have us in
custody if we don't cooperate.
You've got quite an imagination.
Where did you bury it
in the middle of the war?
The Godwing Valley.
The place where
the gods descend.
Right where
he buried the vault!
Are you serious?
W--Who are you?!
What the hell?!
You sold us out you traitor!
Um...
the remote?
We might wanna try to get
that remote control?
Uh...
right!
I saw it myself!
If there was a bomb,
we'd all be dead by now!
You fool...
Graceland's Liberation
Forces will continue
the fight against
the Federation!
This definitely reminds me
of that old proverb
about your allies being
the very last to turn on you.
Ridiculous!
If they'd just let things be,
Graceland wouldn't be
in any danger right now!
Let's go.
This ship is toast!
People like that
are nothing but idiots!
So they start wars to
figure out who's stupidest.
May, I've got everything
I need from you.
Hm?
We've got a little more
than half a day left before
the Federation drops
the bomb on this planet.
For all I know,
we could end up dying here.
And I don't want to see
that happen to you, you know?
And of course, I not in a
rush to die myself, mind you.
After all,
I've never been married...
And also...
And you haven't captured
Mister yet, either, have you?
It's time we part company.
I really enjoyed
the talks we had.
Seriously.
Thank you.
When I tell my Mother
and sisters about you,
she might try
to come after you.
I don't think they'd bother.
What makes you say that?
Just call it my "intuition."
Huh?
May!
Damn jamming signals
are all over the place.
There's no way for us to
contact the Coyote like this.
We'll just have to
go down there.
So how much time
do we have left, anyway?
About as much time as we've got
left to live, I'd dare say.
So are ya still
goin' down there?
Damn straight!
So do we stop the bomb first...?
or take back Bruce's
legacy first?