All right.
We have the pendant...
It's time to find out
about Bruce's legacy
and what it really means.
Franca...
Our friend Bruce was the only
man in this whole galaxy to be
known as "The Pirate King."
And he loved Franca
so much he left her this.
It contains a memory chip
from his artificial eye.
With a complete record of
the universe's greatest heist.
Cops said it couldn't be done,
and most Coyotes
wouldn't even try it...
The theft of 10 billion space
dollars from the Central Bank.
What?!
That can't be!
I've never heard about
any heist like that!
Think about it, Mister.
A job as big as hitting
the Central Bank?
It would have been
all over the news!
And that's why the bank
kept it under wraps.
Central Bank isn't just the
backbone of universal finance,
folks look up to it.
If people found out
about Bruce's heist,
it'd be chaos out there.
Anyway...
why don't we take
a look at this...
Attention passengers:
we are decelerating
for atmospheric entry.
Please fasten your seatbelts
and lock your tray tables
in their original positions.
You feelin' all right, Franca?
The final exam for Central
Bank executive trainees will
begin at 10:00 am local time
at Central Bank's main facility.
Have a nice day!
Looks like the place.
That's a helluva building!
Well when you think about it the
entire planet is a giant bank.
But yeah, at first glance,
that is impressive.
Cameras were off--limits.
And they sure as hell
didn't want the media
snoopin' around there.
So let me get this straight.
Shouldn't we be able
to use the video
like some kinda
"treasure map" or something?
'Fraid not.
Tell 'em why, Swamp.
Bruce knew that "The Pirate
King" wasn't going be able
to assault the Central Bank's
vaults so he just decided
to be someone else.
And of course, that's
the day "Mister Otis Ray"
showed up to class.
Got the answers yet, Katana?
Shut up - I'm workin' on it!
So, Mister Ray, why do you want
to work with the Central Bank?
Sir, I believe my experience
in the Silver Stocks division
will be most helpful.
Leveraging our
universe--wide network,
we can acquire several planets'
finances over the next 10 years.
All above--board, of course.
Ladies and Gentlemen, this
is Mister Ray, who will be
in charge of the New Ventures
Division as of today.
Hi, my name is Otis Ray.
Pleased to meet you.
And without further ado,
let's take a look at the first
order of business, shall we?
The Primary Planetary Survey
Commission offered this report.
Bruce adapted to the
tight-assed culture in the bank
by working harder than all of
them, but he never lost sight
of the prize.
Getting acceptance
wasn't a problem, either.
If you know what I mean.
And with all that
wheelin' and dealin...
he still found time
to do research on how
to get that 10 billion.
That was incredible getting
out to 4 different planets
this month AND getting them all
to sign off on the project!
Just don't go popping off
the champagne corks until
the Investment Division
signs off on it.
Piece o'cake, Mister Ray!
The Bank President
knows you'll get it done!
Alex, you're going out
to Planet Columbus.
Yes, sir.
Kris, you'll go to Teuton.
Right!
Give me everything
you've got out there.
Yes, sir!
He was there a year:
kickin' ass, takin' names
and lookin' good doin' it.
He got their trust...
now it was time to
get some of their money.
Don't move.
Whatever you do, don't shoot...
It's me, Swamp!
Bruce, man!
What's wrong with you?
I almost messed
my damn drawers!!
Haven't caught up
with you in a while, man.
Hey, man!
You're gettin'
kinda porky, huh?
How 'bout you stop showing me
all this "brotherly love,"
all right?
So...
that's really our target?
The Central Bank?
That's right.
It's just sitting there.
The grand prize.
It might be the grand prize,
but it sure as hell
ain't gonna be easy, chief...
Wait a minute...
These are the plans to
the Central Bank's vault.
No way, you gotta be
kiddin' me, Bruce!
I mean, it's so damned
impossible to break into,
even God himself
ain't got the key!
Genuine blueprints for the
old "Gigabanks!" Aw, man...
howdja get ahold of this stuff?
That's only the beginning.
These plans are to help us
make a "certain something"
that we're gonna need.
What "certain something?"
Heh, you're gonna love it.
Anyway, shouldn't you be gettin'
ready for your part in this?
Hold on!
I haven't even decided
if I'm gonna do this!
I mean, sure, it's a once
in a lifetime job an' all...
But I don't really know if I'm
ready for somethin' like this.
Hey.
Point taken.
I gotcha.
No, really.
I hear you.
Perimeter checks out.
Got anything else?
Nah.
You did good out there.
That map right there has all
the guards' patrol routes
and video camera locations
between you and the Gigabanks.
Nice...
I'm impressed.
Did a good job out there.
Ah, thanks.
I was just thinkin', Swamp...
Huh?
Get some time off.
'Bout the middle of next week.
Um...
sure.
I've got a little
something to show you.
I also have Hank
and Norman coming in.
Really?
Finally, this is
startin' to get good.
Yeah.
What planet is that?
That's Graceland,
believe it or not.
Sure doesn't look like
today's Graceland.
Yo, D--Boni!
Gentlemen, this is the last
member of our operation...
Say hi to D--Boni.
Hey.
Well, Maestro.
It's time for the unveiling.
What the heck is that?
A full--scale working replica
of the Central Bank's vault.
They call it "Gigabanks."
Whoa, that's a bank vault?
Yeah.
Bruce gave me this as
a memento of the job.
It's a thousand to one scale
model of the real thing.
Gigabanks used 50
moving modules around
12 different
articulation points.
THOUSANDS of combinations.
But here's the kicker:
withdrawals and deposits
always got processed
through the "central ball."
The five sections of the vault
that actually had cash in 'em
would rotate to the top
on every major transaction.
Otherwise, they can't connect
to the elevator that takes money
the last mile to the top.
Vault operator
never touches a dime.
Wanna look inside?
Me?
What the hell is
that crazy thing?
If I had the answer
to that question,
I wouldn't need the mock--up.
There's another catch: the
modules get "reshuffled" after
every authentication attempt,
and every 30 minutes regardless.
So, even if you find your way
in, you'll be screwed if you
lose your bearings in
there for even a second.
One wrong move and you're
a permanent resident.
Greeeat...
"Hotel California," huh?
Well I guess it's
my turn, isn't it?
Hey Bruce, quit messin' around.
Come on, man!
I didn't build this mock--up
just to stare at it and say,
"ooh, pretty...
"Besides, the
damn thing cost me
a hundred million
space dollars to build.
WHAT!
A hundred million bucks!
When you gamble, you gotta
put money in the pot to play.
Yeah, but you could buy
a used battleship for that.
So why in the hell waste
the time, effort and money
building a replica of
the Gigabanks on a planet
as far away as Graceland?
I mean wouldn't it have been
easier on a closer planet?
Yeah, exactly!
Then this whole thing
wouldn't have to be
such a wild goose chase!
Planet Graceland is where
my father first met my mother.
Huh?
That's the reason...
Take a good look.
All told, there are 4 security
measures that stand between us
and getting in.
First, there's the master key.
Then the system
demands a voiceprint.
The rain in Spain
falls mainly on the plain.
Retinal scan...
digital vascular pattern scan...
and after all that,
you're as good as in.
But Bruce, that's three levels
of biometric authentication!
And the bank president's
probably the only guy
the system's keyed to.
Hey.
Who do you think
you're dealin' with?
Yes, what is it?
Mr. Ray is here to see you, sir.
Oh yes, well let him in.
Pardon the intrusion.
Otis, my boy!
How have you been?
I have the mid--term report
on "the project" for you.
Wonderful.
Let's see...
3 out of 4 mines anticipate
over a 200% profit increase
within 2 years...
Ah, I see, I see...
Nice, this is a very
nice forecast indeed!
Hey there.
How's it comin'?
Ya done yet?
Now that's niiice.
So that's not working yet?
Well, I'm sure you'll
figure something out.
So, on the night
before the job went down...
Synchronize your
watches to 20:15 in 3...
2...
and 1!
We're gonna do it
just like we drew it up.
And we meet at
the bank tomorrow.
Hello?
Who is this?
Bruce, is that you?
Yeah.
So to what do I
owe this pleasure?
Tomorrow...
I'm hitting the Central Bank.
Thought you'd have
more to say than that.
What do you want me
to say, Bruce?
You say you're gonna do it,
so go ahead and do it, right?
Heh!
Guess that's true, huh?
Just get home safe
when the party's done.
Will do...
Oh, and hey - I ran into
Little Bear a while back.
Heh!
That guy's still alive?!
Yep!
Bastard hasn't
changed a bit, either!
Here we go!
Good morning.
Normally the 5 vault rooms
with all the cash in Gigabanks
don't all come together on the
top level at the same time.
There is one exception, though.
Hey!
How are you this
morning, Mister Ray?
Natural disasters that threaten
the vault such as floods,
fire or earthquake
set off the emergency reset,
bringing all the cash up
to the top at once.
It gets airlifted out until
the vault is safe again.
Good morning, Mister President.
Ah, Otis, my boy!
Now what can I do for you?
It's me.
Don't let anyone in here
for the next hour.
No phone calls either.
Understood, sir.
It's the President.
Hey, you don't need to report
it when it's him, ya know...
Yeah, I guess you're right.
The rain in Spain
falls mainly on the plain.
Huh...
he's gone all the way
to the last checkpoint.
Yeah!
You still don't
have to report it!
Uh... hey...
Ah, it's back on.
So where'd the President go?
He's probably in
the center ball.
That's about the only place we
don't have any cameras set up.
Damn!
That's the center
of Gigabanks?!
That's right.
Only one man in the universe
has seen it up close.
Bingo!
What was THAT?!
An explosion from
inside the Gigabanks!
What?!
What are ya doin'
just sittin' there!
GO!
Yessir!
Like Bruce said: a major
disaster will cause Gigabanks
to spin all of its cash vault
modules to the top to meet
the cash elevator.
So, he made sure
a disaster happened.
Oh!
Thank god you guys made it!
We're here to recover
the funds in accordance
with the disaster
recovery outlines, sir!
This way!
Hurry up!
Come on!
All right, it looks
like we've got all of it.
Good.
Thanks.
No way...
It can't be!
What's that guard doing?
Why is Mister Ray there?
Huh?!
Mister Ray?!
No way...
That kicks ass!
Friggin' hilarious!
That guy's--freakin--unreal!
Well, there you have it -
a complete record of
the Central Bank heist.
Anyway guys, that's the
beast we're up against.
So...
you wanna go?
Boss, you don't
even have to ask.
I'm all over it!
And after that went down,
Bruce gave us the shares we
agreed on and that was that.
He put the rest in the vault on
Graceland, and sealed it away.
So how did the latest
caper go, boss--man?
It was incredible.