Megazone 23 Part II:
Please Give Me Your Secret
[ARCADE SOUNDS]
~b~Backup singers: ~i~Lonely
sunset... Woohoo...
Lonely sunset...
~b~Eve: ~i~The pavement on
the final day of summer.
I was watching him from behind.
His skin was so fair and hot...
and suggested-
[MOTORCYLE REVS]
The silver-
-quietly.
[BUZZER BLARES]
Operator: All Fighters, sixty minutes
to launch. Number One Port Gate is open.
Launch stand-by, all clear.
Announcer: FX escort crew
to Number Four Port, Deck 1.
Airgrain FX-101,
59 minutes to launch.
- Main crew to Number Three Port, Deck 2.
- [ROCK GUITAR MUSIC]
Admiral: What do you think of the gallantry
of the Airgrain FX, Mr. Yumekano?
- Yumekano: It's most impressive.
- Signs: \"Young people! We need you now!\"
- Man: Look at that! There's supposed to be
a war going on! - \"Take back our peace.\"
I am pleased to see that the support
the financial community has...
given this project has
been well rewarded.
With the FX, we will shift the
tide of this war in our favor.
Just leave it to us.
We're counting on you, Admiral.
Eve: Operator of 7G, please
respond. Operator 7G-
Excuse me, Major, but aren't you attending
the launch ceremony for the FX-101?
Nakao: I understand Mr. Yumekano will
be there representing the companies.
You should be there, sir.
B.D.: Is it as important as sweeping Section B
for the source of the Eve ghost one more time?
- Not when that may be the key
to winning this war. - Right.
~b~Song resumes: ~i~Lonely sunset...
We're both to blame.
~b~- Huh? - [ANNOYING HORNS]~i~
- Lonely sunset...
It's stupid of me...
to be thoughtful...
[ANNOYING HORNS]
Preparing for Gate Departure. All support
personnel to Launch Bay shelters.
- It is a magnificent sight, isn't it?
- [SCOFFS]
- It's just a bluff.
- A bluff?
It's already quite clear that we have
no chance of winning this conflict.
And that the wisest course action, at this point, would
be to surrender, rather than prolong it further.
However, our own technological
resources are not unimpressive.
Imagine what heights we and the Dezalg
might achieve, were our forces to join.
To that end, we already have a faction,
working within the military...
making contact with
them on our behalf.
Hmmm... but what about B.D.?
B.D. isn't the only
soldier out there.
And with enough money, one
can always buy another one.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
Wait! Feed it back again.
There! Look how the power barrel
is focusing at one point.
There ~i~is~b~ an unidentified section.
There's definitely a link between
Section B and Eve's ghost, Major.
The power vectors are matched,
and directly proportional.
As the output continues to increase,
Tokyo Base is bound to be affected.
That's fine. If that happens, then
Yahagi is bound to notice it.
Which will force his hand.
Keep scanning the unidentified
sections, Nakao.
- Yes, sir.
- And you, Lieutenant. Find Yahagi.
Yes, sir!
I won't fail you, sir.
Not again.
[DISTANT TRAIN SOUNDS]
[DISTANT POLICE SIREN]
Our new top priority is resolving the
Tomomi Murashita murder investigation.
The murderer, Shogo Yahagi,
must be brought to justice.
All: Yes, sir!
But, why the rush now, sir?
Why now?!
- Owww!
- [GASPS]
It's been half a year, six full months,
that you've been searching! Just find him!
Uhhh... I... I'm sorry, Lieutenant.
We'll do everything we can!
Then get moving, damnit!
All: Yes, sir!
[HEARTBEATS]
Yui: [SIGH, INTAKE OF BREATH]
Thank you for coming today, Miss.
Announcer: The train is now
approaching the station.
[GASPS] I know, you don't
have to tell me, I'm late.
- Sorry.
- Lightning: No tails?
Mmm.
- [INTERCOM BEEP]
- Background: Yes, ma'am. Traffic control.
Hello, Traffic Center.
How may I help you?
Yui: Umm... I just saw the suspect in the
Tomomi Murashita murder case.
- Yes... On East Kichijoji Street, huh?
- Uh huh.
Next to the big parking lot. Right.
Thanks for your help.
Hey! What're you doing?
[GASPS] Shogo Yahagi!
No! Wait! For god's sake,
don't shoot!
- [AIRSOFT GUN SHOTS]
- [SCREAMS AND WHIMPERS]
- So long, sucker!
- [BOUNCY ACTION MUSIC]
~b~Shogo: ~i~Eve...
[PEDESTRIAN SCREAMS]
- Comin' through!
- [SHOPPER SCREAMS]
Moron! What the hell
were you thinking?!
- Megaphone Cop: Take care of all the exits!
Don't let him get out of there! - Yes, sir!
Gangway!
What an idiot.
That's a dead end.
- [MUSIC STOPS]
- [SCOFFS]
Heh!
Let's rock!
Jacket: \"Kumi For Life\"
[BOUNCY ACTION MUSIC RESUMES]
[SHOCKED GASPS]
Eyaah...!
Halt! Halt, or else I'll shoot!
- Is that nice gun for me? Thanks!
- Ahh!
[SHARP GROAN]
Cape: \"Kamikaze Squad Leader\"
[STRANGLED GROAN]
- Sign: \"Safety First\"
- Jayce: Guts, scrap the car!
Guts: OK! You got it!
[GRUNTS WITH EFFORT]
Shirt: \"Blaze\"
Score!
Code F. You are to leak the information through
one of our civilian sources at 1500 hours.
I'll send two Garlands. I want Yahagi,
not apologies, Lieutenant!
Right. I'll take care of it
personally, Major.
I have a new update, sir.
A review of Dezalg operations
over the past six months...
indicates their focus thus far has all
been concentrated on two points:
The first being our infrastructure,
and the second being...
the unidentified section of
the Bahamut program Eve.
If we can acquire what
the enemy wants...
we may be able to find a weakness
that we could use against them.
- The unidentified section again.
- [COMMUNICATOR TONE]
Satcom reports that the FX Fleet has encountered
a squadron of carrier-based enemy craft, sir.
Send in Special Forces.
If anything happens to the FX...
our command structure
is compromised.
We don't have a moment to lose.
Yes, sir.
[DRAMATIC ACTION MUSIC]
- Dau One to Leader. Enemy units confirmed.
- Dau Two, I see them too.
- They're all around us. - Go to instruments.
Switch to single-line formation.
- Roger. - Roger.
- The Dau Unit!
- Don't worry about them!
- Formation X!
- Roger! - Roger!
Fire all missiles! And after firing,
return to airspace at full speed!
Sir! Multiple enemy fighters
directly ahead!
Our fighters have come into contact
with carrier-based enemy elements.
The enemy carrier is now in range
of our main guns, Admiral!
We'll engage with
cannon and torpedo.
All ships, target that carrier.
All ships, prepare to engage
torpedoes with energy cannons.
Target the enemy carrier.
Distance: two-zero, two-zero.
Commence energy injection.
Steady as you go!
Automated tracking devices, ready.
Enemy units closing fast! Anti-aircraft
cannons, put up screening fire!
All missile tubes launch.
Enemy unit over the bridge!
[SCREAMS]
Enemy units to port!
VF-10, what's wrong?
- Missiles hit, no response.
- Enemy units, 12 o'clock!
What the?! [SCREAMS]
Enemy carrier-based craft
approaching, sir!
- Admiral: Energy level? - Energy injection
will be complete in sixty seconds, sir.
And what about our escort ships?
They're all currently engaged
with enemy fighters, Admiral.
Woodsman Unit, launching now!
Woodsman Unit, launch complete!
Enemy units closing fast!
Woodsman to all units:
go to Circus Formation A.
- Roger!
Damn you! You're
not getting away!
No!
- Yellow, one's headed your way.
- What about the other one?
He's headed for the bridge
of the FX. Red, cut him off!
What the hell...?
What's happening?!
We're not going to make it!
Oh my god, it's-!
Enemy unit is punching through!
[ALL GASP]
That's amazing! That new
reflection shield really works!
Energy injection to main guns
is now complete, sir.
Good, start the countdown.
Sir, main gun one's tracking
device is showing an error.
Hmm... Can the computers
correct the error?
Something's wrong in tracking.
I'm switching to manual.
Targeting reticule centered.
Distance: two-zero, two-zero.
Angle of fire, check!
Elevation, check!
What the-?!
[SCREAMS]
[BUILDING SUSPENSE MUSIC]
Admiral, no response from
main guns one or two.
Switch main fire control
to the secondary bridge!
The secondary bridge
isn't responding either!
[SCREAMS]
No! We have no choice!
[DISTANT ALARMS]
[DISTANT EXPLOSIONS]
[TRANQUIL TRILLS]
[URBAN AMBIENCE]
Yes, sir. Nothing to report.
Right. We'll reinforce
the security at once.
[YAWNS] These new orders
just make no sense.
No sense, how?
Well, you know, this place was attacked by
right-wing guerillas back when the war started...
but we handled it.
However, there's been nothing
for the last six months.
And now they want to
double the security?
Well, if we knew what the brass were
thinkin', we wouldn't be guards, right?
I guess I just wish everything
would stay like it is now...
and the war would end without
anything else happening.
[PARTY SOUNDS]
[LAUGHTER]
[LAUGHS]
And when I took his gun, that cop's face
looked like a blowfish caught in a net.
Ah, yeah, makes you
feel good, don't it?
[LAUGHS] Man, that is so far out! You shoulda
seen the way I just, like, elbowed...
Glam: Damn, it's noisy. How'm I
supposed to concentrate in here?
Dump: You always say that...
whenever you're losing.
Oh, yeah?
Always blaming others.
I waited...
but you never came back
for me. What happened?
The reason I didn't go back to your place
is because I knew you'd be there.
And what would have been the point of both
of us getting stuck in the mess I was in?
I didn't want any
of this to happen.
But at least I kept both of us
from becoming losers.
I moved out. I waited for weeks...
but I couldn't stand the looks.
\"There she goes...
the lover of that murderer.\"
And besides, how long could I keep waiting
for someone who might've been dead?
[SIGHS] I'm not a strong
person, Shogo.
I can't survive alone.
- Yeah.
- Man, what's up with our two lovebirds?
Hey, lighten up, you two.
Six months! That's
how long it's been.
After all that time, I know what
most of us would be doing now.
And it ain't talking.
You guys are smart.
I guess you've all got stories.
Not smart, tough. When you've been
rejected by the world, you have to be.
Shogo's girlfriend is hot.
Cyndi: Hey, he's got more
going on than you think.
Reina: Shogo may still look like a little kid,
but at least he's got balls. I could go for him.
And you probably will,
you tramp!
There's nothing with balls
you don't go for, hmmm?
- But it's Glam that she wants!
- That's not true.
I'm just letting you know
I'm playing handicapped.
I mean, what's the fun
in always winning?
Huh.
Now pay attention, Dump.
OK, I lose. Does that make
you happy, showoff?
No, what makes me happy is the three
dozen of these you owe me now.
Yeah, yeah. Y'know, there's a reason
no one hangs out with you.
- You really need to fix that personality of yours.
- Why fix what works for me?
So I was like, \"You gotta be shittin'
me, you bastard!\" [LAUGHS]
There's no way that cop
could catch me.
But he just kept following me
on his punk-ass little 400.
And being on a 1200,
I had my pride too, right?
So I just kept hauling ass until I realized
I was in some kinda ruins. Blew my mind.
And speaking of blowing, if you don't cut back on
those, Glam, even Dump'll stop playing with you.
- Uh-huh...
- Eve: Operator of 7G, please respond.
- Huh?
- Hey, everybody, Eve is naked!
- Eve is on TV, naked!
- [EXCITED CHATTER]
- Hey, move aside!
- Operator 7G, please respond.
Operator 7G, please res-
[DISTORTION]
So do you believe me now?
That was Eve.
The real one, and not the government fake
that makes all that military propaganda.
Just like I saw while the cops
were chasing me this morning.
God damn, it's just
like you said.
Operator 7G.
- And the real Eve-
- Yeah.
She hasn't fallen to the
military completely yet.
And if we got the Garland back, then
all of you could talk to her yourselves.
- If that's true, let's do it!
- [ENTHUSIASTIC AGREEMENT]
By the time we arrived, the entire FX Fleet
had been destroyed, with no survivors.
We recovered the voice recorders
from the FX-101...
and that of Centurion
Commander Woodsman.
In addition, we took to the lab the remains of
three of the smaller enemy craft, for study.
That concludes my report.
Very well. Dismissed.
Sir! Thank you!
- Nakao.
- Yes, sir. Playing now.
Admiral, no response from
main guns one or two.
Switch main fire control
to the secondary bridge!
The secondary bridge
isn't responding either!
[SCREAMS]
No! We have no choice!
[GUNSHOTS]
[RISING INTRIGUE MUSIC]
Major, FX-101 is down.
It's no use, sir. But now we know for certain
that a part of Level 7 survived somewhere.
I already know it survived. I want
somebody to tell me where the hell it is!
And we'll keep going back through
the system 'til they do! Just find it!
There are just too many unknown sections and
black boxes to pinpoint the point of origin.
Operator 7G, please respond.
- Operator of 7G, please respond.
- Our only lead is this Operator 7G.
I'm sorry, sir. Shogo Yahagi
escaped again.
Operator 7G...
Shogo Yahagi...
- [MOTORCYCLES]
- Hey, what is this, a kindergarten?
- How's it hanging, Dump? - Hi, guys!
Welcome back! - I love you, Reina!
Reina: Yeah? Well no chance,
loser! Hey, where's Rakko?
Dump: He probably wiped out
somewhere. Got any beer?
- Rakko had it. He'll be here soon.
- Uh-huh. Later!
Wow, you're doing
great, Yui! Great!
- Now try second gear.
- All right...
- [YELPS] - [LAUGHTER]
- Dump: Oh! Ahhh!
[TITTERS]
Just keep trying, don't quit!
Don't be afraid to push it in!
Hey, Reina, we all agreed that I'd be the
one teaching, so don't be butting in!
[EXCITED CONVERSATION]
Ugg! I can't stand this!
- \"Ultimate Evil\"
- Just watch me!
That's how it's done. Got it?
Don't forget that Yui's never driven
before, brain-donor! Give her time.
Yeah, you're mean. Don't let
the big grouch bother you, Yui.
I know that I'm slow, Dump.
But I really will learn this... huh?
- Yo! Late again, Rakko?
- Rakko: Shut up! I had to get rope!
- Rope? - True. Mr. Brewski kept
escaping, so I had to tie him up.
- Just tell me you got my beer.
- Yeah, yeah. I got your beer. Right here!
Don't forget my girls!
Keep 'em coming!
Yeah, sure. Heads up!
- Mm-hmm...
- Let's make a toast!
- Toast? To what? - Who cares as long
as we got something to toast with!
- Then, \"Chug it!\"
- Chug it!
[SQUEALS]
Rakko! I'll kick your sorry ass!
I told you that's why
I was late, bitch!
- [LOUD ROCK MUSIC] - Dude! Get 'em
as they come down! Light them up!
- Yeah, like he said!
- You gotta light them up!
- Dude, not bad! - You suck!
- Lemme have a go!
[BACKGROUND SQUABBLE]
Here.
Thanks.
[DOOR OPENS]
Woah! Hey everyone, the supply
unit's back with the munchies!
- Sorry for making everyone wait, dudes!
- Here's the booty. Come and get it!
Waaaaooooh!
[GIGGLING]
Damn that Rakko. I'd punch
his brains out if he had any!
- Hey, Reina, it's your turn to pump.
- Sure.
I could use the exercise now that
I've got some real competition.
She's one hard body.
You're a dancer, aren't you?
Yeah, but not that kind.
Hey, want one, Yui?
What...?
Umm, Yui?
You're spacin' out.
Is there somethin' wrong?
Huh...? Uh-Uh.
Oh no, nothing really.
I was just thinking...
about... things...
Chasing the wind...
Finding love...
before this blue city falls apart.
The sky reflected in the
window of a building.
I want to deliver myself to you.
Old Eve, huh? She was
better back then.
Still smoking that same old stinky
tobacco, huh? Gimme one, OK?
- I'll trade you suck for suck.
- [SARCASTIC CHUCKLE]
Budweiser, huh?
- You can pay me back later.
- Thanks.
- Got any Heineken?
- Back there on the table.
Eve... there's something about her...
- [OVERLAPPING MUSIC]
- Huh?
Yo! Hey, how 'bout some
brew for the Brewmeister?
Just turn off that radio and that
military propaganda, dickhead.
Yeah, aint'cha got no couth? We're listenin'
to classic Eve, not that new shit.
All right, all right, I'm turning it off.
- No, wait, Rakko! Don't change anything!
- Huh?
Operator of 7G, please
respond. Operat-
There's no way to suppress it, sir.
It's just outputting too much power.
Hmm... right... Just screw it!
Let's go to Code F!
Proceed according to your
previously laid-out orders.
Connect me to Yumekano Heavy
Industries. Analysis Lab Three.
That's right, emergency
code F-3-7-D-0-0.
Operations Division. I need the Proto-Garland
ready to be moved within thirty minutes.
Thirty-five minutes, then.
In front of elevator B-37. Fine.
- Oh, and one other thing-
- Central Division's waiting for resupply.
We can't hold out at this rate
unless we do something...
[FOOTSTEPS]
- Hmm...?
- [FAINT INSTRUMENTAL POP MUSIC]
Hey, Jayce!
Oh, fuck!
Man, don't kick the door.
This shit is delicate. [SIGHS]
- Now watch you step.
- Yeah, sorry. [LAUGHS]
I'll be more careful from now on.
- Here, have some smokes.
- [GRUNTS]
- So, how are things goin'?
Grrrr... Oh, all right.
- [SMIRKS]
- Huh?
- Yes, I confirm that we have received
one Proto-Garland. - Hmm...?
If you have any other questions, please direct
them to Yumekano Heavy Industries, extension 307.
At Analysis Lab Three, right?
Yes, that's where it's stored, sir.
Great! Give Chief Tabatake
my regards.
- I will, sir. Excuse me.
- [LOUD SQUEAL]
Yahoo! We did it! Yeah!
- [EMBARRASSED SOUNDS]
- Asshole.
And that, gentlemen,
summarizes our mission plan.
Three units have been allocated,
one of which is a decoy.
The operation begins at 1700 hours this evening
and will continue as long as required.
If the operation time
exceeds twenty hours...
an exchange of personnel
will be scheduled at that time.
The mission's code name will be \"7G.\"
So, are there any questions?
That's amazing, Yui! I can't believe
it's only been three days.
That's 'cause she had the
best teacher! Right, Yui?
- You twit, Yui's just got a knack for it.
- [CHUCKLES]
- Whew, I'm wiped out!
- She's my best pupil ever!
- Hey, quittin' already?
- For now. Have you seen Shogo?
- When in doubt, try his room.
- Great. Thanks, Dump.
- [DOOR OPENS]
- [INTAKE OF BREATH]
Yep, Dump was right.
Sitting in the dark.
You're OK, aren't you?
- Well, as for me, I'm bushed!
- [DOOR CLOSES]
But I gotta say, bikes
are some fun shit!
[CHUCKLES]
- Don't you agree?
- Uhh...
What? Don't tell me, has the
pussy got your tongue?
Um... No...
What did you do to your hair?
Oh, this? I was just
feeling... different.
And I thought... why not just
go for it? I'm a fast learner.
Like bikes... Vrmm! Vrrm!
Vrrrrrmmmm!
You just listen to the
sound of the engine...
- and sync up the timing by twisting
like this, and then... Yui...
Really, Shogo, Dump says
I have knack for it.
Yui!
[GASPS] Wait!
I...
[ROMANTIC MUSIC]
[SOFTLY] Yes...
Damn, it's cold!
[SOFT URBAN AMBIENCE]
It's been over twenty-six
hours, Lieutenant.
And we'll wait twenty-six more.
What if he doesn't show up?
He'll show! Now close your hatch.
You're lighting up the room, you idiot!
Yes, sir.
[GENTLE MUSIC]
This Operator 7G...
is that me?
I mean, I'm pretty sure it is,
but, it's just strange.
Why?
Because the Eve who was supposed
to have been erased barely knew me.
Why would she call me?
What does she want?
\"Are you sure about this, Yui?
This is your last chance.\"
\"Do you really want
me to cut it?\"
- [SCISSORS CLACKING]
- ~i~ \"I'm certain.\" ~b~
We found out where the
Garland is being stored.
And... If everything goes according to
plan, we might be able to get it back.
But... I've got to go today.
- This is it, right?
- It should be.
Hey! Look! Over there...
Score!
Operator 7G, please respond.
Eve, it's Shogo!
Shogo Yahagi!
Shogo Yahagi,
you're under arrest!
There's no way that you
can escape now!
Drop your weapons and
surrender quietly!
[SIGHS]
- Mm-hm?
- Mm-hm.
Mm-hm!
[ENERGETIC ROCK MUSIC]
Get on!
Don't kill Yahagi!
Use the capture nets!
Run!
The target's heading south! Sudo,
Yamahata: block off from the east!
Roger!
Squadron A, there's only one way
through that south corridor!
- Take your men around and
block off all the exits! - Roger!
What about these branches here?
We have it covered, sir. This path
leads to the south corridor...
while this one merges with it, and
also leads to the south corridor.
The narrow one's a dead end,
and at the far end we have...
- three Flaggers and two full squads waiting.
They won't escape. - Where are they now?
B Squad and the Sergeant are driving
them from two different directions.
They're heading straight
into our trap.
Looks like they're gone.
[MECHANICAL CLANKING]
Hmm...? [GRUNTS]
It's morning.
[YAWNS] And the trains'll
start running soon.
Hey... what's this thing?
Hmm... a transmitter, I think.
Hey, let me see that.
[TRAIN APPROACHING]
[SNICKERS]
[LAUGHTER]
- [RAPID BEEPS]
- There's no escape this time.
Have you located the
transmitters yet?
They've been separated, sir. One's in
Shinjuku, and the other's in Minato.
So they've found the decoy,
as expected. Good.
We're returning to HQ.
Keep us updated.
So, where did they hide the
second transmitter?
Inside the mirror.
- You are the Eve I spoke to before, right?
- [MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
- The real Eve?
- Yes.
But this program has been purged from
the majority of Bahamut's memory...
and can no longer access
the external work systems.
However, I believe that if my external connections
to the main system were to be severed...
I would then be able to function
as an independent system.
Hold on. Exactly where would
this main system be located?
On Bahamut's Seventh Level, Area 49BA,
as shown in this display.
So it's inside Bahamut.
That is correct. However,
there is little time left.
You must come to me as
quickly as possible.
If what she says is true...
then we could bust our way into
Bahamut and set Eve free, right?
Please come as quickly
as possible.
There are things that I
must do that I cannot.
But what can I do?
Quite a lot, if you
bring friends, right?
- Are you with me?!
- [GENERAL AGREEMENT]
We're with you, Shogo!
[CONTINUED CHEERING]
Yeah!
Then it's decided.
Let's do it!
What do we have?
We located transmitter one
attached to a train to otemachi.
However, transmitter two
is in Roppongi.
For the last thirty minutes
it's been stationary...
nine meters underground, at the
site of an old embassy building.
Damn! They're right
under our noses...
- [PHONE RINGING]
- [DRAMATIC TAPS]
Front gate. Huh? Yes sir!
Acknowledged!
Man! We're gonna meet Eve!
Screw the cops! Screw the army!
I'm really gonna meet her!
Oooh... So, are you taking
a notepad for signing?
Yeah. And I'm gonna get her picture,
and shake her hand. [LAUGHS]
Asshole, there ain't no way
she's shaking your hand!
Shut up!
[ALARM BUZZER]
Remember: Don't let them know you're out
there until they're completely surrounded.
- Keep it moving! Hurry!
- Yes, sir!
[EXCITED CONVERSATION]
Hey Jayce, toss me
some of that, will'ya?
Bleeeaah!
- Bam-bam-bam-bam-bam!
- [LAUGHS]
[DRAMATIC BEATS]
The 3rd and 4th Companies? Those are from
the Nakano Division. Yes, understood.
- Move it, people! Move it!
- Almost there, sir!
Come on!
[EXCITED CHATTER]
Lightning! Trouble!
Big trouble!
Cops everywhere! We're
completely surrounded!
[WAR CRIES]
Hey! Take the back way,
and I'll cover ya!
Gene, Suri-ko, Ike! Follow me!
Use the secret exit while Guts' team
holds the front! Evacuate!
- Jayce, you and your squad head for Shibuya.
- Riot! - You got it!
- Watch you ass!
- OK.
Cyndi, Yui can't handle a bike and a weapon
at the same time, so cover her rear!
- It's covered! - Thanks.
- Yui, make sure you stay close to me!
And you stick by me, Shogo,
even if you're dead!
Just remember, that
works both ways!
- We're in, sir. - [ANNUNCIATOR]
- Huh...
Transmitter two's moving.
It's heading southwest, sir.
- Send the Garlands in now.
- Yes, sir.
Gaaaah!
I'm Guts, Suicide King!
Who wants to dance?
- Take him down!
- Yeah!
Eat this!
Go to hell, you pigs!
That's it! Go!
Aw, shit!
That's it! To hell with you!
Kick his metal ass!
We've lost track of transmitter two,
sir, and our containment of...
blocks B37 and A40
has been breached.
I'm afraid most of them managed
to make it out into the city.
Get a helicopter up on the roof.
I'll be handling this part personally.
- How long will it take?
- I'll have it there in five minutes, sir.
Understood.
Oooh! So scary!
I don't care how many there are,
you're not getting past me! [LAUGHS]
Fire!
[LAUGHS]
[CHUCKLES]
[SOMBER ROCK BEAT]
\"Honored Parents...\"
\"I am sorry I have not
contacted you recently.\"
\"I cannot divulge why;
however, at this moment...\"
\"I am on a mission I must complete,
even if the cost is my own life.\"
\"If you are reading this letter, I will
no longer be a part of this world.\"
\"I know that this is not something that
a son should do to his parents, but...\"
\"I feel great honor
in my work.\"
\"Please forgive me for being
such an inconsiderate son...\"
\"and forgive me for
leaving this world first.\"
\"I hope for your good health,
and please take care.\"
\"- Yuichiro Shiratori.\"
[DRAMATIC ACTION ROCK MUSIC]
Yeah! C'mon!
Dudes, this is one
helluva field trip!
OK, I'm tired of running!
It's your turn!
[SHOCK]
Man, that was just sad!
[LAUGHS]
Can't you read? This road's
closed to through traffic.
How can those kids beat you? Use the
Flaggers to drive them into the open.
You heard me!
Playtime is over!
And where's Yahagi?
Haven't you located him yet?
- [EXCITED WHOOPS]
- Reinforce the entrance to the second level!
All right! Here they come!
Here!
[EXCITED YELLS]
Yo! Lets have some fun!
Those are just decoys!
Move in and eliminate them!
Huh?! What the hell?!
That little bastard!
Eyaah!
Woah! That was radical!
Eat this!
Fire!
[GROANS]
What's the matter?
Want some more?
[GRUNTS]
Where's Yahagi hiding?
How the fuck should I know? If you want him
so bad, find him your own fucking self!
You got a big mouth, bitch!
We've spotted a group traveling
east near Aoyama Avenue.
We believe it includes the
Proto-Garland and Shogo Yahagi.
Right. Converge the Flaggers
on that point!
- [ALERT SIRENS] - Enemy infiltration
on the second floor, Block 29!
The 5th Ground Unit is responding.
Send Centurion Unit Number 3 to Block 29.
I want that situation handled.
What's Shiratori's current status?
The Lieutenant reports they're about to
corner the Proto-Garland and Yahagi, sir.
Tell them to hurry!
[ENERGETIC ROCK MUSIC]
Yui! You OK back there?
Sure! Don't forget,
she's got me!
Keep it up!
Back off!
Out of bullets!
[SCREAMS]
Cyndi, rear-view!
Motherfucker!
I think it's time for the Trash
to hit the tracks!
They're trying to enter
Bahamut via Shaft 16.
All units, proceed to D-4.
We've got to cut them off!
Leave this to me.
Get off our fucking asses,
you bastards!
They're just ahead of us!
Turn around! [SCREAMS]
Time to hit full throttle!
That was too close!
Huh?
[MUSIC RESOLVES]
End of the line, Yahagi!
If you don't want to lose any more of
your friends, you'll surrender quietly.
As for the rest of you, get off your bikes
and raise your hands in the air.
No way! We can't stop
after coming this far!
- Just leave this to me.
- Shogo!
I'm warning you. Try anything,
and we'll shoot!
- All right, I'm coming.
- No, Shogo. Wait!
- You're better than that, Shogo!
- Don't be a chickenshit!
Drive forward slowly.
That's far enough!
Drop your weapon!
Now raise your hands slowly, stand up,
and get off the Garland.
Hold it! Show me what's in
your hands! Show me!
- Ha! Suckers!
- [EXCITING MUSIC]
- Awesome!
- Right! Let's go!
- Don't worry, it's me.
- Shogo!
C'mon! This way!
We're dead without out bikes.
But I've got an idea.
They must be hiding here someplace!
We can't let them escape!
Incoming!
Get ready to take him out!
Wait, that's not a Garland!
- Eyaaah!
- Eyuuuh!
We missed the first two, but they
were on standard bikes.
Forget the small fry!
Catch the Proto-Garland!
Are you OK, Glam?
Looks like we're both going
to be screwed this time.
[GASP] It figures. It's like those
big-budget action flicks. [GROANS]
The secondary characters
always get killed off.
But if I'm going, it's going
to be with some class.
Geez! Only you would be concerned about
dying in some really pretentious fashion.
[GRUNTS]
Shogo, run! We'll handle our own
screwups. We're not kids!
- That's right!
- Come on out, Yahagi!
Or your friends are going
to burn to death!
Shogo! No! Why didn't you run?
Leave us, you idiot!
[MUSIC RESOLVES]
You're nothing but kids!
A bunch of damn brats!
How dare you mock the military!
How dare you?!
[GASPS, GRUNTS]
So, you're out of ammunition,
are you?
Come on out of there, Yahagi!
[CHUCKLES]
[LAUGHS UPROARIOUSLY]
Sneaky little bastard!
Bastard? Huh!
Yahagi? So sorry!
Wrong asshole!
[LAUGHS DEMENTEDLY]
- Hah! Wrong jackass in the box!
- [LAUGHTER]
Help! We're under attack!
No! It's impossible!
Not here!
Commander! They've got
us surrounded!
Shields! Use your sabres!
What in the-?
How could the enemy have
penetrated this far?
Sergeant! Are you all right? The
brats pulled a fast one on us!
Yahagi was the one
that escaped first!
Sergeant! What's wrong,
Sergeant?!
We made it!
That came from back where
Lightning was! You don't think...?
No way! He's immortal.
[MYSTERIOUS MUSIC]
Huh? Yui! Are you...?
I... I'll be fine.
We're almost there.
Are you all right, Yui?
Yeah...
I'll wait here for Lightning
and the others. Be careful.
We made it, Eve!
What should I do now?
Operator... 7G?
That's right.
Confirming identification.
Please wait.
Confirmed. I am now
removing the barrier seal.
[MACHINES SPIN UP]
Shogo, when you didn't
come back for me...
Shhh... Don't try to speak.
- [GROAN]
- [GASP]
[SAD RISING NOTES]
Hey Yui! Yui...!
We've gotta get you to a doctor.
No, Shogo! Please... I have
to ask you something first.
But... you need help.
Six months ago...
I kept waiting for you...
I kept waiting all night long.
[SOFT GASP]
And all the next month...
I kept waiting.
Yui...
Why didn't you come
back for me, Shogo?
Because... I was trying
to protect you.
- Because...
- What good is safe...?
If I... couldn't be with you?
[GASPS]
Yui, hold on!
You can't die!
- [EERIE MUSIC]
- Do not despair.
Her life has not yet ended.
Eve...
Please, bring her here.
You can help her?
Hold on, Yui.
You can't die now.
She will not. Treatment
is still possible.
[GASPS] Eve?
Is something wrong?
Please come over here and have
a seat, OK? Talk with me.
I did come to you!
And all of us risked our lives!
And I didn't come all this way
just to watch you put on a show!
Do not be upset.
But we need to talk.
Then start talking, OK?
Stop beating around the bush,
and be straight with me!
Is this... all some kind of test?
But what would you
be testing me for?
I don't have anything to hide.
Why didn't you join the army?
I... I don't like the way
they do things.
What don't you like?
Let's start with the whole \"might makes
right\" mindset, and enforced conformity.
And how if you're against
them, you're trashed.
And how everything is handled
by procedure instead of thought.
Five hundred years ago, mankind brought
Earth to the brink of total destruction.
At that point, the United Nations passed
the Earth Preservation Law...
and gave all control to ADAM.
To allow the Earth time
to heal itself...
the surviving cities were sent into
space for a period of five hundred years.
Now that time has arrived.
Tell me... do you love Yui?
I like her.
[WEIRD TRILL]
Define \"like.\"
It's how I feel like I always
want to be with her.
How I want to protect
her from harm.
[SIGHS] To be honest, if that's what
you want to define as love...
I guess I love Yui.
Or, more accurately,
that I'm beginning to.
If you had a wish,
what would it be?
[SIGHS]
That I could go back
to my favorite cafe...
My friend's bike shop...
Hang out with my friends, and ride our
bikes through the old neighborhood, y'know?
- Uh-huh.
- To be able to see 'em whenever I want.
Or just to talk on the phone,
and shoot the bull.
I want to live... and be happy.
That's all, really.
What does... being an adult
mean to you, Shogo?
[SIGHS] An adult...
Well, it's something I wanted
to be when I was little.
But now I've learned to see
adults for what they really are.
Lying, hurting, killing each
other, and for what?!
To make themselves rich.
To gain more power!
They do it just
because they can!
That's why! And that's why
I don't want to be an adult!
Not if it means being like them, and
not the ones I worshipped as a kid!
The ones I saw in the
movies, and on TV.
[SIGHS] Could you do that? Be like
the adults you admired back then?
You mean, be...
an adult?
If you could, you could change
this whole misguided society.
- Will you?
- Now, hold on, Eve-
[SYNTHESIZED QUAVER]
Why are you asking
me these things?
[PULSING ALERT]
[SOFT GASP]
ADAM is calling me.
I must answer.
- What the? - What happened?
- What's going on? - What happened?
[BASS RUMBLE]
Where's this data coming
from? Analyze it!
- It's something called ADAM!
- We can't block it, or convert it.
The ADAM protocols are
loading... Initiated.
But as for mankind's
return to Earth...
only the ADAM program can
make that determination...
as to whether the data I send
meets the allowed criteria.
The EVE program was designed
to return to Earth...
only those who would not
repeat the same mistakes.
I am now sending
my data to ADAM.
You said the Earth. Is that
where we're heading?
We are already there.
However...
- What? - Is this for real?
- The Earth? She can't be serious!
Won't this ADAM let us
return to Earth?
I'm afraid I don't know.
But why not?
Because ADAM is refusing
to answer my queries.
His authority supersedes my own.
I cannot make him answer.
[CONTEMPLATIVE MUSIC]
Hey, it's OK.
Actually, I'm not sure we're good enough
to warrant continuing anyway.
I'm just glad that someone cares
about me and my friends.
And that I could meet you.
Thank you, Eve.
Thank you...
Thank you, Shogo.
Please don't let go of the
hope in your hearts.
I will do everything
I can for you.
For all of you.
I won't.
[PHASE OUT]
Shogo? Where's Yui?
With Eve.
So where are Lightning and
the rest of the gang?
They haven't made it yet.
- You don't think they-
- They'll be here.
Lightning's immortal, remember?
- [VEHICLE APPROACHING] - Huh...?
- [GASP] - Someone's coming!
[MECHA TWANG]
Yahagi!
[GASPS]
You're... not getting away,
you bastard!
[GROANS]
- He's dead.
- [METALLIC CLANK]
[GASPS] Shogo!
Oh my god, the sonofabitch
really is immortal!
You really are alive!
Don't kill me off just yet!
- You bastard!
- You had us worried.
You scared the piss out of me!
- [SNIFFLES]
- Sorry we're late.
[SIGHS] Dump was dragging
her ass. [LAUGHS]
Well, excuse me!
Glam's just out cold.
So where's Yui got to?
- I left her with Eve.
- So you met her? Really?
Yeah...
- That's awesome!
- Yeah...
Thanks to you guys.
Sir, Bahamut has now completely removed
itself from our control system.
The entire Megazone
is starting to fall apart.
The ADAM program is now
controlling everything, sir.
It's ordering Megazone 23
to tear itself to pieces.
Sixty minutes until complete collapse.
And there's more, sir.
We've been detected by defense
systems on the Moon?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
All forces, cancel
current operations.
All units will escort as many residents as possible
to either the spaceport or emergency shelters...
after which, we will
abandon MZ23.
Citizens of Tokyo, this is
a national emergency.
Please remain calm, and proceed to the nearest
public shelter as quickly as possible.
You are to take whatever spaceships
are left on Megazone 23...
and get as many of the citizens off
as possible. Is that understood?
All: Yes, sir!
[FAINT CONFUSED CROWD CHATTER]
Shuttles from this shelter are proceeding
towards the spaceport.
There's no danger! Please remain calm and
move quickly to the rear of the shelter!
I see. So that's how it is.
I'm in love with Eve
all over again.
- You and me both.
- Hey hey! You've already got Yui, you dog!
And you've got me!
I want a ring!
Ow! OK, OK, you got it!
- How are you guys?
- Well, my head's swollen... bigtime.
But, that's normal, and
otherwise I feel pretty good.
- I'm fine. Don't baby me.
- Just drink it.
- Hey, Shogo!
- Huh?
[SCREAM OF RAGE]
What'd you expect? That I'd stand there?
That's not how this world works!
Right doesn't make
might, understand?
Stand up, Yahagi!
Get on your feet!
Why do you bastards... always
think you can look down on us?
Is it because you're older?
Is that what it is? Just because you're
strong, you can do anything...?
Destroy everything? If you're strong,
that makes it right?!
Well this is the result.
That's it? That's all you got?
Would there be any point?
It's all just a waste of time!
[TWANGING VIBRATION]
That's ADAM, the Moon's
defense system.
The entire Moon is
one giant weapon.
And that is Dezalg.
The enemy that we've
been fighting.
[HAPPY POP MUSIC]
By the light of the stars
coming through the window...
I gauge the distance
between the two of us.
Feeling around, I fear your lips.
Though I couldn't make a sound...
I tried calling out your name.
~i~Somewhere inside me...~b~
- And I guess this ship's next? - Perhaps.
But where there's life, there's hope.
You can never give up.
What can the two of us do for love?
- I want you to tell us.
~b~- And a new age begins.~i~
You're not scared?
The world that we had was
one worth living for.
[SIGHS]
However, the time when I could live
as I thought was right has ended...
at least for now.
And the truth is that I envy all
of you for what will come.
Shogo Yahagi, it's not likely
that we two will meet again.
B.D....
A pig-headed showoff
until the very end.
The way you always smiled at me...
I could not tell you how
clumsy it made me feel.
Because it made you seem so far away...
it made me feel lonely.
I want the two of us to find
words of passion for love.
Don't forget love.
Please give me a dream-like secret.
What can the two of us do for love?
I want you to tell me.
Don't let go of love.
Please give me a dream-like secret.
I want the two of us to find
passionate words of love.
Please don't forget love...
Is everyone OK?
It's quiet.
It's just a matter of time...
even in here.
Well, if we're gonna die...
I'd rather do it someplace where there's
enough light to see the faces of my friends.
[GASPS]
Yui!
Shogo!
Hey... are your wounds
hurting you?
No, they're all completely healed.
So, were you able to see Eve?
Yeah, and she told me something.
To grow up like the adults
I used to admire as a kid.
- [GENTLE SCOFF] You?
- Yeah. It's a bit late now.
~b~[A cappella]~i~ By the light of
the stars coming through the window...
~b~- [WIND WHISTLING]~i~ - ...I gauge
the distance between the two of us.
Feeling around, I fear your lips.
~b~- [BIRDS CHIRPING]~i~
- Though I couldn't make a sound...
I tried calling out your name.
Somewhere inside me,
someone else is there.
- What can the two of us do for love?
~b~- [INSTRUMENTS JOIN]~i~
Hey, Shogo!
[CHUCKLES]
[TRANQUIL TRILLS]
[ENERGETIC POP MUSIC]
Lonely sunset... Woohoo... Lonely sunset...
The pavement on the final day of summer.
I was watching him from behind.
His skin was so fair and hot...
and suggested something to me.
The silver pendant fell off quietly...
(Lonely sunset)
making a small sound.
We gazed at each other...
as if there were very serious....
(Gazed)
reasons for it.
Lonely sunset...
I'm afraid to weep.
(Afraid)
Lonely sunset...
I'm so scared, it's so hard.
(Hard)
I sensed the ending of our relationship.
I don't want to figure it out that way.
How stupid of me to be so understanding.
[SAXOPHONE SOLO]
(Lonely sunset... Woohoo...)
(Lonely sunset)
We used to go... (Lonely sunset)
arm-in-arm...
all the time back then...
(Lonely sunset)
but even that is tough to do now.
Everything we do implies some meaning...
(Implies)
but it's too much for me to bear.
Lonely sunset...
We're both to blame.
(Blame)
Lonely sunset...
It's stupid of me...
(Stupid)
to be thoughtful...
to make our farewell...
easier.
Lonely sunset... (Lonely sunset)
I'm afraid to weep.
(Lonely sunset)
Lonely sunset... (Lonely sunset)
I'm so scared, it's so hard.
(Lonely sunset)
Lonely sunset... (Lonely sunset)
We're both to blame.
(Lonely sunset)
Lonely sunset... (Lonely sunset)
I hate it because it's our fault.
(Lonely sunset)