[alarm blaring]
[SOLDIER A]
Go!
[SOLDIER B]
Get back!
[SOLDIER C]
Attack!
[SOLDIER D]
Move in!
Wha-- What is that thing?
[NARRATOR]
Since the beginning of time,
mankind has always
been at war with things
"out of this world."
Luckily, the humans have
had a secret weapon.
At the forefront of these
battles were "The Witches."
Teenage girls with
extraordinary magical powers.
[NARRATOR]
However, in the year 1939,
an enemy unlike any known
before overwhelmed Europe
and was poised to
take over the world.
This enemy became
known as "The Neuroi."
No one knew where
they came from or why,
but their attacks
were so deadly,
they left behind nothing but
heartbreak and devastation.
People were driven
from their homes.
Cities were destroyed, and
countries were left in ruins.
[NARRATOR] In an effort
to overcome their new,
vicious enemy, mankind
developed "Striker Units."
These modern day magical
brooms would boost
the Witches' power and,
more importantly,
allow the girls to take
their battle to the skies.
The best and most
powerful Witches
from around the world
were then dispatched
to take their place on
the front lines in Europe
with this new weapon.
They became known as
"The Strike Witches."
[SCHNAUFER humming]
Looks to be all
clear, once again.
That does it for me.
Time to head in.
[SCHNAUFER sighs, giggles]
The moon is just so beautiful.
Maybe I'll fly around for
a little while longer.
[static]
[gasps]
[MINNA] Saint Trond base
to Major Schnaufer.
Do you copy? What's your status?
[SCHNAUFER]
Uh-- Sir, yes, sir.
Major Schnaufer
to base. All clear.
There's nothing
unusual to report.
[MINNA]
Copy.
The Neuroi in
Karlsland have been
pretty quiet the past few weeks,
so that's what we were
expecting to hear.
[SCHNAUFER]
Roger that.
I'm still on alert but
anticipate continued peace, sir.
[MINNA]
As do I.
Be careful, though,
don't let your guard down.
We aren't familiar
with Neuroi...
[static]
Saint Trond?
Sir, do you read me?
Colonel, you there, sir? Sir?
A Neuroi.
[SCHNAUFER]
I know you're here somewhere.
Are you playing a
little hide and seek?
There you are!
How could I not notice
that it was so close
to me this whole time?
Target acquired and locked.
The Neuroi just changed!
Lost him! Must've seen me.
Yep, he saw me!
[SCHNAUFER grunts]
You're fast!
[SCHNAUFER]
You are good, but so am I.
[SCHNAUFER grunts]
You're about to go down.
[pants]
[static]
[MINNA]
Saint Trond to Major Schnaufer.
Are you all right?
What happened?
Yes. I'm fine.
I did just take down
a Neuroi, though.
[MINNA]
Wait, you're fighting a Neuroi?
[SCHNAUFER]
No. Well, not anymore.
It's been destroyed.
[MINNA] I'm going to need
a full report, Major.
Return to base, now.
[SCHNAUFER]
Roger that, Colonel. On the way.
[MICHIKO]
Yoshika! Where did you go?
Yoshika?
[gasps]
[BROWN BEAR growls]
[MICHIKO screams]
[YOSHIKA]
Hi, Michiko!
[giggles] He's safe. C'mon
Huh?
Hey, Yoshika? I think
I recognize this bear.
Isn't he that cub you healed?
Yeah. He's grown
a lot, hasn't he?
[giggles] You can
say that again!
How's the studying?
You applied to that school,
right? What's it called?
Teito Girl's Medical
School or something?
Actually, I haven't filled
out my application, yet.
[MICHIKO] That's understandable.
I mean, you were busy
fighting the Neuroi.
[YOSHIKA] Yeah. But the
entrance exam is almost here,
and I have a lot of
catching up to do.
I won't let it
get to me, though!
I'll do whatever it
takes to be a doctor!
[BOTH gasp]
Hey look, I bet that's his mom.
Thanks for the ride. You can
drop us off right here.
See ya later!
[sighs] Oh! I forgot
about the herbs!
I found some Saint John's wort!
Really? That's amazing!
That stuff works wonders
healing minor cuts and bruises.
--Where'd you find it?
--[PUPPY barking]
[barking]
[YOSHIKA gasps]
Oh, no!
[MICHIKO]
Yoshika! Please be careful!
Come here!
[PUPPY barks]
Gotcha. Don't worry!
You're safe now.
[sighs] Good. They're okay.
[YOSHIKA grunts, yelps]
[gasps] Oh, no! Yoshika!
[gasps] Sorry, puppy dog!
Hang on, I'll get us
out of this, I promise.
[MICHIKO]
Yoshika!
[gasps]
Oh, Yoshika!
[MICHIKO]
Are you okay?
[laughs] Yeah, that
was kinda scary!
[yelps]
[MICHIKO gasps]
[gasps]
[YOSHIKA screams]
Is that what I think it is?
H-How am I flying?
Rescuing the dog was
an honorable thing to do,
but next time, maybe
think about your own
swimming skills
before you jump in.
You're right. Sorry about that.
[HATTORI]
No need to apologize.
[YOSHIKA]
I can't thank you enough.
[PUPPY barks]
[barks]
Hey! Are you thanking
her for saving us?
Yoshika! I'm so
glad you're okay!
Michiko!
Yoshika? Wait!
You're not the Ensign
Yoshika Miyafuji, are you?
Uh-- Yes,
but, how'd you know
what my last name was?
Sir! Sgt. Hattori.
It's an honor.
I'm a First Year at the
Fuso Imperial Academy.
Please forgive my
ignorance, sir.
I've always admired you,
Ensign Yoshika Miyafuji.
I mean, you saved the
Akagi aircraft carrier
on your first flight ever.
And there's no
question to me at all
that the 501st Strike Witches
are the best of the best!
Your squadron fought to save
both Gallia and Venezia.
You truly are a legend.
[YOSHIKA]
I don't know what to say.
Major Sakamoto has told me
so many stories of your bravery.
About all of your missions in
Europe and what a hero you are.
What? Sakamoto?
Yes!
In fact, the reason
I came here today
was to bring you orders
directly from Major Sakamoto.
She wants you to come to
Europe and study abroad.
Go to Europe?
To study abroad?
[MICHIKO] Yoshika, I didn't
know that you were an Ensign.
[YOSHIKA]
Yeah!
They gave me a promotion right
after we liberated Romagna.
Wow! That's amazing.
[GRANNY MIYAFUJI]
Well, wouldn't that be nice?
Yoshika studying abroad at
a Medical School in Europe.
[HATTORI]
Yes, ma'am!
And I'm honored to say
I have been asked
to accompany Ensign Miyafuji.
Is something the
matter, Yoshika?
It's just that this is
all a little sudden.
Understandable.
Well, there's a school
interested in you.
And I think their
offer is incredible.
The Helvetia Medical School
asked me to tell you
that they would like
you to come to Europe
and enroll to be a
student of theirs.
Huh? How wonderful!
Helvetia has one of
the best Medical Schools
in the whole world.
What? Do they really?
Yep!
It's one of the top three
Medical Schools in Europe.
Uh...
Helvetia, here I come!
Wait, are you sure?
It's a big decision.
Shouldn't you think about it?
Nope! Don't need to.
This is my chance to
become a great doctor.
Excellent! I was
hoping you'd go.
Promise me this, though.
Study hard and do your best,
learn all that you can
about Western Medicine,
and then, bring it home to us.
Yes, I promise.
[ship horn blows]
Goodbye! Wish me luck, everyone!
Please, take care
of yourself, Yoshka.
Good luck and do your best!
Goodbye, Yoshika!
Have fun in Europe!
Don't forget to write!
Bye-bye, I'll miss you!
It's kinda crazy
how fast they were able
to rebuild, don't you think?
Yeah, totally! Look!
They're already working
on the bell tower!
It's my favorite
part of the city.
I hope they finish it soon.
[gasps]
[FRANCESCA]
It's the Regata Storica!
Uh, what? I don't speak Italian.
It's one of the
biggest gondola races,
and it starts next week!
[chuckles] Now there's
a language I do speak.
[CRESPI] I was afraid there
wouldn't be a Regata this year.
Weren't you, Captain?
Of course, and
luckily, the Neuroi
aren't occupying
this area anymore.
Um, Martina.
Could you please stop
rocking the gondola?
[laughing] Oh, the
sweet taste of victory
will be ours, yet again.
That's the truth.
As long as we have
Luciana rowing for us,
we'll be unstoppable.
[SHIRLEY]
I'm the fastest there ever was!
Oh, no!
[SHIRLEY]
I will not be beaten!
[CRESPI]
Not the 501st...
[MAZZEI] Charlotte Yaeger
and Francesca Lucchini!
Hiya, losers!
You wanna race, Squad Redpants?
What?
Oh, it's so on!
No!
Why in the world do you
always have to do this to me?
The first one to the
Rialto Bridge wins!
It's time to kick it
into high gear, Luciana,
and that's an order!
Okay, here goes!
[WITCHES shouting]
[MAZZEI]
Can we settle this another way?
[SHIRLEY]
Now, that's a winner talking!
Ha, ha! Hope you
enjoy the view!
Ugh! Shirley!
[laughs] What are you
worried about? I got this.
[MALVEZZI]
Why won't they just give up?
[CRESPI]
You're doing great, Luciana?
Seriously-- No more
jumping! Please!
No!
They're cathing up, Captain Fer!
We gotta do something!
Luciana, I need you to
activate your magic power!
Huh? But, Captain,
wouldn't that be cheating?
Are you questioning an order?
Quit messing around and do it!
[laughing]
[FRANCESCA]
Hey! That's not fair!
Oh, no, you did not!
You messed with the wrong witch!
[FRANCESCA]
Go get 'em, Shirley!
[SHIRLEY]
You got it!
It's time for the 501st
to teach you how to lose.
[CRESPI]
They're gonna pass us!
[MALVEZZI, MAZZEI yelp]
How 'bout this view? Enjoy!
[SHIRLEY yells]
We're not slowing down.
[FRANCESCA, SHIRLEY screaming]
[FRANCESCA screams]
Guess we lost.
[FRANCESCA]
Owie!
[MALVEZZI]
That looks pretty swollen.
[CRESPI]
And pretty painful.
[sobs]
It's like a clown nose
sitting on your head.
Do you think you could use magic
to try and heal her, Captain?
[MALVEZZI sighs]
I'll see what I can do.
Hey-- That's super itchy.
[MALVEZZI] Oh, relax.
It always feels that way.
That's how you
know it's working.
Not Yoshika's.
Her healing magic
was never itchy.
True. I wish I knew
how Yoshika did it.
And Miyafuji's patients
saw results immediately.
If I remember
correctly, that is.
Are you actively trying
to hurt my feelings?
No, sir! That was
nothing against you!
I'm just joking.
Come on, everyone knows
that Ensign Miyafuji's gift
for healing is like
one in a billion.
Agreed.
Which makes it extra sad that
she lost all of her magic
and healing abilities
during the Mars Operation.
[sighs]
If it wasn't for Yoshika,
we wouldn't be able to have
a Regata Storica this year.
I wonder where she is.
And what she's doing right now.
[CRESPI] Oh, wow!
It looks so much better!
Very impressive, Captain Fer!
Yeah, but it still itches!
[MALVEZZI]
Oh, quit being such a baby!
You poor thing. All better now?
[alarm blares]
No way!
[MALVEZZI]
A Neuroi?
[SHIRLEY]
This can't be happening!
[FRANCESCA]
How'd we miss it?
[CRESPI] This area was clear!
Where did it come from?
And why wasn't there an
alert from the lookouts?
Captain Fer!
I'm not getting a
response back from base!
What's going on?
Francesca!
I'm on it!
[gasps] They brought
their Striker Units!
The 501st is always prepared!
[grunts]
[growls] Well, what
are we waiting for?
We don't have any
Striker Units, sir.
[MALVEZZI growling]
Why weren't we prepared?
Francesca, the radios
aren't working
and we need to keep
each other posted,
so don't go too far.
Ah--
You ready? Let's do this!
[FRANCESCA]
Roger that!
[SOLDIER E]
All units, hold your fire!
[SOLDIER F]
We've got reinforcements!
The Strike Witches are here!
[gasps]
[SHIRLEY]
Almost there, Francesca!
Just a lead 'em
out a little more!
You got it!
[yelling]
[SHIRLEY]
It's time to finish him.
The shot's all yours! Take it!
[FRANCESCA]
Copy that!
I've got him!
Look down! He's below you!
[FRANCESCA]
How'd it-- What?
[SHIRLEY]
It transformed!
[FRANCESCA]
You're mine!
[FRANCESCA grunts]
So you wanna play rough, huh?
Hey! Hey!
[gasps]
What is she doing?
[FRANCESCA] Shirley, I think
she means the bridge.
Oh, I get it!
[laughing] Follow me,
big guy! Let's dance!
[SHIRLEY] There's the bridge!
Time to put an end to this!
They're almost here!
Exactly as planned.
You are not getting past me!
He's all yours!
[yelling]
Woo-hoo!
[MALVEZZI] Another brilliant
plan from yours truly.
[MAZZEI] I must agree.
It was a wonderful plan, sir.
Shirley.
I'm glad we got him,
but where do you figure
that Neuroi came from?
He put up a pretty good
fight for just a straggler.
You don't think
there's more, do you?
Our job is to be
ready either way.
[HATTORI]
I feel so lucky!
I still can't believe
Major Sakamoto trusted me
with the honor of bringing
Ensign Miyafuji to Europe.
I'll do my best, I promise.
And I'll make you very
proud of me, Father.
[door clicks]
Can I come in?
Oh, yes, of course,
Ensign Miyafuji.
[YOSHIKA] This ship is
so big. I kinda got lost!
That might be because the Amagi
is the largest aircraft
carrier in Fuso's arsenal,
coming in at exactly
260 meters long.
Wow.
You sure know a lot
about ships, Miss Hattori.
Just like Michiko does!
Sir, It's not necessary
to call me "Miss."
Sgt. Hattori is fine.
[sighs] Hey.
Do you mind if I ask
you how old you are?
No, not at all, Ensign.
I just turned 14 years old.
Whoa!
I can't believe that you're
two years younger than me.
I guess I just thought
you were older
because you seem so mature.
Oh, I didn't mean to
confuse you, Ensign Miyafuji.
[giggles] Don't
worry about that.
And call me Yoshika.
No, that's out of the question.
Military Regulations.
Well,
a few years ago, Major
Sakamoto told me something
I'll never forget.
She said that we didn't
necessarily have to worry about
each other's' rank all the time
if we were friends, first.
Major Sakamoto said that?
Yep! So I'll call you Shizuka.
Or maybe Hattori
if you'd rather?
And you can call me Yoshika
or Miyafuji, I guess.
I'll let you decide.
Okay. Ensign, uh, Yoshika, sir.
[giggles] Thanks, Shizuka!
Of course. Uh, Yoshika, sir.
Would you like me to
help you get settled
and unpack your things?
Military regulations state
that all belongings
be stored in one of these
while you're on the ship.
It helps us to stay
organized, otherwise,
personal items tend to pile up
over time, as you may know.
Yoshika. Where's all your stuff?
It's in the bag, right here.
That's all you brought?
One bag? You fit
everything in there?
I sure did.
But... I don't understand--
Where are your uniforms?
What about all your books?
Or your first and
second military dresses?
Oh, I didn't bring them.
What?
So, wait.
You're an Ensign and
you didn't think to pack
your officer's uniforms?
Well, no, why would I?
I'm not in the military anymore.
What are you talking about?
Of course you are!
You're an Ensign in the Fuso
Navy who's studying abroad
at a Medical School
in Europe, now.
And as a responsible,
high-ranking officer,
you're expected to abide
by Military Regulations--
including uniforms!
U-Uh... I'm so sorry.
[HATTORI]
Hm?
Where did Yoshika go?
[YOSHIKA humming, giggling]
Okay, I'm all done
chopping up the vegetables!
Great! That was quick!
Now, would you mind
starting on the mackerel, too?
[YOSHIKA] Sure! You want
three pieces, right?
What are you doing?
Oh, hi, Shizuka.
Are you having a good morning?
Just a few more minutes
and breakfast will be ready.
[HATTORI]
You are violating regulations.
Don't you understand
you're an officer?
And, as an officer, you
should know that cooking
isn't one of your duties.
But we're a team.
Which means that we
should work together
and help each other out.
That may be true.
But an officer
is still an officer.
[YOSHIKA]
Whoa, wait a second!
What about the fish?
[HATTORI] I am quite sure
it will all be fine.
Ready, Set, Take-off!
[YOSHIKA]
And a hard left turn--
Comin' at ya, Yoshika!
[gasps]
[YOSHIKA]
Got it! Yes! Thank you so much!
I love this stuff--
it's my favorite!
Ah! So delicious!
What exactly are you doing, now?
Oh. Just drinking a Ramune.
Do you want one? It's good!
[HATTORI] The Naval Officer
Regulations clearly state
that "One must behave
according to one's rank."
Therefore, an Ensign must
always act appropriately
in a way that respectfully
reflects the title of Ensign.
It's of the upmost importance
that you respect the rules
and traditions of the military.
I know.
You're one of the
most courageous
and admired Strike Witches ever.
Personally, I've always
looked up to you.
You're a hero of Fuso,
and it's about time
you started acting like it.
But when people
are so kind to me,
I feel the least I can
do is help them out.
Plus, I don't exactly
have what it takes
to be a Witch anymore.
[gasps] My apologies.
Even so, you're still
an Ensign, sir.
And because of that, it's part
of your job to set an example.
Our traditions have taught
us diligence and respect.
They've helped us...
[YOSHIKA]
Why do I think this must be
what Hartmann feels like
after talking to Barkhorn?
A-Achoo!
Cover your mouth!
Hygiene is an important part
of being a great soldier.
We must always be
in perfect health
so we can serve at our best.
Coming down with a cold
makes it impossible
to fight in battle.
And, even worse,
your compromised germs
could make others sick.
A multi-vitamin would--
[screams]
[BARKHORN] Di-Did you just
rub your snot on me?!
I just got finished--
[HATTORI] Do you understand
what I'm saying?
Yes, I understand.
I just don't know what to do.
[HATTORI] Study this.
And follow Regulations.
Right. Got it!
I can't believe it's
taken three weeks.
But at least we're
in Cape Town, now.
Looks like it.
But it's hard to tell in all
this fog we've got to deal with.
I mean, have you ever
seen anything like this?
[YOSHIKA grunts]
Yay. We're almost to
Cape Town, Africa!
[creaking]
[alarms ringing]
Oh, no! It's a Neuroi!
Captain!
It appears the ship's path has
been intercepted by an iceberg.
[CAPTAIN]
That's not possible!
The spotters should've seen it!
[OFFICER B]
Sir!
A fire alarm triggered near
the auxiliary generator.
Not now!
What's the status?
We have a fire in the corridor!
That's right by the ammunition!
Have you contained it?
The extinguishers
aren't working.
So we keep trying!
What about emergency valve?
[SAILOR C] It's on the other
side of the fire, sir.
Chief Petty Officer Yuki
is trapped there.
Tell me how it's looking, Chief.
[YUKI]
Not good, sir.
The collision with the iceberg
has damaged the valve.
It won't turn!
Then we're gonna need to
think of something else.
[HATTORI] I got here as soon
as I could, Lieutenant!
Is there anything you can do
to help get this fire contained?
I'll give it a shot, sir!
[grunting]
[HATTORI grunting]
[gasps]
[OFFICER D]
What do we do now?
Chief! Are you all right?
[YUKI]
Sir, the fire is spreading fast.
I need you to seal
this compartment
and flood it with water!
Hurry!
There's gotta be another way!
[gasps]
Sir, we don't have time!
Please, I'm telling you--
It's our only choice!
[OFFICER C]
Chief, you won't make it.
And if the fire gets
to the ammunition,
none of us will survive! Please!
We're running out of time!
What's the order?
The "Chief" has served this ship
longer than anyone. We must
respect his decision.
Flood the corridor.
The captain has okayed
the Chief's call.
This is our only choice.
Time to move.
You have your orders, Soldier.
Sir, yes, sir.
Please forgive me. I'm sorry.
[water splashes]
[gasps]
[YOSHIKA panting]
Yoshika, what are you doing?
[SAILOR C]
Ensign Miyafuji, stay back!
[YOSHIKA]
I can't!
[HATTORI]
Ensign, you have to stop!
They're flooding
the compartment!
But there's still
someone in there!
The Captain gave the order!
I'm not letting him die!
[gasps] Yoshika! No!
[YUKI coughing, wheezing]
Forget me. Just save the others.
You have to hang on!
You have to get outta here!
You help me, and we can do it.
[grunts]
What's the status?
[OFFICER C] The ammunition room
has taken severe damage
and will approach critical
temperature in three minutes.
Then you are to begin
the flooding in two.
[OFFICER C]
Yes, sir.
If there's another way,
she needs to find it fast.
There's nothin' else we can do.
It's not gonna budge.
We've got no other option.
Keep going. We can
do this, Yuki!
It's been two minutes.
We have to start flooding.
I failed you.
[gasps]
[OFFICER C]
The sprinklers!
[OFFICER D]
Yes!
[SAILOR D]
They got it!
[SAILOR C]
They really did it!
I knew they'd come through!
[OFFICER C chuckles] I thought
we'd lost 'em for sure!
[OFFICER D laughs]
They both made it!
[SAILOR C] Yoshika! Yuki!
Here, let me help you!
--Thank God you're both okay.
--[SAILOR D] Are you hurt?
[SAILOR D]
Thank you for saving him!
She's really
something, isn't she?
[YOSHIKA]
Wow, it sure is cold.
For some reason, I always
imagined that Africa
would be really hot.
I shouldn't have yelled
at you back there.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
But, yet again, you neglected
to follow Military protocol.
And you disrespected the Captain
by not following orders.
I know I did.
And I'm sorry
about that, but hey,
everyone made it out okay!
You don't get it!
Your reckless choice
could have sunk the ship!
When will you understand
you have to follow orders?
It was just dumb luck,
and if it hadn't worked,
we would all be dead.
I was just--
You follow orders! End of story.
Now, if you'll excuse
me, Ensign Miyafuji.
Uh--
I'm so sorry.
[HATTORI panting]
[HATTORI]
I see land!
We made it!
[YOSHIKA] Hey, Shizuka,
is that really Pas-de-Calais?
Uh--
[motor humming]
Huh?
[gasps] I know that sound.
[HATTORI]
Witches!
[HATTORI] That's a Hispano-Sulza
12Z and a Griffon 61!
That's--
The 501st!
Lynne, is that you?
Hello, Perrine!
Hi, Yoshika!
[YOSHIKA]
It really is you!
I was so excited to see you,
I flew straight here!
I'm glad you did!
It's great to see you!
[BOTH laugh]
[gasps] Wait.
Is this the real Master
Sergeant Lynette Bishop?
[PERRINE] Well, it's clear
they haven't changed a bit.
I mean, really, it's
only been two months.
[gasps] And you! You're--
[gasps] Lieutenant
Perrine Clostermann.
It's a real honor
to meet you, sir.
Hello. I'm Sergeant
Shizuka Hattori.
And I am reporting
for duty, sir.
[PERRINE chuckles] I've heard
quite a bit about you,
Sergeant Hattori.
You must be exhausted.
Yoshika can be a handful, huh?
What? No! It's not that!
[LYNNE] It's like I haven't
seen you in forever!
[YOSHIKA]
I know!
[BOTH giggling]
[YOSHIKA]
I missed you!
[LYNNE]
I missed you more!
Wow, I can't believe
you traveled so far
all by yourself!
That's so brave!
Thanks!
My father thought I should
take a trip to celebrate
my independence
now that I'm 14.
[PERRINE] I've been meaning
to ask you, Yoshika.
How is Major Sakamoto
doing these days?
Good? Did she say anything?
About me or about
the good ol' days?
I dunno.
When I came to visit the base
a while back, she wasn't there.
Someone did tell me that
she'd been sent away
on a big emergency
mission, though.
I wonder why I didn't
hear about that.
Wow! Look at all those grapes!
I'll bet they're delicious!
[LYNNE] They look sweet, but
they're actually pretty sour,
because these grapes
are used to make wine!
[PERRINE]
What do ya think?
Gallia's beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah.
It's almost hard to
believe it's real!
[LYNNE]
What's even more unbelievable
is that this area
belongs to Perrine.
[YOSHIKA]
Wow!
Good morning!
And what lovely news!
[gasps] Is that a real castle?
[PERRINE laughs]
[PERRINE] It looks so
much better than it did
right after the liberation.
We've worked to restore
everything we can.
Hello, ladies! Welcome back!
Good to see you!
Good day, Perrine!
We've made a lot of progress!
Hi, Perrine. Do you
wanna play with us?
[BOY A] We can't now,
it's almost time for class!
[PERRINE] Of course,
I promised you we would,
as soon as we finish math.
Good morning, Miss
Perrine. Welcome back.
I trust I didn't
miss anything eventful
while I was gone.
No, but a senator stopped by,
hoping to have a
word with you today.
Would he mind waiting
until after class?
I'm sure something
can be arranged.
[PERRINE] Okay! Shall we
get this class started!
--[GIRL A] Yeah!
--[KIDS giggling]
[PLANCHARD] Hey! Where are
you off to now, little buddy?
Hey, Lynette, who
are those kids?
All of these children
lost their parents
during the war
against the Neuroi.
Perrine was devastated and
decided to take them in.
Since then, they've
become one big family.
[PERRINE]
Now, raise your hand
if you know the
answer to this one.
[BOY B, GIRL B, GIRL C]
Me!
[PERRINE]
That easy, huh?
Uh?
[KIDS giggling]
You're a great teacher, Perrine!
It's so amazing what
you've done for them.
Well, it was the
right thing to do.
Besides, my mother and
father told me to always
help those in need.
Now, I have to run
to a quick meeting
with the Senator.
But if it's not
too much trouble,
would you do me a favor?
Yes, of course!
[PERRINE]
Would you mind making dinner
for all of the kids?
I think it would be a
special treat for them.
Especially from their
three new friends.
Sure!
Sounds good!
Cooking...?
Did you say something?
Sorry, I didn't hear you.
Sir! No, sir, not at all.
I'm very excited to cook.
[BOTH giggle]
[HATTORI grunting]
[YOSHIKA] How's everything
going over there?
Going great!
[GIRL B]
Whoa! This looks really fancy!
[BOY B]
I can't wait to eat it!
And now, let's show our thanks.
[ALL]
Thank you for the food!
This is so yummy!
It's delicious!
I can't believe we made
it all by ourselves!
Me neither!
We should do this again!
This soup sure smells good!
Sergeant Hattori, you said this
was your specialty, didn't you?
Yes, it was my
Mother's recipe, sir.
This is gross and
tastes like boogers.
U-Uh...
So yucky.
It's... unique.
An interesting flavor.
Yes.
That's exactly what I
was thinking, Lynette.
[screams] I'm sorry. I failed
you. It's awful. Forgive me!
[PERRINE]
Are you still thinking about
the soup mishap at dinner?
[HATTORI]
Lieutenant.
No! Well, yes.
I'm sorry I let you
and the children down.
Wanna hear something funny?
When I was young, I used
to think that cooking
was only done by cooks.
Me, too.
I come from a Military family
and everyone had a title.
That's just the way it was.
I bet when you were a child,
you had the talents of
a Witch, so they expected
you to behave as
a soldier would.
Why would they teach you to cook
when that wouldn't be your job?
[HATTORI]
Exactly. My family isn't like
the other Witches' families.
My father and grandfather
expect a lot from me.
[PERRINE]
Oh, now it makes sense why
Yoshika's getting
under your skin.
You come from a home with
very strict boundaries.
And she likes to
do her own thing.
[HATTORI]
That doesn't bother me!
I admire Ensign Miyafuji!
She's brave, and she
helped to liberate Europe.
She's a hero and I respect her.
I know you do,
but it frustrates you
that she doesn't act the way
you think a hero should.
She ignores Military rules.
She never follows orders,
just thinks for herself,
and trusts her "gut."
When we first met,
I didn't like her.
[gasps]
[PERRINE] Originally, she
didn't even wanna fight.
In fact, she hated
the idea of war.
The Neuroi wanted to kill us,
and she didn't wanna
go to war with them.
At first, I didn't
understand why she bothered
to join the 501st Unit.
It's kind of funny, now.
The truth is, she made
our squadron stronger.
Without her, who knows
would've happened
to my home here in Gallia.
[gasps]
[PERRINE] Myafuji and I may
not agree with each other,
but we're a family.
That's stronger than anything.
Thanks, Lieutenant.
There's no need to thank me.
Now, go get some rest, Sgt.
And you can consider
that an order.
[HATTORI] We're estimating our
arrival at 1800 hours. Over.
[HQ] Eighteen hundred
hours. Copy That. Over.
[HATTORI]
Sgt. Hattori out.
[PERRINE]
So you're going to want to head
southeast towards Reims.
Then, if you
continue from there,
you should make it
to Dijon by evening.
And that's where
we're staying tonight,
correct, Lieutenant?
Yes, that's correct.
But whatever you do,
stay clear of the border on
the freeway's eastern side.
If you cross the Rhine,
you will be in enemy territory.
And as soon as you enter
their camp, we can't help you.
[HATTORI]
Yes, sir.
[LYNNE] Here, Yoshika.
I want you to have this.
[YOSHIKA]
Uh, what is it?
It's a lab coat!
It's perfect! Exactly what
a real doctor wears!
Yep!
Every physician needs their
very own lab coat, don't they?
Lynette, how did you
hurt your fingers?
It's nothing. Really.
Just a little accident.
I guess I've still got
a lot of learning to do.
She learned to sew
just so she could make it
and has been working on that
coat for the past month.
You're the best
friend ever, Lynette.
I promise.
I'm gonna study hard
and be an amazing doctor!
I know you will.
I believe in you.
[YOSHIKA]
Thanks!
[engine revs]
I packed you a lunch.
Don't forget to eat, okay?
[YOSHIKA]
Okay!
And here's a little
something for healing
from our herb garden.
It's called Saint John's wort.
Never know when you'll need it.
Thank you, both. For
everything. See you later!
All right. We should get going.
Goodbye, Lynette!
Goodbye, Perrine!
See you later!
Have fun, Yoshika!
I promise, I'll send
you lots of letters!
[EILA]
Wonder what Nikka's deal is?
I mean, what could be so
important that you can't
take a minute to say
goodbye to your friends?
You know finishing her
assignment takes priority.
If she can find a way
to be here, she will.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
[POKRYSHKIN] I know that
Nikka's doing everything
she can to get back in time
to give you a proper send off.
Thank you for that.
And, Captain, it's been
an honor to serve you.
Yes, thank you, Captain.
You're both great soldiers
and you will be missed.
The 502nd won't
ever be the same.
[KATAJAINEN]
I made it!
Guys!
Hold on! Don't
leave yet! Please!
I told you.
She made it back just
in the nick of time.
I'm so glad.
And it looks like there was
no activity to report.
I dunno.
Wouldn't bet on that
if I were you.
[KATAJAINEN screams]
[EILA]
Really?
[SANYA]
I hope she's okay!
[EILA]
Seriously.
She has gotta have the worst
luck of anyone in the world.
[POKRYSHKIN sighs]
[POKRYSHKIN] That's the
second time this month.
What are we going to do?
These repairs will be expensive.
And, unfortunately, our
budget is tight as it is.
I'm sorry, but it's not
like the lightning
was my fault.
[sighs] The weather's getting
pretty bad out there.
You'll need to be careful!
Huh?
[SANYA]
Got it.
We'll do everything we can to
try and stay above the clouds.
See ya later, Nikka.
Try not to get struck
by lightning again!
See ya. Wait up--
Hold on a sec!
Nikka?
[KATAJAINEN]
Bye!
Don't forget to come visit!
You guys be careful out there
and watch out for
storms and Neuroi!
Oh, I almost forgot!
Remember, strikers
don't like lightning!
Yeah, we know!
[EILA sneezes]
Cold?
Yeah, maybe a little bit.
How about we try to
fly a little lower.
[EILA] I can't stop
thinking about Yoshika.
[SANYA]
I know.
Why'd your Tarot reading
have to worry me?
[EILA] It was your
idea to use the cards
to see the future
in the first place!
Let's hope for the best.
but it's not a good sign.
She's in Gallia, right?
On her way to that
medical school?
Yeah, and Gallia was
declared a safe zone
a while ago.
That's why it
doesn't make sense.
[BIRDS squaking]
That's strange.
Eila!
[EILA]
No! There's no way!
[SANYA]
I can't believe it. A Neuroi.
Oh, sorry. Hey, Shizuka,
did you want some?
It's really good.
I'll pass. I'm not
all that hungry.
I'm busy looking at the route.
Hope they're okay.
I need help!
Can I borrow
your radio, please?
[YOSHIKA]
Tell us what happened, sir.
[DRIVER] My village was
devastated by a landslide.
--People are badly hurt!
--[HATTORI] A landslide?
Oh, no!
I tried to call for help,
but all the phone
lines are down.
We have to help!
[HATTORI]
Understood, Ensign!
How strange, I can't
seem to get a signal.
I'll keep trying to see
if I can get it working.
I'll go back to
the village with you
to treat the injured.
We haven't got much time;
we have to hurry!
Wait. Are you some
sort of doctor?
Ensign, you can't!
That village is on the
other side of the border!
Perrine made it very clear
to stay on this si--
We're going! That's an order!
Yes, sir.
[DRIVER]
Right this way.
[panting]
This is awful.
First, we'll need
to stop the bleeding.
Those herbs that Perrine
gave me will hopefully
take care of that.
But I need-- Ma'am.
Do you have any bandages?
I'm sorry.
We've already used up
what we had.
Okay, well, what about
any clean sheets or towels?
[OLD WOMAN]
No. We have nothing left.
I have to do this. Sorry, Lynne.
[gasps]
They're alive. And it's
all thanks to you.
There's no way to repay
you for all you've done.
[sighs] Goodness. I can't
believe it's so late.
Any luck getting
in touch with base?
[HATTORI]
No. And it's not looking good.
I've tried to contact Saint
Trond, Sedan and Dijon.
But there's too
much interference.
Do you think it might
just be broken?
[HATTORI]
I checked before we left
and the radio was working fine.
I'd offer our phone,
but we still can't call out.
Can we offer you
a place to stay?
We don't want you on
the road after nightfall.
That's very kind! Thank you!
What a terrific idea,
don't ya think?
It is.
But we have to get
back on the road now.
We haven't made any of
our scheduled check ins.
[YOSHIKA whines]
Can't we do that tomorrow?
It's our duty to make
our appointments.
But you do whatever you want.
[DELIVERY MAN]
Sign here, please.
I can't believe it's
been almost a month
since the last delivery.
Well, I consider it
to be a good thing
that we're not busy.
Yes, sir, the rest
of the front line
is the same way.
I, for one, would love
for it to stay like this.
Me, too.
Well, that's gonna
do it for me, sir.
[MINNA] Much appreciated,
but stay alert out there.
[HARTMANN grunting]
Ugh. I broke a nail.
I can't feel my fingers.
This hurts so bad!
Please tell me I can
stop. I don't wanna...
[BARKHORN] Maybe you'll
be a little more careful
with your loader.
I don't wanna hear
it from you, okay?
This is so hard!
No, it's not. Now pay attention.
You just have to focus.
Only because you
have troll hands.
What did you say?!
Tell me something,
how do you even
lose your loader
in the first place?
Because, as every good
Karlsland soldier knows,
securing and inspecting
your weapons are of...
[SCHNAUFER] Lieutenant Colonel.
Pardon the interruption.
You have a call, sir.
[MINNA] So, a Neuroi has been
spotted in Venezia as well.
[SHIRLEY]
I'd say, I just don't know
where it could have come from.
There are no hives within
a 200-mile radius,
and the lookouts at
the Romagna border
haven't picked up anything.
We'll have to figure it out.
Go forth with the joint mission,
and keep me updated
on any changes.
[SHIRLEY]
Roger that!
First, they attack in Belgica,
and now we have Venezia.
[MINNA] We know the closest
hives are in Berlin,
Nuremberg, and Prague.
So, let's look at their
spheres of action.
Well, would you look at that.
These attacks are out
of the hives' range.
Tell me again about that Neuroi.
Of course.
Sir, it was a single
pilot, mid-sized craft,
spotted south of base, appearing
to be headed northeast.
So it didn't match the specs
of a normal scout, then?
Its mobility and firepower
were of a higher caliber.
And the shape was unlike
anything I've seen.
Interesting.
That description matches
with the Neuroi attack
that Shirley reported.
Do you think they could be
from the same hive, sir?
[MINNA] Venezia is approximately
800 kilometers away.
So, I can't rule it out.
However...
[gasps]
[MINNA] There aren't any
hives on that direct line.
Which means, the lookouts
should've been able
to intercept them.
But both of the recent attacks
somehow went undetected
by the border patrol.
I just don't understand
how these Neuroi
could slip through
our surveillance
and attack out of range.
Maybe there's a new hive
we don't know about.
If there is, we need to
investigate and find it.
I don't wanna.
How do we know the
lookouts didn't slip up?
I really don't see why it's
up to us to conduct recon.
The surveillance team
has been getting
a reputation for slacking
off and I don't see why
--it's on us...
--[HARTMANN] Hey, guys?
Isn't Miyafuji passing through
here on her way to Helvetia?
Engines on!
[BARKHORN]
RPM looks good.
Captain Barkhorn,
ready for takeoff.
Waiting for the go-ahead, sir.
So, I take it Captain
Barkhorn is rather fond
of this Ensign Miyafuji.
Yes. Yoshika Miyafuji is
basically her little sister.
Huh? Really?
That is very misleading.
We share no biological bond.
You shouldn't take
her seriously.
She has a habit of
manipulating the truth.
I'm gonna go on ahead
to find your sis.
She is not my sister, Hartmann!
We've almost made
it to the Rhine.
I need you to stay alert.
But everyone knows
this side of the river
is out of the range
of Neuroi activity.
We're completely safe here.
That's why we
need to investigate.
[HARTMANN]
Okay.
The Karlsland side is
looking pretty awful.
There's nothing we can do.
Any closer, and we would
be in grave danger.
Yeah, I know that,
but it's still my home.
[sighs] It'll be different soon.
'Cause we're gonna get our
land back from the Neuroi.
[HARTMANN]
Yeah! You got that right.
Seems to be all clear to me.
Looks like we can head back?
Not yet.
I think we should keep heading
south towards Lorelei.
Aw...
[stomach growls]
Ugh. My stomach can't take it.
Can we go now? I'm so
hungry, I'm about to die!
I suppose it would be nice
to get something to eat.
[gasps] Yay, food!
[BARKHORN]
Honestly.
Could you be any more immatu--
[gasps] Over there!
Do you see that?
It's a Neuroi!
Coming from underground?
I've never seen that before!
This is why we couldn't
predict the attacks!
Right, Hartmann. Let's go!
Yes, sir!
[BARKHORN yells]
One down!
Let's get the other.
Back to back!
Whoa! He transformed!
[BARKHORN]
I'm overheated.
Done with you.
So, I'm still hungry.
Well, you'll have to suck it up.
[growls]
Get 'im!
[yelling]
Can we eat now?
We still got that
chimney-looking one.
Where is he?
[sighs] He went that way.
[BARKHORN] Ugh! He just crossed
over into a safe zone.
Well, what do we do?
I'm out of ammo and magic.
And my empty stomach is
seriously eating itself.
[BARKHORN]
Picus! Do you read me?
This is Captain Barkhorn.
Minna, do you read me?
We've got a Neuroi on the
move at grid position G-14.
It has officially breached
the Rhine River barrier.
[HARTMANN]
He's moving fast.
I'm getting too
much interference.
Hey, what's this stuff?
Ah--
Maybe the reason I
can't get a response.
We need to get back to base!
I don't have the
strength to move.
I swear. You're so difficult!
This is the end. I don't
think I can make it.
Hang in there, okay?
No! I'm dying!
You are not!
You're unbelievable.
[HARTMANN giggles]
[BARKHORN]
Here. Eat it.
You have chocolate?
Yay! Here you go! We can split!
Thanks, but I'm okay.
You can have it all.
What? Really? Thank you!
No way! There can't
seriously be more!
[HARTMANN]
He's coming right for us!
[BARKHORN]
This isn't good.
We don't have any
weapons or magic left!
Hartmann!
I love chocolate!
Get out of there!
And sturm!
[sighs] I must admit.
I've never thought
of doing that!
Oh, no! She's fallen asleep!
Wake up! Hartmann!
Minna, what are you doing here?
I was worried when
we lost contact
that something had happened.
[BARKHORN]
Minna! We've got a problem.
The Neuroi have
crossed the border.
[YOSHIKA] That breakfast was
really delicious, huh?
[HATTORI]
Yes.
[YOSHIKA]
Did you get the radio working?
[HATTORI]
No.
We'll be arriving in
Helvetia tonight, right?
Yes.
So after that, then,
I guess I'm going
to be on my own?
I was assigned the
duty of delivering
you to your destination.
I'm going to miss
seeing you every day.
[HATTORI sighs]
[rumbling]
[YOSHIKA]
Stop the car!
[gasps]
It can't be!
A Neuroi!
I'll try to get through
to the nearest base!
I still can't call out!
We need to get to the
Bastogne base, immediately!
I won't! Those people need us!
It's too dangerous, Ensign!
It'll be my job to
evacuate the village.
It's up to you to try
and figure out a way
to buy us more time.
Me? But, how?
[VILLAGERS screaming]
[panting]
[yelps]
I can do this.
Ammunition loaded.
And safety off!
[HATTORI]
I know what to do.
Just follow the training
and everything will be fine.
You hold the rifle steady...
Close in on the target...
Until it's right in your sights.
Place the upper part
of the index finger
on the trigger...
And finally, you
focus on the shot.
And fire!
I did it! Just like my training!
[giggles]
Come on, we're almost there.
We've just about made it
to the raid shelter.
I've got this! It's
actually pretty easy!
[gasps]
[HATTORI]
One more...
Got 'im!
[gasps] How'd he do that?
[gasps] It transformed?
[gasps]
[yelps]
[HATTORI grunts]
Shizuka, no!
[YOSHIKA]
Are you okay? What happened?
Say something!
Yes, Ensign.
Can you stand?
We need to get you
to the shelter!
[gasps]
All able-bodied Witches
are needed in the field!
If you are seen slacking off,
you'll go without food.
[GRUNNE]
Major Heinrike!
I'll handle things here at base.
You're needed in battle, sir.
Have you gotten a hold
of the Dijon base?
[GRUNNE] No luck, sir.
I haven't gotten a response.
You don't think they've
been wiped out, do you?
This is Bastogne, Unit A!
We are under attack!
I repeat Bastogne, Unit--!
[COMMANDER]
We've got reports of Neuroi
in Malmedy and Clair-vu.
[COMMS A] Sir, I've lost contact
with the base in Sedan.
[COMMS B]
I'm unable to connect
with Büllingen, as well, sir.
Send the 101st Air Division
to Bastogne, now.
I want these Neuroi contained!
We're dealing with
a constant increase
of Neuroi activity.
This is bad.
They've got us
completely surrounded.
All right, it's up to us
to figure out a
way to stop this.
Otherwise, the Allied Forces
on the front lines
will be surrounded as well.
What about HQ?
What are they doing?
The enemy is interfering
with the radio.
That way, we can't
organize and retaliate.
It's not just the radio,
it's the phones, too.
I never imagined
they'd go underground.
They've literally been right
under us the whole time.
It almost reminds
me of the strategy
we used to defeat
the Neuroi at Malta.
So, what should
we do now, Minna?
[MINNA]
Given the scale of this attack,
we're either looking at
an unknown Neuroi hive,
or we've got an
enemy mother-ship
carrying a large number
of smaller Neuroi.
[door creaks]
We've got a big problem!
We've officially lost
contact with Yoshika.
What? Where is she?
It's heading straight
to the shelter!
I've got to get it
away from the village!
[grunting]
Hey! Over here!
He saw me!
[screams]
[gasps]
Did I lose him?
[sighs]
It really worked.
--Huh?
--[BIRDS screech]
[gasping, whimpering]
[YOSHIKA grunting]
[yelling]
[gasps]
Ensign Miyafuji...
Ensign! Come on,
Miyafuji. Talk to me!
[grunts]
Huh? Hey, Shizuka.
Where's the Neuroi?
[groans] Is everyone safe?
The target's been destroyed.
Everyone's alive and the village
is safe, all thanks to you.
That's good.
I'm glad to hear it.
Yoshika! Please,
you have to hang on.
What are we gonna do now?
[static]
This is Sergeant Hattori.
I'm near Saint Vith,
do you read me?
We've been attacked by Neuroi,
and Ensign Miyafuji has
been seriously injured.
Again, this is Sergeant Hattori.
I'm requesting emergency
medical aid. Do you copy?
[static]
Why won't they respond?
Please, someone, we need help!
[HATTORI]
What is this?
Maybe whatever it is, is what
they're using to jam the signal.
[grunts]
Yoshika!
[YOSHIKA grunts, pants]
Please, just hang on
a little longer, Yoshika.
I promise, I'll be right back.
Minna, are we getting close?
This is it.
The center of all the
recent enemy activity.
Be on alert!
Roger that.
Especially since we
still have no signal.
Sir, do you think
the enemy might
be causing this interference?
[BARKHORN]
Yes.
Most likely they're trying to
keep us isolated to cut off
our supplies and
catch us off guard.
I hope Yoshika's okay.
Please be okay.
That antennae of yours
is our only hope.
We're really counting on you.
[gasps] Yes... sir.
I will not let you down.
[HATTORI]
This is Sergeant Hattori.
[SCHNAUFER]
Wait...
I think I'm getting something.
[BARKHORN]
Really?
[MINNA]
What are you hearing?
[SCHNAUFER]
There's too much interference.
I'm not sure.
Just a little higher.
I need to get above the Neuroi.
Then I should be
able to get a signal.
Anyone! Come in! Do you read me?
This is Sergeant
Shizuka Hattori, over.
I need help. I've
got a soldier down.
Ensign Miyafuji needs help now!
Sir, I've got a signal.
I'm patching you in.
[HATTORI]
Please! Ensign Miyafuji is hurt!
It's an emergency!
Ensign Miyafuji?
Miyafuji!
Oh, no!
We have to save her!
Not Yoshika!
We're on the way!
Hang in there!
Roger that!
We'll be there soon!
[SAKAMOTO]
Miyafuji!
Someone heard me!
[MINNA]
Yoshika, can you hear me?
[BARKHORN]
Please, say something!
[HARTMANN]
Are you there?
Yes I... I can hear you.
[PERRINE]
Don't you give up!
[LYNNE]
Please tell me you're okay!
Please, please be okay.
[SHIRLEY]
Keep fighting, Yoshika.
[FRANCESCA]
Yeah, we're almost there!
Do you hear that, Ensign?
They'll be here soon.
Everything's gonna be okay.
[gasps]
[BARKHORN]
Miyafuji!
[HARTMANN]
Where are you?
[LYNNE]
Yoshika, say something!
I can hear them all.
They're coming to help me.
But with the Neuroi,
it's not safe.
I have to find them.
I need to hurry.
[HATTORI gasps]
Oh, no. What do I do?
[YOSHIKA] I can do this.
I'm gonna help them.
We will stop the Neuroi.
This has got to end.
What? The Neuroi stopped.
[YOSHIKA grunting]
[MINNA]
Is that...? It's a magic circle!
It's Yoshika!
How'd she do it?
She couldn't. There's no way!
When it comes to Yoshika,
anything can happen.
[FRANCESCA]
It's her, it has to be!
Way to go! I knew she
was gonna be okay.
My magic! It really came back!
[gasps] That's unbelievable.
[gasps]
[YOSHIKA]
No way.
I thought I already
stopped them!
[gasps]
Artillery fire?
Where is it coming from?
[PERRINE]
Did you hear that?
[HARTMANN]
It's a battleship!
The Yamamoto!
How did they know they
were needed in the Rhine?
I guess they broke
through the interference.
How did they get this far south?
They're insane!
[SAKAMOTO laughs] When one
of my own is in trouble,
I'll do whatever it takes.
I know that voice!
[PERRINE]
It's Major Sakamoto!
[MINNA]
Mio!
[SAKAMOTO] I did what I
had to in order to keep her
off the river bottom.
[HARTMANN]
I don't know about that.
[EILA]
Hey! Good to see ya!
[LYNNE]
Eila! Sanya!
[HARTMANN]
Um, guys? We got a complication.
[SHIRLEY]
Yahoo!
[FRANCESCA]
Let's do this!
[BARKHORN]
Shirley! Lucchini!
Just like old times!
[SAKAMOTO]
Hey, Minna!
I've got a little
surprise for Yoshika.
I need you to cover me.
Yes, sir. Battle
Formation immediately.
We will cover the Major
and show the enemy no mercy.
They need to know who we are!
[WITCHES]
Roger!
No. There's no way!
They're really gonna
take them on?
Time to sturm!
Tonnerre!
Are you ready
for this, Francesca?
Born ready!
[SHIRLEY]
Combine!
[LYNNE]
Huh?
[LYNNE screams]
Wow! They did it!
They're here!
[MINNA]
Looks like more are on the way!
[BARKHORN] And we're
gonna take 'em all down!
You won't be getting past me!
[SHIRLEY yelling]
[SHIRLEY]
You're going down!
[SAKAMOTO]
Incoming!
It's Major Sakamoto!
Got something for ya!
[gasps] The Shinden...
I missed you.
I wish I could be a Witch again.
I just wanna fight
alongside them.
I would give anything.
If I could fly... one last time.
Take off!
[laughing]
[LYNNE]
Yoshika!
Hello, Lynette!
I don't think so!
[LYNNE, YOSHIKA giggle]
You're back! I'm so happy!
I am, too! Can you believe it?
Oh, honestly.
I don't think she's ever
gonna stop being so reckless.
Yoshika's got her magic back!
[SHIRLEY]
Now, that's more like it!
[SCHNAUFER] We gotta know
how you did that, Yoshika!
[SHIRLEY] Yeah! What
changed to make it happen?
I'm not really sure.
I just remember hearing
all of your voices
and knowing that I
wanted to help, too.
I wanted to fight
alongside you guys
one more time.
[BARKHORN] Hey. Yoshika.
If you wanna fight...
...then you're gonna
need one of these.
[gasps]
Right!
[gasps] Where's Shizuka?
Is she okay?
[SCHNAUFER]
Sergeant Hattori is fine.
[gasps]
[SAKAMOTO]
Yoshika, look up.
It's good to see you, Yoshika.
You saved me. Thank you.
[SAKAMOTO laughs]
It's good to have you back.
It suits you.
Being up here in the sky,
back with your unit.
It's where you belong.
Welcome home.
Thank you, Sakamoto.
Lieutenant Colonel Minna!
I've got a mission
for you, Yoshika.
Are you ready?
Yeah!
[HARTMANN]
That's a pretty big Neuroi.
[BARKHORN] It must be
the enemy's mother ship.
[MINNA]
All right, Formation Julius.
Our target is the giant
Neuroi dead ahead.
[ALL]
Roger!
Amazing.
That's the 501st
from the stories.
Yes, they are.
Also known as
the Strike Witches.
Major...
How was Ensign Miyafuji
able to fly again
and get her magic back?
A Witch's magic can
work in mysterious ways.
And when it comes to
the power of genuine love
and real friendship,
anything can happen.
Friendship?
Maybe someday. Maybe...
I hope that one day I'll be able
to fly with friends like that.
[laughs] I know you will.
The core is revealed.
Witches, fire on my call.
What do we do now, Minna?
[LYNNE]
Yoshika, wait!
[BARKHORN]
What are you doing?
I'm gonna take him down.
Okay, everyone, deploy shields.
Follow Ensign Miyafuji.
[WITCHES]
Yes, sir!
Are they crazy?
Pay close attention.
This is what makes
them legendary.
The mark of true Witches.
Attack!
[gasps]
[HATTORI]
You did it!
Huh?
You really saved us, Ensign!
Shizuka!
You know, you really don't
have to call me that, right?
Right. Got it, Yoshika.
[SCHNAUFER]
Lieutenant Colonel.
I've just received word
of enemy movement.
HQ has detected Neuroi
ships heading toward
the Karlsland border.
You all heard her. Let's move!
It's up to us to take
down this new threat.
We must work as a team,
follow our instincts,
and stick together.
I think it's time for the
501st Joint Fighter Wing,
the Strike Witches,
to be reinstated.
What do ya say?
[WITCHES]
Yes, sir!