Alice, no!
Cassa!
Don't do that! You scared me.
You're such an utter failure.
You're better suited to be her
playmate than her protector.
Don't be so hard on him.
Jiro's doing the best he can,
so why don't you cut
him some slack for once?
If you say so.
Cassa.
Cassa. What a weird dream.
What the--?!
Oh. Good morning, Mimiko.
And good morning to you, Kotaro.
What's going on?
Don't worry about it.
I just had a little accident
and I don't wanna talk about it.
Oh.
Nice, huh? We've got a great
view of the river from here.
Yeah.
So is this still
the Special Zone?
That's right. Why do you ask?
Cause it looks a lot different
than it did last night.
Oh. Right.
The Special Zone's
a pretty big place.
What you saw
yesterday was the New Yard.
But now you're in the Old Yard.
And I guess that this area is
what you'd call our Downtown.
Looks like someone's moving in.
I didn't know that
the building across
the street was residential.
Can we eat soon, Mimi?
I'm starved.
Oh, right. Sorry about that.
Let's see what we've got to eat.
Do you think we should
wake Jiro up for breakfast?
Yeah.
I can't feel him breathing. You
sure he's still alive, Kotaro?
He's fine.
He's just sound asleep.
I bet he's really tired.
He didn't get to sleep
any during the day yesterday.
It doesn't look
like he's gonna wake up.
Well, I hope he
does soon, 'cause we have
to find you guys a
place to live today.
But I thought that we would
all just live here together.
Don't you think that it
would be a little cramped?
And besides,
grown-ups don't usually
move in together so casually.
But it's a pretty nice
apartment, don't you think?
Yeah. It's small,
but that just makes it feel
like a secret
hideout or something.
Thanks, I guess.
Oh no!
What time is it?
I have to go to wo--
Brother did that earlier. He
doesn't get modern appliances.
So he couldn't figure
out how to turn it off.
I'm massively late.
Wake the hell up!
You're sure about this?
Has the Silver Blade really
entered the Special Zone?
Yes. I have no doubt.
And I believe that every
other powerful group within
the Special Zone
is currently trying to
determine how best
to deal with his arrival.
Do you think they plan
to gain him as an ally?
Or perhaps, their aim
is to put an end to him.
Hypothetically speaking, if
Silver Blade and Zelman were to
clash in the Special Zone...
Could the suppression
team gain control of
the situation and
put them down quietly?
Impossible.
The battle between
the Hero of the Crusade
and an eight hundred year old
Black Blood
would be devastating.
I doubt that we
would have any chance of
stopping it once it began.
They're too powerful.
Then, allow me
to express my opinion.
We, the Company, must
seize control of Silver Blade.
We must have him,
no matter what the cost.
Keeping him in our custody, is
like harboring a bomb, Chairman.
I think it's better to
have him in our custody
than to hand him over
to the affiliate houses.
But that's just my opinion.
I'd like to hear your
thoughts on the matter...
As one of the human heroes.
Let's just say that I've...
already taken action on this.
You've always been
quick on the draw.
I ask this merely out
of personal curiosity.
But what kind of man
is this Silver Blade?
You are acquainted
with him, are you not?
That was a long time ago,
a lot's changed since then.
When I knew him,
he was just an immature brat.
A child to say the least.
Well then.
I'll leave him to you.
Chairman!
Are you sure about this?
I have my doubts.
Jinnai. Don't screw up.
Don't hurt me.
Please don't hurt me.
I promise it won't hurt.
It'll be the most pleasurable
thing you've ever experienced.
Prepare for the
ultimate physical pleasure.
Don't make me chase you.
What do you propose we
do about the Silver Blade?
I assume he'll approach
the Sei or Warlock house.
That makes sense. They do
have a history with him.
They met when they were in the
crusade together in Hong Kong.
So, it is possible that he'll
join forces with one of them.
Either way. It won't
be good for us if they
become any more
powerful than they are now.
This might be a
good opportunity for us to
show them what The Coven
is truly capable of.
No doubt about it.
So the Hero of the
Hong Kong crusade is here.
We'll need to
lay down the law...
as one of the leaders
of the Special Zone.
So this is where I work.
Cemetery management
is just our front.
Alright. Wait here a minute
and I'll see if I can find
anything that will help us.
Good morning everybody.
Uh, I'm sorry I'm so late.
Looks like nobody's here.
Oh, I'm sorry. Wait
a minute, Miss Mimiko.
Where in the
world have you been?
Hey, Hibari?! Good morning.
Don't "good morning"
me, Mimiko.
Everyone's been in an
uproar all morning long
because of what
happened yesterday.
The chief's been trying
to reach you all day.
He must have called
you a hundred times.
What's the deal? What have you
been doing all this time anyway?
Oh, you know,
stuff came up, things.
Everyone went
racing off to their
assigned affiliate houses
a couple of hours ago.
You might want to think
about joining them soon.
Yeah. I guess
I should get going.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Sure.
More importantly, Miss Mimiko.
I have some top
secret information that
has to stay between us.
Don't tell anyone, but
apparently yesterday's incident
involved the
famous Silver Blade.
Oh, right.
Did you hear what I said?
The Silver Blade!
The hero of the
Hong Kong crusade that
took place a decade ago.
He's the most powerful vampire
to ever side with humans.
A legendary man that
everyone in our line of
work surely knows about.
They say the
suppression team was
completely helpless
against him yesterday.
And they said he was laughing
as he wiped out the group of
vampires that
caused the commotion.
And now, they think
that this Silver Blade guy
may have made his way
into the Special Zone.
And to top it all off,
they think that somebody who
works for the company
actually invited him in. Crazy!
Okay, Hibari. Just calm down.
And now I might end up coming
face to face with him someday.
What'll I do? What'll I do?
What if he attacks me
and wants to suck my blood?
Talk about embarrassing!
What's the matter?
Oh. There you are.
Mimiko!
Look! I'm hangin' out!
Hot, hot, hot, hot,
hot, hot, hot, hot!
I must be really tired.
I think I'm seeing things.
That little kid was
a vampire, wasn't he?
Owie! Owie! That
wasn't very nice of her.
That's what you get
for not staying here
like she told you to.
Miss Mimiko! Is that--?!
Don't say another word!
Listen. You can't tell a
soul what you just saw, okay?
You understand, don't you?
I'm not playing around here.
Keep your mouth shut!
Now I have to go out for
a while to run some errands.
So please, keep our
little secret just between us.
Big news! Big news!
I have to tell everyone!
Aw man!
We need to lay low for a while.
At least until
things calm down a bit.
But who knows when that'll be.
Sounds like a
splendid suggestion.
Let's go back to your place
and catch up on our sleep.
No way!
My superiors could decide to
come by my house to see me,
and then there'd be no escape.
You poured water
on me this morning.
And I've been walking
around in the sun all day.
I can't tell you how
incredibly tired I am.
I've got an idea. Let's do
something relaxing, huh?
I've got it.
Here's what I'm gonna do.
I am going to find
you guys a place to live.
But, I want to
live with you, Mimi--
No discussion.
Okay. In the Special
Zone, once you've decided
where you want to live,
you go introduce yourself to
the head of
the House that
claims leadership
of that territory.
Those who belong to the same
house live clustered together.
And then those people
who don't belong to any of
the Houses are considered
to be guests of the House that
controls the area in
which they take residence.
Firstly, we need to decide
where you want to live.
There are three major Houses
that control different areas of
the Special Zone.
And the first one is--
The Mainland faction.
Another is the European faction.
And the final
group is a coalition.
Or to put it another way, they
are Snakes, Dogs, and Darkness.
Does that about sum it up?
H-How did you know all of that?
It's simply a microcosm
of the world at large.
Things never change, you know?
And, since I myself never age,
I've come to understand
a few things in my long life.
You're so smart, brother.
It's common knowledge.
Well, then. You'll have
to choose between the
three houses you mentioned
when you pick a place to live.
I know you ruled out one, right?
No Darkness.
I see. Those from the House
of Darkness who settled here
show no signs
of progress either.
Mimiko!
Are you ready to get started?
As we look for a place to
live we should treat ourselves
to a tour of the Special Zone.
Now, let's get going.
All right! We're off
to explore the Special Zone.
Hey. Hold on! Wait for me!
Now, this isn't a field trip.
Choosing you area
is serious business.
'Kay!
I mean it!
May I enter now?
Hello, Lord Zelman. I've come
to report my findings to you.
Good.
I've been waiting, Sayuka.
What is this, Zelman?
Don't throw a fit.
Auguste's crew
sent her over to me
in an attempt
to curry my favor.
Please tell me that
you've restrained yourself.
A human prepared
for you by the Coven.
There's no telling what
the Company will do to you
once they've
caught wind of this.
Don't worry, Sayuka.
I've made sure
to keep her alive.
If you find yourself
thirsting for blood,
then please, summon me.
After all. That's one
of the reasons why
I'm here to serve
you, Lord Zelman.
You dare to reprimand me?
You've grown
annoying as of late.
So...
What is it you've come
to report to me, Sayuka?
Well... The executives
of the Company have
entrusted the handling
of Silver Blade to
the Mediation Department.
Mediation. That's Jinnai, then?
He was a member of
the Hong Kong group.
Isn't that right?
Yes, sir.
And I believe
he fought alongside
Silver Blade in the crusade.
So he'll be on the
Company's side for sure.
No. He appeared
at the Marine Bank
earlier today to
seek a residence.
Oh-ho. The Warlock house, is it?
But it appears that
Cain Warlock refused to
see him for some
reason or another.
And now, the Silver Blade is
headed towards the Old Yard.
Given this information,
most likely,
he is now on his
way to meet with Sei.
That's great. This
is getting interesting.
However, Auguste Wyker's
group is beginning to show signs
of movement. And I'm
afraid that you will be
held responsible
if they run amuck.
I don't care
about that. Ignore them.
But sir--
I'm over it.
Does The Silver Blade have
a companion traveling with him?
Yes, his younger
brother, supposedly.
I see.
Then who's this I sense?
Has Sei grown so weak
that he hasn't even noticed?
Talk about pathetic.
Pardon me, sir?
Your report
is much appreciated.
It was... nothing.
I'm going out.
But the sun hasn't
set yet. You can't go out.
A VIP who's maintained
his silence for
ten years has come to town.
There's no way I'm
gonna miss his appearance.
Please, Lord Zelman, wait!
Quite impressive.
This is amazing. I can't
believe you can buy things here!
Wow, they sell pots,
clothing, food...
You can find anything!
I wanna live here, brother.
Um, Mimiko.
I just don't
understand why they had to
have such a
bad attitude about it.
I mean, did they
have to be that rude?
Can you believe
the condescending look
that teller gave me?
That ticked me off.
So what if
they're a huge bank?!
They can't treat
people like that.
Just try not to
let it bother you.
And I could have
used a little more help.
I'm doing this
for you, you know?!
Come on now.
Let's just all try to
calm down a little bit.
Oh, uh... Would you
mind paying for these?
I guess.
Yay!
Kotaro! Get a
hold of yourself!
You keep jumping like that this
whole boat's gonna turn over.
Sorry.
As you can see,
the float mart is kind of
like the Old Yard's kitchen.
You can get just
about anything here.
Can we go in there?
Please, please?
Sure thing. You guys feel
like grabbing some lunch?
Jiro, are you
affected by garlic?
Don't move.
I think that they
have us surrounded.
How'd they find us out here?
Brother, are you okay?
It seems that members
of the Darkness have come to
welcome us to the Special Zone.
Don't worry.
They're not the most formidable
group I've come across.
We'll just try to sidestep
them here and draw them away.
Let's get outta here so
innocent people don't get hurt.
Hey, Kotaro. You think
that you can follow me?
Sure thing, brother.
Let's go, then!
Woo-hooo!
We're really
sorry about the boat, sir!
Just send the
bill to the Company.
Can't you draw less
attention to yourself?
That's not an option.
My only concern is getting
you back onto dry land safely.
I'm gonna be in so much trouble.
Now I'll see what the
Silver Blade's capable of.
How do I get myself
into these situations?
Impressive. You managed
to dodge all our
bullets out on the water.
I'm sure that was tiring.
What's wrong? Was that too
much of a work out for you?
Oh, that little
bit of action was
a piece of cake
for the legendary hero.
No doubt about it.
But now I've got you in my
sights, so don't make a move.
Or there'll be a mountain of
bodies caught in the crosshairs.
Why are you doing this?
Shut up, you company woman.
If I wanted to, I could
shoot you down right now.
You can relax. We don't
on fighting anymore... today.
However, if you
decide to take up
residence here
in the Special Zone...
Well, you may be safe today,
but you never know
what might happen tomorrow.
Is that supposed to be a threat?
How about it, Silver
Blade? If you insist on
staying in the Special Zone,
why not join our proud Coven?
We'd certainly welcome you,
if you were one of us.
I've heard enough.
Kotaro.
What are you doing, Jiro?
You launched this
sneak attack on us.
And you've treated
us with such rudeness.
And now you ask, at gunpoint
no less, that I join you.
Your stupidity and ignorance
will lead you to your demise.
At my own hands.
I'll mete out your punishment.
After that, maybe
you'll finally wise up.
Die!
Did you say your name
was Kotaro? To be honest,
I've developed quite an interest
in you and your brother, Kotaro.
So how about it?
Why don't you stay here
and join forces with me?
Episode six: "The Coven"