It's incredible! Like
nothing humanity has ever seen!
Vampires are completely
destroying the city!
News crews have been barred
from entering the hot zone,
so we're limited
in what we can show you.
What is obvious is that
the city's functioning
capabilities are dead.
We have reports
that citizens left behind
are rioting in the streets!
This entire city
has become a battlefield.
We are witnessing with our
own eyes a sacred
war between humans and--
Here they come.
The rumor we heard that
Walkerman aided
them seems to be true...
Which is a little unsettling.
It is.
How many?
Too many.
You're not going anywhere...
Stay here and
guard the Lord Dragon.
Did you even hear
what I just said to you...?!
You're going nowhere!
My strengths are better
suited to this than yours are.
While you may possess
the power that rivals that of
a source blood... now is not the
time to deviate from our plan.
Lord Dragon...
open the barrier.
You insolent bastard!
Do you have any idea
who you're talking to?!
It's fine.
But Lord Dragon...
Jiro... If you kill them,
it will not save
you from your grief.
I'm begging you...
I need... I need to do this.
Very well then.
You have my thanks.
Lord Dragon...
Cain, please... I would
expect you to empathize with
the sorrow of losing,
what you strived to protect.
Silver Blade...
In this world, there's no
such thing as something useless.
It's good to see you, Jiro.
Stop it.
You always were troublesome...
Once you get worked up,
there's practically
no way to hold you back.
I said stop it!
Long time no see... I hope
you've been doing well...
But from the looks
of you, that's not the case.
You bitch... You bitch!
You bitch, you bitch...
you bitch!
Oh... Come on...
You can't say my name?
It's been a long time
since I've teased you.
You know... It's kinda funny.
When she first chose
you to be her guardian,
I thought it was foolish.
I guess I was right.
But you know
what's even funnier?
In the vast expanse of time
since we last saw each other...
I've learned that
I've never been happier than
in the days I spent
with the two of you.
Amazing isn't it? I cherish that
time in my life so very much...
Both then... and now.
Then why did
you betray us?! Why?!
Times change, Jiro... She said
it herself, remember...?
Just accept it.
Shut your mouth!
That was unreal, Jiro...!
You gave me the chills...!
But alas...
we'll have to stop here.
I would have enjoyed introducing
you to my new family, but
that will have to wait...
for another time.
Your family?!
That's right. Oh, I know you
hate the The Kowloon Children,
but I think
they're just so cute.
Stop talking!
That was careless.
So long, Jiro.
Cassa, wait!
No need to
bother missing me now...
Because today is only the
beginning of the whole thing.
Both ceaseless lamentation
and overflowing jubilation.
It's all laid out before us.
Cassa!
Tired yet?
No, but I'm getting there.
Well, we're almost there.
Yup... Looks like we'll
be in Yokohama by sunup...
I guess I'll
leave the bridge to you.
Sure. Get some rest.
Right.
Hey, brother?
Brother!
I think we're
still on the ocean...
I thought we'd be there by now?
Oh, great
Wake up, brother...
Wake up brother.
Wake up brother! Wake up, wake
up brother! Wake up brother!
Wake up brother! Wake up
brother! Wake up brother!
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up!
Wake up brother!
Wake-- Oh you're up.
That wasn't nice.
I forgot that you don't like
ships... Being on water and all.
Hey, brother... I think
I'm gonna wander around outside
and explore some.
Listen to me, Kotaro.
I need you to be
good and stay asleep
until we reach the harbor.
Remember, we're stowaways.
Not guests.
But... He's asleep...
How would he know anyway?
Sleep well!
Sorry, but... Who are you?
Chan.
Nice to meet you, Chan...
I'm Kotaro Mochizuki.
I forgot. It's supposed
to be a secret that
I'm traveling on this ship.
So... would you
mind not telling anyone?
Sure!
Thanks a lot, Chan...
And in return I'll...
I'll let you look
at the picture I drew.
What...? Uh, Chan...? Chan!
Chan!
Hey, Chan? Where'd you go?
That's awesome!
There they are!
They found me.
I can't believe
they actually shot at me.
What are they
gonna do now that
they know there're
stowaways on board?
Return fire!
Spread out men!
Don't give them a target!
Wait a sec...
They're not coming after me...
Damn it all! They brought
sunlamps with them!
If the sunlight is hurting
those people on the boat,
then that must
mean that they're like us.
Hey, kid--
What are you
doing out here alone?!
I apologize sir!
It can't be, Are you the...
Wait, um,... Have we
met somewhere before mister?
I guess that's silly,
huh? I'm sorry.
No, it's... it's fine I...
This is it.
That's my brother...
He's awake now.
Open fire, men!
A good morning
to you gentlemen.
I trust that, everyone
is doing splendidly today.
Hi, brother!
Oh... Kotaro...
Good morning to you...
Gorgeous night
don't you think?
Yeah!
Incidentally... I was curious as
to what you were doing up here.
Oh, yeah... That.
Your brother...
Ow, that hurt!
...was firm...
...when he told you...
To be good... and stay
asleep... until we arrived.
I only hope you didn't
wander around the ship...
And get into any more
trouble than you already are.
Like what, brother?
Like marking up any surface
you please with graffiti.
Whoa... How'd you know that?
I guess since
this is a Chinese ship,
I should've drawn
a panda bear instead.
That's hardly the point.
I'm really sorry.
Tell me... Why do
you always have to do
dumb things like this...?
You're such a pain.
That was mean tricking me into
thinking you weren't mad at me.
I don't want to hear it.
You're the one who couldn't
just do what he was told...
And now you turn around
and blame your brother...
It's disgraceful.
Fine.
Good grief brother.
Pardon me, gentlemen...
I'm sorry that you
had to witness that.
Please do you
best to not mind us.
And now...
since we've been able to
set aside
this private matter...
perhaps someone can tell
me what this fight is about...
See, while I don't
understand your reasons,
I take it that the ship itself
is not part of the conflict...
So all of the noise
wasn't appreciated.
Just who the hell
do you think you are?!
If you wish to ask my name,
I suggest that you start by
introducing yourself first.
Or have, such simple courtesies
been surrendered to the will of
disrespect during
my absence from Japan?
Alright then...
We're the suppression
team for the Company.
The company... Certainly
you must be referring to
the Order Coffin Company
from the Special Zone.
Yeah.
That's quite odd... I was
under the impression it's
an organization serving
as an intermediary between
the humans and us.
Ostensibly, yes.
Oh.
But this is how they
operate behind the scenes.
They seek out our brethren, only
to murder us indiscriminately...
They're nothing
but homicidal maniacs.
Homicidal...? I assure you we
don't go around killing humans.
You bastard!
Allow me to set you
straight on one more point.
Word is out there that the
Special Zone is considered as
some kind of haven
for you sick suckers,
which is a very
misguided perception.
The city that we guard is
not a lawless district that
we've let the monsters rule...
It's carefully maintained
location and strict order
is active twenty-four/seven.
Illegal immigrants from
some unknown bloodline
would never be allowed inside.
However, if you have a valid
referral from an affiliate house
then you don't
have any worries...
The Special Zone
will accept you...
But if you do not...
it doesn't matter if
you're an Old Blood with
hundreds of
years under your belt...
we'll show you no mercy.
That's the reality
for a Black Blood.
Reality for a
Black Blood... Ah...
I have been hearing that this
is what they've been calling
vampires these days...
And it's true...
My little brother and
I are, in fact, vampires.
This is quite a conundrum...
I have associates
in the Special Zone,
but I am afraid
I am unfamiliar to
this concept of
"affiliate houses".
Really?
That's too bad for you.
I don't think so.
Give him backup! All of you!
Are you serious??!
Do you even who that guy is?!
It doesn't matter
who he is, damn it...!
What matters is that
with him we can win...!
Or have you given
up on the Special Zone?!
No matter how
many times I explain...
you just don't understand.
What kind of power is that?!
This is bad...
Dammit!
Was he bitten?
Yes, sir. But
thankfully he wasn't
bitten by a Kowloon Child.
What'd headquarters say?
They said they'll handle it.
But you might wanna strap in
for a big slap on the wrists.
First you open fire,
big time, on a ship,
and the whole thing explodes.
Not something you can
just cover up that easily.
That's the Intelligence
Department's problem.
As soon as we're back
at base I want everyone
suited up with
anti-Old Blood equipment...
We've got a zero percent
chance of rain tomorrow...
and a full moon on the
docket for tomorrow night...
We've got to settle
this thing by sundown
no matter what the costs.
What's bothering you, Wong?
That guy... It's obvious, that
he was one of the Old Blood...
But there was something
unusual about him...
With the right motivation maybe
he could have been our ally.
Right.
Miss Wong!
I'm begging you!
Please give her your blood...!
She's dying...!
If she becomes a
vampire like you then
she can be free
of death, right?!
Thank you! Thank you,
you've saved my little girl!
I will never forget this!
I don't understand
why we got off the ship.
It's just a little change
of plans, that's all...
By tomorrow... well...
the day after tomorrow,
we'll be arriving
in the Special Zone.
We will?!
Yes... Of course we will.
Alright... I'm hungry again.
It's amazing... Chan,
You're such a little glutton.
Kotaro...
Hello...? This is Katsuragi.
Mimiko, it's Jinnai.
Hey Chief...
What's got you calling
me this early in the morning?
What?! Now? Wait, I can't
hear you, you're breaking up.
Chief, where are
you calling me from?
In order to be clear
when we talk of our two races
we call your kind Black Bloods
and we call our kind Red Bloods.
It shows equality between
two races of sentient beings,
that were equal
as living creatures.
Next time: "Compromiser"