Mochituki, Mochi--
Wait, I'll get it.
Ah! Mochi...
What's wrong with just calling
me Jiro, like you always have?
Well...
I think you're making things
too complicated, my lady.
Why can't you call me Alice?
Fine. Then why don't
you just call me Jiro.
No way!
I want to be able to
call you by your full name.
Jiro Motizuki? Jiro
Mochidizuki? Mochitu--
It's Jiro Mochizuki.
So, what exactly
does Motizuki mean anyway?
Mochizuki.
Don't be so mean.
Look.
The full moon?
The full moon!
So your name must
mean "full moon" am I right?
Jiro Motizuki! Jiro Motizuki!
Mochiduki! Mochiduki!
Mochituki! Mochituki!
What are you
doing here, Auguste?
He an acquaintance of yours?
No way. He's a known criminal.
He's a coven extremists and
one of Zelman Clock's cronies.
Did you say Zelman?
Wait, you mean
Crimson-Eyed Zelman?
What's he doing here?
Well... He's the ringleader
of our group, the Coven.
Interesting.
The Coven is a group that
completely defies the Company
and the Special
Zone's conventions.
And Zelman's at
the center of it all.
Have you have you
heard of him before?
Yes. And I'm
beginning to see...
the Special Zone is home to
the most unexpected people.
I'll have you know,
I've been appointed
Zelman's right hand man.
If anything were to happen to
me, he wouldn't take it lightly.
Is that right?
Yes. So think twice
before you kill me.
Believe me, I
have no desire to
pick a fight with
Crimson-Eyed Zelman.
I'm no fool.
But what about
a coward like you?
When you return will
you ask for an appeal?
Will you ask him to
avenge your honor because
Silver Blade mocked you?
You little bastard.
He's not strong at all,
but he's braggin' about
how powerful his friend is?
He's the bastard.
Language!
I think you're right.
And now I have just one
question I'd like you to answer.
What's that?
Was this attack
sanctioned by Zelman?
No.
Auguste has acted on his own.
Is that so?
And who might you be?
My name is Sayuka.
I'm the personal
assistant to Zelman Clock.
It's an honor to meet you.
My master wishes
to speak with you.
So please, come with me.
Come on, Hibari.
It may be a juicy rumor,
but don't you think
it sounds a little
too good to be true.
But it is true!
You see. The person acting as
the Silver Blade's guide is--
Ooooh it's Mimiko Katsuragi!
Mimiko Katsuragi. Sorry,
that doesn't ring a bell.
I promise I'm not lying
to you. She's the one.
Okay, sure thing, Hibari.
Thanks you for the heads up.
Stories are the lifeblood of an
information broker, after all.
I just thought that I should
return the favor
from the other day.
So I guess you
could say we're even now.
Well, I sympathize
with the girl.
This Mimiko Katsuragi. She's
gonna be in for a rough time.
I wouldn't want
to be her, right now.
Your guests have arrived.
You're here.
I know. Humans are
attracted to us vampires.
I feel it in the way you stare.
It's written all over your face.
Wow you're pretty.
Thanks.
How are you?
My name's Kotaro Mochizuki.
It seems that you're
the only one in this bunch
with any manners, little boy.
That's an odd little brother
you have there, Silver Blade.
He somehow seems different
than the reincarnations of Sei.
You speak as if
you knew The Sage.
No. Unfortunately
I've never met her.
But then...
If you live as long as I have,
you tend to hear
all sorts of stories.
Enjoy the cola.
Yes!
You shouldn't be so tense.
Staying on edge all the time
will only be to your detriment.
Go ahead.
Thanks for the cookies.
I didn't expect such
a low brow reception
from the Crimson-Eyed Zelman.
Oh please. Can we
stop with these games?
Didn't know I was playing.
You're so uptight compared
to your little brother.
Did you not learn anything
from the Sage's teachings?
That's a subject that
I'd rather not talk about.
Surely the matter is of
no concern to you, Zelman.
Well. That's true enough.
Let's say we...
start from beginning.
It's a pleasure to make your
acquaintance, Zelman Clock.
He with eyes the color of blood.
The last descendent of
the legendary Warrior
Asura's bloodline.
My name is Jiro Mochizuki.
And I am of the
Sage Eve's bloodline.
Ten years ago,
during Kowloon Shock,
I became known
as the Silver Blade.
Though I have lived a hundred
years, my pulse is yet shallow.
So may your
course be unhindered.
And may our hearts
both beat strongly.
That was quite
the formal introduction.
Auguste acted
without my permission
and for that I
apologize to you.
I thank you.
So, will you be joining
forces with the Company?
Have you not yet heard
of their plan, compromiser?
It seems that
your executives want
the Silver Blade
all to themselves.
They do? Oh.
Why would Jinnai assign
someone like her to
the task without even
explaining the situation?
If you have no intentions
of befriending anyone,
then I suppose that siding
with the Company is a good idea.
That way you'll retain a neutral
position when dealing with
the various houses in power.
Neutral. You must be joking.
I'm sure the Company
already has enough problems
keeping things
running smoothly.
Welcoming a nuisance
like myself would be
too much of a challenge.
What do you mean?
I don't think
that's true, brother.
I mean, Mimiko's really nice
and she works for the Company.
Maybe they'll be
as nice as she is.
I mean, you can't assume they'll
reject us without even asking.
The Company would only
welcome us for their own gain.
But you don't
know that, brother!
The Company people
need us, right?
What would be so
wrong about helping them
with their problems?
You may be right, Kotaro.
People's hearts often have
both a hidden and an open side.
And just because
there is a hidden agenda,
that doesn't mean that what's
out in the open is meaningless.
Right. Right!
Yes.
It seems your older brother
was being a little presumptuous.
I hope you'll forgive me.
Unbelievable. Did you
say your name was Kotaro?
Yeah.
To be honest, I've
developed quite an interest
in you and your brother, Kotaro.
So how about it?
Why don't you stay here
and join forces with me?
That's very nice,
but you're a bad person,
aren't you, Mr. Zelman?
Yes, but being one of the bad
guys can have its advantages.
I like to fight for justice.
I don't want to give that up.
Evil never wins,
but good always will!
Is that so?
Then that's too bad.
But if you ever tire
of the Company's justice,
don't hesitate to come back.
You'll always be welcome.
Thanks but I don't want you
to hold your breath waiting.
My brother and I
are vampires of justice
and I don't see us changing.
Silver Blade, Kotaro,
and the compromiser.
I'd like to thank
you for the visit.
This was truly a pleasant
way to stave off boredom.
When next we meet,
we may be enemies.
But yet I look forward
to seeing you again.
Farewell for now.
I can't believe it.
He's just letting
them walk out of here?
Auguste, you need
to just calm down.
It has yet to be determined if
the Silver Blade is our enemy.
It seems Zelman's fangs have
dulled with the passage of time.
Or perhaps he's
simply lost his nerve with
the return of this Kin-Killer.
You arrogant fool!
Damn it. I can deal with
this humiliation no longer.
The great Auguste Wyker will
not back down without a fight.
You'll pay for what you've
done to me, Silver Blade.
The master is busy right
now and can't be disturbed.
You'll have to try again later.
Hey.
Wait. What's going on?
Don't worry, Mimiko.
I'm sure they have reason for
not meeting with us.
Remember, not everything is
always as it appears to be.
But what are we gonna do?
That was unexpected.
I can't believe that the Sei
and Warlock Houses would
both refuse to
accept the Silver Blade.
I was sure they would
jump at the opportunity to
bring him into their fold.
If they did so they would
definitely strengthen
their influence.
They must have a reason for
rejecting him of
which we're unaware.
The affiliate houses have
continued to show honesty
and deference to us to
ensure that humans will remain
in the position of leadership.
Even if they don't
believe in what we do,
they've always made a
public show of supporting us.
But now it seems that
they're keeping secrets.
I will investigate
the matter immediately.
Please do.
Mimi, what're we
going to do now?
Let's just go
back to my place.
I'll cook you
something for dinner.
Yay!
Hey. Why'd we stop?
There's something I
haven't asked you yet.
And what's that?
Now, be honest with me.
Why did you come
here to the Special Zone?
The truth. Jiro, now.
And look me in the eye.
Um, well, it's just that I--
Ah! Look at me.
And if you use
the Eye Raid on me
I'll beat the crap out of you.
I have no intention
of doing that.
Then answer.
Well, I...
Hey, there!
We had just about
given up on you.
Where on earth
have you been hiding?
Jiro, darling.
Do you know how long
we've been waiting for you?!
What's the--?
Well, you know,
I just didn't feel right,
inviting ourselves
into this girl's apartment.
That's no excuse for forcing the
Lord Dragon to dine outdoors.
It's fine.
But...
I haven't had
a picnic in a while.
It's fun.
Oh, I see then. I'm so happy
to hear that. In that case,
I'll do my best to refrain from
complaining for
the rest of the evening.
It's quite insulting
to make promises to
the Lord Dragon that
you incapable of keeping.
What did you just say to me?
So what is the reason for
your visit to the Special Zone?
I'm not obligated to
answer any of your questions.
Then why don't you leave!
Nor am I obligated
to do as you say.
You're nothing but a nuisance.
And why is that my problem?
He's the general
manager of the Marine Bank!
I don't think talking to him
like that's such a good idea.
Don't worry.
Excuse me for
saying so, but you've
certainly reincarnated
into a rather cute new form.
It's good seeing you.
I never got a chance to
thank you for what you did.
It's in the past.
Forget about it.
So, you're a black
blood too, aren't you?
And you live at
that giant mansion
we went to earlier today?
Yes.
That's awesome.
And your name must
be Sei, am I right?
That's right.
Nice to meet you.
My name's Kotaro.
Kotaro?
Yup! You don't
talk much, do you, Sei?
I don't know why,
but for some reason
you remind me of the princess.
She's my older sister.
What?
The Dark Princess of
the North. That's my sister.
No way! Really?!
Really. We have
the same parents.
What a surprise!
But I haven't seen
her in a very long time.
I can't wait till
we see each other again.
Wow. That's amazing!
I never thought I'd meet
the princess' little brother.
We can be best friends.
I just came out of
the princess' sanctuary
and I really don't know much
about the outside world yet.
Your name's Cain, right mister?
And you're my
brother's friend, huh?
I-I wouldn't say that.
Cain and I are simply
old acquaintances, Kotaro.
He used to run out on errands
all the time to fetch bread
and milk for our
group back in the day.
The hell I did!
Oh yeah? But you
always took care of
an assortment of
chores for us, remember?
You're such a fool.
I did that for the
Lady Sage and Cassandra.
I was merely looking after the
best interests of the Lady Sage.
I never did anything for you.
Ummm. Excuse me.
May I say something?
Yes. What is it?
Earlier this afternoon, I took
these two by the Marine Bank
and to Sei's residence. They
wanted to gain acceptance to
one of the houses,
but in both cases...
Jiro, I--
Lord Dragon.
Allow me to explain it to them.
The real reason they refused
to grant you an interview today
is because I
ordered them not to.
At the moment, I'm
afraid we cannot welcome
the Silver Blade
into our house.
And, furthermore,
we can't allow him to
stay in the Special Zone.
What? Why can't he stay?
You two are old
friends, aren't you?
Jiro fought against
the Kowloon Children.
He protected the Special Zone.
I think he's earned this.
I'm afraid that's
neither here nor there.
Wherever the Silver Blade goes,
unnecessary commotions
arise and follow in his wake.
And there's no guarantee
that the next commotion that
arises around Jiro will be as
easily contained as
the float mart incident.
The presence of the
Silver Blade is nothing but
kindling for conflict
in the Special Zone.
That's terrible.
You can't blame him for that.
He shouldn't have to leave.
He's has nowhere else
to go! I can't believe this.
You're just going
to abandon your friend?
It's... it's so unfair.
He hasn't done anything wrong.
The Special Zone....
is not as peaceful
as it appears to be.
I know that you're not
happy with what I've said.
But you're a compromiser
so you must understand
and you must
respect our decision.
I know.
What are we gonna do?
We've been turned
down on all sides.
It's okay.
I'm sorry. There must
be a way for you to stay.
I hate to ask you
for another favor, but--
Would you mind putting
us up for another night?
You wanna go home?
Enough is enough.
Have you not
learned your lesson?!
I told you,
didn't I, Silver Blade?
That you wouldn't get
away with making a fool of me.
It's made of silver.
And all insolent newcomers...
get their heads lopped off.
And that's the Coven's code.
I heard nothing of
this code from Zelman.
That's because he doesn't
know anything about it.
That Zelman. He doesn't
care about our Coven.
Damn it all!
Are you intoxicated
or just insane?
If I were you I'd
stop taking this so lightly.
Damn it!
Don't worry
about them, just fight!
Could he be turning into--
No. If he were, the change
would be instantaneous.
That kind of
delay shouldn't occur.
You three, tell me
what you've done to him!
W-What are you're talking about?
Damn. That's it!
I'm getting out of here!
Hey!
Damn lowlifes.
Come on Silver Blade...
I don't know why
I ever gave a damn
what that fool
Zelman thought about me.
I haven't felt
this excited in ages.
You give me no choice.
No Jiro, don't do it!
If you stir up trouble now,
you'll give everyone the
excuse they've been looking for.
Pardon me. I guess I was
just being a little impatient.
I'm not playing
around, Silver Blade!
It's a matter of life or death!
Hate to disappoint you.
But we're done here.
I won't kill you now.
Even though I have no qualms
with cracking your head open.
So go home to Zelman.
And receive your punishment.
Bastard!
Have it your way.
But I'll make sure
you acknowledge me,
no matter what it takes.
I'll burn your ass for sure!
Brother, he didn't
hurt you, did he?
I'm fine.
Thank goodness.
But I have my suspicions.
Something was different.
Huh?
Auguste was like
another person from
when we say him
earlier at the market.
Yeah, I guess he was.
Well, Mimiko. What do you
say we go home for the night?
Sure thing.
No. That's my house.
I promise, Auguste Wyker,
I will carve the ways of the
Black Blood into your bones.
Episode Seven: "Silver Blade"