I am so sorry...
You've been very
kind to me, but...
You don't
have to say anything.
And you dont need
to be sorry, Alice.
What's done is done.
I'm happy being with you.
Jiro!
I can see the moon...
But my moon is here...
My full moon...
Stop on by for
a delicious pork bun!
Wow, those look yummy... No!
If I get sidetracked
brother will get mad
and punish me again.
Hey...
I'm glad to see you managed
to make it out alive.
Whoa...
Hey...! Is she
gonna be all right?
She'll be fine. More
importantly, what happened to
your brother
and that company woman?
We split up so
we wouldn't get caught
and now I have no idea
where my brother and Mimi are.
So, you're alone?
It'd be best if
you came with us.
We're about to
head to our hideout to
meet up with our group.
Really... Oh, but I have
to keep looking for my brother.
Come with us
and we'll help you.
You shouldn't be
wandering around alone.
You'll help?
It appears that Wong
here has grown awfully fond of
your brother, little man.
I must say my interest
has been piqued, too...
In your brother...
as well as you.
In me?
Kotaro!
Mimiko!
Would it be at all possible
for me to come along?
Sure, but you'll be
treated as a prisoner,
I understand... I promise I
won't cause you any problems.
I guess it's settled then...
I'll lead the way
back to our hideout.
Follow me. It won't take long.
Were together again.
Wake up!
What the hell's
the matter with you?!
You know, your treatment of
prisoners leaves
much to be desired?
How dare you disrupt my sleep,
and for the
second day in a row?
Shut up! You're lucky
I'm letting you sleep at all.
The sun hasn't even set.
It's only natural for a vampire
to sleep during daylight hours.
You don't understand the
weight of your situation...
And I'm getting
tired of your attitude.
Sorry my confidence
threatens you,
But I can't help but be myself.
And I don't intend
to change just for you.
So do what you must,
but do it quickly.
Let me get this straight.
You honestly expect me to
believe you know nothing about
those refugees we
encountered on the ship?
I didn't know them.
I have no reason to lie to you.
Yeah?
Then why won't you tell me the
truth about who you really are?
Enough with that already.
I told you,
I'm one of the last survivors
of a severed bloodline.
My only blood
relation is my brother.
And I bet you'd like to know...
where your brother is...
I'm warning you...
If my brother is
harmed in any way...
I will be able to detect it,
even if we are separated
by a great distance.
So don't you dare
lay a hand on him.
Yeah? That a threat?
Not a threat... A promise.
I think you should be
more worried about what those
refugees will do
to your little brother.
Our intelligence says he met up
with them in the city earlier.
And that the Compromiser's
with them as well.
Mimiko's with him.
Why's she there?
I don't know... Mediation
Department's always interfering.
Bastards...
And I assume you
know where they are now.
They're in Chinatown.
We're about to move in.
You idiot!
Escalating this conflict will
only serve to make things worse.
We have reason to believe
that there's a Kowloon
Child among the refugees.
That can't be...
We haven't been able
to determine which of them
are Kowloon Children yet...
And because of
this we have no choice
but to wipe
them out completely.
We can't leave
any of them alive.
It's time. Move out.
Yes, Sir!
Wait! Let me come with you.
I assure you, we can solve
this problem without your help.
But if you miss even one of them
they'll continue to multiply.
The battle could
very quickly grow
beyond your capabilities.
We'll handle it.
That was quite
a stunt you pulled.
What are you talking about?
This afternoon in the park...
I bet keeping a lid on that
commotion cost the
company a ton of money.
With nothing to show for it.
How do you plan on explaining--
Shut up!
It's not my problem if the
public becomes aware there are
still vampires on the loose.
It's my job to rid the earth of
the plague of Kowloon Children
and I'll do everything
in my power to do so,
no matter what the cost.
The board of directors can
all go eat shit for all I care.
Oh, Badrick, you're so rough!
But what's the hurry?
Shouldn't you wait for backup
before you go after the Kowloon?
I don't have time.
They've almost made
it to the Special Zone.
Remember ten years ago,
when vampires fought
alongside humans
in their effort to
destroy the Kowloon Bloodline?
Such blind heroism.
You fold this
corner here and then...
See...? A crane!
Wow! That's so cool!
Now it's my turn.
Well...? What's that Kotaro...?
Do you know origami too?
My brother taught
me how to make this.
Really?
Ta-da!
Oh wow!
What's that?
Watch!
Hello, Miss Wong.
It flew.
Here's another one.
That flew far.
Why don't you go play with Chan
and keep an eye on her, 'kay?
Roger!
Hey, Chan. Wait for me!
Chan has a new friend.
They seem happy.
You look better.
Has your injury healed?
Yeah... I had a fresh meal and
now everything's back to normal.
So... Our friend Jiro
must have been really worn out
from the fight
the other night.
Why didn't you let
him drink your blood?
Well... it's just...
I'm sorry.
Did I embarrass you?
It's just...
He'd use his mouth to...
What's wrong with that?
In return you'd be rewarded
with an exquisite pleasure.
And in all honesty,
sex pales in comparison.
Well... be that as it may...
It... It carries, you know,
a psychologically
addictive quality...
And under Company policy
it is strictly forbidden
for us to allow ourselves to--
It's against the rules.
Besides... I don't
know if he's...
Don't worry. He's not.
He's not a Kowloon child.
Do you know something
you're not telling me?
About Jiro?
If he's who I think he is...
He can't be a Kowloon.
He is an Old Blood.
If you would have let
him drink your blood,
he could have easily escaped
from that ambush earlier.
Are you sure?
Last night he
completely overwhelmed
the suppression team.
No way... The Company's
suppression team is known as
one of the most effective
vampire assault units
in the whole world.
You'll see soon enough.
Chan! Where'd you go?
When you said earlier
that you would accept Jiro,
even if he were a Kowloon
Child... Did you mean it?
'Course I did.
How could you?
You're aware of how infectious
the Kowloon are, aren't you?
Under normal circumstances,
humans will not turn
unless we drink the
blood of a vampire.
But the Kowloon can turn humans
just by sucking their blood.
They can even convert other
vampires to their bloodline.
If we allow them
to exist unchecked...
it could spell disaster.
Back in my country,
there's no place left
for broken bloodlines.
It's a wretched existence.
This hasn't
been an easy journey.
We've already lost
two from our group with
no explanation as to
where they went or why.
As if they had
anywhere to go, anyway.
Just as humans fear
and persecute vampires,
vampires also fear and
persecute the Kowloon Children.
We're all forsaken.
The differences between
our races are inconsequential.
No, you're wrong!
Excuse me?
It's been ten years
since the Kowloon Shock.
If even one of them
had survived the purge,
then at least half the
world's population should be of
their bloodline by now.
But that's not the case.
And why do you suppose that is?
I don't know...
It's because the Kowloon kill
the people that they feed on.
They callously take
the lives of those who
they have converted
over to their bloodline.
So no, Wong,
you are nothing like them.
Chan!
Hey, Chan... Where are you?
Chan... What's that?
My airplane.
Kotaro...
Is that you?
There you are! Finally! I've
been looking all over for you.
Chan?
Kotaro... Want to play?
I'm sorry... My darling, Jiro!
I'm super repentant! A bunch of
unforeseen circumstances arose
one after the other and since
you don't even have a cell phone
I had no way of
getting in contact with you.
I promise it'll
never happen again.
You're dead!
Oh my... Are you mad at me?
I should have known
it was a horrible idea to
leave all my travel
arrangements up to you.
It was an unfortunate
series of mishaps.
I couldn't have
known there would be
other stowaways onboard.
Enough of this.
Did you bring it?
Oh, but of course I did.
I must say that I'm a little
concerned about Kotaro...
Please take care of him.
Oh. Now it looks like you
mean business. Go get 'em.
I'll deal with you later.
But first I'll settle things
with the ghosts of the past.
Right. Let me
show you the way.
Welcome back, Silver Blade.
Could I ask you something?
Sure.
I want to know why
you decided to come with us.
Well... I guess...
I'm still new at this
to tell you the truth.
But I wanted to see this thing
through to its completion.
I am a Compromiser after all.
Even if you may be
dealing with Kowloon Children?
If I wasn't
working for the Company,
then I wouldn't have
anywhere else to go...
'Cause I'm an orphan.
The company gave me a home.
They took care of
me when nobody else would
and they became my family.
That's why now I want
to be the one who gets to
tell everyone that
they'll never be alone.
'Cause I understand.
I've been there, too.
Oh. You don't
have to cry for me.
There are a lot of
kids in the Special Zone
who've lost their parents.
And are all these other orphans
compromisers just like you?
Like me? Just what
is that supposed to mean?
It's settled.
I'd like for you to talk
to the Company on our behalf.
But... What would I say?
Ask permission for us
to enter the Special Zone.
If they'll give us a
place to live I promise that
we'll accept any
conditions they deem necessary.
We just want a place
where we can live in peace.
I beg you...
Please don't forsake us.
You're the
only chance we have.
What's that?
Miss Wong!
Damn it!
The suppression team...
Garlic gas!
You have to stop,
you can't...
Wait... it's the compromiser.
We need to get you out of here.
Hey, stop!
Stop it!
These people are under the
care of the
Department of Mediation.
Cease your assault immediately.
Don't listen to her.
Keep firing.
I swear! I won't let
you get away with this.
This raid is
nothing but a massacre.
This is none of
your business, Compromiser.
Now get the hell out of
the way before you get hurt.
Your actions here today clearly
break Company regulations.
You can't justify slaughter.
I'll explain
the circumstance later.
Let go of me!
Damn it! Let go!
That's enough, Mimiko.
You've done plenty.
Miss Wong...
We surrender...
We have no intention of
resisting you any further...
So...
I ask that you please
spare the lives of my friends.
Shoot them!
What are you doing...?
Shoot them! Shoot them all!
No!
It's the Hide Hand!
It's just as we had suspected.
You're harboring a
Kowloon Child, aren't you?
That's ridiculous! We're
all from broken bloodlines.
That's all the more
reason why you wouldn't
be able to distinguish
one in your group.
And no vampire from
a broken bloodline would
be able to master
the Hide Hand technique.
Am I wrong?
I-I don't know...
But we've been together
since we left our homeland.
We would've found
out about it by now.
We've lost two from our group.
It's because the Kowloon kill
the people that they feed on.
Then it's true...
But who...? Who is it?!
Get a hold of yourself!
Don't lose it now.
We're so close.
What happened to the bravery you
showed when we left our country?
Come on, Wong. Let's
destroy these Company scum.
Tsang...
I just want you to know... It
did make me happy earlier today
when you said you'd even welcome
someone of my dubious bloodline.
We Kowloon Children
are used to being hated.
I guess you could say
we're starved for kindness.
Open fire!
You fools!
Now... Let's get started.
Where's Kotaro?
I have to find him!
We can't afford to
let them overtake us.
We have to put them down!
These guys are fighting under
the control of their master.
Call it liberation.
Now then...
I owe you my
thanks, Compromiser.
After all, if it
wasn't for you...
Attack! Get him!
Quite an entrance...
You escaped!
I don't know where
Kotaro is. I'm so sorry...
Don't worry about it.
He hasn't been harmed.
Now hand over my brother.
You'll have to
ask nicer than that.
You've succumbed to
my eye raid so easily.
You were already half-dead
before you
even joined the fight.
It's such an
unfortunate mistake.
I've heard a lot about you.
But how pathetic. So much
for the great kin-killer.
Did you call him the
kin-killer? That means he's...
the silver blade.
Wait... The silver blade?
I will not ask you again...
Give me my brother!
Look, it's Kotaro!
And Chan!
Oh, look...
What an emotional reunion.
Chan, now!
No don't!
You bastard!
Jiro!
Help! Get me outta here!
Brother, you have to help me!
Ah! This hurts like hell!
I guess that I underestimated
our little friend here.
Makes no difference...
I think it's time to
get this thing started.
So you're running away.
It's no fun here.
Let's go elsewhere.
You fool... Don't you know...?
That entire island
is surrounded by a barrier...
Kowloon children aren't allowed
to enter the Special Zone
without an invitation
from the Company.
I'm not worried.
You see... I've been invited.
You won't forsake
us now, right, Compromiser?
You won't get away!
See you guys later.
I'm bored with this.
Kotaro!
You'll never understand us.
You, whose bloodline
has transcends death
will never know
what we go through.
True. I don't
understand your hardships.
But neither can you
understand the destiny
and curse of my bloodline.
So don't assume that you do.
Episode four: "Old Blood"