Lady Cassa, please wait!
It'll be dawn in under an hour.
I don't care. I need
to take care of this.
I'm surrounded by incompetence.
If only someone had saw fit to
contact me earlier, then I
wouldn't be in this predicament.
Surely you understand.
The mistress wishes to keep
you separate from this matter.
If you continue to act
with such wreckless abandon,
the mistress will take
action against you herself.
Why that would be splendid.
I'd love to settle things with
that old hag once and for all.
Cassa, no.
And when the time comes...
I expect you to be
standing there by my side.
Though I won't force you
if you really are opposed to it.
"I can't wait to
see Jiro again."
For ten years, that's
what she's been saying.
My sister Cassa.
What's the meaning of this?
Why did you stop him
from attacking Mimiko?
He was your kin, and yet you
cut him down dead in his tracks.
It was nothing special.
As you well know,
it is our misfortune that
everyone we bite is
turned into one of us.
Leaving him alive would
have only caused more problems.
Jiro. Hey...
I only did what was
in my best interest.
I will not fault you for it.
I am a being that
feeds on human blood.
So I have no
problem engaging in
horrendous acts
to ensure my survival.
Well that's a surprise,
coming from you.
There are few among us who are
kind enough to see it that way.
It's for the same reason that I
cut down those of your own kind.
The Kowloon Children are a
menace that I cannot ignore.
For their existence
threatens my survival.
That is why I
eliminate your kind.
Whether you have
done wrong or not,
I assure you that
I will finish you.
I understand.
I guess I should have expected
as much from the Kin-Killer.
But I'm glad you
left the sanctuary.
My siblings and I warmly welcome
your return, Lord Silver Blade.
You welcome the one
who hunts your kind?
The Kowloon Children
have always craved chaos.
And it's been boring not
having a worthy opponent.
You okay, Mimi?
And where is your
sister, Cassa, now?
She's on her way here.
Damn you!
Worthy opponent, my ass!
I will not play games with you!
It's no game, Silver Blade.
I've heard stories
about you my entire life.
I know how you fight.
I know everything about you!
Y'know, I didn't come here just
to track you down for my sister.
What?
I've come to test my skills.
Be careful.
You're not taking me seriously!
What's the matter, you can't
even hold your own against
someone as young as me?
It's the suppression team!
You disappoint me.
Brother!
Jiro, are you alright?
Sorry, Mimiko,
but this is goodbye.
It's not safe for
you to be with me.
I don't want you to get hurt.
Wait!
I think we should
get going, Kotaro.
What? But I
don't want to leave.
You have to at least tell
the Company about that guy.
Sorry, but after what's
happened, I have no intention
on involving myself
with the Company.
Brother, we can't go.
We have to stay here
at least a little longer.
I really don't want to argue
with you right now, Kotaro.
Now do as I say and come along.
Brother, please.
I won't discuss it any
further. We need to go now.
Okay, Okay.
I understand, that's fine.
But before we go, we should
have a talk with Sei and Cain.
I don't know how
to say this exactly...
But I don't think you can
protect us on your own anymore!
I agree with him.
Jiro, please
stay a little longer.
I'm so sorry, Mimiko.
No, don't apologize to me.
Just say you won't leave.
Brother.
Why would you do
something like that?
Jiro.
There's a case of
contagion in the Special Zone.
Not only that, but the
source of the contagion is
a second generation Kowloon
Child who is still at large.
This is the worst
possible situation.
The company must put
all of its resources towards
capturing the source
and eliminating
any further outbreak.
You will have
our full cooperation.
The fugitive vampire's
name is Yafuri Chao.
It has only been ten
years since he was turned.
As long as the
conditions are right,
I believe the suppression team
can deal with him themselves.
Then why did the Silver
Blade fail to finish him?
I do not know. But more
importantly, the fact that
he managed to make it
into the Special Zone
suggests that he is working
with someone on the inside.
Excuse me, Sei. What are
the conditions necessary to
cross the barrier
into the Special Zone?
It's quite simple.
In order to cross the barrier
one must merely be invited.
And the one inviting them
must know they're a vampire.
Also, there's one more
requirement for entrance.
And that is?
The person who invites
them must be a resident,
and they must be human.
And exactly how is
residence determined?
There is no formal rule.
He must simply live upon
this land and
consider the Special Zone
to be the place
where he belongs.
Then if that's the case.
We have a pressing
need to find this insider.
It was never my intention
to keep this from you, but...
Yafuri mentioned
an old acquaintance of
mine to the Silver Blade,
and claimed he was her brother.
Cassandra Jill
Warlock is her name.
She was formerly a prominent
figure in the Warlock house,
and I was once her servant.
Ten years ago,
when the source of
the Kowloon bloodline was born,
she was one of the first to
become tainted by their blood.
She is a traitor.
Impossible. You mean
she's still alive.
If she is involved
at all in this incident,
then I'm afraid that
the situation is
truly turning grave.
She has even been called the
second coming of
Morgan the Witch,
who is the Source Blood and
originator of our bloodline.
She is incredibly skilled
in the art of magic.
I must confess that I have a
history with this woman as well.
And, anyone else involved in
the Crusade will definitely have
some strong feelings regarding
Cassandra Jill Warlock.
Including Jiro.
The Silver Blade?
Yes.
And this boy Yafuri, even
though he is a Kowloon Child,
I don't think he will be
too much for Jiro to handle.
He must have been
quite unsettled at
the mention of Cassa's name.
That inexperienced idiot!
Answer me honestly, Sei.
Do you think you would
stand a chance against Cassa?
I do.
I'm relieved to
hear that, Lord Dragon.
The Special Zone was developed
as the successor of Hong Kong.
And we must now prevent it from
sharing the same fate as that
destroyed city no
matter what it takes.
Gentlemen!
We must sever the
Kowloon bloodline
as quickly as possible!
Yo.
Oh, it's you Yafuri. It's
good to see you. Welcome back.
You seem surprised I'm alive.
Want something to eat?
Have there been
any new developments?
Why, yes. Our sis has arrived.
For real?
Yep, she was here. And she
seems really enthusiastic.
She couldn't wait
to get things started.
She had an odd look in her eyes,
though. It could mean trouble.
Where is she?
She's already out
for a night on the town.
What do you think, Yafuri?
Here we are, working hard, and
she hasn't even lent us a hand.
Talk about self-centered, huh?
Did she say anything
when she was here?
Nuh-uh. Not really.
Oh, I see.
Well, she didn't seem that
mad at you for running off.
So go ahead and relax.
Do you not care where I was?
Huh?
I came across the
Silver Blade while I was
searching the Special Zone.
I know you did.
But how? We were
the only ones there.
There was a half-dead
member of the Coven
lying on the
ground. That's how.
I was watching
through his eyes.
Oh. Right.
You shouldn't have
approached him alone.
Don't ever do that again.
If you were watching
me then you know!
I had the upper hand
against the Silver Blade.
If we hadn't been interrupted,
I would have beaten him!
Why are you and sis
so hung up on that guy?
He didn't look
like anything special.
Is that jealousy in your voice?
What? You wanna
take this outside?
Bring it on!
Yafuri, if you had
continued your fight,
you wouldn't have been able to
stand against the
Silver Blade for long.
Just trust me on this one.
You don't know what
you're dealing with.
What do you know?
More than you think.
So try to get some rest
until the sun comes up. Okay?
Then you can start your
day by cleaning up this mess.
Whatever.
We can't do it.
We cannot stay here.
Kotaro. We're leaving.
I'm gonna go
say goodbye to Mimi.
I'll be right back,
so don't worry about me.
No!
I'm late again.
Jiro.
It's not safe for
you to be with me.
I don't want you to get hurt.
Jiro!
Oh, Miss Mimiko. Did I
wake you up? I'm so sorry.
No, it's okay.
The Chief gave me
a message for you.
He said you could
take the day off.
I guess you've been
serving in a critical capacity.
He said your hard
work is much appreciated.
I don't know what the
Chief is talking about.
Doesn't he know that I failed
to accomplish my mission?
He didn't mention it.
So you shouldn't be upset
with yourself about it.
Besides, that's just
par for the course for you.
How dare you!
Whoops. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean it.
Miss Mimiko...
Cheer up. There's no reason
for you to be sad. Not really.
It's all the Silver
Blade's fault anyway!
That darn Silver Blade. How
could he just dump you like that
after you
helped him out so much
and got him into
the Special Zone.
And on top of that.
He brings you to
a hotel like
you're some floozy!
You so deserve better!
Huh?
Oh, but hey it's okay. You don't
have anything to worry about
because yesterday I checked
the regulations for you.
If a compromiser allows a
Black Blood to drink her blood,
she will be
severely punished.
But it's okay if she's
assaulted against her will!
Wait. Hibari, what
are you talking about?
What exactly did the
Chief tell you anyway?
He didn't tell me
anything. But I can sense it!
So today to help you relax
I'm going to take you to
the Seventh Yard
and we're gonna party!
Oh, but before we take off,
I think that you should
maybe go to the hospital.
You little freak!
Huh?
Nothing like that happened! If
I ever hear you say it did,
you will regret it.
You understand me?!
No way. Seriously? Nothing?
You seem so disappointed.
Well, when the Chief
talked to me earlier he seemed
really concerned about you.
He wanted me to come and
make sure you were okay.
He said, "Mimiko's at
the hotel and she's really
depressed, so go
cheer her up."
And when I heard that
I just assumed--
Assumed what?
Oh. Uh, it's nothing.
Then I guess I had it all
wrong about the Silver Blade.
Maybe he's not
so bad after all.
That woman must have
been telling me the truth.
I guess I should have listened.
And who was that?
Oooh some lady.
She's downstairs waiting.
Who's there?
Oh, you should have
waited in the lobby for us.
We were about to leave.
I'm sorry. I just got worried
when you hadn't come down yet.
Hey, Mimiko.
Wong, it's you!
Where are you, Kotaro?
And you're just
gonna let him go?
From what you've
told me, it seems like
the Special Zone
really needs him.
And isn't it your
job to try and find him?
But, I--
She can't.
It's too dangerous.
I wasn't asking you,
I was asking Mimiko!
I wanna know how you
honestly feel about this.
Tell me, are you
really okay with
the Silver Blade
just leaving you?
Miss Mimiko?
I'll do it.
I'll try to find Jiro
and see if I can
talk him out of leaving.
But how? How are
you going to find him?
He could be anywhere,
and there's no way you can
search the Special
Zone by yourself.
If the Silver Blade
is going after Yafuri,
I have an idea of
where he might be.
Tsang told me about him.
Evidently he has friends
in the Eleventh Yard.
What's the matter?
It's just that...
Did Tsang not tell you?
The Eleventh Yard is an urban
legend here in the Special Zone.
It's what?
There are only ten official
districts on record in the city.
So, the Eleventh Yard doesn't
really exist as far as I know.
It doesn't exist?
No.
After the Hong Kong crusade
there were stories that
some kind of legacy was
brought in to the Special Zone,
which was still under
development at the time.
And this legacy is said to be
hidden in the Eleventh Yard.
A district that
no one was ever seen.
I never heard that story.
Anyway even without any clues,
I'm sure I'll be
able to find Jiro.
Um, I know someone who's
researching the Eleventh Yard.
What?
Who's that?
An information broker's
been coming to see me.
And he's been asking a
lot of questions about it.
He comes by every so often
and we exchange information.
Now then, what should I eat?
Call the affiliate houses and
gather information from them.
We need clues to whereabouts of
the Kowloon Child
before it's too late.
Damn it! Things
are moving too slow!
And Cassandra is
always, always so...
I'm looking for my brother.
And why have you come here?
I don't know where he is.
I can't sense his aura
and I'm afraid something
may have happened to him.
You idiot! Why didn't you
finish those Kowloon off?
Because of you they might
spread throughout the city.
Please help me. Even the
smallest bit of information.
I'm begging you. Please
help me find my brother.
Do you realize how dire the
situation is at the moment?!
You really
think we have time to
concern ourselves
with one child?!
Where are you going?
To look for Kotaro.
How? He's severed your
empathetic link, hasn't he?
I don't know how,
but I will find him.
So you can either help
me out or just shut up
and keep your
people out of my way.
You're behaving rashly.
Just calm down.
Calm down?!
I can't. Cassa could find my
little brother at any moment!
Damn it. If you're
not gonna help me,
then stop meddling in
the affairs of my bloodline.
Jiro!
Get up.
And you call yourself the chosen
protector of the Lady Sage?
Listen. The Special Zone has
been in grave danger as of late.
And I assure you that the enemy
is not after you or your kin.
You arrived in the Special
Zone only two days ago,
but this plan of theirs has
been meticulously devised
over a long period of time.
Then why? Why has Cassa
come to the Special Zone?
I'm afraid I
can't tell you that.
At any rate, now that the enemy
is aware of your presence here,
there is no guarantee
that they won't start to
cause problems for
you and your brother.
Go to the park
we were at yesterday.
I'll send Rinsuke to meet you.
He may not be of much help,
but he's the only person
I can afford to send.
At the very least, he knows the
Special Zone better than you do.
Thank you.
Save it. We really don't
have time for that now,
so just get out of here.
That boy will never grow up.
What have you found?
We've discovered their hideout.
I'll be right there.
Everything is falling apart.
But in a way
it's coming together.
Then what are they after?
Cain said the same thing.
He said Cassa wasn't after us.
Then what is their objective?
Why would they risk so much
entering the Special Zone?
Episode Nine:
"The Eleventh Yard"