Jiro, you need to learn to be
more mindful of
your surroundings.
But I'm always aware
of what's around me.
If I wasn't, then I wouldn't
be very good at protecting you.
That wasn't really
what I was talking about.
I don't know how
to say this exactly.
Do you think that
water is strong?
Water? Is it strong?
I don't know.
And the river?
I'm not exactly sure
what you're getting at.
And then what about
the ocean? Is it strong too?
I guess you could say it
possesses a certain
kind of strength.
But when I think of the ocean,
I don't really think of it
in terms of
strength or weakness.
When you find yourself
facing the ocean,
the question of
whether or not it's strong
doesn't really matter anymore.
Water is water,
no matter where it is.
And it's the same
with blood, Jiro.
That's the nature of who we are.
Our true value is
not in being the water,
but in that we
could be the ocean.
I think I get it.
Good. Can you
be the ocean, Jiro?
I promise I'll try.
Mimi...
I'm so glad.
What in the world do
you have to be glad about?
Your apartment just exploded.
I'm glad because my
apartment was the only one that
got damaged in the blast.
I've always complained
this building was too old
and run down, but I guess the
foundation's in
pretty good shape.
I'm really impressed
it's still standing.
What? Have you gone crazy?
Don't cry, Kotaro.
But I-I can't help it,
brother. I feel bad for Mimi.
You don't see
Mimiko crying do you?
So there's no reason
for you to cry either.
We better go.
We can't leave.
If we stay we'll be
interviewed by the police which
is more trouble than it's worth.
Listen to me, Jiro. We have
to go to the Company now.
I'll report to my superiors and
have them deal
with this appropriately.
And don't worry. Even if my
boss says no, I'll find a way.
You and Kotaro will stay here
and live in the Special Zone.
I promise, Auguste Wyker,
I will carve the ways of the
Black Blood into your bones.
I never expected Auguste
to engage the Silver Blade
in battle so quickly. Man,
that was a pretty close call.
If our cover's
blown, we're screwed.
It's a good thing that
I always make a point to
prepare for the worst. But...
with the mess he's gotten into
with the Silver
Blade I don't think
we can leave Auguste
to his own devices.
I guess I'll have to
ask you to take care of this.
I hope you don't mind.
Hey, Yafuri?
Oh no! This is not good!
If sis finds out I--
Oh man!
Hi.
Hey, sis. How are ya? Haven't
heard from you in a while.
Thank you for coming.
I appreciate your presense
here, Miss Katsuragi.
I heard about what
happened to your apartment.
I'm sorry for your loss,
but I'm glad to see
that you were not harmed.
Thank you for your
kind words, Chairman.
Zhang, how have we
been handling the media?
We told them the explosion
was caused by a gas leak.
And said that the
resident is currently on
a month long vacation
in mainland Japan.
Mimiko. I'm very sorry.
It all comes with the territory
when you're a compromiser.
Do you have
anything you'd like to
report to us
about the incident?
I heard the Silver Blade let
that idiot Auguste get away.
Yes. He escaped by
jumping into the canal.
He should have cut that rebel
fool in half. Talk about sloppy.
What kind of attitude is that?
What do you mean?
He's not my subordinate,
so what do I care?
For this outburst, we must
ensure that Auguste Wyker
and the rest of
his Coven pay dearly.
But, we must also
take into consideration,
how we might prevent
another from taking
Auguste's place
when he's disposed of.
Thanks for taking care of it.
No problem.
Son of a bitch!
What's going on? Janaway!
Oh no.
I told you we
have no intention of
accepting the Silver Blade as
a resident of the Special Zone.
We cannot allow
anyone to live here
who is constantly surrounded
by disorder and chaos.
Well then, if that's the case.
I'd be more than happy
to welcome him into my House.
Do you have any idea
of the consequences
that action would
bring upon you?
Of course not. I may be
older than most everyone here,
but that doesn't mean I can
accurately predict the future.
What an interesting development.
You would actually
have him join you?
Please, enlighten us
with your reasoning.
What can I say?
When I met him earlier
today he piqued my interest.
And I must say
his little brother is
quite a piece of work.
I hope you get
the chance to meet them.
You'll be pleasantly surprised.
As a former vampire hunter
I'm sure you've
heard the stories of
the legendary Silver Blade.
Hunter?
Do not lay a hand
on the Sage's blood.
Or have you forgotten
the unwritten law of this land?
What a scandalous accusation.
I assure you, Zhang,
that I have no intention of
harming the Sage.
Oh. Then please tell me why
the great Crimson-Eyed Zelman
would be so interested
in a stripling such as Jiro.
What does it matter to you,
Cain. Why do you even care?
Just answer my question.
Don't play dumb with me.
You know the reason.
Sure, he's the
Hero of Hong Kong,
and he's of the
Sage's bloodline.
But I'm not interested
in any of that.
What impresses me is the fact
that he killed the Kowloon King.
Zelman, enough.
Stop it. Control your tongue.
Lord Dragon, stop. Look
at what you're doing to her.
Oh I-I'm sorry.
Are you all right, Mimiko?
Oh, yes.
Hey! You can't go in there!
But Mimi's in there, right?
What's this kid doing here?
Is that Kotaro?
It's fine. Let him in.
Hey Mimiko.
I have terrible news.
What happened?
Brother went out
and left me alone.
He went out? Where did he go?
He said he was going
to mount an assault.
He was smiling,
but his eyes were scary.
Oh no...
That's what I'm talking about.
He really is quite interesting.
Damn that idiot!
What's he doing?
Zhang. Give the orders
to the suppression team.
Have them take care of this.
I want them mobilized
in under ten minutes.
Yes, Chairman.
Wait a minute.
You're not really planning
on attacking Jiro, are you?
Hopefully it
won't come to that,
but we can't take any chances.
There has to be some other way.
We can't afford for
this thing to get out of hand
and for the public
to find out about
the battles between
the Black Bloods.
And to put it bluntly, as long
as it stays under the radar,
we won't have to get involved.
Miss Katsuragi.
There's a vampire out there
trying to stir up trouble.
You're a compromiser, aren't
you? So mediate the situation.
Jiro Mochizuki is
your responsibility.
So go find him and try to
talk him out of this fight.
That's an order, Mimiko.
Come on, Kotaro!
We have to go stop Jiro.
She's a sassy one.
Tell me, Jinnai.
What is it?
I hear that you're
the one who decided to
send that girl
after the Silver Blade.
Did you pick her
just because she was
the only one
available at the time?
I don't remember
why I chose her.
It was before the crack of
dawn when I made that decision.
I think I was half asleep.
You sly fox.
We're not done here yet.
What's that?
If there are no objections,
I'd like to move
on to the main agenda.
I thought we were
only going to discuss
how to deal with
the Silver Blade today.
Of course, handling
him is a delicate issue,
but there is a more
immediate problem at hand.
And that problem is this...
Who's that?
Johan Tsang, he tried
to enter the Special Zone
late last night.
And he's a Kowloon Child.
Move aside!
I see. That's unfortunate.
But it's too late to do anything
about Yafuri's overzealousness.
Thought so.
Then I guess we better figure
out a way to rescue him somehow.
Forget about him.
You can't mean that!
He's sure to get himself
killed by Silver Blade.
He brought it on himself.
Cold bitch.
Did you say something?
Nope!
He may not be able to win.
But he'll at least escape
by the skin of his teeth.
He is my little
brother, after all.
I wish I could see
the panic on Jiro's face.
Is that all you care about?
Alright. I think
I'm ready to go in.
Please tell me
you're just joking.
Once you go in, it won't
be easy for you to get back out.
Cain and Sei have
grown complacent
during this time of peace.
Just you wait,
I'll give them the
wake-up call
they've been needing.
Pig-headed.
What did you say to me?
Nothing.
Okay. Do it.
I welcome you
to the Special Zone.
Miss Cassandra Jill Warlock.
Hello.
Jiro.
This is how it works, huh?
Kill anyone who crosses you?
You don't have
to thank me, Mimiko.
You idiot! It was
just a stupid apartment!
This will only make your
situation here even worse.
So why? Why did you do it?
I taught them a lesson.
What? What do you mean?
I showed them what
would happen if they
decided to mess with me again.
Think I got my point across?
Ugh! You can't do this.
Not here in the Special Zone.
If you want to stay here. You'll
have to stop this right now!
I don't think they're
going to let me stay here
much longer anyway.
I'll make them!
I promised you that! And
I intend to keep my promise.
I'm not even sure that
we should stay here anymore.
What if you had died
in that explosion today?
Have you considered the chain of
events that would have unfolded?
Both Cain and Sei would
have been completely enraged.
Without a doubt, Auguste
and his gang would have been
turned to ash
and scattered at sea.
That would surely
strike terror into those
who are at odds with the
Company, and it would have
further strengthened
the peace in the Special Zone.
All would live
happily ever after.
It may seem harsh,
but you know I'm right.
Mimiko. I'd never
forgive myself if
I was responsible
for your death.
I hate to say this after all the
trouble I've put you through,
but it's not
right for us to stay.
I feel we must leave.
For your safety.
But you can't.
And good evening to you, sir.
I had a feeling we hadn't
seen the last of you yet.
After studying our intelligence,
we've come to the conclusion
that arrangements were made for
him to enter the Special Zone.
There's someone in
the Special Zone who
would invite a Kowloon Child?
If a Kowloon Child
were to cross the barrier,
would it be at all
possible for us to detect it?
No sir. The barrier
that I constructed
does not have that capability.
The barrier doesn't just
keep them from entering.
It would also keep
them from leaving.
A Kowloon Child
that somehow makes it in
would have no choice
but to settle here.
Zelman!
Hello?
No, I'm still in the meeting.
What's that? What
are you trying to say?
Hey. Just wait.
Calm down, Sayuka!
What happened?
A man who Auguste drank dry
today has come back to life.
And then?
Janaway was bitten by the
man and he started going crazy.
He and the other three
ended up killing each other.
And then they all turned to ash.
What. What could have
caused all this to happen?
Could it be?
Please say it isn't.
That's all for today.
Go home and get some rest.
Yes, sir.
Just let me confirm one thing.
You're completely sure
that it was Auguste who
drank that man's blood?
Yes. There's no doubt about it.
Got it. Good night.
Have the suppression team
switch everything over to
anti-Kowloon
equipment immediately.
Yes!
Lord Dragon.
By the will of heaven,
Jiro is there.
Through him, we'll live.
I feel more powerful
now than I ever have.
Even when I was first turned.
I must confess that
I never felt so alive.
Bastard. Don't tell
me you're one of them now.
One of whom?
Don't play dumb!
In Hong Kong, I cut down more
of you than I care to remember.
I've seen this before.
There's no mistaking it!
You are one of them.
So it is as I suspected. I see.
So this is what it is
like to be a Kowloon Child.
Tell me who bit you.
But I haven't
been bitten by anyone.
Liar. Then how?
I don't care how it happened.
Mimi? Don't worry.
My brother will never
lose to a guy like that.
I hope you're right.
But I've been feeling
strange lately and I don't why.
I've got a bad feeling
in the pit of my stomach.
Shall we duel Silver Blade?
Quite impressive, Silver Blade.
As you know I have a long
history with Kowloon Children.
And I've vowed to never
let a single one escape.
It's a shame. You were
an excellent swordsman.
It's not over.
You're wrong. It is over.
I drank from my own men.
What did you just say?
As long as this blood survives,
then I'll be immortal.
Then I'll kill them... all.
It looks like Auguste
has left me a parting gift.
Oh no!
Mimiko! Kotaro!
Sorry I'm late.
Just who are you?
Pleased to meet you.
Jiro Mochizuki.
The Kin-Killer.
Hero of the crusade.
And the protector of Old Blood.
The brave descendent
of the Sage Eve's bloodline.
You're a descendent of
the Kowloon, right? How odd?
Yes. I am and my
name is Yafuri Chao.
During the crusade,
I was bestowed with
the kiss of darkness by
the Kowloon King's own fangs.
"I can't wait to see Jiro
again."
For ten years, that's
what she's been saying.
My sister, Cassa.
Cassa.
The Kowloon Children are
a menace that I cannot ignore,
for their existence
threatens my survival.
That is why I
eliminate your kind.
Whether you have
done wrong or not,
I assure you that
I will finish you.
Episode Eight: "Protector"