Uhh...
What?
Good evening, sir.
Oh... Good
evening to you, too.
Are you okay?
You weren't hurt were you?
I feel fine. I don't
think I'm injured.
But thanks for asking.
That's good to hear.
The carriage...
This is a horse
drawn carriage.
The horse on the
right is called Gale
and I like to call
the one on the left Gust.
We have to stop them.
Why would
you want to do that?
Because they're out of control!
It's okay. I almost
wish they could go faster.
But... Why?
Because we're...
running from someone.
Kotaro!
Enough!
No, Jiro. Wait!
You can't... You'll never
catch them in your condition.
Please let go.
You idiot... Go after them now
and you don't stand a chance.
I know what I'm doing.
And I don't have time to
stand around arguing with you.
Why didn't you tell me?
You wouldn't have
believed me, even if I did...
Not without this.
When I hold this
sword I am devoured by
the overwhelming
desires it bestows on me.
I thought I could
overcome these urges.
But I was wrong.
And because of that
I find myself in
this disgraceful state.
So please, Mimiko. I have
to find... my brother.
I'm sworn to protect him.
I'm all that he
has left in this world.
I can't let him down.
I have to save him.
You might as well give up.
He won't listen to you no matter
how much you try
to persuade him.
I'll lend you my motorbike.
Maybe it will help
you catch up with those guys.
You know each other?
We sure do.
I've gone ahead
and shut down the streets
you'll be traveling on.
You'll have the
road to yourself.
Mimiko... We don't
have time for this.
And if you do catch up
with them, what will you do?
You can't possibly hope to
defeat them in your condition.
Just think!
I grow tired of your meddling.
Drink my blood
before you go then.
Wait a minute...
You're a compromiser, right?
This is strictly forbidden.
So don't tell anyone!
Sure thing.
I might not act like it...
But I am a
criminal investigator.
I'll let this slide.
Are you sure about this?
Just do it.
Well... While I
appreciate your offer
I do hope you
haven't forgotten.
Your company
currently restricts me from
entering the Special Zone.
You want to go save
Kotaro, don't you? So...
Hurry up and do it already.
More! Please more...
Mimiko...
Jiro?
It's over... I really
appreciate what you've done.
What... What's going
on? Where am I?
This was your first time
being bitten, wasn't it?
Huh? What are
you talking about?
Just take it easy... Start by
trying to stand up on your own.
I think I can hear
what you're thinking.
That's the phenomenon
know as resonance.
The blood of yours that is
now coursing through my body
is calling out to
the blood in your own.
Then does that
mean that you can...
Mimiko...
What is it?
You're drooling.
Please tell me that
this doesn't mean that
you can read my mind too.
Give it back. Give it back now.
Give my blood back
to me this instant.
I was kidding.
My blood has not entered
your body, so therefore...
There's really no way
for me to read your mind.
Really?
Right now, you can tell whether
or not I am lying. Can't you?
Yes... I can...
Don't worry.
It's only temporary.
The resonance will
disappear over time.
You've done a brave thing.
I can never thank you enough.
I am greatly indebted to
you from this day on, Mimiko.
I want to go with
you on your mission.
Miss Wong...
You would just slow us down...
Besides, they're no longer
the people you once knew.
I know...
But... I owe it to them...
They're my friends...
I want to see this through.
You need to go with them.
Who...? Me?
This woman here is not
a Kowloon Child. And so...
She's still
under the purview of
the compromiser who
started the negotiations.
Yes, that's true.
Mimiko... Thank you.
Just doing my job.
I have no intention of
apologizing at the moment.
But when this is all over
you'll have my gratitude.
So it's you...
The Silver Blade?
I'm well aware... That I'm in no
position to ask you for favors,
but please... Help me...
Well, Jiro!
Since I am a hopeful
resident of the Special Zone...
I will make sure that the
Kowloon never make it in.
Okay, if you guys are done
with your pow wow session,
I think it's best that
we get this thing started.
So Jiro... Go do your thing.
With pleasure.
Damn it! Quit squirming!
And keep your mouth shut!
Brother, where are you?
Come beat this
rotten vampire to a pulp!
I think I might be sick.
Watch out!
Oh, right.
Keep going. Try to
link your senses with
Jiro to maintain your balance.
I'll try...
Incredible...
There they are!
Where?
Jiro has them in
his sights right now.
We're coming up
on the Twilight Bridge.
Then we should be there soon.
He's here... Impressive speed.
I wasn't expecting you to
catch up with us so quickly.
I guess what they
say about you is true...
Silver Blade.
Damn...
This annoying
little brat's been squirming
the whole time I've had him.
I only have one
arm, after all...
I don't need this unmanageable
little brat slowing me down.
I think I should
teach him some manners.
Tsang... That's
your name, isnt' it?
Yeah. Surprised
you remembered.
It's such an honor.
I'm touched. Really I am.
I'll forget it soon enough.
That's impossible!
He's using the Hide Hand!
Chan!
You shouldn't let your emotions
get the better of you...
Pathetic.
That's it!
Now you can play
together... in Hell.
What the Hell?
I was so close, dammit.
What pathetic last words.
You'll never understand us.
You, whose bloodline
transcend death,
will never know
what we go through.
True. I don't
understand your hardships.
But neither can
you understand the destiny
and curse of my bloodline.
So don't assume that you do.
All my life I've
been surrounded by death.
I eat to live.
And I kill to eat!
That's... the life
of a Kowloon Child.
And that is no life.
You're a parasite for
whom I feel no sympathy.
You were very brave through
this whole ordeal, Kotaro.
Thanks, brother.
Chan...
Miss Wong... Bye...
The media's coming.
We have to get
away from here fast!
Do you think we should
go back to Chinatown?
I'm sure that area is still
crawling with Company forces.
And I bet the media
has gathered there as well.
What then?
We've only one place to go.
But, Mimiko, the barrier...
I can't get in.
What are you talking about?
Jiro Mochizuki...
Kotaro Mochizuki...
On behalf of the Company...
I invite you
into the Special Zone.
I, Mimiko Katsuragi,
welcome you
and sincerely hope
you enjoy your stay.
I see. Got it. Looks
like we've managed to
avoid the worst
possible scenario.
I hope you're not
getting ahead of yourself.
I mean... just think
of all the bad publicity
this incident
is sure to stir up.
But he did well for us. Why
not give him a little credit?
Credit?
Don't fool yourself.
His involvement in this
matter has only resulted
in greater losses
for the Company.
But it still makes
me laugh thinking of
him falling into the ocean.
He didn't fall into the ocean.
He jumped in without hesitation
to save the Lord Sage.
It was impressive really.
I see... So you were there
to witness the whole thing?
I envy you. I wish I
could have been there as well.
I would have liked
to have seen him drown.
I win.
I went out waiting for a pair,
so it's three limit hands.
Three... Limit hands!
Wait a minute, Lord Dragon.
Are you sure such
a hand even exists?
Yes.
You're... you're sure?
He would know.
Damn... I hate losing
to a little kid all the time.
It's just not fair.
Do you want to
play poker instead?
No, no it's fine. We don't have
to switch games on my account.
Now, let's go again.
We should invite
another player to join us.
Not purple boy, I hope.
Soon...
All of us... will play together.
Indeed, Sei.
Are you okay?
I've finally made it
into the Special Zone,
but there's no one
here to share it with.
I want to...
bury her in the earth
of the Special Zone.
Is Kotaro all right?
Yes. By tomorrow, he'll
be brimming with energy.
I just can't believe
Chan's really gone.
I can't either.
Kotaro will never forget
her, though. I'm sure of it.
But he won't be
depressed forever.
He's really a tough
kid and he'll make it
through this hardship.
I'm sure you're probably right.
I guess that the
resonance... faded away.
What's that?
Oh nothing. I was
just talking to myself...
I was thinking you
guys could stay at my house,
at least for the night,
if that's all right with you.
How generous of you, Mimiko.
No problem.
But are you
sure it'll be okay
for a unmarried
woman to have guests?
Maybe not, but
don't remind me...
I'm kinda trying not to
let that bother me right now.
And on top of that,
you're a virgin.
It's really quite a rarity
in this day and age.
And I must say
that a virgin's blood
is a delicacy
to us vampires.
You pervert! Pervert!
Pervert! Pervert!
Just wait... I wasn't
trying to offend you!
I was merely... trying to convey
to you my vampire's appreciation
for virgin blood!
You're overre--
Just shut your mouth and
don't say another word to me!
Damn it! I wish I'd taken
Miss Wong's submachine gun
from her... But maybe...
Maybe I'll just throw you
into the ocean. Feed the fish.
Now listen... I absolutely
will not stand for
any more sexual harassment.
Sure... No more
sexual harassment.
Uh! Man, you piss me off!
Look, I'll give
you a place to sleep...
But it's gonna be on the floor.
Tell me something, Mimiko.
Are these normal tactics that
compromisers use when
dealing with their clients?
You still talking?
One more word from you
and you're out on the street.
You don't have to
worry about me, Mimiko.
I promise to be
a perfect gentleman.
Oh, I'm not
worried about it, Jiro.
Because I'm sleeping
with a bucket of Holy water.
Yes, I have no doubt.
And I believe that every
other powerful group within
the Special Zone is currently
trying to determine how best to
deal with his arrival.
Or perhaps... their aim
is to put an end to him.
Episode five:
"The Special Economic Zone"