Amazing how quickly time passes.
It's been ten years since
you came here with Kotaro.
He was just a baby then.
This entire decade, I have
never forgotten the debt of
gratitude I owe
both you and the princess.
Truly, I owe you everything.
We have a few more years
before Kotaro emerges.
You two should stay here
until then. It makes more sense.
I'm sorry, Crow, but we've
been over this already.
Listen to me, Jiro. I'm worried
about you. Both of you.
Here the princess and I
can help you, but out there...
Well, out there's
a different story.
It's the destiny
of my bloodline.
If I wait until Kotaro
emerges, it will be too late.
I want him to know
the outside world before
it's out of reach for him.
His only thoughts
shouldn't be that of
unnatural things in
the darkness of night.
Wait up, Grand Duke Bow-wow!
Hi, princess...
What are you doing?!
That's for me?
Thanks, this is
really nice of you...
Did you knit the
whole thing yourself?
Don't bother...
This whole thing will get
covered in snow out here.
Please, your highness.
There's no need to be so sad...
When I'm in the Special Zone...
I'll write you all the time.
Thanks again for the scarf...
It means so much to me ...
And every time I wear it I'll
think of you, your highness.
I always knew you were
pretty amazing princess...
But I had no
idea you could knit...
Was it a hard
thing for you to do?
This is now my most
prized possession.
Uh... I'll just wipe
it off... See...?
Well, Crow... It looks like
Kotaro is up to no good again.
Oh, gimmie a break.
It must be nice to
be young and having fun.
I have next to zero
for my vacation time
and my salary
hardly makes it worth
my while in the first place.
That whole business
with the phone call
this morning
was a bunch of crap.
Calling a girl before dawn
and ordering her out of bed.
"Just get up, go down
the beach and investigate."
What the hell is that?
Is that it?!
What's that?
That's a... person.
Uh...
Go grab your phone...
We gotta call an ambulance!
Right!
Hey dude... You okay?
Can you stand?
Cut! Excellent guys,
Juuust great!
I've never seen
a performance like that!
Just masterful...
And the makeup! Wow...!
And let's see here.
Looks like you lived
to see another scene kid.
Now let's get you on to
the next set. Up and at 'em.
They've got crew and
extras ready and waiting.
You're a vampire right...?
I'm aware that
you don't know me...
But just trust me on this...
I came here to help you.
Anyplace out of the sun.
Leave it to me.
You kids and
your method acting. Ha!
What just happened?
I have no idea.
Have we gotten
any word from Johan?
Not yet.
Then our hands are tied... Just
stick to the plan for now...
The rest is in your
hands, Master Strategist.
It's what I do best, sis.
I can't do this anymore!
I'm finished.
I can hear it now.
For the rest of the summer
it'll be nothing but rumors
and stories about skeleton guy
and the crazy
giggling idiot lady!
I'll never be able to set foot
on that beautiful beach again.
I would like to thank
you for your assistance...
Without you we would've--
That's the biggest
load of crap-- I mean...
You have a name?
It's Jiro... Mochizuki.
Jiro's a pretty common name...
Should be an easy
one to remember.
Then please make
sure that you do.
I already have. So the
little one there next to you--
That's Kotaro, right?
As I said...
Our situation
happens to be grave
and is of no fault of our own.
To all appearances...
we have simply been caught up
in the chaos created by
your esteemed colleagues.
We brothers are
victims here. Nothing more.
Don't you think I know that...?
For ruining your voyage, as a
representative of the Company,
I would like to
offer our apologies...
We are very, very, very, sorry.
That's the biggest load
of crap... And you... are?
Mimiko Katsuragi!
Oh, yes, Mimiko...
What a very unusual name...
It's rather funny
sounding when you hear it.
Just do me a favor
and don't forget it...
You don't want to tick me off.
Oh, don't worry...
I remember it already.
Great, we agree...
Now, since I know that you
and the kid are traveling
to the Special Zone...
The least I can do
is offer you guidance.
I'll show you the way myself.
How does that sound?
Is it at that point
you'll hand my companion
and I over to
the suppression team?
Mr. Mochizuki.
Yes?
Let me take a moment
to make myself clear.
Okay, I'm listening.
While I'm part of
the same company as those
you met earlier,
I am a compromiser.
I act as more of a
mediator than anything..
In our line of work, the subject
always given top priority is
the continuing peaceful
co-existence between
Black Bloods like you
and the Red Bloods like us.
You call yourselves Red Bloods?
Oh right. You probably don't
know any of this, huh?
In order to be clear when we're
talking of our two races...
We call your kind Black Bloods
and we call our kind Red Bloods.
It shows equality between
two races of sentient beings...
that we're equal
as living creatures.
That's just two minutes
and seven seconds...
Yafuri, go ahead.
It's nothing personal pal.
How long are we
going to keep doing this.
Who knows? It's just one
of those things we have to do
in order to survive...
And remember if you
slack off, I'm telling sis.
Here... This is next.
Yeah, don't worry I'm on it.
Good boy.
Please, no!
So we've got red
bloods and black bloods...
Are we sure
there's nothing else?
Good morning, Kotaro.
Oh hey, brother! Good morning.
How are you feeling today?
I feel kinda salty...
It's gross!
Looks like you
didn't fall apart though.
I remember now. I was
on the ship and then I--
You must have
jumped in and saved me!
I sure did.
Thank you brother. I always
knew I could count on you.
It figures... He's a lot
nicer to him than he is to me.
So brother...
Who's that... that girl?
Allow me to introduce myself...
My name is Mimiko Katsuragi...
It's nice to meet you.
Mimiko...
That name's kinda weird.
Yeah... It's different...
I get that a lot...
Now I know you feel
salty from the water...
But you can at least
get the taste out of
your mouth with a
few bites from this.
I can have this...?!
Are you serious?!
Thank you so much!
She's really nice, brother.
So, Mimi, what are you
doing here with us anyway?
Actually--
She's our guide.
It's her job to escort
us to the Special Zone.
We place
ourselves in your care.
She's really our guide?
It won't be a long trip,
but we'll have lots of fun.
Hey Mimi...
What's the matter?
Uh... Oh... I was just
noticing how different
you two are for being brothers.
We may look and act different,
but we're brothers for sure.
And outside of that
we've got no one.
We're the only
ones in our bloodline.
You shouldn't speak too
much of our family, Kotaro...
What my younger brother
here is saying is true...
We are brothers, but while
he can handle the sun...
and flowing water...
this obviously doesn't happen
to be the case with me...
And that's all there is to it...
I hope that's
satisfactory for you.
Sorry I noticed.
Awesome! Awesome! Awesome...!
This is so cool
brother...! Yes! Yes!
You can calm down now, Kotaro!
Okay! Right!
That's it!
That's the Special Zone!
It sure is. We just cross
that bridge and we're there.
Is something wrong?
How thoughtless of me.
What?
There's a barrier
surrounding the Zone.
Wait. What are
you talking about...?
They don't have
anything like that here.
It is a barrier that
cannot be felt by humans.
Most vampires would find that
they have no
reaction to it either.
The barrier serves
only one purpose.
And that is...?
To keep specific bloodlines from
entering without an invitation.
Yes... Ten years ago...
During the Kowloon Shock...
This method was developed
to establish defensive lines
and enclosed camps.
Wait a second, but...
That means--
It's not what you think...
Neither my brother nor
I are Kowloon Children.
Fine then. What are you?!
You may not see it...
but I am in fact descended from
a noble line of vampires...
and I always adhere
strictly to their traditions.
Kotaro...
Come over here please.
What?!
Come over here.
But Brother...
Just do it.
So what is it?
Mimiko's job as our
guide has come to an end.
Awe...
That was the arrangement from
the start. Now you know that.
Mimiko, I'd like to thank
you for your hospitality.
This young lady has
been nothing but good to us...
If you lay a hand on her, I
won't just stand by and watch.
I think you're aware I'm
not interested in the girl.
Our objective is you.
Huh?
Sorry for the trouble we
put you through last night.
Target has made contact.
Roger that.
My name is Kelly Wong...
and I need your help to
get into the Special Zone.
You see, unfortunately my
knowledge of which bloodline
I belong to is
minimal at best.
Shortly after I was transformed
my parents died in the
Kowloon Shock, taking with them
any information about my past.
One of the so-called
broken bloodlines...
So I take it you
were born in Hong Kong?
Basically... And I
overheard your conversation...
If you're parting ways
here with the company,
it works out for all of us...
I was hoping you would
join forces with us.
Join forces with you...?!
You're kidding me!
Well, aren't you clingy...
The man just said that
he was leaving you here
and you can't let go.
But I'm a compromiser...
I can't just abandon a job
before it's been completed.
Then you're invited
to come along too.
Well I don't, know, uh...
Hey, brother... You're pretty
popular, you know that?
Trust me, Kotaro,
that's not always a good thing.
But at the very least you can
write to Crow and brag about it.
Now if I did that he'd never
let me hear the end of it.
You've been listening,
so I assume you know...
I'm, to my regret,
suspected of being one of
the Kowloon Children you see.
And to invite one of that
bloodline into your group--
It doesn't matter what
bloodline you belong to.
We'll accept you... Even
if you are a Kowloon Child.
Let me make myself clear,
what I did last night was
not meant to benefit you.
I understand.
You reacted logically based on
your knowledge of the situation.
What we need from
you is your power...
And in exchange we
can provide you with
something that you
need but don't have.
Just what
exactly would that be?
Friendship of course.
A whole bunch of new friends...
What do you think?
Should we join up with that
lady and her group of people?
There's a young girl
traveling in our group that's
about the same
age as you are...
I'm sure the two of
you will be good friends.
Uh... But I...
It's settled... Now then...
Let's get out of here.
The first thing we'll do
is meet up with the others and--
Wong, wait a minute.
I wasn't sure at first, but...
I think this guy
is the kin-killer.
Is that true?
Fantastic...! I heard every
story there was about you
when I was a mercenary!
I couldn't imagine a
better ally...! This is great!
Get Down!
Wong!
Are you okay?
Silver!
I never thought
they go so far as to
attack us in broad daylight...
It looks like The Company
is feeling rather bold.
Wait...! I didn't do this!
Don't worry. I know.
I may not look it but
I'm a hundred years old...
I've learned a
lot along the way.
A hundred... years old...? That
makes you an Old Blood right?
To be honest, I knew they'd
try to make this kind of move.
They really had no choice but to
set up an ambush
somewhere along the way.
I figured it would
be easier to negotiate
with you around
rather than not.
Kotaro!
What is it?
Listen Carefully... because
I had to save you in the ocean,
I've drained all of my energy...
so I'm too weak to break
down their lines and carry you.
I'm going to play decoy and
try to draw them away from you.
Which means that you'll have
to get past them on your own.
Do you think you can do that?
I don't know...
I guess I can try.
I'll go with him!
But Mimiko...
I appreciate the offer.
But I'd prefer not to
rely on your sympathy.
That wasn't
exactly why I offered.
At any rate, we'll be on
our way here very shortly.
You can explain
this situation to
the suppression
team when they arrive.
Aw... You mean we're gonna have
to say goodbye to Mimi anyway?
Yes, now let it go! You
have to get out of here.
If you don't escape
soon, they'll catch you.
All right! I'm going!
Kotaro?
What is it now, brother?
You take care of
yourself out there.
You got it! See you later!
Is this the right move...?
I don't know.
Is the Japanese sunlight
really this powerful?
Move it!
Damn!
Over there!
What an idiot.
Under normal circumstances,
humans will not turn unless we
drink the blood of a Vampire.
But the Kowloon can turn humans
just by sucking their blood.
They can even convert other
Vampires to their bloodline.
If we allow them
to exist unchecked,
it could spell disaster.
Episode Three:
"The Kowloon Bloodline"