Welcome.
Excuse me.
I want to buy him.
You want him?
Yes.
I'm sorry, but
he's not for sale.
You see, I'm giving him to my
granddaughter for her birthday.
I'm afraid I
can't sell him to you.
What?! Oh, no.
It's okay, Alice.
Please don't get too upset.
You don't have to tell me that.
Then can I ask you to
pass a message along
to your granddaughter?
Sure.
Tell her to take
good care of him. Okay?
I'll tell her that.
Thanks very much.
Alice.
What?
Oh, it's nothing.
Mimiko.
I'm sorry, but I
really don't think you can
protect us on
your own anymore.
Never underestimate
the people who live here.
I'd just like to see him again.
It's been over
ten years, you know?
So tell me. Can you
be the ocean, Jiro?
So that river
will lead to the ocean.
Jiro. Kotaro. You aren't alone.
For starters, you have me.
Brother!
You won, didn't you?
I'm so glad.
Yeah.
Hey, Mimiko.
Hi, Jiro.
It's time.
You should finish this.
Kotaro.
Forgive me. I was trying
to keep you out of harm's way.
But it appears now I
have no choice but to--
Don't worry.
I understand, Brother.
Now get 'em!
Damn it!
Jiro.
I have seen your resolve.
I will clear the
way for you. Now go!
Thank you, Sei.
Mimiko.
I need to tell
you why Kotaro and I
came here to the Special Zone.
Oh, actually, I already--
I brought Kotaro here so
that he might make new friends.
I don't want him to be lonely
when I'm not around anymore.
The vampire that turned me
was the Alice Eve, the Sage.
She was a Source Blood.
And she was one of the most
ancient among the Black Bloods.
A Source Blood?
But she did not attempt to
create any of her own kinsmen,
with one exception. Me.
I am the only one she has
ever shared her blood with.
As her protector,
it is my duty to
keep both her body
and her blood safe.
Alice!
She was killed in Hong Kong.
But then reborn
in the form a child.
Kotaro is that child.
He is her reincarnation.
What?
Cassa!
Jiro!
Alright then, name yourself!
I am the Child of
the Sage. Jiro Mochizuki!
So that's what you're
calling yourself? Fine then!
Here goes, Jiro!
Kotaro. Does he know about this?
In her reincarnated
state she is powerless.
She is alive,
but without a sense of
herself or her memories.
When her reincarnated
form is mature enough,
I will return her blood to her.
That is my responsibility
as her protector.
And afterwards I
will live on through her.
That's why it is called the
bloodline that transcends death.
But. Then, someday, Jiro will--
I live so that I
may be consumed by her.
It... it can't be...
Damn it all! Why'd he have to
show up and ruin everything?
Uh...
Wait a minute, Zaza, don't tell
me you're the cause of this.
I guess you could say I
stirred up the hornet's nest,
but it was what
sis wanted after all.
You-- You can be
such an idiot sometimes.
Fighting amongst yourselves?
Damn!
This is what it
means to be a vampire.
It is our destiny to sacrifice
anything and everything for
the sake of our bloodline.
Jiro!
Cassa!
Damn you, Zelman!
Isn't this fun, Jiro?!
Well... That should
just about do it.
I can't believe that they
actually made it through that.
That's some pretty
impressive driving.
Damn, Zelman.
This has nothing to do with you.
It looks like sis
is on the defensive.
That's what she
gets for being picky.
What?
She hasn't drank any blood.
Not for the last three months.
That doesn't sound good.
Damn it!
This is the end!
It's over. Give it up, Cassa.
You'd like that, wouldn't you?
But for my bloodline,
surrendering is not a choice.
Why?
Because it would mean
the complete
eradication of our people.
And that is why we will continue
battling to the bitter end.
And that is the way
of the Kowloon Child.
Well then, at the very least
you can fall beneath my sword.
Cut out the hero talk.
And let's just fight.
Such incredible pain! Jiro!
Brother!
As expected.
When it comes to the sword,
you have a slight edge.
With this, it will be finished.
It's about time.
You bear an
unfortunate weakness.
The border!
Once we pass through there,
we'll be outside the barrier!
Seems that's it for today!
You'll see me again.
If you survive, of course.
Cassa!
Zaza, no!
Jiro!
Don't ever, come anywhere near
us again, or you'll regret it.
Well, we'll see.
I had fun, Jiro.
They got away.
I'm sorry I failed you.
Well, at least we're
rid of them for now.
Oh, Mimi. Good morning.
What's wrong? Are you
feeling sick or something?
Was that all just a dream?
Huh? A dream? Oh, brother
told me to give this to you.
It's not much, but here you go.
What's this for?
It's for rent.
What?
He wasn't sure exactly
what rent was like here
in the Special Zone, so
he said that's just for now.
He did?
Yup.
We're trying to find a place,
but it might take some time.
So we'll have to stay with you
for a little while longer, Mimi.
Brother wanted to make a good
impression by paying in advance.
Oh no. Why are you
crying? What's wrong?
Mimi, is that
not enough for rent?
Hey. Hey, Mimi!
What's the matter?
Ah, Master Swordsman!
I cannot thank
you enough for--
Shougo!
Hey, now. We haven't seen
each other in ten years.
No way to treat an old friend.
Rinsuke told me everything.
You're just awful.
Now tell me if it's true.
Mimiko's apartment
wasn't bombed by
the Auguste Wyker,
now was it?
The bomb was placed
at your command.
It's-- It's true.
You better have
a damn good reason.
I wanted you to stay together.
You and Mimiko
need to be a team.
What? That's just absurd.
Right or wrong, it
was to make sure you would
remain in the Special Zone.
There's an empty
building the Company
once used as a warehouse.
It's really old, but
it's more than big enough
for three people to live in.
You had this planned
from the start, didn't you?
Yeah, that's right.
But why would you go
to such lengths just to...
What's in the Eleventh Yard?!
Ashes.
But it can't be--
I'm afraid so. The ashes were
brought here from Hong Kong.
The Special Zone
is a burial ground.
The Eleventh Yard holds the
ashes of the Kowloon King.
Cassa and her people came here
to retrieve the King's ashes.
They wanted to resurrect him.
You defeated the Kowloon
King once before, Jiro.
So we need you to be
here if he comes back again.
I-I can't do that. There
won't be a miracle this time.
I'm sorry, but you're
the only chance we've got.
So the Lord Dragon
and Cain were
attempting to
alienate me because--
That's right. They were trying
to free you of that burden.
Jiro, if you're staying
in the Special Zone,
I want you to work for us.
You want me to guard
the King's ashes?
No. To protect
Mimiko Katsuragi.
Mimiko? But why her?
You have to understand.
For a human, ten years is
not a short amount of time.
I'm afraid I'm no
longer capable of
fighting alongside you.
Protect her for me,
along with the Lord Sage.
Please, Jiro.
I will.
Jiro! You don't
have to push yourself
so hard just to help out.
No, no. I need to help.
We are going to be
imposing on you, after all.
Oh! Hot!
Let's get you inside.
Talk about lucky. We sure
found a great new place,
and so close, too.
I guess good things do
happen every once in a while.
Damn you, Shougo.
What?
Nothing.
I've been meaning to
talk to you. I need a favor.
Listen. You can't
tell Kotaro what you know.
Kotaro is that child.
He is her reincarnation.
Once you've returned
the blood to Kotaro,
then what's gonna happen?
I'll probably be
completely consumed by her.
Please don't be sad about it.
It's my fate,
and I'm very proud to
carry on the life
of my Source Blood.
Yeah, but--
I found something awesome!
Where did you get
that thing, Kotaro?
Found him upstairs.
Can I keep him?
I promise that I'll always
take really good care of him.
Well all the stuff here
belongs to the Company...
But I doubt anyone
will really miss it.
Awesome!
And from now on you're
going to be known as
my best friend,
Lord Bowwow.
You're going to be spending
all your time with me!
Yes? Katsuragi here.
Yeah.
I understand. We'll head
over there right away.
Jiro, Kotaro.
Let's get to work.
Does it have to be in
the middle of the day?
Oh, quit your complaining!
You're my closer, aren't you?
I suppose so.
Now let's kick some ass!
Yeah!
Come on, this is our first
gig! So try to look sharp!
Okay, fine.
It'll be all right. We'll
figure something out, Jiro.
I'm sure of it!
Right!
Oh, come on!
Do you have to walk so fa--?