You shouldn't have interfered.
Alice, are you hurt?
Alice.
I know that this isn't fair.
Normally, we have the person
make the choice for himselves.
We explain
everything to them,
and make sure that
they properly understand,
and then having done that, we
give them the right to choose.
We don't force it on them.
They have to accept it first.
But this time
we couldn't do that.
There wasn't enough time
and besides... Besides...
No matter how hard I tried, I
just couldn't hold myself back.
I'm sorry, Jiro. I'm so sorry.
Forgive me for
falling in love with you.
Jiro?
Alice, I--
What is it?
It hurts, so much.
It hurts, Alice.
What's happening to me?
What's the situation?
At last count there were
thirty-two confirmed cases
of infection in the city!
Where has it hit the
hardest? What location?
Tsukimiya Hospital, sir.
Damn it! If only we'd
realized it at the dock.
There are
confirmed sightings of
Kowloon Children
in the Third Yard!
A compromiser has
just been injured!
There's an unknown
number of infected!
A death in the Ninth Yard!
We have witnesses!
People are panicking!
The prisoner in the
basement has just escaped!
What?!
Footage incoming!
Damn that boy!
What is this?
He infiltrated the Company,
but he's been dealt with.
Did you hear of the outbreak?
Yes, unfortunately.
It seems their plan to
distribute the tainted
blood has been a success.
We have no other choice but
for you to take the field in
opposition to the
Kowloon Children, Sei.
Otherwise, the
Special Zone will fall.
You can't mean that?
I'm afraid so, which means,
we must temporarily raise the
seal which now
protects the Special Zone.
I leave this place to you.
Quiet the confusion
among the people.
It can't be.
Cain.
Lord Dragon!
I must end this plague
of Kowloon Children.
Go after Cassa and
Walkerman for me, understand?
Did you say Walkerman?!
Then, the one who freed
Yafuri must have been--
It was him.
Allow them to escape,
and they will be the
seed of future trouble.
Stamp them out now!
We'll move heaven
and earth to do so.
Listen closely.
The Dragon King of the
East himself has gone to
return peace to
the Special Zone!
As of now, you are
to pour all your
efforts into
regulating information!
I will take
the offensive as well!
What?
That's... the Dragon
King of the East.
Hah! In the end, he's a Black
Blood, same as the rest of us.
That's the spirit.
How do you like
the boat, Yafuri?
Bro, it's you!
Where's sis at?
She hasn't come yet.
The Dragon King's
on the move tonight.
And I'm afraid we're
quickly running out of time.
Yafuri. Incoming!
It's Cain!
I know!
Come on, now. You're gonna
have to do better than that.
You want us
to get caught again?
Just shut up! I'll handle this!
Time to show 'em what
you're made of, Yafuri!
Now return to the Darkness!
Thank you.
You really saved us.
My work is finished here.
I'll leave the rest to you.
Stop it! What the
hell are you doing?
I'm so sorry. I can't
help myself anymore.
Really...
They're such a pain in the ass.
Are you sure you're
all right, Mimiko?
I wasn't able to do
anything. I'm worthless.
No, don't say that.
What's wrong?
It's Sei!
What?
Wow!
Cain is with him, too.
And so is Zelman.
You can tell?
Yeah, I'm not sure why. It's
like I can sense them somehow.
This sure is a great city, huh?
I see why you like
living here so much, Mimi.
Huh?
Everyone's trying
so hard to save it.
They're giving
everything they've got
in order to help
the city live on.
It must be a wonderful city
if everyone is willing to
lay down their
lives to protect it.
That's why you wanted us
to live here, too, isn't it?
Mimi, I want to thank you.
You invited us to live
in a really great place.
We're lucky to have you.
So, can I ask a
favor of you, Mimi?
What is it?
It's about my brother.
Will you try talking to
him one more time for me?
Yeah. But he won't listen.
Well, I know that my brother can
be really stubborn sometimes,
but I'm asking you
anyway, because I believe
deep in my heart that you
might be the only person who
can convince him
to save this city.
You think so?
I want to live here in the
Special Zone for a while.
After all, that's why we
came here in the first place.
Oh really, I
always meant to ask,
but surely
there's more to it.
No, that's it.
You're hiding
something aren't you?
Please Kotaro,
if there's another reason
why you guys are
here, I need to know.
Okay? Just tell me.
Don't tell brother, okay?
I won't.
He brought me here so that
I could make some new friends.
Just to make friends?
Yeah. I've been in
the sanctuary all my life.
And Grand Duke Bowwow
was my only friend
when I was living in there.
I guess it's because
everyone else who lived there
was so much older than me.
Oh, I see.
Brother was afraid I
couldn't be happy there,
so he decided that we should
leave for the outside world.
He said that I had a lot to
learn about things
outside the Sanctuary,
and that I'd make human and
vampire friends along the way.
So I guess you're
my first friend, Mimi.
You consider us
friends, don't you?
Yeah, I consider
you a friend.
Alright. No promises.
But I'll talk to him,
and we'll see what happens.
Where have you been?
I thought I'd lost you.
Kotaro, honestly,
sometimes you are just so--
Brother.
Are you okay?
What about Cassa?
The black-haired woman.
Did she do
anything to hurt you?
She didn't even touch me.
Mister Zelman scared her away.
Zelman did?
That's good.
I'm just so grateful to
see that you're alright.
I'm sorry if I
scared you brother.
I wanted to see Mimi again.
I know. It's my fault for
not taking your
feelings into consideration.
But please, don't ever
run off on me like that again.
Promise me that
you won't, Kotaro.
I won't. 'Kay,
I promise. I'm so sorry.
It's good to see you, Jiro.
Mimiko, listen. I'm sorry
for trying to leave,
but it was for your own good.
I'm afraid if you continue to
associate with us, it'll only
cause you more suffering.
Especially now that
Cassa is in the Special Zone.
There's no telling
what she might do.
What? What's the matter?
She sure was a strange person.
She's very dangerous
and can't be trusted, but under
different circumstances,
I'd like to talk to her more.
Mimiko! She's known as Cassa
the Black Snake for a reason.
Just stay far away from her!
I noticed she was very
interested in you, by the way.
I'm sure she was. Before
she became a Kowloon Child,
she was very close
to the Sage and me.
Makes sense.
Well, then why was she
so interested in Kotaro?
That damn snake. Why can't she
just leave the two of us alone?
She didn't seem particularly
hateful or resentful.
Maybe she's
not out to get you.
I don't know what Cassa's
true intentions
are with Kotaro and me.
And I haven't
for quite some time.
In Hong Kong, she betrayed
me in the vilest way imaginable.
But she saved Kotaro.
Wait, she saved Kotaro?
Can't this thing go any faster?
He's catching up with us.
She's maxed out at top speed.
Damn!
Glad to see you!
It's a good thing she's here.
Lady Cassa.
The fight has only just
begun. Let's take it easy.
Jiro, you're making a mistake.
What?
Running away is a mistake.
Having met her, I understand.
If you run, Cassa will
pursue you wherever you go.
That's the kind
of person she is.
Surely by now, you know that.
Please Jiro. You and Kotaro can
live with me here
in the Special Zone.
I'm afraid that I've
already made up my mind.
And I'm telling you, I
think leaving is a mistake.
You'll just never
understand, will you?
The world doesn't work
the way you think it does.
Not everything is
so easy and simple.
Oh is that right?
What exactly were you
doing all day today, Jiro?
'Cause you sure
weren't there to
help Kotaro when he
was in danger earlier.
Zelman saved him.
Hey, Mimi, listen.
When I asked for your help,
this isn't exactly
what I had in mind.
You're wasting your time
trying to provoke me like this.
Protector, my ass.
You try to do everything
yourself, and by doing so,
you're putting Kotaro
in danger, for no reason.
In the end, you're only
looking out for yourself.
How dare you
talk to me that way!
You're just a pathetic
human who's barely
been alive for twenty years.
And you think you can
admonish an Old Blood?
What about you?
You've lived a hundred years,
and what have
you made of yourself?
What do you have to
show for your heroism?
Who do you think you are?!
Listen!
Kotaro has been
kept safe up 'til now.
But it's not because of you.
Everyone in the Special
Zone has tried help.
You'll never be alone here,
because we all look
out for one another.
That's how the people here have
decided to lead their lives.
Understand?
How formidable Cassa is.
How dangerous the
Kowloon Children are.
Everyone knows about all that.
That's why they're
banding together now
and fighting for
all they're worth.
Because they know they
don't stand a chance alone,
but if we all fight together,
we can protect what's important!
We can't do it without you.
We need you, so please for
Kotaro's sake join forces
with those already fighting.
Only then will you
be able to defeat Cassa.
Only then will you become
a great river that can
stand fast against the
most powerful of forces.
So that...
someday, that river...
will lead you to the ocean.
But Mimiko... How in the
world did you know that?
No!
Wasn't the smartest move
using your body as a shield.
You're still far too erratic.
Silver Blade, my boy.
Brother!
Stay away!
Mimiko, no!
You aren't alone.
For starters, you have me.
Episode twelve, "For the
Eternal Pulse of Mine Bloodline,
I Would Offer
this Blood in Totality"