[YOSHIKA] Today, Barkhorn is
teaching us a combat lesson.
Here's something
to keep in mind
when fighting Neuroi.
They use Beam Weapons,
so even a split second
of lapsed concentration
could be fatal.
That's why you have to keep
your eyes open at all times
and not look away.
All the time?
But, that sounds impossible.
It was, at first,
no one could do it.
Right, Hartmann?
--[YOSHIKA] Huh?
--[HARTMANN] Hmm.
[BARKHORN]
But, with the proper training,
you'll be able to keep those
eyeballs peeled in no time.
[HARTMANN snores]
All right, wanna give it a go?
[gasps]
It involves a gun...?
Could you show us first, maybe?
Can you demonstrate? Hartmann?
What's wrong?
Get up here, right now.
Oh, fine, then.
I'll just show you
while she's asleep.
[YOSHIKA]
Hartmann, please wake up!
[HARTMANN shrieks]
No, please!
[MINNA]
This is an emergency alert.
All witches report
to command at once.
I repeat, all witches
to my office at once.
What could this be about?
I guess we'll learn
more when we get there.
Hey, Mio. I want you
to keep me up all night.
Sure. My pleasure.
I really wish I hadn't
seen or heard that...
Have a good night...
Come back!
We've received intel of
a Neuroi attack this evening.
So, I will be assigning
extra night duty.
You're going to be
on watch till dawn,
so you won't be able to sleep.
Ah! You're on night duty
tonight, too, Yoshika?
Yeah, looks like it.
Wait, isn't everyone?
Well, let me see.
No, I think you and the regular
night crew can swing it.
♪ Nothing can make me mad! ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm the best! ♪
Hey, Sanya. Do you
have any pointers on how
to be the best night
watch witch I can be?
Sure. I would love to teach you
how to use your body.
[EILA screams]
[HARTMANN]
No sign of the Neuroi yet.
Ooh, I have an idea:
wanna go for a walk?
No, bad idea.
You shouldn't wander
around at night,
not even within base walls.
Yeah, you're a fragile
little girl, y'know?
--She's outside.
--She doesn't count.
What is she even
doing out there?
[YOSHIKA] I caught the gleam
of a Fuso blade in the dark.
[sighs]
So tired..
You guys ready?
[YOSHIKA]
Are the Neuroi here?
No, but I heated
up the big bathtub.
Thought we could take a dip.
Heck yeah!
So that was it.
You were out chopping
up logs for the fire.
[YOSHIKA]
Sorry I'm late to the party!
Yeah, jeez. You took your time.
Well, it was sorta tough!
[HARTMANN, BARKHORN]
Miyafuji!
Ah. Way too hot!
[laughs] In Fuso,
this is the normal temperature.
Yeah. It feels great.
I like it to be so hot
that it's almost unbearable.
Well, you heard her.
Bathing in water
that's too hot is dangerous
and can lead to
heart attack or stroke!
Miyafuji, you like it hot?
That does answer my question,
just not literally.
[HARTMANN]
As a very sexy girl,
I have some special tips for
a good bath beauty routine.
First of all,
I recommend using Sturm
to move air all around
the body and create
your own personal jacuzzi!
It relaxes and beautifies!
[sighs]
This feels so good!
[BARKHORN] Ugh, can't
you pass gas elsewhere?
[SANYA] Doesn't the sauna
feel amazing, Eila?
Yeah! Glad we begged for one.
Although, to be
perfectly honest,
I would have preferred
a savusauna.
No one agreed.
Wait, this says it's 176?
That's too cold.
Wanna go outside?
Outside? No, It's too hot!
Low 40s.
We are in the tropics.
--I feel so relaxed!
--Same!
Should I make coffee?
Yeah!
That bath was perfect, huh?
Oh, that's right.
Hey, Shirley, and Lynne?
[SHIRLEY]
Hmm?
Um, yes? What is it?
You two can go to bed now.
Then why the heck did
you bring us here to begin with?
[YOSHIKA giggles]
Do you have any gum?
It helps me stay awake.
No gum, but I have this.
We used to eat
this back in Fuso.
[screams]
A devil fish! Away!
[SAKAMOTO]
I take it you don't like them?
No, I hate them,
and you better not forget it!
[BARKHORN chuckles]
Ah. Wow. Ah, you freaked out.
Yoshika. May I use the kitchen?
Are you gonna cook something?
Yeah, everyone
is getting a little hungry.
But wait...
Doesn't eating make you sleepy?
We could make it
taste disgusting.
That sounds kinda fun.
Hold on! This requires
some serious thought!
We're going into battle,
so we need nutrition.
No, we don't!
For once, I think Mio's right.
That's not what I meant!
The Neuroi aren't coming!
So, you guys had better
not ruin Sanya's cooking!
Just a minute!
The Neuroi never came...
Who should we
blame for this disaster?
The Neuroi, duh.
We'll make them pay for this.
[YOSHIKA] I've never wanted the
Neuroi to attack us more.
Um, pardon me, everyone.
--Don't tell me, they're here!
--Oh, come on!
Good, I'm sick of waiting.
I expected a warm welcome,
but this is ridiculous!
[GIRLS gasp]
I'd like to introduce Marseille.
She's come all the way
from the African front
to do a photo
shoot with you all.
And, about those Neuroi...
Yeah, they got in my way.
So, I took them all out
before I got here.
By the way I'm happy
to shake hands,
but I don't do autographs.
[GIRLS growl]
[MARSEILLE chuckles]
Uh, what?
[HARTMANN]
Technique! Open-eyed sleeping!
I have a very special
announcement for you today.
I'm Hanna Justina Marseille.
I have been sent from
the PR division to do
a little photo shoot with you!
I'm honored to be here!
Wait, where is everyone else?
[LUCCHINI]
Hmm-hmm!
They were up all night
guarding against the Neuroi.
So, the only reason they
were awake when I showed up
is they were waiting for
the Neuroi I defeated?
I guess it's up to you
to represent us, Lucchini.
Do us proud and give
her what she needs.
Roger!
[MARSEILLE] Ah! But they wanted
photos of me shaking hands
with another ace!
Sorry, the aces
need their sleep.
Minna! I know
this is the front lines!
But if one late night
knocks your people out,
that's sure sign of abuse!
[MINNA]
That's not why!
They slack off all day,
so they've gotten soft!
But I can't say that!
[YOSHIKA]
They woke us up again...
I'm Marseille,
one of the Storm Witches
from Africa. Hello, girls.
I'm here as part of a military
propaganda campaign called
the "Meeting of Aces."
And I'm honored to be here.
[GIRLS snoring]
Sorry. I woke you up.
Anyone want an autograph?
No apologies, please,
it's not your fault!
Looks like she's
still a pain the butt.
Hold on, do you know her?
Rumor has it she was Hartmann's
only real rival
back in Karlsland.
She turned every little thing
into a competition between us.
Eating contests.
Bathing tournaments.
Training was the worst of all!
Like I said, a pain in the butt.
For real. She sounds
like a total stalker.
[BARKHORN]
Wow, you're one to talk.
Oh, I just remembered.
My little sister really wanted
me to get your autograph.
Yeah? Of course.
I love signing autographs.
I thought... she hated them.
I bet she was just
using reverse psychology.
[gasps] I won't sign anything
for a block-headed sister lover.
Hanna, shut your mouth!
Trudy's no block-head, and she's
definitely not obsessed with--!
Yeah, you're right, never mind.
[BARKHORN]
How dare you?!
Why don't we all just
sit down for a nice lunch?
We could have an
eating competition, Hartmann!
Fine, but be forewarned,
you're cruising for a losin'.
Ooh!
You'll say yes to
your arch nemesis but not me?
[MARSEILLE]
We're off!
[HARTMANN]
Thank you for this food
we are about to receive, amen.
Young lady, such bad manners!
Well, I guess we have a winner.
It appears
my plan has backfired.
Pardon me, kitten.
May I have a glass
of milk instead of tea?
Will that pair well
with your lunch?
Yes, of course.
It's the best way to
maintain good eyesight.
And, thanks to milk, I've
officially got the loveliest
proportions in the entire world.
[GROUP]
You did not just say that!
Uh, Yoshika...?
Why would she need
to compete when she's blessed
with unique, valuable skills
like the butt reload?
Whoa, what is that?
[HARTMANN] She carries
her ammo at her hip,
then bounces it with her
butt up to her hand
so she can reload her weapon.
[YOSHIKA]
That's a neat trick!
Oh, right. Yeah, it is true.
Say what you will about me,
but I'm the world's
greatest Butt Master.
Ha! More like Butt Apprentice.
'Scuse me?
Check out this butt load!
Commander Minna
uses her butt to--
So. Who are
you gonna pair up with?
Oh, right, I almost forgot.
Well, after all,
I rearranged my schedule to come
and see my old friend, Hartmann.
I've never pitied Hartmann more.
Yes. Hartmann
is the strongest witch
living on this base,
I have no doubt.
[YOSHIKA groans]
Oh, you're right!
Ha, ha, sure, looks
like I'm your girl!
[MARSEILLE]
I'm picking up on a weird vibe.
Excellent work, you two!
Hartmann's pretty impressive
when she decides
to stop slacking off!
Yeah, well,
that's my rival for ya!
Brave in battle,
beautiful on the ground.
She's part apex predator,
and part lily in bloom.
Having a stalker must be hell.
Eila. We need to have a talk.
All right.
Better start the long trip home.
Are you leaving already?
Why not have a nice,
hot bath first?
Uh, Yoshika...
Ah, wait. This is for you.
Wow, an autograph? Thanks a lot!
You should
stay longer next time.
No contests, though, okay?
Deal. Thanks for
being a sport, old friend.
Welp, see you around!
[GIRLS] I can't believe
they woke us up for this.
[HARTMANN]
See, guys, I can be serious!
[MICHIKO] Hello, everyone!
It's that time again!
Michiko Yamakawa's Strike
Witches Classroom!
Today, I'll be
teaching you about Minna!
Her full name is
Minna Dietlinde Wilcke!
[MICHIKO]
She's the fearless leader of
the 501st joint fighter wing!
All the other girls
report to her!
And she also
happens to be one of
the Karlsland Empire's
ace witches!
In her time
fighting for the 501st,
she's accomplished a lot!
Because of the
beautiful and elegant way
she fights, she's sometimes
referred to as
the "Flying Fürstin,"
which means "Princess."
And, she navigates delicate
military politics with grace.
After all, as the witch
who created the 501st,
leadership comes
naturally to her!
She sure knows
how to give orders!
Her inherent ability is called,
"Three Dimensional
Space Understanding."
This allows her to find the
positions of all enemies
and allies instantaneously,
even in the middle of a battle!
I guess you
could say that Minna is
the ideal commander!
However. Minna
has also dreamed
of being a famous singer,
and she's widely regarded
as the most talented vocalist
of all the witches!
I can't believe
Yoshika gets to work with
such a well-rounded witch
who's a fighter and a singer?!
Way to go, Yoshika!
[MICHIKO]
Me, again, Michiko Yamakawa.
I've gotten word that Yoshika's
having a hard time lately.
I wonder what's going on.
I'm a little worried!
Next time: "501st.
You Can't Fly Anymore?"
You've never seen witches
like these before!