[YOSHIKA]
Combat stress?
When you're at war
for a long time,
it can cause mental
and emotional problems.
The symptoms include:
denying reality, impulsive
aggression, intense fatigue,
and a general sense
of self-loathing.
Which means, we all
have to take good care
of our mental and
emotional states, ya know?
Yeah, those two are
obviously very concerned
about the subject.
Oh, you mean Hartmann
and Barkhorn?
That's something else,
called domestic violence.
That's what Lynne said,
and I'd never
heard of it before.
Combat stress.
And she's right.
We have to take excellent care
of our bodies and minds.
I agree. I guess we
need to make sure
everyone spends more
time training, don't we?
Wha...?
We'll run marathons!
That, and 1,000 practice
swings with our swords
every morning will work wonders
for our mental states!
Minna! Listen to this!
Miyafuji has some great
ideas about training!
[YOSHIKA]
I'll never understand the way
the major's mind works.
How'd she get that
from what I said?
Mental care!
That's a great idea!
I asked Eila to help
with things like that,
but she never did,
so I just let it go.
Mental care? Don't need it.
Speak for yourself, Mio!
Some of the other girls might!
[YOSHIKA] Has anything been
stressing you out lately, Lynne?
[LYNNE]
No, ma'am!
Hey there, ladies!
I hope you haven't forgotten
about yours, truly.
No, Hartmann!
As a future doctor, like
yourself, I spend a lot
of my time thinking of
ways to reduce stress
for my comrades, to make
their lives easier!
I'm highly suspicious.
This sounds like fun,
and I want in on
the ground floor!
[YOSHIKA] Um, can we not
resort to violence?
I'm fine now, but when Chris
was in a coma, I was a mess.
Look, ladies, in love
and war, you can leave
all your puberty-related
problems to me!
[gasps] What did I do to
deserve this hateful glare?
[HARTMANN]
Could it be?
Did I, a queen among women,
make some kind of mistake? No.
She must have been driven
mad by my girlish figure
and can no longer cope
with the tension.
Allow me to present
the other major
source of all my stress.
Ah...
And, like I said before.
Chris stresses me
out all the time.
Oh! Siscon!
[yelps]
[BARKHORN]
That's not it at all!
But, if I say that,
then Miyafuji might think
that Chris is a hideous loser.
That's right.
Chris is one of the cutest girls
ever to walk the
face of the earth.
She is cute, but I don't know
if I would take it that far.
So, Shirley, is there
anything that's
been stressing you out?
I've been worried
that my flying speed
has hit a plateau.
My sister is a
brilliant engineer,
so leave it to me.
I can help you figure out
what's causing the lag!
These two are to blame!
They're screwing with your
aerodynamics for sure!
They're messing with
my back and my dreams?
You see, some boobs are
more powerful than others.
If you were to set up
your Striker Unit
like an airplane, with the
propellers spinning to push air
away from the
direction of flight,
would that help speed you up?
Great idea! I'll
try it right now!
[SHIRLEY]
Here I go!
[HARTMANN]
I saw that coming.
[EILA]
I've heard the rumors.
I know what you two are doing.
[HARTMANN, YOSHIKA]
Eila?
Is something really
stressing Eila out?
Better stay on your
guard, Miyafuji.
So, what kind of terrible
darkness lurks in your heart?
Is that seriously what
you two think of me?
I, Eila Ilmatar Juut--
[YOSHIKA, HARTMANN]
Full name?
I object to this.
You should have consulted me
before you even started!
[YOSHIKA, HARTMANN]
But, like, why?
I've used my future sight
to solve all kinds
of people's problems with
a great deal of success,
so what were you thinking?
Wait, you have?
That's fantastic, Eila,
we would love to have your help!
Why yes, of course you would!
[HARTMANN]
I feel so betrayed!
So who are you planning
to talk to next?
[HARTMANN]
She's even wagging her tail!
[YOSHIKA] Well, Perrine
is right over there.
Bad idea.
She'll bite your head off.
Okay, how 'bout
Lucchini, then?
Nah, she doesn't need our help.
We could ask her,
just in case.
Were you two really
planning to walk away
without asking my opinion?
Look me in the eye!
[HARTMANN] We couldn't find
Lucchini anywhere!
Why don't we ask Commander
Minna to look for her?
She's busy.
I think we opened up a
can of worms over there.
[HARTMANN]
Yeah, let's skip her.
Well, then, what about Sanya?
We haven't checked
in with her yet.
Has anything been stressing
you out lately, Sanya?
And please, be
completely honest!
[SANYA] Eila carries me in the
morning when I'm sleepy.
I was assigned night patrol
tonight, but it's gonna rain,
so Eila offered
to take my place.
No, I'm all right!
Thanks to Eila, I don't
have any issues!
Oh, Sanya!
I'll make your bed,
do your laundry,
and even take care of
you when you're sick!
If you need anything,
anything at all, let me know!
That's kind of creepy, Eila.
Hey, why are we
even doing this?
I guess I should have
asked you that before.
Lynne told me that
combat stress can become
a problem when
soldiers are at war
for long periods of time.
Aw, well, it's good
to know you care!
Not sure we're helping, though.
Maybe not, but my
intentions were good.
Stress relief stresses me out!
[SHIRLEY, EILA, SAKAMOTO, MINNA]
Life is stressful.
[yelling]
Lucchini!
She always has so much energy.
Good timing!
Did Lucchini pass this way?
[SHIRLEY, HARTMANN]
Ah-ha!
Wait, what? A cavity?
But why is she running away?
I told her how that's
typically treated,
and she bolted like a
frightened house cat.
[SHIRLEY]
Ah...
Where do you guys
think she went?
We'll never be
able to catch her,
she runs like the dang wind!
Oh, don't worry,
I know an easy way
to make her face the music.
Oh, that's right, you're
kinda like Lucchini's mom!
[gasps] I love it!
Of course. Let's go.
What kinda bait do you think
they'll use to trap her?
My money's on dessert or pasta.
[gasps] They're already back!
That was faster than I thought.
[YOSHIKA, SAKAMOTO gasp]
We're gonna use Sanya's
magic to find her!
Brilliant, right?
Uh, I guess, if you say so.
She's on night
patrol, so go easy.
What did you use the
stick and rope for?
You don't need
to worry about it.
We kidnapped Sanya from
right outta the tiger's den!
Our blitz tactics are unmatched.
Oh, god, what have
you done to Eila?
What? Where's Eila?
Tell me, Hartmann.
I can't now.
We really need to find
Lucchini, so I'm afraid
I don't have time to explain.
Oh, okay. I'll help
you look for her.
[YOSHIKA] She's not worried
at all? Orussians are strange.
She seems to be
in Shirley's room.
Why in my room? Let's get her!
Hey, Lucchini, you in there?
[LUCCHINI]
Shirley? Are you alone?
Yeah. Wanna let me in?
--[YOSHIKA] Uh...
--[HARTMANN gasps]
I heard what was going on.
Just leave it to me, okay?
Promise?
I promise. Would these
eyes lie to you?
Shirley!
All right, Doctor! Do it!
[sighs] Helping others
is so rewarding.
You think this is how
Miyafuji feels all the time?
You know, we're really lucky
she's here to help us out.
Huh? Yeah? Why?
The home remedy for
a cavity is to pull out
the freakin' tooth,
and that's no easy feat.
Ugh. Scary!
Yep, like I said,
we're lucky. Oh, no!
Ah! What the heck?
[HARTMANN]
What happened?
[YOSHIKA]
I don't understand!
[HARTMANN] Did your
healing spell strengthen
the bacteria in the cavity?
Is that even possible?
I wish that I could just heal
the tooth and call it a day.
I guess we're gonna have to
ask around for more help.
[YOSHIKA gasps]
You should take her
to the hospital.
I think the hospital's
your answer.
I know of a great way
to get rid of a cavity
without having to resort
to drilling the tooth.
[YOSHIKA]
Really?
Uh, that seems a bit extreme.
Not only does it heal
fast, but that's what
a hospital would use, too.
If you say so.
I do!
Hold it right there!
Welcome back. How did it go?
Well, I gathered a bunch
of stuff that's supposed
to help with toothaches.
She consulted all
the wrong people.
What kind of backwoods
treatments did they recommend?
Try this. Crushed dried plums.
Which are good for
treating pain.
[LUCCHINI]
Ew, gross, it's too sour!
Okay, then let's
try grated garlic.
[LUCCHINI]
Ew, gross, it's too stinky!
Resin-flavored candy?
[LUCCHINI] Ew, gross,
stinky and sour and nasty!
[YOSHIKA]
Glance.
Don't lose your conscience!
Hello, everyone!
[YOSHIKA]
Oh. Hi, Lynne.
I did some research
and found a way
to get rid of
cavities instantly!
[YOSHIKA]
What is it?
First, you tie some string
around a door handle.
Then, you tie the other end
around the decaying tooth.
Lastly, you slam the door
really hard and, apparently,
the tooth will pop right out.
What?
If you go to the hospital,
they'll take it out, as well.
But if we do it here,
where there's someone
who can do healing magic,
it'll hurt less
and heal faster, so,
I think it's our best bet.
Yeah, that's a
really good point.
Miyafuji!
[YOSHIKA] Here I come,
Lucchini. Open wide!
Go! Run for your life!
[screams]
Are you okay?
Ah! The tooth!
Ow! My face hurts!
[HARTMANN] Hey, look! It was
the tooth with the cavity!
[YOSHIKA]
Hang on.
There's a new tooth
where the old one was!
[HARTMANN]
It wasn't a cavity, then?
[SHIRLEY]
A baby tooth?
Hooray! New tooth!
That was no cavity.
There was just a new
tooth coming in.
My girl. Growing up so fast!
Good, now, let's do everything
we can to make sure
nobody here gets any
cavities, okay, Yoshika?
Yeah. You got it. No cavities.
What are these here for?
[SANYA] It's sure is relaxing
in this tiny basket.
[MICHIKO]
Hello, everyone!
Time for Michiko Yamakawa's
Strike Witches Classroom!
The subject of today's lesson
is Francesca Lucchini!
She's an ace witch from
the Romanga Air Force,
and the youngest witch
in the 501st.
Her abilities were identified
when she was just
ten years old, and that's
when she joined the military!
She's what you might
call a prodigy!
Because she's super cute,
she's sort of become
the group's mascot.
And all the other
witches think of her
as their goofy little sister.
But, when the battle begins,
she shows no fear,
and she'll never back
down from any Neuroi!
She's so courageous!
Her inherent abilities
allow her to manipulate
light and heat, and she can use
multiple layers of shields.
Her attacks have a power
you would never believe
could come from someone
so young and tiny,
and that power has led her
to countless victories!
They say she's far more
courteous and caring
than her age would suggest,
and she has a reputation
for being quiet and studious!
I can't believe
Yoshika gets to work
with such amazing people!
She's amazing!
[MICHIKO]
Me, again, Michiko Yamakawa!
February is Setsubun
season in Fuso.
I wonder if Yoshika
and her friends
are gonna be throwing beans!
Next time: "501st, get
ready for Setsubun?"
You've never seen witches
like these before!