It's been forever since
we've done day training.
Yeah, it's almost
weird to see you two
wearing your Striker Units.
[SHIRLEY]
What?
[YOSHIKA]
Hey, guys, I'm ready to train!
Miyafuji, you're late--
Uh, sorry.
[yelps] These two have
finally corrupted you
with their influence!
[SHIRLEY, HARTMANN]
How dare you!
We had nothing to do with this.
So, why can't you use
your Striker Unit?
I wish I could say,
but I don't know!
What I do know is that,
every time I've put on
my unit lately, it's
felt a little tight.
[BOTH]
I see.
[YOSHIKA]
And I have to work really hard
just to get off the ground!
[HARTMANN, SHIRLEY]
Could it be?
Could it be what?
Tell me what you think,
so I can fix it!
[SHIRLEY, HARTMANN]
You've gained weight?
I'll tell you more if you
promise not to get mad.
Okay.
Well, uh. You're way
more imposing lately.
[YOSHIKA]
Huh?
So, are ya thirsty?
You want a milkshake?
I know how much you love 'em!
Stop it! I'm not getting fat!
I eat exactly what
everyone else does!
[SHIRLEY]
You always say it's wasteful
not to clean your plate,
and you finish
everybody's leftovers!
You can't help it--
after all, you're the
mom of the 501st!
Oh, I get it.
It's partially our fault,
since we can never finish
all the food that you
give us. We're sorry.
Oh, no.
Hold the phone.
As her honorary big sister,
sometimes I help her
finish the leftovers.
Will that make me
gain weight, too?
Good job, Aunt Barkhorn,
you figured something out
by yourself for once!
Any issues besides
the flying thing?
No, I actually feel
better than ever.
Well, that's
something, at least.
Now heal Shirley and
she'll take a look
at your Striker Unit.
Sure, I'll help ya.
So, where's your unit?
Well, you see, uh.
Sakamoto said the best way
to fix my Striker Unit
was to just punch it repeatedly.
So, I did that, and
now it's even worse.
[SHIRLEY groans]
It could also be mental,
like a psychological
block or something.
Yeah, maybe she's suffering
from Spring Fever.
Master of all things
Spring Fever.
Bestow us with your wisdom!
Too lazy!
A true master.
Ridiculous.
Oh, yeah?
Spring Fever is a
well-documented phenomenon,
but you don't believe?
Don't make assumptions
about me. I suffer, too!
I've even allotted extra time
this month for slacking off!
Wow. A true master.
In any case.
We'll figure out a solution
to your Striker Unit problem,
don't worry.
For now, let's focus on how
to get you to the battlefield.
Piggyback! Hop on, Miyafuji!
That's a negative!
Carry me in your arms!
[SHIRLEY] Lately she treats me
like I'm just a pair of boobs,
but I have a heart under here!
[YOSHIKA]
Let's go!
I wanna fly 60 miles per hour,
the speed of dreams!
[HARTMANN]
Jerks.
[BARKHORN] At this point,
there's nothing we can say
to get through to her.
The 501st has an
image to uphold!
You have to consider how
others might perceive this.
[HARTMANN]
Hold on, I have an idea.
Shirley, help me out here?
Ta-dah!
[YOSHIKA]
She's hiding under the coat?
[BARKHORN] Well, I guess that's
kind of an improvement.
Oh, wow! Now look!
[BARKHORN yelps]
[HARTMANN]
Hey, Lucchini! Hello!
[screams]
You better stop screwing around!
Come on, you guys.
How hard can it be?
Just carry her around
like this, jeez.
I'm sorry.
Right, I'll focus
on firing my gun.
You try to keep a shield up
around us while we fly.
Okay!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow! Hot!
The cartridges are burning me!
Get them off me, quick!
Sorry.
[YOSHIKA]
No... I'll be okay.
I think Sanya's the
only witch whose weapon
doesn't use cartridges.
I dunno, without
my inherent magic,
she felt heavy, even for me.
But I didn't say that.
[HARTMANN]
I think Sanya can handle it.
She's one of the strongest
witches in the whole 501st.
Okay, then. Let's go see
if she's up for it.
Ah, well, there's one
added complication.
Rawr, rawr!
[BARKHORN]
Come on, Eila, relax!
This is all your fault!
I hold you responsible!
What did you guys do?
To be honest,
I think we both might
be innocent, for once.
I foresaw a future where
you guys were bugging
the crap out of Sanya,
so I warned her,
and now she refuses
to leave her room!
So, like I said,
it's all your fault!
[GROUP]
Uh...
[SHIRLEY]
We can't apologize to her
if she won't let anyone see her.
Well you can't see her,
and that's final!
What do we do?
Guess we'll have to
break out the big guns...
...and use the spare key!
Uh, why do you even have that?
Sanya gave it to me
so I could come hang out
with her any time I want to.
Shut up, you're
stalking her, you liar!
Sorry to bug you
on your day off!
No. I said you could come
hang out any time you want.
[EILA]
Why? Why would you say that?
'Cause she's my friend?
[YOSHIKA] Dang. That had to
feel like a punch to the gut.
I figured you wouldn't
need your own key
to my room, since
you and I spend
all of our time
together, anyway.
Oh, well, that makes sense!
[YOSHIKA] I dunno, sounds
like a lame excuse to me.
So, we're hoping
you guys could do
a combination attack thingy
until Miyafuji can lose weight.
Oh. Miyafuji, I've
been looking for you.
We figured out the real reason
you haven't been able to fly.
Huh?
As you've matured
and gotten stronger,
your magic improved so much
that your Striker Unit
just couldn't keep up anymore.
Wait. Then it's not
because I'm too plump?
Why would that prevent
you from flying?
It's because of all the combat
experience you've gained.
It is?
Yeah, look around.
You've been using
your healing magic
--every day since you got here.
--[YOSHIKA gasps]
Hey! Wow! That's great!
Ha! I guess you have
us to thank, huh?
I knew all along it wasn't
because you got fat.
[sighs] All that fuss today
ended up being for nothing.
I wouldn't say for nothing.
We did learn that we
need a contingency plan
for when the Striker
Units break down.
Yeah, and I suppose I learned
a lot about myself, too!
[HARTMANN]
You did?
Oh, yes. Valuable stuff.
I discovered that you think
I've been getting
a lot more imposing.
And I learned I shouldn't
be eating all your leftovers.
From now on, you'll
be cleaning your plates!
[YOSHIKA] Lucchini's
inherent magic is called.
"Sunlight Strike!" She
turns her magical energy
into heat energy,
which really comes in handy
on cold winter days!
Good morning, everyone!
It sure is a chilly one, huh?
Yeah. It's rare to
get a cold snap
so late in the season.
Gah! She overheated!
Miyafuji! You better
come heal her, quick!
[YOSHIKA]
Put her outside.
Hey, do you think we
could use the fireplace?
You should be more
like the Major.
She's been outside
training in the cold
since the sun came up today.
Now, that's what I
call a real soldier.
Take a page from her book.
Hey. Trudy, check it out.
What is it?
[SAKAMOTO laughing]
Miyafuji, explain.
There's this winter
tradition in Fuso
where you rub yourself
down with a towel.
It's for health
reasons, supposedly.
Major! Trudy wants
a word with you!
No, I do not!
I get it, it's cold!
You can use the fireplace!
[YOSHIKA]
She got spooked.
What are you doing
with that poker?
Trying to see if the
chimney is clear enough
to ventilate smoke.
It needs to be cleaned
before we can start a fire.
Next step, firewood.
We'll go chop some.
You two stay in here and get
going cleaning the chimney.
Don't worry, you
can count on us!
We'll get it clean!
I wonder what
happened to the axe.
Sakamoto's right outside.
I'm sure she would
lend us her katana.
Thank you, Miyafuji.
Sure! I'll be right back.
Ah, great, there
she is. Hey, Sakamo--!
There could be men
on this base, too.
What in the world
were you thinking?
Yeah, she's right!
It may be cold,
but that doesn't mean
people aren't gonna be around!
I mean, everybody
in Fuso does it
as a way to stay healthy.
Everyone?
[YOSHIKA] Uh. I think I'd
better keep out of this.
Miyafuji! I know you're there.
Don't hide. Show yourself.
[yelps]
You better tell me what
you're doing out here,
and it better be
something wholesome.
[PERRINE] You saw that
the major was naked
and you seized the opportunity
to ogle her bits!
No it's, um...
She understands.
This may seem odd to you
Puritans, but it's normal.
Maybe it is.
Sorry for judging you.
Now show them how
it's done, Miyafuji.
[YOSHIKA] Sorry! Can't
right now! Gotta go!
[SAKAMOTO]
Huh?
You lied, it isn't normal!
How could you?
Welcome back.
Jeez, it's a veritable
warzone out there.
We'd better stay indoors
just to be safe.
Okay.
[YOSHIKA] I feel sorry for
the girls on night patrol.
They're gonna be
freezing tonight!
Well, we'd better make sure
we can get a fire going, then.
Hang on. The wood's
already chopped,
so I'm guessing you
found the axe.
Did not.
[YOSHIKA]
Barkhorn's a beast--
it's a miracle
Hartmann's still alive.
You're good with that thing.
You been practicing?
No, but I used to have
to do a similar chore
back at home.
Lighting a fire for the bath?
No, killing chickens.
Huh?
Okay, that's probably
enough for right now.
This will make things
a lot more pleasant.
[SHIRLEY]
C'mon! Clean! Hurry up!
They'll be back soon!
Inherent magic: "Acceleration!"
[HARTMANN] Wax on! Wax off!
Wax on! Wax off!
No! I promise,
it's not how it looks!
Yeah! Some snow
got into the room!
It's fresh powder! So beautiful?
We thought it'd be faster to use
our Striker Units to
clean the chimney,
but all it did was blow soot
all over the room, our bad.
It was an honest mistake.
Barkhorn, no!
Using magic for
violence is wrong!
Better use this poker instead.
Good call!
[BOTH] Her creepy smile
is like a suspense mystery!
You're the culprit!
[MICHIKO]
Hello, everyone!
It's time for Michiko Yamakawa's
Strike Witches classroom!
Today, we'll be
learning all about
Sanya Vladimirovn Litvyak.
Sanya originally
comes from Orussia!
And before joining the military,
she was busy studying
music in Vienna.
That's in Ostmark!
She's very graceful,
and shier than most
of the other witches.
She has an ethereal,
delicate beauty, like a flower.
So, the others
call her "Lilija,"
which means "the white lily."
But, just like the
other Strike Witches,
she's strong and
fierce in battle.
She carries a huge
Fliegerhammer rocket launcher,
and never fails to fight
courageously against the Neuroi.
No lesson about Sanya
would be complete
without a discussion of
her incredible abilities
as a night witch.
While on night patrol,
she can use her magic
to guard the entire base
and surrounding area.
Just like her world-famous
radio broadcast,
her patrolling skills
are one of the main things
people think of when
they hear the term,
"Strike Witches!"
My best friend gets to work
with an incredible witch!
Yoshika's amazing!
[MICHIKO]
Me again, Michiko Yamakawa!
Yoshika tells me that summertime
in Europe gets really hot!
I wonder how the members
of the 501st cool off!
Next time: "501st,
Are You Feeling the Heat?"
You've never seen witches
like these before!