I'll master Shin Reppuzan,
a fighting style
even stronger than
regular Reppuzan.
Reppuzan!
[SHIRLEY screams]
[LUCCHINI screams]
Shirley!
[BARKHORN] You were developing
the Shin Reppuzan,
and there was, in your own
words, "an accident"?
[SAKAMOTO]
Yes.
If I could just master
it, then no Neuroi
would ever match me. So...
I'm worried about Shirley:
she went kinda bald
when the shockwave hit her
and now her head's shiny.
I think healing magic can
fix it, but I'm concerned
that it can't, and she'll
have to live her life
as a bald woman.
It's happened to me
before, too, Shirley,
so don't fret. Okay,
that's a lie, but still.
Miyafuji.
Please, do something--
heal her hair! Quick!
I'm on it!
[SHIRLEY]
Oh, thank you, Miyafuji!
[YOSHIKA]
Yeah, you're welcome.
Sorry, I know you're tired,
but there's somebody else
we need you to heal.
Wha--? Don't tell me more
people were badly injured!
Well, no, not exactly: Trudy
pulled an abdominal muscle
laughing too hard.
Miyafuji, if you wouldn't mind,
I'd like your help
with something, too.
Dare I ask?
I need freshly spilled blood
to complete the ritual.
[YOSHIKA]
Mm?
Sorry, I didn't quite
catch that, come again?
I said, I need
freshly spilled blood!
I would blame this on
the language barrier,
but the major and I speak
the same native tongue.
[SAKAMOTO] I need to make
a katana that can handle
the Shin Reppuzan,
and I've heard that one
can use fresh blood to
strengthen a katana blade.
[YOSHIKA]
Heard where?
I don't have any
blood lying around.
Maybe I wasn't
being clear enough.
I'm planning to
use my own blood.
I'll just need you to heal me.
[YOSHIKA] Why didn't you say it
like that from the beginning?
The time has come at last.
[MINNA] The Allies are launching
an attack on a Neuroi nest.
They're not using witches.
Instead, they'll turn
the battleship Yamato
into an artificial Neuroi, and
then launch a full-scale attack
with the rest of the fleet.
This battle will decide
humanity's fate.
I've got big news, witches!
What the hell is going on here?
You've got the wrong idea!
[SAKAMOTO sighs] All right.
Let's get back to work.
--Here goes!
--[YOSHIKA] Stop! Jeez!
What's wrong? I wanna
get this done.
Do you have to
cut your stomach?
Can't you pierce your skin
somewhere that isn't as risky?
Don't worry. It's just the tip!
I won't stick it in all the way.
No offense, Major, but
you're way too clumsy
to pull that off, okay?
You're just gonna get too
excited and lose control
and stick it all the way in!
Why don't you
trust me, Miyafuji?
Don't do this.
[SAKAMOTO sighs]
What's your problem, guys?
You mean you really
don't trust me
to pull off a stunt like this?
Also, why are your
faces all red?
They're naughty girls
with dirty minds
and they heard you and Miyafuji
talking about "sticking it in."
You might have to
spell it out for me.
[LYNNE chuckles]
Forget it, Major,
just promise me
you'll never change.
I still don't get it,
but I assure you
I'll always be myself.
Medics, go find
some fresh blood
so we can get this over with!
And that's an order, you hear?
[BOTH]
Huh?!
[HARTMANN]
What do we do?
I'll let you know
when I have an idea.
Ah! Wow, Medics,
I am truly impressed!
Now, time to make the blade!
If you're about to do
that Reppuzan crap again,
please aim it away from all
the people and buildings!
[MINNA] We've already
got to rebuild the base,
so why don't you take this
to some remote location
where you won't blow things up?
[SAKAMOTO gasps] What's the
whole Allied fleet doing here?
[MINNA] Huh, that's an
excellent question.
Well, you might as well
ask them to drop you off
at one of those little
desert islands.
She gets a vacation? No fair!
We all deserve
to go to the beach!
This is the furthest thing
from a vacation, but sure.
Oh, fine. You can all
go get some R and R.
Minna!
Really?
[MINNA] It's not like
we can train or do chores
with the base like this, anyway.
[YOSHIKA]
Mm-hm.
You don't think getting a lift
from a battleship
is against the rules?
I requested it as a special
mission and was approved,
no questions asked.
You still haven't said
why they're even here.
I vaguely remember
getting a call about it.
But all the details seem
to have slipped my mind,
so I guess it couldn't
have been important.
It just dawned on me.
There's no way this is gonna
be a restful getaway, is there?
It all feels like a setup
to make sure no one
interferes with
repairs on the base.
But, it's an officially
approved vacation--
we might as well
take advantage of it.
[SOLDIER 12A] They call the
final battle a vacation?
[SOLDIER 12B] No, look at Major
Sakamoto's funeral kimono!
[SOLDIER 12A] She's prepared
to sacrifice herself in battle!
Such courage!
[SOLDIER 12B] The witches are
prepared to give their lives!
Sakamoto, it's a bit
early for this.
Don't spoil her excitement.
[SAKAMOTO]
That island will do nicely!
All right, 501st,
follow my lead!
Please keep a safe
distance from the island.
The last thing you want is
to get caught in this blast.
[SOLDIERS]
Yes! We'll stay away!
Everyone, salute the 501st
and pray for their victory!
[BARKHORN] What did you
tell those guys, Minna?
[SOLDIER 12A] That's it!
I've spotted the Neuroi nest!
[SOLDIER 12B]
Let the battle begin!
This fight determines
the fate of humanity!
Vacation time!
The sweet smell of freedom!
Can you at least
carry your own bags?
Good, I see the perfect spot
for making my katana.
[YOSHIKA]
Good luck with all that.
Now, time to enjoy
a tropical holiday!
Heck yeah, time to do all
the awesome vacation things!
[LUCCHINI] Hm. Isn't this
what we always do?
[HARTMANN]
Hey, Miyafuji.
Do you think the
commander just wanted
to get us out of her hair?
Do you really wanna know?
We need to figure out
what to do for lunch.
Way ahead of you--I brought
enough fish for everyone!
Okay, but why did you drain
their blood in advance?
Hang on. That's it?
You're not gonna skin them?
Your people eat grapes
with the skin on
all the time, don't they?
Finally done! Ha!
I call this one the Reppuu-maru!
[SHIRLEY]
Its energy is incredible.
[SAKAMOTO] At last, I've all but
mastered the Shin Reppuzan!
[HARTMANN, YOSHIKA] I can't
believe the fish blood worked.
[SAKAMOTO] Time to get
masterin'! Reppuzan!
[BARKHORN] She's so excited.
Like a kid with a new toy.
[SAKAMOTO]
Reppuzan!
Sakamoto. I think
you mastered it!
It's not me! The
katana's taken over!
[gasps] Was it the seafood?
Will the same thing
happen with the knife
I used to cook the fish?
It didn't happen with the
chickens the other day.
[SOLDIER 12A] Oh, no! A bunch
of stuff happened offscreen,
and now the Yamato 's been
absorbed by the Neuroi!
[SOLDIER 12B] Could this be the
end of the human race itself?
[SOLDIERS]
What's this?
Will Major Sakamoto's
Reppuzan save the day?
[SOLDIER 12A]
Ha, ha! The Neuroi nest!
[SOLDIER 12B] Thank goodness!
Europe is free at last!
She's under the
katana's control--
be careful where you grab her!
Miyafuji, please
don't grab me there!
What do we do with it?
All we can do is keep firing
till my magic runs out.
[BARKHORN] I'm terrified of
what's happening beyond
the horizon, so I'm gonna
suggest we just ignore it.
Miyafuji, you have
to use your magic
to block the major!
Do it to protect your friends!
Huh?!
[SAKAMOTO] I'm sorry,
Miyafuji--here goes!
[yells] I won't let
my dinner win!
[BARKHORN, HARTMANN, LUCCHINI,
SAKAMOTO, SHIRLEY] Her dinner?
Miyafuji, you didn't
really have to block
all the katana's attacks
until its magic ran out.
It was a fight I had to see
through to the bitter end,
for the good of the human race.
Does this mean I
can't fight anymore?
I can no longer protect anyone?
[HARTMANN] She's collapsing
under the weight of her guilt!
No, my magical energy
may be depleted,
but I can still fight
the Neuroi in other ways!
[SOLDIER 12A]
Amazing!
[SOLDIER 12B]
Why can't I stop crying?
[MINNA]
Hey! Big news, witches!
The Neuroi nest
has been destroyed!
Europe is free at last!
[SAKAMOTO]
Wait, why does it say I did it?
I don't remember that!
What?
The Shin Reppuzan struck
right to the nest's core?
The one that I fired
from on the island?
Yeah, seems like that's
what it says here.
You're so amazing, Major!
Now, I have some
not-so-great news.
The 501st will have to
be split up temporarily.
[ALL]
Huh?!
It's only for a short time.
The Neuroi are gone now,
and to top it off,
we don't even have a place
to live at the moment.
I hadn't thought about that.
But this is just so sudden!
The military can't
realistically concentrate
all its ace witches here.
It's a non-functional base.
But we never actually did
anything when it functioned!
Do you guys have any idea where
you're gonna go when
you leave the base?
We're still soldiers,
so we'll probably
just get sent back
to our old units.
What about you, Miyafuji?
I'm going back home to Fuso
so I can study medicine.
If anything happens,
you call me!
I'll save you, even if it
means abandoning my post!
Oh, sweet Barkhorn!
And to think she used to be
such a stickler for the rules.
Yes, it's so very moving!
I dunno, to me, she just
sounds like a stalker.
Where will you go?
I'm gonna go to Suomus
with Sanya to help her
look for her missing parents.
I'm gonna work
to rebuild Gallia,
now that it's finally
free from the Neuroi!
I'm gonna tag along and
assist the reconstruction!
The Neuroi are persistent,
so we're gonna
work to stay prepared for
their inevitable return.
I'm close to everyone else,
so not much is gonna change.
[BARKHORN] There's gonna
be one less person around
to help keep these
lunatics in check?
[SHIRLEY] This crazed maniac
will be unleashed upon us
and we'll have no healer
to counteract the damage?
It may only be temporary,
but after everything we've
been through together,
we'd better make
sure that we leave
this base on good terms.
Yes, well said.
Ya better start cleaning, then.
Hold on!
What if we preserve
this room as is
and turn it into a 501st Museum!
In 100 years, people
will know how we lived!
[HARTMANN screams]
Miyafuji. I hope you won't
feel too out of place
when you get to Fuso.
Cooking and cleaning are
my chores at home, too,
so it won't be that
big of a change.
Oh, wait. My parents run
a clinic in my hometown,
and we have tons
of patients every day,
so I'll be studying medicine,
treating patients...
I might even feel useful
around there for once!
[BARKHORN] But, you're
gonna came back, though,
right, Miyafuji?
[SHIRLEY]
Please, Miyafuji! Come back!
[HARTMANN]
Yeah!
[YOSHIKA] And so, the
501st Joint Fighter Wing
was dissolved.
[MICHIKO]
Hello, everyone!
It's that time again:
for Michiko Yamakawa's
Strike Witches Classroom!
Since this is our last
class, I'd like to take
this opportunity to teach you
about a very special witch!
Guess who it is!
None other than my best friend,
the one and only
Yoshika Miyafuji!
Her father is Doctor
Miyafuji, and he was
one of the people who
developed the Striker Unit!
As his daughter,
Yoshika has always
had incredible
magical potential.
Sakamoto recognized her talent
and recruited her to the 501st.
I was so excited for
Yoshika when I heard!
She quickly put her
talents to work
and became a crucial
member of the squadron!
And solidified her place
on the team in no time!
Her inherent magic comes
in the form of "healing."
It gives her the ability
to heal any wound,
no matter how bad it might be!
Yoshika has helped me
countless times
when I've been hurt.
She's the type of person
who will do anything
in order to help others.
As you might recall from
earlier, Yoshika sacrificed
all of her magic
to defeat an army
of attacking Neuroi
and destroy their nest!
She's a veritable hero!
I'm so proud of all she's done!
It's an honor to call her
my best friend! She's amazing!