[HARTMANN] Hello, everyone!
It's me, Hartmann!
During the day, I'm sure I look
like the laziest person ever.
But I'm just tired from studying
in secret to be a doctor!
Lately, I've been practicing on
this mannequin that
I bought with my paycheck.
He's helping me learn
how to give exams!
That's why I haven't been
getting enough sleep or cleaning
as much as I probably should,
but it's also just who I am!
Hey, it's noon! Get up, now!
[HARTMANN groans]
[yells]
[BARKHORN groans]
Jeez! Can't you knock?
Get outta here!
Uh. Sure.
[BARKHORN] Should I call
the Military Police?
No, maybe I'm wrong.
Who knows what I saw?
Maybe it wasn't
at all what I thought.
You know...
I haven't seen Eila all day,
and she's not on night patrol.
Really? Then I suppose
Sanya will have to do it alone.
[BARKHORN] Could Hartmann
have murdered Eila?
I have to call the cops!
No, Eila wouldn't want a family
member to get arrested.
Um, Barkhorn?
[BARKHORN] Well. I guess I'll
just have to break the rules.
Hartmann.
Show me where you hid the body,
and I'll just take care of it.
Aww, so you did see it, then?
I tried to be discreet.
Oh, dummy lost an arm.
[BARKHORN] Hide that!
What if somebody sees it?!
What? You saw. So?
I'm the only one
who knows right now.
If we hurry and get rid
of it, this stops here.
Huh? I need it! How else
am I supposed to study?
You murdered Eila
just so you could study?!
[HARTMANN]
Huh?
[BARKHORN] Sorry, I didn't
realize it was only a mannequin.
It's fine. I'm used to it.
Miyafuji might
not always be here,
so I want to learn to heal.
Good point.
It's important to have a way
to treat people
without using magic.
Should I start
studying medicine, as well?
Maybe I should teach
a class on emergency healing!
Can I take part in it?
Yeah, of course!
Should I bring that mannequin
to be my visual aide?
Okay, good. Hold 'em steady.
Right!
Oh, the bag seems
to be a little too small.
It should fit
if we just stuff it in.
[BOTH]
Heave ho!
What's the matter, Trudy?
It's probably a shocking scene
for a strict rule-follower
like her to stumble upon.
Eila. There you are.
We wondered where you went.
Well, I'm here!
Let's save lives!
If just for Sanya's sake!
How did you find out?
By looking into
the future, naturally--
Duh, how else?
If you knew this was coming,
then why didn't you tell me?!
[EILA chuckles]
You'll never land one on me.
Don't mess with medicine!
I am Coach Hartmann.
Miyafuji's my helper.
All right, time to get
this class started.
[EILA, PERRINE, BARKHORN]
Miyafuji's the helper?
The first step is to
bring the injured soldier
to the rear lines.
In Fuso, this is called
"changing course."
Fuso won't even
call it a retreat
when that's literally
what it is.
It's not a retreat! Is it?
Okay, kids. Now let's practice
getting the soldier on a
stretcher and calling a doctor!
Negative!
You don't understand.
What we really need more than
anything right now is to learn
how to come to the major's
aid when she's in trouble.
Yeah, we want
to be able to come to
the heroine's rescue
when she's in danger!
Sic 'em, Trudy!
All right. First,
you check to see
if they're conscious.
Then, you make sure
they're breathing.
If they're not, you have
to clear their airway
and perform CPR.
Eila, why don't you go first?
Now, go ahead and
blow gently into the mouth.
[EILA] She wants me to waste
my first kiss on a dummy?
No way!
You better do it.
If you're not gonna
take this seriously,
then let me.
[PERRINE] I have to waste
my first kiss on this thing?
No way!
Why did you even come here?
People's lives are at stake,
stop screwing around!
It's hard to take
this seriously with
that thing's goofy
face staring at you.
Yes, you make
an excellent point, Eila.
[BARKHORN]
You rang, boss?
We'd retain the
knowledge a whole lot better
if the mannequin had a more
likeable face, you know?
That does make sense.
No, it doesn't!
[BARKHORN]
Okay, let's mold some faces!
[PERRINE]
Yes! In the name of medicine!
[EILA] Right! Get ready
to save some lives, ladies!
They seem to be
taking this seriously now,
but it's all an illusion.
I brought some modeling clay
and candles we can
use to make the faces.
Do you think this
will be enough?
Chris looks
a bit more like this.
I'm off by a whole millimeter!
Miyafuji, the candle, stat!
Okay, fine.
Hey Miyafuji, I'm sorry.
[YOSHIKA]
You need candles, too?
Huh-- Ahh!!
I'm sorry, Chris.
Forgive your sister for
being such a clumsy jerk.
I mean, maybe she'd
be flattered by your sacrifice?
Shouldn't we be teaching them
not to discriminate when
trying to save people's lives?
If it'll make them care,
I'm willing to let it slide.
What other things are we
going to teach them?
I'm planning a lesson
on cardiac massage.
Oh, yes, very important.
Should we get Shirley
and Lynne to come help
by acting as patients, then?
Nope, that's it.
Go stand over there
with the other pervs.
Wait, why?!
I'm just trying to keep
everybody safe and healthy!
It's a masterpiece!
Wow, that's great!
Oh, no. Looks like
you're having a hard time.
[EILA whimpers, screams]
Eila! Where are
you taking that clay?
[YOSHIKA]
What happened to you?
[EILA chuckles]
Oh, I had a fantastic idea.
I poured hot wax into this
mold and let it harden.
Behold! A Sanya mask!
Good god, what have you done?
I just smashed
the clay onto Sanya's face
to create the mold.
A living death mask?
It may be frowned upon,
but I'd do anything for Sanya!
Maybe I love her more
than you love yours.
[PERRINE whimpers]
Wanna bet I'm the one
who gets punished for this?
Well, you're supposed
to be in charge.
Whatever, let's just
get back to it.
All right, guess I'll start.
[YOSHIKA] So, you decided to
use the original face after all?
Yes, of course I did.
It's wrong to discriminate based
on the way someone looks!
Are you kidding me?
Miyafuji, wouldja get
the torso for me?
Sure, here you go!
How could you?!
Who's next?
All right Eila, are you ready?
Hundred percent! See?
[HARTMANN] Why is it wearing
Sanya's actual clothes?
I put them on it!
That is impressive!
I don't like the fact that its
proportions are inaccurate.
Looking back, I should
have taken more clay
and gotten a mold
of her whole body.
Sanya! Please, wake up now!
What is happening?
[SANYA (EILA)]
Eila, you came to save me.
I promise I will!
I'll save you with CPR!
Mmm...
What the heck? Eila...
I'm teaching a class
on emergency medicine,
but I should have
set way stricter rules
for the practice dummies.
I'm really sorry, Sanya.
I can write an apology
letter if you'd like.
Ahh, what happened
to your clothes, Sanya?
You know there are male soldiers
on this base, too, right?
So. Why'd you
decide to take this course?
I thought it'd come
in handy someday
when we search for your parents.
[sighs]
I can't stay mad at you.
Oh, sweet, Sanya!
Ugh, are you done
with your little act yet?
It's my turn to
practice now, thanks.
I shall also be rehearsing
a little improvised scene that
might someday come to pass.
Remember, no small parts,
only small actors,
so please take this seriously.
I need you to dig deep, commit,
and play your intentions, okay?
Well, since you
seem so gung-ho about
your "scene," I guess I'll help.
Good, remember to stay
in character, no matter what!
Okay, in the first beat,
we witness the major
getting attacked.
What are you guys
doing over here?
Oh, Lynne, what perfect timing.
Now, shoot this.
[screams]
Ugh, here we go.
[PERRINE sobs]
Major?
[SAKAMOTO]
Hmm? Someone call me?
[PERRINE]
The major! This is terrible!
It must have been
a Neuroi attack!
Wait, what happened?
I'll begin CPR!
Hate to tell ya,
but it's too late.
Yeah, there's a big hole
where her heart was.
--[PERRINE sobs] Miyafuji, help!
--No. Please, no...
Is that me...?
Eila, how did
this future happen?
Hey... You guys...
Tragic. If only I'd been
able to foresee this.
[PERRINE sobs]
[SAKAMOTO]
I see. It all makes sense.
I've died and become a ghost.
Farewell. Nice knowing you.
[MINNA gulps]
What's gotten into you, Mio?
So, what do we do
with these things now?
Set 'em on fire?
No, we can't burn them!
I'll just take them
back to my room.
[screams]
Should we destroy
the major's dummy, too?
[PERRINE]
No, please don't!
Um, listen...
The Major won't have a good
impression of you anymore.
And people would freak out
seeing them in the trash,
so we should just bury them.
Yes, you make a good point.
Mio, don't be ridiculous.
You are not a ghost,
you're still alive.
No. I saw the others
mourning over my dead body.
There you guys are.
What are you doing out here
in the woods with a shovel?
[MINNA screams]
Mio!
[EILA, BARKHORN]
We're busted.
Uh, Minna! What happened was--
[BOTH] Hartmann
put us up to the whole thing.
--[MINNA sobs]
--But...
[YOSHIKA] I may be ugly,
but I deserve to live!
[MICHIKO]
Hello, everyone!
It's time for Michiko Yamakawa's
Strike Witches Classroom!
Today's lesson is all
about a very special witch:
Perrine Clostermann.
[MICHIKO] She's an awesome
ace witch who hails from
the Republic of Gallia!
And get this: she's a member
of the Clostermann family,
the Lords of the
Chartreux Province!
In other words, Perrine
is a real-life aristocrat!
Not only does
she comport herself like
an elegant, distinguished, noble
lady, but she has powerful
combat abilities that set
her apart from the rest.
She was recognized for
them even in her time living
in the Free Gallia Republic!
She was famous,
and her nickname was
"Blue Premier," or
"Blue Number One!"
So, when the 501st was
initially being formed,
Major Sakamoto went to her
directly and personally invited
her to join the team!
Her inherent magic
is called, "Tonnerre,"
or "Thunder." It allows her
to emit all her magic energy
at once, creating
a powerful electric blast!
It's incredible to see!
But it takes time to
recharge before she can
use it again, so she
has to be very selective
and only bring it out
when it's necessary!
Like a true noblewoman,
she has a strong sense of
noblesse oblige at all times.
I can't believe my best
friend gets to work with
such an awesome witch!
Yoshika's amazing!
[MICHIKO] It's me, again,
Michiko Yamakawa.
The Allies have decided
to launch a full-scale attack
on a Neuroi nest!
What fate is in store
for Yoshika and the 501st?
Next time: "501st.
You're Splitting Up?"
You've never seen
witches like these before!