[HARTMANN] Autumn is here,
and these yams are my jam.
[SHIRLEY]
Yeah, I've been imprisoned
by these "Freedom Fries."
Hey, not to be rude...
--...but you're fat.
--[BOTH] No, stop!
We know you're practicing that
new inherent magic ability
called "hurtful words", but it's
s'posed to be for the enemy!
So, you know you've
plumped up, huh?
Uh. You know they call me
"Glamourous Shirley," right?
It's my voluptuous figure.
I've always had a little extra.
I mean, sure,
I've been putting away
Miyafuji's Fuso-style
cooking, but how can I get fat
from eating nutritious
vegetables like potatoes
and rice and tons of beans?
Because you do nothing
but eat and sleep all day long.
I have a child-like body,
so my cute li'l belly sticks
out, no matter what I do.
[BARKHORN]
That's utter nonsense!
Hey, Miyafuji.
Do you have a few moments
for a quick chat?
[YOSHIKA]
Sure, lemme just wrap this up.
I hope you two are ready.
[BOTH squeal]
[BOTH]
Fattening us up to eat?
What the heck is this,
Hansel and Gretel?
Maybe she could just
cut off your excess fat
and then heal you two.
The key isn't eating less.
It's just exercising more.
Does that make sense?
I know! The Major and I
were planning to do
some endurance training today.
You guys wanna work out with us?
Oh, that's right,
why are you guys
doing all that, again?
'Cause autumn is for sports-ing?
[BOTH] Oh! You're in training
for the next Neuroi attack!
You idiots!
Shut up!
We didn't forget, we just
didn't remember, that's all.
Yeah, it's been pretty
quiet around here,
so it slipped our minds.
[BOTH] Right! We hold
the Neuroi in our hearts,
not our brains!
Okay, Mio.
I want you to whip these
little piggies into shape!
Haven't you whipped them enough?
All right, look, maybe
I've gotten a little soft.
But I'll show you I can still
haul ass with the best of 'em.
[GROUP panting]
You have to
stop and rest already?
Gimme a break.
Look, my ladies might not have
the movement that Shirley's do,
but they're mine!
Big juicy melons are all fine
and good, but the best fruits
are the ones grown
with tender love and care.
So, be tender.
Did you hear me?! Tender!
Sit-ups are very
stimulating, aren't they?
Uh, I guess so.
Look, good stamina is important,
don't get me wrong,
but we're on the
front lines, ladies.
I think we'd be way better
served focusing
on combat training.
We've got some of
the top aces in the world
all in one place out here.
For real! Listen--
Why don't we take turns
pretending to be Neuroi
and stage an epic mock battle?
[BOTH panting]
I think we need to work on
our stamina a little more.
Doesn't it feel good to
get your blood pumping
and your lungs working?
[BOTH]
We're dying.
Miyafuji. I'ma let you
in on a little secret, 'kay?
At about 37 miles per hour,
the wind pressure creates
a sensation that's
nearly identical
to the feel of boobies.
And! When we're flying around
in our Striker Units,
we get to feel that pressure
all over our bodies!
You see what I'm
getting at here, right?
No, I'm far too
innocent to see
what you're getting at.
But, for some weird reason,
I really like it!
I'll go get my Striker Unit now!
What'd you tell her?
I promised her there'd be boobs.
There are so many
different types though,
the Neuroi are quite advanced.
Yeah, there are bugs
and battleships,
and some Neuroi that
can even multiply!
They evolve in ways we
humans could never imagine.
I've seen red Neuroi
a few times, too,
not just the black kind.
And some Neuroi
even know how to sing!
I could even picture a
person-shaped Neuroi.
[BOTH] A humanoid Neuroi
who wears red and sings?
You mean... Commander Mi--
That's quite enough.
You're not allowed to insult
your superior officers.
All right, mock battle time!
Come and get me if you
think you can, stupid Neuroi!
You're not gonna
use your Striker Unit?
No way, an ultra-ace
doesn't need any help.
Don't tell me...
No. I definitely did not
lose it in my messy room.
Go clean up your life!
I can't, we're in peak
yam harvesting season.
You're seriously
growing yams in your room?
Is that where those
yam fries came from?
I feel sick.
The last time
we cleaned it for her,
it was like she'd built a shrine
to the god of rotting garbage.
Why did you replace all
that with new garbage?
I don't know why I'm
like this, but I can't help it!
--[gasps]
--[HARTMANN screams]
Why, Lynne, why...?
I'm sorry. I thought
it was her Neuroi role play.
[SHIRLEY, YOSHIKA]
She's terrifying.
[alarm blares]
[MINNA]
Witches! Prepare for battle!
Oh, no. It's been so long.
I'm getting nervous!
What's that sound?
It feels vaguely
familiar somehow.
What? Really?
Judging by the looks
on your faces,
it's the angel of death,
heralding the apocalypse!
Have you gone insane?!
Aww, don't be such an idiot.
We haven't even seen
the four horsemen yet.
It's the Neuroi alarm!
[GIRLS]
There will be boobs.
What's this? Do we
have special plans today?
That's right, you're from Fuso,
of course you wouldn't
know about this stuff.
Shh!
What? Is today some
kind of top-secret holiday?
In a way, yes.
It's trick-or-treating time!
[gasping]
[YOSHIKA]
Uh. Um. What? Why...?
[BOTH]
Commander!
[SHIRLEY]
We bestow this gift upon you!
[LUCCHINI]
Please accept it!
Oh! Is it like New Year's day?
[SAKAMOTO sighs]
Halloween!
The modern version of
All Hallow's Eve,
which was based on the
Celtic festival of Samhain.
That night,
spirits wander freely,
and children dress up
to confuse them.
Kids go around asking for candy,
and if they don't get it,
they can play tricks on people!
Aw, man! Why'd you
let the cat outta the bag?
We had big plans
to play a trick on Yoshika
and give her some culture shock!
You guys have already
given me a shock.
Just now.
All right, fine then.
Guess we gotta find new victims.
Want to help us out?
You can immerse yourself
in new culture!
I think I'll pass.
But if you need to be healed,
you know where to find me.
Don't worry.
Today's sort of like a
pranksters' free-for-all.
You can play all the
tricks you want without
fear of being punished.
Sounds great...
First up, is Eila!
This is Halloween!
A festival for
upstanding young ladies!
--Ahh...
--Right. Watch and learn.
[knocking
What do you want?
I'm trying to take a nap.
Give us all of
your candy, witch!
If you don't, we'll
play tricks on you
that'll scar you for life!
What the heck has
gotten into you two?!
This is so wrong.
What is your problem?!
Can't you see I'm
trying to sleep here?!
You can't sleep!
I'll scream like a banshee!
We won't let you rest
till you appease us!
[screaming]
[SHIRLEY]
We're sorry... It's Halloween...
If you give us candy,
we'll leave you alone...
Ugh. Wait right here.
--[SHIRLEY] Miyafuji...
--[LUCCHINI] Yoshika...
All right.
Now hold out your hands.
[SHRLEY, LUCCHINI whimper]
[SHIRLEY] Waugh! The pumpkin's
growing on my head.
I can't breathe!
Oh, no! I'm sorry!
Shut up! Here you go.
Now will you go away?
-[LUCCHINI, SHIRLEY]
Stingy.
Come on, guys! You've
gotta learn some self-control!
What jerks.
Don't they know I'm trying
to get some sleep before
my night patrol shift?
Halloween, huh?
The only day that
tricks go unpunished.
So, uh, trick or treat, I guess.
Oh, you don't have
any candy, you say?
Well, you know what that means.
Watch and learn.
Those who pretend to be perfect
are often the most devious.
But, still.
On this day, we can't
turn her over to the police.
That's the ironclad
Law of Halloween!
Oh, sorry, proceed, if you wish.
[EILA]
Here, I got you a special gift.
Oh, wow, how sweet!
This is Halloween...?
Is it just, like,
a holiday for criminals?
No, no, we never
trick-or-treat
where we're not welcome.
Oh, you mean we're
gonna skip over Perrine?
Hey, Major Sakamoto
says she wants you
to teach her all
about Halloween!
Both tricks and treats
are welcome today!
I'm honored to teach
you the customs, Major!
Huh? Major?
By "her," I meant Miyafuji.
Hey, That was a dirty trick!
Those treats were for
the major and you stole them!
You're a bunch of monsters!
Them's the brakes,
it's Halloween.
The rules say that
we show no mercy, cupcake.
Good evening.
No, Lynne! Get out! Run away!
[SHIRLEY]
After you, milady.
[LUCCHINI chuckles]
I thought you tricked everybody!
What, it's not like
we have a death wish!
Nobody wants to
get killed over a prank!
Our next target
is the queen of rules!
Get ready, everyone. Here goes!
Ready.
[chuckling]
Hand over the sweet
stuff, Sweet Stuff.
Come in. I'll make you some tea.
It makes sense to be prepared,
in light of the risks.
[SHIRLEY] I'm disappointed
in your willingness
to surrender, Barkhorn.
[LUCCHINI]
Way to ruin all the fun!
[BARKHORN]
Fun, eh? All right, then.
Trick or Treat, girls.
Now gimme some treats, Shirley.
You, too, Lucchini.
[gasping]
Hold on a second, you're 18!
You're totally too old
to be trick-or-treating.
Halloween is for kids!
You should be
ashamed of yourself!
Welp, you heard 'em, Commander.
[screaming]
[ding]
You know, I don't think I saw
Hartmann at all yesterday.
Oh, yeah. I forgot.
She refused to give me candy.
So I had no choice.
[gasps]
No! Hartmann, why?
She's not talking!
Barkhorn, go get help!
What's this?
Wait, where'd she go?
[SAKAMOTO] Gotta get
them before they get you.
[MICHIKO]
Hi, there, everybody!
It's time for Michiko Yamakawa's
Strike Witches classroom!
Today's lesson is all about
Eila Ilmatar Juutilainen!
She's from Suomus,
which is all the way
in Northern Europe.
She's one of their greatest
aces, but not just there!
Eila's one of the very best
in the whole wide world!
And she was the recipient
of their highest honor,
the Mannerheim Cross!
You can't talk
about Eila without
mentioning her inherent ability:
the gift of "Foresight!"
This ability allows
her to see slightly into
the future, which means she
sees Neuroi attacks before
they even happen and
can dodge them better
than most witches can!
Because of that,
Eila's almost never
taken any hits in battle!
She makes it through the most
dangerous missions alive,
and has even been called,
"The Miracle Witch!"
Since she doesn't
need to use a shield,
she's able to conserve
her magical power,
and fight for very
long periods of time.
She's awesome! A true
ultra-super witch, for sure!
Her hobby is doing
tarot card readings!
Because of her ability
to see into the future,
she's a natural at it.
And her readings are
always incredibly accurate!
Yoshika's so amazing.
She gets to work with one of
the world's superstar witches!
To be perfectly honest,
I'm a little bit jealous!
[MICHIKO]
It's me again, Michiko Yamakawa!
Even on the battlefield,
the witches are all
still teenage girls!
Which means they like
to express themselves
through their appearance!
Next time:
"Five-hundred and first.
Time for a Haircut?"
You've never seen witches
like these before!