[YOSHIKA]
It's finally pay day!
Well, Miyafuji, you've done
a fantastic job this month!
Thanks, that's nice
of you to say!
Is this right? It feels
like way too much!
Oh, don't worry about it.
There's a little bonus
in there 'cause
you stopped that Neuroi advance.
[YOSHIKA] Wait, the Neuroi
haven't tried to advance
once in the last month.
Just take it and be proud!
It's a reward for
all your hard work.
But, I haven't done much,
besides help out
with the chores.
Keeping this place in good shape
is an important part of the job.
Everyone here appreciates you.
[YOSHIKA]
Wow, thank you for saying that.
I mean it. There are people here
who never do a darn
thing to help out.
Man work's hard.
I need a vacation.
I just about died from overwork.
In any case,
it's shopping day.
Come into town with us
if you need something.
Let me see.
I have been needing some
stuff for the kitchen,
like utensils and ingredients.
But nothing I could
ever need would
be worth the terror of
being trapped in a car
with Shirley driving
like a maniac.
I understand, but you
might not have a choice.
No one wants to ride with her.
They're all fighting about it.
Time for the "Ride with Shirley"
rock-paper-scissors game!
[YOSHIKA whimpers]
Miyafuji, Barkhorn, you're
coming with me, right?
Yeah, but only if you
promise not to kill us.
Mind if I come
with you guys, too?
--[EILA, HARTMANN yelp]
--[YOSHIKA] Aw, thanks, Lynne!
If we crash, at least
we'll be together!
Aw, it's really
nothing, Yoshika.
--[YOSHIKA whimpering]
--Hey, look alive over there!
I'm sorry.
[SHIRLEY] Right! I'm gonna
set a new record today!
A record?
Wow, they're gone already?
Yeah, they just pulled away.
Do you know who all
ended up going with them?
Miyafuji, Lynne, and
Trudy, as far as I know.
I see. Well, that's not good.
Forgot to ask them to
get something for you?
No, I was just hoping there'd
be more people to cook for.
[HARTMANN, EILA groan]
I'm happy to make us all lunch,
since our chef went out.
[BOTH] No, thanks.
You don't need to bother
yourself with that.
Oh, it's no bother--
you know how I love to cook!
It's been so long since
we had rations for lunch!
You're right! Let's do that,
it'd be just like old times!
Well, if that's what you
guys really wanna do.
I'll make dinner later on!
[HARTMANN, EILA]
Come back, Miyafuji!
[BARKHORN] Did you guys
sustain any injuries?
[YOSHIKA] No, but I regret
every choice I've made
that led me to this point.
[SHIRLEY]
What a sorry bunch of wimps.
I shaved 30 minutes
off the trip
so you'd have more time to shop!
[YOSHIKA] Yeah, and your
cliff jumps and river fording
shaved a few years off my life.
[BARKHORN]
Lunchtime already?
[LYNNE] I heard a really nice
café just opened up near here.
Maybe we should try
their lunch menu.
Wow, you're a
regular local guide!
[SHIRLEY]
So peaceful.
[BARKHORN]
What do you think the others
back at the base
are up to right now?
[SHIRLEY] Probably goofing off
and having fun, as usual.
[EILA] We got through
lunch, but I don't see
any way of surviving dinner.
[HARTMANN]
We have to do something, fast.
Problem is that there's
no one around here
who knows how to cook.
What can we do with these
cards we've been dealt?
Only one choice.
I'll just have to gaze into
the future and figure out
some way to get through this!
My queen!
It must be hard to do
all the cooking yourself,
but I can help!
I know exactly what
you're thinking.
You're concerned because
my flavor palate
is a little more
sophisticated than yours.
Uh, not quite how
I'd put it, but sure.
Rest assured, Miyafuji's
Fuso-style cuisine
has broadened my
culinary horizons!
[HARTMANN, EILA]
Ooh!
Yeah! I've realized,
the stinkier, the better!
[HARTMANN]
No. She's only getting worse.
Oh, don't you worry.
Commander, may I
offer a suggestion?
I'm open to that.
Like you said, the stinkier
the better, right?
Yeah!
[screams] Please! Stop this!
You see, from the smelly cheese
and fermented bean soup,
to the putrid fish
Miyafuji introduced us to,
one thing certainly is true.
For us, "the stinkier
the better."
That might even be our
cardinal rule of cooking!
I like what I'm hearing!
--[HARTMANN] Please save me!
--Miyafuji taught us so well!
I know exactly how to
satisfy our cravings!
Canned Baltic herring is
the stinkiest of all foods!
Good god.
Imagine hot, rotting
garbage in the middle
of a feral cat colony.
But canned herring isn't
all that different
from our rations, is it?
I've got just the thing to
spice it up a little more.
Ammonia!
Neuroi! Take me now!
When you open the can, the
liquid tends to squirt out,
and it's caustic, so be careful.
You didn't even consider
opening it outside?
[EILA]
Uh-oh. The can is so swollen
I can't get the
can opener to work.
That's a sign you should stop!
[MINNA]
Oh, no! The cap on this bottle
won't budge, either.
I'm telling you, it's a sign
from the heavens to give it up!
I know!
Let's get Major Sakamoto
to slice through
these stubborn containers.
Good idea!
She can open both of them
in one fell swoop!
Can you guys hear me?
Were they seriously considering
opening that stuff indoors?
[HARTMANN] I begged them to
at least open it outside!
Calm down now.
I'll talk some sense
into them. So...
You're gonna absolutely
love it, Mio!
Everybody from Fuso goes on
and on about this stuff,
so I'm really eager
to give it a try!
Uh. Okay. I'll
open it, if I must.
Tell them no!
There are some things
that even I can't say.
[MINNA]
Right, Mio, now go for it!
[SAKAMOTO]
Uh, sure.
[HARTMANN]
Best of luck, Major!
Hartmann, is that
really necessary?
[HARTMANN]
You can do it!
Here goes nothing!
Major!
Stay back!
How dare you try to stop me?
Let me go! There's still
time to save her!
[HARTMANN]
It's called, "Decoy Fishing,"
and it's nothing but a trap!
[EILA]
That aroma.
Doesn't it make you
feel so utterly alive?
[MINNA] Yes, and this
will enhance that!
Did we get everything
that was on the list?
[PERRINE] And now, a message
from our sponsors.
Attention, all members
of the 501st.
Major Sakamoto has collapsed!
Please return to the
base immediately!
We don't know how long
we'll be able to hold them off!
Thank you!
This was a friendly message
from Perrine Clostermann.
[ALL yelp]
Why is Perrine taking
out radio ads?
I don't know, but we better
head back to the base, now!
Hurry, jump in!
I'll get us there in no
time! Quickly, let's go!
Why don't we go back
in our Striker Units?
Come on, just trust me.
Everyone, wait.
With the four of us away,
who do you imagine
is trying to cook
for all the girls
back at the base?
I guess we could wait
and head back after dinner.
Yeah, can't fight
on an empty stomach.
I'll take my sweet
time driving us home.
No, Eila, I refuse!
Come on!
[HARTMANN]
Are Sanya and Eila fighting?
Now I guess I've
seen everything.
And Miyafuji is
trying to mediate.
[YOSHIKA] Eila, you have got
to calm down right now!
[HARTMANN gasps]
[HARTMANN]
Wait, what is going on here?
How could this have happened?
I'm filled with dread.
It feels like my whole world
is crashing down around me.
Gulp.
You won't stop them?
All right, guys,
that's enough, it's time.
[SANYA]
That's our cue, Yoshika.
Okay, just give me one minute.
Here, Eila. I made you
some food to eat later.
It'll make you feel better.
Oh, that's what
the knife was for.
So? What were those
two fighting about?
Well, you see...
[HARTMANN, SAKAMOTO]
Eila?
[HARTMANN]
Eila's got a bad cold, huh?
[SAKAMOTO] Yeah, she's sick,
but she's still insisting
on going out on patrol
duty with Sanya.
I see.
So, how do we help her feel
well enough to do that?
Oh, that's right, you
wanted to be a doctor.
First, we've gotta
bring her fever down.
Major, help me get
her clothes off.
Because they're
drenched with sweat?
We have to strip her naked
and then toss her outside.
Wait! Stop it!
[EILA]
A wet towel.
It feels so cool and refreshing.
Who's that? Oh. Sanya?
[ELIA screams]
Feeling better, right?
Like you had the most
wonderful, healing dream?
[EILA] I thought I had
passed on to the other side!
Hey, Major? Is Sanya
still mad at me?
She is.
Do you wanna know the secret
to getting back
in her good graces?
Yeah! Yeah!
You know you're in
the wrong, don't you?
That's good. It means
you've already cleared
the most difficult hurdle
in the whole process.
Oh?
Next is Ghandi-esque
nonviolence.
You just have to let Sanya
punch you right in the face,
then run to Miyafuji
and ask her to heal you.
[BARKHORN]
Huh?!
[EILA] That's a little too
enlightened of a strategy
for my taste.
Well, watching you two,
I gained some insight.
I think you should be
a little more open
with one another about
how you feel, you know?
I'm naturally
expressive. Listen--
No, I will not.
There's no need to overthink it.
You two fought because
you care too much.
One time, Minna
pointed a gun at me
and told me it was
for my own good,
now look at us:
I didn't hold a grudge
or take it personally.
[EILA]
Too enlightened for me!
[HARTMANN]
She's asleep.
[SAKAMOTO] Good. A little rest
and she'll be right as rain.
Should we leave these,
in case she gets lonely?
Judging by what she's
muttering, I think yes.
Whelp, nighty-night!
We're back. How is everything?
Is Eila feeling any better yet?
Yeah, she's doing just fine.
She's asleep, but go see her.
Eila! Are you oka--?
[EILA sighs]
You better tell me
where Hartmann is, now!
Uh, she was just here,
filing a form
requesting permission
to go off base.
[MICHIKO]
Hi, everybody!
Michiko Yamakawa's
Strike Witches Classroom
is now in session!
Today, we're learning
all about Shirley,
whom you may also know
as Charlotte E. Yeager.
She's from the
United States of Liberion.
One time, she attempted to break
the world speed record
on her motorcycle!
She succeeded!
And shortly after that,
decided to join the military.
There, she aspired
to be the first person
ever to break the speed
of sound in a Striker Unit!
She ascended the ranks
super fast and became
a top ace assigned to the 501st!
She's a genius witch,
head and shoulders
above the rest!
Her inherent magic ability
is "Speed Boost."
That means that even
the fastest Neuroi around
doesn't stand a chance
against her lightning speed!
That ability suits her
perfectly, don't you think?
She's sometimes known
as "Glamourous Shirley"
because of her
curvaceous figure.
And military propaganda posters
often feature her as a pin-up!
She's got heart and is
someone other people
can look up to!
She always keeps an
eye on the big picture
and can see any
situation objectively.
Yoshika's so amazing!
I can't believe she gets to work
with such an incredible person!
[MICHIKO]
Me, again! Michiko Yamakawa!
You've heard about the
fall festival in October
called Halloween, right?
I wonder if Yoshika's
having lots of fun!
Next Time: "501st,
It's Time for Halloween?"
You've never seen witches
like these before!