[FUSSHI]
Hey, Abeno!
Ya wanna walk home with us?
Huh?
Uh-uh.
So about the class theme, uh...
Well...
Have you guys
come up with your ideas?
Mine's Russian Roulette
cream puffs.
And mine's
a fake convenience store.
What was yours?
[ASHIYA]
Hmm?
I'll see you guys later.
See ya, bro!
You take care, okay?
Hey, didn't you say you
have the day off, Ashiya.
[ASHIYA]
Yup.
Then let's go to the
store on the way home
and try out that new ice cream.
It's wagyu sukiyaki flavor!
[ASHIYA]
Uh. Hang on a sec.
Who is this?
Oh.
Last month's pork bone broth
and back fat ramen
ice cream sure was great.
Yeah. I have to admit,
it really surprised me.
Right? Even with
all that fat sprinkled on,
it wasn't too rich.
There were so
many different textures.
I didn't know what to think.
[ABENO]
Mononokean, come.
[ASHIYA pants]
Found you.
[ABENO]
Huh?
I told you I had business
in the Underworld today.
You can stay here.
What is it?
[ASHIYA pants]
I need a favor.
[ASHIYA]
Just now.
My mom passed out at the shop.
Apparently, they
took her to the hospital.
I need to be there.
Can you take me to see her?
[ABENO]
Go change your shoes first.
I appreciate this.
[INTERCOM] Doctor Chikamatsu,
you're needed in pediatrics.
Doctor Chikamatsu,
please report to pediatrics.
Mom. Hey.
How're ya feelin'?
They said this
was an anemic thing?
I got dizzy out of nowhere.
I'll be fine,
but they'd like to keep me
here overnight just in case.
I had a good run actually.
Funny enough, I can't
remember this happening to me
ever since having you.
I'd pass out from anemia
all the time when I was young.
You know, getting sick like
this again kind of takes me back
to the good old days.
Strange as it sounds.
I'm just glad
you're doing so well.
[ASHIYA]
Fuzzy?!
Oh, sorry, honey,
my headache suddenly
feels a lot worse.
[ASHIYA]
Did Fuzzy give her anemia?
Uh. Hold on.
Fuzzy just got here.
Don't tell me.
Hey, Mom, could you do me
a favor and sit up real quick?
[ASHIYA'S MOM groans]
My body just feels so heavy.
[ASHIYA gasps]
I knew it!
What'cha doin'?
[ASHIYA]
Nothing, one sec.
Oh wow.
Do you feel any better now?
So much better.
My headache's gone, and I don't
seem to be nauseous anymore.
I feel incredibly light now.
I think I'm healed!
Uh...
[ASHIYA]
Hm?
[ASHIYA'S MOM]
That surprised me.
Remember how I said I used
to go through this pretty often?
[ASHIYA]
Mm.
[ASHIYA'S MOM]
When I'd get anemic,
there was no amount of medicine
or treatment that could help me.
But you know what?
No matter how bad I felt.
Sakae could always
make it better, just like that.
He'd take a look at
my back like you did,
then do some secret thing
and I'd feel good as new.
Seems you're more
like him than I thought.
Your dad, I mean
[HINOHARA] Are you part of
Ms. Ashiya's family, sir?
[ABENO]
No...
So how are we doing?
You're sitting up!
That seems like a good sign.
Now, that my son's here,
I suddenly feel a lot better.
Ah, so then you must be Hanae.
I'm Hinohara, we spoke on
the phone a little while ago.
Oh. Nice to meet you,
thanks for calling me.
I should ask you.
The blonde boy out in the hall,
is he your friend?
Did you say he was blonde?
[gasps]
[ASHIYA]
Abeno?
I came to retrieve
the escaped hairball.
So what's with the yokai
that stuck itself to his back?
[ASHIYA] It was doing this
to my mom until a second ago.
Once I took it off her,
she was fine.
Hello there.
[ASHIYA]
Huh?
It felt like I was hugging
something strangely fluffy.
I must've switched
perches in my sleep.
But at any rate, I need to get
back to that human now, so bye.
[ABENO]
Excuse me, sir.
I apologize for detaining you,
but would you allow me
a moment of your time?
[ARANAKI]
Huh?
You see,
I'm Abeno, Master
of the Mononokean.
You're with the Mononokean?
[ARANAKI] I was only clinging
on to the human for a moment!
Not long at all. I swear!
[sobs]
I had been walking for
such a terribly long time,
and then I saw a human
who looked easy to possess,
so I decided to
take a short rest.
I knew it would
weaken the human,
but I figured she had
a little strength to spare.
[sobs]
It wasn't like I was trying
to cause the human trouble!
So please, sir!
Don't exorcise me
to the Underworld!
I won't touch any more humans!
Please, I don't wanna
be buried in yokai hell!
[ABENO] At this rate,
he'll bust through the ceiling.
[ARANAKI]
I see.
So the Underworld isn't
a graveyard for yokai.
[ABENO]
Right.
I'm glad that's clear now.
Well, Aranaki,
would you like for me
to exorcise you now?
Or should I wait?
With my body like this,
I think I'd get tired even from
moving a small distance.
But if I get some rest, I think
I can return to my normal size.
So if I could ask a favor.
What do you need?
Ideally, I'd like to
cling onto the human
from before again.
She was exceptionally
comfortable.
To be honest,
I haven't slept that deeply
in a really long time.
So would you mind?
[ASHIYA]
Hmm?
[ABENO]
Let's try a substitute.
That really hits the spot.
This human's an
absolute joy to possess.
He's brimming with energy.
I feel stronger already.
[ABENO]
It looks like you're compatible.
I feel like I just
donated half my blood.
You've found your calling
as a yokai magnet
[ASHIYA]
This exhaustion.
It isn't like when
Fuzzy possessed me.
I'll be careful not
to suck out too much.
Hold on.
Just what are you "sucking out"?
Dude!
Stop whining.
If you're strong enough
to talk, you're fine.
Well, Aranaki, I'll send for you
in about two hours, all right?
Until then, please take
your time recuperating.
I'd almost forgotten.
You still have work
to do in the Underworld,
isn't that right, Abeno?
Yeah, I need to head
that way pretty soon.
Ready, Hairball?
You're comin' too.
Hanae, I need a favor.
[gasps]
Uh. Sure thing.
What's the matter?
Hello there, I'm Abeno.
It's a pleasure
to meet you, ma'am.
I'm Ashiya's mother, Nara.
It's a pleasure
to meet you as well.
Though I wish I wasn't
in a hospital gown.
The Monono--
Uh... I mean Abeno
brought me to the hospital!
That's very kind of you.
Did you come by bus?
Let me reimburse
you for the fare.
Oh!
But I don't have my wallet.
[ABENO]
Please, don't worry about it.
You mentioned needing
help with something?
--[ASHIYA] That's right!
--[ASHIYA'S MOM] Oh yeah!
I forgot!
I didn't get to lock the house
before they brought me here.
Plus I never closed the store.
No worries. I'll head
back and lock things up.
Thanks so much, sweetie.
Golden hair and eyes to match.
They're the same hue.
The same as Sakae.
Just like a sunflower.
Door's unlocked,
but is anyone home?
Hanae!
Your beloved sister's here!
This is the last one, Ashiya.
You're doing a fine job!
You can do this!
Just keep pushing!
Yeah!
[ARANAKI]
Whoa... Steady does it.
Baby steps!
Took long enough,
but we're done here.
I'm sure your mother
would be proud.
Yeah. I try.
[ASHIYA]
Can I sleep here?
[ARANAKI]
I probably wouldn't advise it.
[ASHIYA'S SISTER pants]
He's not breathing!
Live, damn it, live!
I'm not gonna let you die!
[ASHIYA'S SISTER]
It's not enough.
Then here goes!
[ASHIYA grunts] Stop!
I was breathing fine, 'kay?
Just relax. Will you?
So I came back on a whim
to pay the two of you
a surprise visit.
Only to find out
Mom's in the hospital
and then to see you
splayed out on the ground.
I'm glad that you'd be quick
to act if I did need saving,
but maybe take a second
to check next time.
Felt like you were
gonna kill me yourself.
I dunno, kinda feel
like I did check first.
Well, ya didn't.
So how do you like it?
I've been trying to up
my omelet rice game.
I can tell, it's tasty.
Now why don't you
stop watching me eat
and start working on yours?
Oh, that smells delicious.
You wouldn't mind if
I had a bite, would you?
You know, actually,
I think it could use
more ketchup.
Could you grab some?
[ASHIYA'S SISTER]
You wanted more?
Yeah, just a little bit.
[ASHIYA'S SISTER]
Okay.
[ASHIYA]
While she's not looking.
[ARANAKI]
Mm, mm, mm, mm, mm! So good!
It's completely delicious!
Oh!
It seems that delightful flavor
turned my body back to normal!
[ASHIYA]
Nice, omelet rice!
Ya did good, gurl!
[ASHIYA]
No reaction,
even with Aranaki
talking right in front of her.
Doesn't look like
Sis can see yokai.
Mom either.
[ASHIYA'S MOM] Seems you're
more like him than I thought.
Your dad, I mean
[ASHIYA]
Are you Santa Claus?
No, I'm not.
[ASHIYA]
Huh?
[SAKAE] But it was Santa
who asked me to come by.
Oh.
Well are you my dad, then?
There ya go.
Sorry I took so long.
I'm glad to meet you.
Got enough ketchup?
Ya tryin' to drown out
the actual flavor?
[ASHIYA]
My hand slipped.
Can I ask you something weird?
Huh?
Back when Dad was around,
did you notice anything
strange about him?
What are you getting at?
[ASHIYA] Did he ever
say he could see yokai?
Or if not that, do you
remember him acting oddly?
Like, when Mom would get anemic,
do you remember what
he would do in response?
Did you ever see him try to wave
it away with his hand, or--
Hanae.
I'm not interested in discussing
a man who abandoned his family.
Don't make me remember.
[ASHIYA]
Okay.
[ASHIYA'S SISTER]
Sorry about before.
It's fair to want to know
what kind of dad he was.
And aside from mom,
I'm the only person you can ask.
First off,
of course I don't remember
him saying he could see yokai.
Why is that on your mind?
Don't tell me you started
believing in the supernatural.
What, did you watch one
of those ghost-hunter shows
over the summer?
You've always
been a scaredy-cat,
so I bet that stuff
really gets to you.
Yup, you caught me.
[ARANAKI]
Tell her, I'm right here!
[ASHIYA'S SISTER]
But...
Huh?
Well, what you said about
Mom's anemia reminded me.
She'd get sick pretty
often back in the day,
but then he
would go near her,
and she'd feel perfectly
fine all of a sudden.
On days like that, I'd catch him
throwing glances at no one.
or hiding in some corner,
nodding and talking to himself.
It was pretty strange.
Guess that's why those
memories stayed with me so long.
Anyway, that's about all
I can think of right now.
I'm glad you told me.
Thanks, sis.
Sure.
[ASHIYA'S SISTER] Let's go and
visit Mom together tomorrow.
She might pass
out again from surprise.
Huh?
Any guess what that was?
[ARANAKI]
Greetings, my fluffy friend!
You must be here to
take me to the Mononokean.
Ashiya!
You have my eternal thanks!
I feel that I'm ready
to be exorcised at last.
What's so funny,
and why're you
nodding to yourself?
It's nothing.
I think I'm gonna go
and take a little walk.
[ASHIYA'S SISTER]
What?
This late at night?
Don't worry, I'll be right back.
[ASHIYA'S SISTER]
Uh... I...
If you walk out on us
like your worthless father did,
I won't forgive you.
Abeno, I just found
out something huge!
That's odd.
Where is he?
Hey, Mononokean.
Where's Abeno?
[ABENO] Mononokean Master
Haruitsuki Abeno,
hearby requesting a
portal to the Underworld.
Thank you both
for all your help.
But you in particular Ashiya.
I shall never forget the
wonderful meal you provided me!
No prob.
It was just a
bite of omelet rice.
I wish only the best
for you and your family.
Thanks!
[ASHIYA]
My family, huh.
So...
What is it you wanted
to tell me about?
[ASHIYA]
Uh.
It's not your mother, is it?
Don't tell me she got possessed
by a different yokai.
No, N'I don't think it's
too big of a deal for you,
or at least, it shouldn't
mean any extra work for you.
It's actually my dad.
I think he was
able to see yokai.
Huh?
He's not around, by the way.
He disappeared
a really long time ago.
So there's no way
to confirm this with him,
and it's possible that I'm just
reading too far into things.
But after hearing about his
behavior, I feel pretty sure.
Behavior?
Giving weird looks to no one,
nodding and talking to himself.
Pretty much everything
I'm scared I'll get seen doing.
And if he could see yokai,
then I wonder if he
knew of the Mononokean.
On that note, I don't
suppose you've ever heard
the name
"Sakae Ashiya," before?
Uh-huh.
Huh?
You've heard that name?
When was it? Where were you?
How'd it come up?
A while back,
but I didn't think it mattered
till I heard your mom say it.
Where is my dad?
Are you certain
you wanna hear this?
It ends bad.
Tell me what you know.
[ABENO]
I heard the previous master
of the Mononokean
speak that name.
Only once.
When I was a kid.
You're talking about Aoi?
Yeah, and from what Aoi told me,
Sakae Ashiya died
a long time ago.
[ASHIYA]
Huh?
[ABENO] I wouldn't know the
exact date or even the year.
But unless I'm
somehow misremembering,
he died close to
a hundred years ago.
[ASHIYA]
A hundred years?
Hold on.
Did my parents meet beyond the
boundaries of time and space?
Is my dad like the boy
who leapt through time?
No, but you can see why
I didn't connect this before.
Could it've been someone
else with the same name?
[ABENO]
It's not that.
I know what I heard,
but it's likely that the
number of years was off.
You may have noticed
that most yokai have
a pretty distorted
sense of time.
[ASHIYA]
Oh yeah.
When I first met Yahiko,
he said you two played
together 30 years ago, right?
But it had only
been eight years.
Besides, the power
to see yokai is rare.
Few humans can do it.
Even if we can't be sure,
let's assume it's your dad.
So he died, but how?
Did he get sick
or something like that?
[ABENO]
I don't know.
But if he was ever a
client of the Mononokean,
then we should be able
to find him in the records.
[ASHIYA]
He died.
He first disappeared
over 15 years ago.
Not long before
I was due to be born.
At first, people guessed
he was in a freak accident.
When no body was found,
they thought he must've
gotten involved with criminals
or been murdered or both.
But then, three years
later on Christmas.
Ahh!
Daddy, you came home!
[ASHIYA]
He showed up out of nowhere.
He stayed with us
for that one day.
And then, he left us for good.
That Christmas
was the first and last time
I ever saw my father's face.
So if he's already
dead like you were told,
well, I can't say
when it happened.
But maybe it was
sometime not long after that,
and that's why he never
came to visit us again.
[ABENO]
Well?
Huh?
[ABENO]
What now?
Do you want me
to look into it for you?
I...
I'm not interested
in discussing a man
who abandoned his family.
Where'd he run off to?
Maybe I should
try n'give him a call.
[ASHIYA]
I love my family,
but it's made of three people.
[ABENO]
I understand.
The cultural festival.
Huh? Cosplay?
No. No way.
Hey, Yahiko.
Don't play at my school.
Tch! Or just do whatever.
Next time, "The Messenger."
Trick-or-treat.