[ASHIYA pants]
Fuzzy! Go around the other side!
[gasps]
Utakuni.
I understand that you
harbor regrets about your time
in this plane.
But you cannot stay in the
Mundane World any longer.
I ask you to prepare
to leave this place.
[ABENO] Allow me to exorcise
you, and I can promise this:
In the Underworld,
you won't be alone anymore.
How does that sound?
Mononokean master,
Haruitsuki Abeno,
requesting a portal
to the Underworld.
Safe travels!
[ABENO]
Ashiya.
[ASHIYA]
Yeah?
[ABENO]
Here's today's pay.
This is all you're giving me?
Huh?
[ASHIYA]
Come on, Abeno!
I may not have been able
to physically catch him.
But I worked my butt off
all day to corner him!
I think that hustle
deserves more than change!
That "hustle" is the
entirety of your job.
You don't get a bonus
for not screwing up.
Do you want me to pay back
the debt I owe you or not?
Because you're
making it impossible!
Oh shut up.
We did what we came here
to do; the yokai 's exorcised.
Let's go.
Uh. I meant to
ask you something.
That yokai .
You told him he wouldn't be
alone in the Underworld, right?
[ABENO]
He's like the hairball.
Someone's poor pet
who passed away,
then quickly became a yokai .
Huh? Another one, huh?
Missed his owners so bad.
He'd possess everyone he saw.
Growing larger
and larger all the while.
If we'd waited much
longer to exorcise him,
he'd have gotten too big
to fit through the
door to the Underworld.
[ASHIYA]
Um. Abeno?
I have a favor to ask.
Fuzzy.
I think I'm balloon-ed out.
But we don't have
to stop playing yet,
we can do
something else.
Hang tight.
I'm just gonna
clean up the room first.
[chuckles]
He's all tuckered out.
[ASHIYA]
When Fuzzy became a yokai ,
he was just like the
one we exorcised today.
He stayed in the Mundane World,
hoping someone would notice him.
And by complete chance,
he ended up in the
company of two guys
who can see yokai ,
Abeno and I.
But most yokai aren't so lucky
and are all alone in our world.
It's because I met Fuzzy that
I became deep in debt to Abeno.
So now I'm working for him
to try and pay him back.
And trust me, this job has
put me through the ringer.
But it's because I know
how those yokai feel
that I want to keep
doing this job,
despite the craziness
that comes with it.
[ASHIYA'S MOM]
Hanae!
Hanae, time to wake up!
[ASHIYA]
Huh? Fuzzy?
Uh. Oh. That's right,
I asked Abeno to let me take
you home last night, didn't I?
Okay, Fuzzy, time to wake up.
All right.
I'm heading out.
[gasps]
Oh, sweetie?
What was all
that noise last night?
[ASHIYA]
Huh?
I noticed I've gained
some weight recently,
so I was just
exercising in my room!
With what? Gymnastics?
One second.
Hold still.
There was some lint
on your shoulder.
Oh.
Well, thanks for
catching that, then.
You're the best, Mom!
You're so jumpy, you're not
feeling sick again, are you?
Are kids at school
still calling you
"the kid from the
nurse's office."
Wait, where did
you hear that nickname?
I never told you!
But no, I feel fine!
Don't worry about me.
I'm as healthy as can be!
What?
Japanese rowan.
In flower, they mean
"I'm watching over you."
Come on!
Do you have to express
everything through flowers?
Anyway, I gotta go!
Stay out of trouble. 'Kay?
It totally feels
like summer now.
[TEACHER] Well, summer vacation
is right around the corner,
and since this is your
first as high schoolers.
I've got some advice.
It's never too early
to start planning.
You wouldn't want to waste
your precious time off.
Take me for example.
I'm already planning
my family trip.
I was thinking of going
camping in the mountains,
but my daughter says
she wants to go to the beach!
She's so cute
I can never say no to her.
[FEMALE STUDENT]
See you tomorrow.
[MALE STUDENT]
Later.
[ASHIYA]
I wonder where Abeno is.
He didn't say anything
about having work today.
Well, I should probably
still bring Fuzzy back--
[FUSSHI]
Yo, Ashiya!
[ASHIYA]
Oh, hey, Fusshi. Hey, Saga.
You doin' okay, man?
I saw you staring
at your shoulder there.
[ASHIYA] It's been stiff
since I woke up this morning!
You think we'll ever
get out of class on time?
Not with our teacher.
You guys wanna hit up
the convenience store?
I'm always down for ice cream!
Sorry, I can't.
There's somewhere
I need to go today.
Huh?
[ASHIYA shrieks]
[SAGA]
What?
[FUSSHI]
Are you okay, man?
Yeah, I'm fine. Uhh...
Whoa!
What's that behind you?
Anyway, see ya, bye!
[SAGA, FUSSHI]
Uh...
Can you not connect
the Mononokean
to the classroom door
without warning?
And where have you been?
In here sipping on tea all day?
[ASHIYA]
SOS?
What? Was there an accident?
Do we have a new case?
What's the deal?
Alcohol.
[ASHIYA]
What does that mean?
Did someone drink
themselves sick?
How much should I worry?
Probably not at all, in fact.
Also, volume.
[ASHIYA] Wait, don't tell
me it's the Mononkean--
[ABENO]
Decrease, not increase.
Look at the bottom.
[ASHIYA]
SOS.
With a chance of clouds?
Mononokean.
What does that
mark at the end mean?
Knew I could count on you.
If I remember correctly,
the Legislator is one of the top
three figures in the Underworld.
The one I met before.
[gasps]
So if this is his seal,
that means something
bad happened to him, right?
[ABENO]
Likely just a hangover.
[ASHIYA]
Me, too?
What does he expect?
Does he want us to nurse him
back to health, or what?
All I know is
we don't have to go.
[ASHIYA] You'd just
leave him hanging like that?
[ABENO] A guy like him
could easily get someone else
to take care of him.
[ASHIYA] It could be
a really bad hangover.
My! Hello there, come in.
We've been expecting you.
I am grateful you made
the journey here.
So this is what
the inside looks like.
Man, when I was here before,
I only saw the outside.
Enough gawking.
[LEGISLATOR'S SERVANT]
Mr. Legislator.
The young Master
of the Mononokean
and his employee are here
to see you, as requested.
[LEGISLATOR]
Send them in.
I'll be taking my leave now.
Legislator?
Aren't you hurt?
Sure am.
You came at just
the right time, Itsuki!
Do me a favor and refill
my pipe with tobacco.
It's such a bother
with only one hand.
He broke his arm?
This is broken, huh?
[LEGISLATOR]
Yes, I think so.
He's using his full grip
strength on an arm in a cast!
The tobacco, if you would?
I wouldn't.
[ASHIYA] Legislator,
what happened to your arm?
Also, you shouldn't
smoke if you're injured.
I mean, it's bad for humans at
least, I don't know about you.
Listen to this sweetheart!
He's showing more concern
for me than you are, Itsuki.
Even a master can learn
from their employees.
Now, I know this
may be embarrassing,
but perhaps you should
act more like him.
Coming from the guy
who sends out an SOS
every time he's hungover.
You realize this
interrupts my work, right?
Perhaps you should take
your own advice and think about
how your actions affect those
around you, O great Legislator.
So talkative today.
Are you angry with me?
You lied about a serious injury,
so we could stuff
your tobacco pipe!
This is a serious injury.
Honest.
Despite that, I'm still
lucky to have gotten away
with nothing worse,
all things considered.
I wasn't exactly prepared to be
attacked as abruptly as I was.
You were attacked?
Don't tell me someone was
trying to assassinate you!
It was dreadful,
I'll leave it at that.
[ABENO]
Liquor and women?
Uh! To be fair,
she didn't know she'd
be a violent drunk.
And afterwards she actually
apologized to me.
Isn't that adorable?
Anyway, as you can see,
the altercation
resulted in this cast.
I simply cannot make any
progress on my work now.
Which is why...
...I called you
here to lend me hand.
So will you?
[ABENO]
Ask your own employees to help.
I would,
but I can't very well let them
know I've been slacking off,
now can I?
I'd be in deep trouble.
[ASHIYA]
I'm starting to think
you didn't really
break your arm.
I don't know what I'll do
if you two won't help me,
I've run out of options.
Besides, I'm not
asking you to work for free.
Consider it a time-sensitive
job for the Mononokean.
Does this pay seem fair to you?
Obviously you'd
split it into thirds
with Ashiya and the hairball.
Ah! I'd get a third of that?
[ABENO] This fat cat just
grabbed a wad of cash
out of the drawer
without looking, didn't he?
We'd be crazy
not to take this job!
[ABENO] He's just trying
to take advantage of us!
Who cares,
if it gets me that much
closer to paying off my debt!
I don't plan to stop working for
you but I want to pay you back!
[LEGISLATOR]
That's the spirit, Ashiya.
Good boy.
Even if Abeno refuses,
I can do it by myself!
[ABENO]
This guy.
And he's not gonna quit even
after paying off his debt?
[LEGISLATOR]
Anything would be a huge help.
What say you, Itsuki?
You say yes!
[LEGISLATOR] I need you
to get through all of this...
...by today.
[ABENO, ASHIYA]
Now the SOS makes more sense.
Hey, Legislator?
I was wondering.
What's this scroll that
I'm stamping now for?
Nothing you need to worry about.
It's better if you don't know.
What's that supposed to mean?
Let me put it this way,
it's something that'll
be a problem if you mess up.
[ASHIYA] What kind of
problem are we talkin' here?
You can come in.
[SHIZUKU]
But don't you have guests over?
[LEGISLATOR]
It's fine.
Well, if you say so.
How's your hand doing?
It's Shizuku!
Oh. No way!
Didn't expect to see you guys.
Did you come to visit my brother
while he's recovering?
That's one way to put it.
Ow. It hurts.
Actually, we were sent an SOS.
By who? My brother?
Ah! Give me a break!
I thought you told me you were
done with all of your work!
[LEGISLATOR]
Well, I knew you'd yell at me
if I told you the truth.
Though I enjoy any time spent
with you, yelling or not.
And I can't believe
you're this behind, too!
[ABENO] Why don't
you jump out the window
and really break your arm,
so you have an excuse
if we don't finish this?
I keep telling you,
it's broken, probably.
[ABENO]
Forget it, just stop slacking.
I'm not used to signing my name
with my left hand,
it's very tiring.
I'm taking a quick break.
Look how squiggly my writing is.
[ABENO]
Does it even matter?
Would you take over?
I can't legally sign your name.
You can if no one finds out.
Technically Ashiya shouldn't
be stamping my seal either,
but he's willing--
Uh oh.
I'm screwed.
What happened?
[ASHIYA] Whoa, that's a
twisted expression on his face!
Is he pissed or excited?
[SHIZUKU]
What's the problem, Ashiya?
Well, uh...
I just noticed this.
But I stamped a seal
in the wrong direction.
Oh. Just once? That's fine.
You serious? What a relief.
[ABENO]
Tch!
[ASHIYA] Did he just
click his tongue at me?
[sighs]
I'm all jittery from that scare.
Let's take a break Abeno,
I need it.
[LEGISLATOR]
Let's all take a break.
[ABENO]
Weren't you already on one?
How many more times do I have
to stamp this stupid seal?
[LEGISLATOR]
Dunno.
[SHIZUKU]
Hey, bro?
I'll get back to it
once I finish this pipe.
Look it.
[LEGISLATOR]
Hmm...
Well, that is a problem.
[ASHIYA]
Huh?
Ashiya, you're fired
from stamp duty.
Huh?
What'd you do?
And in your place,
I appoint Shizuku
to be the new stamper.
I've got a new job for you.
Me?
What?
I'd like you to take this scroll
to the Executive's place
as soon as possible.
[ASHIYA] I've never met
the Executive before.
If I remember right,
like the Legislator,
he's one of the leaders
of the Underworld.
[ABENO] Let me guess, that's one
of the Executive's scrolls then?
That's right.
It looks it got mixed up
with mine by accident.
Since Ashiya's not familiar
with this whole process,
he mistook it for one of mine
and stamped my seal on it.
Tell him I said.
"I accidentally stamped
my seal on your scroll!
No idea how it happened.
Sorry!"
And "also, I'm seriously
injured, so come visit me!"
Repeat that word for word
and give him the scroll.
[ASHIYA]
Word for word?
It's so casual!
[ABENO] Got any more BS
you want him to remember?
I do!
Make sure to say, "My deadline
is tomorrow, isn't it?" Heh heh.
You're extending your
own deadline by a day?
Won't I take the heat for
being the one to say all that?
[LEGISLATOR]
No, you'll be fine.
It's not so simple as having the
Mononkean connect to his door,
it can't enter the
Executive's territory.
[LEGISLATOR]
I'm aware.
I guess we could have it take us
as close as possible
and walk from there.
Take "us"?
Don't you mean "him"?
I need you to stay here with me.
There's still work to do.
For real? I'm supposed
to go there by myself?
I'll have one of the tadpole
lines take you to him.
So you don't have to worry
about getting lost on your way.
[ASHIYA]
How are tadpoles gonna help?
Is chaperoning some
baby frogs supposed make me
feel better or something?
Because it doesn't!
Come on, Abeno,
you can't let me wander
around the Underworld alone!
I have a record, remember?
[ABENO sighs]
Itsuki stays here.
So it won't do you
any good to plead with him.
Then why don't I go with him?
I'd be happy to.
Because you're on
stamp duty, so you can't.
The hairball?
Hm. I appoint
the little one here.
[ASHIYA]
Huh?
[ABENO]
Wait, appoint him to what?
To be Ashiya's guard
on his excursion.
[gasps]
Allow me to translate.
The hairball said, "If you need
someone to protect Ashiya,
then I'm your yokai ."
I'll make sure he reaches
the Executive's
place safe and sound.
Just leave it to me.
Quite the reliable one,
isn't he?
You saved me Fuzzy!
[ABENO] I get the feeling
we can't completely
trust that translation.
I'm glad we've come
to an understanding.
Send my warmest regards.
[pants]
We're finally on something
resembling a path.
Hope I didn't get
these clothes dirty.
They're borrowed,
so I gotta be careful.
[bubbly sound]
[squeak]
[LEGISLATOR]
Ashiya? Ashiya?
Can you hear me?
[ASHIYA]
Uhh, sorta!
[LEGISLATOR]
Where are you right now?
Describe your surrroundings.
"Surroundings."
I just came off of a game trail
and now I'm on a narrow path.
[ASHIYA] Sorry I can't
describe it any better.
How much further do you
think I have left to go?
Just keep walking
along that path,
and you'll reach
the Birdcage soon.
[ASHIYA]
Birdcage?
[LEGISLATOR]
Where the Executive resides.
One more thing,
Itsuki expressed concern
that you may lose track
of the scroll as you
make your way there.
Did you drop it?
No, of course I didn't!
I have the thing tied
around my neck!
Hello?
Legislator?
Can you still hear me?
[ASHIYA]
We got disconnected.
[rustling]
[shrieks]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What was that sound?
I know I heard something!
[ASHIYA]
A bird.
Well, this is a forest.
So that checks out.
[ASHIYA]
I've got my own personal guard.
And my guide tadpole!
So I'm not alone.
I'll be fine!
Just fine.
[shrieks]
Don't just climb all
over me like that, Fuzzy!
Can you hear me now?
Legislator?
Abeno?
Anyone with ears!
SOS!
I guess it's no use.
It's hard to get a good
reception around there.
This was bound to happen.
Uh...
[ABENO]
Hmm...
I can tell that you're worried.
What gave you that idea?
[sighs]
I'm not worried.
I just hope he doesn't
cause any trouble this time.
The guy's my employee;
I'm responsible.
All right!
Who goes there?
Don't move a muscle!
[ASHIYA]
Uh, nevermind. Uh...
[sighs]
Sorry.
Didn't mean to startle you.
Just another bird, huh?
It scared me.
Well, "bird" is a bit
of an understatement.
It sounded more imposing
than that at first, though.
Guess it was
just my imagination.
[slurps]
[ASHIYA] All I wanted was to
come check on the Legislator
and make sure he wasn't like,
dying or something.
Why am I in the middle
of some dramatic adventure
all of a sudden?
Next time, "The Tail."
Help!
Fuzzy!