[slurps]
This is fine; don't freak out.
I'm in the Underworld!
This must be a yokai,
which means I should
be able to speak with it.
How's it going, buddy?
[ASHIYA]
Abeno!
SOS! SOS!
Call the Mononokean!
I need an emergency
evac, like, yesterday!
There's this giant beast yokai!
It's huge!
"Step on me and I die" huge!
Hurry up, before it catches me!
Huh?
[ASHIYA]
Huh...
It's not... chasing me?
Unless it's about to jump out.
Crap, my legs feel like jelly.
Huh?
[shrieks]
[gasps]
[YAHIKO]
Ugh. Zenko.
Stop moving so much, Yahiko.
I wanted to make Haruitsuki
play with me today.
But I can't find him!
Why don't you ask Hanae instead?
No, he sucks!
Blegh.
I'll just play with Okina.
Okina? Who's that?
You mean the god in
the shrine on the mountain?
[YAHIKO]
Yup!
We've been playing
together recently!
[ZENKO] Before you go,
clean up the garden.
Awww.
You only get to stay here
because you promised
to help around the
temple, remember?
I don't wanna!
You can't make me!
I wanna go play with Okina!
Okay.
But you're not getting any
of the rakugan I bought.
You got rakugan?
I'll do it! I'll do it!
Gimme that thing!
So can I have some?
You can when you're done.
Sweet! Don't forget, okay?
Can I have three?
You get two.
[YAHIKO]
What?
Zenko, you're such a cheapskate!
[CAT]
You dropped something.
Uh?
[CAT]
This. Your sandal.
[ASHIYA]
Huuuh?!
Wait... Did he just
throw up my shoe?
Hey, it's one of you.
You're a tadpole line
from the Legislator, right?
Does that mean you
work for the Legislator?
And are you going
to the Birdcage?
'Cause I'm on my way there, too.
[ASHIYA] You're telling me this
purple cat knows the Executive?
I guess it's possible
he works for him.
[CAT] But I dropped
something around here,
so I can't go any further yet.
What do I do?
[ASHIYA]
Quite the pensive cat.
[CAT] Would you guys
be able to help me find it?
[ASHIYA]
Normally I would, but I'm sorry,
we're on our way to
deliver something important.
And we're in a hurry.
Well, if you can't...
[ASHIYA]
Now I feel bad.
[sighs]
It's gold, shiny and
catches your eye,
so I thought I'd be able to find
it without much trouble, but...
If it's gold and shiny, then...
Hey, maybe I can help!
Is what you're looking for
made of metal by chance?
[CAT]
Hmm?
Just wondering.
Huh.
I feel like it's around
here somewhere.
[ASHIYA]
Heh. This reminds me
of when we were looking
for Manjiro's ring.
Oh! There it is!
[ASHIYA]
Back, safe and sound!
Wow, you're really amazing!
You found my
tail ring in no time!
How'd you do that?
I'm just good at finding
metal things, honestly.
Weird talent, I know.
Anyway, we should head
back to the path we were on
and make our way
to the Birdcage.
Uh. Hey, so...
Yeah?
[CAT]
Wanna ride on my back?
We are going the
same way, after all.
All aboard the Gorou express!
[GOROU'S OWNER]
I think he likes you!
Hanae, no!
No riding animals!
[ASHIYA]
He's just like Gorou.
Are you sure that's all right?
Yeah?
Fluffy!
You ready to go?
Sure am.
Whoa! So fast!
[ASHIYA] I didn't realize I
signed up for a roller coaster!
[ASHIYA screams]
Ugh. I think I'm gonna throw up.
You better hold on tight
if you don't wanna fall off.
[ASHIYA] Could have said
something sooner.
No, no, no!
[CAT]
Oops.
Looks like I jumped too far.
[CAT] That's okay,
just gotta climb a little.
[sighs]
Well, we're here.
I noticed.
[knock, knock]
[EXECUTIVE'S SERVANT]
And HOO might you be?
[ASHIYA] I'm here to deliver
something from the Legislator.
From the Legislator, you say?
I'm not gonna eat you.
At the moment, I'm not
allowed to eat meat at all,
so for now consider
me an herbivore.
I'm not really
sure how it happened,
but it looks like this scroll
was mixed up with a few of his,
so he sent me.
Is it too much trouble to
ask you to pass this along
to the Executive?
Not at all, I appreciate
you coming all this way.
No problem, just doing my job.
[EXECUTIVE'S SERVANT]
Forgive me for saying so,
but you look pale.
Would you like to rest
inside for a short while?
Thanks, but I'll be fine.
Huh? Are you sick or something?
[CAT] I can take
you home, if you want?
Nah, I feel fine!
I can get back on my own.
Don't be so shy.
Really, I can
walk back no problem.
Well, I suppose if you're sure.
[ASHIYA]
Why is he drooling?
I should get something
to eat anyway.
Looks like we'll be
going our separate ways
if you don't need me.
Seems so.
It will take you
quite a long time
to walk back to
Newt Lake, will it not?
I could take you back myself,
if you're open to it.
Thank you.
But it isn't as much of
a trip as you'd think.
I'll just have the Mononokean
take me part of the way.
So I'm good.
[CAT]
The Mononokean?
Then these guys
are going to see Itsuki?
Well then, I should
start heading back.
Thanks for letting me
ride you over here.
[AHSIYA] You know, that
capybara set a bad example
for beast yokai.
This guy was pretty nice!
Tadpole.
I'm counting on you
to lead the way back.
Oh, speaking of which,
can you connect us again?
I need to tell Abeno
to come pick me up
at the same place
he dropped me off.
He actually patted my head.
It's embarrassing.
[EXECUTIVE'S SERVANT]
In all of my time working
for the Executive, I've never
seen those employees
at the Legislator's residence.
However, you seemed
very close to them.
Were you acquainted before?
First time.
We just happened to bump into
each other on the way here.
[EXECUTIVE'S SERVANT]
Oh, is that right?
Maybe they're newly employed.
[CAT]
Oh.
Now that I think about it,
I didn't ask for his name.
[EXECUTIVE'S SERVANT] I wonder
if the Executive can tell you.
Perhaps you should ask him,
Mr. Justice.
[SHIZUKU]
I made you some tea!
How thoughtful.
It's all done.
And with such a smile on!
You finished writing all
of this incredibly quickly.
To be honest with you,
I didn't think we'd
actually complete it today.
[ABENO sighs]
You must be tired
after all that work.
Want some tea?
No thanks.
I'll pass.
I'm borrowing this guy, though.
Huh?
That's not a problem, but...
[ABENO]
Mononokean, come.
Where are you going?
[ABENO] To where I
dropped Ashiya off earlier.
You're gonna leave already?
Don't you think it makes
more sense to just wait here
until he calls
asking for a ride back?
[SHIZUKU]
Well, there he goes.
I don't know why he's
always in such a hurry.
He could have at least had
some of the tea I made.
[clattering]
[LEGISLATOR]
Hmm?
Ughhh!
Welcome back, Ashiya.
What does it even matter?
I delivered the
scroll, didn't I?
[ABENO]
Huh?
Am I supposed to ignore
that you said you rode
"a beast like Gorou"?
What does that even mean?
And what's a Gorou?
It's the name of a dog
who lived near me.
[ABENO]
I knew you'd do something
to mess this whole thing up!
And I was right!
[ASHIYA grunts]
Well, who cares?
It'd be one thing if he
was a dangerous beast,
but he was very civil!
He even told us he that
he was an herbivore!
So he couldn't eat us
if he wanted to!
What if he said that to make
you put your guard down?
Well...
I hadn't thought of that,
but I still think you're
being too negative!
It all worked out!
[ABENO]
You're so dumb!
[ASHIYA]
What?
[ABENO]
You heard me!
[ASHIYA]
Why do you have to be such a--
"Everyone's at
fault in a fight."
[LEGISLATOR]
Good job, everyone.
Thanks to your help, I was
able to finish my work on time.
So... Here's your promised pay.
[ABENO] Man, I can't believe you
can't even run a simple errand.
"Can't run a simple
errand" my butt.
I did exactly what
was asked of me.
It doesn't matter
how I got it done.
I seem to remember the
Mononokean warning you
not to go anywhere
with unfamiliar yokai.
Yet you jumped on one's back
the first chance you got.
Like I said,
I tried to run.
At first, anyway.
I didn't just tackle the
poor guy and yell, "giddy-up"!
Ugh!
[LEGISLATOR] Neither one
of them is listening to me.
[ASHIYA] Well maybe you
should have come with me,
like I asked you to.
I'm sure with your supervision,
none of this would
have happened.
What'd you say?
I don't care for
your tone, buddy.
[LEGISLATOR] Usually
"everyone's at fault in a fight"
works like a charm.
[LEGISLATOR] As the one
who sent Ashiya on his trek.
I can't let you two
go home still fighting.
Now then,
shall we have a drink?
--[ABENO] Huh?
--[ASHIYA] A drink?
[SHIZUKU]
Can we come in now?
[LEGISLATOR]
You may.
Mr. Legislator, the preparations
for the party are complete.
I know you wanted saké,
but we got more than just that.
They're either
really fast or psychic.
Or he's screwing with us
and planned to have
a drink anyway.
You caught me.
If it's not too much trouble,
I have a request
I'd like to ask of you.
What is it?
And there's no need
to be so formal.
Well, since we have the whole
Mononokean crew here already.
I was hoping to invite Koura
to our get-together, too.
That okay with you?
Koura from the Kiyakudo?
I wouldn't mind seeing her.
I've been planning to thank her
for taking care of
Fuzzy that one time.
She's usually pretty busy,
so we'll have to see.
Itsuki.
Yeah?
Use the Mononokean to bring
Koura here right away.
This is a rule.
[ASHIYA]
He only looks like a boss
when he's abusing his authority.
On it.
[ASHIYA] Abeno doesn't look like
much of a subordinate, though.
Aww, thanks bro,
you're the best!
Oh, Itsuki!
Why don't I go
with you to pick her up?
[ASHIYA, KOURA, LEGISLATOR]
Cheers!
[ABENO]
Why are we doing this here?
Because...
...if we don't,
the Mononokean can't
join in on the festivities.
Right?
There may not be much space,
but it feels like we're
a happy family this way.
[ABENO]
Hmm...
[ASHIYA]
He is so obviously not happy.
I agree, it's totally
cozier this way!
Your ears are exquisite
as usual, Ashiya.
My dear.
They would make such great
ingredients for medicine.
How can you let
them go to waste?
Is that a compliment?
I, uh...
Mine would be even better.
His are probably
all old and crusty.
Why even bother?
Would you like me
to pour you some?
It's not saké.
No way.
Uh... Forget about him!
I'll gladly have some myself!
It's gyomaroppe.
A kind of juice.
"Gyoma"? Hmm..
[ASHIYA] I'm not sure I want
to drink this, but if I don't,
I'll put a damper on this
party that they went through
all the trouble of preparing!
[ASHIYA] Seriously, what am
I drinking right now?
Would you like to try
some of this, as well?
Absolutely.
[ASHIYA] And what
am I eating right now?
[ASHIYA]
Abeno's having everything,
so it's gotta be fine.
It all tastes good, too,
so what have I got to lose?
Be honest, did ya have the saké?
[ASHIYA moans]
I... I thought everything
was non-alcoholic.
My stomach's on fire.
Abeno, please.
Water. Water.
I'll grab some
water and medicine.
Hang on a sec,
I'll be right back!
Now that I think about it.
We've never given you food
from the Underworld before.
He could be having
a bad reaction to it all.
Water would be great,
or tea if there is any.
But actually, café au lait
would be perfect.
[ABENO]
Hmm...
Hey, Mononokean.
Open a link to
the Mundane World.
[LEGISLATOR] I could always
have someone make us tea.
If he's thirsty,
water from the Mundane World
is probably best.
We don't want to
give him something
that'll make him sicker.
If you're heading to the Mundane
World, get some ice cream too.
My tummy is burning.
So hot. So hot.
So cold.
You sure changed
clothes quickly.
Mononokean,
I'll be right back,
so please keep the nijiriguchi
in the same place.
[KOURA]
Have a safe trip!
Is he unconscious?
[laughs]
Did I miss something funny?
Or are you just a giggly drunk?
No. Heh.
It's just that Itsuki's finally
showing some human kindness.
Right, Mononokean?
Really? Is that how it
looked to the two of you?
I hadn't noticed.
He seemed the same
as always, to me.
Well, he always treats us
yokai with respect.
Doesn't he?
But he has a tendency to be
strangely cruel towards humans,
almost as if to keep
them at a distance.
One time, I asked him
a rather tough question.
[KOURA]
Hmm?
[LLEGISLATOR]
If both were in danger
and you could only rescue one...
[LEGISLATOR]
Would you save the yokai,
or would you save the human?
The yokai.
No deliberation?
And why would you choose that?
The yokai over the human?
[ABENO]
Because for the human.
There's always someone else.
Someone who would
help them, even if I didn't.
[KOURA] That makes me worry
he would abandon Ashiya
if he were in danger.
I wonder how he'd answer now.
Just from what I saw today,
he was very worried about Ashiya
when we lost contact with him.
That's got to be the first time
I've ever seen him so invested
in the wellbeing of a human
And that makes you happy?
[LEGISLATOR chuckles]
I don't know that it
makes me happy,
so much as curious.
Heh. Perhaps I'll ask
him about it again soon.
Just be careful.
If you put him in
a tough position
by asking him that again,
he'll probably keep his
distance from you even more.
Even more?
Even more.
Maybe I won't do it, then.
Do you plan to do
something about him?
[LEGISLATOR]
What do you mean?
I'm not trying to say it
wouldn't be a good change
for Itsuki if he cared more
for humans from time to time.
But considering he's the
master of the Mononokean,
that may not be the
most desirable outcome.
Maybe not.
However,
I'd say the
opposite bet is safer.
Right, Mononokean?
[LEGISLATOR] I wonder
which bet is the safer one
in your opinion,
Aoi?
[EXECUTIVE] Who brought
this scroll to my domain?
[EXECUTIVE'S SERVANT]
Well, I believe it was
an employee
of the Legislator's, sir.
However, I've never
seen him before.
[EXECUTIVE]
Interesting,
I've heard nothing about him
employing someone new.
What was he like?
Other than looking very pale,
there was nothing
that stuck out.
Oh, actually, I remember
him mentioning something
about the Mononokean.
[EXECUTIVE]
The Mononokean?
I see.
[ASHIYA] I don't spend
all my time with yokai.
I'm a part-time normal guy, too.
I've got a regular
school life and--
Oh! Of course there's
one at school now!
Next time, "Greetings."
I'll tell you everything
you need to know
about having an average
school experience!