[ASHIYA]
Ugh.
It's so hot out here.
I'm only wearing
a polo and I'm melting.
How are you good in that kimono,
aren't you uncomfortable?
Of course I am.
[ASHIYA]
What? Really?
All right, Mononokean, come.
I feel like heat hits me way
harder than it does most people.
Yesterday I got super hot.
It wore me out.
So today I'm'a play with
Fuzzy here in the Mononokean.
Huh?
That's a lot better!
Nice and cool here!
Hey Fuzzy!
It's burnin' up today,
and there's no shade
on the school roof.
So I figure we can
just play here instead.
Hmm?
Fuzzy?
You on the ceiling?
Nah, That wouldn't make sense.
Hey Abeno, I can't find Fuzzy.
I'm about to ask you
a very serious question.
Okay.
Did you steal something
in the Underworld?
Well, uh...
Nothing that I remember.
And what exactly is
that supposed to mean?
You steal so much
you can't keep track?
[ASHIYA]
No!
Of course I didn't
steal anything!
But I thought it was possible
I might've taken
something by accident.
Uh.
When I'm asked
the same thing twice,
I get less sure.
[ABENO]
How about three times?
Did you steal or not?
No way.
Ah! You're not talking about
that scroll I took to the
Executive, are you?
I marched that scroll
all the way to his door
and handed it off
to his servant!
Fuzzy saw!
Right? Back me up!
Crap.
Did you even hear me telling you
about how Fuzzy
had gone missing?
Yeah, I heard you.
[ASHIYA]
Huh?
You're saying that Fuzzy
was accused of stealing?
[ASHIYA]
The Justice had Fuzzy arrested?
No way.
Wait a sec.
Don't tell me.
Hey.
[ASHIYA shrieks]
What's wrong?
Do you have a sudden
confession to make?
No, Fuzzy wouldn't
do that either.
But I might know what happened.
I saw a yokai that looked
like Fuzzy the first time
I went to the Underworld.
And it was a thief.
We can't be sure,
but what if Fuzzy got arrested
because someone mistook
him for that guy?
Regardless, we need to
go to White Sand Prison
and see the Justice.
[ABENO]
Something isn't right.
What is it?
Mononokean, take us to him.
[ASHIYA] So uh, you're
going to Justice's place?
Yeah, and I'm gonna
need you to come, too
[SERVANT C]
Excuse me, sir.
Apologies, but uh...
[bubbly sound]
[EXECUTIVE]
Hello? Justice, you there?
Justice.
Can you hear me?
You ate my tadpole
line again, didn't you?
I thought I forbade you
from eating meat.
Did you need something?
[EXECUTIVE] Just checking
to see if you finished the job.
[JUSTICE]
Oh, is that all you want?
Yeah, it's been taken care of.
The Mononokean employee
is in my custody.
[EXECUTIVE]
Excellent work.
This is Hanae Ashiya!
Employee of the Mononokean!
We brought him
here with great haste,
just as Your Honor commanded us!
[JUSTICE]
Hmm...
Wrong guy.
Huh?
[JUSTICE] I told you
that he had a human form.
Come on, transform already!
[SERVANT B]
You can do it, right?
Show him!
[JUSTICE]
I remember this yokai.
It was with the guy
I took to the Birdcage.
The one who
helped me find my ring.
I thought for sure
that he worked
for the Legislator, though.
Maybe he actually works
for the Mononokean?
[SERVANT C]
Pardon me, sir.
Do you have a moment?
[JUSTICE]
Sure.
We just received a
message from security saying
the Mononokean is
in the Underworld.
How interesting.
Tell me.
Was anyone with Itsuk--
With the master I mean,
someone in human form perhaps?
That's right.
The message we
got did mention that.
[JUSTICE] Looks like they came
here to rescue their friend.
Now, what is it people
say about these things?
Oh. I think it starts with
"nothing ventured," right?
[SERVANT C]
Right...
[ASHIYA]
Whoa, he's awake!
Look Abeno,
the fake Fuzzy woke up!
Are you listening to me?
What? Oh. Morning, bud.
You doing okay?
I think he's still
feeling Koura's sedative.
This should help you.
The best way to capture
this little doppelganger
is by putting it to sleep.
One whiff of that potion and
he'll be zonked out all day!
[ABENO] You're not peddling
this to everyone, right?
[ASHIYA]
The fuzzy look-a-like!
He's here!
Well that turned out
to be a good deal easier
than I expected.
Hopefully it actually helps.
[ASHIYA]
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
I met you in the forest!
[JUSTICE] So you are an
employee of the Mononokean.
[ASHIYA]
Abeno! He's the one!
The yokai that gave me a
ride to the Executive's place.
Great. So it looks like
the Legislator was right.
[sighs]
Hey Itsuki.
You don't like this guy, do you?
Nope. How'd you guess?
It wasn't hard.
Your styles clash.
I bet you fight a lot.
He's just so damn noisy.
He was pretty loud
when I met him, too.
[ASHIYA] Man, this yokai was
supposed to be my friend!
Insulting me to my face is
pretty rude, but whatever.
I'm fine.
I already knew that
Abeno didn't like me.
And being noisy is
just part of who I am!
I appreciate the input, Abeno
but this isn't the best time!
Justice.
We want you to free Fuzzy.
[JUSTICE]
Hm?
[ASHIYA] The yokai
that's been stealing stuff
all over the underworld
wasn't actually Fuzzy.
It was this grungy
Fuzzy wannabe.
Take a good look and you'll see
that they're clearly different,
so please let Fuzzy go!
You sure are able
to talk quickly.
Can you speak even
faster than that?
Please say you will.
[ASHIYA] Did you even
hear the words I said?
Come on.
Uh-huh, sure.
I'll let your friend go.
[ASHIYA]
Eh... Do you mean it?
Yep. Leave the look-a-like
here at White Sand Prison,
and I'll judge him
properly later.
Take this little guy
and put him away
'Kay but...
We don't know the entire story.
I mean he might've had
a good reason for stealing,
so please be lenient with
your uh, punishment.
I know I said I'd let
your fuzzy friend go free,
and I meant it,
but I do have one condition.
Huh?
But I thought that Fuzzy had
been cleared of suspicion.
He was never suspected
of a crime in the first place.
I was trying to apprehend
the human named "Ashiya."
You mean...
So if you remain at
White Sand Prison,
your friend can leave.
Do you accept?
[ABENO]
So that's it.
I really should've
seen it sooner.
Of course he was
the one behind all this.
Seemed out of character for you
to plan this scheme on your own.
Not even he has the power
to seize and hold someone
against their will.
But as long as you're willing to
cook up some baseless suspicion.
You do.
"Just charge him with theft or
something and apprehend him."
Right, isn't that what the
Executive told you to do?
[ASHIYA]
Huh?
The Executive?
Okay, so.
My guess is you only
arrested Fuzzy by accident.
But the charge of theft
was fake anyway?
And it was the Executive
that put you up to it?
I've never even met him, though.
Why would he want me arrested?
I'm afraid that this has nothing
to do with you, personally.
The Executive hates
humans is all.
Isn't that right, Itsuki?
It's true.
[ASHIYA]
A yokai who hates humans?
So what's the deal
with the Executive?
May as well talk,
since I've been found out.
It's like Itsuki said;
the Executive told me
to apprehend you.
And I asked him what he
was planning to do with you,
but I just couldn't
get him to say.
At any rate, you know
as much as I do now.
If you wanna find out more,
you can hang around
for a little while.
He should be here soon.
He shuts himself in
the Birdcage year-round,
and now he's coming here?
I know, it's a rare sight.
I invite him to
all sorts of things,
but I can never get
him to come out.
[sighs]
He'll be here any minute now,
guess I'd better freshen up.
[ASHIYA gasps]
He transformed!
Like Yahiko.
Come on.
That's boring.
I was hoping you'd scream in
shock like you did earlier.
I've hit my freak-out
quota for the day.
Does it really surprise you
that I came in person, Itsuki?
Ahh! Hey! Who the heck're you?
Who do you suppose
I might be, Hanae Ashiya?
Are you the Executive?
Or...
[EXECUTIVE] Very good,
I can't imagine how you guessed.
[ASHIYA]
Huh? What is he doing?
I can't talk.
I can't move.
I can't even breathe.
Whoa.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I think so.
Yeah, you're right.
I am surprised that you came.
I was quite surprised myself,
upon learning that the
Justice had apprehended
the wrong employee of yours.
Luckily, you brought
him to me yourself.
Which means
I didn't make the trip in vain.
[JUSTICE]
Hm?
But I haven't said anything
about arresting
the wrong person.
I'm quite sure you have,
as I heard it through
the tadpole line.
The one I sent you
never left, you see.
Ah, so the line was
never disconnected.
You eavesdropped.
[EXECUTIVE]
Yes, and before I came in
you were trying to guess what
I might want with the human.
Is that still a
subject of interest?
Well now that he's here.
I'm happy to explain.
Ever since I learned of
Hanae Ashiya's existence.
I've been trying to decide
if I should let him live
or kill him.
[ASHIYA]
Kill... me...?
[EXECUTIVE]
He can see us yokai.
And despite the
danger that entails,
he has been permitted
to enter our domain.
Shall I simply kill him?
Or should I permit him to live
as an employee of
the Mononokean?
I thought I'd keep him
in White Sand Prison
until I could come
to a decision.
[ASHIYA]
I'm paralyzed.
Just like before.
What's wrong?
Revert now, before you kill him.
[EXECUTIVE]
It's too bad.
I always feel so
at home in this form.
But no one else
seems to like it.
Intriguing.
It would appear that your
employee can't even stand
to be in my presence.
Hm.
[JUSTICE]
Hey. Can you breathe?
[ABENO] If the Executive
stays in this form,
he could kill Ashiya
here and now.
Does he know that?
Executive, I think
you've made your point.
Executive.
Revert to your human form.
[JUSTICE]
Itsuki challenged the Executive.
No one's ever raised a hand
against him like that before.
[EXECUTIVE] How dare you
attempt to bend my will?
I did what I had to do.
[EXECUTIVE] You're quite intent
on protecting this human.
[ABENO]
Huh?
[EXECUTIVE] It became clear when
I sent Egen to investigate him.
You did all that you could
to come between them.
And this time, you went
beyond protecting a human.
You sided with one and raised
your hand against me: a yokai.
An act unbecoming of
the Mononokean's Master.
It's certainly not something
Aoi would've done.
I'm asking you to listen.
You need to realize that the
human known as Hanae Ashiya
is far more dangerous
than you could fathom.
And now that I've seen the
influence he's had on you,
I know that he should be killed.
Now here's an idea.
If you don't want me
to dispose of this threat,
how about you do it yourself?
As the master of the Mononokean,
you're above our laws.
So kill him.
It needs to be done.
[JUSTICE]
That's enough!
I'll warn you not to
forget where you are.
This is White Sand Prison,
where those who
break the law are judged.
You should know better than to
incite murder in these walls.
This is the reason I refused
to tell you what I had planned.
See, if I'd admitted
my actual motives,
you never would've
made that arrest.
[JUSTICE sighs]
Both of you come with me.
Ashiya--
I said come.
I'll arbitrate
this quarrel of yours.
It's best if
Ashiya stays behind.
[ABENO]
Wait here. I'll be back.
I get that you're
glad to be acquitted.
But that doesn't mean you have
free run of the entire prison!
[ASHIYA]
Fuzzy.
I'm glad you're okay.
Really.
I honestly thought
I was about to suffocate.
If Abeno hadn't stood up
to the Executive when he did,
I... I would be dead right now.
[JUSTICE]
Hmm...
The Executive's in the wrong.
In Article Five
of the Prohibitions,
which bind our world's
Three Powers.
We're forbidden
from personal conflict,
and from causing fear
or suffering in others.
The Mononokean is under the
supervision of the Legislator.
That may be, but the
Legislator's supervision is lax.
He's been treating
this matter carelessly.
Which is why I had
no choice but to interv--
Yes, I understand.
Here's the thing, Itsuki.
The Executive's actions
went too far,
but I can't say I disagree
with his opinion.
The Underworld is the only place
where we yokai can live
comfortably, without worry.
If it becomes public knowledge
that humans are
coming and going,
many yokai will feel uneasy.
Perhaps even resentful.
As the Justice, it's my duty
to prevent unrest in this world.
Therefore, I would like
you to keep Hanae Ashiya
from entering the Underworld.
[ABENO]
Understood.
We're going back
to the Mononokean.
Yeah, sure.
Hey Ashiya.
Before you return to the
Mundane World, let's talk.
Okay.
You see.
So I can never come back
to the Underworld?
[JUSTICE]
If you accept that condition,
the Executive promises
to leave you be.
Well if that's what you want,
I understand.
I won't come back.
Then our dispute is resolved.
I've heard rather
positive things
about the work you've
done for various yokai.
As long as you prove to
be beneficial to my kind,
I'll remain civil towards you.
But if I determine that your
deeds have done harm,
you'll find no law in this world
or your own that can save
you from my wrath.
If you expect me to pretend
I didn't hear that,
you're mistaken.
'Twas but a jest.
To reiterate what I said before,
you're forbidden from
coming anywhere near Ashiya.
And I'm happy to comply.
I'm keeping my distance
even as we speak.
Now.
I'll take my leave.
Should you see the Legislator,
send him my warmest regards.
Yeah. He isn't who they wanted.
Hey, Mononokean.
Think you can take
Ashiya home for me?
I need to make a quick stop
at the Legislator's place.
He needs to know what
the Executive did,
so he can reprimand him.
Go home and rest, all right?
All right.
[ASHIYA] He said we'd
have a job today, too.
I wonder what kind of
yokai we'll be exorcising.
What're you doing?
[shrieks]
[ASHIYA'S MOM]
You scared the life out of me.
Morning, sunshine.
G'morning.
Your voice sure is hoarse today.
[ASHIYA'S MOM] That's
cause I just woke up, silly.
[ASHIYA] Thought
she was a yokai for sure.
So you're up early.
Have trouble sleeping, or what?
Uh, well I was sleeping fine,
but it's so hot that I got
thirsty and woke up.
It shouldn't be long until
summer vacation, right?
I'll be counting on your
help at the shop this year.
[ASHIYA]
Mm.
Mom!
I'm sorry.
I kinda just felt
like messing with you.
Anyway, I might as well
get started on breakfast now.
[ASHIYA sighs]
It's good to be alive.
Oh wow, you like
my noogies that much?
Want some more?
[ASHIYA]
Please have mercy, Mom.
[ASHIYA'S MOM chuckles]
[ASHIYA]
Abeno used some kind of power.
Is it something that anyone
who sees yokai can use?
And if it is, I wonder...
Could I learn it too?
[ABENO] Ashiya and I
end up tagging along
with the photography club
to a summer camp of theirs.
It might be a good chance
to teach him something useful.
Next time, "The Seedling."
Yahiko, wanna come with?