[KOMON] Ah. So you no
longer work with Aoi.
[ABENO]
Right.
I'm actually the current
master of the Mononokean.
[KOMON]
That must be tough.
I heard the employee who worked
there before you left as well.
Wait a sec.
Did you know the last employee?
Well, not personally, but Aoi
did mention him in passing.
All that comes to mind now
is that in his earlier days...
[KOMON]
...he was a dangerous sort
who broke many
Underworld taboos.
That said, he'd already left
the Mononokean's service
by the time I heard that.
I sure am glad
that it was Itsuki
who became the next master.
[BIRD YOKAI chirp]
Huh?
[KOMON]
Oh! I'll introduce you.
Meet Chunichi, Chunji,
Chinzo, Chunyon, and Chungo.
I'm sure you boys'll
get along just fine.
How do I tell them apart?
[KOMON]
It took a good while,
but I feel like they've
finally grown up.
We didn't exorcise them earlier
because they were too young and
weak to adapt to the Underworld.
But looking at them now,
I think they would do
just fine there.
[KOMON]
Oh yeah?
So you'll exorcise them?
That would be quite
a load off my shoulders.
Did you hear that, little ones?
You can go to the Underworld.
[BIRD YOKAI chirping]
[chirp]
Should we get started now?
Sure, but I forgot to mention,
only four of the
five are ready to go.
One needs to stay a bit longer.
I don't think you
should exorcise Chungo,
he's still having some trouble.
What kind of trouble?
[ASHIYA]
His plumage is different;
it's like a crescent moon.
[CHUNGO chirping]
[KOMON] He's hasn't quite
gotten the hang of flying yet.
[ABENO, ASHIYA]
Hmm?
Well you can get into
the Underworld by walking,
so I don't think it
would be a problem.
That part would be all right,
but once they got in,
he would have
trouble keeping up.
If they wanted to
fly anywhere as a group,
they'd have to carry him.
[BIRD YOKAI chirp]
I think I get it.
I guess,
but doesn't it seem sad
for only one of them
to be left behind?
He doesn't look to be
any smaller than the rest,
so the problem must
be something else.
Could be a question
of technique.
Might be.
It's too bad he can't just tell
me what the issue is himself.
They talk to each other
and understand me,
but I never worked out
how to interpret those
chirps of theirs.
I trained them all daily.
Told them they couldn't
go to the Underworld
till they'd learned to fly.
And all the others
picked it up pretty quick.
Chungo just can't seem
to stay up in the air, though.
If you don't mind...
[KOMON]
Hmm?
[ABENO] Doubt I'll succeed
where you couldn't,
but could I watch them try to
fly together, Chungo included?
[KOMON]
Sure thing.
Why don't we head to the runway?
[ASHIYA]
The runway?
Abeno!
Can you hear me?
We're ready on our end;
how 'bout you?
I can hear you all right.
You're like an
emergency alert siren.
My ears might bleed.
[ASHIYA]
Did you answer?
Tell you what.
Just wave back
if you can hear me!
Tell 'em to go ahead
and get started!
We're good to go up here!
This is how I first taught them.
By having them fly up
from way down there.
The wind's a bit
gentler over here
than it is on top of the cliff.
The wind?
[KOMON]
Oh yes.
The wind can be somewhat
perilous, even where we are.
[ASHIYA whimpers]
[screams]
I think the bridge is
about to break!
Just hang on!
We're gonna get through this.
No, we're not. We're gonna die!
Looks like it's getting
gusty up around the bridge,
so be careful.
Mind that you don't
get blown away, all right?
[chirping]
[ABENO]
You too, Chungo.
[CHUNGO chirps]
[chirping]
You're kidding.
Before you try to fly again.
I think we should practice
flapping those wings more.
[sighs]
[ASHIYA]
Abeno looks ridiculous.
[KOMON]
He still can't fly.
It doesn't come naturally
to the poor thing.
[ASHIYA]
We might have to exorcise
the siblings
separately after all,
like Komon asked us
to in the first place.
But I would hate to see
Chungo get left behind.
Maybe Abeno will have
a breakthrough with him.
[gasps]
Hey! There's a
strong gust coming.
Hold on tight!
[KOMON]
No! They'll fall!
Oh yeah, I forgot.
There's nothing to worry about.
All of you can fly just fine.
[BIRD YOKAI chirp]
[KOMON] It's a good thing
Chungo wasn't up here with us.
[KOMON screams]
[ASHIYA]
Komon!
[screaming]
Hey, Abeno!
I could use a little help here!
Dude?
Huh?
A crescent moon...?
Wait.
Is that Chungo?
You can fly now?
[ABENO]
Until Komon needed him,
he wasn't even
able to flap properly.
They were told they
can't go to the Underworld
till they learn to fly.
I see now.
That would explain things.
Just try to make sure you don't
take care of them too well.
[ASHIYA]
What's up?
[KOMON] Hey! Stop
fighting up there, will you?
What do you suppose
they're arguing about?
Couldn't tell you.
I've never seen them get
so worked up before.
You have any ideas?
Well I could be wrong,
but still,
it seems to me they're
upset with Chungo
for deceiving them.
He's been hiding the fact
that he could fly all along.
[ASHIYA]
What?
[gasps]
Chungo, is that true?
[chirping]
But flying will only
make life easier for you,
so why would you pretend
that you couldn't do it?
Again, this is just a guess.
But he may have thought that,
as long as he couldn't fly,
you'd let him stay with you.
Just try to make sure you don't
take care of them too well.
[KOMON] I didn't know
what it meant at the time,
but Aoi did warn me not
to care for them too well.
Now, after all these years.
I think I finally understand
what Aoi was getting at.
I wanted them to be happy,
and it seems I succeeded,
but I also made them too
comfortable here in this world.
They're too comfortable here?
[ASHIYA]
So Komon took good care of them,
only for it to
end up backfiring.
[BIRD YOKAI chirping
[KOMON]
Hmm...
Well! That settles it!
I'm gonna tear down the nest
and move somewhere else.
What good is that gonna do?
[KOMON] If their home
here stops existing,
they'll have no
choice but to move on.
The Underworld will be
the only place left for them.
There's no time
like the present.
I'd like to get everything
cleaned up as soon as possible.
Why don't you
boys give me a hand?
[ASHIYA shudders]
[ABENO]
Don't be such an infant.
An infant would
be crawling right now!
Which actually
sounds much safer.
Ha!
You can't just
fling your stuff off the cliff!
Why not?
It's the way I always got
rid of my old things before.
To think that you
even have rules
for how to throw things away.
Being human seems
awfully inconvenient.
[ASHIYA]
Their stares feel so accusing.
I'm destroying the
home they grew up in.
I don't wanna break it down,
but I have no choice.
Huh? Hold up, what's this?
I thought we lost
that a long time ago!
Boy does it take me back.
Yeah? Did you guys use
this for something?
[KOMON] I never used it myself.
It was for them.
Back when I was
building the nest,
I'd put them in there so the
wind wouldn't blow them away.
[BIRD YOKAI chirping]
Look at that.
Guess the youngins
remember it as fondly as me,
[ASHIYA] They seem
to like it an awful lot.
Maybe we should
let them keep it.
Nope, toss it!
[KOMON]
We don't need it.
Not anymore.
Uh?
[ABENO]
Hmm...
I can always sneak
it to them later.
Hey, Ashiya.
D'ya mind checking the time?
[ASHIYA]
Let's see.
It's just after 4:30.
[ABENO] Sun'll be
setting before too long.
We need to head back soon.
It'll be dangerous if we wait
till we can't see
where we're walking.
Komon.
We'd be glad
to keep helping you,
but we need to finish
our work before dark.
It's time we exorcised
the little ones.
That is, unless one of
them would rather stay.
[CHUNGO chirps]
Huh. I'm not sure
what he's saying exactly,
but it seems like he's willing
to go to the Underworld
with his siblings now.
Agreed.
That one's a real trouble-maker.
Okay, Mononokean.
Go ahead.
Mononokean master,
Haruitsuki Abeno,
requesting a
portal to the Under--
[ASHIYA pants]
[ASHIYA]
Abeno!
This is what happens when you
forget cliffs are dangerous!
Anyway, try n' climb back up,
I won't let you fall.
[ABENO]
Ugh... Now, I've done it.
Now, you've done what?
[ABENO] I tried to open
a portal and failed.
It drains me just the same.
The next one'll be rough.
[ASHIYA]
Oh, gotcha.
Well, in that case,
we'd better move to a different
spot in case you collapse.
[KOMON] This place
never changes, does it?
Every time I've seen it,
it looks the same!
[ASHIYA sighs]
Compared to that narrow cliff,
this room seems huge.
[ABENO] Feel free to
join us as well, Komon.
Thanks, but no.
[ASHIYA]
Hmm?
[KOMON]
I'm not coming.
[CHUNGO chirps]
[ASHIYA]
Why not?
I need to find myself
a good place to sleep,
and set up a camp
before the sun goes down.
[ABENO] Would you like
to spend the night here?
It would be no inconvenience
for the Mononokean.
[chirps]
I can find a place just fine
if I start looking right now,
so don't worry about me.
And besides, I've made myself
a promise that the next time
I step foot into the Mononokean
will be the day
I request to be exorcised.
So that's that.
I'll be saying my
goodbyes from right here.
[BIRD YOKAI chirping]
[ASHIYA]
Huh?
[KOMON]
Oh! Hohoho.
[CHUNGO chirps]
[ABENO] Sorry for
pretending I can't fly.
Huh?
Look. That's what
he just said to you.
I'd usually say take our
translator with a grain of salt.
But in this case,
it seems right on the mark.
Ha. That's good to know.
Don't feel too guilty, I'm just
glad I got to see you fly.
This means I get to send you
all off with no reservations.
Chunichi
Chunji
Chunzo.
Chunyon.
And Chungo.
This is the day
when all five of you
finally get to leave the nest.
So I don't have to
take care of you anymore.
[KOMON]
Goodbye.
[ASHIYA] Abeno messed
up the portal earlier,
so this is round two.
[BIRD YOKAI chirping]
[ABENO]
Mononokean.
Connect us to the school roof.
[BIRD YOKAI chirping]
[ASHIYA]
They planned it together?
Hey, Abeno, listen.
[ABENO]
What?
[ASHIYA] I found out why Chungo
acted like he couldn't fly.
[ASHIYA] When they first
started flight practice,
they all
made an agreement.
They decided that
at least one of them
should stay behind
with Komon. Forever.
[ABENO]
Hmm?
And why is that?
Because they were so grateful
to Komon for taking them in.
They could see
that Komon loved them,
so they planned to leave Chungo
behind as a sort of present.
Then Chungo was a farewell gift?
They couldn't just tell Komon,
so they had Chungo
pretend he couldn't fly,
which meant he would have
to stay in the Mundane World.
The Mononokean
translated that for me.
[ASHIYA]
But...
Now, they think that Komon
might be better
off without them.
More carefree.
If Komon would be
happier not having
to take care of any of them,
then there's no need
for Chungo to stay.
He may as well go to the
underworld with his siblings.
At least, that's
my understanding.
So?
So, what?
You'd go to the Underworld
cause Komon said to
or stay here because
of your siblings.
Stop that n' think.
Where is it that you
truly want to be?
[CHUNGO chirps]
Do you want to go to the
Underworld with your siblings?
Or...
Let's go to the Mononokean.
All right, Itsuki?
Would you rather get
to spend more time with Komon?
[CHUNGO chirps]
[CHUNICHI chirps]
[ASHIYA] I guess he decided
to go back to Komon.
[ABENO]
Yeah.
[ASHIYA] You don't think we
should expect a complaint,
do you?
I mean they did say the kids
would be a load off
their shoulders.
Possibly, but still...
Huh?
[ABENO] I get the feeling
that Komon was just pretending
to want the carefree life.
[KOMON whimpers]
[BIRD YOKAI chirp]
[gasps]
[KOMON] I wanted them to be
happy, and it seems I succeeded,
but I also made them too
comfortable here in this world.
[ASHIYA]
Abeno has a good point.
After all, you know
what they say...
[ASHIYA] ..."Two is always
better than one," right?
[ABENO] We were to exorcise five
yokai that had been raised
by the client,
who would stay behind.
However, one opted to remain
in the Mundane World
with the client.
[KOMON]
That must be tough.
I heard the employee who worked
there before you left as well.
[ABENO]
Mononokean.
Before I came,
did Aoi ever use a
different human employee?
All I recall is that
in his earlier days,
he was a dangerous sort who
broke many Underworld taboos.
[LEGISLATOR]
My, you've been working hard.
What? Is something the matter?
You look troubled.
How'd you get injured this time?
Would you believe
me if I told you?
I'd believe you like
the excuse for slacking off.
It isn't so bad,
since it's not my
dominant hand this time.
It's worse cause you've gone
from milking it to faking it.
Huh?
That a Mononokean report log?
I'd planned to look up
just one, but I couldn't quit.
The logs from after Ashiya
became an employee
are just so intriguing.
I couldn't help
but keep reading.
Oh?
Is that the latest issue?
These are formal reports,
not magazines.
Since you made the trip here,
you should stay for tea.
[ABENO]
I have a question.
[LEGISLATOR]
Another human employee?
Look. Uh, just forget I asked.
I'm not sure if this is related
to the subject
you're asking about.
[ABENO]
Go on?
But I am reminded of an
incident in the Mundane World.
One that occurred
before your employment.
[ABENO]
An incident?
[LEGISLATOR] The Justice
should have a record of it.
Secured within
White Sand Prison, of course.
I see.
Don't suppose the Justice
would let me read it.
Now that might prove difficult.
The details of this
incident are classified.
[ABENO]
Classified?
[LEGISLATOR] Whether the
Justice would grant me access
is a semi-open question, but the
simple act of asking about it
might be perceived
as suspicious.
Both by him
and by the Executive.
I see.
[LEGISLATOR]
Now.
That being said, White Sand
Prison's outer premises
are heavily guarded,
but the interior, far less so.
If you can sneak your way
inside, the rest should be easy.
Though, I daresay that's
a very significant "if."
[chuckles]
[ABENO]
Sakae Ashiya.
Ashiya's father and a former
employee of the Mononkean.
The more I learn about him,
the less at ease I feel.
Next time, "The Cobweb."
I hope my gut's
wrong about this.