[ASHIYA]
A request from the Underworld?
To come observe
the Mundane World?
They can do that?
We usually send them
away from here.
[ASHIYA]
If it's so complicated,
why would they go
through all that trouble?
You have any idea?
Abeno?
So they want to observe
a school in our world?
Huh.
Uhh.
All right, let's see
what it says here.
"The purpose
of my visit is this:
To observe a school,
as a necessary step
to advance the standards of
education in the Underworld,"
et cetera, the end.
You skipped way too much!
I got the gist of it.
Our job is to accompany them
during their three-day
observation.
Simple.
[ASHIYA] If we're showing
them around school,
I'll be a bigger
help than Abeno
since honestly he's a bit
lacking in communication skills.
I'll be the perfect guide!
Bring it on.
[SAGA]
What's up, man?
[FUSSHI]
You on your way home, I assume?
[ASHIYA]
Oh, hey guys!
Yeah, I am.
[SAGA] We caught up
to you to ask you something.
Since tomorrow's Saturday,
we're gonna go bowling.
Wanna come with?
Cool! Sounds good!
Uh...
Huh?
Do you have plans already?
It's just...
When is the client supposed
to show up again?
Well, it's probably
not tomorrow.
Never mind, I can go!
[SAGA]
All right, I'm hype!
You guys ready to get wrecked?
[FUSSHI]
Don't go too hard on us, dude.
Morning, Ashiya.
Hey, Fusshi.
Good morning to you too!
[FUSSHI]
Saturday was fun, huh?
[ASHIYA]
As fun as eight games can be.
Saga really didn't want to stop!
I was so sore
I slept all day Sunday.
[FUSSHI]
Same, I was completely wiped.
Morning.
[FEMALE CLASSMATE A]
Good morning you two.
[SAGA]
What's up, Fusshi?
Hey, Ashiya.
[FUSSHI]
Morning, Saga.
Morning.
[EGEN]
Ashiya?
[ASHIYA]
Just ignore them!
[EGEN] If you can see me,
you're Ashiya, right?
Uh...
[EGEN]
That face tells me I'm correct.
I am Egen.
I wanted to thank you
for letting me come
to observe your school.
[ASHIYA]
Observe?
Oh! Right, right, I remember!
From last week!
[FEMALE CLASSMATE A]
From last week?
[ASHIYA]
Augh! I said that out loud!
Abeno!
I haven't seen you since last
week, hardly recognized you!
It's Monday.
Most of us haven't
seen him since last week.
I see you're going
through the ol' textbook, there!
We do have a test
coming up soon!
I should probably study
for it myself, huh?
You got the right idea.
[ASHIYA] So this is the client
Abeno mentioned last week.
The one who came from the
Underworld to observe a school
in the Mundane World for,
what was it, three days?
Hey. Stop staring!
You guys see those bugs
flyin' around the room?
Heh.
[ABENO sighs]
[ASHIYA gasps]
Oh man, Abeno is so pissed off!
I gotta fix this
before he kills me.
[EGEN]
Excuse me. Abeno? Ashiya?
[EGEN] My presence here
may be a hindrance to you,
and for that I apologize.
But observing a school
in the Mundane World
is something I've wanted
to do for a while.
Believe me when I say
I will get the most out of it.
I'll absorb as much as possible,
and take notes on everything.
So I can start a school
where anybody can learn.
For that has always
been my dream.
[ASHIYA] So they're gathering
info to start their own school.
[EGEN]
But my goals are not so selfish!
I must make my dream
come true for all of those
who wish to pursue
higher education!
[ASHIYA]
All right!
I may have just
screwed up a bunch,
but I can make up for that!
I'll use my superior
communication skills
to be the perfect
guide for Egen!
G'morning class.
How is everyone today?
[CHEMISTRY TEACHER]
Let's review.
Atoms and molecules
have nuclei made
of a varying number
of protons and neutrons,
with electrons orbiting
around them in shells.
Those are the basics. Now...
[EGEN sighs]
[EGEN]
Ah! Amazing!
[ASHIYA] What about
this basic chemistry class
is so impressive?
[EGEN]
Every single one of the students
in this room can not only read,
but they can also write!
Superb, truly!
Not to mention how comprehensive
the materials are!
[SAGA]
I got a question.
This "knuckle" thing?
Am I saying that right?
Uh. What is it?
"NaCl"?
That's sodium chloride.
Salt.
[SAGA]
Just call it salt!
[EGEN]
So knowledgeable!
Fantastic instructors.
Wow!
Ah! I'm so envious of
this learning environment!
The big question on my mind
is how much it would cost
to create such an institution
back in the Underworld.
[ASHIYA] I didn't know
that having textbooks,
smart teachers, and the
ability to read and write
was such a big deal.
I guess I take
all that for granted.
What's wrong Ashiya?
Why have you been staring
at the ceiling for so long?
[ASHIYA]
I gotta stop looking at Egen!
[MALE CLASSMATE]
Watcha daydreaming about, buddy?
He was also caught
zoning out this morning!
Try keeping your eyes
on the textbook.
Uh. Sorry, will do.
Yes! He was sleeping!
Close call.
[LEGISLATOR] About the
beast Ashiya encountered
during his errand.
It was, without a
doubt, the Justice.
Did you truly not realize that?
I don't know about you,
but I can't list
more than a few yokai who
would dare enter the Birdcage.
Not to mention someone who would
do so in the form of a beast.
Well, maybe it wasn't
clicking because I was angry.
But when
I consider it now, yeah.
Since he was only
delivering a scroll.
I didn't think there were many
things that could go awry.
And I'd never have imagined
the Justice would appear.
It's entirely possible
that due to this encounter,
the Executive will
find out about Ashiya.
Heh. I was about to
suggest that you be careful,
but I can already tell
that you will be.
Turn to page 87.
Now I know some of you like
to selectively pay attention,
so let me warn you that this
next part will be on the test.
[ASHIYA]
"To Abeno.
I'm really sorry about earlier.
To make it up to you,
I'd like to show Egen
around the school myself.
Maybe take some
of the burden off of you!"
Yeah, that sounds good!
He's still mad at me?
I know I shouldn't have talked
to Egen in front of the class,
but I played it off, didn't I?
And there's no way he
read my note that quick!
Guess who was able to snag
the last croquette bread!
Not that I want it,
but Saga does!
Did you get that just for me?
Thanks, man!
Wait.
[SAGA]
Uh... Where's Abeno?
[FUSSHI]
He was here when we left.
And we weren't
gone all that long.
[ASHIYA]
Huh.
Egen isn't here either.
[EGEN]
Abeno, sir.
Can you tell me
what this is, as well?
That's a place they
call the printing office.
Why?
[EGEN] And what's
the "printing office" for?
Huh?
So, uh...
Whatcha two doing?
Tch!
[ASHIYA]
I still couldn't find you
after I finished eating lunch.
You were hanging out up
here with Egen then, I take it?
You could have asked me
to help explain stuff too, man.
Well, water under the bridge.
I could still give
a tour of the school--
[EGEN]
I'm sorry, Ashiya, was it?
Yes?
[EGEN]
I couldn't help but notice
you changed your clothing.
Why?
Oh, yeah.
I did!
We've got PE next,
so I kinda had to.
That's also why.
I came to get you.
Right, Abeno?
[EGEN]
PE?
Curious name.
What do you study in this "PE"?
You'll see.
But I promise you, it's the
most fun class we have here!
[EGEN]
Your most fun class?
[ASHIYA] You gotta
have PE at your school
in the Underworld, too!
[EGEN] I look forward
to observing this class,
and what makes it so fun!
Um, there's one more
thing I'm curious about.
Go ahead, ask away!
[EGEN]
You are also a human, correct?
That has nothing to do
with your school observation.
Why is he so tense?
[FUSSHI]
Didn't skip today.
It's pretty unusual to
see you out here with us.
Hello? Anybody home?
[EGEN] It's clear as day that
I angered Abeno up on the roof.
I'm lucky he didn't
cancel my observation.
But let's focus on
the positives!
I get to watch PE,
and Ashiya said it's the
most fun class they have!
I must learn all about it!
I won't let any
detail slip by me!
Abeno!
Guess we're on different teams.
No hard feelings, kay!
Hey, check it out!
We're on the
same team this time!
Oh. Yeah!
You can't ignore me now
that we're working together!
What's his problem today?
[EGEN] What are
they learning from this?
It just looks like
they're playing, to me.
Hmm...
I don't think we'll need this
in the Underworld's school
[SAGA]
Nice shot, Ashiya!
[ASHIYA]
All right!
[EGEN]
Huh?
[ASHIYA]
Hey, stop that!
[laughs]
[EGEN]
I see.
In PE, they learn how to
use not just their brains,
but their bodies, as well.
What a fun way to grow.
We'll definitely
be needing this!
It seems there are many
different ways to learn.
[PE TEACHER]
Fushimi! Abeno! Hustle!
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me!
I was supposed to be
explaining things to you,
but I got too caught up in
playing a stupid game of soccer!
[EGEN]
Don't apologize.
I learned a lot
just from watching.
Are you sure it's okay?
Why don't I give you a
proper tour of the grounds
now that school's out?
Would that help?
[EGEN] Thank you,
but there's no need for that.
Huh?
Mononokean master,
Haruitsuki Abeno,
requesting a portal
to the Underworld.
Wait a second!
Was today the
last day of your trip?
[EGEN]
We started over the weekend,
so I got to walk around the
school when it was empty.
On the second day,
I explored other parts
of the Mundane World
with Abeno's supervision.
And to top it all off, I got to
witness an exorcism first hand!
[ASHIYA] I didn't know
there was work on Saturday.
What's that mean? If I didn't
show up to work, then I ditched,
but I was never
told to be there,
so how could I possibly ditch?
Did I ditch?
Did I ditch? Did I ditch?
Is that why Abeno's been
so angry with me all day?
Because I wasn't at work?
[EGEN]
Ashiya.
You don't look so good.
If there's a problem,
you should go to the place where
you can be healed of all things!
The nurse's office!
[ASHIYA] You are way
overestimating that place!
[EGEN]
I see.
So the nurse's office
cannot heal everything.
I'm glad I understand
better, now.
Even if it can't
remedy all ailments,
it's incredible that this school
has a place of healing at all.
This observation really has
been one surprise after another.
[EGEN] Instead of
studying a single subject
for the entire day,
you have set periods of time
dedicated to different subjects,
so you can study more at once.
I also discovered
that you can learn
not only while
sitting at a desk,
but also while exerting your
body, surrounded by your peers.
Schools in this world
really are amazing.
[ASHIYA]
To me, this is all normal.
But the only reason I can even
feel that way about school
is because there are
people just like Egen,
working hard to keep everything
running behind the scenes.
I'm all motivated!
Gotta study harder!
Okay, Egen. Let's go.
[EGEN gasps]
I'm sorry, I got caught up
in our conversation.
Good luck!
See you again, soon!
[EGEN]
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Come to think of it.
How about I walk you partway?
[EGEN] My, that's very
considerate of you.
[ABENO]
Ashiya, you can go home now.
What? Why, I can come
with you, can't I--?
Abeno?
Is he still ignoring me?
[EGEN]
Ashiya?
Please, pay him no mind.
[EGEN] If you think
that's for the best.
So was your visit to a school
in the Mundane World
all you hoped it would be?
[EGEN]
Absolutely!
And thank you
for all of your help.
It was quite difficult
to get permission
to leave the Underworld,
even temporarily.
But it was well
worth all of that effort!
I couldn't see everything
I wanted to in just
three days, however.
Perhaps when we get
the opportunity, I can ask
you and Ashiya more about the
overall school experience--
Forgive me, but...
[EGEN]
Yes?
May I ask you a question
that's been on my mind?
[EGEN]
Of course, what is it?
[ABENO] How exactly
did you get permission
for this school observation?
[EGEN]
Um, by normal means.
Were you forced
to make a deal with someone?
Ordered to investigate
the Mononokean
in exchange for clearance
to go to the Mundane World?
By the Executive?
[EGEN gasps]
And more specifically,
to look into Ashiya?
[EGEN]
Do what?
No!
And there was no reason
why I asked if Ashiya is human.
I just happened to be curious!
Moreover, to suggest
that the mighty Executive
would ask a lowly
yokai such as myself
to investigate the Mononokean in
his stead is simply ridiculous!
Don't you think?
You said this was so you could
open up an Underworld school.
Was all of that talk
about your dream a lie?
[EGEN]
Not at all, that part was true!
"That part"? Seriously?
[EGEN]
Oh, no!
[ABENO]
What a bad liar.
[EGEN]
I'm such an utter fool!
The Executive won't be
happy my cover was blown.
[ABENO]
You're fine.
[EGEN]
Hmm?
Knowing the Executive,
he probably knew
I'd figure it out.
That bastard.
Oh, and just so you know,
I didn't actually think you lied
about wanting to see the school.
If I did get the
feeling you were lying,
I'd have exorcised
you on the first day.
[EGEN] At least you know
I wasn't lying about that.
It's as you suspected.
I was asked to investigate
the Mononokean by the Executive.
But to be clear, he didn't force
me to make a deal with him.
The Executive
has helped a great deal
with my plans to start a school,
so I accepted his request as
a way to repay that kindness.
Believe me.
He has not wronged
me in any manner.
[EGEN] I must go
report to the Executive
as soon as I'm able to.
Since I'm in a hurry, I'll
continue onwards on my own.
If you'll excuse me.
[ABENO]
Egen.
If you can believe it,
Ashiya didn't pick up on this.
He didn't suspect
anything of you,
and he certainly wasn't trying
to make you like
him or something.
You can report exactly
what you saw today.
However, if I can
ask you one thing,
it's that you don't tell
anyone but the Executive
that Ashiya is human.
Oh, and send him my regards.
[EGEN] If Abeno had told me
all of this on the first day,
then perhaps
I wouldn't have asked him
for so much during my time
spent visiting the school.
He must have waited until
now so I could learn more.
For my sake.
Wait.
The door is still here.
That's weird.
Does that mean Abeno's
coming back soon?
Hmm...
I can't just go home.
He's been pissed at me all day!
If I leave now,
it'll only get worse.
Hey. Stop staring!
[ASHIYA] That was
all he said to me today
until they were about to leave!
He never responded
when I talked to him,
and he avoided me
at every opportunity!
I thought he was mad
because I stared at Egen
when I got to class,
so I went out of my way
to be nice to him,
and look where that got me.
[EGEN] Today was the
third day of my observation.
[ASHIYA]
Man, he didn't even tell me
this gig started
over the weekend.
[yawns]
Are you mad at me because
I didn't work over the weekend?
I didn't mean to
not show up to work,
but you didn't tell me
Egen was coming
before the
school week started!
If you've got a problem with me,
or I'm doing something wrong,
tell me straight like
you usually do!
I know you're mad,
but that doesn't mean
you should just ignore me!
[ABENO]
Whoa, whoa.
Calm down,
I'm not mad at you, man.
Huh?
[ABENO] And I know I didn't
contact you over the weekend.
I didn't need you.
Hold on, if you're
not mad at me,
then why have you been
ignoring me all day?
You've barely spoken
two sentences to me,
and you kept avoiding me!
Don't creep
closer to me like that.
See? You've even avoiding
me as we speak!
[ABENO]
That doesn't make any sense!
You're just acting weird!
[ASHIYA]
Then why'd you dodge me all day?
Do I disgust you?
Dude, you gotta respond to that.
[ABENO] I guess I don't really
remember any conversations.
Did we really not talk all day?
You weren't aware of this?
So you didn't ignore
me on purpose?
You just didn't have
anything to say to me?
That's... probably the case.
[ASHIYA]
He subconsciously ignored me.
It wasn't because
I made you mad somehow?
There was no ill-will intended?
And here I was, desperately
trying to brighten the mood
because I thought you
didn't want to talk to me
because of
something stupid I did!
I thought it would make things
even more awkward between us
if I just ignored
you in response.
Do you have any idea
of stressed I was all day
because you wouldn't
say a word to me?
And now I find out you weren't
even doing it on purpose,
you're just
naturally anti-social?
You are such an idiot!
Hold on.
Did I just call Abeno an...
[shrieks]
[sighs]
That's true.
Guess you could say
that I am an idiot
for what I've been worrying
about over the past few days.
Huh?
What was that?
I didn't just hear you
lock that door, did I?
[ASHIYA] You can just
summon the Mononokean!
[ABENO]
What?
[ASHIYA] And by the way,
I didn't mean it.
You're not an idiot!
See ya tomorrow?
You've gotta be
kidding me, come back!
Unlock this door!
He actually went
home, didn't he?
I'll summon the Mononokean
after a quick nap.
I swear, he's got the social
graces of a five-year-old.
I'll get him back tomorrow.
But now that I think about it.
It'd make sense if it seemed
like I was ignoring him.
There was a yokai with us,
so I was already
watching who I spoke to.
And plus, there was that
whole thing with the Executive.
[gasps]
He's too unsuspecting.
[ABENO]
But maybe I'm overcautious.
[YAHIKO]
So bored!
Haruitsuki won't play with me.
Zenko's not home and
Ashiya's, Ashiya!
Ugh, come on!
I don't care who, but someone
better play with me real soon!
Next time, "The Mortar."
Ooo! Who are you?