I'd like you to help me
make a disguise, please.
So that humans can see me
without knowing I'm a yokai.
So can you make
my wish come true?
I just wanna look
like a pretty human.
[ASHIYA]
Uh...
Before we get to the disguise,
maybe we should try
and fix her up a little.
It's sticking!
[ZENKO]
The cracks seal up a bit
and become less visible
if you put water on them.
[ASHIYA]
What? The other eye fell out!
[ZENKO]
You two stay turned around
while I'm helping
her change, okay?
Looks like we've got your
head on pretty good.
My old yukata
fits you perfectly.
[ASHIYA] You've still got a
few cracks here and there,
but we've fixed up all the parts
that look like they could break.
Thanks so much.
Do I look like a real human now?
Not at all.
[KESHI gasps]
[ASHIYA]
All he means
is that your facial
structure is different.
Honestly, her face looks
pretty much transparent to me.
[ABENO]
And to most humans,
she'll just look
like a floating dress.
No... head...
[ZENKO]
Hey, Dad.
Why is that girl... headless?
[ASHIYA] He can't see
her face, he's gonna freak!
Listen, Dad.
You remember that ghost
from around the lookout point?
[ZENKO'S DAD gasps]
Don't tell me that you
brought the ghost in here.
Course not, that's ridiculous!
You're right!
A ghost wouldn't just
stroll out in broad daylight.
Well said.
Everybody knows that ghosts
only come out at night!
[ZENKO'S DAD] All right,
but who's the kid, then?
'Kay, so her name's Keshi,
and she is my oldest cousin's
youngest daughter!
And her parents sent her to
stay with me and my mom
over the summer! Right?
Back me up, guys!
What?
Yeah, and also,
she wanted to go
to the Bon Festival Dance
at the lookout point, but she
didn't bring a yukata with her,
so I'm letting her
borrow my old one.
Right, Abeno?
I want you to help me become
a human just for a day.
And I want it to be during
the Bon Festival dance,
so I can join in.
[ABENO]
We heard about the incident
at last year's Bon Festival
Dance from your daughter, sir.
You can let the
original client know
that the matter
has been put to rest.
It might be best
if you told him that you
exorcised the ghost yourself.
And we would appreciate it
if you kept our
involvement confidential.
If you don't want me
to mention you, fine.
Hmm?
Are you all planning to go
to the Bon Festival Dance?
Yes, sir.
We're going to accompany her.
Yeah.
[ASHIYA]
Mm. Mm.
That better not
be what you're wearing.
[KESHI] Do you wanna look
around before the dance begins?
[ASHIYA]
Sure!
Can we start with
goldfish scooping?
[ZENKO]
Look Hanae.
They've got shaved ice.
So would this count
as a work expense?
[ABENO]
All right.
[ASHIYA laughs]
I knew you were nice deep down.
Hey, Keshi.
Make sure that you don't get
too excited and lose your head.
[KESHI]
I'll be careful!
Hey, ya want me
to grab you a little treat?
They've got a lot of flavors
down at that shaved ice stand.
Strawberry.
Or melon?
Or lemon?
I need you to calm
it down part timer.
And try not to forget
that you're on a job tonight.
Why?
♪ festival music ♪
[ASHIYA]
Hmm?
Keshi. Something wrong?
[KESHI]
I'm just nervous.
[GIRL screams]
[GIRL cries]
[KESHI]
I wanna be near people,
but seeing me
always scares them.
And if it happens again,
I won't get to dance.
There's no need to worry
'cause we'll be
careful for you, okay?
You look cute.
So just focus on
having a good time.
[COUNCIL HEAD]
Zenko! Welcome!
Ah!
And your name's Keshi,
right, little one?
I've been told that
you're a first timer!
Did my dad tell you?
Do you want to dance?
Come right this way;
it's just about to start.
♪ Bon Dance song ♪
[KESHI]
No one's afraid of me this time.
They're actually
including me in the circle,
I'm part of the group!
[KESHI] It's exactly
like I hoped it would be.
[KESHI]
I get to dance.
And this time, I'm not alone.
Join us, young man!
[KESHI]
Come on!
Don't be shy.
[KESHI]
After all this time,
my wish finally came true today!
Okay, bye!
You kids come back
and visit us next year.
[ZENKO] The guy who ran the
shooting booth had a nice voice.
[ASHIYA]
The one you shot?
Well, come to think of it,
he did have a pretty
nice voice, huh?
Yeah. But you know, I think
you have a nice voice too.
[ASHIYA]
Really? Me?
[ZENKO]
It's not that big a deal.
[ASHIYA]
Do you think here might work?
It'll do.
Mononokean Master
Haruitsuki Abeno,
requesting a portal
to the Underworld.
Go ahead.
Whoa.
[KESHI gasps]
I almost forgot, I still need
to give you your yukata.
[ZENKO]
You're good.
It looks really nice
on you, so keep it.
[KESHI] I had more fun today
than I ever had before.
And it's all because these
three were so nice to me.
Thank you so much for
helping me look human.
This day was perfect.
You made my wish come true.
Would you like me to walk
you home tonight, Zenko?
[ZENKO]
You don't have to.
You say that...
Do not let my daughter walk
home by herself in the dark.
I'm sure you'd be
fine either way,
but your dad said
he'd feel better
if he knew you weren't alone.
Well, in that case,
you and Abeno are welcome
to stop by my house and rest.
Wanna come?
[ABENO]
Thanks. But no.
[ZENKO]
All right.
Are you okay?
You sound exhausted.
[ABENO]
Yeah, I'm fi...
Huh?!
[ASHIYA]
Abeno?
[ZENKO]
Huh? What's wrong?
[ASHIYA]
I don't get it.
He only collapses like this
when he opens a portal to
the Underworld twice in a day.
But if he did another job,
why didn't he tell me?
So what gives, Oisuke?
You say your home's nearby?
Yes, you can find my home
beneath the great sands.
Did we need to crawl
under the slide?
[screams]
Huh?
Who could've put such a
heavy thing there?
It'll crush my
poor home into pieces!
No sweat. I'll move it for ya!
[BOYS]
Hey, you!
[shrieks]
That's our watermelon,
so back off of it.
We're tryn'a play
split the melon here!
And we called dibs on
this spot first, so beat it!
[BOY A]
Yeah, scram!
I'm very sorry for
getting in your way.
But if you guys wouldn't mind,
I only came here to
look for something I lost.
So ya lost somethin'?
And how long will it
take you to find it?
Uh... Let's see.
Um, between three
and five minutes?
Okay, well, we're
gonna be finished
in about ten seconds.
So we should go first.
Um, gotcha.
Lemme just talk
to my friend about it.
Didja hear all that?
Whadda we do?
Ten seconds, right?
And that's all you need?
[BOY A]
Blond hair.
[BOY B]
A scraped-up face.
[BOY A]
And no mercy in his eyes.
This guy's bad news!
[BOY B]
It's a kimono wearing gangster!
[BOYS] We've picked a fight
with one dangerous dude!
If you aren't
done in ten seconds...
...then my bro here's
gonna teach you a lesson.
It sure is bright out here.
We can just wait.
You kids go ahead
and enjoy your game.
But once you finish,
it's our turn,
and we'll take our sweet time.
We're done for even
if we let 'em go first!
It'll be okay. We just have
to finish in ten seconds!
Here goes!
I'll start the countdown!
Ten, nine, wait, uhh...
You're gonna hit
this fruit with a stick?
If you do that, you'll crack
my home like a nut!
This is bad.
Stop!
[echoing]
Stop. Stop.
Holy cow. You disarmed him
with a dropkick!
You gangster guys are awesome!
Gangsters?
Ah, you found my sweet home!
So I'm gonna be exorcising
Oisuke over there.
Think you can keep those grade-
schoolers from following me?
Yeah, not a problem.
You're coming with me, Hairball.
[ASHIYA] If this request
had come from the Executive,
Abeno would've
done it by himself.
I wouldn't even know about it.
And this time,
if I hadn't stopped him,
he would've done
something reckless again.
[ABENO] Mononokean Master
Haruitsuki Abeno,
requesting a portal
to the Underworld.
It's ready for you.
Your home didn't get
damaged at all, did it?
[OISUKE]
No, not even a bit.
My home is in perfect condition.
All thank to Ashiya. He risked
his body to protect it.
It was about to be smashed,
but he intervened
with a flying kick!
[ABENO]
Still, I can't help but feel
that the acrobatics
were unnecessarily risky.
Ashiya's a clutz.
And if he'd screwed up,
we'd've had to dig a
grave in that sandbox.
[OISUKE]
Pardon, Abeno.
Huh?
I truly am grateful
to both of you.
Might I ask that you relay
my thanks to Ashiya?
[ABENO]
I'd be glad to.
[BOY B]
Okay, now it's my turn!
To the left, to the left!
Wait, do mean my left or yours?
Oisuke asked me to
pass along his thanks.
For how you risked your body
to protect his home, and all.
Did he really say that?
'S cute how much he loved it.
His lil home.
Yeah, it worked out okay,
but you didn't need
to jump in there.
I couldn't just stand by
and watch
while you got whacked
trying to protect his home.
Like, wham!
That wasn't a possibility
I gave much thought to.
[ASHIYA]
You don't have to lie.
I know you were ready
to take that hit.
I was worried for you.
I thought you were gonna get
hurt right in front of me again.
You didn't have to get
that scratch on your cheek.
I could've caught you.
But since you didn't tell me
you were taking jobs
from the Executive,
I didn't know you'd fall.
I get why you kept
those jobs a secret,
and I appreciate that you
were just trying to protect me.
But from now on,
please tell me about
every job you get
even if they come
from the Executive.
So that next time
you act recklessly,
I can try and catch you,
or at least break your fall.
'N also,
I'm not sure if you already knew
this, but, believe it or not.
[ABENO]
Hmm?
I'm actually an employee
of the Mononokean.
What?
I know I'm not that strong.
But what I lack in muscle,
I've got in spirit.
So you can count on
my help with any job.
Oh, so let me get this straight,
you're saying you're an
employee of the Mononokean?
Crazy.
I thought you
were just a stalker.
Nope, I get money!
Side note,
I'm not your only worker.
Right, bud?
I knew he worked for me.
[BOY B]
Hey!
It's your turn to try it,
okay, Blondie?
I'll tell ya the rules
while we blindfold ya!
[BOY B]
No need to be nervous,
we're not gonna make it
harder for you or anything.
Just think of that
watermelon like it's the head
of a rival gang member!
[BOY A] And think
of the stick like the pipe
you use to break windows as
you vroom by on your bike!
[ASHIYA]
Hey, Abeno!
Huh?
You've got this.
I'll give you directions!
[EXECUTIVE]
Itsuki.
As I'm sure you realize,
I'll have more requests for the
Mononokean in the days to come.
They may prove challenging.
So I do hope you'll
allow Hanae Ashiya
to provide you with assistance.
But of course,
that's assuming the human
opts to stay as your employee
when we both know he may as well
choose to run
for the hills, right?
[ASHIYA]
Be careful!
You're about
to take a step down!
[BOY A]
Oooh! Nice!
[BOY B]
Sweet! You can do it!
[BOY A]
Way to go! You got this!
Just keep on goin' straight!
[BOY A] Bet'cha two marbles
and a slinky he gets it.
[BOY B]
Deal.
You're there! Go!
[ABENO]
Executive.
Your plan failed.
You nailed it!
With just one try!
What a gangster!
Wow!
This watermelon looks so tasty!
Yeah. We tried to
head out at first,
but the kids were
just so insistent.
It would've been kinda awkward
if they had decided
to follow us back.
Mononokean, let's go
over next week's schedule.
Why the wardrobe change?
Could it mean that he's doing
another job after this?
[ABENO]
I can hear you,
and we're both done for the day.
Is that the truth?
Well, if the Mononokean
says so, it must be true.
[ABENO]
Ashiya.
Yeah?
[ABENO]
About the Executive's requests.
We don't have any currently.
We don't, right?
That said,
the next time we
get a job from him...
...please help.
[ASHIYA]
Was it that hard to say that?
But at least it sounds like he's
trying to be honest with me.
I'm glad to hear it.
And I'm ready whenever.
It's pretty lukewarm.
[ASHIYA]
What do you expect from me!
I tried to cool it in water!
[ABENO]
Mononokean.
School starts up
again next week.
So we'll need to
adjust the schedule.
[ASHIYA] Felt like this
summer lasted forever, but...
...it was too fast
at the same time.
Huh.
Tastes good.
[ASHIYA] Mom passed out
and had to go to the hospital.
I see the flickering
shadow of a yokai.
And now my sister's come home!
Next time, "The Shadow"!
The Ashiya family secret
will be revealed at last!
Possibly.