[FUSSHI]
Let us in, Abeno.
We wanna have a pillow fight.
I'm good.
[FUSSHI]
We insist.
I warned them that
this was a bad idea.
C'mon man,
pillow fights are fun!
Let us in and we'll show you.
[SAGA] We already asked
Mr. Fuji for permission.
He talked to the inn's manager,
and he said to
knock ourselves out!
Or knock each other out.
[FUSSHI] We even got a hold
of a bunch of unused pillows!
[SAGA] Yeah,
so this is basically, like,
a club requirement.
[FUSSHI] Don't hole
yourself in there all night.
Come out and play!
We'll have fun!
Aw yeah!
[ASHIYA] Looks like he had to
open his fort to let Fuzzy out.
I want a good, clean match.
[YAHIKO]
No fair.
I wanna have a pillow fight.
Why can't I play too?
Are we ready?
Then go!
Hyaah!
Abeno! We're supposed
to throw the pillows,
not smack each
other with 'em.
[ASHIYA]
This isn't a pillow fight.
It's a pillow massacre!
Your left hand?
That's correct.
For real?
You dizzy at all?
Not even a bit!
And I didn't hold
my breath this time either!
[ABENO]
Hmm...
Well then. I suppose you pass.
Aw, sweet!
Huh?
How are you gonna pass him
when he got four out of
his ten guesses wrong?
[ABENO]
Hmm...
Guessing which hand a yokai's
in is really hard, okay?
It's a lot harder than sensing
one's direction from far away.
[SAGA]
Ashiya!
Abeno!
The bus is here!
You guys comin' or what?
Time to go!
Thanks, Saga!
Give us a second.
Be right there.
Oh, by the way, Abeno.
And this applies to you
and Fuzzy as well
[YAHIKO]
Hmm?
Because of you three,
I've gotten a lot better
at using this ability.
So thanks for training me
these past few days.
I mean it. Really.
So... you all good now?
Yeah.
I feel way better.
Then during work tomorrow,
we'll test you for real.
See if that clairvoyance
is still useless.
[YAHIKO]
You trashboat.
[MR. FUJI]
Okay! Line up, everyone!
[ASHIYA] I thought
I already passed the test.
When does it end?
[MR. FUJI]
Squeeze in a bit if you can.
Rumor has it you and
Abeno are the only ones
who didn't take
a single picture.
We kinda forgot.
It's easy to get
distracted out here.
So, yeah.
See ya later.
Don't work too much!
[ASHIYA]
I won't.
[YAHIKO]
Bye-bye.
Hey!
It's occupied.
[gasps]
Look. It's a bit
difficult to talk
when you're acting
so wary of me.
[ASHIYA] No offense,
but what are you doing here?
Oh. Did Itsuki not pass
my message along to you?
No, he didn't.
He intended to apologize.
[ASHIYA]
For what?
Itsuki and the Justice
told me about your encounter.
How you met the Executive.
I'm sure it was a
terrifying experience.
[LEGISLATOR]
First, allow me to apologize
for his treatment of you.
I'm truly sorry.
Oh, um, well, I'm all
right now, so don't worry.
Heh.
And now for a question:
Might you be a betting man?
Uh, what do you mean?
Like gambling?
I've brought some things that
could make it all up to you.
[ABENO]
Isn't that--
[LEGISLATOR]
Itsuki.
[ASHIYA]
Hmm...
So can I ask what you
have inside the boxes?
[LEGISLATOR] One of them,
the losing box, is empty.
To find out what's inside the
winner, you have to pick it.
And what happens
if I choose right?
Uh?
[LEGISLATOR]
Hmm...
The truth of it is, I made a
little wager with the Executive.
Should you manage
to pick the winning box.
Your permission to
enter the Underworld
will be conditionally restored.
Huh?
What?
You're kidding.
You can really lift my ban?
Yeah.
And the Executive
agreed to this?
Do you think that
I'd suggest this if he hadn't?
I even convinced him
to sign a contract.
Care to read it later?
How the hell did you
make that happen?
[laughs]
Let me assure you, I did nothing
that wasn't my prerogative.
I oversee the Mononokean,
and therefore,
when one of its
employees is harmed,
it's my responsibility
to take action.
[ASHIYA] I'm grateful
that the Legislator did this.
So, I can never come
back to the Underworld?
[JUSTICE]
If you accept that condition,
the Executive promises
to leave you be.
[ASHIYA] But if going back
to the Underworld could mean
the Executive comes
after me again,
then I might be better off
letting things stay as they are.
You're quite intent on
protecting this human.
As the master of the Mononokean,
you're above our laws.
So if you don't want me
to dispose of this threat,
do it yourself.
[ASHIYA] Lifting the ban
might make trouble for Abeno.
Better if I just do nothing.
Thank you.
--But I don't think tha--
--[ABENO] Hey. Trashboat.
Eh?
[ABENO]
Pick the winner.
Huh?
If you pick wrong,
I'll revoke your passing grade.
[ASHIYA]
What's he talking about?
[gasps]
Okay. I'll pick.
Make your choice.
Right or left.
Be calm.
The left one.
[JUSTICE]
Looks like we have a winner.
I know that voice.
Did you hear everything?
Justice?
[JUSTICE]
Yeah.
I caught every last word.
Congrats.
It looks like you won the bet.
As promised, I'll lift the ban.
On the condition
we discussed, of course.
I can go tell the
Executive right away.
Wait a second.
Is this something you
can tell me about?
[JUSTICE]
The condition that was set
between the
Executive and Legislator
is that each and every time
you enter the Underworld,
the Legislator has
to get down on his knees
and beg the Executive.
[LEGISLATOR]
Hmm?
That's peculiar.
The condition I recall agreeing
to was somewhat different.
[JUSTICE]
Yeah.
I made that up.
But I honestly believe
that it could've been
a good alternative.
Anyway, I guess you want me
to say the real condition.
Hanae Ashiya is only allowed
to enter the Underworld
when I can accompany him.
That is the deal.
You have to be with me?
And since the
Justice is currently present,
that condition is fulfilled.
Why, you could enter right
now with no problems.
Whoa there,
Legislator, hold on a second.
You're gonna
make me fall in there!
It's okay if you come in.
I've given you my word Ashiya,
and I have no
reason to lie to you.
Oh. I don't think you'd lie.
And I really am grateful
that you helped me
to get my ban lifted, but...
...the thing is, I--
[ABENO] I'm not letting him
back into the Underworld.
So, yeah, when you
talk to the Executive,
feel free to let
him know that too.
'Kay. Will do.
It's too bad, seeing as
you picked the winning box.
Ah.
So be it.
We have to abide by
the master's decision.
And here I was planning
to throw a little celebration
once your ban had been lifted.
What a shame.
Huh?
[JUSTICE]
A celebration?
Does that mean you made food?
[LEGISLATOR] Yes. I did
prepare a few appetizers.
[ASHIYA] I picked the winning
box, like Abeno told me too.
But was I actually supposed
to pick the losing box?
[JUSTICE] Well,
since Itsuki's forbidden it,
it seems unlikely
that you'll get a chance
to enter the Underworld again.
And judging from the way you
acted earlier, it seems like
you have a personal
aversion to coming here.
[ASHIYA]
Mm.
I can understand.
But anyway,
if you ever do decide to
come back to the Underworld,
I'll be at your side.
Partly to keep an eye on you.
Should I believe
that you're a threat.
And I mean to any
yokai in the Underworld.
I won't hesitate to give
you a good, hard bite.
But for as long as
you aren't a threat.
I will protect you, as an
employee of the Mononokean.
[ASHIYA] That certainly
isn't the same as saying
I'd be welcome there.
But regardless, someday,
I may decide to go back.
[ASHIYA] If I ever do return,
I'll be counting on your help.
[sighs]
Did I miss something?
Should I have picked
the empty box?
Huh?
Just thought I'd ask,
since you don't want me going
to the Underworld after all.
Oh. Yeah. I see.
Well, don't worry about it.
You did good.
In fact, the Legislator
deliberately put a yokai
in the winning box to be
sure that you would pick it.
Huh?
So the Legislator knew that I'd
learned how to sense yokai?
But you didn't
tell him, did you?
[ABENO]
Sure didn't.
I haven't even spoken a word
to him since I trained you
at that summer camp.
Then, how else
could he have known?
[ABENO]
I can think of one other source
he might've heard it from.
Mononokean?
How are you so bad
at playing dumb?
Wait! So are you
saying that he rigged the bet
against the Executive
and the Justice?
That's crazy,
even if he is the Legislator!
Oh no.
What if the Executive finds out?
[ABENO] No need to worry
about what happened
with the Executive now.
From the looks of things,
the Legislator's lost
patience with him.
Say what?
The Legislator's wrath
is a thing to be feared.
He won't risk
incurring it twice.
[ASHIYA]
Wrath?
That's a strong word.
Was the Legislator
really that mad?
[ABENO] Judging from
the smug look on his face
when you picked
the right box, yes.
[JUSTICE]
Are you satisfied?
[LEGISLATOR]
Hm?
No, not in the slightest.
What I wanted, was for Ashiya
to re-enter the Underworld.
And for you to have to tell the
Executive that it happened.
But Itsuki had
to go and stop me.
Well, on the bright side,
at least you won the bet.
If I could just see
the look on the Executive's face
when he finds out he lost,
perhaps I would feel
a bit more satisfied.
I'm pretty sure he'd prefer
if you weren't there for that.
You're probably right.
Well, anyway, looks
like the matter's resolved.
That should be the end
of our internal feud.
I hate when you two fight.
I always end up getting
stuck in the middle.
It can be a real headache.
[LEGISLATOR]
The blame for this one
lies with the Executive
and his aggressiveness.
I'm of a gentle and
kind-hearted temperament.
Yet I just can't
forgive him this time.
[sighs]
Gentle, you say.
Huh.
Yeah, here's the thing,
if that were true,
you could keep things
civil without having me
as your go between.
When you do see
the Executive again,
you'd better be nice to him.
That understood?
Fine.
By the way,
you've done a lot for me
these past few days.
When next we meet,
I'll cook you something.
Until then,
give the bird my regards.
It's a ghost!
It's just a tanuki.
Come on, Zenko, would you mind
walking a little slower for me?
Yes, I would mind.
Anyway, the lookout
point's just ahead.
[ZENKO'S DAD] Zenko,
is that one also a tanuki?
That was strange.
But I don't know.
Are you sure what we saw up
there was really a ghost?
Oh yeah. I'm sure.
She had long black hair
and a flowing white dress.
And her hand was see-through.
Huh? Hold on,
you mean you saw her hand?
Interesting.
All I could see
was a girl's hair
and dress
floating in the air.
Guess it was too dark for
me to make out the body.
[ZENKO'S DAD] It was probably
just some kid pulling a prank.
[ZENKO]
I wonder...
If dad could only see
the hair and clothes...
Oh, well.
I gotta call the neighborhood
council head now.
Why call him?
'Cause I saw an apparition,
and... he said to call if I did.
He's trying to decide
if he should cancel
the Bon Festival Dance
this year, you see.
Huh?
[ZENKO'S DAD] There was a
related incident last year.
A child fell and
was injured as a result.
Oh, I think I get it.
Her translucency.
It reminded me
of how Fuzzy looks.
It could be that this ghost
is really just a yokai.
[ZENKO'S DAD]
Hey, Zenko.
Remember those
weird priests we met?
[ZENKO]
Which priests?
What temple were they from?
One's name was Abeno.
Think the other was Ashida?
[ZENKO]
No. It's Ashiya, Dad.
[ZENKO'S DAD]
Right, right.
Point is, they're psychics.
Let's get them
to deal with this.
That's it.
Do you sense a yokai?
[ASHIYA]
Mm-hm.
[gasps]
At least I think it's a yokai,
but what if my yokai
radar also works on ghosts?
[ZENKO] It's broad daylight
and you're still scared?
We could always wait
for Abeno to get here.
He's finishing up a job, right?
Yeah, he is, but I'll be fine.
Let's do this!
The presence is over that way!
[ZENKO] Are you using me
as a human shield?
[ASHIYA]
Oh crap, she sees us!
It's not a ghost, okay?
Not a ghost.
She's just a yokai.
Totally safe!
Just a yokai!
Don't be scared, you'll be fine!
G'afternoon, how's it going?
My name's Ashiya and
I work for the Mononokean.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm here today because I
received a request to help you!
Finally, it took you
long enough to find me!
Mononokean,
make me a human being!
Make you human? But why?
No.
Her head.
I killed her.
Wait, is this a wig?
Put my hair back right now!
[ASHIYA shrieks]
[ABENO]
Hmm?
Welcome back, Master.
[ABENO]
What's he done this time?
So I found the ghost
Zenko mentioned.
It was really a yokai
just like we thought.
If you'd like to meet her,
she's right there.
We were careful not to
leave any pieces behind.
[ABENO]
Can you still hear us?
Of course I can.
This kind'a thing happens
to me pretty often actually.
It'll stick back on
if ya use water.
You can call me Keshi,
who might you be?
My name's Abeno, and I'm
the Master of the Mononokean.
A pretty good while ago.
I was talkin' to another yokai.
They told me they knew
of a magical place
that could make
my wish come true.
And so I started
searching far and wide,
looking everywhere I could
for the Mononokean.
But no matter how hard
I tried, I couldn't find you.
Then I had the idea
to make you find me.
I started wearing
a wig and clothes,
so that humans would
see me and get scared.
I made as much of
a fuss as I could,
so you'd have to come stop me.
These rumors about a ghost.
They've been going
around for about a year.
It seems like she's a pretty
determined yokai.
Tell me, Keshi.
What is the wish
you'd ask us to grant?
I want you to help me become
a human just for a day.
And I want it to be during
the Bon Festival dance
so I can join in.
You want to be human?
Ashiya already told me
that the Mononokean isn't able
to turn a yokai into a human
for real and that's okay.
I don't mind it.
But instead,
I'd like you to help me
make a disguise, please.
So humans can see me,
without knowing I'm a yokai.
[ZENKO] Going around
fulfilling requests from yokai
sounds like pretty hard work.
But to my father at least,
nothing's harder than
remembering Ashiya's name.
Next time, "The Removal."
It should be kind of fun.