Goodnight, Romeo.
Parting is such sweet sorrow.
The school! The bomb's in locker D-12!
I've regained visual!
No! Stop!
Five, what...?
Excuse me. I'm here to turn myself in.
What?
I'm Sphinx Number One.
Freeze, buddy!
Don't do anything stupid!
Hands behind your head!
You gotta be kiddin' me.
Yes, we're checking to see if it's really him.
Captain! Sphinx just surrendered!
What? Is this a joke?
Got it. I'll take care of it right away, sir.
Yeah. Things are still, uh, up in the air.
Sphinx kid's telling us to
get a detective named Shibazaki.
He won't say anything until we do.
I'm Kurahashi, First Investigation.
Shibazaki is currently on leave.
I'll hear what you have to say instead.
Why did you turn yourself in?
Why would you commit these crimes?
You can start by telling me who you are.
I've set a timer on the nuclear device we stole.
Huh?
If you wanna stop the clock,
I suggest you agree to my demands.
What demands?
Hm? What's wrong?
Huh? Oh. Nothing. I went to see Haruka.
Really?
You could've at least mentioned it
first. I wanted to give her a few things.
Right. Jeez. She's so grown up.
It's funny how kids turn into
adults in the blink of an eye, y'know?
Something happen?
Hm? No.
Weirdo.
Hey. This guy down there looks suspicious!
What?
You're creepin' my wife out, man.
Just keeping an eye on you so I
can come with when you go see Mamiya.
And if anything happens?
Fine. I'm prepared for the worst.
Then I have an important request to make of you.
Sure!
Buy me some cigarettes.
What?
It's a superstition.
When I feel like I'm about to hit on something big,
there's a brand I always smoke.
Right.
A press conference?
What could he wanna talk about?
I don't know. He just said that it should be at 8 PM,
and requested that we gather
all the different news outlets.
If we don't hold this thing.
I'm afraid this kid will actually set off an atomic bomb.
So you plan to negotiate with a terrorist?
I plan to think of the safety of our citizens.
He said as long as we give him this,
he'll turn the bomb over to the police.
We can't trust 'im!
They have kept their promises in every
crime announcement they've made so far.
But this is different.
It's the first time they're making a demand.
And?
If he's lying and the worst were to happen?
I doubt it will, but, I'll be accountable.
Yes?
Detective Shibazaki, Metropolitan PD.
I'd like to speak with Shunzo Mamiya.
I'm sorry, but he's not receiving
any visitors at this time.
Please tell him I'm here on behalf
of the children that disappeared.
All 26 of them.
One moment please.
Yeah, a pack of Shinsei, please.
Looks like we don't have 'em.
This is the eighth place I've tried.
You want the truth. But are you prepared to hear it?
Damn right.
I imagine your resolve must be
strong if it brought you here to see me.
Yes, and after 15 long years, at that.
I'm sure you don't remember me, but,
I have quite the personal grudge to settle with you, too.
You may leave us.
I don't know the details.
All the locals said was that
the suspect had turned himself in.
Five!
They've never seen a case like yours before.
Ya need more tests, so try to take it easy.
He's mine. I won't let anyone else have him.
You're just a youngster.
So, you probably can't imagine it,
but Tokyo used to be a burnt field.
It's been almost 70 years.
70 years since the end of that damned war.
However, this country remains a defeated one.
Even now our spirit is that of a loser, no shred of
dignity left, and no pride left to stand up to anyone.
This country must become truly independent once more.
So that's why you implemented the Athena Plan.
Exactly.
To artificially create humans whose intelligence
and sensitivity surpass that of ordinary people.
To raise personnel more useful than any weapon.
To win, again. That was the goal.
The plan was considered a failure.
But if you ask my opinion,
it became a fine foundation for the country.
A fine foundation? What are you talking about?
Most of those poor orphans were killed.
And two who lived are now terrorists.
Sphinx came back to commit patricide.
Their goal is to kill you all.
So they took the last thing you expected,
and the last thing you want the
rest of the world to know about.
We need to prove that when this country's
constitutional interpretation changed,
they started secretly producing atomic weapons.
It's imperative we secure the target alive.
That's the only way to get our evidence.
Please do not forget that.
Allow me to ask you, since you know so much.
Do you plan to bring this to the authorities?
You realize, no matter what a single detective shouts,
it'll be no more than a tiny voice in a storm of noise.
It will be swallowed up.
The voice will never reach a single soul.
Even if you're right,
I'll continue to shout the truth.
You won't get away with this one. None of you will.
Excuse me, sir.
My assistant here tells me Sphinx has surrendered.
We have just received word that someone
identifying himself as "Sphinx" has turned himself in.
The suspect has demanded a press conference tonight.
He said in a deposition that he
will explain everything at 8 PM.
Twelve!
Sphinx surrendered! Nine turned himself in.
I don't get it.
Why would Nine go to the police?
Do you know? What should we do?
I dunno. You wanna go over there?
Come on, let's ride that!
Kurahashi, please!
Do this for me. All I need's a quick look!
It's impossible.
Even within the department, only a
select few have access to the suspect.
Can't you do something? I know
him better than anyone else!
Shibazaki!
I'm taking care of this.
He specified the conference's location.
Any idea what he wants to talk about?
You'll likely have interference
from different quarters.
No matter what happens, do not let anyone else have him.
Yeah.
What's that?
The location of the press conference.
You "found" that note. Stumbled across it.
It's a trap, no matter how you look at it!
There's always an ulterior
motive when they turn 'emselves in.
Besides, there are two perps. Where's the other one?
Yeah, right? Y'guys think he'll
bomb the press conference or somethin'?
Hey, you smokin' now?
No, probably not.
I bet our guys are ready for that.
Come on, we should at least mention it, though.
How? We're all suspended, remember?
We walk in there and tell them before it's too late!
Here, take 'em!
Why the hell didn't you wait for me?
Because you were takin' too damn long.
You met with Mamiya, didn't you?
Yeah.
I'm gonna follow this through
to the end, no matter the cost.
But there's something I still need to see first.
Their future. With my own eyes.
I told you. Only the Japanese police
are being allowed to escort him there.
That's the Sphinx boy's demand, not mine.
I see.
You comply with the demands of a terrorist,
and yet refuse the American government?
Do I understand correctly?
No. That's not what I'm saying.
I certainly hope you won't disappoint us.
You wouldn't wanna let my bosses down.
You're wasting your time.
If you want something, you should just take it.
Ever since your airport stunt.
We've been on less than good
terms with the Japanese government.
We can't afford to interv...
What about an attack from an
armed group of unknown affiliation?
That wouldn't have anything whatsoever to do with us.
Look. Isn't this cute? Here.
Thank you.
Nine's holding a press conference tonight.
So, what do you think's gonna happen to him?
Will we ever see him again?
Eh. Doesn't matter.
Really. S'not my concern.
Twelve...
I mean it. I have no right to face Nine.
I left. Betrayed him.
You're being so stupid!
When I saw you there. When you came for me.
I was so relieved, and so happy!
I think he'll feel like... he'll feel that way, too!
Only press designated by the police allowed.
I am the police.
Hey! Did you take my badge?
Shibazaki!
Here.
ETA is in 15 minutes, at 19:20 hours.
Stay alert.
Trace all vehicles that've left the police
department in the past three hours and make it quick.
All of 'em?
Get to it!
Yes, ma'am.
Go, hit the gas!
Do not let them stop us! Cut through!
Right!
The transport's a decoy!
Okay, remove D-6 and E-7.
Understood, ma'am.
This one?
Clarence.
All right. We'll attempt to detain it.
Slow down!
Oh just calm your tits.
She's here.
Shit!
So be it.
You're relieved of your duties,
Five, effective immediately.
This your idea of a joke?
Multiple instances of insubordination,
not to mention breakin' the law.
Your weakened physical condition pretty much sealed it.
It's regrettable. It really is, Five. I'm sorry.
It's me. The situation's changed.
Have another vehicle pursue the target.
Idiot. What are you thinkin'?
You want to be our enemy, now?
I was very clear.
I'm not going to let anyone else have Nine.
Nine. I always wanted to beat you, but I never could.
Did you realize this was going to be my last opportunity?
Here we are.
Time was always going to catch up with us.
I finally get to thank you, though.
The only reason I was able to survive
until this point is because of you.
Yes. All along, you are what gave me a reason to live.
Five. I'm sorry.
I know.
Now's as good a time as any to part ways, don't you think?
So. Let me help you live this time, Nine.
Good luck, Nine. Goodbye. I'm going on ahead.
Five!
What the hell? Why aren't they here?
Good evening. This is Sphinx Number One.
Because of your interference, today's
press conference has been cancelled.
Oh god.
Isn't this the press conference?
It's cancelled?
This is an automatic broadcast set to
air if the press conference fell through.
It will be the last message.
That being understood, all negotiations are
off the table, and the final bomb is in place.
It is an atomic bomb and will
detonate without fail at 10 PM.
Unfortunately, no one can stop it now.
So I guess that's it. People of Japan, sayonara.