Who's there?
Lisa?
Lisa, is that you?
There you have it. The answer to your riddle.
Oh, ho!
I hope you boys realize the joker
you're wavin' around is not a toy.
The cops have connected it.
They definitely know we were
the ones who stole the plutonium.
I will take you both out myself!
Hey. I got stuck in Shibuya.
It totally started raining cats and dogs.
Yeah, like out of nowhere.
And of course, I just got my hair done.
Uh-oh. The cops just stopped two guys.
They look like high schoolers.
That sucks. They're both kinda cute.
What can I say? I like bad boys.
The expert analysis of the bomb we recovered
from the building next to the Shirahige Shrine in
Katsushika has produced some interesting results.
This device was an "ammonium nitrate fuel oil
type" commonly used as an industrial explosive.
From the model number left on the electric detonator.
We've been able to trace its purchase back to a
demolitions manufacturer called Showa Gunpowder.
Wait a minute.
Therefore...
These parts commonly used by terrorists to
make bombs are just available to the public?
As long as their application form has been approved,
yes, someone could gain access to these items.
Please continue.
Yes sir.
The suspect posed as an employee of Hanabayashi,
a building contractor.
They forged the application and illegally obtained
someone else's credit card info to purchase the gunpowder.
How were they able to use some else's credit card?
Probably through an illegal website from Russia or China.
A clean card's info can be bought for next to nothing.
Because they used a form of virtual currency to
buy the card, the transaction is impossible to trace.
My subordinates are currently combing through
surveillance footage from Showa Gunpowder.
We hope to find an image of
the suspect picking up his order.
In addition, we have the relevant
usage history of the credit card.
They bought electrical tape and a delivery box. As
well as a soba shop worker's outfit all on the same day.
Where were they purchased?
Entirely online, from Amazon.
Each time, the packages were picked up at the supermarket,
but any surveillance footage has been deleted.
So you're telling me we don't have a
single clue that'd lead us to the culprits?
Is that the long and short of it?
Get back to me when you know something.
It sorta feels like we're just treadin' water here.
The more we chase, the more they leave us behind.
Yeah. Wonder if these leads could've
been planted as disinformation.
Like counter-intelligence?
You really think a couple kids could
pull off such a complicated stunt?
Shibazaki seems to believe these two are capable of a lot.
Yeah. Speaking of Shibazaki.
Where did he go?
He said something about heading to Aomori.
Excuse me. You're Yoshiharu Ebisuno.
Is that right?
Yeah?
I'm Detective Shibazaki, Metro P.D.
So what. This fella do somethin'?
Nah he's just a witness for a minor incident.
I've been asking around all day.
But no one seems to remember anything about the guy.
Well, he weren't one to
fraternize with his coworkers much.
Even durin' lunch, he'd always
have them earphones in his head.
So I said "you always got them earphones in.
What're ya listenin' to?" Then, he just
looked at me and says "Music from a cold land."
"A cold land?"
Anything else stand out in your memory as odd?
Even the most trivial detail?
Uh-huh.
I asked him what his old man did for a livin' once.
The kid just clammed up real fast.
It seemed like maybe I'd hit
a nerve or somethin' like that.
Father. Oedipus killed his father.
Riddles.
Bombings.
Missing plutonium.
They're all interconnected. But how?
What were you expecting? A welcome mat?
No. But this is a Dual EC encryption.
There has to be a backdoor.
Hm. That one looked weird.
Hello!
It was a web shell.
Jackpot!
So, like, I messaged him back, and it said he read it.
But then, like, that was it, no response.
I mean. What's with that? Boys are so weird, right?
How was Aomori?
It's cooler up there, isn't it?
It was pretty much the same as here.
Can I bum one of those? What? I thought you quit smoking.
One. Just having one.
So you learn anything about our culprit?
He wasn't much of a social type.
Very few of his fellow employees even remembered
him working there, much less anything noteworthy.
It's almost as if this guy
never existed in the first place.
Then this kid is practically a ghost?
They've been careful to cover
their tracks up to this point.
They sure didn't leave any clues in Aomori.
Yeah? Then why'd you bother to go all the way up there?
No matter how cleverly you erase records and cover tracks,
you can't erase a person's memory. Besides...
What's that?
I needed to be there in person.
To see the view they saw. To hear the same sounds.
To breathe the same air.
To feel the same things.
Hey. I'm headin' out to run a few errands.
Sounds good. I'll finish up the next present.
A summer gift, eh?
Just in time for the Obon Festival.
This year, we have a reason to celebrate.
Look, Shibazaki,
I hate to say this since you're paying and all,
but I wouldn't mind something
other than ramen once in a while.
Hey. The phrase "music from a cold land".
What does that make you think of?
"A cold land"? Hm. Every single Christmas song?
Or maybe like the Russian anthem?
Huh.
We interrupt this program to bring you this breaking news.
We have just received updated information
regarding the recent spate of terrorist bombings.
A new video has now been made public on a
media sharing website announcing the next attack.
Yeah.
I'm watching it now.
Good evening. This is Sphinx Number One.
Ladies, I like moonlit strolls, romantic
dinners and explosives! I'm Sphinx Number Two.
When exactly was the video posted?
...are you ready to play Time Shock Bomb?
At the place where the king who solved the riddle
received a frightening prophecy, whose appellation
would you carve on its entrance?
Solve the riddle to stop our biggest bomb yet.
Buzzers ready? It's time to play!
And I sincerely hope you'll play with
boys like us without resorting to cheating.
Until then, we'll be wishing you good
luck at the king's final destination!
Oh! And when you come, make sure
to use letters, not bronze, okay?
Crazy, right?
The footage you just saw was made public mere moments ago.
Wait! Shibazaki! You didn't pay!
The king who solved the riddle.
Oedipus' final destination was the underworld.
After gouging out his own eyes,
his two daughters acted as his guides leading him down the
great bronze stairway to the very gates of the underworld.
Bronze stairs. But in the video
they said to use letters instead.
A letter staircase?
Right. Let the letters lead you down to the gateway?
That's it.
C'mon.
That's not good.
So the Internet is the underworld?
Delphi?
The Oracle of Delphi gave him the prophecy.
There are three maxims inscribed
on the entrance to the temple.
"Know thyself." "Nothing in excess."
And, "Make a pledge and mischief is nigh."
It was in a shrine last time. Could be in a temple?
Forget it.
If we enter the name of the person the
maxims are referring to as the password,
the bomb will probably deactivate.
Can't be that easy.
I bet it's just something they
put in to make us waste time.
He's right! This could just be a decoy.
No.
That's the police station they attacked over in Roppongi!
So we have until midnight?
Well, I'm not gonna sit around on my thumbs!
We need to coordinate a search of all temples and shrines!
We're on it, sir.
Hey wait. What're you up to?
Would you quit messin' with it?
This is the first time those
two have made any kind of request.
It could be their version of a response
to what I said the other day on the news.
They want us to play.
Hey baby. Whatcha doin'?
You alone? Maybe you want a little company?
I know a real nice place.
No!
Hm.
"I won't get too involved." That's what you said.
Yes, I know.
And I won't get too involved. But uh...
But what?
Well, she's... It looks like she ran away.
If she gets taken into custody.
She may end up saying something about us.
That would be bad.
Your point?
I'm just saying.
I think it'd be better if we kept a close eye on her.
Trapped your Queen. You should have sacrificed her.
Here, guys. Take a look.
This is footage of the suspect picking
up their order from Showa Gunpowder.
A few minutes later, he shows up again.
This is surveillance footage
from a nearby apartment building.
Last stop.
He gets off on the sixth floor.
Nice work, son.
We'd better move. There isn't much time.
Full emergency deployment.
Yes, sir!
Hey! We got a lead on where they're hiding out!
Huh?
Little twerps have finally screwed up!
C'mon, let's roll!
I'll leave that to you.
Huh? There's no need to solve their stupid riddle anymore.
That's where you're wrong.
The video said to stop the bomb.
Last time they said "search for", this time it's "stop."
Are you serious?
I am.
They gave us a puzzle, and said not to cheat.
Meaning.
Do you wanna play their twisted game?
Or do you wanna help us put an end to it?
Shibazaki? You gonna be all right?
Whatcha doin'?
You should go home.
Places like this aren't very safe at night.
Leave me alone.
I can't have you wandering
around, it could cause problems.
Just shut up!
Hm?
I don't really have a home I can go to anymore.
I'm so stupid. I thought that somehow.
Somehow I could escape from it all. Like...
Like someone would come and lift
me out of my miserable, boring life.
Like it was all a bad dream.
But that's impossible, right?
I'm here. I'm awake. This isn't some weird dream.
And things don't just work themselves out.
So stupid.
Good evening, miss.
Is there any reason you're out so late?
Ah! Hey, what do you think you're doing, Shibazaki?
You can't smoke in here!
Window.
Ah. Is your head screwed on straight?
Aw, jeez.
It was hard enough for you to quit the first time around!
I'm serious!
I know you better than you know yourself!
Hey!
"Know thyself" was carved at the gate.
Don't tell me!
Well done!
Wait. Why won't it stop?
Even though you answered correctly.
These friends of yours decided to cheat.
Which means. Uh-oh!
The hidden bomb cannot be stopped!
So, ka-boom!
The hell?
Wait a second. Are those?
Yeah. They're sending out all
of our investigation reports.
Yes sir. The files are authentic.
It's unclear how they broke in.
Hey. Do you wanna destroy it?
Huh?
The entire planet? Do you, like, want to blow it all up?
It's been so long.
I haven't laughed like that in forever.
I forgot how nice it felt.
Ah.
So, uh...
Yeah, no.
Wait! Uh...
Having someone the cops aren't
looking for would be kinda nice...
She can't be trusted. Don't you understand?
We're running out of time, here!
But that doesn't mean that Lisa would...
Huh?