The bomb is set to blow at eight sharp.
We have to personally retrieve it before then.
What is this, Mission: Impossible?
It's her. She's back.
You pulled us off the bomb so they could deal with it!
I was given every assurance they would.
Hey, Nine, is this?
There's no doubt.
Five is back.
You've never behaved like this before.
You seem excited. It's weird.
Excuse me for having fun.
I've been so bored playing this game by myself.
I don't even care about winning anymore.
I just want an opponent worthy of my attention.
And now...
...the prodigal son has returned.
Let the games begin,
Nine.
Whoa.
Our initial subway bombing report is complete.
Although there were no fatalities.
72 people in total were injured.
More than any of the prior Sphinx attacks.
My men are currently analyzing surveillance
footage from the Shuto Shinjuku Line,
as well as bomb fragments we recovered.
We also have people looking into the connection
between the bombings and the recent interruption
in cell phone service across all networks.
That should just about do it, people.
But before you leave. Let me say one thing.
Go ahead, Chief.
The United States Government made an offer
to provide assistance with our investigation.
From this point on, we will coordinate our
efforts with the FBI's Counterterrorism Division,
to bring an end to these attacks.
We'll work with them, and put their experience to
good use. Any requests they make should be prioritized.
Dismissed.
Nine? Are you okay?
Why don't you get some rest?
I can't. Five's not gonna wait for that.
So what?
Is she holding some kind of grudge against us?
I don't understand.
Neither do I.
If she had wanted to escape with us, she could've.
I think she just likes playing the game.
Now she wants to pick up where she left off.
She's quite the adversary.
Somethin' tells me she's not gonna go easy on us.
Um...
I don't mean to eavesdrop, but maybe I could help out?
What the hell could you do?
U-Uh, I am capable of things, y'know!
Like what?
I could, uh...
Blow up buildings? Hurt bystanders?
I don't know.
Could you do that?
No. I couldn't.
'Cause this is what we're doing. Look at them.
But Nine, we didn't detonate the bomb in the subway...
So just stay out of our way, alright?
You wanna help? Do that.
Their offer of support is just a front.
The Americans are planning to take control, aren't they?
If that happens, we're gonna have a
real hard time getting a single thing done.
I'm afraid you're right.
From here on out, my hands are effectively tied.
This have anything to do with you
getting called out of yesterday's meeting?
Where'd you run off to?
The Chief Cabinet Secretary's office.
Something seemed off the minute I walked in.
All the Department heads were
sitting there waiting like whipped pups.
That's where I met our new "partners."
Kurahashi. Let me introduce you.
This is Special Agent Clarence, from the FBI.
It's a pleasure, sir.
I'm First Division Chief Kurahashi.
They've kindly offered help getting
a handle on this Sphinx situation.
The FBI? You're sure?
Absolutely.
The cabinet has already approved our decision.
One thing. This is a domestic incident.
Why bring in the FBI?
Surely their capable personnel have better
things to do than worry about bombs in Japan.
There's a bit more to it.
Six months ago, a nuclear fuel processing
facility in Aomori was infiltrated by persons unknown.
The United States Government is "extremely
interested" in the item that went missing.
We're here now 'cause we've reason to suspect
the ones behind the attack at the Aomori facility
are the same as your serial bombers.
More than just "reason to suspect."
We have proof.
What kind of proof are you talking about?
If you don't mind sharing that
information, we can arrest...
On top of allowing those silly boys to
wreak havoc across your beautiful city.
You let them leak sensitive
intel about the case to the public,
and now you have the gall to puff
your chest and talk about making arrests?
That's the funniest joke I've heard all year.
From what I gathered, the woman is a researcher
with the American Nuclear Emergency Support Team.
NEST for short.
A researcher? That doesn't seem right.
I confirmed her official job title.
I'll be damned.
Apparently the FBI believes Sphinx
stole that Aomori plutonium as well.
Yeah.
Seems to make 'em think they've got the
authority to mess with those kids however they want.
Like that crap that went down yesterday.
What happens when they back the perps into a corner?
They gonna force that joker into play?
Your voice is like the color of straw.
A pale yellow.
What?
Oh, sorry.
Y'see, I have this condition known as synesthesia.
I experience sounds as colors.
Colors?
Yeah. It's funny.
There're lots of blues, greens and reds.
But I hardly ever hear yellow.
Oh.
We're talkin' rare. Unique.
I'm in the way. I know I am.
It would be better if I just left, wouldn't it?
What? No way. Nine was just bein' grouchy.
He may say mean things, but he doesn't hate you.
But he said... Huh?
That's just mild sadism.
Makes sense.
I guess you know him pretty well by now, huh?
Hm?
I'll admit. I'm a little bit jealous.
Well we've been together for most of our lives.
Just the two of us.
We interrupt with live, breaking news.
The serial bombers called Sphinx have resurfaced.
Once again antagonizing authorities through riddles.
Nice! Looks like we've got an impostor.
Guess that's one way to know we've hit the big time.
She's made the first move.
Okay, "Gaius Julius Caesar gone to Arab."
"Gone to Arab?"
But he went to Egypt. I think
I know what this means, though.
It's a simple Caesar cipher.
So does that mean it needs to
be changed to Arabic numerals?
The Caesar cipher is an ancient substitution
coding system that shifts each letter
a fixed number of places down the alphabet.
If there isn't an assigned shift, the
default is three letters to the left.
Since there was no assigned shift sent with the message,
we'll have to hope the default does the job.
No dice. Maybe, coordinates?
Could be.
Haneda Airport, International Terminal.
Yeah. It's one of our targets.
All right! Get a hold of the airport right away!
Yes sir!
So what's with the twenty at the end?
The time the bomb's set to go off, most likely.
"VON voyage"?
As in "Have a nice trip"? They're just messin' with us!
Also, they've misspelled it.
No. It's intentional.
"VON voyage?" They're really
trying to make this look like us.
This is it. Her message to us.
Her way of saying that she's seen through everything.
Yes.
I have already been briefed on the situation by the MLIT.
Thing is, this is very hush-hush.
Every single operative involved
has top-tier security clearance.
What we need from you is discretion.
Therefore, any communication with
the terrorists should be through us.
An' we'll pass the info onto the police.
I understand. I'll make the necessary arrangements.
Do you really think those two are gonna bite?
They gotta be smart enough to realize this is a trap.
They will come.
They will come to see me.
Isn't it possible the bomb's a fake?
If it's Five, and she never does anything half-assed,
she'll blow it up for real. Because she has nothing
to lose. She knows the cops will blame it on us.
Let's put out a video saying it wasn't us!
The word of a mysterious fringe group, or Metro PD.
Which one would you buy into?
So messed up.
Try to stop the bomb and get caught. Or option two:
we ignore it, and are implicated as murderous psychopaths.
'At's one hell of a trap!
It's summer vacation, so the airport's gonna be packed.
Depending on how strong the bomb is and where it's placed.
Hundreds of those people could die!
She's gone insane.
You know there was never any sanity to begin with.
Not for her, and not for us.
Detective! Over here!
Sir! On my way!
What's buggin' you?
I don't think this is really from Sphinx.
Yeah? Why do ya say that?
The clue's too cut and dry. Doesn't feel like
there's a message hiding below the surface.
Look, we don't have time to
think about that stuff right now.
We only have four hours to find and disarm the bomb.
Let's go earn our salaries, old man!
Attention! Everybody listen up.
We have orders straight from the top.
The Explosives Ordinance Disposal
team is en route to remove the bomb.
We're supposed to stay here
and await further instructions.
But, wait a sec! Director!
This was a challenge issued to Metro PD!
Please let us go!
C'mon, sir!
We want some payback!
Yeah! Why do we have to stay put?
What the hell is this?
Everyone, calm down!
Director. You said these orders came from the top?
From the Superintendent General's mouth.
I shouldn't have to say this, but
renegade cops will not be tolerated.
No one get cute.
Uh, yo, Shibazaki. Where're you going?
To grab some food.
I have a feeling we'll all be stuck here for a while.
This is gonna suck.
The international terminal is freakin' huge!
Yeah.
So, how are we supposed to find the bomb?
Well most likely,
we'll receive the next riddle once we get there.
I counted about 1500 surveillance
cameras spread throughout the terminal.
And naturally, Five'll be
monitoring every single one of 'em.
Which means we need to act under
the assumption we'll be apprehended.
No way. We just need someone new.
Someone whose face hasn't been tied to us yet.
No! Sorry. I thought I'd make noodles. You hungry?
No way in hell.
To what? The noodles?
Where do you think you're going?
It's against the rules to use official
vehicles for personal food breaks.
Or were you planning to get yourself into trouble again?
Times have changed, gramps.
The lone wolf shtick's kinda done.
That goes for you too, Hamura.
Sorry, boys. 'Bout those "dinner" plans?
We'll be joinin' ya.
Impossible.
Think about it. Wouldn't someone amateurish
be useful in a situation like this one?
Amateurish?
Let's go.
Wait. Kokonoe. Uh. Nine!
It's just that. I want to be one of you.
Let me help your cause!
And maybe I can't handle the bombs.
Or any of this other stuff yet, but please!
I'll study hard!
We'll move separately.
To avoid the security cameras.
Take the train out to the airport.
Ah, the irony.
Here we are, a couple terrorists,
heading out to try and prevent a bombing.
Everything's in place.
Pull up the "Runpass" activity log.
Yes, ma'am.
Filter down to users active in the last 15 minutes.
Check with all airport personnel lists.
Sure, one moment.
Move!
My apologies.
You're getting careless. Nine.
Show the camera C15 feed from ten minutes ago.
It'll take about three minutes to transfer the data.
You're kidding me.
Bring up F12 to G6 on the main monitors.
Done.
S'about time, isn't it?
Yeah, let's move out.
Target confirmed.
A chessboard?
That's crazy.
You think she wants to continue the game from before?
Uh-huh. She's planning to use the airport as the board
and us as the pieces.
And lemme guess.
If we win, the position of the last
piece will match the bomb's location.
Yeah.
King's Knight to F6!
Good luck!
It's been far too long since we last played.
Run, Nine.