The serial bombers called Sphinx have resurfaced,
once again antagonizing authorities through riddles.
Nice! Looks like we've got an impostor.
Guess that's one way to know we've hit the big time.
We'll have to hope the default does the job.
Haneda Airport, International Terminal.
I don't think this is really from Sphinx.
It's just that, I want to be one of you.
Let me help your cause!
Everything's in place.
Pull up the "Runpass" activity log.
Yes, ma'am.
Filter down to users active in the last 15 minutes.
You're getting careless, Nine.
It's about time, isn't it?
Target confirmed.
A chessboard?
That's crazy.
You think she wants to continue the game from before?
Uh-huh. She's planning to use airport
as the board, and us as the pieces.
And lemme guess. If we win, the position of
the last piece will match the bomb's location.
Yeah.
King's Knight to F-6!
Good luck!
It's been far too long since we last played.
Run, Nine.
The bomb should be in here somewhere.
I think we'll have to split up.
Hang on, so,
we gotta figure out a way to search this entire airport?
Just the five of us?
Yeah, and keep in mind,
a message will appear soon. It could show up anywhere.
Like there! D4?
Exactly.
I hate this airport.
What happened to the dang map?
Ok, here we go. It's her next move.
All we have to do is get to the checkmate.
That's where we should find the bomb.
What? You got orders from the police?
Yep. They didn't tell me why.
I was just told to make sure
these images got on the screens.
And you're positive it was the police?
How did you guys not know about it?
You should've, unless you're not really cops.
Target B Lost.
It's like he knows exactly where
all of the security cameras are,
and he's hidin' in their blind spots.
That ain't possible, is it?
Get the footage of Target B to the airport police,
and have them start searching for him, immediately.
Tell them this is their top priority.
Yes, ma'am.
The next move is NC3.
Is she saying she's seen through everything?
Damn it! Why would the police
order him to put up that image?
And what does it even mean?
It's some kinda message.
I'd guess the sender is whoever set the bomb.
They're communicating with someone trying to disarm it.
So, who's got the authority pull this off?
Wait a minute. You're sayin' cops did this?
Someone on the force planted the bomb?
Then the riddle from earlier was just a fake
prepared by the department for the real Sphinx.
Which means they must be here too.
Sounds right. But I think we'll be better
off tracking the movements of the police.
Other than the restrooms, there
are 12 blind spots on the floor.
Nice. There's the welcoming committee.
Target B has been located.
Then go pick him up.
Roger.
Castling.
BD3.
Not a bad move.
As far as that code goes,
I think it means the location of a chess piece.
A chess piece?
So whoever's behind this is having a match with someone?
Damn it! This doesn't make any
sense. What are they planning? Ideas?
How's it goin'?
Perfectly.
Good! Then, I guess it's time for
us to introduce Sphinx Number Three?
If you insist.
Seriously?
Yep! What you're lookin' for is
in the locker next to counter 12.
Okay. Wait a sec, first, um.
What, can't do it?
No, I'm fine. I'm totally in.
Let's see...
Bingo!
C'mon. Stop freaking out.
Hey, there's a police truck here.
That's weird. Wonder what it's doing.
Come with me!
Yessir!
N capture, F4.
Impressive, Nine.
But...
A1 equals Q. And that's checkmate.
Whoa.
What's that?
Smoke detected in the building at Area 17B.
Tell airport police to get over there now.
Yes, ma'am.
Bring up camera 15. Give me a close-up.
Clarence, you there?
All right, let's find that truck.
Good call, but where do we start looking?
Places where a large truck wouldn't stand out.
Like right there!
Got it!
Get off.
Tch.
The time!
Don't move.
We haven't seen each other in so
long, Nine, and this is how you greet me?
Are you trying to hurt my feelings?
I can't believe I didn't notice it sooner.
There you were in all your glory,
but the whole thing was just a recording.
You found your opportunity and switched out
the live feed with recorded surveillance footage
from five minutes earlier. Clever trick.
Why are you trying to get in our way?
You ask like you don't know.
Surely you realize I'm here to settle our score.
And the bomb? Gate 1O6.
It's where the checkmate is. Am I wrong?
No, you're right.
After changing the surveillance footage,
Twelve started heading directly for the bomb.
But what about that plus one of yours?
They helped camouflage you both by
causing a commotion with that little fire?
I can't tell you how delighted I was to find out you
boys had made a friend, but, you know what that means.
And oh, how I love a good weakness.
Shut up and come with me.
I have extended her a special
invitation to see the bomb in person.
I didn't want her feeling left out.
Don't move!
Get him!
No, you do what I say!
But...
I don't remember asking your opinion
or giving you permission to shoot.
Can somebody get me the control room?
Those were gunshots. Now what?
What the hell.
Like we don't already have enough on our plate.
Shibazaki! What's the hold up?
Nine! I don't think the bomb is here!
What?
I don't get it.
This was supposed to be the checkmate spot!
I can't get out! Please, you have to help me!
I'm on a plane and it's moving.
What? Why are you on a plane?
This guy just showed up and grabbed me,
and then forced me to get on. The bomb is in here, too.
Tell me what to do!
Hey. Wasn't that plane headed for the hangar?
Jus' stay calm, 'kay?
First of all, who's piloting that thing?
Um. There's no one in there.
It's moving by itself!
Of course.
That's why you couldn't find
the bomb at the gate we thought.
Because they put it on a plane instead.
Yeah. Now, that bomb is on the move,
and I bet it's headed right this way.
Gate 1O6, where we're standing.
Damn it. What is her problem?
She's settling old scores.
Okay, it's clearly being driven remotely.
Which means we should have a
pretty good idea where she is.
In the control tower!
Here we are, Nine: the final stage.
Can you clear it, though?
What do we do?
The tower is crawling with armed special assault forces.
We can't get anywhere near it.
We have to create some kind of commotion.
The general public needs to be evacuated.
Wait, what're you saying?
You know what'll happen to Lisa.
She's trapped in there with the bomb!
I know.
There is one way, but it's risky.
Detective Shibazaki?
Who's this?
Sphinx Number One.
What the hell? How do you have this number?
No time to explain.
The bomb you're looking for's not one of ours.
I'm sure you already have an idea of who'd wanna frame us.
But right now I need your help.
You do?
At the moment, there's a passenger jet
with a bomb on it heading toward Gate 1O6.
I have every reason to believe it's real.
There's only one way to stop it.
You have to get into the control
room and take over the autopilot system.
It has to be you because the special
assault team is swarming that area.
No way we can get near it.
Seriously. You're asking for help from the police?
The way I see it, if that bomb goes
off, it becomes a problem for both of us.
So you're saying we have mutual interests.
Well yeah. Isn't that kinda your job?
To protect and serve?
Ha. Funny guy.
Not a line I'd expect to hear from a terrorist.
Five minutes left.
Lisa, can you hear me?
You were told not to let anyone through, rookie!
Yeah, but these guys say they're detectives.
This is an emergency. Get out of our way!
We have orders, sir!
Hey, we're all cops here!
And we got business in the control room!
Back off, man!
There's no time!
Get back!
Will you just listen to me!
Ya just have to do what I told you.
You'll be fine. Stay calm and breathe.
I know you can do this.
Shibazaki, run!
We're on the same team!
Hey, wait!
Let go!
Lisa!
Oh, thank God. Okay.
Damn it!
No!
Hold it.
You'll be taking orders from me, now.
Tch!
I'm stuck.
Outta time! Hurry!
You realize you're just his pet dog.
I can't believe you're trusting him!
Here!
C'mon! You're not done yet.
I will make you regret this.
It's locked!
No, wait!
Damn you, Sphinx.
Lisa, you won't get away again.