It's true you may be an accomplice.
You're not one of us, though.
Nothing personal. But one false
move, and I'll have to kill ya.
I think these guys have every intention
of picking a fight with this entire country.
We need you back. I'm sorry.
Come on out. I'm waiting for you.
I can't believe this!
No! Some random, crusty old dude from
Archives comin' up to be my boss? It's a joke.
What. You haven't heard of him before?
He's not random.
Shibazaki used to be one of our best guys.
Huh?
It's the truth. He was incredible.
Everyone called him "Razor Shibazaki".
Wish I had a nickname like that.
Wish I had a nickname, period.
An' how long's it been since he was a detective?
This guy was basically sent down to
Archives to rot until retirement. And now he...
Morning.
Hey, welcome back.
Come on, Shibazaki.
You realize I'm not helping
you move all this crap for free.
Anyone know where my desk is?
Yeah, it's right over here. Scram.
Man, you should treat me to lunch or something for this.
You like ramen, right?
Stop doing that!
I mean, yeah, I do, but quit assuming
all fat people worship at the carb altar!
Hey, Hamura!
It's tough. I don't know, Nine.
What if the riddle is too hard for them?
It's fine, Don't worry.
Yeah, so you say.
I'm just not sure what we're gonna
do if no one can solve it again.
The other day, when they were
investigating the Roppongi bomb.
I saw vans from the Nuclear, Biological,
and Chemical Terrorism Special Forces.
Makes me think.
It's possible they've got someone
who's figured out what we're up to.
This ought to help us know for sure.
As you can see,
the culprit entered the police station like this.
Ignoring surveillance cameras,
he calmly planted a delivery box containing the
plastic bomb, turned around, and left. In my opinion,
we should consider this act our confirmation.
They are directly challenging the police force.
Understanding this threat,
we have no choice but to assume they're
likely working on their next bomb as we speak.
So, I've got more on the stolen plutonium...
from the nuclear facility in Aomori?
One of the fugitives was an employee.
But he had only been working there for a few months.
In the files he's Yuzu Miyajima.
Apparently, though, that person has never existed.
How's that happen?
Best guess?
He used the Basic Residents'
Registration Network to get hired on.
He infiltrated the government
office and fabricated a new identity.
An identity with local ties, since the facility tends
to hire from within their community whenever possible.
And?
Look at his face. There's a sketch of him in that file.
They didn't bother takin' a photo?
No, they did. But it was mysteriously deleted somehow.
At the time, we sent out an emergency deployment.
But Miyajima and his accomplice have seemingly vanished.
No trail, no trace, no evidence they even existed.
Looks like he's only a kid.
Yeah.
I've told you about what it was
like where I grew up, haven't I?
About being surrounded by old people.
Oh yeah. You're from Hiroshima.
I'll never forget those summers.
Man, I hated them.
Once it started to get warm,
the city became a ghost town.
The elderly stayed in, almost never leaving their houses.
They'd say they didn't feel well because of the heat.
I spent a lot of time with my grandmother.
I always felt as though the summer would
steal her from me. She'd turn into someone else.
Yeah. I hated summer. I resented it.
That's why you took this case.
Second-generation victim of The Bomb?
Must be hard to watch a couple of
kids playing around with nuclear weapons.
Yeah. They bother me.
Somethin' about this, though.
I dunno. Just doesn't add up.
Mister Kawai.
You've been doing this a while, right?
How could you make such a simple
mistake while working the crane?
I told you. I was tired from tons of overtime, okay?
I've said it for years, man. That company's a sweatshop.
So uh, why don't you investigate that?
You listen!
Shibazaki.
S'cuse me. Mind if I have a chair?
I have a bad back.
Oh, sure.
So, Mister Kawai. You're a big fan of gambling.
Yeah? What's your point?
Horses or fights? I'm guessing fights.
Huh?
What kinda bet did you lose, guy?
I hear someone's hired gun's been payin' you visits.
No, uh, not recently.
Why's that?
Why would a man whose job is to
get money from you stop showing up?
Uh...
What's this?
Maybe it's the debt collector
in question comin' to answer that.
I got something, Shibazaki.
All the proof we needed was just
sittin' there on your computer.
Surprising, since you handed it over to us voluntarily.
Kawai confessed to everything.
He got an email saying if he cut the
power line and made it look like an accident,
he'd receive two million yen for the effort.
And the money?
Did they ever actually deliver any of it to him?
Yes.
Apparently, Kawai replied saying he could do it.
And even though he never told anyone his account
number, he had one million transferred to him.
Have we looked into the sending
account and time of transfer?
Nothing there, either.
The transfer came from a dummy account.
There's a bigger issue, though.
These guys knew what would
happen if that power line was cut.
They planned this "accident" so
there'd be a citywide blackout,
cutting off power to the government building.
But we're talking about well-prepared criminals here.
Why would they choose to leave
behind an email that could be traced?
Not to mention the footage from Roppongi Station.
It's as if they're intentionally
leaving behind evidence for us to find.
Uh.
What's the problem?
We got another one! It's Sphinx!
Sorry to keep you waiting, fans!
It's time for "Can you solve Sphinx's riddle?"
I'm Sphinx Number One.
And I'm Sphinx Two.
Now, for today's riddle.
What is the building next to the
house of the god who solved the riddle?
Remember, there will be another
"boom" if you don't solve it in time!
You have until 10 AM tomorrow.
Good luck, everyone!
Keep walkin' until you have to drag your foot
behind you like a good, old-fashioned cripple!
Right.
Can you replay the video?
Sure.
That's good.
10 AM tomorrow.
Good luck...
Sphinx Two is clapping his hands like he's praying.
I'd say "house of the god" has
to refer to a shrine somewhere.
Okay, then what god are they talking about?
Which one solved the Sphinx's riddle correctly?
That was Oedipus!
Oedipus is from Greek myth. You think maybe
he's got some kind of analog in Japanese tradition?
Yeah. I like how you're thinkin'.
What do you think that "drag your
foot behind you" comment was about?
Best guess, it has to do with the name Oedipus.
It means "swollen foot".
Why name him that?
Because after abandoning Oedipus in the forest,
Laius didn't want him to run away,
so dear ol' dad put a nail through his son's heel.
Well, that's brutal.
He wound up being saved by a shepherd
and then adopted by the king of Corinth.
When the king saw the child's injured leg,
he named him "swollen foot", or Oedipus.
How literal.
According to one theory.
Oedipus remained disabled to some extent his whole life.
"Crippled".
We need to move fast.
They gave us an exact time of
day, which they haven't done before.
Check out all the shrines in the
city 'til we get somewhere with this.
Yes, sir!
Lisa, please! Lisa! Lisa! Lisa! Lisa!
Shibazaki. I wanted to lie down
there and play. Will you move?
No dice. I need it more. I do
my best thinking on this couch.
Come on!
You just wanna play a video game.
Why don't you go home for that?
Because I'm keeping you company, bro.
I don't want you to get lonely here.
You're welcome, by the way.
Yeah, thanks a bunch.
Hey. That's prob'ly Sphinx's problem, you know?
They're just lonely and want some attention.
Couple of brats.
Blowing things up 'cause they're desperate for attention?
I can't accept that.
No! Aw, man.
Is that an online game?
Yeah, you work with other players to
defeat monsters. It's pretty addictive.
Really?
I usually assume kids these days play
this stuff to avoid dealing with people,
but it looks like making
connections might still be a thing.
That's not good. You just made
a "kids these days" comment.
Proof you're officially old.
I did it! Look! I finally beat the green dragon!
I swear, I've been stuck on this jerk for days!
A dragon.
That's right. He was an ancestor of Oedipus's mother.
Of course! Mukasa, you're a genius!
Huh?
Who's there?
Lisa? Lisa, is that you?
Yeah, I dunno. You think that'll work?
Yes.
I don't understand. Are you trying to provoke them?
Not at all, but I'll take the heat if I do.
If that's what you want.
What are you talking about? You won't take the heat!
If something goes wrong, the
Director's up the creek, not you!
Well, in that case, I apologize
ahead of time if that happens.
Huh?
A name is a gift of love.
But you have been abandoned.
Love does not exist in your world.
Your old names are signs of pretense;
which is unacceptable. Pretense must be eliminated.
Therefore, you will be given new, practical designations.
You okay? Are your ears ringing again?
No. My ears are fine.
We swore not to lie. Don't forget.
I won't. But you're not supposed to lie, either.
You met up with Lisa.
That obvious?
Don't worry, I won't get too involved.
Because, I know if I do,
it'll be much more painful later.
Okay, any time.
Hello. This is for Sphinx One and Two.
I'm Detective Shibazaki.
Nice!
You'll be happy to know I have an answer for your riddle.
You asked us "What's the building next to
the house of the god who solved the riddle?"
We know the one who solved
the Sphinx's riddle was Oedipus.
He wasn't the child of a god, but the ancestor
of his mother and wife was a dragon in human form.
One theory states that Oedipus was crippled,
as you so eloquently put it, for his entire life.
A dragon who drags his feet? Arahabaki.
Oh, ho!
Arahabaki is a mysterious god
found in the Kanto and Tohoku regions.
The god of fighting and iron-making.
He's also known as "god of feet".
At one point, he had to wander
different areas after losing his home.
He became so exhausted that he dragged his feet.
Please, excuse me. We have breaking news.
We're being told the Metropolitan Police Department
is using the internet to answer the bombers' riddle.
Also. The "habaki" part of "Arahabaki?"
It's derived from "dragon tree".
Connecting it to the dragon god.
The most famous Arahabaki shrine is in Miyaki Prefecture.
However, he's still worshipped
within Tokyo proper, as well.
Right here.
Shirahige Shrine in Katsushika.
This is the building next to it.
We've just finished disarming the bomb, sir.
Thanks. Good work.
There you have it. The answer to your riddle.
Not bad.
Yes, that's right.
We've just been told the bomb has been disarmed.
Well that's what you wanted to hear, right?
How's it make you feel?
I'm betting it doesn't make you feel anything at all.
I don't know if this is a game to you or what.
But don't get carried away.
I hope you boys realize the joker
you're wavin' around is not a toy.
...And if you play that card. ...Cut the feed.
Right.
I will take you both out myself!
Shibazaki! What the hell was that?
Were you just antagonizing them on purpose?
Don't worry. I've asked Director
Kurahashi to follow-up if necessary, right?
Oh yeah, right.
Did you notice?
Yes, I did.
Hazmat suits mixed in with
their bomb suits and other gear.
Can only mean one thing.
Yeah. The cops have connected it.
They definitely know we were
the ones who stole the plutonium.
A bomb was removed from the building
next to Shirahige Shrine in Katsushika.
The Metropolitan Police Department solved
the bombers' riddle from a video streaming site,
and the bomb was found succes...
Um, excuse me, Director Kurahashi?
Hm? What is it?
It's about Shibazaki.
What is his deal? I heard he used to be an ace.
But then what? I'm just curious what happened.
It goes back 15 years, when a Diet secretary from
the ruling party fell to his death from a hotel room.
Okay?
It was initially ruled to be an accident or a
suicide, but Shibazaki refused to accept that.
He insisted on the possibility
that the dead man had been involved
in some kind of conspiracy,
and even went so far as to investigate
the leader of the victim's political faction.
That couldn't have ended well.
The faction leader?
Originally from the Police Department.
Totally get why he was demoted to archives, now.
Shibazaki had a family.
He had his life. The only thing he could
do at that point was accept the transfer.
However, he has never forgotten.
And he hasn't given up. That was a long summer.
Nother hot one again today.