Because they put it on a plane instead.
I can't get out! Please, you have to help me!
Hold it.
You'll be taking orders from me, now.
Here!
Damn you, Sphinx.
Lisa, you won't get away again.
We have some new information regarding
the bombing incident at Haneda Airport.
The explosion occured on an unoccupied
runway, fortunately resulting in no injuries.
Based on suspicious text messages, the attack is
suspected to be connected to the terrorist cell, Sphinx.
"We're supposed to stay here."
It's called direct order, gentlemen.
In spite of that, you lot somehow
got into a fight at the airport,
and even managed to significantly
interfere with the investigation.
Was it worth it?
Because you're all now suspended.
You're off the case. I don't
want to see you for three months.
Three months?
If you even piss without orders
again, you'll be out permanently.
We clear on this?
Won't be terribly easy to find another job.
Don't punish them. The whole thing was my idea, sir.
And I'm prepared to take full responsibility.
Oh, I don't need you to tell me that.
You are getting special treatment.
Mister Shibazaki, at this point
you are suspended indefinitely.
Indefinite?
So basically you're saying he's fired?
Look, you need to know I saw Sphinx with my own eyes.
They're not guilty of that bombing.
Whoever set up the whole airport
thing was just trying to frame them.
Don't dig yourself any deeper than you already have.
Shibazaki. Leave your badge.
Tch!
I get what you're tryin' to say. I do.
But you have to understand you still got off easy.
That girl was behind this, right?
Pretty much, yeah.
Seemed she was the only one who wanted you out.
You said she was a nuclear physicist or somethin'?
Nice story, but what is she really?
I actually put out a few feelers about that,
and looks like she was transferred from the ISA.
Intelligence Support Activity?
So this chick came from US Army Special Ops?
You got it.
Why are we working with a former spy?
And why do they care about our stolen plutonium?
Because the situation may be much worse
than we could ever have assumed.
Okay, what's wrong?
Why are you visiting out of the blue?
What? Oh, you know.
How's Mom doing?
Dunno. Fine and at home, I guess.
Wow, Dad.
I take it you're too obsessed with work
to notice her or some cliché like that?
So I'm payin' for you to study somethin'
along the lines of physics at this school.
I'm in the department of science and engineering.
Then you should know about
nuclear power stuff, too, right?
Come on. Are you worried I'm
not studying hard enough, or what?
No, no, I just have a couple o' questions for ya is all.
Like how plutonium's used to make a bomb.
For real? Don't tell me this is for an investigation?
Oh. No.
You can't smoke in here, Dad.
It's a precision machine, so the right tools
would be necessary.
Can't imagine it'd be easy for
amateurs to pull off, though.
But in theory, it's possible. That's what worries me.
Yeah, but there's more to it than just building the thing.
Whoever's handling the material
would be exposed to serious radiation.
Your investigation must be pretty serious.
'Cause that's a heck of a look on your face.
Oh, no.
I was just thinkin' how weak your barley tea is.
Now to let the curry simmer for a bit...
You Lisa Mishima? There's a package for you.
Really, for me?
Thank you!
Who coulda sent it?
Wha... Bomb?
So we're gonna move out of the hideout?
She's been seen, now.
We have to.
They can't find us.
We're too close to risk it.
I really liked that roof. Man, this totally sucks.
Even for just a threat, this was too far.
You know our government's orders.
Securin' the object is our top priority.
If the worst were to have happened today...
Nine would never hide it in his own apartment, please.
In the end, all they want are results, right?
My point is you need to show some restraint.
Ya need to realize there's only so much
I can do to hold off the local police.
This isn't funny anymore.
I've actually never found this funny.
I didn't think we'd end up using this spot.
Cool! We can play all the games we want in here.
They're all super retro, but still.
You know whose fault this is, don't you?
It's mine.
And I'm sorry.
The top officials at all the buildings
where bombs have been placed took part
in a seminar led by a group
called the Rising Peace Academy.
They had previously implemented
something called the Athena Plan.
Athena, the goddess of wisdom,
appears in Greek mythology. Just like the Sphinx.
Hello? Oh, Shibazaki!
Hey.
I thought I had heard that you were
gonna be out of the office for a while.
Stopped by to say hi,
and figured I could look somethin' up.
You want one? It's a chocolate.
Hm?
I also got some of those pink ones you like.
If that's your idea of a farewell gift, keep it.
Hey, wasn't there a recent thing where the
son of some bigwig in the Ministry of Health,
Labour and Welfare injured someone?
Yeah. Heard about that.
I think they settled the case out of court.
Hate to ask, but think you can find the paperwork?
Oh, and uh...
"Oh, and uh" what?
You better save me one of those Pon de Rings.
Whoa. You seriously wanna go there already?
We didn't take Five into consideration before.
Accelerating the plan's our only choice.
I guess so.
But?
Nothin'. Except. Well...
I was just thinking, maybe we should
stop this whole thing altogether.
I'm hungry.
I gave you a snack five minutes ago.
Let's get straight to the point.
About ten years ago, there was a
project created called the Athena Plan.
Their "goal" was to properly educate gifted children.
However, the specifics of the project
cannot be found anywhere on the public record.
But I do know members of the Rising
Peace Academy spearheaded the project.
And since you were one of those members.
I'm assuming you must have known about this plan?
I'm very sorry, but I don't
know what you're talking about.
Although, even if I did, I certainly wouldn't be
able to divulge classified information regarding it.
I'm assuming a detective must have known that, though.
How's that son o' yours?
Behaving any better?
Now, why would you bring that up?
It has already been resolved.
Yes, and I'm sure you're relieved.
But it seems he didn't quite learn his lesson.
You bastard. A detective using extortion?
How dare you? You should know your place.
Funny how one can change when they're about to be fired.
Turns out I don't give a damn about "my place."
How can you quit?
Because if we keep this up,
there's every chance we'll...
Are you scared?
Is it Lisa?
Twelve. Think back.
Remember where we came from.
We're only doing what we have to, here.
Or have... have you changed your mind?
I get it, I do. That bomb almost killed her.
Okay. We'll stop involving Lisa, then.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
But I'm afraid it still won't keep her safe.
Thought I'd help you investigate today.
How'd you find me?
It wasn't very hard.
Just had to bribe someone with some ramen.
You'll be fired if you disobey
orders again, or did you forget?
Got a job lined up if you lose this one?
Folks own a grocery store.
Always got that to fall back on.
Orphanages?
Yeah.
According to that politician, they tested the
children at all the orphanages in the country,
then gathered up the ones they
considered the most "gifted".
So what, you're gonna check 'em all out?
One by one?
Yeah.
Probably ought to act like a detective at some point.
Yes, I believe there was a test like that.
Far as I recall, though, no children
from our institution passed it.
Well, I was only five.
So I don't remember what was on the test.
But I do remember being interviewed.
What's that?
Oh. I love those Sphinx guys. They're legit.
Okay, so afterwards, the boy
was taken by a government official?
That's right, and we never heard from him again.
By chance, do you happen to
remember anything about that official?
Sorry, but I think he gave me a business card.
This is definitely weird.
All of these places and not one person we
talked to has a clue where those kids ended up.
Yeah.
Almost like they're ghosts or something.
They just disappeared.
But at least we've got this
guy, and we know he's no ghost.
The Athena Plan?
Right. Get me whatever you can about the project.
Check the Ministry of Health, Labour and Welfare.
Look into their past employees, too.
You should be able to find this Aoki guy's address there.
If I'm caught, I won't get off with just being fired.
Isn't hacking the cybercrime division's specialty?
No you ass, we try to prevent it.
To be clear, if we don't figure
this out a lot of people are gonna die.
Mm-hm.
Ooh! I can feel it moving!
Gimme a bit. I'll call you back later.
Hey, Hamura.
That young guy we talked to who's a "fan" of Sphinx.
You know what's happening there?
Oh yeah. Seems a lot of kids are
startin' to treat them like heroes.
Course, they conveniently forget the truth.
You know, that they're just criminals.
Interesting.
Years ago, when I was young like them,
there were these teens who threw rocks at cops.
Fought against the government.
Sphinx may be called terrorists, now,
but in a different time.
These boys might've been thought of as somethin' else.
Just my opinion.
Yes, I've found Aoki's address.
Also. I've got some goods on the Athena Plan.
Pharmaceutical companies, neuroscience researchers,
and medical organizations were involved, too.
No kiddin'?
The plan itself was terminated 7 years ago.
I see.
Oh, and, there's one more important detail.
Of course.
Poor thing.
You should take better care of your
nails or they'll get weak and break.
Lisa Mishima.
Supposedly living with her
caring mother, just the two of them.
I researched everything about you, Lisa.
I even know you've run away
from the guys because you think,
rightfully so, that it would be better for them that way.
You didn't want to distract them any
more than you already have. Isn't that right?
You're just so sweet.
Please, understand. I actually want to help them, too.
Huh?
They still have a chance to atone for their crimes.
However, if they carry out the next part of their plan,
they will be tragically beyond redemption.
You can still help.
Tell me what you know and save them.
Why were you even with Nine and Twelve?
By accident.
I saw them at the Tokyo government office building.
They told me I had to choose between
becoming an accomplice and dying, so...
You should've chosen to die.
That was stupid. Unbelievably stupid.
To have an idiot girl following them around.
I can't imagine how annoying that must have been for them.
I don't... I don't care what happens to me.
But please, please let them go.
Why would I do that?
Surprise sweetie, I don't care
what happens to you, either.
You are nothing.
I care more about a roach than you.
Back to the point.
You don't honestly think those boys have a future, do you?
Where are you going?
I'm gonna find Lisa. I'll be back.
Is that a good idea?
What if she's ratting us out to the cops.
She would never!
And that's not just what you want to think?
It's from Lisa's phone.
Lisa!
From Five. There's no doubt.
Twelve. Wait!
This is a trap.
I know it is.
Then why go? We can't afford to take chances.
We're running out of time!
I know that, too!
Don't you see?
I'm going because I'm out of time.
Twelve...
Don't do this.
I'm sorry, Nine.