Even though you answered correctly,
these friends of yours decided to cheat.
Which means. Uh oh!
The hidden bomb cannot be stopped!
The entire planet?
Do you, like, wanna blow it all up?
Huh?
Are you crazy?
You shouldn't have brought her here.
A runaway wandering around?
The cops almost caught her, and she could identify us.
She's helpless, Nine. We should keep an eye on her.
The girl is an outsider.
She stays, and everything we've
fought to achieve is jeopardized.
The thing is. She hasn't got anywhere else to go.
And when she talked about making
her escape, it really hit home.
Lisa isn't that different from us.
I seem to remember you promising you
wouldn't get involved. It's for her own good.
Getting all mixed up with us?
You know that only leads to more misfortune.
I was, that is, I'm sorry!
Wow. Talk about lucky.
What?
This little guy's no ordinary phone.
See, that extinguisher is packed with plastic explosives.
And that phone serves as the detonation switch.
If the fuse had been connected,
we would all be dead.
Ka-bang!
My bad. I forgot about the whole "you being sick" thing.
Looks like the weather's held after all.
Oh no. You're wrong. A storm's on the way.
Make sure she cleans the filth
from the tub when she's done.
Chill out.
I think it's been a while since she last had a bath.
This girl isn't planning on gradually moving in, I hope.
Anyway. Once her fever goes down, she has to go.
Now, hold on! Keeping her here is absolutely pointless.
She'll just get in the way.
The data leak caused by Sphinx's
recent attack exposed the progress of our
current investigation to the general public.
Now they know how little we know.
Further failures will not be tolerated.
We plan to increase personnel, focusing
on the cybercrime department specifically.
We will then redouble our efforts to capture the bombers.
To be frank, we have no other options.
Thank you. You're all dismissed.
Go make me proud.
'Scuse us, coming through.
Just some routine maintenance.
Whoa!
Excuse me.
Yeah. Yeah, we just got here.
Hang on a sec. Nah, it's nothin'.
Don't worry about a thing. Okay. Gotcha. I'll tell her.
What?
Something wrong?
Don't cha smell it? There's a fire!
Hurry!
Uh... Welcome home!
There was no recipe, so I just kinda free-wheeled it.
Dig in!
Think I'll pass.
What?
Yeah it's inedible.
Hey! You don't have to be so rude about it!
Why don't you have a bite, then?
Terrible.
Told ya.
Doesn't really matter.
We never asked you to play house-mom for us, did we?
If this was an attempt to show us how useful you are,
then that plan backfired.
Aren't cha still runnin' a fever?
You should probably be back in bed.
It's fine. Just go lie down.
You know. Even the crummiest food is worth somethin'.
Huh?
Think about it. The food we ate at the institution.
Do you remember?
So many meals.
I don't remember enjoying any of them.
There was no taste. Just a task.
Another job to be completed.
It's almost time.
Hey, it's here! Come on!
Greetings! I'm Sphinx Number One.
I'm lookin' for a girlfriend to cook up
some bombs and tasty snacks. I'm Sphinx Two!
Now then, everyone, you've seen our videos before.
You know what happens next!
That's right! It's riddle time!
Today's mega-mystery question:
Where do you go when you connect the dots
between the punishment of F-E-Z 58-89 and
the angel who planted a grapevine?
You have until, oh, eight o'clock this evening.
Fail to solve it in time,
and you're gonna have another big boom on your hands!
Well then. Happy hunting, officers!
God, I hate them.
Kato, grab some analysts and get to work on this.
Yes, sir!
F-E-Z 58-89. What does that mean?
License plate or...?
Hey!
Shibazaki, wait!
Mukasa.
Hm? Shibazaki?
F-E-Z-5-8-8-9.
Does that sequence mean anything to you?
Huh? Yes, well?
Come on. How many years you worked archives?
What're you doing in the file room?
Find something that'll help solve the riddle?
Document numbers. An old case file?
The bombers must've seen our departmental
filing system after they hacked us.
They only leaked files from the
current investigation to the public.
But it's a reasonable assumption they
also got a hold of some older documents.
So long story short, they intentionally
made a riddle only the police would understand?
Guess these terrorists have taken a shine to us.
5-8-8-9. Found it!
Let's see... Corporal punishment case
from the public high school in Tochigi?
After showing up late to their club's
morning practice, four students got heat stroke
after being forced to run in over 100 degree weather.
All charges against the offender were dropped. Odd.
So what's this got to do with the bombings?
There's a passage in the Apocalypse of Baruch.
The story of an angel who angered God.
His offense was planting a
grapevine in the Garden of Eden.
The Kabbalah identifies him as Samael,
but he's also known as the Red Serpent.
Hell of a nickname.
So, tie it with the information from the file.
High school kids punished by being forced to run.
A red serpent forced to run.
What does that sound like to you, Mukasa?
Running red serpent? No clue.
What could be stretched out
like a snake that runs? In a city?
A train.
Right.
And a red train in the middle of the city would be?
The Shuto Shinjuku! Time to move!
We gotta tell somebody!
The bomb's probably in one of the train cars.
Then we'll have to check them all!
Subway, huh?
These targets are all inter-connected somehow.
I'm saying these aren't random acts of terrorism.
Hey so, Nine. That last riddle we gave.
Do you think it was a bit too simple?
It would be problematic if it
was too hard for them to solve.
I knew you made it easy on purpose!
Yes. This Detective Shibazaki should have figured out the
connection between all of the bombing locations by now.
Since we never make any demands,
he's the kind who would look for a
connection to figure out what we're after.
You sure have put a lot of
trust into a government official.
What?
Heh! Nothin'. It was a joke.
Governor Aohara, office in the Tokyo Metro
Government Building, site of the first bombing.
Chief of Police at Roppongi Station,
location of the second bombing.
A former Chief Cabinet Secretary and owner of the building
next to Shirahige Shrine, the failed third bombing.
And last, head of the municipal organization
that manages the Shuto Shinjuku Line.
There's a connection between 'em.
They all took part in a seminar
run by the Rising Peace Academy.
The Rising Peace Academy?
Yeah.
'Promoting interaction between
the government and its people'.
Looks like a non-profit on the surface.
But their seminars have attracted a lot
of big-wig types over the last few years.
From politicians to captains of industry.
Pretty weird.
No, not weird.
This connects the dots between their targets.
You're probably overthinking it.
These kids just wanna watch our reaction.
Not make a point.
Oh, you've got some insight on terrorist psychology? Huh?
Uh... I wonder if they're done.
Dealing with the bomb, that is.
Anything?
Whole lotta nada.
That's strange. There's been no
report about the bomb being removed.
Maybe the riddle was still too hard for them?
I don't think so. That detective's smart.
He should've figured it out.
So what do we do?
At this rate, in a little over
an hour, we'll be mass murderers.
Not to worry. This will deactivate it.
Huh?
What's wrong?
That's crazy. No signal.
What the...? Oh, ya gotta be kidding me!
Wha...?
No signal.
Are you there?
Weird.
None on this one, either.
Every carrier, same issue, same time?
That's impossible!
No, it's possible.
Someone's creating this interference on purpose.
Like who? Nine?
Have you lost your mind?
Why haven't your people removed the bomb?
We were given orders. Straight from the top.
What?
They said the special assault team would take care of it
and we should standby for further instruction.
But sir!
So we just twiddle our thumbs?
That's what you're saying?
I'm afraid so.
And this electromagnetic jamming.
It's got something to do with this?
Look. I am out of the loop.
Shibazaki! Don't do anything stupid!
Has the past taught you nothing at all?
Shibazaki!
Check in. Can you hear me, Twelve?
Loud and clear.
Let's work fast.
I can calculate the general location of the train car.
But I won't be able to pinpoint it yet.
For that, I'm gonna need to
access their system via a backdoor.
I'll give you a more precise location later.
The bomb is set to blow at eight sharp.
We have to personally retrieve it before then.
Remove and disarm the bomb in 50 minutes, undetected?
Correct.
What is this, Mission: Impossible?
This is the only way.
We used five kilos of gunpowder this time around.
That's more than enough to destroy the entire train car.
Well, that's awesome.
They should've solved the riddle by now.
So what are the police up to?
The electromagnetic interference
is blocking out cell service.
I don't think this is a coincidence.
Are you telling me someone outside the
police department is creating these problems
to try and screw things up?
And whoever that is, doesn't want the bomb stopped.
They want the thing to go off?
It's the logical answer.
That person's nutso.
To say the least. Yes. I'm in.
Wait. Whaddaya mean by "multiple signals?"
Damn it! There's no way another train car
could have the same signature. It's impossible.
Obviously not.
We're being cornered with fake operations data.
Someone's doing this.
There must have been a trap in the backdoor I used
to infiltrate the train company's security interface.
So the person behind all of this
knew we'd hack into the system.
They set up a fake backdoor to trap us?
Looks that way. Wait, here.
I'll make another sweep through the normal OS now.
Try to track the train down.
In the meantime, hop onto the train car closest to you.
But we only have 30 minutes.
We don't have a choice!
Gotcha! No rest for the wicked!
What?
They cracked their way in?
Whoever this is knows their stuff.
No way.
Ready or not!
Here I come!
It's her. She's back.
Shibazaki. I've been looking for you.
Hamura. Any thoughts on this?
On?
They dispatched the Special Assault
Team without an official runner,
and Kurahashi said the order came from top brass.
Don't tell me...
Do I have to?
Y'know ferreting out rats is a real pain in the ass.
You just gonna stand there, or are you comin'?
Coming!
Come on, 9-18! Damn!
Uh, excuse me. I was...
Son of a...
Anyway. Could you...
What? It's close by?
If I head there from here, I might make it.
Sounds good. I can wipe the camera feeds!
Thanks!
It's a bomb! Run, hurry!
There's a bomb on the train!
You wanna explain what the hell's goin' on?
Shibazaki! Where was Special Assault Team?
You pulled us off the bomb so they could deal with it!
I was given every assurance they would.
Yeah, from who? What bastard let this happen?
Everyone please, try to stay calm!
Exit the subway in an orderly fashion.
Nine! Can you hear me?
Yeah.
Are you okay? Are you alive?
Of course I am.
Please calm down, help is on the way!
Hey, Nine. Is this?
Yeah. There's no doubt.
Five is back.
Such a spectacular fireworks display.
Perfect for celebrating our reunion.
Don't you think? Nine?