It's the police. Hey.
Do you know why they're here?
No clue.
Guardroom. What do you need?
All right. That's good.
Huh?
What's that about?
Think it's a drill?
I dunno.
Hey, what's going on?
Watch out!
I dont' know, sir!
He's getting away! Gate Three!
Stop! Hold fire!
Woo-ho-hoo!
Man, it's stupid hot.
That makes sense. I mean, it is summer.
Come on, Nine.
Don't tell me you're not dyin' out here.
Speaking of don'ts. Don't do anything to stand out.
Try to act like a normal student.
Look! Kururin!
It's so cute how his bangs look like ant antennae.
I love that guy.
I know. Did you listen to me at all?
Ooh, I can smell chlorine!
Do it already. Jump.
Don't be lame, Lame Lisa.
Yeah! Dive!
Fly away, Lisa! Forever!
Hey ladies, whatcha up to?
What?
Um. Do we know this creeper?
Oh! I get it! This is what they call "bullying"!
No, it's not. She told us she wanted to swim.
We're basically in a resort.
Might as well take advantage.
Right?
Are you serious?
You're gonna swim with your clothes on?
Yeah. I guess so.
'Cause I'm really hot.
Cool, me, too!
Woo-hoo!
That smile... It reminds me of something.
The sun on a hot summer day.
But those eyes are like ice.
This is our new transfer student,
Arata Kokonoe.
It's nice to meet all of you.
Right. Okay, let's see.
Looks like you can take a seat by the window over there.
I call dibs.
Hooker!
You already have a boyfriend!
Wow...
This is, um, wow, uh, Toji Hisami. Yeah.
Jambo!
We-hell!
How sweet. Your boyfriend's in our class, Lame Lisa!
And a cat won the internet, Shibazaki.
That sucker is owning the moonwalk!
I bet.
I'm sure your shogi game's so
much more interesting, though.
Huh? What is that? You have to check this out.
Look!
Tch.
A'ight, people!
Let's do this!
What's up? I'm Sphinx Number One.
Mm-hmm!
I'm lucky Spinx Number Two, and I heart curry!
So here's the thing, we've got
tomorrow's weather forecast for you all!
After three PM, Tokyo will be enveloped in darkness.
Ooh!
Large sparks will fly, scattered around the Shinjuku area!
I'd be careful out there if I were you.
We wouldn't want anyone to die.
Well then, folks, have a nice day!
Really, this crap is already showing up?
These kids aren't even out for summer break, yet.
Hey!
Try to remember you both are still on the clock.
Stop screwing around.
Oh, sorry, I, uh.
Shibazaki.
You're not still acting like a detective, are you?
Because you're not one.
Yeah, I know. I am well aware.
Hello? We're talking to you!
Can you hear us? Hey, Arata!
Seriously!
So, can I have your number?
Yeah, I want it too!
Me three!
Let me send you my...
No. I don't have a cell phone or anything.
Huh?
What?
Idiot.
Oh, hey! How's it goin'?
I've already heard people talking about you, so guess.
Not what we need right now.
It's not a big deal, people are talking about you, too.
No, they're not.
Yes, they are.
Shiori Nonami and Haruka Asami had a lot to say about you.
Apparently, they think you're, like, "so hot."
Why are you taking the time to remember
names of students from other classes?
It's just not necessary.
Yeah, yeah.
Look, it's Lisa.
Poor girl's takin' her lunch with her.
Bet she eats in the bathroom.
Do not get involved.
I won't.
More texts from Mom.
Nine?
Oh. Same nightmare again?
To be honest, I had a feeling that would happen.
Well because of Lisa.
Her eyes look exactly like those
kids' eyes from the institution.
You know it's true.
All of those children were weak.
That's why they died.
We were weak, too.
That's why we couldn't save them.
And now?
Now, things are different. We're strong.
Alright.
Right?
I mean, yeah.
So adorable.
Three more minutes.
26 until the power generators
kick in and electricity is restored.
Roger!
Are we straight on the plan?
Who do you think I am?
It's almost time.
I wish they'd all disappear.
Plus wi-fi... Uh?
The lights?
Huh? Is it a blackout?
Hm? Ah, it'll switch to the backup generators eventually.
Yeah, I guess.
"After three PM, Tokyo will be enveloped in darkness."
Mukasa can you find that video
from yesterday on your phone?
Huh?
Your attention, please.
You'll need to use the stairs to exit the building.
I'm scared, mommy. I'm scared.
Mommy! Mom!
It's you. Hey.
You really shouldn't be in here, you know.
Eh?
So what... are you playing hide and seek?
You can borrow that.
It sucks hiding all by yourself. Now you won't get lonely.
Oh, I, uh!
Promise me something.
Don't let go of him. Not until I say it's okay.
Hold up. What is this? Where are you going?
After three PM, Tokyo will be enveloped by darkness.
Ooh!
Large sparks will fly, scattered around the Shinjuku area!
Nah. This has to be a coincidence.
Wouldn't want anyone to die.
Well then, folks...
Did all go according to plan?
Mostly. There's just one little hitch.
It's Lisa. She saw me inside.
I left her in there.
If we don't do anything, she'll most likely get killed,
but I did give her a Kururin.
This way,
we can either put her out of her misery,
or we can go in and save her.
I figured you'd like to have a choice in how we proceed.
What is this?
Are you trying to make me relive that moment?
You know she's not one of us.
I'm aware. It's just...
I dunno.
I thought maybe this could
help you stop having that dream.
Hello.
Huh?
Did you keep your promise and hang onto him?
Give it. Listen up, you have two options here.
Choice one, you can die where you stand.
Or choice two: you can become an accomplice.
Accomplice?
It's up to you. What'll it be?
I, uh, I don't know.
I don't...
...wanna die.
Alright!
From the resonance I'm getting on my end,
you must be in the stairwell. What floor?
Uh, the sixteenth?
Got it.
Take the stairs all the way down to the fourth floor.
When you get to Four, take 15 steps forward.
Then move 23 steps to the right.
Take 12 steps forward. When you're there...
...leave the plushie at your feet.
Go back the way you came and hide
in the hallway. Keep to the shadows.
Do it now!
Do it already.
Fly away, Lisa! Forever!
It's up to you. What'll it be?
So, what? Playing hide and seek?
Remember, you chose this path. Not us.
Do you understand what you've agreed to?
I...
Lisa, there's no going back.
That smile...
It reminds me of something.
The sun on a hot summer day.
But those eyes are like ice.