[ANN] My story is set
in the olden days,
when we of France were still
at war with England.
There was a young witch
living near our village,
who hated wars with every
beat of her fiery heart.
The witch plied no trade in
curses or hexes or evil deeds.
Instead, she sought to end all
conflict by sheer force of will.
Her name was Maria. The same
as the Blessed Mother.
And just like her holiest of
namesakes, Maria was a virgin.
That fateful day, despite
the loss of her magic,
Maria sped towards the
battlefield with all haste.
Was it recklessness or courage
that burned within her?
Or perhaps...
[GILBERT whimpers]
[RÉGLISSE] Meow.
The shield's fading, Master!
[GILBERT gasps] Dear God. The
medicine was the work of a--!
Brother Gilbert.
What of the witches?
They must all be
brought to judgment,
and burn for their audacity.
Huh? So, the weird fog
that paralyzed me was...
Forgive me, Maria.
Had I known their intent,
I never would've
sold the mixture.
Nobody blames you, Edwina.
None of this was your fault.
[RÉGLISSE] The monk said the
barber-surgeon had need of it,
so I merely assumed.
Master! What if the gunpowder
was also used for villainy?
It was meant as a curative.
Oh, Réglisse, I shudder to
think what they did with it!
Pardon me, but do you think
the other guild members
are going to come?
Well, Viv did say she
would track them down.
No! I can't believe I left her
behind at my place!
[RÉGLISSE]
I'll go to her right meow!
Fly like the wind!
And the battle.
How far away are we?
Do you really wanna go there?
Even without use of
your magic, Maria?
[MARIA] It doesn't matter!
I have to be there!
[CHANTAL] Anybody know why she
had us rush back home?
The gate's been blown to bits.
There's not much
left to see here.
Not to mention, there's
no sign of Viv or Edwina.
[SUZANNE] Say, what if
the trouble Maria's in
has nothing to do with
the fight below?
You don't think that the Church
got the better of her, do you?
--[ALL] Not a chance.
--[explosion]
Uh?
[FRENCH MESSENGER A]
Milord, the gate has fallen.
The English continue
to harry our vanguard,
but our victory's
all but assured!
Excellent! Notify our forces to
advance! Lay claim to the fort!
Sir!
[GUILLAUME]
At last, a day of reckoning.
I wonder. Will Joseph finally
unsheathe his blade?
[GALFA grunts]
[JOSEPH groans]
Look at you!
[GALFA chuckles] What's the
matter, Joseph? Afraid?
[JOSEPH]
Tell me!
[GALFA]
Huh?
[JOSEPH] Why did you steal...
Lady Maria's purity?
[GALFA] Ha, ha.
That's just work, y'know?
Devil.
Damned if I'd bed a witch
otherwise, pretty or not.
Who knows what pox I'd catch?
[JOSEPH]
Galfa!
[GALFA grunts]
[GALFA chuckles]
[JOSEPH]
Was it the monk?
Did the monk pay
you to do this?
[GALFA] Why don't you
go ask him yourself?
[GALFA chuckles]
Show a little respect, Joseph.
After all, this is a church.
Why are you so angry?
So what if I took your
little witch's virginity?
That's far better than her being
burnt at the stake, ain't it?
[JOSEPH] How dare you? You speak
as though you did her a mercy!
[GALFA] Maybe you're just mad
that I've tasted her favors,
and you haven't!
[JOSEPH yells]
Put down the sword. You don't
get that arm tended to
right quick, you're
gonna bleed to death.
Even if you live,
Guillaume will abandon you.
Your master's ashamed.
All this for a witch.
God, what a waste.
You could never know her value!
I'll make you beg for your
life at milady's feet!
[GALFA]
Hmph. I'd like to see you try.
[meow]
I'm awake, you can
stop mewling now.
You shouldn't be
sitting up yet.
Just relax. I'll fetch
your medicine--
[VIV]
Hold on.
How is she?
Maria? My master rushed
in and saved her.
Wait, Edwina?
[RÉGLISSE] Uh-huh. And now the
two of them are heading to a
fortress, which your besieged
countrymen fight to defend.
What for?
[RÉGLISSE]
I'm not entirely sure.
Devoid of magic as she is,
it's not like Maria can
halt the bloodshed.
My goodness.
What a spine she's got.
[clanging]
Now! Claim recompense!
[MERCENARY A]
Look alive, Lolotte!
You'll miss out on the best
of the spoils at this rate!
Yeah, thanks for the tip!
Those mercenaries
vex me almost unto death!
Lay low the defenders before
you pick the town dry!
[BELLA]
I guess it's almost over.
Probably no money to be made
around these parts anyway.
I wonder if we should
head east next.
[CHANTAL]
Hm...
What's wrong?
I can't figure out why humans
continue to do the same
things over and over again.
Look at them scramble
about, like ants.
[panting]
Hey, there's plenty of fish
in the sea, you know.
Go hook yourself a fresh one.
[JOSEPH gasps]
[GALFA growls] Those eyes!
I've a mind to pluck 'em out!
I've hated 'em from the very
first time you looked at me!
You look at the world like a
goddamn babe in arms!
I don't know who
your father was,
but I'm sure as hell you never
had to worry about food
or clothes or a roof
over your head!
[GALFA] That's why you're here,
bleeding like a stuck pig
over your damned Maria!
'Cause you've never had
to face the consequences!
Cry out! Do it!
Beg for your life!
Stop worrying about the witch
and save your own neck!
Come on!
Ever since I met you, I've
been envious of you, Galfa.
Envious of what you possessed!
The hell?
[JOSEPH] Ambition guides
your every step.
And though it is a path of evil,
you have the strength to
see your dream fulfilled!
You do what you want, in pursuit
of a larger goal, and in that,
you remind me of no one
more than Maria herself!
[GALFA]
What?
[JOSEPH]
And that's why...
You will beg her forgiveness for
daring to threaten her!
How dare you compare
me to that witch?!
I should cut out your tongue
for saying that, Joseph!
Has the girl had
to fight, and claw,
and kill for
everything she's got?
[JOSEPH] I don't want to kill
you, Galfa, but I will!
You bade me to deliver
medicine crafted by a witch.
Did you know the provenance
of those herbs
when you sent me to fetch them,
time and again?
I did.
Uh? Why would you
do such a thing?
That medicine was sorely
needed by the people.
The hands what mixed
it matter not.
[GILBERT] You speak
of contact with a witch
in phrases cavalier.
Feel you no shred of remorse?
If something can be exploited in
pursuit of bettering this world,
I do not blush at it.
It doesn't matter if it's
politics, war, witches.
Even God Himself.
[GILBERT gasps]
[GALFA grunts]
[sighs] Maybe Viv and Maria
aren't coming out.
[CHANTAL]
Uh...
[SUZANNE]
What is that?!
[BELLA]
Huh?
[MARIA]
Everybody outta the way!
[ALL scream]
That sounded like...
...Maria!
[CANNON SOLDIER A yawns]
Huh?
Uh, Vraiment?
Hey! Maria! Your staff!
[sighs] Or, just go.
We need to find Joseph! Hurry!
[PRIAPUS]
Right, Master!
[ARTEMIS]
Leave it to us!
[JOSEPH yells]
[PRIAPUS]
Artemis! He's over here!
[ARTEMIS]
Where?
[PRIAPUS]
What do we do now?
At this rate, he's not going
to last much longer!
[ARTEMIS]
I'll fetch Maria!
[PRIAPUS]
Take this!
[JOSEPH gasps]
[GALFA]
Get away!
[JOSEPH]
Priapus? But how?
I'm gonna run you through!
[MARIA yells]
[GALFA]
Huh?
[GALFA groans]
[MARIA grunts]
[ARTEMIS]
Are you all right?
Well. I still
don't have one.
[JOSEPH] Lady Maria?
What are you doing here?
Need you ask? I was
saving your life.
Yes, Milady. I'm in your debt.
[MARIA]
May I ask you something?
Yes.
How dumb do
you have to be
to try your hand
at warfare again?!
Uh! What?
[MARIA] Remember that battle
after you kissed my hand?
I had to save you then, too!
[GALFA]
Look who's here!
Ah. Came back for more,
huh? Very good.
[JOSEPH]
Milady! The help is appreciated,
but get yourself to safety!
I will take care
of this villain!
It's my lucky day.
What I started in
your hut the other night.
Right in front of dear Joseph.
How dare you
speak to her like that?
Joseph?
I'm sick to death of you
judging me, you bastard!
[JOSEPH grunts]
[GALFA grunts]
Damn it!
Why, you...!
[JOSEPH yells]
[GALFA groans]
[JOSEPH screams]
[ARTEMIS gasps]
[JOSEPH] How dare you?!
How dare you say such a thing?!
[JOSEPH grunting]
Joseph?
Joseph!
[MARIA]
Stop it! You have to stop!
You're going to
kill him! Please!
[JOSEPH gasps]
But, I'd...
[LOLOTTE]
Joseph? Fancy meeting you here!
You haven't seen Galfa
about, have you?
He said he wanted to loot
the church's sacristy.
What a sight!
Very well done, Joseph.
[GALFA groans]
Oh, is he still alive?
I'm sure he had it coming,
but how 'bout you let me
take him off your hands?
Huh?
Yeah?
[LOLOTTE] Hold this for me,
would you, dear?
[MARIA]
Uh!
[LOLOTTE]
If a chief isn't around...
Sometimes the nobles try to
welsh on the agreed-upon rate.
Why the long face, kid? You just
bested a killer in combat.
You're allowed to smile.
♪ Going to grave with
coins in hand ♪
♪ Make we no reprimand ♪
♪ The reaper takes his due
No matter where we die ♪
♪ It matters not to I.
O lady fortune deal my hand ♪
♪ Whether ghastly or grand ♪
♪ No matter what we do
The fates will cast the die ♪
♪ And let their arrows fly ♪
--[CERNUNNOS] Young one.
--[ANN yelps]
What brings you to this place?
[ANN]
Who's there?
[CERNUNNOS]
I am no one. Forgotten.
I keep a lonely vigil.
Are you a friend of
Maria's, perhaps?
[CERNUNNOS]
Perhaps. But are you?
How come people treat
Maria so badly?
Why are they mean?
[CERNUNNOS]
Just forget.
[ANN]
Huh?
[CERNUNNOS]
Let it fade.
Forgetting can be
a mercy, child.
Maria is not a
member of humanity.
Forget her, and the pain
you feel shall be--
No! I won't!
Maria's one of my
favorite people!
I'll never forget her!
So don't you try to take Maria
away from me, you buncha smoke!
[CERNUNNOS chuckles]
[MARIA] That's right. If Edwina
hadn't come when she did,
they would have
burned me at the stake.
[JOSEPH]
Burned at the stake?
How did they reach a
verdict so quickly?
And Le Comte said you would
be banished from the land,
at the very worst.
What am I saying?
Are you badly hurt?
Hey. We can talk
about this later.
If only that were so.
Lady Maria, leave this
place without me.
[MARIA]
Huh?
I do not have the right
to stand at your side
after how I've behaved.
[MARIA]
What are you going on about?
I, well... I share your
vision of a world in which
bloodshed has no place,
but that didn't stop me
from beating a man near
unto death just now.
[MARIA]
It weighs upon you?
It does. My whole life.
I have strived to be
an upright person.
Righteous in word and
deed to all whom I meet.
And now, I espy
the beast within.
Joseph, you attacked him
to keep me free from harm.
[JOSEPH]
That's true, Milady,
but even after you
were safe, I beat him.
He'd earned a bit of that.
[JOSEPH]
No. I'm merely a puppet
that leaps at his
master's command.
A painted fool, devoid
of purpose or will.
[ARTEMIS] Did he always grate
so on the nerves, Priapus?
[PRIAPUS] He should count his
blessings. One, especially.
[MARIA] We can figure all this
out after we've gone home.
[JOSEPH] How can you
say that so blithely?
In your hour of tribulation,
I wasn't able to free
you from your bondage!
Lady Maria. Leave me sitting
in this church, I beg of you.
In light of my failings, such
abandonment is all I deserve--
[MARIA]
Shut up!
[ARTEMIS]
Yes, thank you!
[JOSEPH grunts]
What is wrong with you?!
All this whimpering
is insufferable!
"O happy day! I won!
All is well!"
That's all you needed to say!
Why do you insist on taking
the whip to your own back?
[JOSEPH]
Milady, I.
Come on, Joseph! Spit it out!
Never mind...
[MARIA groans] You've got a
lot of nerve, going off to war.
Risking your life while I
was powerless to save it!
My duty is to my liege lord,
Le Comte Guillaume.
He ordered me hither, so I went.
Wait. Why did you come here,
instead of returning to
the safety of the woods?
[MARIA growls]
Because you needed rescuing,
you doe-eyed simpleton!
[JOSEPH]
But I... I'm no one.
Well, you're someone
to me, all right?
If you want to
beg my pardon,
how about for putting that
dusty Count Guillaume
ahead of me all the time?
Just once, why not do
what you want to do, huh?
How?!
You are the master of
your own fate, Milady.
But one such as I, I lack the
magic and force of will
to do just as I want!
Huh? Magic has nothing
to do with this!
All you need to do is
follow your heart!
You think...
I didn't want to?
It slaughtered me
departing for battle,
knowing all the while they'd
locked you in a damned cage!
[MARIA] The past is dead and
gone, Joseph! Follow it now!
[JOSEPH]
I'm not at liberty to do that!
--[MARIA] Yes, you are!
--[JOSEPH] Tell me how!
[MARIA]
Just stay with me!
[gasps]
Stay with me, Joseph! Be my
bulwark, and my comfort!
Please, I need you.
[MARIA]
I'm not some force of nature!
I fall prey to doubt,
and regret, and fear!
I lose sight of who I am and
second-guess my actions
again and again, with
no answer to be found!
That doubt disappears every
time you but look at me!
It melts clean away!
Stay with me!
Now and always!
[PRIAPUS]
Um...
[ARTEMIS]
Maria?
[MARIA]
What?
[PRIAPUS] I could be wrong,
but it sure sounded like...
[ARTEMIS]
...you were proposing.
[MARIA]
Huh?
[JOSEPH]
I... I'm sorry, Milady.
Uh. My mouth outpaced my brain.
Hearing you speak with
such resolve all the time.
It's easy to forget that a very
fragile heart beats within you.
Would that I were its bulwark.
Huh?
[JOSEPH] Yes. I know now what
I desire above all else.
In truth, there was never
a time when I did not.
No matter how dire
the hardship.
I will face it with courage
if you are beside me.
I love you with all of my heart.
Please, marry me, Maria.
[MARIA laughs]
[ANN]
Uh?
[CERNUNNOS]
This feeling!
Wait. What?
[CERNUNNOS]
It's Maria!
"Magic dwelleth in
a steadfast heart."
She now lives the
truth of that tenet.
[ANN laughs]
Her magic's back,
and then some.
[GUILLAUME gasps]
What's going on?
[ENGLISH SOLDIER A] Our
weaponry! Damn it! Not again!
[CANNON BEARER CHIEF]
She's stealing the bombard!
Look! Isn't that Maria?
She's using her
magic so brazenly!
So, are my bruises gone?
Yes. [grunts]
[EDWINA chuckles]
[MARIA]
Everybody! Thank you all!
The French and
the British alike!
Every living thing
and souls departed.
I thank you from the
very bottom of my heart!
I couldn't have found
my way back without you!
Now, at last!
I found my happiness!
[PRIAPUS laughs]
Look at how happy she is.
[ARTEMIS]
Wait 'til she kisses him.
[MARIA laughs]
Archers! Shoot her
right out of the sky!
[FRENCH VASSAL A]
Our bows are aloft!
[GUILLAUME growls]
[MARIA] Everyone! Isn't it time
that we all returned home?
Come to me. Cauldron!
Those forgotten by men of the
new faith, here, shake off the
dust of bygone centuries, and
heed this witch of the hearth!
Arise, with tooth and claw, and
scatter these soldiers homeward!
[FRENCH SOLDIER A]
There's so many of them!
[FRENCH SOLDIER B]
Run for your lives!
[FRENCH SOLDIER C]
Don't look back!
[MARIA]
They'll only pose a threat
if you're fool enough to tarry.
You have my guarantee! The
witch Maria hates bloodshed!
Take my words to heart!
Now, go!
[JOSEPH yelps]
[ARTEMIS]
Maria!
[ALL gasp]
Why are we leaving here?
I need to give that brat
his comeuppance.
What'll ya do when he makes
a fright of your face again?
[GALFA] Who says
I lost to him, huh?
[LOLOTTE]
Any with eyes in their head.
[GALFA]
I'll cut him to ribbons!
[LOLOTTE]
Be still my heart!
[GALFA]
Saucy harlot!
[JOSEPH]
Lady Maria!
Just Maria!
A slip of the tongue.
So where are we going?
I'm being summoned
for a tête-à-tête.
Good day to you,
Michael! Look!
I guess the two of
us are paramours!
[OLD ANN]
Her name was Maria.
The same as the Blessed Mother,
and just like her
holiest of namesakes.