[JUNKER] The whole thing
started a few decades ago,
when a rogue nation launched
a genetic bio-weapon.
[JUNKER] Not long after,
another country retaliated
with a thermonuclear warhead.
The war went on for years.
Millions of people all
over the world died.
And the ones who lived have no
interest in space or the stars.
I guess I say all of that so
you know things have changed.
The world you knew,
and everything you
remember about it,
doesn't even exist anymore.
[YUMEMI] I have made
many attempts to connect
to the support
center's databases,
but I can never get through.
Shocker.
[YUMEMI]
On another note, Mr. Customer,
if you don't mind my
changing the subject--
Here's this tool.
I thought you may need
to use it for the repairs.
[JUNKER]
Well, I don't.
Oh, really?
Like I said, don't do
anything unless I ask.
Yes. Order acknowledged.
Excuse me, Mr. Customer.
Do you think you'll be using
this tool anytime soon?
[JUNKER] Why don't you use it
to clamp your mouth shut?
[JUNKER] I have no idea
why I'm even doing this.
Boredom, maybe?
A change of pace?
I do know it's dangerous to
leave now that it's dark out.
I guess I've got
nothing better to do.
Also, I underestimated
how hard it would be.
This ancient machine is more
complicated than I thought.
I've been wondering.
How much time do you
estimate it will take
before the repairs to
Miss Jena are completed?
Who knows? But it
might be a while.
[YUMEMI]
Do you think you will finish up
in time for tomorrow's
11 AM projection?
[JUNKER]
It doesn't look that way.
[YUMEMI] If that's the case,
do you mind if I put up a sign
saying the projection
is cancelled?
[JUNKER]
Do whatever you want.
Consent acknowledged.
I will register this
in my database
as a critical directive.
Hey, this lightbulb is burnt out
and I think that's
part of the problem.
Do you have another
one somewhere?
[YUMEMI] Mr. Customer, I
apologize for interrupting you,
however, I must inform you
that it's almost midnight.
According to my
established protocol,
at that hour I must switch
my functions to sleep mode.
[JUNKER]
What?
[YUMEMI]
At 9 o'clock tomorrow morning,
I will reactivate.
Upon that time,
I will have 75 hours
of operational time remaining.
I must go now.
Have a good night.
Hey, wait a minute!
Whatever.
[YUMEMI]
Mr. Customer!
Good morning, Mr. Customer.
Did you sleep well?
Were you trying to talk to me?
Yes.
Sorry. I was dreaming.
Oh, that's wonderful to hear.
Were you having
a pleasant dream?
Nope.
Robots are incapable of that.
So the idea has always
been fascinating to me.
To be perfectly honest with you,
I long to know what
it's like to have them!
Most of them aren't
worth longing for.
Dreaming's kind of overrated.
Is that really true?
[JUNKER]
Wait a second.
Let me get this straight,
you mean you're only
operational for one week
outta the whole year?
[YUMEMI]
Yes.
For the last 30 years, the
amount of electricity supplied
to the department store has
significantly decreased.
Per protocol, I entered
energy-saver mode
when power levels declined.
I powered on two
days ago at 9 AM.
It's the first time I've
operated in 8,601 hours.
[JUNKER sighs]
[JUNKER] I showed up
right at the perfect time.
What're the odds?
[YUMEMI]
Five days from now, at midnight,
I will return to my long-term
power charging mode.
Right, I get it.
[JUNKER] I can't believe
the emergency power
is even on anymore.
[YUMEMI]
I've been wondering,
why are you using that
flask to collect the rain?
[JUNKER] I'm gonna drink it.
I am human, after all.
Unlike you, I need
water to live.
If you're thirsty, I would
be delighted to prepare
a nice beverage for you.
[JUNKER]
Are you serious?
[YUMEMI]
Yes.
I don't mean to boast,
but I have been programmed
to make an incredible
cup of tea.
Or would you prefer a cup
of freshly ground coffee?
Coffee, huh?
Do know where to
find any alcohol?
Like, bottles of distilled
liquor with unbroken seals?
That kind of thing is
particularly important to me,
you know.
Yes. We have that!
Really? Where is it?
Well, the liquor store
is on floor B1.
You can find a wide
variety of spirits there.
Right. Sure I can.
Great!
On another note, Mr. Customer,
what is the situation
with Miss Jena?
Are there any updates on
the state of her repairs?
Same as it was last night.
I'm still working on it.
Understood.
In that case, I will announce
that today's presentation
is cancelled.
[JUNKER]
Hey, so, uh,
do you know where I could find
any replacement lightbulbs?
[YUMEMI] Two of the
latest 905 series models
were recently assigned
to work at the help desk
by the main entrance
of the store.
Both of them are top of
the line FT editions.
And they are designed to look
much more grown up than I do.
Their faceplates were made
with superb, life-like detail,
and they can even
shed real tears.
Robo-tears, weird.
'Kay, you can turn it on now.
[YUMEMI]
Yes, sir, switching it on.
This one's working. Good.
So does that mean
you can't shed tears?
Hold this.
Yes. I am one of
the older models.
Crying was introduced
in the 9,000 series,
just before the 905s.
Oh, yeah? That's
really fascinating.
Now--
Flip it.
[YUMEMI]
Yes, sir.
Looks like we have a dud.
So we've got two live bulbs.
By the way, would
it be all right
if I removed this maintenance
cable from my ear port?
It's just that I'm usually not
allowed to let customers
see my emergency procedures,
and I feel rather ashamed.
Hold on a bit. I wanna
try the motors first.
Yes, I understand, sir.
May I ask a question?
[JUNKER]
Seems I can't stop you.
I would really like to know,
what does it feel like
when you're crying?
[JUNKER]
I don't know.
I guess it just
feels like crying.
I've never thought about it.
Oh, really?
Well, this might sound strange,
but I have always wanted
to be able to cry.
I'm just a bargain
edition model.
I don't have that capability.
But I would love
to experience tears.
It's not as great as
you make it out to be.
[YUMEMI]
Do you really mean that?
Yeah. I'd rather not cry.
All right, move the
latitude axis upwards.
Slowly, though.
[YUMEMI]
Yes, sir.
For your safety, please move
out of the radius of revolution
while Miss Jena is in motion.
[humming]
[BOTH sigh]
Excuse me. How much longer
do you think it will take?
When do you estimate the repairs
to Miss Jena will be complete?
I can't tell.
Do you believe that
you will be finished
in time for tomorrow's
11 AM projection?
I dunno. Pray it will be.
Okay. To which god do you
recommend that I pray for help?
What did you say?
For example, I know
about the Greek gods.
There's Zeus, Athena,
Apollo, Hermes,
Artemis, Demeter,
Poseidon, Hades.
You sure know a lot.
Well, pray to whichever
one you like best.
Right. In that case, I would
like to pray to Dionysus.
[JUNKER]
Who in the hell is that?
The god of wine and fertility.
In Rome, he's referred
to as Bacchus.
I thought this god would be most
to your liking, Mr. Customer.
You know how I feel
about alcohol.
But wouldn't it make more sense
if you prayed to your
god instead of mine?
What do you mean by my god?
[JUNKER]
The god of robots, of course.
[YUMEMI]
I have searched my database,
and no information on a
god of robots turns up.
[sighs]
That figures.
[YUMEMI] That being said, I did
discover something related
that I would like to share.
This is from a meeting we had
about the mythological Heavens,
which we featured in
a special presentation.
I saved it in my
database as a hologram.
[YUMEMI] Is there a Heaven
for deactivated robots, too?
Of course! Robots get
their own Heaven!
Right, Manager?
Uh. Yes. That's the truth.
[YUMEMI]
What is it like in Robot Heaven?
Well, let's see... Uh...
No one ever malfunctions,
and batteries last forever,
and everyone can dream and cry!
What else?
Um, there's no such
thing as software bugs,
and parts never need to
be repaired or replaced!
And on top of all that,
every little wish you've ever
had will come true there!
[YUMEMI]
Is all of that real?
--Yeah. Sure.
--Uh-huh!
Well, there you go.
Then the god of your kind
is up in Robot Heaven.
Pray to that one.
Good. New critical data
registered in the database.
I'm quite happy to
learn about this.
It's nice to have a god.
I know of one thing for
which I would like to pray
to my new deity, now
that I know one exists.
Oh, yeah?
What's that? What would
you ask god for?
Well, Robot Heaven--
[JUNKER]
Hm? What's the matter?
Mr. Customer, I'm sorry,
but midnight approaches.
As per established protocol
due to limited power,
I'll have to continue with
this conversation later.
At this time, I must activate
sleep mode until tomorrow.
It got late fast, huh?
I'll resume normal
function at 9 AM.
Remaining operation time
upon reactivation
will be exactly 60 hours.
Good night. See you tomorrow.
[YUMEMI] Come visit our
majestic planetarium!
The sparkling, eternal Heavens,
whose beauty will never
fade, no matter what!
Join us and see for yourself?
All the stars in
the sky await you!
[JUNKER]
Hey, I'm done with the repairs.
Oh, Mr. Customer.
Do you mean to say that
Miss Jena has been restored
to her full
operational capacity?
Yeah. That's right.
I did the best I could,
and I'm pretty sure it worked.
[giggles]