Hmm.
That was quite some shooting, Kiramman.
Did my parents pay you to let me win?
Hmm… That's a serious accusation.
You held your shot, I saw you.
The trophy is yours. You earned it.
You haven't answered my question.
No, your parents didn't pay me.
I just thought you deserved it.
I'm an enforcer.
For me, knowing how to handle this
weapon means being able to protect people.
To be of service to the city. And that's trophy enough.
Begs the question, young
Kiramman. What are you shooting for?
I took a look at your file.
There's no record of you or
your crimes. What are you here for?
My sunny personality.
You attacked an inmate. Why?
Why not?
He was a witness in an ongoing investigation.
Hmm, bummer.
This was a waste of time.
Couldn't have put it better.
Hey, give Silco a kiss on that
winning eye of his, will you?
Silco? The industrialist?
Okay, this is getting old.
Can you just send in whoever's gonna kick the
shit out of me, so I can get on with my night?
Does this mean anything to you?
Where did you get this?
My question first. He worked for Silco?
Uh, they all do.
How can anyone not know that? Where did you find this?
There was an attack. This is evidence.
I need proof if I'm to believe
what you're saying about Silco.
I could get it for you. Just not from in here.
In what mad world would I trust someone like you?
Someone like me?
You enforcers are all the same. Just
asshole criminals in fancy uniforms.
You know what? Find Silco yourself.
I will, thank you.
Hmm… Undercity's gonna eat you alive.
I've got orders from Councilor
Talis, concerning Inmate 516.
Not cooperative, huh?
You, uh, you want us to have a chat with her?
No.
Oh.
It's for her release.
Huh. Since when's he a Councilor?
Since today.
How many chats have you had with her?
You know, I never even thought to count.
These brave Enforcers sacrificed their
lives to defend the values of our great city.
To some, they are mothers…
fathers,
sons…
daughters…
but to all, they are heroes.
Who was this, Daddy?
A good woman.
You said you could control her. I lost six officers. Six!
She pushed it too far this time. The Council's up in arms.
I can't make this go away for you
unless you give me something to work with.
Arresting her would be doing you a favor.
I don't need favors.
I need you to do your job.
The Firelights have been a thorn in both our sides.
They ambushed my shipment at the
Hexgates on the same day as the attack.
It seems to me the Council has its culprit.
Oh, that's tidy for you.
What if I'm not interested in playing along?
We've accomplished a lot together, Marcus.
Sheriff.
And there is more yet to achieve.
I hope you can remain a part of it.
For their families. From an anonymous, concerned citizen.
Yesterday's smuggling fiasco was nothing.
These manifests are full of
discrepancies, dating back months.
This is a poor use of our time.
I'm a Councilor now, Viktor.
It's my responsibility to make sure
the Hexgates are safe and protected.
What about our pledge to improve lives,
for those in need? For the undercity?
Look, I'm sorry I didn't announce
our other projects in my speech.
Soon, we can do everything we...
Soon?
There are people who need our help now, Jayce.
You wanted to see me?
Have your people ever reviewed these logs?
Mr. Talis, I assure you...
Councilor.
And the only assurance I need is that you will
search and seize any unauthorized merchandise.
I've made a list of suspicious transactions.
All due respect, Councilor,
today's your first day...
Second.
Right.
You sure you don't want to confer
with the other Councilors before...
This corruption runs deep, Sheriff.
I intend to root it out.
Have you made any progress with the stolen Gemstone?
Yes. Chief suspect is an undercity gang.
They call themselves the Firelights.
They operate like phantoms, doing hit-and-runs
on civilians and disappearing into the night.
How soon till we track them down?
I've got my best officers on it.
Viktor? You all right?
A… a headache. I just… I need to get to the lab.
Boring…
Boring. Wow. Super boring…
Here we go!
It's all about these runes.
They form some kind of math-y, magic-y gateway.
To the realm of heebie-jeebies. And this… Turns it on.
So… here goes.
No!
No! It was a mistake! It was a mistake.
I heard the bathysphere has a nice view.
That could be a good way to get a lay of the land.
Too risky.
What…
Nice jacket.
Welcome to the Lanes.
You almost got me killed.
My little sister could do that when she was seven.
All us fissure folk can. Don't you want to blend in?
You had a vision?
What if we've been looking at it backwards?
We've been trying to discover runes that invoke specific
effects and then molding them to a useful function.
Tools, as you like to put it. But, but…
If the legends are true, mages
aren't bound to single functions.
It's said the Arcane speaks through them.
I'm still not following.
They think. They adapt.
You think Hextech can… learn?
Are you sure this is safe?
Of course not.
Oh, Jericho! Have I missed these.
Hmm?
No. Thank you.
You're missing out.
Are you going to question him?
About what? The meat?
Definitely not above board.
Silco. His connections? Isn't that why we're here?
We're here because I'm hungry. Do
you know what prison food is like?
No, of course, you don't.
Unbelievable. I didn't break you out of jail to eat… slop.
I knew this was a terrible idea. You
don't actually know anything, do you?
Mm. Better than I remember.
Hmm.
I haven't been here in years.
Since my parents brought me for the winter fest.
We're not here for the
performance. Your House is in trouble.
That merchant formerly enjoyed certain leniencies
with regard to her trade in exchange
for her generous Academy patronage.
By leniencies you mean corruption?
Hmm, Amara's harmless.
Oh, look at those two stooges.
Councilors Hoskel and Salo. Don't they hate each other?
Hmm. But they share a taste for the finer Noxian spirits,
technically an illegal import.
I tightened our security.
And in so doing, put a target on your back.
There are those who covet your power
over the wealth the Hexgates afford.
And would take any opportunity to seize it from you.
You've just made yourself everyone's common enemy, Jayce.
Oh, what's the matter, Mylo?
You worried Powder's gonna beat you again.
Vander.
Because you're a jinx!
What makes you different makes you strong.
Hmm.
Well, that place does look like it
has bodies buried in the basement.
You don't know anything.
I can't compromise the safety
of the Hexgates for collateral.
No one's asking you to. These
are simply favors amongst friends.
I never wanted anything to do
with politics. You pushed this on me.
You're a symbol of the future now,
Jayce, whether you like it or not.
With that comes the potential to shape your own destiny.
The Council assumes you'll fail. Time
to prove them all wrong. Once again.
Welcome, Amara. How's little Rohan?
Councilor Medarda. Councilor Talis.
He's just as precocious as ever.
I had quite a shock this morning.
Enforcers banging on my door.
Oh, I hope you'll understand,
Jayce had to make a show of safety.
But he's here now to negotiate all his deals personally.
Councilor Talis is willing to reinstate former
trade privileges to those who share his vision.
Can we count you amongst them?
Councilor Bolbok seems to think other
arrangements would be more profitable.
The man's a fool.
With him, you'd be investing in the past.
With us, you'd be investing in the future.
You know, Councilor Medarda's right.
The Hexgates are only the beginning.
In fact, we're currently looking for
new partners in our Hextech research,
and as a supporter of House Talis,
you'd be the first in line to any of our advancements.
How can I say no to such an auspicious offer?
Hextech partners?
Has a nice ring, doesn't it?
Mm. Your audience awaits, Councilor.
He's been quite the investment.
Indeed. Better than expected.
The one place all the secrets are spilled.
Oh.
How exactly do you propose we go about this?
Let 'em think you work here.
Excuse me?
I will not.
You know what your problem is?
Please. Tell me.
You expect everyone to give you what you want.
If you really want people to talk to you, you
have to let them think you have what they want.
And what do I have?
You're hot, cupcake.
So what'll it be, man or woman?
Um…
Hi.
I'm Pim. What's your name?
Matilda. But you can call her whatever you want.
Ah, yes. Matilda.
My parents named me Matilda.
After my great-grandmother Matilda, the, uh…
Would you believe it?
Sheriff, what a lovely surprise.
The Hextech wonder boy is on the Council now,
and he's asking questions.
It's only a matter of time before he finds the truth.
What is truth, but a survivor's story?
If I'm discovered, we're both finished.
Good thing you've located proof
of the Firelights' involvement.
This has gone too far.
Hmm? Imagining yourself a hero?
One final act to make you the
martyr you've always seen yourself as?
Then what are you waiting for?
Ah, he's faltering.
You need to weaponize the Hextech soon.
Once we've cracked their prize,
topside will have no power over us.
I can't do it. Just… give it to the doctor.
You're the only one I can trust with this, Jinx.
I keep… seeing them. That day.
Fear haunts us all, child.
Sweetheart, I was real sad to hear about Vander.
And the kids. Just terrible.
By the looks of it, no one down
here lifted a finger to stop Silco.
A few tried but Silco's got the muscle… and the money.
He took over the Last Drop.
I saw.
Things have changed without Vander looking out for us.
Have you heard anything about
Powder? I think Silco has her.
I have to find her.
Silco's number two's a regular.
I can have Miguel tell you where to find her.
I owe you.
It's nothing.
I've only ever imagined the gardens…
This is all I've seen.
You did well today.
I had a good teacher.
It's only a matter of time before those old
fools on the Council officially accept your research.
My father put hammers in the hands of the
people, and they built this magnificent city.
Imagine the wonders they could
create if we put magic in their hands.
The world will never be the same.
The Medardas usually only take from the world.
We're not often in the position to give anything back.
I couldn't have done it without you.
Hmm.
It's beautiful.
I can't figure out why it's not working.
You will.
Are you headed home soon? I
thought we could walk together.
I'm, uh, probably going to sleep here tonight.
Again? You know there's always tomorrow, right?
Good night, Miss Young.
Mm.
I almost drowned in these waters.
You told me a million times.
Vander wasn't the man you thought he was.
Right, he was like a brother to you, and
he turned his back and blah, blah, blah.
Did I miss anything?
I've got a new one for you.
That day, I let a weak man die.
And another was reborn.
Betrayal, that pain that feels like
it'll eat you from the inside out,
can either break you or forge you into something greater.
You need to let Powder die.
So the fear of pain will no longer control you.
You're strong now. Just like you were always meant to be.
Jinx is perfect.
Jayce?
Viktor, the doctors, um, they said you're…
How much time do I have?
Rotten luck, boys!
Vi?
You filthy traitor.
Vander had his chance.
I see you never learned patience.
Where's my sister? Where's he keeping her?
Keeping her? You mean Jinx?
She works for him.
She's like his daughter.
I'll give her your regards.
Why did you let her go?
Do you ever say "thank you?"
He's gonna know we're here now.
Whose fault is that?
You're an all-right shot.
I'm an excellent shot.
You gonna help me out, cupcake?
Stop calling me that. My name is Caitlyn.
But you're so sweet.
Like a cupcake.
Shut up.
You're making a mess.
The sister.
She's back.
From the dead?