Ever wonder what it's like to drown?
Story of opposites.
There's peace in water.
Like it's holdin' you, whisperin'
in low tones to let it in.
And every problem in the world will fade away.
But then there's this thing…
…in your head, and it's raging.
Lighting every nerve with madness.
To fight.
To survive.
And all the while, this question lingers before you:
"Have you had enough?"
It's funny. You could pass a lifetime
without ever facing a choice like that.
But it changes you forever.
For that, I thank you…
old friend.
Vander?
We don't have much time.
How did you find me?
I'm proud of you. Always have been.
I'm sorry, I… This is the only way to protect the others.
Vander.
You've got a good heart. Don't ever lose it.
No matter how the world tries to break you.
Protect the family.
What are you...
No.
Vander.
Let me out. This isn't right.
I'm guessing that's for me.
You gonna let us make the arrest or not?
You'll oblige a doomed man one last smoke.
Won't you?
I'm not putting you away, Vander.
The Council needs its pound of flesh.
Without you down here, it all falls apart.
Benzo will handle things.
I may not have my devilish
charm, but he runs a tight ship.
Vander, no. You can't do this.
You won't be coming back for a long time.
I know.
Why?
Mm.
It's the only way.
Benzo, open the damn door.
What's happening?
Hey. Stop right there!
What the devil…
No.
Silco?
You animal. Go crawl back into
whatever hole you came out of.
Benzo, stay back.
You never did know when to walk away.
Wait.
No!
Hmm. Stubborn to the end.
What the hell have you done? This wasn't the deal!
Deal's changed.
No.
No!
This entire time, I thought I
needed to dampen the oscillations.
The crystals will only stabilize at high frequency.
You have to...
Crank it.
Yes. Yes. You have to… crank it.
It works.
Eh… On paper.
Well, we could test it if we had access to my equipment.
Which is being destroyed tomorrow.
What?
Oh. I… Yeah. I, I meant to tell you.
That research is everything. My… my whole life.
Maybe if we showed them the equations, they'd let us...
We need more than promises.
We need proof.
Not without the crystals. The
enforcers took them all. They're gone.
Yeah. Locked away in Heimerdinger's lab.
No. No. No. You heard the Council. If we're wrong…
Better be right then.
Why? Why would you risk this?
Do you think it was my life's ambition to be an assistant?
Scientists seek discoveries.
Ways to make the world a better place.
This Hextech dream of yours has the potential to do that.
Our Hextech dream.
I saw everything.
Be… Benzo. They…
What about Vander?
They took him.
Where?
It's a little crude, I'll admit.
The base violence necessary for change.
But we both know topside won't listen to anything else.
Even with your monsters, you
won't win a war against Piltover.
I don't have to. I just need to scare them.
They won't dare set foot in the underground again.
You'll get people killed. For what? Pride?
For respect.
Opportunity. Everything they've denied us.
You had my respect.
The Lanes' respect, but that…
that was never enough for you.
We shared a vision, Vander. A dream of freedom.
Not just for the Lanes, but the
whole of the underground, united as one.
The nation of Zaun.
Do you even remember?
I trusted you.
And you betrayed me.
What I did to you…
I've never forgiven myself. You were my brother.
No, you still don't understand.
Can you imagine what it's like?
When your blood mixes with the filth and
the river toxins eat through your nerves.
Oh, I hated you for what you'd done.
But as time passed, so did my hate.
And I was left with an understanding.
The only way to defeat a superior
enemy is to stop at nothing.
To become what they fear.
I hated you, but you kept my respect.
Until you made peace with them.
Played lapdog after everything we suffered.
I had no choice.
Perhaps.
But now you do.
Shimmer. We have the power.
We can finally realize our dream,
brother.
Look at what you've done.
Benzo. These kids.
In fighting topside, you'd
sacrifice everything that we are.
It's not the way. Can't you see that?
Kill me if you have to, but please spare the Lanes.
You'd die for the cause, but you won't fight for one?
I'm just… not that man anymore.
I'll show you what you really are.
Hmm.
So far, so good.
Hmm. Willing to risk exile for your endeavor.
That's quite the conviction.
Councilor.
What a surprise to see you, huh?
How could I have…
Please. We can prove that it works.
Hmm. You couldn't do so earlier
today, how is tonight any different?
We figured out how to stabilize it.
You're the Professor's assistant.
No, he's my new partner.
Even if you manage to prove your
theory, the Council would destroy it.
Heimerdinger will recognize the potential.
He already does.
It scares him. It scares them all.
What about you?
I recognize that any worthwhile venture involves risk.
Councilor, this technology, it's real.
And no matter what happens here,
it's going to change our world.
We should be the ones to lead it.
Piltover, the land of progress, equality, innovation.
I know it sounds impossible, but
when have we ever let that stop us?
Please, just give us a chance.
One night, gentlemen. Impress me,
or I'd suggest you pack your bags.
Harold.
Oh. Oh.
Oh, Councilor Medarda, you… you nearly scared me to death.
Ah. Another late night. The work just doesn't end.
Well, I suppose that's a sign of good business, huh?
Well, if the enforcers hit tonight, we'll be ready…
I think.
Dibs on the bat.
No, no, no, no. I found it.
But I called it.
But I found it.
Respect the dibs.
I called it already.
Stop being such a big baby.
Vi?
Where's the...
Oh, you're back.
Hey. Those are Vander's. Slow down. What's going on?
Benzo's dead.
Dead?
They took Vander.
Who took Vander?
I don't know. But I need to help him.
We're going with you.
Whatever killed Benzo… was like nothing I've ever seen.
It tore him apart.
You're not doing this alone, Vi.
He's our father too.
Do we know where they took him?
Ekko followed them.
The old cannery next to the docks. He said…
I need you to sit this one out, Powder.
What?
You're not coming.
I'm not afraid.
It's too dangerous.
But families stick together. You said it yourself.
I know what I said…
I want to fight. I can help.
You're not ready.
You're all I have left.
I can't lose you.
Here. If they come for you, take this and run.
Where ever you are, light it
up, and I'll find you. I promise.
It's all here.
It's time to crank it.
Are you sure you know what you're doing?
I don't think it's gonna hold! Look at the buildup!
The resonance will stabilize it.
Trust me.
Hey, you seeing this?
I can help them.
Let's get Vander and get out.
I told you it would work.
All yours.
Wow.
It's never done that before.
All right. Here we go.
Disengage!
Incredible.
Vi.
What are you doing here?
We're breakin' you out.
Mylo.
On it.
How… how did you get in?
There's guards everywhere.
It was easy. We found an open window and…
Oh, god.
You have to get out. Now.
Welcome.
You have my congratulations.
But I'm afraid this will be a very short reunion.
Hmm.
Have you heard the rumor?
Vander the coward fled town with his children.
And they were never seen again.
Claggor, see if you can find another way out of here.
Okay.
You don't have to do this.
Yes, I do.
Vi.
Mylo.
Take a breath. You can do this.
We're gonna get you out.
Ready to rise to the surface?
Mylo, hurry.
Vi.
Silco. Let her go.
This is between you and me.
You had your chance.
Vi.
You did good.
Open up.
Stop this lunacy at once.
They're almost through. No pressure.
That sounds like pressure!
Open it.
Excuse me. Underfoot.
You've actually done it.
But just because it can be done, doesn't mean…
Will you please stop hovering?
I'm not sure how to do that, sir.
This is not what Piltover's
future looks like, my dear boys.
That's for the Council to decide.
Perhaps it's time.
For the era of magic.
Uh, Hextech. For the era of Hextech.
You have to work. For me. Okay?
Kill them.
I knew you still had it in you.
Find the girl.
Silco!
Vander.
Vander…
Take care of Powder.
No!
Vi, it worked.
What?
Did you see me?
My monkey bomb finally worked.
You did this?
Why?
Why did you do this?
I… I didn't…
I was saving you.
I only wanted to help.
I only wanted to help. I only wanted to help.
I told you to stay away.
Please. Please. Please...
I told you to stay away!
No. Why did you leave me?
Because you're a jinx. Do you hear me? Mylo was right.
No. No. No. No. Violet, please.
Violet, please.
Vi! Vi, come back! Please come back!
Please, Violet. I need you. Please.
Violet…
Violet. Please.
Powder.
Pow...
Shh.
He'll kill you if he hears you.
Come on. Let's go.
Hello, little girl.
Where's your sister?
She left me.
She is not my sister anymore.
It's okay.
We'll show them.
We will show them all.