- ( theme song playing )
♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR PICTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ YOU'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- Yamato: I'M NOT GOING
TO HOLD BACK ANYMORE.
I'M GONNA BE THE NUMBER ONE
SPRINTER IN JAPAN!
JUST YOU WAIT!
- WHY ARE YOU OUT HERE
ACTING ALL DEPRESSED?
SHOULDN'T YOU BE CELEBRATING?
YOU'VE BEEN NAMED NUMBER ONE
FOR THE ENTIRE YEAR.
- I'M NOT ANYMORE.
LOOK.
- ( papers rustling )
- SECOND PLACE?
- MY TIME WAS 10.68.
EMERSON'S WAS 10.50.
I DON'T KNOW HOW THAT BASTARD
PULLED AWAY FROM ME SO EASILY.
- MAYBE HE JUST...
WELL, YOU DID PLACE SECOND,
YOU KNOW. DON'T FORGET,
YOU STILL QUALIFY FOR
THE METROPOLITAN MEET.
- SECOND OR THIRD PLACE
MEANS NOTHING TO ME!
I JUST...
I WANT TO WIN FIRST PLACE!
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY IS HE SO SERIOUS
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- YEAH!
- AKITSUKI! YOU GOT A MINUTE?
- HUH?
- YOU SAID YOU FELT LIKE YOU
WERE LOSING YOUR TOP SPEED
TOWARD THE SECOND HALF OF
THE HUNDRED-METER RUN,
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
- UH, YEAH.
- I DID SOME RESEARCH
TO TRY AND FIGURE OUT WHY.
- TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
- HMM.
WHAT DOES ALL THIS MEAN?
- IT SHOWS THE STATS
FOR YOU AND ARIMA
AT TWENTY-METER CHECKPOINTS.
THE RED LINE IS YOU.
THE BLUE CURVE IS ARIMA
AND THE BLACK IS FOR THE NUMBER
ONE SPRINTER IN THE WORLD.
EVEN THOUGH THE TIMES
ARE DIFFERENT,
THE CURVE IS PRETTY MUCH
THE SAME.
ACCORDING TO THAT GRAPH,
ARIMA'S RUNNING STYLE
GIVES HIM THE POTENTIAL
TO BECOME NUMBER ONE.
- IN THE WORLD?
- ON THE OTHER HAND,
THE RED CURVE, WHICH IS YOU,
SHOWS THAT YOUR TOP SPEED IS
ALMOST THE SAME AS ARIMA'S.
BUT SINCE YOU REACH IT
EARLIER IN THE RACE,
YOU TEND TO LOSE SPEED
AS THE FINISH LINE GETS CLOSER.
- OH. OKAY, I GET IT.
SO I JUST NEED TO EXTEND THE
TIME THAT I RUN AT TOP SPEED.
THAT SHOULD BE EASY,
SHOULDN'T IT?
- WELL, NO, NOT EXACTLY.
IT'S PHYSICALLY IMPOSSIBLE.
THE LONGEST A HUMAN CAN RUN
AT TOP SPEED IS SIX SECONDS.
- ARE YOU SAYING THAT I'M NEVER
GOING TO BE ABLE
TO BEAT THIS GUY?
- NOW, WAIT A MINUTE.
EVEN THOUGH YOU CAN'T INCREASE
THE TIME YOU STAY AT TOP SPEED,
YOU CAN TRAIN TO REACH YOUR PEAK
LATER IN THE RACE.
IF YOU CONTROL YOUR UPPER BODY
IN THE FIRST HALF,
AND THEN TAKE
YOUR TIME ACCELERATING,
IT MAY HELP YOU NOT TO TURN UP
THE SPEED SO SOON.
- IF I DO ALL THAT,
WILL I BE ABLE TO INCREASE
MY OVERALL SPEED?
- WELL, YES, MOST LIKELY.
SPEED IS ONE THING,
BUT CHANGING YOUR RUNNING STYLE
MAY BE MORE DIFFICULT.
- ( men panting )
WE DON'T HAVE
A WHOLE LOT OF TIME
BEFORE THE METROPOLITAN MEET.
I THINK IT MAY BE BEST JUST TO
LEAVE THINGS AS THEY ARE.
- NO, I CAN DO IT.
- ALL RIGHT.
THEN I'LL START WORKING
ON YOUR NEW TRAINING REGIMEN
AND YOU CAN BEGIN TODAY.
SO I GUESS I'LL SEE YOU AFTER
YOU FINISH YOUR INTERVALS THEN.
- THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR YOUR HELP!
ALL RIGHT!
ASAHINA!
I FIGURED OUT THE ANSWER
TO THAT QUESTION I ASKED YOU!
- OH? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- WHEN I TOLD YOU I LOST
MY SPEED IN THE SECOND HALF
OF THE HUNDRED-METER RUN?
- YEAH.
I THINK I REMEMBER
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
I FIGURED OUT THAT IT ALL HAD TO
DO WITH MY RUNNING STYLE.
If I JUST MAKE A FEW
SMALL CHANGES,
I'LL BE ABLE TO GO EVEN FASTER.
- IS THAT SO?
THAT DOESN'T SOUND
RIGHT TO ME.
- WELL, IT'S TRUE, ASAHINA.
MIYAMOTO SEMPAI TOLD ME SO.
- EVEN SO...
THERE ARE ONLY TWO WEEKS
BEFORE THE METROPOLITAN.
DO YOU REALLY THINK IT'S SMART
TO CHANGE YOUR RUNNING STYLE
AT THIS POINT?
BESIDES, YOU NEED
A LOT MORE PRACTICE
THAN THE AVERAGE PERSON, YAMATO.
I REALLY DON'T THINK
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO DO IT.
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU'RE SO WEIRD.
HEY...
- JUST SHUT UP!
LEAVE ME ALONE, YOU IDIOT!
RUN WHICHEVER WAY YOU LIKE!
THIS DOESN'T HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH ME!
- HEY! ASAHINA, WAIT!
GEEZ... WHAT'S WRONG WITH HER?
- ( grunting )
- AH!
- IT LOOKS LIKE EVERYONE'S
WORKING HARD.
- SET!
GO!
- Kinugasa: ALL RIGHT!
THREE MINUTE BREAK!
- ( panting )
THIS... SUCKS!
- HOLD ON! TOWEL?
- Kinugasa: HEY THERE, AKITSUKI!
YOUR STAMINA IS PATHETIC!
YOU CAN'T ALREADY BE WORN OUT
FROM THAT WUSSY TRAINING!
AND DON'T YOU FORGET ABOUT THAT
LITTLE GIRLIE STUNT YOU PULLED
IN THE RELAY!
YOU ALMOST KILLED US!
IT'S A GOOD THING FOR YOU
THAT THE TEAM STILL QUALIFIED
FOR THE METROPOLITAN!
- WILL YOU LET GO, PLEASE?
YOU'RE HURTING ME!
- WELL, AT LEAST HE MANAGED TO
PASS THE BATON, RIGHT, AKITSUKI?
- UH, YEAH.
- I'M SURE I HAD A LITTLE
SOMETHING TO DO WITH THAT.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- UH... HEH.
- OH, NOTHING REALLY.
- Yamato: IF I'M GOING TO BEAT
ARIMA IN THE RELAY RACE,
I HAVE TO CHANGE
MY RUNNING STYLE.
- Hashiba: THAT'S RIGHT!
- Kinugasa: WELL, THEN YOU NEED
TO PRACTICE MORE, DON'T YA?
- Yamato: YES, SIR!
( laughing )
- ( bird squawking )
I WONDER IF AKITSUKI HAS BEEN
PRACTICING THIS WHOLE TIME.
- ( Yamato panting )
- 11.23 SECONDS!
- DAMN IT!
JUST GREAT!
MY TIME ISN'T
IMPROVING AT ALL.
- WELL, OF COURSE NOT.
DO YOU REALIZE HOW LONG
YOU'VE BEEN RUNNING OUT HERE?
I THINK WE
BETTER STOP NOW.
- NO, LET ME JUST RUN IT
ONE MORE TIME. PLEASE?
- WELL...
OKAY, I GUESS ONE MORE
TIME WON'T HURT.
- THANKS. I'M SORRY
ABOUT ALL THIS.
I JUST DON'T KNOW ANYONE ELSE
I CAN TURN TO.
- ARE YOU SERIOUSLY APOLOGIZING
BECAUSE YOU ASKED FOR HELP?
- YEAH. I GUESS SO.
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS IT.
THE LAST ROUND.
- ARE YOU FEELING OKAY?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- I SEEMS LIKE I'M TALKING TO
A COMPLETELY DIFFERENT PERSON.
WHAT HAPPENED TO THE GUY
WHO COULD NEVER
HOLD ON TO THE BATON?
- I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T FEEL DIFFERENT. MAYBE
IT'S BECAUSE I HAVE A GOAL NOW.
- A GOAL?
- YEAH.
I'M DETERMINED TO BEAT ARIMA
AND BECOME NUMBER ONE IN JAPAN.
- WELL, GREAT! I THINK
YOU CAN DO IT.
I'VE ALWAYS BELIEVED IN YOU.
WHAT I DON'T GET IS
WHERE THIS IS COMING FROM.
WHY NOW?
- I DON'T WANNA TALK ABOUT IT.
- YOU STILL LIKE SUZUKA,
DON'T YOU?
AM I RIGHT?
- YEAH.
AND I PLAN TO TELL HER
EXACTLY HOW I FEEL
AFTER I BECOME THE NUMBER ONE
SPRINTER IN JAPAN.
- HUH?
BECOMING NUMBER ONE
ISN'T GONNA CHANGE
HOW SUZUKA FEELS ABOUT YOU.
SHE DOESN'T LIKE YOU
BECAUSE OF HOW FAST YOU CAN RUN.
- I KNOW THAT.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO IMPLY THAT
ASAHINA WAS SUPERFICIAL.
IT WOULD JUST HELP ME FEEL
MORE CONFIDENT, THAT'S ALL.
I FEEL LIKE I WON'T BE SATISFIED
WITH MYSELF IF I CAN'T DO IT.
I'M TIRED OF NOT FEELING WORTHY.
I WANNA BE HER EQUAL.
- I SEE.
WELL THEN, I DON'T
WANNA BE INVOLVED.
THAT'S THE MOST RIDICULOUS THING
I'VE EVER HEARD YOU SAY.
- HASHIBA.
- YOU SHOULD PAY ME BACK
FOR ALL THE TROUBLE.
TAKE ME TO GET
SOMETHING TO EAT.
- ABSOLUTELY!
HOW 'BOUT WE GO TO THE
OKONOMIYAKI PLACE AFTER THIS?
- NOPE! SOMETHING
MORE EXPENSIVE.
- WHAT ARE YOU TRYING
TO DO TO ME?
- YAKINIKU!
- YAKINIKU?
- COME ON! WHO DOESN'T LIKE
KOREAN BARBEQUE?
- OKAY, FINE.
- SO AKITSUKI IS DOING
ALL OF THIS FOR ASAHINA.
- DO YOU THINK YAMATO IS STILL
OUT THERE PRACTICING?
- HE SAID THE COMPETITION
WAS COMING UP SOON.
SO I GUESS HE IS.
- IT'S SO UNUSUAL TO SEE HIM
WORKING THIS HARD FOR ANYTHING.
I THINK I WANNA DO SOMETHING
NICE TO SUPPORT HIM.
- ME, TOO.
I THINK I'LL MAKE
SOMETHING DELICIOUS FOR HIM
TO EAT BEFORE THE TOURNAMENT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, SUZUKA?
- AH... SURE.
- I WONDER WHAT HE WOULD LIKE.
- DON'T YOU THINK HE'D WANT
SOMETHING RICH AND HEARTY?
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH
FOR DINNER.
- OH, DID YOU GET ENOUGH TO EAT?
- ( water running )
- WHAT IS IT ABOUT HIM?
- I JUST... I WANNA BE THE
NUMBER ONE SPRINTER IN JAPAN!
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
- Honoka: NANA? IT'S ME.
I'M SORRY TO BOTHER YOU.
I KNOW YOU MUST BE REALLY BUSY.
ARE YOU WORKING?
DID I CATCH YOU AT A BAD TIME?
- UH-HUH, NOT AT ALL.
IS SOMETHING WRONG, HONOKA?
- KINDA. THERE'S JUST SOMETHING
I WANT TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
- OF COURSE.
IS THIS ABOUT YAMATO?
- YEAH.
- I'M COMING OVER
TO SEE YOU, OKAY?
- I'M SO SORRY.
I KNOW YOU'RE BUSY.
- STOP WORRYING ABOUT IT.
THIS WAS ON MY WAY BACK
HOME ANYWAY.
BESIDES, I'VE BEEN
SO BUSY LATELY
THAT WE REALLY HAVEN'T
HAD A CHANCE TO CATCH UP.
I'VE GOTTA SAY, I'VE BEEN A
LITTLE WORRIED ABOUT YOU, HON.
OH, HONOKA, WHY AREN'T YOU
OVER HIM YET?
- THE THING IS...
I WAS...
I WAS REALLY WORKING ON
BUILDING MY CONFIDENCE
SO THAT I COULD EVENTUALLY
ASK HIM OUT AGAIN.
HE'S PRACTICING SO MUCH.
AND NOW I KNOW WHY.
HE'S DOING IT ALL
TO IMPRESS ASAHINA.
AND WHAT IF IT'S NOT
JUST ONE-SIDED?
WHAT IF SHE LIKES HIM, TOO?
THEN THAT WOULD MEAN THAT
EVERYTHING I'M TRYING TO DO
IS A WASTE OF TIME,
AND THERE'S NO ROOM FOR ME
IN HIS HEART.
- SO JUST FORGET ABOUT HIM.
YOU DON'T WANNA BE WITH SOMEONE
WHO'S TOO STUPID TO REALIZE
HOW AMAZING YOU ARE.
YOU'RE GONNA BE FINE.
THIS JUST MEANS YOU CAN ACTUALLY
FIND A REAL BOYFRIEND. OKAY?
- THANKS, NANA.
- Yasunobu: YOU'RE REALLY
WORKING HARD THESE DAYS.
I KNOW YOU SAID YOU WANTED TO BE
THE NUMBER ONE SPRINTER
IN THE COUNTRY
BUT YOU'RE PRACTICING
FROM MORNING UNTIL NIGHT!
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- EVEN THOUGH I THINK
YOUR MOTIVATION
IS SERIOUSLY MISPLACED,
I GOTTA TELL YA, I'M IMPRESSED.
- THANKS, MAN.
I'M DOIN' EVERYTHING I CAN.
I SWEAR. NOTHING IS GOING
TO STOP ME
FROM BECOMING NUMBER ONE.
- HAH!
- AND HERE I THOUGHT YOU WERE
ALL TALK AND NO ACTION.
WELL, JUST MAKE SURE
YOU DON'T BLOW IT, OKAY?
- YEAH.
- Kinugasa: ONE MORE!
RUN LIKE YOU MEAN IT, AKITSUKI!
TIME!
TAKE A THREE
MINUTE BREAK!
- ( gasping )
I'M GLAD THAT'S OVER.
- HEY, AKITSUKI, CAN I HAVE
A MINUTE WITH YOU?
- SURE.
- I WANTED TO SHOW YOU THIS.
IT'S A GRAPH OF YOUR RUNNING
PATTERN OVER THE LAST WEEK.
- HUH?
- BUT THIS ONE SPECIFICALLY
SHOWS YOUR TIME FROM YESTERDAY.
- IT'S MY RUNNING FORM,
ISN'T IT?
I'M GONNA KEEP WORKING ON IT.
- OH, NO. THAT'S NOT
WHAT I MEAN. LOOK.
YOUR TIME COULD STILL USE
SOME WORK
AND THAT WILL COME
WITH PRACTICE.
BUT THE SHAPE OF YOUR CURVE
IS STARTING TO LOOK VERY
MUCH LIKE ARIMA'S.
- IT IS?
- YEAH. WHATEVER YOU'RE DOING
IS WORKING.
SO KEEP IT UP, AND I'M SURE
YOU'LL DO WELL AT THE MEET.
- I'LL BE THE BEST.
JUST YOU WAIT!
- ( chuckling )
WELL, DON'T WORK YOURSELF
TOO HARD.
- OKAY.
ASAHINA!
GET THIS!
MIYAMOTO SEMPAI JUST TOLD ME
THAT MY RUNNING STYLE
IS IMPROVING!
PRETTY COOL, HUH?
DON'T YOU THINK SO?
- JUST BECAUSE YOU'RE IMPROVING
DURING PRACTICE
DOESN'T MEAN YOU'LL PERFORM
THE SAME WAY DURING THE RACE.
- BUT...
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- I'M SURE YOU'RE GREAT.
I'M JUST SAYING YOU SHOULDN'T BE
OVERCONFIDENT AT THIS POINT.
- HEY, WAIT JUST A MINUTE!
WHAT IS UP WITH HER?
WHY DID SHE HAVE TO SAY
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
WHO DOES SHE THINK
I'M DOING ALL THIS FOR?
DOESN'T SHE GET IT?
- BECOMING NUMBER ONE
ISN'T GONNA CHANGE
HOW SUZUKA FEELS ABOUT YOU.
SHE DOESN'T LIKE YOU BECAUSE OF
HOW FAST YOU CAN RUN.
- I KNOW THAT.
I CAN'T THINK ABOUT
THIS RIGHT NOW.
I HAVE TO FOCUS ON PRACTICING.
I HAVE TO WIN!
- Soichi: ALL RIGHT!
WE'RE ALL DONE FOR TODAY!
- Crowd: YEAH!
- MAN, I AM GLAD
THAT'S OVER WITH!
- YEAH. TELL ME ABOUT IT.
LET'S GO GRAB SOMETHING TO EAT.
- AKITSUKI, YOU WANNA GRAB
SOMETHING TO EAT BEFORE YOU GO?
IT'LL BE MY TREAT, OKAY?
- THAT'S VERY NICE OF YOU, BUT I
THINK I'M GOING TO STAY HERE
AND RUN A LITTLE MORE.
- ALL RIGHT.
WELL, YOU KNOW THE MEET
ISN'T TOO FAR AWAY.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO INJURE
YOURSELF BY PRACTICING TOO MUCH.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
- SEE YA!
- GOOD JOB TODAY!
WELL, GUESS IT'S TIME FOR ME
TO START RUNNING!
YOU'RE PRACTICING BY YOURSELF
TODAY, ASAHINA?
I'M SURE YOU'LL DO GREAT.
- HEY... YOU KNOW
YOU SHOULDN'T WASTE TIME
MAKING CHEERFUL CONVERSATION.
IT'S NOT GONNA HELP YOU
DURING THE RACE.
YOU RECENTLY CHANGED
YOUR RUNNING STYLE.
IF YOU SLACK OFF NOW,
YOU'RE JUST GONNA RETURN
TO YOUR SAME OLD WAYS.
- OH, OKAY.
GREAT. WHAT DID I DO NOW.
I DON'T GET IT.
- ( bell tolling )
DAMN IT!
I AM SO ANGRY RIGHT NOW!
WHY THE HELL
DOES SHE ALWAYS THINK
SHE CAN TALK TO ME LIKE THAT?
I HAVE TO FOCUS!
- HEY!
- YOU NEED TO TALK TO ME?
- YOU NEED TO GO HOME.
YOU SHOULDN'T PRACTICE
THIS LONG.
RUNNING LIKE THIS JUST HAS
THE OPPOSITE EFFECT, YOU KNOW.
YOU'RE JUST GONNA
WEAR YOURSELF OUT.
DON'T BE STUPID.
- AHH!
WHAT? I KNOW
WHAT I'M DOING, OKAY?
- OH, DO YOU REALLY?
WHY IN THE WORLD WOULD YOU
EXPECT ME TO BELIEVE
SOMETHING LIKE THAT
WHEN YOU'VE NEVER BEEN
SERIOUS ABOUT ANYTHING?
- ALL RIGHT,
THAT'S ENOUGH ALREADY.
WHY DO YOU HATE ME
SO MUCH, ASAHINA?
SHE JUST SAYS
WHATEVER SHE WANTS.
SHE HAS NO IDEA
WHY I'M WORKING SO HARD.
I'VE HAD IT.
I'M GOIN' HOME.
- WAIT! YAMATO!
DON'T LEAVE YET!
HEY! COME BACK!
PLEASE WAIT.
I'M SORRY.
I REALLY SHOULDN'T HAVE SAID
ALL THOSE AWFUL THINGS
TO YOU, YAMATO.
I DIDN'T MEAN IT. PLEASE DON'T
BE SO ANGRY WITH ME.
- WELL... I, UM...
I'M NOT ALL THAT
ANGRY WITH YOU.
- SO, ARE WE OKAY?
- YEAH. SURE.
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
UH, ASAHINA?
- GOOD LUCK AT THE METROPOLITAN!
- HOLD ON!
"GOOD LUCK," HUH? THANKS.
I KNOW YOU STILL DON'T SEE IT...
BUT I'M ABOUT TO BE
THE FASTEST IN THE COUNTRY!
- ( birds chirping )
- ( humming a tune )
( chuckles ) LOOKS DELICIOUS!
- Hashiba: THIS IS IT!
I'M FREAKING OUT!
- CALM DOWN. WHAT ARE YOU
SO NERVOUS ABOUT?
- UH, IT'S THE METROPOLITAN?
I CAN'T IMAGINE
HOW AKITSUKI FEELS RIGHT NOW.
I WONDER WHAT IT'S LIKE TO
COMPETE IN A MEET THIS BIG.
- I GUESS YOU MIGHT KNOW
IF YOU WORKED HARDER, HUH?
- YOU'RE SUCH A PRETENTIOUS
JERK, YOU KNOW THAT?
- OF COURSE I DO.
BUT THAT'S WHAT MAKES ME
SO DAMN CHARMING, ISN'T IT?
- YOU GOTTA BE KIDDING.
- Kinugasa: IT'S ALMOST TIME.
- SURE IS.
- YES!
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WHEN I TURN AROUND♪
♪ YOU'RE RIGHT THERE
NEXT TO ME ♪
♪ ON YOUR FACE A SMILE
SO COMFORTING AND FAMILIAR ♪
♪ THE CLOSER YOU BECAME
THE LESS THAT I COULD SEE ♪
♪ AND NOW I'M WONDERING
SO LOST AND ALL ALONE ♪
♪ PEOPLE CHANGE
A LITTLE AT A TIME ♪
♪ AND NOW I KNOW I'M CHANGING ♪
♪ WHEN I CALL YOUR NAME
SHOUT IT OUT INTO THE SKY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN I WILL FIND
THE LOVE I KEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'RE WITH ME
AND YOU TAKE MY HAND ♪
♪ SOMEHOW EVERYTHING
SEEMS TO WORK ITSELF OUT RIGHT ♪
♪ WHEN I SEE YOUR EYES
STARING BACK AT MINE ♪
♪ THERE INSIDE I FIND
A LOVE THAT NEVER DIES ♪
♪ TOGETHER I KNOW
WE'LL FIND A WAY ♪
♪ JUST YOU AND I ♪
- Yamato: I WANT YOU TO KNOW
THAT I STILL LIKE YOU, ASAHINA.
- Suzuka: WHY ARE YOU
SAYING ALL THIS?
- Yamato: LOOK, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO ANSWER ME NOW.
I'M GONNA PRACTICE
EVEN HARDER.
I'LL RUN FASTER THAN I
EVER HAVE BEFORE
- AND THEN I'LL BE...
- Suzuka: JUST STOP IT!