- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THAT
THE INTER-HIGH MEET
IS BEING HELD IN HIROSHIMA.
IT FEELS LIKE GOING HOME AGAIN.
PRETTY COOL.
- AKITSUKI!
I'M RETIRING AFTER
THIS COMPETITION,
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS?
IT MEANS YOU BETTER DO
YOUR BEST OUT THERE,
YOU HEAR ME?
- YEAH, I, OKAY, I'LL TRY.
- TRYING'S NOT ENOUGH!
YOU'RE COMPETING NEXT YEAR!
YOU'VE GOTTA FEEL IT IN YOUR
GUT! ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME!
SO, WE'VE GOTTA GET YOU ON
A SPECIAL TRAINING PROGRAM
RIGHT WHEN WE GET THERE. NOW...
- WHERE'RE YOU GOING?
- I NEED TO GET SOME JUICE!
- AKITSUKI, GET BACK HERE! HEY!
- I WON'T LAST IF I HANG OUT
WITH HIM FOR VERY LONG.
HEY, ASAHINA! DO YOU WANT
SOMETHING TO DRINK?
I'M GONNA GET SOME JUICE.
- NO, I'M NOT THIRSTY. THANKS.
- OKAY, WELL YOU MUST
BE HUNGRY THEN?
SOMETHING FROM
THE DINING CART?
- NO THANKS. PLEASE
DON'T TALK TO ME RIGHT NOW!
I REALLY NEED TO
CONCENTRATE. SORRY.
- OH, OKAY.
EVER SINCE THAT DAY,
ASAHINA'S BEEN SO COLD
AND DISTANT TOWARDS ME.
- AKITSUKI...
- HEY, DON'T FALL!
- YAMATO DOESN'T LOOK ANY
BETTER FROM THAT ANGLE.
- UH, WHAT?
WHAT'RE YOU DOING
HERE, ANYWAY?
YOU DON'T EVEN BELONG TO
THE TRACK AND FIELD CLUB.
- I CAME TO SUPPORT THE
ATHLETES, THAT OKAY WITH YOU?
ANYONE WHO WANTED
TO COME WATCH
JUST NEEDED TO
INFORM THE SCHOOL.
BESIDES, I DIDN'T HAVE ANYTHING
BETTER TO DO OVER SUMMER BREAK.
HEY, I'VE BEEN MEANING
TO ASK YOU SOMETHING.
IF YOU LIKE YAMATO SO MUCH,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST TELL
HIM HOW YOU FEEL?
- THIS IS GETTING OLD.
- DON'T BE SO LOUD.
SOMEONE WILL
HEAR YOU!
IT WAS HARD ENOUGH
FOR ME TO TELL ASAHINA
THAT I LIKED AKITSUKI.
I CAN'T SAY IT AGAIN.
ESPECIALLY TO HIM.
- LOOK, IT'S NONE OF MY BUSINESS
AND I REALLY DON'T CARE,
BUT IF YOU SLACK OFF YOU
MIGHT LOSE HIM TO SOMEONE
MORE AGGRESSIVE, YA KNOW?
- AGGRESSIVE?
- I JUST DON'T FEEL THAT
WAY ABOUT HIM...
- YAMATO.
- ASAHINA SAID SHE DIDN'T
LIKE HIM LIKE THAT.
BUT...
- OH, MAN! YOU'VE
GOTTA BE KIDDING.
THEY SERIOUSLY EXPECT
US TO SLEEP IN THIS DUMP?
THOSE WHO ARE COMPETING
NEED TO REST UP
AND PREPARE YOURSELVES
FOR PRACTICE.
- YOU GOT IT!
- All: GOT IT?
- THIS IS PROBABLY
NOT THE BEST TIME
TO ASK IF SHE'D LIKE
TO GO FOR A WALK.
- AKITSUKI SEEMS LIKE
HE'S A LITTLE UPSET.
I WONDER IF HE'S OKAY.
- HEY, YAMATO!
LET'S GO EXPLORING!
YOU CAN SHOW ME WHERE
ALL THE GIRLS HANG OUT!
- I DON'T REALLY KNOW
MY WAY AROUND HERE.
I'M AFRAID YOU'RE ON YOUR OWN.
- ON MY OWN? WAIT A SEC!
YOU USED TO LIVE HERE, DUDE!
- JUST BECAUSE
I'M NOT COMPETING
DOESN'T MEAN I DON'T HAVE
OTHER THINGS TO DO.
- C'MON, MOVE IT!
- SNAILS MOVE FASTER
THAN YOU DO, MAN!
- I'M SO SORRY!
- Yamato: IT, IT'S
THAT ARIMA GUY.
HI. HOW ARE YA? SO WHAT DO
YOU THINK OF HIROSHIMA?
- DO YOU KNOW HIM, ARIMA SENPAI?
- NOPE. NEVER SEEN
HIM IN MY LIFE.
- SO THOSE ARE INTER-HIGH
ATHLETES. WOW.
- NO THANKS. PLEASE DON'T
TALK TO ME RIGHT NOW.
I REALLY NEED TO
CONCENTRATE. SORRY.
- ARIMA AND ASAHINA ARE
ALIKE IN MANY WAYS...
AND THEY'RE BOTH SO
DIFFERENT FROM ME.
- HEY, AKITSUKI, WHAT ARE YOU
DAYDREAMING ABOUT?
- OH. HEY!
- SO AFTER DINNER, WE'RE
ALL GONNA LIGHT FIREWORKS
IF YOU WANNA JOIN US.
YA KNOW, IF YOU DON'T
HAVE ANYTHING BETTER TO DO.
- OH, UH, NO THANK YOU.
THE CAPTAIN TOLD TO ME PRACTICE,
SO YOU GUYS GO AHEAD.
- WAIT, AKITSUKI!
OH, WELL.
- ( clock chiming )
- ( chattering )
- YOU MEAN YAMATO?
- YEAH, HIM. HE JUST SEEMS
REALLY DEPRESSED LATELY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
HIS TIME HASN'T BEEN
IMPROVING THAT MUCH EITHER.
I FIGURED HE'D BE MORE
ADVANCED BY NOW.
I WONDER IF THE STRESS
OF BEING HERE
AT INTER- HIGH IS
TOO MUCH FOR HIM.
- I DON'T THINK SO.
YOU CAN'T EXPECT
HIM TO IMPROVE
AFTER JUST ONE OR TWO
MONTHS OF PRACTICE. RIGHT?
- RIGHT. AND I THINK HE'D LOVE
TO HEAR THAT RIGHT NOW.
IN FACT, I THINK YOU SHOULD
BE THE ONE TO TELL HIM.
- WHAT FOR?
WHY SHOULD I TELL HIM?
- BECAUSE YOU GUYS ARE
LIKE BEST FRIENDS.
- NO. I WOULDN'T SAY
THAT WE'RE BEST FRIENDS.
- OKAY. WHATEVER.
WELL, YOUR FRIEND IS PRACTICING
ALONE AFTER DINNER.
I THINK YOU SHOULD
PRACTICE TOO. OKAY?
- NO, IT'S COOL. HE CAN PRACTICE
WITHOUT ME HOLDING HIS HAND.
- SUZUKA!
- ( grunts )
( panting )
DAMN! MY TIME HASN'T
IMPROVED AT ALL!
TIME FOR A BREAK.
I'M EXHAUSTED!
WHAT KIND OF AN IDIOT
DOES THIS TO THEMSELVES?
I'M NOT EVEN COMPETING TOMORROW.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
- HEY. YOU OKAY?
- UH, HEY, HONOKA. WHAT
ARE YOU DOING OUT HERE?
- IT'S LATE. YOU'VE BEEN
PRACTICING A LONG TIME.
I THOUGHT I'D CHECK ON YOU.
- ACTUALLY, I'VE JUST
BEEN WORKING HARD
FOR THE PAST FEW MINUTES.
- YEAH HIM. HE JUST
SEEMS REALLY DEPRESSED LATELY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
HIS TIME HASN'T BEEN IMPROVING
THAT MUCH, EITHER.
- Suzuka: MAYBE I SHOULD
TALK TO HIM.
- WELL SINCE I'M HERE,
DO YOU MIND IF I SIT DOWN?
- NO, PLEASE.
- POOR AKITSUKI.
HE LOOKS SO SAD.
- DINNER WAS REALLY GOOD
TONIGHT. DIDN'T YOU THINK SO?
I CAN'T BELIEVE I ATE TWO
WHOLE BOWLS OF MISO SOUP.
I HOPE IT DOESN'T MAKE ME FAT!
I THINK YOU'RE GONNA BE ALRIGHT.
- AKITSUKI, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- HUH?
- YOU DON'T SEEM LIKE YOURSELF.
DO YOU WANNA TALK ABOUT IT?
- IT'S NOTHING. JUST NOT
VERY CONFIDENT LATELY.
- WHY'S THAT?
- WHEN I FIRST JOINED TRACK AND
FIELD, EVERYONE MADE SUCH A BIG
DEAL ABOUT HOW
FAST I COULD RUN.
AND THEN I LOST AT THE
REGIONAL AND MADE A FOOL
OUT OF MYSELF IN
FRONT OF EVERYONE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I
DECIDED TO TAG ALONG
AFTER NOT MAKING THE
INTER-HIGH TEAM.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT I'M DOING
HERE. WHAT'S THE POINT?
- PLEASE DON'T SAY THAT.
- THE CAPTAIN EXPECTS
SO MUCH OF ME,
BUT I'M JUST NOT THAT GOOD YET.
KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
INTER-HIGH TRACK AND FIELD
ATHLETES ARE ON AN ADVANCED
LEVEL THAT I'M JUST
NOT READY FOR.
AND I DON'T KNOW IF I
COULD EVER LIVE UP TO THAT.
- OF COURSE YOU WILL.
I THINK YOU'RE JUST AS
TALENTED AS THEY ARE.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE HOW
FAST YOU ALREADY WERE
WHEN YOU FIRST JOINED
TRACK AND FIELD.
THAT TRAINING THE CAPTAIN PUT
YOU THROUGH LOOKED INTENSE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU
GOT THROUGH IT.
YOU'RE AMAZING, AKITSUKI.
THERE'S NO DOUBT IN MY MIND
THAT YOU'LL BE NUMBER ONE
ON THE TEAM NEXT YEAR!
- THANKS A LOT!
I FEEL SO MUCH BETTER!
- GOOD, I'M GLAD.
IT FEELS GREAT TO JUST
SIT NEXT TO HIM.
IT'S ENOUGH TO MAKE ME HAPPY,
FOR NOW.
- ( gate opens )
- HMM? WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- NO!
PLEASE DON'T TURN AROUND!
DON'T STOP LOOKING AT ME!
- FOR A MOMENT, I DIDN'T REALIZE
WHAT'D HAPPENED TO ME.
AND NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
I DON'T REMEMBER MUCH
ABOUT THAT NIGHT.
EXCEPT THAT HONOKA'S
LIPS WERE VERY SOFT.
- AKITSUKI...
- ( gasps )
- I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT I'LL
ALWAYS BE THERE FOR YOU, OKAY?
- HONOKA! WAIT!
- HI, HONOKA.
- ( sighs ) WHY WOULD SHE DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT SO SUDDENLY?
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
IT ACTUALLY HAPPENED.
I DID IT. I KISSED SOMEONE.
HONOKA AND I KISSED.
- HELLO? ARE YOU DEAF?
- ( gasps ) UH...
DON'T DO THAT!
- I DIDN'T MEAN TO WAKE YOU,
JEEZ, WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
DID YOU FINISH PRACTICING?
- UH, YEAH
A WHILE AGO ER...
I, I MEAN, I JUST GOT DONE!
WHY AM I SO NERVOUS
AROUND HER?
IT'S NOT LIKE SHE'S MY
GIRLFRIEND OR ANYTHING.
- YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T STRESS
SO MUCH ABOUT YOUR TIME.
- WHO SAYS I'M STRESSING
OUT ABOUT IT?
- NO ONE. YOU JUST SEEMED DOWN,
BUT I'M GLAD YOU'RE OKAY.
- WELL, I'M FINE.
- ALL RIGHT. WELL YOU GUYS
BETTER NOT FORGET
TO CHEER FOR ME TOMORROW.
IT'S MY FIRST INTER-HIGH
COMPETITION, SO I'M KINDA
NERVOUS.
- TOMORROW? WHAT'S GOING ON?
- THE INTER-HIGH COMPETITION.
I JUST TOLD YOU.
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
SO YOU CAME ALL THE WAY DOWN
HERE JUST TO TELL ME THAT?
- WELL, SORTA, YEAH...
IS THAT OKAY WITH YOU?
- YEAH. YEAH, THAT'S...
THAT'S GREAT.
- WELL, IT'S BEEN SWELL, YAMATO.
TRY NOT TO SLEEP IN TOMORROW.
- HEY, WAIT! ASAHINA!
WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
JUST TRACK AND FIELD?
I STILL LIKE ASAHINA.
MY FEELINGS FOR HER HAVEN'T
CHANGED, BUT...
HONOKA...
DOES THAT COUNT?
I THINK THAT WAS
MY FIRST KISS.
- ( crowd cheering )
- ( grunting )
- ( cheering )
- I WANT YOU TO KNOW THAT I'LL
ALWAYS BE THERE FOR YOU, OKAY?
- THAT COULD MEAN SO
MANY THINGS. I WONDER.
ASAHINA'S UP.
UGH! WHY CAN'T I FOCUS?
I'M SUCH A STUPID IDIOT!
I PROMISED ASAHINA
I'D CHEER HER ON.
SHE MUST BE SO
NERVOUS RIGHT NOW.
- IS THIS SEAT TAKEN? AKITSUKI?
- HONOKA... NO, IT'S NOT.
YOU CAN SIT THERE.
- WELL, THANK YOU.
- I JUST KISSED THOSE
LIPS LAST NIGHT.
UM... HI... UM...
- SORRY, ABOUT LAST NIGHT.
I WASN'T THINKING.
- IT'S COOL.
- ( all cheering )
- WHAT THE...
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN "WHAT JUST
HAPPENED?" WEREN'T YOU WATCHING?
ASAHINA JUST WON THIRD PLACE!
- OH, WOW.
- ONE HUNDRED AND
SEVENTY-THREE CENTIMETERS.
- THAT'S A NEW PERSONAL
RECORD FOR HER.
- INCREDIBLE!
LOOK AT ALL THE
REPORTERS AROUND HER!
- ( chattering )
- A HUNDRED AND SEVENTY-
THREE CENTIMETERS.
THAT WAS HER UNOFFICIAL
NEW RECORD THE FIRST TIME
THE TWO OF US PRACTICED
TOGETHER THAT DAY.
AND NOW IT'S OFFICIAL.
ASAHINA IS SUCH AN AMAZING GIRL,
NOT TO MENTION VERY CUTE.
AFTER THIS, EVERYONE WILL
BE PAYING ATTENTION TO HER.
SHE'S MOVING IN A DIRECTION THAT
IS SO FAR BEYOND MY REACH.
AT THIS POINT, I'LL NEVER
BE ABLE TO CATCH UP TO HER.
AND I'LL BE ALL ALONE.
- AKITSUKI...
- Woman: HEY, WE'VE GOTTA SET
UP THE PLATES!
YEAH, BRING 'EM IN!
BRING 'EM IN.
- YOU KEEP PUSHING
THOSE CHAIRS IN.
- MAN, THIS IS PAIN. WHY DO I
HAVE TO HELP WITH THIS STUFF?
I'M NOT EVEN ON THE TEAM.
- BECAUSE YOU'RE A
FRESHMAN, SWEETIE.
NOW STOP BEING SO LAZY.
HOLD THAT CORNER UP FOR ME.
- THANKS.
- NO PROB. UGH...
SO MUCH FOR PICKING UP GIRLS.
WHERE THE HECK IS YAMATO?
THAT JERK. THIS IS
SUCH A WASTE OF TIME.
- HEY! I SAID HOLD IT UP!
YOU'RE MAKING IT UNEVEN!
- HERE WE GO...
- Boy: SAKURAI! OVER HERE!
- COMING!
- Boy: CAN YOU BRING
ME A SNACK, TOO?
- SURE THING!
- Yamato: HONOKA IS
SUCH A HARD WORKER.
UNTIL THAT NIGHT, I JUST THOUGHT
OF HER AS A GOOD FRIEND.
BUT...
HER LIPS WERE SO SOFT...
- YOU'RE BLUSHING
WHAT'S THAT ALL ABOUT?
- WHAT? NO I'M NOT. SHUT UP!
- SHOULDN'T YOU BE HANGING A
BANNER OR SOMETHING?
- I REALIZED, I WAS LOOKING FOR
HER WHEN I WALKED IN THE ROOM.
I WAS LOOKING FOR HONOKA.
- EVERYONE DID A
GOOD JOB TODAY.
BUT, YOU SHOULD
NEVER BE SATISFIED.
CHEERS, TO THE FUTURE OF THE
AOBA TRACK AND FIELD CLUB
AND TO ASAHINA'S THIRD
PLACE WIN TODAY!
- All: CHEERS!
- ALRIGHT!
- OH, MY GOSH,
LOOK AT THAT!
- COME ON, DRINK UP, SUZUKA.
YOU'VE EARNED IT.
- THANK YOU!
- OH, MY GOSH, I SAW YOU ON TV
YESTERDAY! DID YOU SEE IT?
THEY CALLED YOU THE
"HEROINE OF HIGH JUMP"
- YOU'LL BE SCOUTED
BY UNIVERSITIES!
- I BET YOU'LL GET AWESOME
SPONSORS, TOO!
- HEY. AKITSUKI! WHERE ARE
YOU? GET OVER HERE, NOW!
HASHIBA, WHERE'D AKITSUKI GO?
- I DON'T KNOW. HE WAS HERE
JUST A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
- THAT KID'S REALLY STARTING
TO BECOME A PAIN.
I HOPE HE INTENDS TO
WORK HARDER NEXT YEAR
BECAUSE THIS ISN'T CUTTING IT.
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
GO AND LOOK FOR HIM?
WE NEED TO HAVE A TALK!
- SURE...
- ( sighs ) WHAT'S GOING
ON WITH ME? I DON'T GET IT.
JUST THE OTHER DAY I WAS
TOTALLY INTO ASAHINA,
AND NOW, I CAN'T STOP
THINKING ABOUT HONOKA.
AND WHAT FOR?
JUST BECAUSE WE HELD HANDS?
OR IS IT BECAUSE...
SHE KISSED ME?
IS IT OKAY TO BE THINKING
ABOUT HER SO MUCH?
- THERE YOU ARE!
- HEY, HONOKA.
- YOU JUST DISAPPEARED.
I GOT WORRIED,
SO I CAME LOOKING FOR YOU.
- WELL, YA FOUND ME.
- MIND IF I JOIN YOU?
- OH LOOK, CARP!
- YEAH...
IT'S HARD TO EXPLAIN, BUT...
- LOOK HOW CUTE THEY ARE!
AND THEY'RE NOT AFRAID
OF US, EITHER!
- WOULDN'T IT BE FUN TO
FEED THEM SOMETIME?
- YEAH, IT WOULD.
I FEEL DIFFERENT WITH HER
THAN I DO WITH ASAHINA.
IT'S A DIFFERENT KIND
OF HAPPINESS.
LIKE, I CAN RELAX
WHEN I'M WITH HER.
- IT'S COLD!
- HEY. YOU'RE OKAY NOW.
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
- THANKS.
- HONOKA, I...
- WAIT. JUST HOLD ON, OKAY?
- NO...
- I, UM, SORRY.
- NO, I'M SORRY. I UNDERSTAND.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO...
I KNOW I'M NOT
YOUR GIRLFRIEND, SO...
- AND AT THAT MOMENT, ALL I
COULD THINK ABOUT WAS...
HOW SWEET SHE LOOKED.
- AKITSUKI!
WHOA! NO WAY!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ABOVE ♪
♪ NOW IS ALL WE HAVE ♪
♪ WITH A LITTLE FEELING
AND A LOT OF LOVE ♪
♪ WE TURN UP THE HEAT AND RUN ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- ♪ ALL MY LIFE HERE ON THE
GROUND ABOUT TO RUN AND NOW ♪
♪ I FIND I MUST
ASK MYSELF WHY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE SOMETHING IS STIRRING ♪
♪ I FEEL IT WHISPERING IN ME ♪
♪ SOME DAYS I WAKE UP ♪
♪ BUT MY HEART'S
STILL SLEEPING ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME
TO RUN AND TRY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME TO FLY ♪
♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ON HIGH ♪
♪ WITH OUR GOAL IN SIGHT ♪
♪ WE WILL RUN
WITH ALL OUR MIGHT ♪
♪ TOMORROW AND TODAY
WILL NEVER EVER PASS US BY ♪
♪ WE WILL NOT STOP NOW ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR HEART ALIVE
AND YOUR DREAM SURVIVES ♪
♪ AND YOU CROSS
THE FINISH LINE ♪
♪ LET IT GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- Suzuka: SO, IS IT TRUE THAT
YOU AND HONOKA ARE GOING OUT?
- Yamato: UH, YEAH!
- Suzuka: WOW, GOOD FOR YOU.
THOUGH I HAVE TO ADMIT,
I'M A LITTLE SURPRISED.
I NEVER THOUGHT YOU'D
ACTUALLY HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
HONOKA IS SUCH A TROUPER.
- Yamato: UH, YEAH.