- ♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- Yamato: MAN,
IT'S ANOTHER HOT DAY.
SUMMER'S STARTED
WITH A VENGEANCE.
- BE HONEST WITH ME, ARE YOU
REALLY COMING TO PRACTICE TODAY?
- YEAH. I'LL BE THERE.
- WELL, GOOD.
- UM... ANYWAY,
I WAS THINKING...
- WE BETTER HURRY UP OR
WE'LL BE LATE FOR SCHOOL.
- ( he sighs )
- WHY IS SHE SO COLD?
- ( bell tolls )
- AND NOW WE'LL BE MOVING ON
TO SOME WORD PROBLEMS,
EVERYONE'S FAVORITE.
TRAIN A LEAVES STATION...
- I WONDER IF SHE'S
STILL MAD AT ME.
I'M TIRED OF BEING COMPARED
TO SOME DEAD GUY...
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
- ( he screams )
- AFTER A FIGHT LIKE THAT...
I DON'T KNOW IF OUR FRIENDSHIP
WILL EVER BE THE SAME.
- AS MUCH AS I DON'T
WANT TO ADMIT IT,
I KNOW THAT AKITSUKI
STILL LIKES ASAHINA.
- ( puffing and panting )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
YOU IDIOT! RUN!
- ASAHINA DOESN'T SEEM
TO LIKE HIM.
BUT THEN WHY DID
SHE SAY THAT?
MAYBE SHE JUST DIDN'T WANT
TO SEE HER TEAMMATE LOSE.
OR DOES SHE LIKE
AKITSUKI LIKE I DO?
- ( people chattering )
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- ( whistle blows )
- THAT'S GONNA DO IT FOR TODAY.
- ALL RIGHT!
- MAN... FINALLY.
- GOOD PRACTICE, AKITSUKI...
HERE'S A TOWEL.
- THANKS.
HAS ANYONE EVER TOLD
YOU HOW NICE YOU ARE?
- NO. NOBODY'S EVER
TOLD ME THAT BEFORE.
- HEY, MANAGER.
I SURE COULD USE A TOWEL.
- I THOUGHT YOU
MIGHT BE THIRSTY.
SO I BROUGHT YOU A
BOTTLE OF WATER AS WELL.
- SHE IGNORED ME.
- I GUESS IT'S TIME
THAT I GET GOING.
OH. WAIT. AKITSUKI?
WE COULD WALK HOME
- TOGETHER IF YOU WANT.
- AKITSUKI!
- ( he coughs )
- FOR YOUR PUNISHMENT YOU HAVE
TO DO TWENTY EXTRA DASHES
EVERY DAY AFTER PRACTICE.
- WHAT'S THAT? I CAN'T
RUN ANY MORE TODAY.
AND WHAT'S THIS
PUNISHMENT FOR, ANYWAY?
- HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN ALREADY?
- OKAY, OKAY. I REMEMBER WHAT
I DID. I'M SORRY, CAPTAIN.
- ALL RIGHT. YOU BETTER GET
STARTED THEN.
- HE DIDN'T HURT YOU,
DID HE? AKITSUKI?
- WHY DOES HE HAVE TO BE
SO HARD ON ME ALL THE TIME?
HE THINKS HE'S SO TOUGH.
- I THINK HE JUST EXPECTS
A LOT OUT OF YOU.
- YOU'RE JUST SAYING THAT.
- YOU SHOULD GET STARTED.
I'LL STAY WITH YOU
UNTIL YOU FINISH UP.
- DON'T BE SILLY. THERE'S NO
REASON FOR YOU TO STAY.
- YEAH. BUT I...
- DON'T WORRY, I'M NOT
GOING TO SLACK OFF.
I'LL TAKE
MY PUNISHMENT. PROMISE.
- GOOD LUCK THEN.
I'LL SEE YA.
- LATER.
- AFTER I LEAVE, HE'LL BE
HERE ALONE WITH ASAHINA.
- GEEZ, ARE YOU SETTING UP
TO TRAIN SOME MORE?
- YEAH, IF I WANT TO DO
WELL AT THE REGIONALS,
I HAVE TO WORK HARD.
- I WONDER IF AKITSUKI
WILL EVER LIKE ME
THE WAY HE LIKES HER.
- ( puffing and panting )
- MAN, THIS IS ROUGH.
I WONDER HOW MUCH LONGER
SHE'LL GO ON IGNORING ME.
SHE'S SO MAD, IT'S LIKE I DON'T
EVEN EXIST TO HER ANYMORE.
I FEEL SO EMPTY AND HUNGRY.
I SHOULD FINISH AND GO HOME.
- I CAN'T LEAVE. I WANT
TO SEE HIM AGAIN.
HE MUST BE DONE BY NOW.
SHOULD I GO CHECK?
- ( exhaling loudly )
- I'VE FINALLY
FINISHED ALL OF THEM.
ASAHINA.
SHE MUST BE LEAVING.
DAMN IT. CAN'T SHE EVEN
SAY A SINGLE WORD TO ME?
IT'S ONLY "GOODBYE."
- IF YOU WERE A BIT NICER,
THEN MAYBE I WOULD.
- I THOUGHT THAT YOU
HAD LEFT ALREADY.
- I FORGOT SOMETHING THAT
I WANTED TO TELL YOU.
- OW!
- YOU REALLY SHOULD
BE STRETCHING
EVERY DAY
AFTER PRACTICE.
AND YOU CAN'T JUST
PRETEND TO STRETCH.
- YOU SAID YOU HAD
SOMETHING TO SAY.
WAS THAT IT, OR IS THERE MORE?
- I HAVE MORE.
- OW, OW, OW, OW, OW!
- YOUR STARTING STANCE
COULD USE WORK.
AND YOU LEAN FORWARD TOO
MUCH WHEN YOU'RE AT TOP SPEED.
I'VE BEEN WATCHING YOU
THE LAST FEW RACES
AND I THINK YOUR TECHNIQUE
NEEDS SOME IMPROVEMENT.
- WHAT? YOU MEAN THAT
YOU'VE BEEN WATCHING ME?
- YOU SHOULDN'T LET
IT GO TO YOUR HEAD.
I JUST THOUGHT I COULD HELP.
- OH. THANKS THEN. I GUESS.
MAYBE SHE DOES STILL
CARE FOR ME AFTER ALL.
BUT AS LONG AS WE CAN BE
FRIENDS, THAT'S ENOUGH FOR ME.
HONOKA. ARE YOU STILL HERE?
I THOUGHT YOU HAD
GONE HOME ALREADY.
- OH. I FORGOT SOMETHING
SO I THOUGHT
I'D STOP BY AND SEE
HOW YOU WERE COMING ALONG.
- I SEE. WELL, I JUST FINISHED.
ASAHINA WAS JUST POINTING OUT
ALL OF MY SHORTCOMINGS TO ME.
ACCORDING TO HER,
I'VE GOT QUITE A FEW.
- I THOUGHT I'D GIVE
YOU SOME ADVICE
FROM ONE TEAMMATE
TO ANOTHER, GEEZ.
- OH. OKAY.
I'M SURE ASAHINA HAS HIGH
EXPECTATIONS FOR
AKITSUKI AS AN ATHLETE,
AND JUST WANTS HIM TO GET
BETTER TO HELP THE
TEAM AS A WHOLE
BUT I STILL WONDER, IF THERE'S
MORE TO IT THAN THAT.
- ( whistle blows )
- OKAY. THAT'S ALL FOR TODAY.
- YOU DID WELL, AKITSUKI.
YOU DIDN'T SKIP PRACTICE
FOR A WHOLE WEEK.
- I BARELY MADE IT.
- WELL, YOU WON'T HAVE TO
PRACTICE THE DAY AFTER TOMORROW.
YOU'LL HAVE THE
WHOLE DAY TO REST.
- AT LEAST I DON'T HAVE
PRACTICE ON SUNDAY.
- ( doorbell rings )
- HELLO?
- GOOD EVENING, SIR.
I'M WITH THE CABLE COMPANY.
- I THOUGHT THAT YOU WORKED
FOR THE NEWSPAPER.
- TODAY I'M HERE TO GET YOU
TO SIGN UP FOR CABLE.
SELLING NEWSPAPERS IS
MY OTHER PART TIME JOB.
- OH, IS THAT SO?
- IF YOU SIGN UP TODAY,
I'LL EVEN THROW
IN THESE FREE TICKETS
TO THE WATERPARK.
THESE ARE THE LAST
TWO THAT I HAVE.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- LIAR. YOU'VE PROBABLY
GOT TONS OF THOSE.
- YOU'RE SUCH A SUSPICIOUS KID.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT, THIS TIME
I'LL MAKE AN EXCEPTION.
TAKE THESE AND GO
WITH YOUR GIRLFRIEND.
AND IF YOU DECIDE YOU WANT
CABLE, LET ME KNOW.
- BUT I DON'T
HAVE A GIRLFRIEND.
- WHAT? THE WATERPARK?
- YEAH, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- YOU MEAN, ABOUT ASKING
SUZUKA TO GO WITH YOU?
- RIGHT.
- LISTEN, MAN. WHAT KIND
OF A RELATIONSHIP
DO YOU THINK A GUY
AND A GIRL HAVE
IF THEY GO TO THE POOL ALONE?
- UM, WHAT KIND?
- IT'S NOT LIKE YOU'RE IN SOME
MANGA OR TV DRAMA SERIES.
SO UNLESS SHE'S GOT
SOMETHING FOR YOU
OR YOU'RE ALREADY GOING OUT,
THERE'S NO WAY SHE'D
GO WITH YOU.
- GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
- AND BESIDES. SHE ALREADY
SHOT YOU DOWN ONCE.
IF I WERE YOU,
I WOULDN'T WANNA GO
THROUGH THAT DISGRACE AGAIN.
DIDN'T YOU LEARN
ANYTHING LAST TIME?
- BUT I THOUGHT THAT
MAYBE SHE'D WANT TO GO
BECAUSE IT'S SOME GOOD
LOW-IMPACT EXERCISE.
- YOU DON'T NEED TO CONVINCE ME!
YOU'RE PROBABLY TOO
LATE ANYWAY.
I BET A GIRL LIKE SUZUKA
ALREADY HAS PLANS
FOR HER DAY OFF.
- YEAH, I BET YOU'RE RIGHT.
SHE'LL PROBABLY GO HOME.
- I THINK YOU SHOULD JUST
FORGET ABOUT IT, DUDE.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
I SHOULDN'T ASK HER.
BESIDES, I'M AFRAID TO HEAR
THAT SHE ALREADY HAS PLANS.
- OH, AKITSUKI,
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
- OH, HEY, HONOKA.
- IT'S HOT TODAY, ISN'T IT?
- UH-HUH, IT'S JULY ALREADY.
- AND I BET IT'S GONNA BE
ANOTHER HOT DAY TOMORROW.
- PROBABLY.
- SO TELL ME, AKITSUKI,
DO YOU HAVE PLANS TOMORROW?
- NOT YET. I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M GONNA DO.
- I'VE GOT AN IDEA.
HOW 'BOUT WE GO TO
THE WATERPARK TOGETHER.
SEE, LOOK, TWO TICKETS.
A GIRL GAVE THEM TO ME
FOR FREE LAST NIGHT.
- WHAT? WITH ME?
- I KNOW WHAT THOSE ARE FOR.
THEY'RE FOR THAT
BRAND NEW WATERPARK.
ARE YOU GUYS GONNA GO?
BECAUSE I WOULD TOTALLY
LOVE TO JOIN YOU.
- YEAH, BUT WE WERE...
I WANTED THE TWO OF US TO GO.
JUST ME AND AKITSUKI.
- I WANNA GO, TOO.
I'LL BE ABLE TO GET A
GOOD LOW-IMPACT WORKOUT
WITHOUT STRAINING MY
HIP AND LEG JOINTS.
- HEY! SUZUKA. DO YOU
WANNA GO WITH US?
- GO WHERE?
- OH. THE FOUR OF US ARE GOING
TO THE WATERPARK TOMORROW.
YOU SHOULD TOTALLY JOIN US.
- MAYBE SHE ALREADY HAS PLANS.
SHE DOESN'T HAVE
TO COME WITH US.
- THERE'S NO WAY SHE'LL COME.
I'M SURE SHE'LL GO
SEE TSUDA TOMORROW.
- ALL RIGHT, I'LL GO.
- WONDERFUL! I CAN'T WAIT.
- SWEET!
- DID SHE DECIDE TO
GO BECAUSE OF ME?
THERE'S NO TELLING
WITH THIS GIRL.
ASAHINA.
I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU DECIDED TO COME.
IT SEEMED LIKE SHE DECIDED
AFTER LOOKING AT ME.
MAYBE SHE CAME SO WE COULD
SPEND THE DAY TOGETHER.
- THANKS FOR WAITING.
- WEREN'T YOU EVER TOLD
IT'S NOT NICE TO STARE?
- I... I WASN'T STARING.
- ARE YOU PRACTICING TO BECOME
A DIRTY OLD MAN, AKITSUKI?
- I SAID I'M NOT STARING.
- HE CAN'T TAKE
HIS EYES OFF HER.
WELL, THANK YOU, BUT,
EVEN IF YOU DID GIVE ME
THE FREE TICKETS, WHO
WOULD I GO WITH?
- I'M SURE THERE'S AT LEAST
ONE BOY THAT YOU LIKE.
YOU SHOULD INVITE HIM
AND THEN TEMPT HIM
WITH A SEXY BATHING SUIT.
- I'LL DO MY BEST. I HOPE THIS
SWIMSUIT'S SEXY ENOUGH.
- IF ASAHINA DID DECIDE TO COME
BECAUSE OF ME,
THEN MAYBE I SHOULD
BE MORE AGGRESSIVE,
AND SHOW HER I WANT
TO BE WITH HER, TOO.
SO, HEY, WHAT DO...
- WE SHOULD GO
RIDE THE WATERSLIDE.
I HEARD IT'S THE TALLEST
IN THE WORLD.
- I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD BE
RUNNING AROUND THE POOL.
- BUT IF WE DON'T HURRY THEN
WE'LL HAVE TO WAIT IN LINE.
- WHAT DO YOU WANT
TO DO, AKITSUKI?
- SAKURAI. HOW ABOUT WE GO AND
CHECK OUT THE WAVE POOL. HUH?
- AKITSUKI, WHY DON'T YOU
COME ALONG WITH US?
- NAH. I'LL JUST STAY HERE.
- WELL, OKAY.
- COME ON, LET'S GO ALREADY.
- ALL I'M INTERESTED IN
TODAY IS TRYING TO GET
CLOSER TO ASAHINA, AND MAKE
HER LIKE ME AGAIN.
- ( both screaming
and laughing )
- HOW MANY TIMES ARE THEY
GONNA RIDE THAT THING?
YOU'D THINK THEY'D BE
BORED OF IT BY NOW.
THEY'VE BEEN RIDING
IT FOR AN HOUR.
WHEN ARE THEY GONNA PAY
ATTENTION TO ME?
- Honoka: AKITSUKI?
YOU HAVEN'T EVEN
GONE IN THE WATER YET,
HAVE YOU? WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- NOTHING. I JUST WANT TO
SIT HERE AND RELAX.
- HE'S SITTING HERE SO
HE CAN LOOK AT ASAHINA.
HEY. CAN I ASK YOU
A QUICK QUESTION?
DO YOU THINK THIS SWIMSUIT
IS TOO SMALL FOR ME?
IT FEELS A LITTLE TIGHT
IN THE CHEST AREA.
- ( he screams )
- I'VE GOT A BUG IN MY EYE.
- I'M SORRY.
- HEY! I THOUGHT I MIGHT
FIND YOU HERE, SAKURAI.
- COME ON, I WANNA GO ON
THE WATERSLIDE TOGETHER.
- OH. BUT I WAS JUST...
- HURRY UP, LET'S GO.
- WAIT, HOLD UP, KOBAYAKAWA.
I DON'T WANNA GO ON
THE WATERSLIDE.
- HERE SHE COMES.
NOW'S MY CHANCE.
- ASAHINA.
I THINK I'M GONNA GO GET SOME
JUICE. DO YOU WANT ANYTHING?
MAYBE SHE'LL GO WITH
ME TO GET A DRINK.
- I COULD SURE USE
SOMETHING TO DRINK.
HOW ABOUT SOME JUICE, AKITSUKI?
- HUH?
- SUZUKA, WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- WELL, I'LL HAVE A MELON SODA.
- I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
- LET'S RIDE THE
WATERSLIDE ONCE MORE
AND THEN WE CAN CHECK
OUT THE WAVE POOL.
- THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
- I'M BEGINNING TO THINK
SHE DIDN'T COME FOR ME.
MAYBE SHE JUST
LIKES THE POOL.
- DO YOU GUYS WANNA GO?
- I'M SO SUNBURNED.
- NOW THAT'S WHAT I CALL
A GOOD DAY. I HAD A BLAST.
- ME, TOO.
- WELL, I DIDN'T MANAGE TO
GET ANY CLOSER TO ASAHINA.
- I HARDLY GOT A CHANCE
TO TALK TO AKITSUKI AT ALL.
- HOW ABOUT WE STOP AND GET A
BITE TO EAT BEFORE WE GO HOME?
- SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
- WHAT DO YOU WANNA EAT?
- I WANT SOME MEAT.
- MEAT?
- YEAH. LET'S GET
SOME BARBECUE.
- HEY, GUYS, WAIT UP.
DON'T LEAVE ME BEHIND.
DAMN SHOELACES.
THEY'RE ALWAYS TRIPPING ME UP.
ASAHINA. IS SHE
WAITING FOR ME?
SORRY.
HEY, ASAHINA.
I WAS JUST WONDERING...
- ( crackers burst )
- OH WOW! THOSE ARE AMAZING.
- HEY. AKITSUKI.
AKITSUKI?
- IT'S SO PRETTY.
- YEAH. THEY'RE REALLY
QUITE NICE.
THEY REMIND ME OF THE FIREWORKS
WE SAW AT THE PARADE.
WHAT AM I SAYING?
I'M COMING ON TOO STRONG.
IT'S JUST THAT...
OH, WELL, NEVER MIND.
- WELL, LET'S GO. I IMAGINE
EVERYONE'S WAITING FOR US.
- ASAHINA.
I JUST...
- IF I WERE YOU,
I WOULDN'T WANNA
GO THROUGH THAT DISGRACE AGAIN.
DIDN'T YOU LEARN
ANYTHING FROM LAST TIME?
- THERE THEY ARE.
- HEY. WHERE'VE YOU BEEN?
- WE'VE BEEN LOOKING
FOR YOU EVERYWHERE.
I THOUGHT WE'D NEVER FIND YOU.
- SORRY. YAMATO'S
SHOELACES WERE UNTIED,
SO WE HAD TO STOP TO FIX THEM.
- YOU'D BETTER BE
CAREFUL, AKITSUKI.
- SORRY.
- LET'S GO GET SOMETHING
TO EAT ALREADY.
- OKAY.
I GUESS SHE MUST
STILL BE MAD AT ME.
- I SAID THAT MY FRIENDS
ASKED ME TO GO
TO THE WATERPARK
WITH THEM TODAY.
THAT'S RIGHT. YEAH.
WITH SOME FRIENDS.
WE WENT EARLY AND
STAYED THE WHOLE DAY.
- THAT SOUNDS LIKE A LOT
OF FUN. I'M GLAD YOU WENT.
I JUST CALLED BECAUSE I WAS
WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE COMING BACK
HOME TODAY TO VISIT KAZUKI,
BUT THEN YOU NEVER SHOWED UP.
- WELL, I WAS COMING, BUT...
- I UNDERSTAND. I HOPE YOU HAD
A GOOD TIME TODAY.
DID YOU GO WITH ANY
BOYS THAT YOU LIKE
OR WAS IT JUST THE GIRLS?
- THERE AREN'T ANY GUYS I LIKE
HERE. YOU'RE OUTTA YOUR MIND.
IF YOU DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
ELSE TO TALK ABOUT,
THEN I'M HANGING UP NOW.
- HEY, WAIT.
I THINK SHE WAS PROTESTING
A BIT TOO MUCH.
I CAN STILL READ THAT
GIRL LIKE AN OPEN BOOK.
KEEPING SUZUKA FROM
COMING BACK HOME, HUH?
I GUESS THAT GUY ISN'T DOING
TOO BAD FOR HIMSELF.
- ASAHINA.
I WAS WONDERING, WOULD YOU
LIKE TO WALK HOME WITH ME?
- SURE. I GUESS SO.
- CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
- GO AHEAD.
- IT'S JUST THAT IT SEEMS
THAT YOU AND AKITSUKI
ARE REALLY CLOSE, AREN'T YOU?
YOU TWO ARE ALWAYS HANGING OUT
TOGETHER AND HAVING FUN.
- IT'S NOT REALLY THAT MUCH FUN.
ALL I DO IS COMPLAIN.
- OH, REALLY? IS THAT ALL?
- I DON'T THINK I COULD I GET
CLOSE TO A GUY LIKE HIM.
WE'RE ALWAYS FIGHTING.
HEY, WHAT'S WRONG?
- THEN, IT'S OKAY?
- HUH? WHAT WAS THAT?
- IT'S OKAY IF I TELL
HIM HOW I FEEL?
I MEAN THAT... THE THING IS,
I REALLY LIKE AKITSUKI
AND I HAVE FOR A VERY LONG TIME,
SINCE BEFORE YOU KNEW HIM.
SINCE WE WERE KIDS.
- WHY ARE YOU TELLING ME THIS?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
- I KNOW I DON'T.
BUT WHEN I SEE YOU TOGETHER
I CAN'T HELP BUT THINK THAT YOU
HAVE FEELINGS FOR AKITSUKI.
- I... I DON'T.
I JUST DON'T FEEL
THAT WAY ABOUT HIM.
I DON'T LIKE YAMATO LIKE THAT.
YAMATO.
- OH. SORRY.
- HONOKA?
- HEY, YOU KNOW THAT I DIDN'T
MEAN WHAT I SAID.
- IT'S FINE. I GET IT. REALLY.
I KNOW YOU DON'T REALLY LIKE ME.
I UNDERSTAND THAT NOW.
- SORRY.
- WE SHOULD REALLY BE GETTING
BACK. IT'S ALMOST DINNERTIME.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ABOVE ♪
♪ NOW IS ALL WE HAVE ♪
♪ WITH A LITTLE FEELING
AND A LOT OF LOVE ♪
♪ WE TURN UP THE HEAT AND RUN ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- ♪ ALL MY LIFE HERE ON THE
GROUND ABOUT TO RUN AND NOW ♪
♪ I FIND I MUST
ASK MYSELF WHY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE SOMETHING IS STIRRING ♪
♪ I FEEL IT WHISPERING IN ME ♪
♪ SOME DAYS I WAKE UP ♪
♪ BUT MY HEART'S
STILL SLEEPING ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME
TO RUN AND TRY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME TO FLY ♪
♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ON HIGH ♪
♪ WITH OUR GOAL IN SIGHT ♪
♪ WE WILL RUN
WITH ALL OUR MIGHT ♪
♪ TOMORROW AND TODAY
WILL NEVER EVER PASS US BY ♪
♪ WE WILL NOT STOP NOW ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR HEART ALIVE
AND YOUR DREAM SURVIVES ♪
♪ AND YOU CROSS
THE FINISH LINE ♪
♪ LET IT GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- Yamato: UNTIL NOW, I THOUGHT
THAT WE WERE JUST GOOD FRIENDS.
BUT I REALIZED THAT MY EYES
WERE ALWAYS SEARCHING FOR HER.
FOR HONOKA.
IT'S A DIFFERENT
KIND OF HAPPINESS
THAN BEING WITH ASAHINA.
WHEN I'M WITH HONOKA,
I FEEL COMPLETELY AT EASE.