- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATH A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ YOU'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER BLOW AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- THANKS FOR BREAKFAST, AYANO.
IT WAS DELICIOUS.
- YOU'RE VERY WELCOME.
OH, YOU DON'T NEED TO CLEAN UP.
- OH, OKAY.
WELL THEN, I GUESS I'M OFF
TO MORNING PRACTICE.
- DON'T YOU EVER
GET TIRED OF IT?
I MEAN, YOU'RE AT THE TRACK
ALL THE TIME.
- WELL, TOMORROW
IS THE SCHOOL ANNIVERSARY,
SO I'LL AT LEAST
GET ONE DAY OFF TO REST.
- HAVE A GOOD DAY, SUZUKA.
DON'T WORK TOO HARD.
- THANKS. LATER.
( door opens )
- WORKAHOLIC.
- ( door closes )
- IT'S 7:30
ON A BEAUTIFUL FRIDAY MORNING.
LET'S LOOK AT TODAY'S HOROSCOPE.
- I DIDN'T KNOW WE GOT THE DAY
OFF FOR THE SCHOOL ANNIVERSARY.
MAYBE ASAHINA AND I CAN GO OUT
TOGETHER. DO SOMETHING.
UNLESS SHE'S ALREADY
MADE PLANS FOR THE DAY.
MAYBE I'LL TAKE HER OUT
FOR SOME KARAOKE.
THEN AGAIN, KARAOKE
DOESN'T REALLY SEEM
LIKE ASAHINA'S THING.
WELL, MAYBE WE CAN GO
TO THE AMUSEMENT PARK.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE FUN.
BUT IF I ASK HER OUT
TO AN AMUSEMENT PARK,
I RUN THE RISK OF
MAKING HER THINK
THAT I'M COMING ON
WAY TOO STRONG.
WHY ARE THESE THINGS
SO DIFFICULT?
- ( doorbell rings )
- WHO'S THAT?
- GOOD MORNING. I'M HERE ON
BEHALF OF THE MAIASA NEWSPAPER.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO START
A SUBSCRIPTION?
IF YOU SIGN UP WITH US TODAY,
WE'RE OFFERING TWO COMPLIMENTARY
PASSES TO FANTASYLAND.
THESE ARE THE LAST TWO TICKETS.
ARE YOU INTERESTED?
THEY'RE ONLY GOOD
THROUGH TOMORROW.
- THIS IS PERFECT!
SIGN ME UP! AND HAND OVER
THOSE TICKETS, PLEASE.
THEY'RE MINE.
- THANK YOU VERY MUCH, SIR.
YOUR SUBSCRIPTION WILL
START TOMORROW MORNING.
- ALL RIGHT, SOUNDS LIKE A DEAL.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THE ANSWER TO MY PROBLEMS
JUST FELL INTO MY LAP.
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
LEFT FOR ME TO DO.
BUT HOW DO I ASK HER?
WHY AM I SO AWKWARD?
I KNOW! THAT'S IT!
IT'S SO SIMPLE.
( chuckling to himself )
MAYBE I CAN JUST LEAVE THEM
WHERE SHE'LL NOTICE.
THAT WAY, SHE'LL ASK ME
ABOUT THEM. BRILLIANT!
- ( bell dinging )
- ( panting )
SHE DIDN'T NOTICE.
I SUPPOSE SHE WAS JUST
WAY TOO BUSY TODAY.
( sighs )
ALL RIGHT, I THINK
I'M GOING TO SAY IT.
MAYBE I CAN TELL HER
BEFORE WE EAT DINNER,
LIKE WHEN SHE GETS HOME
FROM PRACTICE.
- ( doorbell ringing )
HEY, ARE YOU HOME?
- UH, ASAHINA?
- ( doorbell ringing
repeatedly )
HEY, YOUR AUNT SAID
IT'S ALMOST TIME FOR DINNER.
- OH. OKAY. UM, I...
- WHAT'S UP?
YOU'RE NOT FEELING WELL?
- I'M FINE. IT'S NOTHING,
NEVER MIND.
I PRACTICED THIS
SO MANY TIMES IN MY HEAD.
WHY CAN'T I JUST
SAY IT OUT LOUD?
UH...
- FOOD'S GETTING COLD.
- HEY, WAIT.
( sighs ) I'M SUCH A COWARD.
- ( dog barking )
- THERE'S NO WAY I
WAS GONNA ASK HER
IN FRONT OF EVERYONE AT DINNER.
MAYBE I'LL STOP BY
HER ROOM LATER.
- HEY, THERE YOU ARE.
- I DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD
BE DRINKING OUT HERE, SAOTOME.
- I'VE BEEN WAITING,
MY YA-MA-TO.
- GREAT. JUST WHAT I NEEDED.
- WHAT'S THIS?
WHERE DID YOU GET FREE PASSES
TO FANTASYLAND?
NO WAY!
YOU'VE GOT TWO PASSES.
YOU WERE GONNA ASK
SUZUKA TO GO, WEREN'T YOU?
- NO, I WASN'T.
- GREAT, THEN I'LL GO WITH YOU.
( chuckles ) JUST SO HAPPENS
THAT I'M FREE
TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
WE'LL GO TOGETHER,
IT'LL BE A BLAST.
- NEVER GONNA HAPPEN.
GIVE 'EM BACK.
- MEGUMI, CATCH!
- STOP IT! THEY'RE MINE!
- THAT HURTS.
- SORRY.
- CALM DOWN THERE, SPORT.
WE'RE JUST HAVING A LITTLE FUN.
- THEN GIVE THOSE BACK.
THEY'RE MY ONLY HOPE
WITH ASAHINA.
- HOW PATHETIC!
ARE YOU GONNA CRY?
- JUST GIVE THE
TICKETS BACK TO HIM.
MAYBE THAT'LL MAKE
HIM GET OFF OF ME.
- MAYBE.
- SERIOUSLY, YOUR KNEE IS
CRUSHING MY LEG. CAN YOU GET UP?
- ( purring )
( mewing )
- OH, MY GOODNESS,
WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT?
- GORO! WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE YOU DOING?
MY LAST HOPE, DOWN THE DRAIN.
YOU KNOW YOU'RE GONNA
PAY FOR THOSE, RIGHT?
- DON'T BLAME ME.
BLAME THE STUPID CAT.
I'M NOT PAYIN' FOR NOTHIN'.
- YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME!
YES, YOU ARE.
- YOU'RE NOT GETTING
A DIME OUTTA ME,
AND LET ME TELL YOU WHY.
'CAUSE I HAVE GOT THE GOODS
ON YOU, BUDDY. BLACKMAIL.
- WELL, THAT'S THE END OF IT.
THERE'S NO WAY
I CAN ASK HER OUT NOW.
EVERY TIME I TRY, ALL MY PLANS
KEEP BLOWING UP IN MY FACE.
AND I CAN'T AFFORD
TO REPLACE THE TICKETS.
- ( footsteps approaching )
HEY. I'M GOING TO THE STORE.
WOULD YOU MIND MOVING OVER
A BIT SO I CAN GET BY?
- YEAH, SURE.
I CAN'T ASK HER NOW.
- OH, THERE'S A NEWSPAPER
IN YOUR DOOR.
I JUST NOTICED IT
AS I WAS COMING DOWN.
I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU HAD A SUBSCRIPTION.
- YEAH.
A REALLY PUSHY
SALESWOMAN CAME BY.
SHE SIGNED ME UP FOR A MONTH.
- OH, YEAH, SHE CAME BY MY PLACE
TOO AND I TURNED HER DOWN.
SHE DID GIVE ME TWO FREE TICKETS
TO FANTASYLAND, THOUGH.
- (gasps )
ARE YOU KIDDING?
- NO, SHE JUST GAVE THEM TO ME.
PRETTY WEIRD, HUH?
- SHE WOULD'VE
GIVEN ME THE TICKETS
WITHOUT THE
SUBSCRIPTION. DAMN IT.
- AND EVEN THOUGH
THE TICKETS WERE FREE,
I WOULD SURE FEEL
PRETTY WASTEFUL
IF I JUST THREW THEM AWAY.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU?
- NOTHING. I'M FINE.
I JUST GOTTA BE CALM.
BE SMOOTH.
NOT TOO SERIOUS.
BUT NOT TOO JOKING EITHER.
STOP THINKING ABOUT IT.
JUST DO IT. THIS IS MY CHANCE.
I GOTTA TAKE IT.
WELL, I GUESS I COULD GO
WITH YOU IF YOU WANTED ME TO.
OH, CRAP! I CAN'T BELIEVE
I JUST SAID THAT!
MY HEART FEELS LIKE
IT'S IN MY STOMACH.
I... WAS...
JUST... KIDDING.
- YOU CAN BE SUCH A CHILD.
- WHAT?
- IF YOU WANT TO GO WITH ME,
YOU SHOULD JUST SAY SO.
- I... UM...
- WHATEVER. I CAN GO WITH YOU
IF YOU WANT.
I DO HAVE THE DAY OFF TOMORROW
AND I DON'T WANNA JUST SIT
AROUND THE HOUSE ALL BY MYSELF.
WHAT'S WRONG?
DON'T YOU WANNA GO?
- UH... SURE.
I MEAN, I'D LOVE TO GO.
- ALL RIGHT THEN.
I'LL SEE YOU
EARLY IN THE MORNING.
THAT IS IF YOU DON'T
SLEEP IN TOO LATE.
- OH, I WON'T.
I DID IT. I DID IT!
I DID IT!
- ( mewing )
- ( raining heavily )
- MAN, THIS SUCKS.
WHY'D IT HAVE TO RAIN TODAY?
- HOW AWFUL. THE PARADE
WILL PROBABLY BE CANCELED.
- WELL, CHEER UP, ASAHINA.
AT LEAST ALL THE INDOOR
RIDES ARE STILL OPEN, RIGHT?
- BUT THAT'S NO FUN.
ALL THE INDOOR RIDES
ARE FOR LITTLE KIDS, YAMATO.
- MAYBE. BUT FOR NOW,
HOW ABOUT WE CHECK THAT OUT?
- "THE FLYING DOLPHIN."
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A BLAST.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- NOTHING.
- ( indistinct conversation )
- TODAY ISN'T TURNING OUT
AS I'D HOPED.
THIS IS TERRIBLE.
- Male staff: MOVE UP, PLEASE.
DON'T HOLD UP THE LINE.
- HEY, YAMATO, WAKE UP!
- HUH?
- I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
I WANNA GO HOME AFTER THIS.
- I WOULDN'T HAVE COME
IF I HAD KNOWN
IT WAS GOING TO BE LIKE THIS.
WHY IS SHE IN SUCH A BAD MOOD?
THIS SHOULD NOT BE
AN INDOOR RIDE!
- WOW, AMAZING. YOU CAN SEE
A WHOLE CITY FROM UP HERE.
- HUH?
- THERE'S A CITY
DOWN THERE, LOOK!
- WHAT?
- CITY!
I GUESS I UNDERESTIMATED
THE INTENSITY
OF INDOOR RIDES THESE DAYS.
MAN, I THOUGHT I WAS GONNA
HAVE A HEART ATTACK IN THERE.
I GUESS IT WAS FUN, THOUGH.
LOOKS LIKE SHE'S STILL ANGRY.
SHE'LL PROBABLY WANT
TO LEAVE NOW.
- LOOK AT THIS.
( laughs )
THE LOOK ON YOUR FACE
IS PRICELESS.
- WHAT? WELL, I COULDN'T
HELP IT! IT WAS SCARY!
WHY DID THERE HAVE TO BE
A CAMERA ON THE RIDE?
- WELL THEN. I GUESS
IT'S ON TO THE NEXT RIDE.
- UM, BUT I THOUGHT
YOU WANTED TO GO HOME?
- NO WAY. I'M FINALLY
STARTING TO HAVE FUN.
- ( chuckles ) ALL RIGHT!
YOU WANNA HIT
ALL THE INDOOR RIDES THEN?
- ( chuckles )
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN HANDLE IT?
- ( groaning )
- WELL, THEN.
I GUESS WE COULD GO,
BUT THERE ARE STILL A LOT OF
RIDES WE HAVEN'T BEEN ON.
- I DON'T THINK I CAN MAKE IT.
I NEVER KNEW THAT THIS PLACE
WAS SO ENORMOUS.
IT'S A WHOLE CITY UNTO ITSELF.
- DON'T TELL ME THAT YOU'VE
ALREADY WORN YOURSELF OUT.
YOU'RE HOPELESS.
I'M NOT READY TO GO HOME YET.
YOU CAN SIT HERE IF YOU WANT,
BUT I'M GOING SHOPPING.
- BUT CAN'T WE JUST
RELAX HERE A BIT LONGER?
- NO. NOW COME ON, THE STORE'S
ONLY OPEN FOR A FEW MORE HOURS.
- WHATEVER YOU SAY.
SHE CAN BE SO BOSSY. AND BOY,
DOES SHE LOVE TO SHOP.
YOU ENJOYED FANTASYLAND
A LOT MORE
THAN YOU THOUGHT YOU WOULD,
DIDN'T YOU, ASAHINA?
- UH... WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- OH, NOTHING.
JUST FORGET ABOUT IT.
- WELL, COME ON, LET'S GO.
- OH, ALL RIGHT.
THIS IS HOW IT ALWAYS ENDS UP
EVERY TIME I GO
OUT WITH ASAHINA.
THESE LOOK PRETTY TASTY,
DON'T THEY?
- NO. THEY'RE TOO BLAND
AND DRY FOR ME.
- SHE DRAGS ME ALL OVER
THE PLACE ASKING MY OPINION,
BUT SHE NEVER TAKES IT.
- THIS LOOKS JUST LIKE GORO.
FAT AND UGLY. ( chuckles )
- I GUESS I'LL ALWAYS
JUST BE HER FRIEND.
- ( gasps )
LOOK, YAMATO.
IT STOPPED RAINING.
- AH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I WISH IT COULD HAVE
STOPPED EARLIER.
- LET'S GO. THEY MIGHT
HAVE THE PARADE AFTER ALL.
- YEAH. SURE.
- IT'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
- UH-HUH.
SHE'S STILL HOLDING MY HAND.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
THE MORE I'M AROUND HER,
THE MORE I LIKE HER.
MAYBE THINGS SHOULD STAY
JUST AS THEY ARE NOW.
IF I TELL HER
HOW I REALLY FEEL,
IT COULD DESTROY
THE RELATIONSHIP WE HAVE.
I WISH WE COULD JUST
STAND HERE FOREVER.
I DON'T WANT THIS MOMENT
TO EVER END.
I, UH...
I REALLY LIKE YOU, ASAHINA.
- TELL ME YOU'RE JOKING.
YOU'RE SETTING ME UP FOR
A PRACTICAL JOKE, AREN'T YOU?
- MM...
- AM I RIGHT?
- NO, I... I DON'T KNOW.
THIS IS HORRIBLE.
WHAT AM I DOING?
I CAN PLAY THIS OFF AS A JOKE.
IF I DO, MAYBE THINGS
WILL STAY THE SAME, BUT...
IT'S NOT A JOKE!
I'M BEING COMPLETELY SERIOUS.
I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO TELL YOU FOREVER.
BUT I... I...
I WANT TO BE
YOUR BOYFRIEND, ASAHINA.
- I... I'M NOT REALLY SURE
WHAT TO SAY.
WE HAVEN'T EVEN KNOWN
EACH OTHER FOR VERY LONG.
- THAT DOESN'T MATTER.
- SO, THEN, YOU'RE SERIOUS?
I'M SORRY.
- ( fireworks exploding )
- ( chuckles awkwardly )
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU JUST PRETEND
I NEVER SAID IT.
WE CAN STILL BE FRIENDS,
CAN'T WE?
- I'M NOT SURE.
- WE SHOULD HEAD BACK THEN.
YOU'VE GOT
AN EARLY PRACTICE TOMORROW.
- YAMATO, WAIT. I'LL TAKE THAT.
- I... DON'T MIND.
I'LL CARRY IT.
- BUT YOU... DON'T HAVE TO.
- WELL, OKAY.
- WELL, GOOD NIGHT THEN.
- GOOD NIGHT THEN.
- ( door opens )
- I BLEW IT.
- WELCOME BACK.
HOW WAS YOUR NIGHT?
- HMM.
I THOUGHT I LOCKED THE DOOR.
- SO, I SEE YOU GOT
A NEWSPAPER SUBSCRIPTION.
- YEAH, SO?
- I BET YOU JUST LOOK AT THE TV
SCHEDULES AND THE SPORTS.
I'M RIGHT, AREN'T I?
- SHUT UP.
SO TONIGHT I, UH, WENT TO THE
AMUSEMENT PARK WITH ASAHINA.
- COOL.
- WHEN I FINALLY WORKED
UP THE NERVE
TO ASK HER TO GO WITH ME,
YOU KNOW WHAT SHE SAID?
- NO, WHAT?
- "I CAN GO WITH YOU
IF YOU WANT."
PLEASE...
WHY DIDN'T SHE JUST
SAY SHE WANTED TO GO
INSTEAD OF BEING SO DIFFICULT?
WHEN WE GOT THERE,
IT STARTED RAINING
AND SHE ACTED LIKE I CAUSED
THE PARADE TO BE CANCELED.
LIKE I HAVE CONTROL OF THE RAIN.
SO, THEN SHE DECIDED SHE'D HAD
ENOUGH AND WANTED TO GO HOME,
BUT ONLY AFTER WE RODE
AN INDOOR ROLLER COASTER.
I THOUGHT, "WHAT'S THE POINT?
LET'S JUST LEAVE NOW."
THEN AFTER THE ROLLER
COASTER, SHE'S LIKE,
"LET'S GO RIDE MORE
RIDES, YAMATO!"
WHATEVER.
OH, AND THEN SHE
MADE ME FOLLOW HER
ALL OVER THE PLACE SHOPPING.
JUST LIKE SHE ALWAYS DOES.
AND WHEN THE RAIN
FINALLY STOPPED,
SHE WANTED TO GO SEE THE PARADE.
WHAT'S SO GREAT
ABOUT PARADES, ANYWAY?
JUST A BUNCH OF UGLY COSTUMES
AND GAUDY FLOATS.
BUT SHE SAID IT WAS BEAUTIFUL.
( sobbing )
- WELL, I GOTTA GO.
I'LL CALL YOU LATER.
OH, YEAH. I, UH, GOT THESE
AT THE TRAIN STATION.
YOU CAN HAVE 'EM.
LATER, MAN. DON'T FORGET
TO LOCK THE DOOR.
( door opens and closes )
- I DON'T NEED THESE.
( sobbing ) I DON'T NEED 'EM,
YOU IDIOT.
- WELL, HANG IN THERE.
- Man on television:
UH-OH. LOOKS LIKE SHE'S IN
A BIT OF TROUBLE NOW.
OH, BUT SHE'S GONNA TRY IT.
HERE SHE GOES.
I DIDN'T THINK SHE WAS
ACTUALLY GONNA MAKE IT, FOLKS.
YES, THERE SHE GOES.
- ( crying )
I CAN'T STOP. I CAN'T.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT DID I DO WRONG?
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ABOVE ♪
♪ NOW IS ALL WE HAVE ♪
♪ WITH A LITTLE FEELING
AND A LOT OF LOVE ♪
♪ WE TURN UP THE HEAT AND RUN ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- ♪ ALL MY LIFE HERE ON THE
GROUND ABOUT TO RUN AND NOW ♪
♪ I FIND I MUST
ASK MYSELF WHY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE SOMETHING IS STIRRING ♪
♪ I FEEL IT WHISPERING IN ME ♪
♪ SOME DAYS I WAKE UP ♪
♪ BUT MY HEART'S
STILL SLEEPING ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME
TO RUN AND TRY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME TO FLY ♪
♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ON HIGH ♪
♪ WITH OUR GOAL IN SIGHT ♪
♪ WE WILL RUN
WITH ALL OUR MIGHT ♪
♪ TOMORROW AND TODAY
WILL NEVER EVER PASS US BY ♪
♪ WE WILL NOT STOP NOW ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR HEART ALIVE
AND YOUR DREAM SURVIVES ♪
♪ AND YOU CROSS
THE FINISH LINE ♪
♪ LET IT GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- Yasunobu: WHAT? YOU'RE
JOINING THE TRACK TEAM?
- Yamato: THAT'S RIGHT. I NEED
TO GET CLOSER TO ASAHINA,
AND I FIGURED,
THIS IS MY LAST CHANCE.
I HAVE TO MAKE IT WORK.
I CAN'T STAND TO LOSE HER.
- Yasunobu: I HOPE YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
I DON'T WANNA SEE YOU
GET HURT AGAIN.