- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- HERE'S YOUR TEA, MIHO.
- THANKS. SMELLS GREAT.
- I WONDER HOW YAMATO'S
DOING LATELY.
I'M PRETTY SURE I HEARD HIM SAY
THAT TODAY WAS HIS SECOND MEET.
- I DON'T KNOW. IF IT IS, I HOPE
HE DOESN'T DO ANYTHING STUPID
TO EMBARRASS HIMSELF OUT THERE.
RIGHT, GORRO?
- ( purring )
- BUT I'M SURE SUZUKA
IS GONNA BE AWESOME.
I REALLY WISH THAT
I COULD SEE IT.
YOU KNOW, SHE WON THIRD PLACE
AT THE INTER-HIGH COMPETITION
LAST TIME!
WOULDN'T IT BE NEAT IF SHE SET
A NEW HIGH JUMP RECORD?
- YES, IT WOULD.
SHE'S VERY TALENTED.
I'M SURE SHE'LL DO A GREAT JOB.
- ( grunting )
- ASAHINA...
I CAN'T DECIDE IF I SHOULD
CONFESS TO HER OR NOT.
- I'M SORRY.
- I'VE ALREADY BEEN
REJECTED ONCE.
I'M SURE IT WOULD HURT EVEN MORE
THE SECOND TIME.
I DON'T THINK I COULD
HANDLE THAT AGAIN.
BESIDES, I HAVEN'T CHANGED
AT ALL SINCE THEN.
I HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING
TO MAKE HER LIKE ME.
SO IF I CONFESS TO HER NOW
I'M SURE SHE'LL JUST
TELL ME THE SAME THING.
SHE SAID SHE WOULDN'T
GO OUT WITH ME
BECAUSE WE BARELY
KNEW EACH OTHER,
BUT I KNOW WHAT
THE REAL REASON IS.
- Suzune: HE WAS A YEAR AHEAD
OF SUZUKA AT THEIR JUNIOR HIGH,
AND HE WAS THE STAR
OF THE TRACK TEAM.
SUZUKA ADMIRED HIM A GREAT DEAL.
- IT'S POINTLESS.
ASAHINA DOESN'T EVEN
LOOK AT ME LIKE THAT.
SHE'S STILL...
STILL...
- STALKING SUZUKA AGAIN,
I SEE.
CREEPY.
I THOUGHT YOU HAD A RACE
COMING UP SOON.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE
GETTING READY FOR THAT?
- I STILL HAVE SOME TIME LEFT.
NOT THAT IT'S ANY OF YOUR
BUSINESS. WHY ARE YOU HERE?
- DUH. CHECKIN' OUT
THE GIRLS A'COURSE.
I'M GONNA GIVE HER
A SEVEN AND A HALF
BUT SHE'S ABOUT A FIVE,
SIX AT THE MOST.
- YOU SEEM LIKE YOU'RE HAVING
A GOOD TIME.
- OH, YEAH.
I THINK MY NEW GOAL'S
GONNA BE TO WIN THE HEART
OF EVERY CUTE GIRL IN THE WORLD.
- WHAT FOR?
- WHAT ABOUT YOU? WHAT ARE YOU
DOIN' THIS TRACK AND FIELD FOR?
I MEAN, I KNOW HOW EVERYONE ELSE
FEELS ABOUT YOU DOING IT.
YOU'RE FAST, AND THEY PICKED YOU
TO BE ON THE RELAY TEAM
BUT STILL IT DOESN'T SEEM
LIKE IT'S REALLY YOU.
- NO, I ENJOY IT. REALLY.
- CUT IT OUT, YAMATO.
YOU KNOW YOU CAN'T FOOL ME.
I KNOW YOU TRIED TO HIDE IT,
BUT YOU ONLY JOINED THE TEAM
SO YOU COULD BE CLOSER
TO SUZUKA.
SO TELL ME, HOW ARE THINGS
GOIN' IN THAT DEPARTMENT?
- YOU'RE RIDICULOUS!
I'M COMPLETELY OVER ASAHINA!
OKAY, I STILL LIKE HER.
- DUH.
- BUT THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO ABOUT IT NOW.
- WHY? ARE YOU AFRAID
OF BEING REJECTED AGAIN?
- WELL, NOT EXACTLY.
- THERE YOU ARE.
I'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR YOU.
- OH, SORRY, SEMPAI.
- IT'S ALMOST TIME. YOU SHOULD
START WARMING UP, YOU KNOW.
- RIGHT. THANK YOU.
- HEY, I ALMOST FORGOT.
THIS is YOUR FIRST COMPETITION
AS CAPTAIN, ISN'T IT?
CONGRATULATIONS, MAN.
THAT'S AWESOME.
- YEAH, BUT IT STILL
FEELS A LITTLE WEIRD
BEING CALLED A CAPTAIN.
- WELL, IT FEELS WEIRD
CALLING YOU A CAPTAIN.
I DON'T THINK YOU REALLY
LOOK LIKE ONE.
- WOW. YOU REALLY DON'T
HOLD BACK, DO YOU?
I AGREE WITH YOU THOUGH.
I PROBABLY WASN'T THE BEST
CHOICE FOR CAPTAIN THIS SEASON.
IT SHOULD'VE BEEN
KAZUKI TSUDA.
- TSUDA?
- I GUESS THE TWO OF
YOU WOULDN'T KNOW
WHO HE WAS THOUGH, WOULD YOU?
HE WAS A PRETTY AMAZING GUY.
ASAHINA AND I WENT TO THE SAME
JUNIOR HIGH THAT HE DID.
BUT HE PASSED AWAY IN A TRAGIC
CAR ACCIDENT TWO YEARS AGO.
HE AND ASAHINA ALWAYS FOUGHT.
HE WAS KIND OF COCKY TOO.
EVEN THOUGH HE WAS A PRETTY
IRRESPONSIBLE GUY,
NO ONE WAS MORE DEDICATED
TO TRACK AND FIELD THAN HE WAS.
HE HAD QUITE A PROMISING FUTURE
AHEAD OF HIM.
IN HIS LAST HUNDRED-METER RUN,
HE SET AN ALL-TIME RECORD AS
THE FASTEST RUNNER IN JAPAN.
- WOW. SOUNDS LIKE
HE WAS REALLY TALENTED.
- HE WAS.
I THINK HE PROBABLY
INSPIRED ASAHINA AND ME
MORE THAN WE REALIZED.
- SO IF THAT'S TRUE,
THAT MAKES ME WONDER IF SUZUKA
EVER HAD A THING FOR THIS GUY.
HMM?
- I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETIMES I THINK
SHE MAY HAVE.
I MEAN, SHE STILL
MAKES SPECIAL TRIPS
TO VISIT HIS GRAVESITE EVEN NOW.
SOMETIMES I WONDER IF
SHE'S STILL HAVING A HARD TIME
GETTING OVER KAZUKI
AND DEALING WITH HIS DEATH.
ALL RIGHT. WELL, I THINK
I BETTER GET GOING, AKITSUKI.
DON'T BE LATE
FOR FINAL CALL, OKAY?
- I WON'T.
- I GET IT.
YOU DON'T WANNA
CONFESS TO SUZUKA
BECAUSE YOU'RE AFRAID
OF REJECTION.
YOU THINK SHE'LL COMPARE YOU TO
TSUDA AND THAT SCARES YOU.
- SHUT UP.
- MAKES SENSE THOUGH.
HE WAS RELIABLE AND ACTUALLY
CARED ABOUT TRACK AND FIELD.
NOT ONLY THAT, BUT THE FASTEST
RUNNER IN JAPAN? THAT'S AWESOME!
MAN, IT'S GOTTA BE TOUGH KNOWING
YOU'LL NEVER LIVE UP TO THAT.
- SHUT UP.
( screaming )
SHUT UP!
- WHAT WAS THAT?
- IT LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE'S
SCREAMING OVER THERE.
- THAT SOUNDS REALLY BAD.
I HOPE HE'S OKAY.
- SEE IF YOU CAN RECOGNIZE
HIS SCHOOL JERSEY.
- IS THAT YAMATO?
WHAT'S HE DOING UP THERE?
THIS IS SO EMBARRASSING.
- DUDE, WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
CHILL OUT.
- I ALREADY KNOW ALL OF THAT!
I KNOW ASAHINA STILL HAS
FEELINGS FOR TSUDA,
AND I KNOW THAT I'LL NEVER BE
AS GOOD AS HIM.
BUT I HAVE GOT TO DO SOMETHING.
I JUST DON'T KNOW WHAT YET.
- COME ON, YAMATO. I KNOW YOU'VE
GOT SOME GOOD IDEAS UP THERE.
- HMM.
I'M NOT GOING TO HOLD BACK
ANYMORE.
I'M GONNA BE THE NUMBER ONE
SPRINTER IN JAPAN!
JUST YOU WAIT!
- SO, WHAT EXACTLY
ARE YOU SAYING?
ARE YOU FEELIN' ALL RIGHT, MAN?
- SHUT UP!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
COME OVER ME,
BUT I'M DETERMINED
THIS TIME!
- AKITSUKI!
WHERE'RE YOUR SPIKES?
- HOLD STILL.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- YOU DIDN'T FORGET TO WEAR
YOUR UNIFORM AGAIN, DID YA?
- OH, COME ON.
HE ISN'T A CHILD, SEMPAI.
- I'M AWARE OF THAT,
BUT HE'S DONE IT BEFORE.
- AKITSUKI, JUST DO THE BEST
YOU CAN, OKAY?
- YOU'RE THE ACE ON OUR TEAM,
AND WE'RE COUNTIN' ON YA,
SO YOU BETTER NOT FORGET IT!
- THIS IS THE FIRST TIME
YOU'VE SAID THAT TO ME.
- ALL RIGHT, GO GIVE 'EM HELL!
- AKITSUKI, WAIT.
THERE ARE ONLY ABOUT SEVEN OR
EIGHT PEOPLE IN THIS COMPETITION
WHO CAN MAKE THAT ELEVEN SECOND
MARK, SO JUST MAKE SURE THAT...
- YEAH, I KNOW!
- ALL RIGHT THEN. LOOKS LIKE
WE'RE IN PRETTY GOOD SHAPE.
- I SAW YOU ON THE HILL.
WOULD YOU STOP ACTING SO WEIRD?
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
- I WAS JUST TRYING TO WARM UP.
- OH. WELL, DON'T
OVERDO IT, 'KAY?
- I'M NOT GOING TO FAIL.
I CAN'T!
I HAVE TO WIN,
NO MATTER WHAT IT TAKES!
- ( sighs )
THIS IS SO DUMB.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU LOOK GRUMPY. HERE.
MAYBE YOU NEED
SOME MORE CALCIUM.
- MY DIET'S JUST FINE,
THANK YOU.
IT'S ABOUT AKITSUKI AND SUZUKA.
THEY SEEM TO HAVE MADE UP.
- OH, WELL, I KINDA THOUGHT
THAT WAS A GOOD THING.
BUT MAYBE
YOU'RE A LITTLE JEALOUS?
- NO! THAT'S NOT IT AT ALL.
I'M JUST ANNOYED WITH
THE WHOLE SITUATION.
I MEAN, AKITSUKI'S UPSET
BECAUSE SUZUKA HATES HIM,
SO I TRY TO BE THERE
FOR HIM, YOU KNOW?
I JUST FEEL SO STUPID.
YOU KNOW, I PUT SO MUCH ENERGY
INTO TRYING TO HELP
AND IT DOESN'T EVEN MATTER.
I'M JUST TIRED OF IT.
- WELL, YOU WERE BEIN'
A GOOD FRIEND.
THERE WAS JUST NOTHIN'
YOU COULD'VE DONE.
THAT'S WHY I SAID
YOU SHOULD LEAVE THEM ALONE
- OH, SHUT UP!
WHAT IN THE WORLD ARE YOU
DOING HERE ANYWAY, HATTORI?
- WHAT CAN I SAY?
I'M YAMATO'S BIGGEST FAN.
I LOVE WATCHING HIM RUN!
- HUH?
- I ALWAYS LEAVE THOROUGHLY
ENTERTAINED AND EVEN INSPIRED.
THAT'S IMPORTANT.
I WONDER WHAT
HE'LL DO THIS TIME.
I'M SURE WE'RE ALL IN
FOR A SURPRISE.
- Man 1: HEY, ISN'T THAT
ARIMA OVER THERE?
- Man 2: YEAH, I THINK IT IS.
- Yamato: ARIMA EMERSON.
THAT'S RIGHT. I FORGOT
HE'S IN THIS DISTRICT TOO.
- HIS BEST TIME FOR THE HUNDRED
METERS IS 10.46 SECONDS.
- YOU'RE ANNOYING ME, TUCK YOUR
TAIL BETWEEN YOUR LEGS
AND GET OUTTA HERE.
- I HAVE TO BEAT HIM IN ORDER
TO BECOME NUMBER ONE IN JAPAN.
AND I'M NOT SURE I CAN DO THAT.
- HEY, AKITSUKI!
GO GET 'EM!
- ALL RIGHT.
I GUESS IT'S THE MOMENT
WE'VE ALL BEEN WAITING FOR.
MAN, HE SURE LOOKS
NERVOUS THOUGH.
- OH, GREAT. I WONDER
IF HE FEELS NERVOUS.
- HMM.
- Man: ON YOUR MARKS.
- WHAT IF I LOSE?
I'VE PRACTICED FOR TWO MONTHS
WITHOUT STOPPING.
WHAT IF IT'S NOT ENOUGH?
I'LL CONFESS TO HER ANYWAY
AND SHE'LL PROBABLY REJECT ME.
I HAVE TO WIN!
NO MATTER WHAT THE OUTCOME.
I STILL WANNA BE WITH ASAHINA.
- Man: GET SET.
- THIS IS RIDICULOUS!
I CAN'T THINK ABOUT THAT
RIGHT NOW.
ALL I CAN DO NOW
IS WIN THIS RACE!
- ( gunshot )
HE'S OFF TO A GOOD START.
- NUMBER 136. 10.81 SECONDS.
- ( grunts ) YES!
- WOW. HE DIDN'T MESS UP
THIS TIME.
- 10.81 SECONDS.
- HMM. HE CAN RUN FASTER
THAN TSUDA.
I'LL GIVE HIM THAT.
- Yamato: 10.81 SECONDS!
I BEAT MY RECORD!
I CAME IN FIRST PLACE!
- UM, WELL...
- WHAT?
- Sasaki: YEAH, GOOD JOB.
IF YOU CAN DO THAT IN RELAY,
THAT'D BE GREAT.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
WHAT?
WAS I RUNNING TOO SLOW?
- WE ALREADY KNOW
YOU CAN RUN FAST, YAMATO.
REMEMBER WHAT I TOLD YOU?
DON'T OVERDO IT.
DO YOU KNOW WHY I SAID THAT?
YOU REALLY NEED TO PACE
YOURSELF RIGHT NOW.
STOP FOCUSING ON RUNNING FAST
AND THINK ABOUT
HOW YOU'RE RUNNING.
- I THINK I GET IT.
- SEMPAI TOLD YOU ONLY
A FEW CAN RUN THIS RACE
IN UNDER ELEVEN SECONDS.
BUT YOU NEED TO HOLD THAT SCORE
FOR THE LATTER PORTIONS AS WELL.
AND YOU NEED
YOUR STRENGTH FOR THE RELAY.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- ONLY TWENTY FOUR MAKE IT
TO THE SEMIS.
YOU CAN'T WEAR
YOURSELF OUT.
IF YOU PACE YOURSELF, YOU CAN
MAKE IT PAST THE PRELIMINARIES.
- I WORKED REALLY HARD THOUGH.
- YEAH, WE KNOW YOU DID!
IT WAS REALLY IMPRESSIVE.
GOOD JOB, AKITSUKI!
- ( crowd cheering )
- Kinugasa: THAT ARIMA'S GOOD,
BUT HE SLOWS DOWN
DURING THE SECOND HALF.
- Man: FIRST PLACE NUMBER 91!
11.9 SECONDS!
- ARIMA'S BEST TIME IS
10.46 SECONDS.
AND MINE WAS...
MINE WAS 10.81.
AND I JUST DID THAT TODAY.
THAT'S A DIFFERENCE
OF .35 SECONDS.
IT WON'T BE
EASY TO CATCH UP.
WE PROBABLY WON'T BE IN THE SAME
GROUP AT THE SEMIFINALS.
BUT IN THE FINALS, I'M SURE
I'LL HAVE TO COMPETE WITH HIM.
- UH. HI, AKITSUKI!
UH, DO YOU... DO YOU WANT
SOMETHING TO DRINK?
NEVER MIND. I GUESS YOU
ALREADY HAVE SOMETHING.
SORRY, I WASN'T
PAYING ATTENTION.
- IT'S COOL.
ARE YOU DOING OKAY?
- OH, YEAH, SURE.
I'M DOING JUST GREAT!
OKAY, GOOD LUCK!
I'LL SEE YOU LATER!
WHEN I TALK TO AKITSUKI NOW,
IT FEELS LIKE WE'RE STRANGERS.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE WE WERE SO
CLOSE JUST A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
- UH, WHAT DOES
THAT MEAN, EXACTLY?
- YOU SEE, WE GO BY TIME IN THE
HUNDRED METER FINALS.
SO THAT JUST MEANS YOU DON'T
NEED TO RUN THIS ONE.
- UH.
- THE TOP EIGHT RUNNERS IN THE
SEMIFINALS ARE ALL SET.
THEY'RE QUALIFIED FOR THE
METROPOLITAN MEET.
THAT MEANS THEY'LL JUST BE
RANKED BASED ON THEIR TIMES
AND THAT'LL BE IT
FOR THAT COMPETITION.
- SO BASICALLY WHAT WE'RE SAYING
IS THAT YOU MAY AS WELL CONSIDER
THE SEMIFINALS TO BE THE FINALS.
- SO THAT MEANS I WON'T BE
COMPETING WITH ARIMA THIS TIME.
- WELL, THIS MUST BE A SHOCK.
I BET YOU THOUGHT YOU'D
BE RUNNING IN THE FINALS,
HUH, AKITSUKI?
- WELL, YEAH.
- MAN, YOU NEED TO LEARN
HOW THESE THINGS ARE RUN FIRST.
LET'S GO, AKITSUKI!
- UH, OKAY!
- THAT SASAKI IS STILL AS
DIFFICULT AS EVER, ISN'T HE?
- YEAH, HE'S A LITTLE INTENSE,
AND HE HAS NO
PATIENCE FOR PEOPLE
WHO AREN'T AS SERIOUS ABOUT
TRACK AND FIELD AS HE IS.
I THINK THAT'S WHY HE'S SO HARD
ON AKITSUKI LATELY.
'CAUSE HE JUST CAN'T
FIGURE HIM OUT.
HE DOESN'T KNOW HOW BADLY
AKITSUKI WANTS THIS.
- IT'S OKAY.
I DON'T HAVE TO COMPETE
AGAINST ARIMA IN THIS RACE.
THEY SAID THAT WE'RE JUST
COMPETING BASED ON TIMES.
10.48 SECONDS.
IT'S GOING TO BE IMPOSSIBLE FOR
ME TO BEAT THAT TIME RIGHT NOW.
- HEY! YOU READY, MAN?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
DON'T TELL ME
YOU'RE GETTING NERVOUS.
- I'M SORRY, SEMPAI,
I AM A LITTLE NERVOUS.
- DUDE, YOU'VE GOTTA BE
KIDDING ME.
YOU'VE GOT WEAK KNEES ALREADY?
- NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEAN.
I'M JUST AFRAID I MAY NOT HAVE
ANY ENERGY FOR THE RELAY RACE.
- OH GREAT, AKITSUKI.
THIS IS EXACTLY
WHY I DIDN'T WANT YOU ON
THE TEAM IN THE FIRST PLACE.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK. IF YOU'RE GOING
TO WIMP OUT ON THE RELAY,
AT LEAST FINISH FIRST
IN THE HUNDRED METER.
AND BEAT EMERSON.
- THAT I CAN DO.
- DON'T BLOW THE RACE
WITH A SLOW START.
- I WON'T.
I HAVE TO BEAT HIM.
I HAVE TO RUN AT LEAST .1
SECONDS FASTER THAN ARIMA.
I'LL BECOME THE TOP SPRINTER
IN JAPAN IN FRONT OF ASAHINA!
- I GUESS THE SEMIFINALS
HAVE ALREADY STARTED.
- ( panting )
- SUZUKA!
( panting )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT HERE?
YOU'VE MISSED IT!
AKITSUKI'S ALREADY
FINISHED RUNNING!
- SO, HOW'D HE DO?
- HE FINISHED IN 10.68 SECONDS
AND IS CURRENTLY IN THE LEAD!
ON TOP OF THAT,
HE BROKE ARIMA'S RECORD
FROM THE INTER-HIGH COMPETITION
AND IS RANKED NUMBER ONE
FOR THE ENTIRE YEAR!
- I SEE.
- HE'S AMAZING, SUZUKA! I JUST
KNEW AKITSUKI WAS GOING TO BE
THE ONE TO ACCOMPLISH
SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
- WHY ARE YOU OUT HERE
ACTING ALL DEPRESSED?
SHOULDN'T YOU BE CELEBRATING?
YOU'VE BEEN NAMED NUMBER
ONE FOR THE ENTIRE YEAR.
- I'M NOT ANYMORE.
LOOK.
- SECOND PLACE?
- MY TIME WAS 10.68.
EMERSON'S WAS 10.50.
I DON'T KNOW HOW THAT BASTARD
PULLED AWAY FROM ME SO EASILY.
- MAYBE HE JUST...
WELL, YOU DID PLACE SECOND,
YOU KNOW.
DON'T FORGET YOU STILL QUALIFIED
FOR THE METROPOLITAN MEET.
- SECOND OR THIRD PLACE
MEANS NOTHING TO ME!
I JUST...
I WANT TO WIN FIRST PLACE!
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD TELL ME
WHAT'S WRONG WITH MY RUNNING?
I THINK MY START IS LOOKING A
LOT BETTER THAN IT WAS BEFORE.
AND I DON'T FEEL LIKE MY FORM IS
TOO BAD WHEN I'M AT TOP SPEED.
IT'S JUST IN THOSE LAST TWENTY
METERS THAT I FEEL MYSELF
STARTING TO SLOW DOWN, AND I
HAVE NO IDEA HOW TO FIX THAT.
- UM, ACTUALLY I DON'T THINK
I CAN HELP YOU
WITH THOSE TECHNICAL AREAS.
- I'M SORRY.
- I SEE.
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE A HIGH-JUMPER,
SO NEVER MIND.
SO I'LL JUST GET HELP
FROM KINUGASA SENPAI.
SORRY FOR WASTING
YOUR TIME WITH THIS.
- IT'S OKAY.
- SEE YA!
- WHAT'S GOING ON? WHY IS HE
SO SERIOUS ALL OF A SUDDEN?
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WHEN I TURN AROUND ♪
♪ YOU'RE RIGHT THERE
NEXT TO ME ♪
♪ ON YOUR FACE A SMILE
SO COMFORTING AND FAMILIAR ♪
♪ THE CLOSER YOU BECAME
THE LESS THAT I COULD SEE ♪
♪ AND NOW I'M WONDERING
SO LOST AND ALL ALONE ♪
♪ PEOPLE CHANGE
A LITTLE AT A TIME ♪
♪ AND NOW I KNOW I'M CHANGING ♪
♪ WHEN I CALL YOUR NAME
SHOUT IT OUT INTO THE SKY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN I WILL FIND
THE LOVE I KEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'RE WITH ME
AND YOU TAKE MY HAND ♪
♪ SOMEHOW EVERYTHING
SEEMS TO WORK ITSELF OUT RIGHT ♪
♪ WHEN I SEE YOUR EYES
STARING BACK AT MINE ♪
♪ THERE INSIDE I FIND
A LOVE THAT NEVER DIES ♪
♪ TOGETHER I KNOW
WE'LL FIND A WAY ♪
♪ JUST YOU AND I ♪
- Yamato: YOU'RE
DOING SELF-TRAINING TOO?
COOL! GOOD LUCK, ASAHINA!
- DO YOU REALLY THINK YOU HAVE
TIME TO CHEER PEOPLE UP?
IF YOU CHANGE YOUR RUNNING STYLE
THAT QUICKLY
YOU'RE GONNA RETURN
TO YOUR OLD HABITS
WITHOUT EVEN REALIZING IT!
- Yamato: I DON'T GET IT!
WHAT DID I DO TO HER?