- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- I NEVER USED TO
THINK OF HONOKA
AS ANY MORE THAN JUST A FRIEND.
BUT THE GIRL WHO IS STANDING
IN FRONT OF ME RIGHT NOW
IS DEFINITELY, WITHOUT A
DOUBT, MORE BEAUTIFUL
THAN ANYONE ELSE I CAN THINK OF.
- Honoka: IS THIS OKAY?
I MEAN, I KNOW WE'RE NOT...
YOU KNOW.
- Yamato: BUT WE SHOULD!
BE MY GIRLFRIEND!
WOW. THAT WAS PROBABLY
TOO FORWARD, HUH? I'M SORRY.
- Honoka: NO. IT WAS NICE.
YOU'VE MADE ME SO HAPPY.
FINALLY, HE FEELS THE SAME WAY.
- WELL GOOD. I'M GLAD.
- YIKES!
OH, MY GOSH! DID I
REALLY JUST SEE THAT?
- THIS IS SO RELAXING!
- THIS PLACE IS SO WARM.
- IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
- IT'S SO NICE NOT TO FEEL
WORN OUT AFTER PRACTICE.
- YEAH, REALLY.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
WOULD IT HELP OR JUST
MAKE THINGS WORSE
IF I TELL HER WHAT I SAW?
- I'M HAVING SUCH A WONDERFUL
TIME! AREN'T YOU?
AND MY SKIN FEELS SO SMOOTH!
I LOVE HOT SPRINGS.
- SUZUKA, CAN WE TALK?
- ALRIGHT! AN OPEN-AIR BATH!
- ( screams happily )
- ( water splashes )
- UGH! SERIOUSLY. GROW UP.
- MY GOODNESS, HE SEEMS HAPPIER.
- BUT STILL, THAT DOESN'T
GIVE HIM THE RIGHT
TO BE SO OBNOXIOUS
WHILE TAKING A BATH.
- THIS IS SO HARD.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
MAYBE I SHOULDN'T TELL HER.
AAH! THIS IS SO FRUSTRATING!
- ( insects chirping )
- HEY.
YOU SEEM UNUSUALLY
RELAXED THIS MORNING.
- YEAH. THE SENIORS ARE GOING
BACK HOME TODAY.
INTER-HIGH IS FINALLY OVER.
EVEN THOUGH WE STILL
HAVE TRAINING.
BUT THAT DOESN'T START
'TIL THIS AFTERNOON, SO...
WAIT! WHAT ARE YOU
STILL DOING HERE?
- I THOUGHT YOU WERE LEAVING.
- I CANNOT RETURN
A FAILURE. I NEED TO GET AT
LEAST ONE GIRL'S NUMBER.
- I SEE.
- Suzuka: YAMATO!
OH GOOD. HERE YOU ARE. I WANNA
GO SHOPPING. COME ON.
DON'T YOU WANT SOME SOUVENIRS?
- YOU'RE FREE, RIGHT?
IT'LL BE GOOD FOR YA.
- UH, I'M SORRY. I'M ACTUALLY
KINDA TIRED. I THINK I'LL PASS.
- DON'T BE SUCH A JERK! IT'S
NOT GONNA TAKE THAT LONG!
- I'M SORRY.
- OKAY FINE! I'LL JUST
GO WITH MIKI.
- WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
YOU OKAY?
- I'M FINE.
- REALLY? ALRIGHT,
NEVER MIND THEN.
SO, IS THERE ANYTHING
YOU WANNA TELL ME?
- NO, AS A MATTER OF FACT,
THERE'S NOT, OKAY?
- OKAY.
- SUZUKA, WAIT UP!
AREN'T YOU BROKE, YET?
- JUST ONE MORE STORE.
- WHAT? ARE YOU SERIOUS?
I CAN UNDERSTAND WANTING TO GET
MOMIJI BEAN JAM CAKES.
BUT WHY PUYOMAN?
- IT'S A HIROSHIMA SPECIALTY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU
DON'T KNOW THAT.
- SORRY, I CAN'T KEEP UP. THIS
IS NEVER GONNA END, IS IT?
YOU'RE REALLY GONNA BUY MORE?
- HEY, WHADDAYA THINK?
THE SHIRT.
DON'T YOU THINK IT'S SOMETHING
YAMATO WOULD WEAR?
OH, BUT IT'S A MEDIUM.
THAT FIGURES. HIS SHOULDERS ARE
SURPRISINGLY WIDER THAN THIS.
- SUZUKA...
- I'M NOT GONNA BUY IT FOR HIM
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK!
THAT CREEP DIDN'T EVEN
WANNA COME WITH ME.
WHY SHOULD I DO ANYTHING
NICE FOR HIM?
- NO, NO, IT'S NOT THAT.
- WELL, WHAT THEN?
- WELL, AKITSUKI
AND SAKURAI ARE
SEEING EACH OTHER.
I OVERHEARD THEM TALKING
YESTERDAY BY THE POND.
- THAT'S GREAT.
- ( wind howling )
- ( panting )
- GOOD WORK TODAY, AKITSUKI!
- OH, THANK YOU!
- THANKS!
- HEY! CAN I GET A TOWEL PLEASE?
- ABSOLUTELY!
- IT'S LATE. I'M SORRY
FOR GETTING YOU OUT.
YOU MUST BE REALLY
TIRED FROM PRACTICE.
- NO, IT'S OKAY. I'M
PRETTY USED TO IT.
- THAT'S COOL.
- YEAH.
- I JUST... I REALLY WANTED SOME
TIME ALONE WITH YOU TONIGHT.
LOOK, THE MOON.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
- YEAH, IT IS.
- AKITSUKI, CAN I
TELL YOU SOMETHING?
SINCE WE'RE ALREADY
SEEING EACH OTHER,
I GUESS IT'S OKAY TO SAY THIS.
REMEMBER WHEN WE MET?
AFTER YOU HELPED
ME FIX THAT BELL,
I WOULD WAIT FOR YOU
TO RETURN EVERY YEAR,
AND THEN I WOULD SECRETLY
WATCH YOU UNTIL YOU LEFT.
I KNOW IT SOUNDS KIND OF WEIRD,
BUT I ALWAYS DREAMT ABOUT
HOW GREAT IT WOULD BE
IF THE TWO OF US COULD
TALK TOGETHER LIKE THIS.
SO WHEN I FOUND OUT YOU WERE
TAKING THE SCHOOL ENTRANCE EXAM,
I WAS SO SURPRISED.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT!
WHEN WE ENDED UP
IN THE SAME CLASS,
I'D BEEN THINKING ABOUT
YOU FOR SO LONG
THAT I JUST TALKED TO YOU
LIKE YOU KNEW ME, TOO.
- OH. THAT MAKES SENSE NOW.
YEAH, I DIDN'T RECOGNIZE YOU
UNTIL YOU MENTIONED THE SHRINE.
- I BET YOU THOUGHT I
WAS KIND OF WEIRD, HUH?
- WELL, KIND OF.
- I KNEW IT.
- WHAT? NO! I WAS JUST
KIDDING! IT WAS A JOKE!
- THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE.
I ONLY JOINED THE TRACK
TEAM BECAUSE YOU JOINED.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- YEAH I WANTED TO BE AROUND
YOU AS MUCH AS I COULD.
BECAUSE...
I REALLY LIKED YOU.
OH AKITSUKI, I WISH MOMENTS LIKE
THESE COULD GO ON FOREVER!
- REALLY? YOU DO? I FEEL
THE SAME WAY, ACTUALLY.
- I'M GLAD.
- IT WOULD BE GREAT IF THIS
FEELING COULD LAST FOREVER.
- ( birds chirping )
- YOU'RE STILL HERE, HATTORI?
- YEAH, I GUESS I AM.
IS THAT A PROBLEM?
- NO, IT'S NOT A PROBLEM,
IT'S JUST WEIRD...
I MEAN YOU'RE NOT
EVEN IN TRACK.
- WHATEVER. WHAT DO YOU CARE?
YAMATO SEEMS TO BE
DOING WELL FOR HIMSELF.
I SURE WISH I COULD
SCORE LIKE THAT.
I GUESS HE'S REALLY HITTING
IT OFF WITH SAKURAI.
GOOD FOR HIM.
- YOU KNEW ABOUT THAT?
- YEAH, IT'S WEIRD.
YOU'D THINK WE WERE
FRIENDS OR SOMETHING.
- THEN WHY DIDN'T YOU
STOP HIM, SMART ASS?
DON'T YOU THINK
HE'S BEING A JERK?
ALL THIS TIME HE'S BEEN TALKING
ABOUT HOW MUCH HE LIKES SUZUKA
AND NOW HE'S DATING SAKURAI
RANDOMLY? THAT'S STUPID.
- IT HAPPENS.
PEOPLE CHANGE THEIR MINDS.
YOU KNOW THAT.
- WHAT? I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU'RE OKAY WITH IT.
HE'S NOT EVEN THINKING ABOUT
HOW SUZUKA MIGHT FEEL.
- WHAT ABOUT THEM?
WHAT ABOUT HOW SAKURAI
AND YAMATO FEEL, HUH?
FROM WHAT I'VE HEARD,
SAKURAI'S LIKED YAMATO
FOR A VERY LONG TIME.
DON'T YOU THINK SHE'D BE A
LITTLE UPSET IF THEY SPLIT UP?
- I DIDN'T THINK ABOUT THAT.
- I'VE LEARNED THAT THERE AREN'T
ANY RIGHT OR WRONG ANSWERS
WHEN IT COMES TO WHO YOU LOVE.
IF WE'RE NOT INVOLVED, I THINK
WE SHOULD JUST LET IT ALONE.
- BUT, HEY!
- ( upbeat music playing )
- SET...
ALRIGHT! THAT'S
ALL FOR TODAY!
- All: GO TEAM!
- THIS IS CRAZY! WHY AM I THE
ONLY ONE WITH A SPECIAL PROGRAM?
- ( groans )
- MAN THIS REALLY SUCKS!
PLEASE LET ME FINISH EARLY
SO THAT I CAN GO HOME!
- HEY, SLACKER.
- ASAHINA...
- GREAT JOB. YOUR
FORM'S GOTTEN LAZY.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA IMPROVE
YOUR TIME LIKE THAT, YOU KNOW.
- YEAH. I KNOW.
- OH, REALLY?
IT DOESN'T MATTER HOW
MANY TIMES I TELL YOU.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA DO IT.
YOU REALLY NEED TO SHAPE UP.
- I KNOW I DO, OKAY!
- HEY.
- NOW WHAT? AM I SITTING WRONG?
- NO. IT'S NOT THAT. IS IT TRUE
THAT YOU'RE DATING HONOKA?
- OH, WELL, I...
YEAH. WE'RE SEEING EACH OTHER.
- WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
- HUH?
- YEAH, I NEVER THOUGHT YOU'D
ACTUALLY HAVE A GIRLFRIEND,
SO I'M A LITTLE SURPRISED.
BUT GOOD FOR YOU. JUST
DON'T SCREW IT UP, OKAY?
- YEAH, OKAY.
- SO HAVE YOU DONE IT, YET?
STRETCHING. WHAT DID
YOU THINK I MEANT?
I'LL PUSH FOR YOU.
- OKAY. THANK YOU.
I DON'T KNOW HOW SHE FOUND OUT
ABOUT HONOKA AND I GOING OUT,
BUT EVEN THOUGH SHE KNOWS,
ASAHINA IS STILL HER
NORMAL SELF.
- MAN, YOU HAVEN'T
BEEN DOING THIS RIGHT.
-SHUT UP! GEEZ!
SHE'S EXACTLY THE SAME.
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING HAS CHANGED.
- SUZUKA? YOU'RE STILL UP?
IT'S LATE.
- I KNOW.
- YOU NEED TO GET SOME SLEEP.
WE'RE GOING BACK
TO TOKYO TOMORROW.
- OKAY.
- THAT'S IT.
TRAINING CAMP IS OVER.
- MAN, THAT'S STRANGE.
- SO WHERE EXACTLY IS THIS
OKONOMIYAKI RESTAURANT?
- IT SEEMS LIKE WE'RE
JUST WALKING IN CIRCLES.
- WE'RE NOT. JUST GIVE ME
A MINUTE, OKAY?
- MAN, I DON'T CARE
WHERE WE EAT.
EVERYTHING HERE TASTES
PRETTY MUCH THE SAME ANYWAY.
- NO IT DOESN'T, SHUT UP!
THERE'S A SUBTLE
DIFFERENCE IN TASTE
DEPENDING ON WHICH
RESTAURANT YOU GO TO.
- YOU WANT US TO TRUST YOU
WHEN YOU'RE LOOKING
AT THE GUIDEBOOK?
- AKITSUKI, JUST TAKE YOUR
TIME, OKAY? YOU'LL FIND ONE.
- THANKS. CAPTAIN,
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT.
- YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO WANTED TO GO TO
THE "BEST OKONOMIYAKI
RESTAURANT IN HIROSHIMA."
- HEY, HEY! DON'T YOU
BLAME THIS ON ME!
- I JUST HOPE
WE GET TO EAT
BEFORE IT'S TIME FOR
US TO HEAD BACK HOME.
- I'M STARVING!
- THERE YOU ARE!
HERE YOU GO.
SO, ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE OKAY WITH US
NOT GOING WITH
THE GUYS' GROUP?
- YEAH, I'M SURE. THEY WOULD'VE
BEEN TOO NOISY ANYWAY.
- I KNEW IT. YOU'RE TIRED. YOU
DIDN'T SLEEP MUCH LAST NIGHT?
ARE YOU OKAY? WERE YOU
THINKING ABOUT SOMETHING?
- NOT REALLY.
BUT, THE MOON WAS PRETTY.
- THIS SUCKS!
- HEY, AKITSUKI. WOULD
YOU MIND EXPLAINING WHY
I CAME ALL THE WAY
OUT TO HIROSHIMA
TO EAT RAMEN NOODLES?
- I'M SORRY, OKAY? I DIDN'T
MEAN TO RUIN YOUR STAY.
IT'S NOT MY FAULT THAT
ALL THE RESTAURANTS
WERE SO FULL WE COULDN'T GET IN.
- WELL, I THOUGHT THE FOOD WE
HAD WAS DELICIOUS, AKITSUKI!
- THANKS, HONOKA.
- OH! I ALMOST FORGOT!
I GOT THIS FOR YOU.
- DO YOU PUT THAT
ON A CELL PHONE?
- THEY MATCH. SEE?
- HEY, THAT'S PRETTY COOL.
THANKS A LOT, HONOKA.
- WHAT ARE YOU TWO
DOING UP THERE?
THIS SUCKS. MY PICK UP SCORE
FOR THIS TRIP IS ZERO.
GLAD YOU GUYS ARE HAVING
SUCH A GOOD TIME TOGETHER.
- Announcer: NOZOMI,
DEPARTING AT 19:30
WILL BE THE LAST
TRAIN FOR TOKYO.
- LISTEN UP! IS EVERYONE ON
BOARD? IS THERE ANYONE MISSING?
- I'M GOING TO THE
RESTROOM. BE BACK.
- OKAY.
- HATTORI, WHERE'S AKITSUKI?
- Uh, I THINK HE SAID HE
WAS GONNA GET
SOME JUICE OR SOMETHING.
- THAT FIGURES.
WOULD IT'VE BEEN SO DIFFICULT
FOR HIM TO STAY WITH THE GROUP?
- IT WOULD'VE BEEN SO EXPENSIVE
TO GET THIS ON THE TRAIN.
STUDENTS COULD NEVER AFFORD IT.
EVEN SO, I GOT EVERYONE'S DRINK
ORDER. AM I GENEROUS OR WHAT?
- YAMATO?
- ASAHINA! HOW ARE...
- OH, MY GOSH! WHAT'RE
YOU DOING OUT HERE?
- I'M SORRY!
- OH GREAT. GEEZ! IF WE DON'T
GET BACK ON THE TRAIN SOON,
WE WON'T BE ABLE
TO GET BACK HOME!
- ( train bell rings )
- SO YOU BETTER HURRY IT UP!
- WHAT'S TAKING HER SO LONG?
DID SHE FALL ASLEEP IN THE
RESTROOM OR SOMETHING?
- WHAT THE...
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
OH, MY GOSH, YOU TOTALLY
MISSED THE TRAIN!
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
GOING TO THE RESTROOM!
- WHAT NOW?
- WHAT?
- BUT I SAW BOTH OF
'EM GET ON THE TRAIN!
- YEAH. BUT THEN THEY GOT
OFF AGAIN AND MISSED IT.
- AW, MAN. I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
WHAT WERE THEY THINKING?
OKAY. CAN YOU TRY CALLING
ASAHINA ON HER CELL PHONE?
- SURE.
-WHY IS AKITSUKI WITH ASAHINA?
PLEASE ANSWER YOUR PHONE.
PLEASE.
- ( cell phone ringing )
- PLEASE PICK UP.
- ( cell phone vibrating )
- THE TRAIN LEFT.
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT,
YOU KNOW!
- SORRY. I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
- ( cell phone rings )
- IT'S MIKI.
HELLO? MIKI?
OH, HI CAPTAIN.
YES. NO, YAMATO MISSED
THE TRAIN, TOO.
OKAY. WE WILL.
-SO, WHAT'D HE SAY?
- WELL, HE SAID WE
NEED TO LOOK FOR A WAY
TO GET BACK TO TOKYO TONIGHT.
- SO I SUGGEST YOU GO LOOK
FOR THE STATION ATTENDANT!
- UH, RIGHT.
- SORRY. I'M AFRAID THAT
WAS THE LAST TRAIN
GOING TO TOKYO TONIGHT.
- WHAT? BUT, WE NEED
TO GET BACK TONIGHT!
- I SEE, I'M SORRY.
THERE'S REALLY NOTHING ELSE
I CAN DO ABOUT IT.
THERE MAY BE SOME LATE NIGHT
BUSES DEPARTING SOON
IF YOU WANNA TRY
THE BUS STATION.
- YEAH, I'M SORRY
THEY'RE ALL FULL.
THEY FILL UP EARLY
DURING THIS SEASON,
SO YOU REALLY NEED
TO MAKE A RESERVATION.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN
THEY'RE ALL FULL?
WHAT IF WE WAIT FOR
SOMEONE TO CANCEL?
- YOU CAN DO THAT I SUPPOSE.
BUT THAT'S THE CANCELLATION
LINE OVER THERE
AND THOSE PEOPLE HAVE
BEEN WAITING FOR A WHILE.
- I SEE. THEY TOLD ME THE
SAME THING OVER HERE.
ALRIGHT. WELL, I'LL DISCUSS
THIS WITH THE TEACHER
AND GET BACK TO YOU. DON'T GO
WANDERING AROUND TOO MUCH.
TALK TO YOU LATER. BYE.
- WHAT DID HE SAY?
- HE TOLD US NOT TO WANDER.
- I SEE.
- WHAT DO WE DO
NOW? THIS SUCKS.
- I WISH I HAD ANSWERS FOR YOU.
WE'LL THINK OF SOMETHING.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ABOVE ♪
♪ NOW IS ALL WE HAVE ♪
♪ WITH A LITTLE FEELING
AND A LOT OF LOVE ♪
♪ WE TURN UP THE HEAT AND RUN ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- ♪ ALL MY LIFE HERE ON THE
GROUND ABOUT TO RUN AND NOW ♪
♪ I FIND I MUST
ASK MYSELF WHY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE SOMETHING IS STIRRING ♪
♪ I FEEL IT WHISPERING IN ME ♪
♪ SOME DAYS I WAKE UP ♪
♪ BUT MY HEART'S
STILL SLEEPING ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME
TO RUN AND TRY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME TO FLY ♪
♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ON HIGH ♪
♪ WITH OUR GOAL IN SIGHT ♪
♪ WE WILL RUN
WITH ALL OUR MIGHT ♪
♪ TOMORROW AND TODAY
WILL NEVER EVER PASS US BY ♪
♪ WE WILL NOT STOP NOW ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR HEART ALIVE
AND YOUR DREAM SURVIVES ♪
♪ AND YOU CROSS
THE FINISH LINE ♪
♪ LET IT GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- Yamato: C'MON, ASAHINA! MY
DAD'S COMING BACK SOON,
SO WE NEED TO GET READY!
- DO WE HAVE TO? CAN'T I
JUST STAY ONE MORE NIGHT?
- Yamato: BUT WHY?
- Suzuka: I WANNA
SEE THE FIREFLIES.