- ♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ YOU'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER BLOW AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- ( chattering )
- Captain: BEFORE WE START
TODAY'S PRACTICE,
I WANT TO INTRODUCE YOU ALL
TO A NEW MEMBER OF OUR TEAM.
- I'M AKITSUKI. I'M LOOKING
FORWARD TO MEETING ALL OF YOU.
- HE ACTUALLY SIGNED UP?
- YEAH, CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
- I'M SURPRISED.
I NEVER THOUGHT HE'D
ACTUALLY JOIN US.
- WE'VE SURE BEEN LOOKING
FORWARD TO MEETING YOU.
YOU BLEW US AWAY WITH YOUR
TIME ON THE
HUNDRED-METER DASH
THE OTHER DAY.
- I WAS SURPRISED THAT YOU
WERE ABLE TO BEAT KOBAYAKAWA.
- THAT WAS AMAZING.
- ( chuckles )
- SO, AKITSUKI... HAVE YOU
DECIDED WHICH EVENT
YOU'D LIKE TO FOCUS ON YET?
- HUH? I THINK I'LL CHOOSE
THE HUNDRED-METER DASH.
- GOOD CHOICE.
I THINK THAT'S THE PERFECT
PLACE FOR HIM, CAPTAIN.
HE SEEMS NATURALLY SUITED FOR
SHORT DISTANCE RUNNING.
- I AGREE.
PRACTICE MAY SEEM
A BIT ROUGH AT TIMES.
JUST TRY YOUR BEST TO KEEP UP.
- I'LL DO WHAT I CAN, CAPTAIN.
- ALL RIGHT, LET'S GET
STARTED! I WANT EVERYONE
TO SPLIT UP INTO TWO
GROUPS, GUYS AND GIRLS.
START OFF WITH THE "GOLDFISH
DROPPINGS" EXERCISE.
- WELL, THAT SHOULD BE A GOOD
ENOUGH WARM UP FOR ME TODAY.
- WHAT'S A GOLDFISH DROPPING?
THIS DOESN'T SEEM SO BAD YET.
THE PACE IS KINDA FAST,
BUT I THINK I CAN KEEP UP.
HOW MANY LAPS ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO RUN, MIYAMOTO SENPAI?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
DON'T TELL ME WE HAVE TO DASH
FROM THE BACK OF THE LINE...
ALL THE WAY TO THE FRONT.
- YOU'RE NEXT, AKITSUKI. GO!
- OKAY.
I CAN'T MAKE IT.
EVERYONE'S RUNNING
WAY TOO FAST.
THIS SEEMS LIKE WAY
MORE THAN JUST A WARM UP.
( panting )
I NEVER KNEW I COULD
FEEL THIS BAD.
IT FEELS LIKE MY BODY IS
COMPLETELY SHUTTING DOWN.
NOBODY ELSE EVEN SEEMS
PHASED BY IT.
- SO, ARE YOU HAPPY
WITH YOURSELF?
YOU TOTALLY RUINED THAT
EXERCISE, YOU KNOW.
YOU TALKED WAY TOO MUCH AND
KEPT CHANGING YOUR FORM.
EVERYONE'S PACE SLOWED DOWN.
ALL YOU DID WAS SLOW US DOWN.
I KNEW THAT YOU WOULDN'T
BE ABLE TO HANDLE IT.
- Miki: GEEZ, WHAT A
TASKMASTER, HUH?
YOU MUST BE AKITSUKI. I'M MIKI
HASHIBA, NICE TO MEET YA.
I'M A SPRINTER, TOO. SO I'LL
GIVE YOU SOME TIPS IF YOU WANT.
- OH, THANKS, I GUESS.
- NOW THAT WE'RE
WARMED UP WE SPLIT UP
INTO OUR SEPARATE EVENTS.
SO COME ON, LET'S GO.
- WAIT. CAN'T I REST JUST
A BIT LONGER?
- SORRY, WE DON'T
HAVE TIME FOR THAT.
WE STILL HAVE A LOT LEFT
TO DO TODAY, YOU KNOW.
- ( groaning )
- Boy: EVERYBODY
FALL INTO FOUR LINES.
- WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO NOW?
- ALL RIGHT, LISTEN UP. I
WANT YOU TO DO FOUR SETS
OF FIFTY-METER
DASHES. YOU GOT IT?
- All: GOT IT!
- THAT DOESN'T SOUND SO BAD.
( exhaling heavily )
- WE'RE NOT DONE YET.
TWO MORE SETS TO GO.
COME ON, AKITSUKI. WE'RE
ONLY HALF WAY THERE.
- MY SIDES ARE CRAMPING...
THERE'S NO TIME TO CATCH
MY BREATH BETWEEN SETS.
- BECAUSE BEING
ON THE TEAM TAKES
A LOT OF HARD WORK
AND COMMITMENT...
WE'RE CONSTANTLY WORKING TO
IMPROVE OURSELVES.
BY ONE SECOND.
BY ONE CENTIMETER.
DO YOU REALLY THINK YOU CAN
HANDLE IT, YAMATO?
- SHE MAKES IT SEEM SO EASY
EVEN AFTER ALL OF THAT
RUNNING THAT WE JUST DID.
- Boy: AKITSUKI.
STOP DAYDREAMING.
- OH, SORRY.
- ( whistle blowing )
- Captain: THAT'S IT FOR
TODAY. GOOD JOB, GUYS.
- ( exhales ) I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S FINALLY OVER.
- Boy: MAN, I COULD DIE
FROM STARVATION.
- Soichi: LET'S GO GET
SOMETHING TO EAT THEN.
- GREAT IDEA.
- HEY, AKITSUKI! DO YOU WANNA
COME AND EAT WITH US?
- THAT'S ALL RIGHT, I CAN'T EVEN
THINK ABOUT FOOD RIGHT NOW.
- WELL, OKAY THEN, BUT MAKE
SURE THAT YOU STRETCH
AND COOL DOWN
PROPERLY, ALL RIGHT?
- I'M ALREADY DOWN AND OUT.
- ( Soichi chuckling )
- NO, I MEAN THAT YOU SHOULD
DO SOME COOL DOWN EXERCISES.
- YOU MEAN I HAVE TO
RUN SOME MORE?
- Soichi: TRUST ME, IT'LL
MAKE YOU FEEL BETTER.
- Kobayakawa: LATER, ROOKIE.
- MY MOUTH IS SO DRY I CAN
BARELY SWALLOW...
I NEVER KNEW IT WOULD
BE THIS HARD.
MAYBE ASAHINA WAS
RIGHT ABOUT ME.
MAYBE I UNDERESTIMATED
WHAT IT TOOK TO BE ON THE TEAM.
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE WORKS OUT
THIS HARD EVERY DAY
AND THEN SHE SEEMS TO BE TOTALLY
FINE AFTERWARDS.
HUH? ASAHINA?
SHE'S STILL PRACTICING?
- Miki: SHE'S QUITE
THE WORKAHOLIC, ISN'T SHE?
BESIDES WHAT SHE
DOES WITH THE TEAM,
SHE HAS THIS SPECIAL
TRAINING PROGRAM.
SUZUKA AND I WENT TO
DIFFERENT JUNIOR HIGH
SCHOOLS GROWING UP...
BUT I SAW HER AT
EVERY TRACK MEET,
AND SHE ALWAYS IMPRESSED ME.
SHE WAS SUCH A PERFECTIONIST.
- WHAT?
SHE WOULDN'T TOLERATE
ANYTHING BUT THE BEST
FROM HERSELF AND HER TEAMMATES.
WINNING WAS SO EASY FOR
HER. BUT SHE DIDN'T SMILE,
NOT EVEN WHEN SHE HAD WON.
DOESN'T THAT MAKE YOU ANGRY?
GOSH, I HATED HER.
BUT ONCE I GOT TO KNOW HER
BETTER, I BEGAN TO UNDERSTAND.
HER GOALS ARE
JUST MUCH HIGHER.
SO SHE'S NEVER SATISFIED.
EVEN IF SHE'S THE CHAMPION.
AND I REALLY RESPECT
THAT ABOUT SUZUKA.
HOW SHE'S ALWAYS TRYING
TO BETTER HERSELF.
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M THINKING.
I'M TRYING TO
IMPRESS HER WHEN
SHE'S THE STAR OF
THE TRACK TEAM.
I WISH I COULD JUST
BE MYSELF AROUND HER...
BUT SHE ALWAYS
MAKES ME SO NERVOUS.
I FEEL LIKE THE CLOSER I GET TO
HER, THE FARTHER SHE SLIPS AWAY.
- MIKI, CAN I GET YOU TO TELL
ME HOW MY FORM LOOKS?
- SURE.
WELL, I GUESS
SUZUKA NEEDS MY HELP
SO I'LL BE SEEING YOU LATER.
YOU SHOULD GO HOME AND
GET SOME REST.
- I'D LOVE TO BUT I
DON'T THINK I CAN GET UP
RIGHT NOW, MUCH LESS WALK HOME.
( laughs )
- HEY! THERE YOU ARE, YAMATO.
YOU READY TO GO HOME YET?
YOU DON'T LOOK SO HOT.
- SAY SOMETHING TO US, AKITSUKI.
- WHY ARE YOU GUYS HERE?
- 'CAUSE I KNEW WE'D
HAVE TO DRAG YOU HOME.
I FIGURED YOUR FIRST DAY
WOULD REALLY WIPE YOU OUT.
GUESS I WAS RIGHT.
- HERE, LET ME HELP TOO.
- WELL, I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
BE CAREFUL ON YOUR WAY HOME!
- SURE THING.
- SO ARE YOU STILL
GLAD YOU JOINED THE TEAM?
- AMAZING.
- HUH?
- ASAHINA'S AMAZING...
SHE REALLY IS.
- I THINK YOU'RE SO TIRED YOUR
BRAIN'S SHUTTING DOWN ON YOU.
- NO, I KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING.
- Honoka: I'M LOSING MY GRIP.
OH, I'M SO INCREDIBLY
SORRY, AKITSUKI.
- ( chuckling )
DUDE! YOUR FACE!
- THERE'S NO OTHER WORD TO
DESCRIBE ASAHINA THAN "AMAZING."
( screaming )
- AND THAT'S EVERYTHING THAT
WILL BE COVERED ON THE TEST.
NOW MAKE SURE YOU'RE NOT LATE
TOMORROW, 'CAUSE IF YOU ARE,
I'M LOCKING YOU OUT.
- ( groaning )
- HE LOOKS LIKE HE'S IN A
LOT OF PAIN.
EVERY DAY, YOU PUSH YOURSELF
SO HARD. I DON'T GET IT.
- AH, I THOUGHT I'D
FIND YOU HERE.
- OH, HEY THERE, HATTORI.
- I DIDN'T THINK IT
WOULD LAST THIS LONG.
- I KNOW, HE'S BEEN ENDURING THE
PRACTICES FOR OVER A WEEK.
- ( sighs ) NOT HIM. I WAS
TALKING ABOUT YOU, SAKURAI.
- WHAT ABOUT ME?
- YOU'VE BEEN COMING HERE
EVERY DAY AFTER SCHOOL
AND WATCHING HIM PRACTICE.
WHY DON'T YOU GO AHEAD AND
JOIN THE TEAM ALREADY?
IT'S TAKING UP ALL
YOUR FREE TIME AS IT IS.
BUT I GUESS THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE...
'CAUSE YOU'RE WAY TOO SLOW.
- WHAT DOES HE KNOW?
( panting )
IF I WANTED TO...
I COULD RUN FAST.
- HURRY BEFORE THEY CLOSE.
- DON'T WORRY, THE COMIC SHOP'S
OPEN FOR ANOTHER HOUR AT LEAST.
- OH, WOW. ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
KIDS SURE ARE FAST THESE DAYS.
IT'S PERFECT.
- NOW LISTEN. THIS'LL BE OUR
LITTLE SECRET, OKAY?
- EVER SINCE THAT DAY,
I'VE HAD A CRUSH ON AKITSUKI.
- ( cat meowing )
- OH, HELLO, GORO.
AND HOW ARE YOU TODAY?
YOUR NOSE SURE IS DIRTY.
SOMETIMES I WISH
THAT I WERE YOU, GORO...
'CAUSE THEN I'D BE ABLE
TO BE AROUND AKITSUKI
WHENEVER I WANTED.
AND HE'D GIVE ME TONS
OF ATTENTION.
'CAUSE THE WAY
THINGS ARE NOW,
HE HARDLY SEEMS
TO KNOW I'M ALIVE.
AND I HAVE ABSOLUTELY
NO IDEA WHAT I SHOULD
OR EVEN COULD DO TO
MAKE HIM NOTICE ME MORE.
I DON'T SUPPOSE THAT YOU HAVE
ANY WORDS OF ADVICE, GORO.
- Yuka: THAT'S SO SAD.
I HAVE TO SAY I'M A
LITTLE BIT DISAPPOINTED
YOU DIDN'T COME TO ME
WITH YOUR TROUBLES, SAKURAI.
I MEAN, I'M FULL OF GOOD ADVICE.
- UM, SO THEN, WHY DID WE HAVE
TO COME TAKE A BATH TOGETHER?
- THEY SAY YOU HAVE
TO BE NAKED IN ORDER
TO HEAR THE NAKED TRUTH.
- I SEE. AND BY THE WAY, I DON'T
THINK YOU EVER TOLD ME.
HOW EXACTLY IS IT THAT
YOU KNOW AKITSUKI?
- OH, HE AND I GO WAY BACK.
- OH.
- AND TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH,
LATELY I'VE BEEN A
LITTLE BIT WORRIED
ABOUT YAMATO'S STATE
OF MIND, YOU KNOW.
HE CAN BE SO IMPULSIVE.
ALWAYS MAKING DECISIONS
WITHOUT THINKING
THEM THROUGH.
- WELL, I GUESS I COULD
SEE THAT...
BUT TO ME, AKITSUKI'S
ALWAYS SEEMED SO SINCERE,
AND SERIOUS, AND RELIABLE.
- REALLY? EVEN AFTER HE'S
MADE THIS INSANE ATTEMPT
FOR ATTENTION FROM A GIRL
WHO REJECTED HIM?
- HUH? WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT, WHO REJECTED HIM?
- OH, WELL...
NO ONE.
- JUST TELL ME. WHO WAS IT?
- WELL, I SUPPOSE YOU WERE GOING
TO FIND OUT SOONER OR LATER.
OKAY, YAMATO TOLD SUZUKA THAT HE
LIKED HER, RIGHT?
BUT SHE REJECTED HIM. AND HE
INSISTS THAT HE STILL LIKES HER.
- ( gasps )
AKITSUKI TOLD ASAHINA
THAT HE LIKED HER?
- HE SAYS THAT HE'S NEVER
GONNA GIVE UP ON HER,
AND THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
THAT HE JOINED THE TRACK
TEAM IN THE FIRST PLACE.
BUT DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT
TOO MUCH, HONOKA...
LIKE ALL MEN,
YAMATO IS ALWAYS CHANGING HIS
MIND ABOUT WHAT HE WANTS.
YOU'LL GET YOUR
CHANCE, I'M SURE.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE I'VE
BEEN SO FOOLISH.
- HEY, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- THAT'S WHY HE'S BEEN
PUSHING HIMSELF SO HARD.
HE'S TRYING TO IMPRESS ASAHINA.
I DON'T HAVE A CHANCE WITH HIM.
- WAIT, NO, THAT'S NOT THE
WAY TO THE DRESSING ROOM.
- I HAVE TO BE STRONG. I WON'T
LET THIS MAKE ME CRY.
I'M NOT GONNA CRY...
I'M NOT GONNA...
( whimpering )
( Honoka sobbing )
- I SWEAR I DIDN'T
SEE ANYTHING, HONOKA.
I COULDN'T HAVE. THE
STEAM MADE IT HARD TO SEE.
- NO, IT'S NOT THAT.
THAT'S NOT WHY I'M UPSET.
- ( gasps ) THEN WHY
ARE YOU CRYING?
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT TO DO IN A
SITUATION LIKE THIS.
I'LL WALK YOU HOME,
IT'S GETTING DARK.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO,
IF YOU DON'T WANT.
- NO PROBLEM. I'D WORRY
ABOUT YOU IF I DIDN'T.
- YOU MUST BE REALLY TIRED
AFTER PRACTICE.
- I'M ALL RIGHT, ACTUALLY.
I'M GETTING USED TO IT.
- I SEE. AND HE DOESN'T MIND
BECAUSE HE GETS TO
BE WITH ASAHINA.
COULD YOU WAIT HERE
WHILE I RUN INTO THE
CONVENIENCE STORE REAL QUICK?
- SURE.
- Store Clerk: THANKS.
COME AGAIN.
- I'M SORRY TO KEEP
YOU WAITING, AKITSUKI.
- THAT'S OKAY.
- WHAT DID YOU GET, ANYWAYS?
- NOTHING MUCH, REALLY.
YOU WANNA SIT DOWN FOR A MINUTE?
HERE.
I REMEMBERED YOU
SAID YOU LIKED THESE,
SO I WENT AHEAD AND GOT YOU ONE.
- YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO DO THAT.
- I KNOW.
BUT I WANTED TO THANK
YOU FOR WALKING ME HOME.
- THEN THANKS, I APPRECIATE IT.
I'M STARVING, AND I'M SURE
THIS WILL HIT THE SPOT.
- TASTY.
- IT'S SO GOOD.
- I KNOW. BUT ASAHINA
WAS SUSPICIOUS
AND DIDN'T WANT TO TRY THEM.
BUT SHE DID AND LOVED THEM,
'CAUSE THEY'RE SO DELICIOUS!
- THEY ARE.
EVEN THOUGH HE'S HERE WITH ME,
HE'S STILL THINKING OF ASAHINA.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, HONOKA?
- OH, I'M FINE.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG.
IT'S JUST... HEY.
I WANTED TO TELL YOU
THAT I'M THINKING OF JOINING
THE TRACK TEAM, TOO.
- REALLY? ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- YEP.
I WON'T GIVE UP EITHER.
- YOU KNOW...
IT'S A LOT OF HARD WORK.
- I THINK I CAN HANDLE IT.
I'LL DO ANYTHING TO BE WITH
YOU AS MUCH AS I CAN.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
I'M HONOKA SAKURAI.
I'M YOUR NEW TEAM MANAGER.
- YOU'RE SO CUTE.
- WE'VE NEVER HAD A
MANAGER BEFORE.
- EVERYONE'S JOINING THE TEAM.
BUMMER! I'LL HAVE TO FIND
SOMEONE ELSE TO HANG OUT WITH.
HEY, YUKA. IT'S ME. WANNA GO
HIT UP SOME KARAOKE?
- I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU MEANT THAT
YOU WERE GONNA BE
THE TEAM MANAGER.
- I'M HORRIBLE AT SPORTS, BUT I
WANNA BE PART OF THE TEAM,
SO I THOUGHT I'D
BE BETTER SUITED
TO MANAGERIAL TASKS INSTEAD.
- I SEE.
- SO THE NEW GIRL'S PRETTY GOOD
FRIENDS WITH AKITSUKI.
- I GUESS SO.
- MAYBE SHE'S HIS GIRLFRIEND.
- DON'T BE RIDICULOUS, MIKI.
LET'S GET GOING.
- HEY! WOULD YA HOLD ON A
SECOND! SUZUKA.
- THIS IS THE LAST
ONE, AKITSUKI.
I WANT YOU TO GIVE
IT ALL YOU GOT.
- SURE.
- I DIDN'T KNOW THAT I'D BE
DOING SO MUCH LAUNDRY.
YUCK!
I THOUGHT THAT BEING A
MANAGER WOULD HELP ME
TO GET CLOSER TO AKITSUKI.
BUT IT HASN'T REALLY
TURNED OUT THAT WAY.
- Captain: THAT'S IT.
WE'RE DONE FOR TODAY.
- GEEZ, I FEEL SO EXHAUSTED.
( panting )
- LOOKS LIKE YOU'RE COMING
ALONG NICELY, AKITSUKI.
YOU EVEN MANAGED TO KEEP
UP WITH THE BEST OF US.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- NOTHING. JUST A
LITTLE MUSCLE PAIN.
- WELL, IT HAS BEEN A WEEK SINCE
YOU JOINED UP, YOU KNOW.
I'LL BET YOU'RE AT THE PEAK
OF YOUR SORENESS.
I CAN GIVE YOU A MASSAGE
IF YOU WANT.
I'M PRETTY GOOD AT IT. I'LL
WORK WONDERS ON YOUR BACK.
- ( exclaiming in pain )
- STOP SQUIRMING.
- CUT IT OUT.
- HOW LONG DO YOU PLAN
ON FOOLING AROUND?
WE STILL HAVE WORK
TO DO, YOU KNOW.
- YOU'RE NOT CALLING ME LAZY,
ARE YOU, ASAHINA?
- SO WHAT IF I AM?
- OKAY, I'M NOT GREAT YET,
BUT I'M WORKING HARD.
- HEY! AKITSUKI AND HASHIBA,
GET OVER HERE,
WE'RE ABOUT TO START WITH
THE TWO-HUNDRED METER INTERVALS.
- BE RIGHT THERE.
IF SHE'S JUST GOING TO PICK
FIGHTS WITH ME ALL THE TIME...
THEN WHAT WAS THE POINT OF ME
JOINING THE TEAM?
- DON'T YOU THINK YOU
MIGHT HAVE BEEN
A LITTLE HARD ON HIM, SUZUKA?
HE'S REALLY TRYING HIS BEST,
YOU KNOW?
- MAYBE HIS BEST
ISN'T GOOD ENOUGH.
AND YOU SEEM TO BE SLACKING
OFF TOO, MIKI.
- SUZUKA, WHAT'S WRONG?
YOU'VE BEEN ACTING
REALLY WEIRD LATELY AND...
- WHAT? NOTHING'S
WRONG WITH ME. I'M FINE.
- WHATEVER YOU SAY THEN...
BUT YOU ALWAYS GET SO
IRRITATED WITH AKITSUKI.
JUST GIVE HIM A CHANCE.
HE'S NOT ALL BAD.
AND HE IS WORKING REALLY HARD.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND ASAHINA.
I KNOW SHE WASN'T HAPPY
ABOUT ME JOINING THE TEAM.
I THOUGHT THAT IF I WORKED
REALLY HARD, SHE'D COME AROUND.
BUT I'VE BEEN
DOING REALLY WELL,
AND SHE'S STILL AS
BITTER AS EVER.
MAN, WHY'S SHE GOTTA
BE SO CUTE?
- HEY, QUIT YOUR
DAYDREAMING, YAMATO.
YOU'RE HOLDING UP THE LINE.
- SORRY.
I'LL JUST HAVE TO KEEP
WORKING HARD.
AND HOPE THAT SHE FINALLY
COMES AROUND.
- WHAT A SHOW OFF.
- Miki: AND HE IS
WORKING REALLY HARD...
- WELL HE MAY BE
WORKING HARD NOW,
BUT I'M SURE HE'LL GIVE UP
SOONER OR LATER.
- I FINALLY FINISHED IT.
AND NOW I CAN TAKE
AKITSUKI A CLEAN TOWEL.
- HEY! MANAGER!
WILL YOU BRING US SOME
MORE WATER, PLEASE?
- SURE THING.
- ( whistle blowing )
- Captain: OKAY, OKAY.
WE'RE DONE FOR THE DAY.
EVERYONE BE SURE TO COOL
DOWN BEFORE YOU GO HOME.
- WE'RE FINALLY DONE.
- IT'S TIME TO EAT.
- STOP IT, I SAID THAT
I HAD ENOUGH.
- AND I'M SAYING THAT
WE NEED TO DO THIS PROPERLY.
- HEY, AKITSUKI.
I BROUGHT YOU A TOWEL.
- THANKS, MANAGER.
- Honoka: IT WAS MY PLEASURE.
- Yamato: OH, SORRY.
- ( Honoka and
Yamato laughing )
- I HOPE THAT DIDN'T HURT.
- LAZY.
- ( grunts loudly )
- EXACTLY LIKE YOU SAID.
I PUT IT AT 164.
- YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO SET
THE TOP OF THE BAR TO THE MARK,
NOT THE BOTTOM, YOU IDIOT!
- HOW WAS I SUPPOSED TO KNOW?
I'M NOT IN TRACK AND FIELD!
YOU KNOW THAT!
( screaming )
- WHAT HAPPENED?
WOW, AMAZING. YOU CAN SEE A
WHOLE CITY FROM UP HERE.
- THERE'S A CITY
DOWN THERE. LOOK.
- WHAT?
- I'M SORRY.
MAYBE I'M WRONG...
ABOUT YAMATO.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ABOVE ♪
♪ NOW IS ALL WE HAVE ♪
♪ WITH A LITTLE FEELING
AND A LOT OF LOVE ♪
♪ WE TURN UP THE HEAT AND RUN ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- ♪ ALL MY LIFE HERE ON THE
GROUND ABOUT TO RUN AND NOW ♪
♪ I FIND I MUST
ASK MYSELF WHY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE SOMETHING IS STIRRING ♪
♪ I FEEL IT WHISPERING IN ME ♪
♪ SOME DAYS I WAKE UP ♪
♪ BUT MY HEART'S
STILL SLEEPING ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME
TO RUN AND TRY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME TO FLY ♪
♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ON HIGH ♪
♪ WITH OUR GOAL IN SIGHT ♪
♪ WE WILL RUN
WITH ALL OUR MIGHT ♪
♪ TOMORROW AND TODAY
WILL NEVER EVER PASS US BY ♪
♪ WE WILL NOT STOP NOW ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR HEART ALIVE
AND YOUR DREAM SURVIVES ♪
♪ AND YOU CROSS
THE FINISH LINE ♪
♪ LET IT GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- Suzuka: WELL. LOOKS LIKE
I'LL BE HEADED HOME.
- Yamato: SO WHAT IS IT
ABOUT ME THAT YOU DON'T LIKE?
I DON'T GET YOU AT ALL.
- Suzuka: SOMETIMES, I JUST
DESPISE BEING AROUND YOU.