- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- ASAHINA AND AKITSUKI
DIDN'T GET ON THE TRAIN?
- NO. THEY DID. BUT THEN
THEY GOT OFF AGAIN.
- WHY IS AKITSUKI, WITH ASAHINA?
- WHAT DO WE DO
NOW? THIS SUCKS.
- I WISH I HAD ANSWERS FOR YOU.
- ASAHINA, I'M SORRY,
I KNOW THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
- NO KIDDING. SO HOW DO
YOU PLAN TO MAKE UP FOR THIS?
- OH. I KNOW! KARAOKE!
OR A RESTAURANT!
WE CAN KILL TIME
TILL THE MORNING...
AND THEN HEAD BACK ON
THE BULLET TRAIN!
- I GUESS.
- ALRIGHT, GREAT! IT'LL BE FUN!
WOULD IT BE POSSIBLE
TO BORROW SOME MONEY, THOUGH?
I ONLY HAVE ABOUT 600 YEN ON ME.
- THAT'S MORE THAN I HAVE.
I DON'T HAVE MY PURSE WITH ME.
IT'S STILL ON THE TRAIN,
IN CASE YOU FORGOT.
- OH! THAT'S RIGHT!
- ♪ CARP! THE CARP! THE
CARP OF HIROSHIMA! ♪
OH, NO WHAT'S GOING ON OVER
HERE? IS THIS DOMESTIC VIOLENCE?
- NO! IT'S NOTHING LIKE THAT!
- I KNOW THAT LOOK! YOU
JUST GOT CAUGHT CHEATING!
HEY THERE, GIRLIE!
YOU KNOW, CHEATING IS LIKE A
STATUS SYMBOL FOR US GUYS.
WE CAN'T HELP IT!
YOU SHOULD FORGIVE HIM
FOR ONE OR TWO FLINGS.
BESIDES, I CAN TELL THAT SHE'S
THE FAVORITE OF THEM ALL, RIGHT?
( chuckles ) RIGHT?
- YOUR BREATH.
- YOU KNOW, THERE'S A
LITTLE HOTEL OVER THERE.
WHY DON'T YOU
MAKE IT UP TO HER?
- WHAT! WHAT ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- ( man chuckling )
- COME ON! CUT IT OUT!
STOP HARASSING THESE
POOR KIDS ALREADY!
- I HOPE IT ALL WORKS OUT, MAN!
- WHAT THE HECK WAS THAT?
NOT LIKE WE HAVE ANY MONEY
TO GO TO A HOTEL. OH, WELL!
- I WOULDN'T GO IF WE DID!
- WHAT? ME EITHER! I MEAN...
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
TALK ABOUT SOMETHING
ELSE, IDIOT.
WAIT. ASAHINA! I ALMOST
FORGOT! MY PARENTS LIVE HERE!
I BET MY DAD WOULD
LEND US SOME MONEY!
THAT WAY, YOU COULD STAY AT ONE
OF THE BUSINESS HOTELS AROUND
HERE AND I COULD STAY AT HOME
WITH MY PARENTS.
THEN WE CAN GO HOME
TOMORROW MORNING.
- THAT WOULD BE OKAY.
BUT YOUR PARENTS...
- YOU DON'T THINK THEY'D
MIND, WOULD THEY?
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT!
BUT CAN I BORROW YOUR
CELL PHONE FOR A MINUTE?
I'M PRETTY SURE I LEFT
MINE ON THE TRAIN.
- SURE.
- I THINK I'M GONNA GO
CALL OVER THERE, THOUGH.
- WHAT FOR?
- JUST BECAUSE.
I DON'T WANNA SEE YOUR REACTION
WHEN YOU HEAR MY DIALECT.
- SO, NO WORD FROM THEM I GUESS?
- NO.
- WE'RE SAVED!
HE'S ON HIS WAY RIGHT NOW.
- REALLY? THAT'S AWESOME!
ALRIGHT, WELL,
I'LL LET THE CAPTAIN KNOW.
HE'S PROBABLY
WORRIED ABOUT US.
- YEAH. GOOD CALL.
- ( cell phone rings )
- OH! LOOK! HERE THEY ARE!
- GOOD.
- HEY, MIKI. IT'S SUZUKA. CAN I
TALK TO THE CAPTAIN FOR A SEC?
CAPTAIN? YEAH, WE'RE OKAY...
YAMATO'S FAMILY LIVES HERE
AND HIS DAD'S ON HIS WAY
TO COME GET US.
- HERE.
- FOR ME?
OH, GREAT. HE'S PROBABLY
ANGRY WITH ME.
- HELLO?
- Honoka: AKITSUKI?
- Yamato: HONOKA, HI!
- I HEARD YOU DIDN'T
MAKE IT ON THE TRAIN
AND I WAS WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
- WELL, EVERYTHING'S FINE. MY
DAD'S ON HIS WAY TO PICK US UP.
- OH. OKAY. GOOD.
THAT'S GREAT...
I'M GLAD.
- I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE THINKING.
- WHAT?
- DON'T WORRY. I'LL BE
STAYING THERE BY MYSELF.
IT'LL BE OKAY. I PROMISE.
- YEAH. OKAY. THANK YOU.
- OKAY, WELL. I GUESS I'LL CALL
YOU WHEN I GET HOME THEN?
OKAY? BYE.
- HERE. THANK YOU!
- MMM-HMM.
SO... WHAT WAS THE
CONFESSION LIKE?
DID YOU TELL HER THAT
YOU LIKED HER FIRST?
- WELL...
YEAH. IT'S TRUE.
- WELL GOOD FOR YOU.
YOU MUST REALLY LIKE HER.
- I DO, BUT, NOT FOR THE
REASONS YOU WOULD THINK.
I MEAN, SHE'S EXTREMELY
BEAUTIFUL, AND,
KIND AND CONSIDERATE
AND THOUGHTFUL...
BUT THE BEST THING ABOUT HER
IS THAT SHE JUST HAS THIS
AMAZING ABILITY TO PUT
MY HEART AT EASE SOMEHOW.
- I GET IT!
- HUH?
HEY! YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S
ASKING QUESTIONS, ASAHINA!
- I DIDN'T ASK FOR THE ENTIRE
LOVE SAGA! YOU'RE SUCH AN IDIOT!
- ALL RIGHT! THIS DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE! WHAT'S WRONG?
- WILL YOU PLEASE
LOWER YOUR VOICE?
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING
YOURSELF.
- Yamato: AFTER THAT,
THERE WAS THIS UNCOMFORTABLE,
AWKWARD FEELING BETWEEN US.
SHE DIDN'T SAY A WORD FOR THE
NEXT HOUR AND A HALF.
WE JUST SAT IN SILENCE.
UNTIL FINALLY MY DAD SHOWED UP.
- HE'S HERE!
FINALLY. HI, DAD.
( grunts )
- YOU'RE SUCH AN IDIOT!
SO WAS THAT JUICE YOU BOUGHT
WORTH MISSING THE TRAIN?
- I'M SORRY THAT YOU HAD
TO COME ALL THE WAY OUT
HERE LIKE THIS FOR US.
- DON'T MENTION IT.
IT'S NOT A PROBLEM AT ALL.
I'M SURE IT'S ALL YAMATO'S
FAULT, ANYWAY. COME ON.
GET IN THE CAR.
- HUH? THE CAR? BUT THERE'S
A HOTEL RIGHT THERE?
- SHUT UP, YAMATO.
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS!
THERE'S NO WAY WE'RE
LETTING A GIRL
STAY ALONE IN A PLACE LIKE THIS!
I'LL BRING YOU GUYS BACK
SOMETIME TOMORROW.
ARE YOU ALRIGHT WITH STAYING
AT OUR PLACE TONIGHT?
- SURE.
- NO WAIT! WE CAN'T DO THAT!
- IS THE BACK SEAT OKAY WITH
YOU? I'M SORRY IT'S A BIT MESSY.
- UH...
- DAD! LISTEN TO ME!
- YAMATO, I DON'T WANNA HEAR IT.
JUST SHUT UP AND GET IN THE CAR,
UNLESS YOU WANT ME
TO LEAVE YOU HERE. GEEZ!
- BUT, DAD, WAIT!
SO THAT MEANS ASAHINA IS
STAYING AT MY HOUSE TONIGHT?
- ( Dad yawning )
I'M SO TIRED. I CAN'T
BELIEVE I HAD TO MAKE A THREE
HOUR ROUND TRIP
BECAUSE OF YAMATO.
- Suzuka: I'M REALLY
SORRY ABOUT ALL OF THIS.
- Dad: OH, IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT,
SUZUKA. RIGHT, MOM?
- Grandmother: YAMATO! EAT UP!
YOU'RE SKIN AND BONES!
- MAKE SURE YOU GET
PLENTY TO EAT, SUZUKA?
- OH, THANKS!
- DAD, I THINK THOSE
ARE MY CHOPSTICKS.
- YAMATO, DO YOU WANT
ANOTHER BOWL?
- GRANDMA, DON'T FORCE FEED
HIM, HE DOESN'T WANT IT.
- MIKO. WANT
THE REST? HERE.
- WHAT THE HECK IS
GOING ON HERE?
- THE BOTTOM LINE IS, YAMATO,
YOU COULDN'T GET ON THE TRAIN
BECAUSE YOU WERE TOO BUSY
FOOLING AROUND AS USUAL, RIGHT?
- GOODNESS, YAMATO. HOW COULD
YOU? SEE, THIS IS WHY I SAID
YOU SHOULD JUST GO TO SCHOOL
IN HIROSHIMA. NOT TOKYO?
- DON'T BE SO HARD
ON HIM, KOTONO!
HE HASN'T BEEN HOME
IN SUCH A LONG TIME.
- YEAH, IT'S KINDA SAD. TOKYO
HASN'T CHANGED YOU AT ALL.
- YOU'RE STILL A DORK.
- DORK.
- YEP, THIS IS MY
FAMILY ALRIGHT...
WHERE I GREW UP FOR
SIXTEEN YEARS.
BUT THE ONLY REASON I FEEL SO
UNCOMFORTABLE AND
AWKWARD IS BECAUSE...
ASAHINA IS SITTING
RIGHT NEXT TO ME.
- Dad: SUZUKA, TRY THIS
SEA SLUG. IT'S DELICIOUS!
- OKAY. I'VE NEVER HAD THEM.
- DAD, DON'T MAKE HER EAT THAT.
SO, THE TRAIN, IT'S KINDA
FAR AWAY. SO...
WE NEED TO LEAVE EARLY
TO MAKE IT ON TIME.
- WELL, UNFORTUNATELY I WON'T BE
ABLE TO TAKE YOU UNTIL I GET OFF
OF WORK TODAY. BUT IF
TRAFFIC ISN'T TOO BAD,
WE CAN LEAVE BY FOUR AND STILL
MAKE IT THERE BY SIX-THIRTY.
- OH NO! YOU'RE GOING
BACK SO SOON, YAMATO?
BUT YOU JUST GOT HERE YESTERDAY.
CAN'T THE TWO OF
YOU JUST STAY A LITTLE LONGER?
- I WOULD LOVE TO, BUT I THINK
ASAHINA HAS TO GET BACK.
- I'M REALLY SORRY.
I FEEL LIKE I'M ASKING
TOO MUCH OF ALL OF YOU.
- OH, DON'T YOU WORRY
ABOUT IT, MY DEAR.
THIS IS ALL YAMATO'S
FAULT ANYWAY.
- TOTALLY. IT'S ALL HIS FAULT
FOR DROPPING THE JUICE CANS.
- RIGHT, MIKO?
- ( meows )
- GEE, THANKS A LOT, YOU GUYS.
- WELL I GUESS I'M OFF TO WORK.
YOU GUYS KILL SOME TIME.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER ON TONIGHT.
- OKAY.
- Mom: WELL, YAMATO,
I'M GOING SHOPPING.
MAKE SURE YOU TAKE KORO
FOR A WALK WHILE I'M GONE.
- OKAY.
- HEY. SO...
- WHAT IS IT?
- YOU MUST BE REALLY BORED HERE.
I CAN SHOW YOU AROUND
IF YOU'D LIKE?
- NO THANKS. I KIND OF
WANT TO BE ALONE.
- ARE YOU SURE? I MEAN, WE HAVE
A LOT OF TIME TO KILL TODAY.
I'M WALKING THE
DOG ANYWAY, SO...
- IT WAS NICE OF YOUR SISTER TO
LET ME BORROW SOME CLOTHES.
I WANNA DO SOMETHING FOR HER
WHEN SHE GETS HOME.
- OKAY. GOOD IDEA.
- IF YOU DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO SAY,
JUST LEAVE ME
ALONE, ALRIGHT?
- FINE...
JEEZ, I WAS TRYING
TO THINK OF HER TOO.
I MEAN, OKAY. I KNOW IT'S MY
FAULT THAT SHE ENDED UP HERE IN
THE FIRST PLACE, BUT SHE DIDN'T
HAVE TO BE SO MEAN...
KORO! YOUR MASTER'S TALKING TO
YOU, SO YOU SHOULD LISTEN!
HMM...
- ( wind blowing )
- THERE'S NO WAY ASAHINA
CAN ENJOY HERSELF
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS.
THERE'S NOTHING
EXCITING ABOUT IT.
HEY, ASAHINA! WOULD YOU
LIKE TO SEE THE FIREFLIES?
REMEMBER, I TOLD YOU ABOUT THEM.
THERE ARE SO MANY OF THEM BY
THAT RIVER IN THE EVENING.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
SO, IF YOU WANT, WE COULD
STAY ONE MORE NIGHT
AND YOU COULD SEE THEM
BEFORE YOU GO HOME?
- DIDN'T I TELL YOU I
WANTED TO BE ALONE?
- WHAT THE HECK IS
WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU BEEN SO IRRITABLE
SINCE YESTERDAY!
YOU'RE JUST IMPOSSIBLE!
- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S
IMPOSSIBLE, YAMATO.
- HUH?
- SAYING, "LET'S STAY ONE MORE
NIGHT AND SEE FIREFLIES"
WHAT EXACTLY ARE
YOU TRYING TO PULL?
- ( gasps )
- I THINK WE BOTH KNOW I'M NOT
THE ONE YOU WANNA BE HERE WITH.
- I SEE. SO ASAHINA IS TRYING
TO THINK ABOUT HONOKA.
- CAN YOU JUST GO, PLEASE?
- YEAH. WE GOT TO MY
PLACE LAST NIGHT.
- Honoka: OKAY.
ARE YOU HAVING FUN?
- YEAH. I AM. I GUESS.
LISTEN, HONOKA. I HAVE
TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
MY DAD WAS REALLY
PUSHY AND INSISTED
THAT ASAHINA STAY WITH US.
BUT, THE GOOD NEWS IS WE'RE
COMING BACK TODAY!
DON'T WORRY. I DON'T HAVE ANY
FEELINGS FOR HER OR ANYTHING.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
- HUH? I THOUGHT YOU'D BE UPSET.
- WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S
JUST THE TWO OF YOU.
YOUR FAMILY'S THERE TOO RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- THEN THERE'S NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
- THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK!
- UH...
- I'M JUST KIDDING.
I WOULDN'T DO THAT!
NO REALLY! REALLY, I PROMISE!
WE'LL BE LEAVING HERE IN A BIT.
OKAY, I'LL EMAIL YOU
WHEN I GET HOME.
YEAH. BYE.
ASAHINA! DAD SHOULD BE
GETTING BACK SOON,
SO LET'S GET READY TO GO, OKAY?
HEY, DID YOU HEAR ME?
- LISTEN... I CHANGED MY MIND.
DO YOU THINK IT'D BE
ALL RIGHT IF I STAYED
ONE MORE NIGHT AFTER ALL?
- YEAH, BUT WHY?
- I WANNA SEE THE FIREFLIES.
- UH, SURE.
OKAY.
WHAT IS SHE THINKING?
SHE'S SO CONFUSING.
- SAYING "LET'S STAY ONE MORE
NIGHT AND SEE FIREFLIES."
WHAT, EXACTLY, ARE YOU
TRYING TO PULL?
- AFTER ALL THAT SHE CHANGES HER
MIND? IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE!
I TOLD HONOKA THAT I'D
BE BACK BY TONIGHT, TOO.
- SO, WHERE ARE THEY?
- OVER BY THE BRIDGE THERE.
- THERE SHOULD BE A LOT
BY THE RIVER.
- REALLY?
C'MON, LET'S HURRY THEN!
- CAREFUL! DON'T RUN,
IT'S DANGEROUS!
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
SO, YOU'RE SPEECHLESS.
I KNEW YOU'D LIKE THEM!
- I KNEW IT.
NO FIREFLIES.
- HUH...
THAT'S STRANGE! WHAT HAPPENED?
THERE'RE USUALLY TONS OF THEM
OUT HERE IN THE SUMMER. REALLY!
ALL FLYING AND
GLOWING AND...
I'M SO SORRY. I KNOW
THAT YOU STAYED HERE
ONE MORE DAY JUST TO SEE THEM.
- OH, DON'T WORRY. IT'S OKAY.
I HAD A FEELING SOMETHING
LIKE THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
- GREAT. THAT FIGURES.
THEY'RE EVERYWHERE
WHEN I DON'T NEED THEM,
BUT WHEN I ACTUALLY WANNA
SHOW THEM TO SOMEONE...
THIS HAPPENS.
- SO YOU CAME HERE
WITH SOMEONE BEFORE?
- YEAH. WHEN I WAS
IN JUNIOR HIGH,
I ASKED A GIRL I LIKED
TO COME HERE WITH ME.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE
NICE TO CONFESS TO HER
WITH ALL THE FIREFLIES
SURROUNDING US.
- YEAH? THEN WHAT?
- WELL, OF COURSE,
WHEN WE GET THERE,
NOT ONLY ARE THERE NO FIREFLIES,
BUT IT STARTS TO RAIN!
EVERYTHING I'D PLANNED
TO DO AND SAY WAS RUINED.
BUT I GOT DESPERATE AND
CONFESSED ANYWAY.
AND TO TOP IT OFF...
I WAS REJECTED.
- ( laughs )
- WHAT? THAT'S NOT FUNNY!
- IT'S HILARIOUS! I COULD
TOTALLY PICTURE YOU
IN MY MIND. THAT'S
JUST LIKE YOU!
- WHAT'S JUST LIKE ME?
- YOU'RE THE SAME
IN EVERY SITUATION.
YOU CAN'T SUCCEED WHEN
IT REALLY MATTERS.
- SHUT UP! I'M BEING COMPLETELY
SERIOUS HERE! I'M NOT TRYING TO
MAKE YOU LAUGH AT ALL
RIGHT NOW, ASAHINA!
- I KNOW YOU'RE NOT,
BELIEVE ME.
BUT THAT'S WHAT
MAKES IT FUNNIER.
- WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE I HAVEN'T
CONFESSED TO SOMEONE
WITH THE RIGHT ATMOSPHERE.
- HUH? IT REALLY DOESN'T
TAKE MUCH FOR YOU
TO LIKE SOMEONE, DOES IT?
SEEMS LIKE YOU
CONFESS TO EVERYONE.
- ( gasps )
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I CONFESSED TO YOU!
WELL, Y'KNOW.
HEY, LOOK OVER THERE! I KNEW IT
- SO, NOW YOU HAVE ME CURIOUS...
HOW WERE YOU PLANNING TO CONFESS
TO THAT GIRL YOU LIKED?
KNOWING YOU, YOU MUST'VE
PRACTICED. C'MON, WE'VE GOT
EVERYTHING HERE! "A CONFESSION,
BY YAMATO AKITSUKI!"
- WHAT?! ARE YOU CRAZY
OR SOMETHING?
YOU WANT ME TO ACT
IT OUT FOR YOU?
- YEAH, WHY? WHAT
ARE YOU AFRAID OF?
I JUST WANNA SEE HOW YOU
WOULD'VE DONE IT. C'MON!
- IS SHE THREATENING ME NOW?
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE MAKING ME
DO THIS. YOU'RE INSANE.
- WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- HAVE YOU EVER SEEN ONE
OF THESE THINGS BEFORE?
IT'S CALLED A BELLFLOWER.
I'VE LIKED YOU SINCE YOU
FIRST CAME TO OUR SCHOOL!
WOULD YOU PLEASE GO
OUT WITH ME?
OR, SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
- YEAH.
I'LL GO OUT WITH YOU.
- WHAT? STOP MAKING
FUN OF ME, ASAHINA!
- I'M NOT MAKING FUN OF YOU
THIS TIME. I'M BEING SERIOUS.
GOTCHA!
YOU TOTALLY FELL FOR IT!
LOOK AT YOU, YOU'RE ALL RED!
DON'T TAKE IT SO SERIOUSLY.
- WHAT? I KNEW YOU WERE JOKING!
- FIREFLIES! I DIDN'T REALIZE
THAT THERE WERE SO MANY OF THEM
AROUND US RIGHT NOW. MY EYES
MUST JUST NOW BE ADJUSTING.
- RIGHT. THERE'S NO WAY ASAHINA
WOULD EVER SAY ANYTHING
LIKE THAT AND MEAN IT.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WHEN I TURN AROUND,
YOUR RIGHT THERE NEXT TO ME ♪
♪ ON YOUR FACE, THE SMILE
SO COMFORTING AND FAMILIAR ♪
♪ THE CLOSER YOU BECAME,
THE LESS THAT I COULD SEE ♪
♪ AND NOW I'M WANDERING,
SO LOST AND ALL ALONE
♪ PEOPLE CHANGE
A LITTLE AT A TIME ♪
♪ AND NOW I KNOW, I'M CHANGING ♪
♪ WHEN I CALL YOUR NAME ♪
♪ SHOUT IT OUT INTO THE SKY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN I WILL FIND,
THE LOVE I KEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ WHEN YOUR WITH ME ♪
♪ AND YOU TAKE MY HAND ♪
♪ SOMEHOW EVERYTHING,
SEEMS TO WORK ITSELF OUT RIGHT ♪
♪ WHEN I SEE YOUR EYES ♪
♪ STARING BACK AT MINE ♪
♪ THERE INSIDE I FIND,
A LOVE THAT NEVER DIES ♪
♪ TOGETHER I KNOW,
WE'LL FIND A WAY ♪
♪ JUST YOU AND I ♪
- Honoka: AKITSUKI! WATCH OUT!
ARE YOU OKAY?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
YOU'RE STARTING TO SCARE ME.
AKITSUKI? WHAT'RE YOU
DOING? STOP! PLEASE!