- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- SO, YOU GUYS MADE UP AND
YOU STILL HAVEN'T DONE IT?
WHAT'S UP WITH THAT? WHY DO
YOU TWO KEEP PUTTING IT OFF?
- I KNOW IT SOUNDS CRAZY BUT,
HONOKA AND I REALLY DON'T
WANNA RUSH THINGS.
- SURE YOU DON'T.
LOOK, IF YOU KEEP THIS UP,
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA GET ANY.
COME ON! YOU KNOW HOW GIRLS
ARE ALWAYS WAITING FOR
THE RIGHT PLACE AND
THE RIGHT TIME?
WELL, IT DOESN'T EXIST.
YOU HAVE TO CREATE IT.
- LOOK, I REALLY DON'T WANT TO
TALK ABOUT THIS WITH YOU.
- JUST LISTEN!
- NO, YOU LISTEN! WE'RE
GOING AT OUR OWN PACE.
WE DON'T NEED YOUR HELP!
- WELL, THIS SOUNDS LIKE
EXCITING LUNCHTIME CONVERSATION.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS TALKING ABOUT?
AM I ALLOWED TO KNOW?
- YEAH. YOU'RE A GIRL.
MAYBE YOU CAN TALK TO HIM.
- HUH? WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- YAMATO WANTED TO
GET IT ON WITH SAKURAI
SO HE FORCED HIMSELF ON HER.
- WHAT? NO I DIDN'T!
- UH...
- I WAS TRYING TO EXPLAIN TO
HIM THAT THE ATMOSPHERE
HAS TO BE RIGHT
FOR SEX, YA KNOW?
SOMETHING EXCITING
LIKE A HALLWAY.
- ( grunting )
- YOU ARE SUCH A
DISGUSTING CREEP!
HOW DO YOU SLEEP AT NIGHT?
- OW! OW! OW! OW! QUIT!
OW! STOP HITTING ME! OW!
- YOU LITTLE PERVERT!
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT!
ALL YOU THINK ABOUT IS SEX!
- THAT'S NOT TRUE. YOU'RE THE
ONLY ONE THAT THINKS THAT!
- COME ON, AKITSUKI! LET'S GO!
STUPIDITY'S CONTAGIOUS!
- YAMATO AND I AREN'T DONE
TALKING, YET!
- JUST LEAVE ME ALONE. PLEASE!
- Soichi: OK, GUYS, WE'RE DONE.
- ( Yamato grunting )
- HEY, AKITSUKI. GOOD WORK
TODAY. THAT LOOKS HEAVY.
YOU CAN REALLY LIFT THAT MUCH?
- WELL, SURE.
IT'S PRETTY EASY NOW.
- Kinugasa: IT LOOKS
EASY ENOUGH.
- GREAT. IT'S OUR FORMER
CAPTAIN AGAIN.
- OKAY.
UNFORTUNATELY, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO BUILD UP A LOT MORE MUSCLE
THAN THIS AS A SPRINTER.
I THINK WE NEED TO ADD ANOTHER
THREE SETS TO YOUR ROUTINE.
- WHAT? NO WAY!
- HUH? WHAT WAS THAT?
- AH! I SAID I'LL DO IT. I'LL DO
IT, OKAY? PLEASE LET ME DO IT.
- YOU GOT IT!
- I'M BEGGING YOU!
- ALL RIGHT, YOU BETTER
WORK HARD NOW.
- WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
- UM, AKITSUKI?
I HAVE SOMETHING TO DO
TODAY SO I CAN'T STAY.
IS THAT OKAY WITH YOU?
- YEAH, THAT'S FINE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IF YOU NEED TO GO, GO AHEAD.
- IT'S RAINING OUTSIDE.
I BET YOU DIDN'T BRING
YOUR UMBRELLA TODAY, DID YOU?
- WELL, NO. BUT IT'S NOT
RAINING THAT HARD.
IF I NEED TO, I CAN ALWAYS CALL
MIHO TO COME BRING ME ONE.
- OKAY.
- Miki: SUZUKA!
YOU READY?
- YEAH. LET'S GO.
- HEY, SUZUKA. DO YOU WANNA
STOP BY THE CAFE WITH ME?
IT'S CHESTNUT SEASON AND
YOU KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS.
MONT BLANCS AND
CHESTNUT CAKES ARE OUT.
DOESN'T THAT SOUND GOOD?
- NO, THANKS. NOT TODAY.
OH GREAT. THAT'S RIGHT.
I FORGOT I LEFT MY CELL
PHONE IN THE CLASSROOM.
I'M GONNA HAVE TO GO GET IT.
YOU CAN GO AHEAD IF
YOU NEED TO, MIKI.
- OH NO, IT'S OKAY.
I DON'T MIND WAITING FOR YOU.
CAKES DON'T TASTE AS GOOD
WHEN I EAT THEM ALONE, ANYWAY.
- YEAH, BUT I ALREADY TOLD
YOU I DON'T REALLY FEEL LIKE
CAKE RIGHT NOW, REMEMBER?
- OH STOP. THIS IS THE ONLY
TIME YOU CAN HAVE THEM!
- ( grunting )
- ALL RIGHT, JUST TWO MORE SETS.
- DON'T GIVE UP!
- I'M NOT.
THIS IS SO AWKWARD.
- Miki: WHAT?
DO YOU MEAN TO TELL ME
THAT YOUR PHONE HAS BEEN IN
YOUR BAG THIS WHOLE TIME?
- THAT'S RIGHT. I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T REALIZE I HADN'T
ALREADY CHECKED IT.
- YOU'RE REALLY STARTING
TO LOSE YOUR FOCUS.
BUT NEVER MIND, I'M GLAD YOU
FOUND IT. LET'S GO EAT, 'KAY?
- WELL...
I CAN'T. I FORGOT I
HAVE TO WRITE A REPORT.
IT'S DUE TODAY, SO...
- ARE YOU KIDDING?
- NOPE. I REALLY NEED TO
FINISH IT BEFORE I GO.
- OH, COME ON. YOU CAN PUT IT
OFF FOR JUST A LITTLE WHILE.
- I CAN'T!
MY TEACHER WILL KILL ME!
- OKAY, OKAY, FINE.
I'LL JUST GO BY MYSELF.
- MAN, I'M SO GLAD THAT'S OVER.
HEY, GUYS. I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU HAVEN'T LEFT YET.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- JUST HANGING OUT!
- OH GREAT.
NOW IT'S RAINING HARDER.
OH WELL, I GUESS
I NEED TO CALL MIHO.
- WAIT, DON'T CALL HER YET.
UM...
- WHAT IS IT?
- WELL, UH...
HERE. YOU CAN BORROW MY UMBRELLA
IF YOU WANT TO, I GUESS.
- OH, THANKS.
BUT WHAT ARE YOU GONNA USE?
- OH, I'LL BE FINE.
MIKI AND I WERE JUST GOING
SOMEWHERE TOGETHER,
SO SHE'LL LET ME SHARE HERS.
- OKAY.
WELL, THANKS.
THAT'S VERY NICE OF YOU.
- SURE.
- SEE YA!
- UH, SUZUKA?
DO YOU HAVE FEELINGS
FOR AKITSUKI?
- WHY WOULD YOU
ASK ME THAT QUESTION?
- WELL, IT'S BECAUSE YOU'VE
ACTED KIND OF STRANGE
EVER SINCE YOU GOT BACK
FROM HIROSHIMA.
AND JUST NOW IT REALLY SEEMED
LIKE YOU WERE WAITING FOR HIM
SO THAT YOU COULD
GO HOME TOGETHER.
- NO, THAT'S NOT IT.
I JUST... UM...
I DON'T HAVE FEELINGS FOR YAMATO
LIKE THAT. DON'T BE SILLY!
- I SEE. I DIDN'T REALLY THINK
YOU FELT THAT WAY.
- LET'S GO, MIKI.
CAKE IS STARTING TO SOUND
REALLY GOOD ALL OF A SUDDEN.
- WELL ALL RIGHT THEN,
EVERYTHING IS ON ME TODAY,
SO EAT AS MUCH CAKE AS YOU WANT!
- MIKI...
- 'KAY?
- OKAY. THANKS.
- ( whistle blowing )
- OKAY! THAT'S IT FOR TODAY!
DON'T FORGET TO COOL DOWN!
- Track Members: OKAY!
-GOD, I'M SO GLAD IT'S OVER!
- HERE YOU GO, AKITSUKI. DO YOU
WANNA GO GET SOMETHING TO DRINK?
- UH, YEAH, THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
I DON'T SEE HIM HERE TODAY,
SO WE SHOULD BE FINE.
- ( giggles )
- AKITSUKI AND SAKURAI SEEM TO
BE PRETTY CLOSE THESE DAYS.
- WELL OF COURSE THEY ARE.
THEY HAVE BEEN
DATING FOR A WHILE.
I'M SURPRISED YOU DIDN'T
ALREADY KNOW THAT.
- WOW.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- YEAH. WEIRD, HUH?
- THERE YOU ARE.
LET'S GET GOING, SUZUKA.
- YEAH. 'KAY.
- I HAVE AN IDEA.
WE SHOULD GO DO KARAOKE.
I HOPE THEY HAVE
NANA'S NEW SINGLE ALREADY.
- WHO'S NANA?
- ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
SHE'S A SINGER! DUH!
- OH, RIGHT.
- I REALLY DON'T GET
KINUGASA SEMPAI.
I MEAN, WHY IS HE ONLY
THAT STRICT WITH ME?
- BECAUSE HE BELIEVES IN YOU.
- I GUESS.
- Nana: NANA'S SONGS ARE ONLY
PLAYED IN HIGH QUALITY AUDIO!
( Nana singing )
♪ BABY I'VE BEEN GOING CRAZY ♪
- WOW. THAT'S COOL.
- ♪ I LOVE YOU ♪
♪ YES, I ADORE YOU ♪
- ARE YOU ATTRACTED
TO NANA SHIRAKAWA?
- OH, NO, NOT AT ALL.
I WAS JUST THINKING
ABOUT BUYING
ONE OF THOSE REALLY
COOL MD PLAYERS!
- YOU WERE?
- YEAH. I PROMISE!
BUT THEY'RE SO DARN EXPENSIVE.
I COULDN'T AFFORD IT.
- I SEE.
- Waitress: WELL, HELLO THERE!
HOW ARE YOU, TODAY?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER, HONOKA?
- HUH?
I NOTICED YOU SEEM A LITTLE
UNEASY TODAY.
- NO. WELL, MAYBE A LITTLE.
I'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT YOU
A LOT TO A FRIEND OF MINE,
AND SHE REALLY WANTS TO
MEET YOU TODAY.
- WHAT? SHE DOES?
- MMM-HMM. I SENT HER
AN EMAIL AFTER PRACTICE
AND TOLD HER WE GOT OUT EARLY,
SO SHE'S ON HER WAY RIGHT NOW.
- OKAY. THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE SO JITTERY.
- I'M SORRY. I KNOW
THIS IS REALLY SUDDEN
AND I DON'T MEAN TO TROUBLE YOU.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME?
- OH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IT'S NO TROUBLE AT ALL.
BUT, UM, DO I LOOK OKAY?
- THERE YOU ARE!
I JUST GOT OUT OF WORK. I HOPE
YOU WEREN'T WAITING TOO LONG!
- OH MY GOSH.
OH MY GOSH!
- SO, THIS IS YOUR BOYFRIEND?
HE'S REALLY CUTE!
- SHOULDN'T YOU BE WEARING A
DISGUISE OR SOMETHING, NANA?
YOU NEED TO BE CAREFUL!
- NAH, IT'S TOO MUCH TROUBLE!
- WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
YOUR FRIEND WAS HER?
- SO, ARE YOU SURPRISED?
I'M NANA SHIRAKAWA.
NICE TO MEET YOU!
- UH, YEAH, VERY NICE
TO MEET YOU, TOO!
I'M A BIG FAN!
I JUST LOVE YOUR TV SHOW!
- I DON'T HAVE A TV SHOW.
- OH YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT!
- I'M SORRY, I GUESS YOU'RE
A LITTLE STARTLED, HUH?
- MAYBE A LITTLE.
- OH, MY GOSH. IT'S...
IT REALLY IS HER!
- EVERYONE'S STARING.
- WELL THEN,
LET'S GO SOMEWHERE ELSE!
- WOW. SO YOU TWO HAVE BEEN
FRIENDS SINCE JUNIOR HIGH?
- UM, YEAH.
- YEP. I GUESS YOU COULD SAY
WE'RE BEST FRIENDS, RIGHT?
THE OTHER KIDS AT SCHOOL ALWAYS
TREATED ME SO STRANGELY
BECAUSE OF MY CAREER. EVERYONE
ELSE WAS SO AFRAID TO TALK
TO ME, THEY MADE ME FEEL
LIKE SOME KIND OF FREAK.
I KNOW THEY WEREN'T
TRYING TO BE MEAN TO ME,
BUT I REALLY DIDN'T HAVE
ANY FRIENDS AT ALL.
- I'M SORRY, I GUESS SHOW
BUSINESS GETS PRETTY ROUGH, HUH?
- MMM-HMM.
ONE DAY, I HAD A REALLY
HORRIBLE TIME AT SCHOOL
AND DESPERATELY
NEEDED A CIGARETTE.
I STOPPED AT THE INARI
SHRINE TO LIGHT UP
ON MY WAY HOME FROM CLASS.
AND THAT'S WHEN
THE SHRINE MAIDEN
WHO WORKED THERE APPROACHED ME.
- YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULDN'T SMOKE.
IT'S REALLY BAD FOR YOU.
- WHAT? JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
- I'M SORRY, I CAN'T.
YOU GO TO THE SAME SCHOOL AS ME.
SO, WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU DON'T KNOW WHO I AM?
- THAT'S WHY I ASKED
WHAT YOUR NAME WAS.
- I THINK SHE INSULTED MY PRIDE
MORE THAN ANYTHING ELSE.
HOW DARE YOU! I DON'T NEED TO
LISTEN TO SOME BOSSY COSPLAYER!
- WHAT? THIS ISN'T A COSPLAY!
I WORK HERE!
HOW RUDE!
NOW GIVE ME YOUR CIGARETTE!
- NO WAY!
SHE WAS THE FIRST PERSON I MET
THAT TREATED ME LIKE
A HUMAN BEING.
- IT'S NOT ATTRACTIVE,
BELIEVE ME!
- BEFORE I KNEW IT, WE
HAD BECOME BEST FRIENDS,
AND IT'S BEEN THAT
WAY EVER SINCE.
- YEAH, I REMEMBER.
- SO LISTEN, YAMATO,
AS HONOKA'S BEST FRIEND,
I HAVE A FEW THINGS I WANNA SAY.
- HUH? YOU DO?
- THIS GIRL HAS HARDLY ANY
EXPERIENCE WITH GUYS AT ALL.
SHE BARELY EVEN KNOWS
WHAT DATING MEANS.
- I WOULDN'T GO THAT FAR!
- SO DON'T GO AROUND
TRYING TO FORCE YOURSELF
ON HER. IT'S NOT COOL!
TRY BEING MORE GENTLE
FROM NOW ON, OKAY?
- STOP IT NANA, SERIOUSLY.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY THOSE
KINDS OF THINGS TO HIM.
- HONOKA! YOU NEED TO
STOP LETTING PEOPLE
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF YOU!
HEY! JUST WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING?
- TO THE RESTROOM!
- YEAH RIGHT. SHE ALWAYS RUNS
OFF WHEN SHE GETS EMBARRASSED.
- I'M KIND OF EMBARRASSED, TOO.
- OH WELL. YOU SHOULD SING
SOMETHING WHILE WE'RE WAITING!
- ME?
- SINCE WE'RE HERE,
DO YOU MIND IF I PRACTICE
SINGING A FEW SONGS?
THERE ARE SOME I WANNA TRY,
BUT I JUST DON'T HAVE
THE CONFIDENCE YET.
- ♪ THE CARP, THE CARP,
THE CARP OF HIROSHIMA ♪
- Nana: WHAT SONG IS THAT?
- ♪ MARCHING ON,
TOWARDS A VICTORY ♪
♪ NOTHING IN YOUR WAY
CAN EVER KEEP YOU DOWN ♪
♪ WHEN THE FIGHTING
CARP TAKE THE FIELD ♪
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- HELLO.
- YOU ARE SUCH A JERK!
YOU'VE ONLY BEEN DATING
HONOKA FOR A MONTH
AND ALREADY YOU'RE
CHEATING ON HER!
- NO. HEY! NO I'M NOT.
- HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT?
- SUZUKA, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING IN HERE?
- YAMATO'S CHEATING!
- THAT'S NANA.
WAIT JUST A MINUTE! WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE WITH HER, AKITSUKI?
- UM, WELL, I'M NOT WITH...
- WHAT'S GOING ON HERE?
ARE YOU DATING THREE GIRLS?
- NO!
- WELL THEN, YOU'VE GOT
SOME EXPLAINING TO DO!
- IF I COULD GET A WORD IN, I...
- YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING ME!
ARE YOU REALLY GOING
OUT WITH NANA?
- NO! I'M NOT!
- OH REALLY?
- WOW. WHAT'S GOING ON IN HERE?
- OKAY. SO YOU GUYS ARE
ALL FRIENDS FROM TRACK.
I WAS SO CONFUSED!
- ME TOO! I NEVER THOUGHT
HONOKA WOULD BE GOOD FRIENDS
WITH A CELEBRITY!
- UH. OH.
- SORRY.
- IT'S OKAY.
DON'T WORRY 'BOUT IT.
- WELL, SINCE WE'RE ALL HERE,
WHY DON'T WE SING
SOMETHING TOGETHER?
I THINK THAT'D BE
FUN, DON'T YOU?
- OH ABSOLUTELY!
I'M GONNA GO TELL THEM
THAT WE'RE GONNA BE
STAYING LONGER.
- GREAT! COME ON YOU GUYS,
HAVE A SEAT!
- I NEED TO MAKE ROOM FOR MIKI
WHEN SHE COMES BACK.
- UM, AKITSUKI. ER, THERE'S
ROOM OVER HERE IF YOU WANT.
- OKAY, THANKS.
- YOU READY? THIS ONE'S OFF
MY LATEST ALBUM, OKAY?
♪ STAR! ALL MY LOVE FOR YOU ♪
- ALL RIGHT!
- WOW, I CAN'T BELIEVE WE
ACTUALLY HAVE THE REAL SINGER
IN FRONT OF US. THAT'S SO COOL!
- NANA, YOU'RE AMAZING!
- ♪ I LOVE YOU ♪
- NANA'S SO AWESOME!
- AW, THANKS YOU GUYS!
- GET READY! 'CAUSE YOU'RE
SINGING NEXT, SUZUKA! HERE.
SO AKITSUKI, ARE YOU GONNA SING?
- NO, I'M OKAY.
- YAMATO, DON'T TELL ME
THAT YOU ONLY KNOW
HOW TO SING BASEBALL SONGS?
WELL I'VE NEVER HEARD YOU SING
ANYTHING ELSE BEFORE.
ARE YOU TONE-DEAF OR SOMETHING?
- I CAN SING.
JUST GIVE ME A SECOND.
- UM. JUST DO
YOUR BEST, AKITSUKI.
- I'M NOT JUST GONNA SIT HERE
AND LET HER CALL ME TONE-DEAF.
WHERE IS IT?
HERE IT IS.
- Suzuka: YAMATO, YOU CAN'T SING
THAT. THAT'S THE ONE I PICKED.
- IT IS?
OH SHOOT. WELL,
I GUESS I'LL JUST HAVE TO PICK
ANOTHER ONE THEN.
- OH, JUST MAKE IT
A DUET AND SING!
- I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS WE COULD DO THAT.
- YEAH, SURE. WHY NOT?
I'M OKAY WITH IT.
- HERE'S THE MICROPHONE!
NOW TRY YOUR BEST
NOT TO SING OFF-KEY, ALL RIGHT?
- SHUT UP!
JUST TRY NOT TO DIE OF SHOCK.
- ( music playing )
OH, NO!
THAT'S NOT THE SONG I WANTED!
SO YOU'RE SINGING
SOLO AFTER ALL!
- OH. THAT'S COOL.
- YEAH. SORRY 'BOUT THAT.
THE NUMBERS LOOK A LOT ALIKE.
- UH, AKITSUKI,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
- I SWORE I WASN'T GOING
TO DO ANYTHING
TO HURT HONOKA'S
FEELINGS ANYMORE.
- MAN! I SANG SO MUCH!
- THAT WAS FUN!
- WELL, SUZUKA AND I STILL
HAVE STUFF TO DO
BEFORE WE HAVE TO GO HOME.
- OKAY.
- WE DEFINITELY NEED TO
GET TOGETHER AGAIN SOON.
- SOUNDS GOOD.
- LATER. BE CAREFUL.
- SEE YA.
- WELL, I GUESS
WE SHOULD GO, TOO.
- YEAH. NANA?
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
- WELL, UH, YOU GUYS DON'T
MIND IF I WALK HOME WITH YOU
SO I CAN CATCH UP WITH HONOKA?
BESIDES, SOMEONE NEEDS
TO MAKE SURE YOU DON'T TRY
TO DO ANYTHING TO HER AGAIN!
- HUH? BUT I...
- WELL ALL RIGHT THEN,
THIS IS IT.
THANK YOU FOR WALKING ME
ALL THE WAY HOME, NANA.
- IT WAS MY PLEASURE. REALLY.
IT WAS SO GREAT GETTING
TO SEE YOU AGAIN,
BUT I NEED TO GRAB A CAB
AND HEAD HOME.
- YEAH, I KNOW.
I UNDERSTAND. AKITSUKI,
YOU BE SAFE GOING HOME! BYE!
- BYE. SEE YA.
- GIVE ME A CALL LATER, OKAY?
- YOU'RE REALLY GOOD TO HER,
YAMATO. SHE'S LUCKY TO HAVE YOU.
I'VE HAD MY EYE ON YOU
ALL DAY TODAY.
PRETTY TRUSTWORTHY.
YOU'RE A GOOD KID.
IT'S NOT EASY TO FIND A KIND AND
RELIABLE BOYFRIEND, BELIEVE ME.
SO I'M REALLY HAPPY FOR HONOKA.
- OH NO, I'M THE LUCKY ONE HERE.
HONOKA'S SUCH A GOOD PERSON,
NOT TO MENTION A GREAT COOK!
I DON'T DESERVE SOMEONE
AS SWEET AS HER.
SHE'S AMAZING. SO I'M
TRYING TO WORK HARDER
AT BEING A BETTER
BOYFRIEND FOR HER.
I WANNA DO EVERYTHING
PERFECTLY. SHE DESERVES IT.
I DON'T EVER WANNA DO ANYTHING
TO HURT HER FEELINGS.
- ARE YOU STUPID? SERIOUSLY.
- HUH?
- SO, YOU WANT TO BE A BETTER
BOYFRIEND FOR HER SO YOU
"WON'T HURT HER FEELINGS?"
DO YOU EVEN KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING?
- JUST A MINUTE!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU JUST GOT DONE TELLING ME
WHAT A GREAT GUY I AM
A SECOND AGO!
- AT KARAOKE, DID YOU JUST
STOP SINGING WITH SUZUKA
SO YOU COULD AVOID HURTING
HONOKA'S FEELINGS?
- WELL, YEAH.
- SO YOU DECIDED TO REACH OVER
AND HOLD HER HAND.
IS THIS WHAT YOU MEAN BY BEING
A BETTER BOYFRIEND TO HER?
THE ONLY THING YOU THINK ABOUT
IS HOW SHE REACTS TO YOU.
- OH PLEASE TELL ME WHAT
I SHOULD HAVE DONE!
SHOULD I HAVE JUST
SUNG WITH ASAHINA
AND IGNORED HONOKA ALL NIGHT?
- THAT'S NOT WHAT I'M SAYING.
YOU THINK ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS MAKE SMALL,
SUPERFICIAL GESTURES
AND THAT MAKES YOU A GOOD GUY?
WELL, IT'S THAT LOGIC
THAT MAKES YOU AN IDIOT!
- OH. IS THAT WHAT YOU THINK?
WELL GUESS WHAT?
CALLING SOMEONE AN IDIOT
MAKES YOU AN IDIOT!
YOU THINK YOU KNOW EVERYTHING
JUST 'CAUSE YOU'RE IN SHOW BIZ?
FREAK!
- ( sighs )
IRRESPONSIBLE, NAME CALLING,
AND A QUICK TEMPER?
YOU'RE LIKE A LITTLE KID.
IT'S UNFORTUNATE.
- EXCUSE ME?
- NO WONDER YOU FEEL LIKE YOU
HAVE TO PUT ON AN ACT
IN FRONT OF HONOKA!
I BET THIS IDEAL BOYFRIEND
THING IS QUITE
A STRETCH FOR YOU, HUH?
- WHAT? I'M NOT ACTING AROUND
HER! WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
AND I'M NOT BEING INSINCERE!
- IS THAT SO? BECAUSE
IT ALWAYS LOOKS
LIKE YOU'RE TRYING TOO HARD
TO ME. EVEN NOW.
- WELL, I'M NOT.
- LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
DO YOU EVEN KNOW WHAT KINDS
OF THINGS HONOKA LIKES?
WHAT ARE HER HOBBIES?
CAN YOU EVEN TELL ME
WHEN HER BIRTHDAY IS?
- WELL...
NO, I CAN'T. I DON'T KNOW
ANY OF THOSE THINGS.
- YEAH. YOU DON'T REALLY LIKE
HONOKA AT ALL, DO YOU?
AS A MATTER OF FACT, YOU DON'T
EVEN KNOW WHO SHE IS, YAMATO!
THE ONLY REASON YOU WANNA
BE A GOOD BOYFRIEND TO HER
IS SO YOU CAN FEEL GOOD
ABOUT YOURSELF,
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
LISTEN, YOU TOLD ME YOU DIDN'T
WANNA HURT HONOKA'S FEELINGS.
WELL, YOU ARE HURTING
HER BY DATING HER
WITH THAT THOUGHTLESS
ATTITUDE.
- SHE'S RIGHT.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT
HONOKA AS A PERSON.
I HAVEN'T EVEN BEEN TRYING TO
GET TO KNOW HER BETTER.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE
HER BOYFRIEND.
- IT'S SEPTEMBER 16TH.
HER BIRTHDAY,
IT'S THREE DAYS FROM TODAY.
THAT DOESN'T GIVE YOU A
WHOLE LOT OF TIME TO GET
HER A PRESENT, SO
YOU BETTER HURRY.
YAMATO, I'M NOT TRYING TO
BREAK YOU GUYS UP OR ANYTHING,
BUT THIS IS MY BEST FRIEND,
TRY LOOKING AT HER.
I WANT YOU TO SEE HER
FOR THE PERSON SHE IS.
STOP WORRYING SO MUCH
ABOUT BEING PERFECT
AND REALLY GET TO KNOW HER.
- RIGHT. THANKS.
- WELL, THAT'S REALLY ALL I
WANTED TO SAY. SEE YA.
- YEAH.
I NEED TO GET TO KNOW HONOKA.
I NEED TO LOOK AT HER.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WHEN I TURN AROUND
YOU'RE RIGHT THERE NEXT TO ME ♪
♪ ON YOUR FACE A SMILE
SO COMFORTING AND FAMILIAR ♪
♪ THE CLOSER YOU BECAME
THE LESS THAT I COULD SEE ♪
♪ AND NOW I'M WONDERING
SO LOST AND ALL ALONE ♪
♪ PEOPLE CHANGE
A LITTLE AT A TIME ♪
♪ AND NOW I KNOW I'M CHANGING ♪
♪ WHEN I CALL YOUR NAME ♪
♪ SHOUT IT OUT INTO THE SKY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN I WILL FIND ♪
♪ THE LOVE I KEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'RE WITH ME ♪
♪ AND YOU TAKE MY HAND ♪
♪ SOMEHOW EVERYTHING ♪
♪ SEEMS TO WORK ITSELF
ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ WHEN I SEE YOUR EYES ♪
♪ YOU'RE STARING BACK AT MINE ♪
♪ THERE INSIDE I FIND ♪
♪ A LOVE THAT NEVER DIES ♪
♪ TOGETHER I KNOW
WE'LL FIND A WAY ♪
♪ JUST YOU AND I ♪
- Yamato: I'M FREAKING OUT.
HONOKA'S BIRTHDAY
IS IN TWO DAYS.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHAT TO GET HER.
WHERE SHOULD I GO?
I HATE SHOPPING.
HEY, ASAHINA,
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD HELP ME?
- HUH?
- NOTHING. NEVER MIND.
- SURE.
- HUH?