- Yamato:
IT TOOK ME SEVEN HOURS TO GET
FROM THE HIROSHIMA
COUNTRYSIDE TO TOKYO.
I MADE THE TRIP SO I
COULD START MY FIRST DAY
OF HIGH SCHOOL AT A NEW PLACE.
I WAS WALKING BY MY NEW
SCHOOL TO CHECK IT OUT
WHEN I SAW THIS GIRL.
NOT JUST ANY GIRL.
SHE WAS AMAZING.
I'D NEVER SEEN ANYONE LIKE HER.
SHE WAS INCREDIBLE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP THE BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATH A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- YAMATO, WHAT'S TAKING YOU
SO LONG?
- MIHO, YOU'LL CATCH YOUR DEATH
OUT HERE. WAIT FOR HIM INSIDE.
- I'M TOO NERVOUS. HE SAID HE
WOULD BE HERE AT TWO O'CLOCK.
I HOPE AUNTIE DIDN'T CHANGE HER
MIND AND MAKE HIM STAY HOME.
THAT WOULD JUST SEND YAMATO
INTO A TAILSPIN.
- DON'T YOU WORRY.
MY SISTER SAID HE COULD
COME TO TOKYO
AS LONG AS HE STAYED WITH US
WHILE HE WAS HERE.
MAYBE HE GOT DISTRACTED,
RIGHT, GORO?
HE'S NOT EXACTLY THE
MOST RESPONSIBLE KID ON EARTH.
- SORRY, I'M LATE. I GOT
DISTRACTED WALKING AROUND.
YAMATO AKITSUKI REPORTING
FOR DUTY AND AT YOUR SERVICE.
- WELL, I'M GLAD
YOU MADE IT, YAMATO.
BUT YOU REALLY WORRIED
MY PRINCESS.
- OH, SORRY.
- YOU... YOU'RE
SO IRRESPONSIBLE!
- MIHO, I CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW MUCH YOU'VE GROWN!
YOU'VE GOTTA BE IN
THE SEVENTH GRADE BY NOW.
- EIGHTH GRADE.
YOU REALLY DON'T THINK TOO OFTEN
BEFORE YOU TALK, DO YOU?
- YEAH, YEAH, I KNOW, I KNOW.
YOU CAUGHT ME THIS TIME.
MY MOM TOLD ME
YOU GUYS RENOVATED,
BUT THIS IS BIGGER
THAN I EXPECTED.
- YEAH. IT'S A NICE CHANGE.
- Ayano: THE BATH AREA
WAS REMODELED
INTO A DAY SPA AS WELL.
- SO THIS IS MY NEW HOME.
THE PLACE WHERE I'LL BE
STARTING A WHOLE NEW LIFE.
I REALLY APPRECIATE YOU
LETTING ME COME LIVE
WITH YOU, AUNT AYANO.
- STOP ACTING SO FORMAL.
I'M YOUR AUNT.
- ACTUALLY, WHILE I'M HERE,
YOU'RE MY LANDLADY.
- I'M YOUR AUNT FIRST. NOW GET
INSIDE OUT OF THE RAIN.
WE'VE ALREADY SENT YOUR LUGGAGE
TO YOUR ROOM, SO YOU'RE ALL SET.
- YOU GOTTA BE WORN OUT, YAMATO.
COME ON IN AND RELAX.
- OH, OKAY.
- YOUR ROOM IS 301.
IT'S UPSTAIRS.
- JUST SO YOU KNOW,
THIS APARTMENT COMPLEX
IS FOR WOMEN ONLY.
- SO DON'T YOU GO MAKING
ANY TROUBLE FOR THEM.
- HEY, I'M NOT A TROUBLEMAKER.
- I THINK YAMATO IS GOING TO
WORK OUT JUST FINE.
BESIDES, WE COULD USE
SOME MALE HELP AROUND THIS PLACE
AND HE'S BETTER THAN NOTHING.
- GIVE ME SOME CREDIT, WILL YA?
I'M GETTING ROOM AND BOARD
PLUS PAY FOR MY SERVICES,
SO I'LL DO THE BEST JOB I CAN
AT WHATEVER YOU LIKE.
EVEN IF IT'S SIMPLE
LIKE CLEANING THE BATH.
- CLEANING THE BATH IS A LOT
HARDER THAN YOU THINK IT IS.
I DON'T THINK
I'D MAKE LIGHT OF IT.
NO SWEAT. I HAVE CONFIDENCE
IN ME AND YOU WILL, TOO.
FINE, SO MAYBE IT'S A BIT
HARDER THAN I THOUGHT.
BUT THIS PLACE IS HUGE.
THEY'VE GOT JACUZZIS,
THEY'VE GOT SAUNAS.
IT'S TOTALLY HIGH END
AND MODERN.
I BET THIS PLACE FILLS UP
WITH GIRLS FROM THE SCHOOL.
I WONDER IF SHE'LL BE HERE.
- YAMATO, WHY AREN'T
YOU DONE YET?
FOR SUCH A SIMPLE JOB,
YOU SURE ARE TAKING FOREVER.
YOU NEEDED TO BE DONE WITH THIS
LIKE AN HOUR AGO.
- OKAY. I'LL TRY IT LIKE THIS.
NOT BAD FORM, HUH?
- YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO IT
FASTER THAN THAT.
OKAY, THAT'S A LITTLE BETTER.
- THEY'RE HERE.
- WHO'S HERE?
- CUSTOMERS! COLLEGE GIRLS
WHO LIVE IN THE COMPLEX
LISTEN, YOU'VE GOT TO BE CAREFUL
AROUND THEM.
THEY CAN BE VERY DANGEROUS.
- DANGEROUS? HOW?
- GREAT, THEY'RE NOT DONE
CLEANING OUT THE BATH YET.
- HOW MUCH LONGER
ARE WE GONNA HAVE TO WAIT?
- ( gasps )
- HEY, I HEARD ABOUT YOU.
AREN'T YOU YAMATO,
THE LANDLADY'S NEPHEW?
- Oh, I'M SO EMBARRASSED.
ALL I'M WEARING IS A TOWEL.
WHAT A BAD FIRST IMPRESSION.
- YOU KNOW, THE LANDLADY
FORGOT TO MENTION TO ME
HOW CUTE YOU ARE.
- ( exclaims )
- NO!
YAMATO, OUT OF THE BATH. NOW.
YOU CAN FINISH LATER.
- ( exclaims )
THIS IS NOT WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
UH... IT'S NOT...
IT WAS JUST A MISTAKE!
AS USUAL, MY TIMING
WAS JUST PERFECT.
THAT'S WHAT I GET FOR
WISHING SHE'D STOP BY.
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN MORE SPECIFIC
AS TO WHEN.
GEEZ, SHE MUST THINK
I'M A TOTAL PERV.
( screaming )
- Miho: YAMATO?
- Ayano: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- UGH! YOU CREEP! GET OUT!
- Miho: THAT'S SUZUKA'S ROOM!
- I THOUGHT I WAS GOING INTO MY
ROOM. I SWEAR! I DIDN'T KNOW!
- WHAT ARE YOU, BLIND?
LOOK AT THE DOORPLATE!
- IT SAYS SUZUKA ASAHINA
RIGHT THERE NEXT TO THE DOOR.
YOUR ROOM IS OVER HERE.
NUMBER 301.
- I JUST MOVED IN SO I'M STILL
GETTING USED TO THIS PLACE.
- YOU'RE SO CARELESS, YAMATO.
- I TOLD YOU NOT TO MAKE ANY
TROUBLE FOR THESE GIRLS!
- I'M REALLY SORRY
ABOUT THIS, ASAHINA.
NOW, APOLOGIZE
TO THE YOUNG LADY.
- SORRY FOR BARGING IN ON YOU.
I NEVER EVEN CONSIDERED
THAT SHE'D BE LIVING RIGHT
NEXT DOOR TO ME.
THIS IS ONE EXCELLENT DINNER
YOU COOKED UP, AUNT AYANO.
IF I DIDN'T FEED YOU,
WHO KNOWS WHAT KIND OF GRUEL
YOU'D SHOVEL DOWN YOUR THROAT.
I CAN FEED MYSELF.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M A DOG.
- THAT'S TRUE. AT LEAST A DOG
WOULD KNOW WHICH APARTMENT
HE'S SUPPOSED TO GO TO.
- I TOLD YOU,
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
- I REALLY APPRECIATE YOU
INVITING ME TO DINNER.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE I HAD A HOME-COOKED MEAL.
YOU'RE WELCOME OVER
ANY TIME I'M COOKING, ASAHINA.
- WHY IS IT
YOU'RE SO NICE TO HER,
WHEN YOU TREAT ME
LIKE I'M A FOOL?
- BECAUSE, UNLIKE YOU,
SHE'S GOT THE HOPES
OF ALMOST EVERYONE AROUND HERE
WEIGHING DOWN ON HER.
IT'S GOTTA BE EXHAUSTING.
- ASAHINA'S AN AMAZING TALENT.
SHE'S BEGINNING HER FRESHMAN
YEAR AT AOBA HIGH SCHOOL
JUST LIKE YOU. SHE
GOT SCOUTED LAST YEAR
AND OFFERED A SPOT ON
THE TRACK AND FIELD TEAM.
WHILE YOU MADE IT IN
AFTER SITTING ON A WAITING LIST.
- SHE WAS SCOUTED?
THAT'S IMPRESSIVE.
SO THAT'S WHY SHE WAS
PRACTICING ALONE
WHILE EVERYONE WAS ON BREAK.
- MY MONEY IS ON HER MAKING
THE OLYMPIC TEAM SOMETIME SOON.
AND WHEN THAT DAY COMES AROUND,
I'LL TELL EVERYONE SHE USED TO
EAT DINNER AT MY PLACE.
- WELL, I HOPE
I DON'T DISAPPOINT YOU.
- SHE'S SO COOL. ALMOST PERFECT.
THERE'S NO WAY SHE COULD BE
THE SAME AGE AS ME.
- Ayano: ASAHINA, DO YOU WANT
ANOTHER BOWL?
- OH, NO THANK YOU. I'M FULL.
- FOR SOMEONE SO ACTIVE,
YOU SURE HAVE A TINY STOMACH.
- NOT ME!
- THE MOVE HASN'T SLOWED DOWN
YOUR APPETITE.
- I'M A GROWING BOY!
SO, YOU WERE SCOUTED. I CAN'T
BELIEVE IT. THAT'S AWESOME.
WHEN I PLAYED BASEBALL IN JUNIOR
HIGH, I COULDN'T CATCH OR HIT.
THE WHOLE TEAM LAUGHED AT ME AND
MADE FUN OF ME ALL THE TIME.
I GOT SO FED UP WITH
IT ONE DAY THAT I TOLD EVERYONE
I'D BUY THEM ALL SODAS
IF I COULDN'T GET A HIT.
AND WHAT DO YA KNOW, I GOT
MY FIRST BASE HIT THAT DAY.
JUST CALL ME LUCKY, I GUESS.
- THAT'S SO LIKE YOU, YAMATO.
- MMM-HMM. IT'S ALL
OR NOTHING WITH YOU.
- WHAT WERE YOU GONNA DO
IF YOU STRUCK OUT?
YOU KNOW, I DON'T REALLY THINK I
CONSIDERED FAILURE AN OPTION,
SO I GUESS APOLOGIZE.
- NOTHING GETS UNDER
MY SKIN MORE THAN
IRRESPONSIBLE THINKING.
THANKS AGAIN FOR THE MEAL.
- WHAT THE HECK IS HER PROBLEM?
SHE DOESN'T HAVE TO ACT
SO DAMN SERIOUS.
- ( doorbell rings )
- MIHO? WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
- SUZUKA, LISTEN. YOU'VE GOT
THIS WHOLE THING WRONG.
PLEASE DON'T HATE YAMATO.
I KNOW HE CAN BE
CLUMSY AND CARELESS
WITH THE THINGS HE SAYS,
BUT HE'S GOT SOME GOOD
QUALITIES, TOO.
HE'S NICE AND FUNNY,
A GOOD COOK, HE LIKES DOGS.
AND IN THE BATH, WHEN HE FELL
ON MEGUMI, IT WASN'T HIS FAULT.
SAOTOME HAD BEEN TEASING YAMATO.
AND THAT'S WHEN I JUMPED IN
AND PUSHED HIM OUT OF THE WAY.
- SO THAT'S WHY YOU CAME?
- YEAH.
- YOU LOOK AFTER HIM WELL,
DON'T YOU?
- CALL IT MATERNAL
INSTINCT OR SOMETHING,
BUT I DON'T FEEL COMFORTABLE
LEAVING HIM ALONE.
- THANKS.
- YOU'RE WELCOME. HEY.
WOW, HE'S CUTE.
IS THAT YOUR BOYFRIEND
OR A TRACK BUDDY?
- WELL, HE'S, UH...
- IT'S GOTTA BE SOMEONE
YOU ADMIRE.
HE LOOKS A LOT LIKE YAMATO,
DOESN'T HE?
- WHAT?
- OH, NOTHING.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
JUST DON'T HATE YAMATO, OKAY?
THAT'S ALL I WANTED TO SAY.
SEE YA.
- I DON'T THINK
THEY LOOK ALIKE AT ALL.
- WHAT IS UP WITH ASAHINA?
DID I DO SOMETHING WRONG
WITHOUT KNOWING?
OKAY, I DID DO SOMETHING WRONG,
BUT IT WAS AN HONEST MISTAKE.
I MEAN, I SAID I WAS SORRY.
- ( doorbell rings )
- ( gasps ) I... I WONDER
IF SHE'S COMING TO APOLOGIZE.
I DOUBT IT. THAT DOESN'T
SEEM LIKE HER STYLE.
- BOTTOMS UP, YAMATO!
- I DON'T THINK THIS IS
A GOOD IDEA, SAOTOME.
- OH, HE DOESN'T MIND!
- WHAT THE HELL?
- LET'S KICK THIS PARTY
OFF RIGHT!
- Yamato: ARE YOU DRUNK?
- NO!
- 'CAUSE YOU SMELL
LIKE YOU'VE FERMENTED.
- OUCH! WATCH WHERE YOU'RE
GOING, BUDDY! THAT HURT!
- Megumi: SAOTOME, YOU'RE
TALKING TO THE WALL.
COME ON NOW. OKAY?
- SO, YAMUTO, YOU GOT
ANY BOOZE AROUND HERE?
- Megumi:
JUST STOP AND TURN AROUND
AND SIT DOWN BEFORE
YOU FALL DOWN.
- PICK-ME-UP-AND-KNOCK-ME-DOWN,
IF YOU CATCH MY DRIFT.
- OKAY? COME ON.
- NOW DRINK UP, YOU!
- UH, I'M NOT THIRSTY.
- I'M SORRY. I'LL TAKE
HER BACK TO HER ROOM
AS SOON AS SHE CAN
STAND ON HER OWN.
- HOW ABOUT NOW?
- OH, MEG! YOU SPOILSPORT!
THIS IS WHY YOU DON'T EVEN
HAVE ANY BOYFRIENDS.
- HEY! STOP IT!
DO YOU MIND NOT AIRING
MY DIRTY LAUNDRY?
- YOU REALLY NEED
A DRINK, SISTER.
- ( Megumi coughs )
- PLEASE DON'T THROW UP.
- THIS BOTTLE IS ALMOST EMPTY.
HAVE YOU BEEN DRINKING MY STUFF?
- THIS GIRL'S CERTIFIABLE.
- Girl 1: SHOW THAT HIGH SCHOOL
TRACK TEAM WHAT YOU CAN DO!
- Girl 2: WE WISH YOU
ALL THE SUCCESS IN THE WORLD!
- Teacher 1: THAT'S INCREDIBLE!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
YOU CLEARED 169 CENTIMETERS
ON THAT JUMP!
YOU NOW HOLD THE RECORD FOR
THE HIGHEST JUMP IN KANAGAWA!
- Teacher 2:
YOU THINK WE'RE EXCITED,
YOU SHOULD TALK TO
THE PRINCIPAL!
- Teacher 3: YOU ARE THE PRIDE
OF OUR SCHOOL NOW.
- 169 CENTIMETERS.
I'VE GOTTEN MORE ATTENTION
SINCE THAT JUMP
THAN I KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH.
TO BE HONEST,
IT JUST MAKES ME NERVOUS.
EVERYONE EXPECTS
ME TO DO IT AGAIN,
BUT THIS TIME, JUMP EVEN HIGHER.
EACH TIME, THEY WANT
A LITTLE MORE FROM ME.
- ARE YOU LISTENING
TO ME ANYMORE?
- OF COURSE.
EVERY WORD IS SACRED.
- ALL GUYS ARE JUST LIKE YOU.
YOU SMILE AND YOU TALK TO ME
BUT YOU'RE REALLY ONLY GAWKING
AT MY BOOBS.
MY NAME IS MEGUMI MATSUMOTO,
NOT TITS MCGEE, GOT IT!
- THERE'S NOTHING I LOVE
MORE THAN A DRUNKEN LECTURE.
- PAY ATTENTION!
- I AM!
- I HIT IT, DIDN'T I? YOUR
GAZE IS TRANSFIXED
ON MY BOOBS RIGHT NOW.
- NO , I'M JUST LISTENING.
- WHY DON'T YOU TAKE A PICTURE?
IT'LL LAST LONGER!
- I DON'T WANNA SEE THOSE!
- YOU'RE JUST A PERVERT!
- I'M STILL TOO HEAVY.
- (Megumi and Saotome snoring )
- FINALLY, THEY
ACTUALLY PASSED OUT.
BUT WHAT DO I DO WITH THEM NOW?
CRAP! IT'S MIDNIGHT.
I GOTTA CLEAN THE BATH.
I BET ASAHINA HEARD EVERY WORD
THAT CAME OUTTA MY ROOM TONIGHT.
IF SHE DIDN'T HATE ME ALREADY,
I BET SHE DOES NOW.
COME ON. YOU MEAN
I LEFT THE LIGHTS ON, TOO?
AUNT AYANO'S GONNA BE REALLY
MAD! I AM SO DEAD.
ASAHINA! COME ON,
WAKE UP, ASAHINA!
OPEN THE DOOR!
OH, GREAT. IT'S STUCK.
ASAHINA! ASAHINA! WAKE UP!
I CAN'T LEAVE YOU IN THERE.
YOU... YOU'VE GOTTA WAKE UP!
COME ON!
THIS'LL PROBABLY
COME OUT OF MY CHECK.
PLEASE, ASAHINA, WAKE UP!
ASAHINA!
- Ayano: DON'T WORRY ABOUT HER.
SHE'S JUST DEHYDRATED
AT THIS POINT.
BUT SHE DRANK SOME WATER
AND HER TEMPERATURE HAS
GONE DOWN TO NORMAL.
- OH, GOOD.
- JUST FOR THE RECORD,
RUNNING UP TO ME AND
SCREAMING, "ASAHINA IS DEAD!"
WAS PROBABLY NOT THE
MOST EFFECTIVE WAY
TO APPROACH THE SITUATION.
- SHE DIDN'T RESPOND TO ME
AT ALL AND WHO KNOWS HOW LONG
SHE WAS TRAPPED
IN THERE. I PANICKED.
- AND NOW I'M PANICKING,
THANKS TO THE SAUNA DOOR
BEING BUSTED OFF ITS HINGES.
- I'M SORRY. I PUSHED AS HARD AS
I COULD BUT IT WOULDN'T BUDGE.
- BECAUSE YOU HAVE TO PULL IT
FROM THE OUTSIDE TO OPEN IT.
- ( laughs ) I MUST HAVE
BEEN TOO FOCUSED
ON GETTING ASAHINA OUT OF THERE.
- I LOVE YOUR DESIRE TO HELP.
IT'S ONE OF YOUR MOST
ENDEARING QUALITIES.
HOW ABOUT I GO
CLEAN THE BATH FOR YOU.
YOU JUST MAKE SURE SHE GETS
SOME WATER IF SHE NEEDS IT.
- OKAY.
SORRY ABOUT ALL THIS, ASAHINA.
IF I HAD CLEANED THE BATH
AN HOUR EARLIER YOU'D BE FINE.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- I... I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE AWAKE!
- WELL, YOU TALK LOUDER
THAN A TRAIN.
AND WHY DID YOU
KICK IN THE DOOR?
ARE YOU CRAZY OR SOMETHING?
- YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S CRAZY!
I WOULDN'T HAVE HAD TO
BREAK DOWN THE DOOR
IF YOU HADN'T FALLEN ASLEEP
IN THE SAUNA.
THE INSTRUCTIONS
OUTSIDE THE DOOR SAY
"MAXIMUM TWELVE MINUTES".
MAYBE YOU SHOULD TRY READING
THEM SOMETIME
INSTEAD OF POINTING FINGERS
AT PEOPLE WHO SAVE YOU!
- YEAH, I READ THEM.
- THEN DO WHAT THEY SAY!
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHAT
COULD'VE HAPPENED TO YOU...
- I'M THE ONE WHO ALMOST DIED,
SO BACK OFF ALREADY!
I KEPT THINKING TO MYSELF
THAT I COULD JUMP HIGHER
IF I COULD JUST LOSE
A FEW EXTRA POUNDS.
YOU KNOW WHAT PEOPLE SAY?
"GOTTA BEAT YOUR RECORD!"
WELL, 169 CENTIMETERS
ISN'T EASY, NOT FOR ANY ATHLETE.
BUT THEY STILL EXPECT ME
TO JUMP HIGHER.
AND NOW EVERY TIME I
WALK OUT ONTO THAT TRACK,
THE BAR LOOKS LIKE
IT'S BEEN RAISED.
BUT IT'S ALWAYS SET AT EXACTLY
THE SAME HEIGHT.
169.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO FAIL.
- I HAD NO IDEA.
WELL, LISTEN. I'M DEFINITELY
NOT A TRACK EXPERT
AND I CERTAINLY DON'T HAVE
ANY HIGH JUMP EXPERIENCE
TO DRAW FROM HERE,
BUT... I DO HAVE A FEELING
THAT IF YOU DID IT ONCE,
YOU'LL BE ABLE TO DO IT AGAIN.
- THAT MAKES
NO SENSE WHATSOEVER.
- YOU CONCERN YOURSELF
WAY TOO MUCH WITH WHAT
OTHER PEOPLE THINK
AND SAY, ASAHINA.
YOU KEEP DOING THE HIGH JUMP
BECAUSE IT SPEAKS TO YOU, RIGHT?
AND YOU LOVE IT?
- OF COURSE. MORE THAN ANYTHING.
- THEN THE ONLY REASON
YOU SHOULD DO IT
IS BECAUSE YOU LOVE IT SO MUCH.
IF YOU DON'T, YOU'LL END UP
LOOKING LIKE THIS.
- I'M NOT GONNA LOOK LIKE THAT!
- WELL, YOU SEEM TO BE
FEELING BETTER.
SO IT LOOKS LIKE MY JOB HERE
IS FINISHED.
- HEY, WAIT!
PLEASE DON'T TELL ANYONE
WHAT I SAID.
THE LAST THING I NEED IS
PEOPLE KNOWING WHAT SCARES ME.
- I DON'T KNOW. THEY'RE
SOME JUICY TIDBITS
YOU'VE JUST SPILLED.
- YAMATO!
PROMISE ME YOU WON'T TELL A SOUL
WHAT YOU KNOW.
- I PROMISE.
- THANKS. NOW WOULD YOU GET ME
A GLASS OF WATER?
- YEAH, SURE.
- AND ANOTHER TOWEL?
- DON'T PUSH IT.
I THOUGHT SHE WAS ONE
OF THOSE COOL KIDS
WHO HAS IT ALL FIGURED OUT.
BUT I WAS WAY OFF.
SHE'S GOT HER OWN STACK OF
PROBLEMS LIKE ANYONE ELSE.
I THINK I UNDERSTAND HER
A LITTLE MORE NOW.
( yawns ) TELL ME AGAIN
WHAT I'M DOING OUT HERE.
THIS IS YOUR MORNING PRACTICE,
NOT MINE.
- LISTEN, YOU SAID THAT
I COULD JUMP THIS AGAIN,
SO I'M GOING FOR IT.
NOW, ARE YOU GOING TO
BE MAN OF YOUR WORD
AND SHOW ME SOME ENCOURAGEMENT,
OR JUST COMPLAIN?
- I NEVER AGREED TO ANYTHING
THIS EARLY IN THE MORNING.
- GREAT, NOW YOU'RE BREAKING
MORE STUFF!
- SORRY. WHAT DO YOU WANT ME
TO SET YOUR HEIGHT AT?
- SET THE BAR AT 164 CENTIMETERS
TO START.
- OUI, MADAME.
- AND NOW IT'S CROOKED!
IS THERE ANYTHING
YOU DON'T SCREW UP
THE SECOND YOU TOUCH IT?!
- WHY I PUT UP WITH THIS,
I DON'T KNOW.
- DONE. YOU THINK
YOU CAN GET OVER?
IT LOOKS HIGHER THAN I THOUGHT.
GOOD LUCK.
- I'LL SHOW YOU
WHAT I'M MADE OF!
FOCUS ON IT. YOU'VE CLEARED
THE TOP OF THIS BEFORE.
NOW JUMP!
- AMAZING.
YOU TOUCHED THE BAR,
BUT IT WAS REALLY CLOSE.
WANNA TRY IT AGAIN?
- BUT I...
I'VE NEVER HAD A PROBLEM
AT THIS HEIGHT.
- AH, EVERYBODY HAS
AN OFF DAY NOW AND THEN.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
- YEAH, WELL, NOT ME.
I DON'T HAVE OFF DAYS.
- GIVE YOURSELF A BREAK.
IT COULD BE THAT YOUR BODY'S
STILL WORN OUT FROM YESTERDAY.
- CUT IT OUT, YAMATO, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO LIE TO ME ABOUT THIS.
I SUCK. I CAN'T EVEN CLEAR
A 164 MUCH LESS A 169.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
HOLD ON! WHEN YOU SET THE BAR,
HOW DID YOU DO IT?
- EXACTLY LIKE YOU SAID.
I PUT IT AT 164.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO SET
THE TOP OF THE BAR TO THE MARK,
NOT THE BOTTOM, YOU IDIOT!
HOW WAS I SUPPOSED TO KNOW?
I'M NOT IN TRACK AND FIELD!
YOU KNOW THAT!
- YOU'RE SO IRRESPONSIBLE
SOMETIMES, YAMATO
YOU SHOULD BE LOCKED UP!
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT.
I SET A NEW HIGH JUMP RECORD
AND DIDN'T EVEN KNOW IT.
- 173 CENTIMETERS.
THAT UNOFFICIALLY TIES ASAHINA
FOR 12TH PLACE IN THE NATION
AMONG JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL
GIRLS. BUT MORE IMPORTANTLY,
I GOT TO SEE A SIDE OF HER
I'D NEVER SEEN BEFORE,
TOTALLY DIFFERENT FROM
HER USUAL COOL SELF.
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER SEEN A
PRETTIER FACE IN MY WHOLE LIFE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ABOVE ♪
♪ NOW IS ALL WE HAVE ♪
♪ WITH A LITTLE FEELING
AND A LOT OF LOVE ♪
♪ WE TURN UP THE HEAT AND RUN ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- ♪ ALL MY LIFE HERE ON THE
GROUND ABOUT TO RUN AND NOW ♪
♪ I FIND I MUST
ASK MYSELF WHY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE SOMETHING IS STIRRING ♪
♪ I FEEL IT WHISPERING IN ME ♪
♪ SOME DAYS I WAKE UP ♪
♪ BUT MY HEART'S
STILL SLEEPING ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME
TO RUN AND TRY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME TO FLY ♪
♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ON HIGH ♪
♪ WITH OUR GOAL IN SIGHT ♪
♪ WE WILL RUN
WITH ALL OUR MIGHT ♪
♪ TOMORROW AND TODAY
WILL NEVER EVER PASS US BY ♪
♪ WE WILL NOT STOP NOW ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR HEART ALIVE
AND YOUR DREAM SURVIVES ♪
♪ AND YOU CROSS
THE FINISH LINE ♪
♪ LET IT GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- Yamato: GEEZ, YASUNOBU,
I'M STILL AMAZED
BY YOUR SKILLS WITH THE LADIES.
YOU JUST TELL THEM
WHAT THEY WANT TO HEAR,
AND YOU'RE THE
MOST POPULAR GUY EVER.
- Yasunobu: IT'S NOT A SECRET,
DUMMY. CHICKS DIG COMPLIMENTS.
- MAYBE I SHOULD TRY A FEW ON
ASAHINA, SEE WHAT SHE THINKS.
I MEAN, NOT NOW. LATER.