- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- DON'T LEAVE YET.
I STILL LIKE YOU, ASAHINA!
LOOK, I KNOW.
I DON'T NEED YOU
TO ANSWER ME NOW.
I'M GOING TO PRACTICE HARDER.
- I DON'T KNOW,
BUT WE CAN FIGURE IT OUT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO ANSWER ME NOW,
WAIT UNTIL I GET BACK
FROM NATIONALS.
- JUST WAIT UNTIL I WIN
THE NEXT MEET, ASAHINA.
THEN YOU CAN GIVE ME
YOUR ANSWER.
- WITH THE GOLD MEDAL,
OF COURSE.
- JUST STOP IT!
- ASAHINA, WAIT!
COME BACK HERE, PLEASE!
- Hashiba: ( on phone ) SUZUKA?
NO, SHE DIDN'T COME HERE.
WHY? DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
- IT'S BEEN OVER TWO HOURS
SINCE SHE'S BEEN GONE.
THE REASON'S NOT IMPORTANT.
I WAS JUST WONDERING
IF SHE WENT OVER TO YOUR PLACE
TO TALK OR SOMETHING.
- OH, SO YOU GUYS
GOT IN A FIGHT.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
WHAT IS SHE THINKING?
YOU CAN'T DISAPPEAR JUST BECAUSE
I CONFESSED MY FEELINGS TO YOU!
- Megumi: SUZUKA AND YAMATO
AREN'T IN THEIR ROOMS? REALLY?
THAT'S WEIRD.
- I KNOW. IT IS.
MY SISTER JUST SENT ME
SOME PEARS.
I THOUGHT THEY MIGHT WANNA
COME DOWN AND SHARE THEM.
OH, WELL, I WONDER
WHERE THEY COULD'VE GONE.
IT'S GETTING LATE.
- ( door opens )
- WELL, I HEARD SUZUKA
RUN OUT OF YAMATO'S ROOM
A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
SHE LOOKED PRETTY UPSET.
I GUESS THAT MEANS
THEY'RE FIGHTING AGAIN, HUH?
IF THAT'S TRUE, YAMATO'S
PROBABLY OUT LOOKING FOR SUZUKA!
- NOW THAT I THINK ABOUT IT,
YAMATO DID LOOK
A LITTLE DOWN EARLIER.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
HAPPENED TO HIM?
- I BET HE THREW HIMSELF AT HER
LIKE A TYPICAL BOY
AND GOT REJECTED.
- WHATEVER! YAMATO WOULD NEVER
DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT!
MOM, WHAT ARE
WE GOING TO DO?
- JUST LEAVE THEM ALONE.
THEY'RE GONNA COME BACK
WHEN THEY'RE READY.
- YEAH, SHE'S RIGHT. STUFF LIKE
THIS HAPPENS ALL THE TIME.
- ALL RIGHT. WELL, IN THAT CASE,
I HOPE YOU GIRLS ARE HUNGRY.
- I WONDER IF AKITSUKI'S FEELING
ALL RIGHT TONIGHT.
NO, HE HAS FEELINGS FOR ASAHINA.
- ASAHINA, WHERE ARE YOU?
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO
ANSWER ME NOW.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
WAIT TO TELL ME
WHEN I GET BACK FROM NATIONALS?
OF COURSE, AFTER I'VE
WON THE GOLD MEDAL.
- Suzune: TSUDA? REALLY?
- YEAH. IT'S SO COOL. HE'S GOING
TO THE NATIONALS TOMORROW!
- AND?
- "AND"? WHAT DO YOU MEAN "AND"?
THAT'S AN AMAZING
ACCOMPLISHMENT, SIS!
- WELL, SURE IT IS.
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE THIS IS
HIS FIRST TIME GOING.
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU'RE SO EXCITED ABOUT IT.
- WELL, UM, IT'S 'CAUSE...
HE'S FAST AND HAS A REALLY
IMPRESSIVE TIME.
AND HE SAID HE WAS GONNA
WIN, SO THAT'S COOL.
- I KNEW I RECOGNIZED THAT LOOK.
YOU LIKE TSUDA, DON'T YOU?
- NO! WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT?
- I'M JUST KIDDING.
I KNOW YOU WOULD NEVER
GO FOR SOMEONE LIKE HIM.
HE'S SO IMMATURE AND NOT
THE SLIGHTEST BIT ATTRACTIVE!
- YEAH, BUT IT'S DIFFERENT
WHEN HE'S RUNNING.
HE'S ACTUALLY PRETTY COOL.
- BUSTED!
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- SUZUKA, JUST ADMIT
THAT YOU LIKE HIM.
YOU'RE NOT VERY GOOD
AT FAKING IT.
HEY, MOM! GUESS WHAT? SUZUKA
JUST SAID THAT SHE LIKED TSUDA!
- NO, I DIDN'T!
IDIOT! I HATE YOU!
- SUZUKA! WHERE ARE YOU RUNNING
OFF TO? IT'S ALMOST DINNER TIME!
- I'M NOT HUNGRY!
I HAVE THE WORST SISTER
IN THE WORLD!
- I JUST WANTED TO SAY THAT I'VE
HAD A CRUSH ON YOU SINCE WE MET.
- Suzuka: AFTER HE WINS
THE NATIONALS, HUH?
I GUESS IT'S ABOUT
TIME TO START.
I REALLY DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO TALK TO HIM ABOUT.
I GUESS I CAN JUST
TEASE HIM ABOUT
HOW NERVOUS AND NERDY
HE SOUNDED THE OTHER DAY.
NEVER MIND, FORGET IT.
- ( phone rings )
- GREAT! I WONDER
WHO THAT COULD BE.
I HOPE IT'S NOT HIM.
HELLO, ASAHINA RESIDENCE.
- HI. THIS IS MIYAMOTO.
MAY I PLEASE SPEAK TO SUZUKA?
- HI, SEMPAI, IT'S ME.
UM, HOW ARE YOU DOING TODAY?
- OH, UH, I'M GLAD I CAUGHT YOU.
- IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
YOU HARDLY EVER CALL MY HOUSE.
OH! HOW'S TSUDA SEMPAI
DOING? DID HE WIN?
ARE YOU THERE?
- IT'S ABOUT KAZUKI. HE WAS
KILLED IN A CAR ACCIDENT.
THEY WERE GOING
THROUGH AN INTERSECTION
AND A TRUCK HIT THE BUS.
HE'S SUCH AN IDIOT.
HE OVERSLEPT.
IF HE'D JUST MADE IT
TO THE BUS ON TIME,
THEY WOULDN'T HAVE HAD
TO WAIT FOR HIM.
AND THAT TRUCK WOULD
NEVER HAVE HIT HIM.
WHY WASN'T HE FAST ENOUGH?
- ( people sobbing )
- SEMPAI...
WHY?
WHEN I LOOK AT HIS PICTURE,
IT ISN'T PAINFUL FOR ME.
I DON'T FEEL SAD.
EVERYONE IS CRYING AND
COMFORTING EACH OTHER.
I FEEL LIKE I SHOULD
BE CRYING, TOO.
BUT I DON'T' FEEL ANYTHING.
I HAVEN'T SHED ONE TEAR.
I MUST JUST BE
A VERY HEARTLESS PERSON.
- IS THERE ANYTHING
I CAN DO, MIYAMOTO?
- SEMPAI,
I'M GONNA GRAB TSUDA SEMPAI'S
THINGS FROM THE CLUB ROOM.
- GOOD IDEA.
- THANKS. THAT'S VERY NICE
OF YOU TO DO THAT.
- SURE.
- DIDN'T ANYONE EVER
TEACH YOU HOW
TO KNOCK BEFORE YOU BARGE IN?
- HEY! YOU CAN'T JUST SCRIBBLE
ON THE TABLE LIKE THAT!
- YOU'RE AN IDIOT. IT'S NOT
A SCRIBBLE, IT'S A GOAL!
- YOU'RE GONNA BE IN SO MUCH
TROUBLE WHEN I TELL THE TEACHER!
- I WOULDN'T DO THAT
IF I WERE YOU!
I'M WRITING YOUR NAME
ON HERE, TOO.
SO THAT MAKES YOU MY ACCOMPLICE!
- YOU BETTER NOT!
THAT'S A PERMANENT MARKER!
( laughs )
SEMPAI...
LISTEN, I...
I, UM... I HAVE MY ANSWER.
BUT NOW YOU'RE GONE.
I'LL NEVER SEE YOU AGAIN
I CAN'T TELL YOU WHAT IT WAS!
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE TO
ANSWER YOU NOW!
WHY DO YOU EXPECT
SO MUCH FROM ME SEMPAI?
AND WHY...
WHY DID YOU TELL ME THAT?
- I'LL BE RIGHT BACK. I'M JUST
GOING TO THE CONVENIENCE STORE.
- Honoka's mother: OKAY,
WILL YOU LOCK THE GATE
TO THE SHRINE ON YOUR WAY OUT?
- ALL RIGHT!
HI, ASAHINA,
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- THAT'S RIGHT. I FORGOT THAT
YOU LIVED HERE, HONOKA.
I'M SORRY. I SHOULD GO.
- NO, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO GO. REALLY.
BUT, UM, IS THERE
SOMETHING WRONG?
- NO, I'M FINE.
- YOU SURE? IT LOOKS LIKE
YOU'VE BEEN CRYING.
- NO, IT'S...
SOMETHING WAS IN MY EYE.
- OH, OKAY.
WELL, UM...
THE KANTO CHAMPIONSHIP
IS COMING UP!
- MMM-HMM.
- YOU MUST BE EXCITED.
I HEARD YOU'RE THE ONLY FRESHMAN
GIRL WHO QUALIFIED THIS YEAR.
THAT'S AMAZING!
I REALLY THOUGHT
AKITSUKI WOULD QUALIFY, TOO,
BUT UNFORTUNATELY
HE LOST THE PRELIMINARY.
I'VE ACTUALLY BEEN KIND OF
WORRIED ABOUT HIM.
HE SEEMS REALLY
DEPRESSED LATELY.
- SORRY. I HAVE TO GO HOME NOW.
- WAIT!
DID SOMETHING HAPPEN
WITH YOU AND AKITSUKI?
- NO! YAMATO HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH THIS!
WHY WOULD YOU ASK THAT?
- WELL, UH...
IT'S BECAUSE I THINK THAT
YOU HAVE FEELINGS FOR HIM.
- I ALREADY TOLD YOU,
I DON'T LIKE HIM LIKE THAT.
YAMATO IS JUST A FRIEND.
NOTHING MORE.
- YOU'RE LYING.
WHY DO YOU ALWAYS
ACT LIKE THAT?
- I TOLD YOU.
- YOU ALWAYS AVOID ANSWERING
IMPORTANT QUESTIONS
OR JUST LIE ABOUT
THEM COMPLETELY.
I'M SICK OF IT, ASAHINA!
DON'T YOU REALIZE THAT YOUR
ATTITUDE IS CAUSING NOTHING
BUT HEARTACHE FOR
EVERYONE AROUND YOU?
- AND WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
THE WAY THAT I ACT IS
NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS, HONOKA!
- YES, IT IS!
YOU'RE HURTING YOUR FRIENDS!
YOU'VE HURT BOTH ME
AND AKITSUKI.
YOU WON'T BE HONEST
ABOUT YOUR FEELINGS
AND IT'S MAKING
EVERYTHING COMPLICATED!
I KEEP HOLDING ON BECAUSE
I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU FEEL.
I'M CONSTANTLY MAKING A FOOL
OUT OF MYSELF BECAUSE OF YOU!
- BUT YOU...
YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL!
- THERE'S AN AMAZING GUY
WHO WANTS TO BE WITH YOU!
WHY IS THAT SO HARD
FOR YOU TO ACCEPT?
- WELL, I KNOW IT'S HARD FOR YOU
TO UNDERSTAND BECAUSE...
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW IT FEELS
TO HAVE SOMEONE YOU LOVE DIE!
- YOU'RE RIGHT, ASAHINA,
I DON'T KNOW THAT.
BUT I DO KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO HAVE MY HEART BROKEN.
YOU SHOULD GO TO HIM.
HE'S BEEN WAITING A LONG TIME.
HE'S A GREAT GUY AND
HE DESERVES TO BE HAPPY.
OKAY?
HEY, WAIT!
SO DO YOU.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- HI , AKITSUKI.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHY WERE YOU RUNNING?
- WELL, I, UH...
ASAHINA DISAPPEARED
ALL OF A SUDDEN,
AND I'VE BEEN TRYING
TO FIND HER.
BUT I HAVE NO IDEA
WHERE SHE COULD BE RIGHT NOW.
- ACTUALLY, SHE WAS JUST HERE
A FEW MINUTES AGO.
- SHE WAS?
- UM, YEAH. ARE YOU FEELING
ANY BETTER, AKITSUKI?
I MEAN, YOU SEEMED
REALLY DEPRESSED...
- WHICH WAY DID SHE GO?
TELL ME, PLEASE!
- HIS HEART BELONGS TO ASAHINA.
THERE'S NO ROOM FOR ME.
SHE RAN TOWARD THE PARK.
YOU BETTER HURRY. SHE'S FAST.
- THANKS , HONOKA.
- YOU SHOULD GO TO HIM.
HE'S BEEN WAITING A LONG TIME.
HE'S A GREAT GUY AND
HE DESERVES TO BE HAPPY.
- I CAN'T DO IT.
I'D RATHER BE ALONE
THAN HAVE TO GO THROUGH
A PAINFUL EXPERIENCE
LIKE THAT AGAIN.
I'D RATHER BE ALONE.
- ( inaudible )
- DON'T LEAVE YET.
I STILL LIKE YOU, ASAHINA!
- I'M SORRY, YAMATO.
I'LL APOLOGIZE TOMORROW
AND EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE.
WE'LL BE FRIENDS AGAIN,
JUST LIKE WE WERE.
- THERE YOU ARE! FINALLY!
- YAMATO... HI.
- I'VE BEEN LOOKING
ALL OVER FOR YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING OUT HERE?
WELL, IT'S COLD AND RAINING.
WE SHOULD PROBABLY
GET BACK HOME.
- ( Suzuka sobs )
- HEY, WAIT! COME BACK HERE!
- DON'T FOLLOW ME!
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND, ASAHINA!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
- IT DOESN'T MATTER!
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE!
- I CAN'T DO THAT!
- ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T BE RUNNING
IN THOSE SHOES, YOU KNOW.
HEY, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
CAN'T YOU GET UP?
WELL, HERE...
- NO! GO AWAY!
WHY ARE YOU SO CONCERNED
WITH WHAT I DO
AND WHERE I'M GOING, HUH?
THIS IS NONE OF YOUR
BUSINESS, YAMATO! BACK OFF!
I'M TIRED OF YOU CHASING ME
EVERYWHERE! ARE YOU CRAZY?
I DON'T EVEN LIKE YOU. I HATE
YOU! I HATE YOU SO MUCH!
I NEVER ASKED YOU TO COME
LOOKING FOR ME, YOU WEIRDO!
YOU'RE SO ANNOYING!
- I'M SORRY. I WAS JUST
WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
- JUST STOP IT. IF YOU CONTINUE
TO BE SO NICE TO ME, THEN...
THEN I... I'LL FALL FOR YOU.
- OKAY.
- I DON'T WANT THAT AGAIN!
- HUH? WANT WHAT?
- I DON'T WANNA HURT.
I DON'T WANNA FEEL PAIN
LIKE THAT AGAIN.
- OH, IT'S TSUDA. RIGHT?
- I'M SORRY. I CAN'T GO OUT
WITH ANYONE ELSE EVER AGAIN.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND. THIS IS
NOT THE SAME SITUATION!
YOU CAN'T JUST DECIDE
SOMEONE'S WRONG FOR YOU
WITHOUT EVEN GIVING THEM
A CHANCE FIRST!
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW IT WOULD TURN OUT!
- YOU HAVE NO IDEA WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT, YAMATO.
YOU THINK IT'S SO EASY BECAUSE
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN THERE!
- THAT'S NOT TRUE!
- DON'T TOUCH ME!
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE!
- YOU'RE WRONG!
- ( horn honking )
- PLEASE, JUST LISTEN.
I WOULD NEVER EXPECT THIS
TO BE EASY FOR YOU.
- WAIT...
- ( slaps resounding )
- YOU JERK!
- I'M SO SORRY.
- THIS IS SO GOOD!
- YEAH, IT IS!
- YEAH, SO DON'T EAT IT ALL,
YOU GUYS!
SAVE SOME FOR YAMATO
AND SUZUKA.
THEY'LL PROBABLY BE HUNGRY
WHEN THEY GET HOME.
- MIHO, IT'S OKAY. THERE SHOULD
BE PLENTY FOR EVERYONE.
- I'M STARTING TO WONDER IF
THOSE TWO ARE EVER COMING BACK.
- OH, PLEASE. DON'T WORRY ABOUT
THEM. THEY'RE NOT BABIES.
- I BET THEY MADE UP AND ARE
JUST OUT HAVING A GOOD TIME.
FRIENDSHIPS ARE ALWAYS STRONGER
AFTER A FIGHT.
- THAT'S RIGHT. THEY SAY
"THE GROUND GETS HARDER
"AFTER THE RAIN FALLS." RIGHT?
YOU TELL 'EM, GORO!
- THAT'S OKAY, THEN.
- SO THAT'S IT. IT'S OVER AND
THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WHEN I TURN AROUND ♪
♪ YOU'RE RIGHT THERE
NEXT TO ME ♪
♪ ON YOUR FACE A SMILE
SO COMFORTING AND FAMILIAR ♪
♪ THE CLOSER YOU BECAME
THE LESS THAT I COULD SEE ♪
♪ AND NOW I'M WONDERING
SO LOST AND ALL ALONE ♪
♪ PEOPLE CHANGE
A LITTLE AT A TIME ♪
♪ AND NOW I KNOW I'M CHANGING ♪
♪ WHEN I CALL YOUR NAME
SHOUT IT OUT INTO THE SKY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN I WILL FIND
THE LOVE I KEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'RE WITH ME
AND YOU TAKE MY HAND ♪
♪ SOMEHOW EVERYTHING
SEEMS TO WORK ITSELF OUT RIGHT ♪
♪ WHEN I SEE YOUR EYES
STARING BACK AT MINE ♪
♪ THERE INSIDE I FIND
A LOVE THAT NEVER DIES ♪
♪ TOGETHER I KNOW
WE'LL FIND A WAY ♪
♪ JUST YOU AND I ♪
- Yamato: THIS IS CRAZY!
YOU HAVE TO STOP GOING
TO TSUDA'S GRAVE.
IT'S NOT GOING TO HELP YOU
GET PAST IT.
ARE YOU JUST GOING TO
KEEP DOING THIS
FOR THE REST OF YOUR LIFE?
- Suzuka: PERFECT TIMING!
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO ASK YOU
IF YOU WANTED TO COME
WITH ME THIS TIME.
- Yamato: HUH?