- ♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY,
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- YOU'RE GONNA HAVE TO SCRUB
HARDER THAN THAT!
- I KNOW, I KNOW.
- OH, AND THE GENERATOR IS OUT
OF FUEL. YOU SHOULD FILL IT UP.
- THAT WAS THE NEXT THING
ON MY TO-DO LIST.
- DO ME A FAVOR
AND DON'T MESS UP.
- I THINK YOU WORRY TOO MUCH.
- GOOD LUCK.
- IT'S LAME THEY EXPECT ME
TO WORK FOR FREE.
I KNOW I BROKE DOWN THE DOOR
BUT TAKING IT
OUT OF MY PAY SUCKS.
( sighs ) THIS IS
TAKING FOREVER.
ASAHINA! THIS WHOLE THING WAS
HER FAULT TO BEGIN WITH.
WHY ISN'T SHE HELPING ME?
- ( birds chirping )
- ( sighs ) MAN, I'M BEAT.
- YO! LONG TIME NO SEE.
- YEAH, NO KIDDING. WHAT ARE YOU
DOING IN HERE, YASUNOBU?
- LOOKING THROUGH THIS MAGAZINE.
YOUR DOOR WAS UNLOCKED.
- THAT DOESN'T MEAN YOU CAN
JUST BARGE IN AND LOUNGE!
AND THOSE ARE MY FAVORITE CHIPS
YOU'RE EATING!
- BACK OFF THE ATTITUDE, MAN. I
THOUGHT WE WERE BEST FRIENDS,
BUT I GUESS NOT.
- WHAT? WHO SAID
WE WERE BEST FRIENDS?
YASUNOBU HATTORI. BORN IN THE
CITY AND THE SAME AGE AS ME.
A LADIES MAN. WOMEN ARE MORE
IMPORTANT TO HIM THAN EVEN FOOD.
- DUDE, GOT ANY PORN MAGS
AROUND HERE?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK? NO!
- YOU LITTLE LIAR.
- WHEN I MET HIM, IT WAS
DURING MY VERY FIRST TRIP
TO THE CITY TO VISIT MY AUNT.
I HAD GOTTEN LOST
AND WAS JUST WANDERING AROUND
WITH MY FACE BURIED
IN MY SLEEVE.
( sniffling )
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
( laughs ) YOU'RE SO UGLY!
THERE'S SNOT ALL OVER YOUR FACE!
- UH, WHO ARE YOU?
- HERE, HAVE A TISSUE.
- OH, THANKS.
HE SEEMED LIKE A GOOD GUY.
- THAT IS SO COOL THAT
YOUR AUNT OWNS THE BATHHOUSE.
- YEAH.
- NOW I KNOW
HOW YOU CAN THANK ME.
- IT WAS AFTER THAT THAT
EVERYTHING STARTED TO GO SOUTH.
I WOULD COME TO TOKYO
TO VISIT ONCE A YEAR.
- HEY, YAMATO!
TIME TO COME OUT AND PLAY!
- HE'S BACK AGAIN?
- LET'S SNEAK DOWNSTAIRS
AND CHECK OUT THE SECRET SPOT.
IT'S SHOWTIME!
I CAN SEE EVERYTHING!
- YASUNOBU, WE
SHOULDN'T BE DOING THIS.
I COULD GET IN TROUBLE.
- I GOT A SWEET PLAN.
WE'RE GOING TO DO SOMETHING
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT THIS TIME.
- ( girls screaming )
- HELP ME!
HE KEEPS PICKING ON ME!
I TRIED TO TELL HIM
WE SHOULDN'T PEEK IN THE BATH
BUT THEN HE PUNCHED ME
AND HE PUSHED ME IN.
- ( exclaims )
- AW, YOU'LL BE OKAY.
- EVEN AS A KID, HE KNEW EXACTLY
HOW TO PUSH THE GIRLS' BUTTONS.
- YAMATO, HOW COULD YOU?
- BUT I DIDN'T DO IT!
AND I'VE ALWAYS BEEN THE ONE
TO TAKE THE HEAT.
- SO, YOU'RE STILL BOUNCING
AROUND WITH NO GIRLFRIEND?
PEOPLE ARE GONNA START TALKING,
YOU BIG DORK.
- AH, LEAVE ME ALONE.
- DON'T SWEAT IT, THOUGH.
I CAN WATCH OUT FOR YOU,
SINCE WE'LL BE AT THE SAME
SCHOOL AND ALL.
- HUH?
- MIHO'S BEEN KEEPING ME
UP TO DATE. SHE'S A COOL GIRL.
- STAY AWAY FROM MIHO!
THAT'S WHERE I DRAW THE LINE!
- CHILL OUT ALREADY.
I DIG THE OLDER WOMEN.
IF YOU ASK ME, MATURITY IS
SEXIER THAN ANYTHING ELSE.
AND I GOTTA TELL YOU,
BRO, YOUR AUNT AYANO
IS QUITE THE BOMBSHELL.
- I DON'T CARE! NOW GET
THE HELL OUT! I MEAN IT!
- WELL, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO BE SO RUDE.
I ALWAYS LIKED THE NAME SUZUKA.
IT'S SWEET.
SO IS SHE A LOOKER OR WHAT?
- NO, NOT EVEN CLOSE.
SHE'S GOTTA BE, LIKE,
FIFTY OR SIXTY YEARS OLD.
- REALLY? LIVING HERE?
- OH, YEAH. SHE'S FAT, UGLY,
GOT A NASTY ATTITUDE.
- Suzuka: OH, I'M SO SORRY.
I'M SORRY FOR BEING FAT AND UGLY
WITH A BAD ATTITUDE.
- NO, THAT'S NOT...
- YOU CREEP.
- HEY, ASAHINA,
PASS THE SOY SAUCE.
IT'S SITTING RIGHT THERE
IN FRONT OF YOU, SOY SAUCE.
- OH, GEE, THANKS.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- OH, I'M FAT AND UGLY
WITH A NASTY ATTITUDE.
THAT'S PROBABLY
WHAT YOU'RE SENSING.
- I DIDN'T MEAN IT LIKE THAT!
- WHAT DID YOU DO?
- OH, NOTHING.
- Ayano: YAMATO, WAS
THAT YASUNOBU HATTORI
WHO CAME BY TO SEE YOU TODAY?
I'VE ALWAYS THOUGHT
HE WAS JUST THE NICEST BOY.
SO WELL-MANNERED
AND GOOD LOOKING.
- ( scoffs ) HE'S A LADIES MAN
AND HE'S NOT AS
NICE AS YOU THINK.
- I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
SURE THE GIRLS LIKE HIM,
BUT WHEN WE WERE IN
SCHOOL TOGETHER,
HE REALLY HAD ALL KINDS OF
FRIENDS. EVERYONE LIKED HIM.
- SOUNDS LIKE JEALOUSLY, YAMATO,
SEEING THAT
HE'S NOTHING LIKE YOU.
- HOW CAN YOU SAY THAT?
YOU DON'T KNOW A SINGLE
THING ABOUT ME!
- I CAN MAKE AN EDUCATED GUESS.
- WHAT'S UP WITH YOU TWO?
- I ALMOST FORGOT.
YOU TWO START SCHOOL
THE DAY AFTER TOMORROW.
WE SHOULD CELEBRATE.
- UM, CELEBRATE?
- FOR MOVING IN
AND STARTING HIGH SCHOOL.
YOU KNOW, A NEW CHAPTER IN LIFE.
I'LL MAKE SOMETHING GOOD.
- SOUNDS GREAT! I'M IN.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO, REALLY.
- I KNOW, BUT I LOVE
PARTY PREPARATIONS.
HOWEVER, I AM GOING
TO BE BUSY TOMORROW,
SO MAYBE YOU TWO WOULDN'T MIND
GOING SHOPPING FOR ME.
- WHAT?
- HIM AND ME?
- WOULD YOU?
- Suzuka: OKAY.
- ( Yamato sighs )
- ( doorbell rings )
- YAMATO, GET IT IN GEAR!
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO GO SHOPPING,
REMEMBER? MOVE IT!
- ( in sleepy voice ) WHAT?
- DID YOU JUST WAKE UP?
YOU COULD AT LEAST
PUT SOME PANTS ON!
- OKAY.
ISN'T IT TOO EARLY IN THE DAY
FOR YOU TO START NAGGING ME?
- I WOULDN'T HAVE TO NAG
IF YOU WEREN'T SO SLOPPY.
- SORRY FOR THE INCONVENIENCE.
IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE VERY MUCH
HAS CHANGED HERE DOWNTOWN.
TOKYO'S EXACTLY AS I REMEMBER IT
BEING AS A KID.
- WELL, IT'S JUST TOO CROWDED
HERE FOR MY TASTE.
I DON'T CARE FOR IT.
- OH, RIGHT.
- LET'S GET OUR SHOPPING DONE
QUICKLY, AND GET OUTTA HERE.
- HUH, TOILET SEAT COVERS?
- YEAH, YOUR AUNT WANTED ME
TO PICK ONE UP FOR HER.
- WHY DON'T YOU GRAB
ONE OF THESE FROM THE SALE BIN?
WE'VE GOT A WHOLE LIST
OF THINGS TO GET.
ANY ONE WILL BE FINE.
- WE CAN'T JUST GRAB
THE FIRST THING WE SEE.
YOU JUST DON'T THINK SOMETIMES.
YOU COULD TRY TO BE MORE
CONSIDERATE, YOU KNOW.
- WHO CARES
WHICH SEAT YOU BUY HER?
- IT'S NOT LIKE YOU'LL BE
THE ONE WHO'S SITTING ON IT.
- IT'S FOR MY LANDLADY
AND YOUR AUNT.
JUST PRETEND LIKE YOU
CARE, ALL RIGHT?
- MAN, THIS IS WEAK.
SHOPPING WITH A WOMAN
IS ABOUT AS MUCH FUN
AS STANDING IN LINE AT THE BANK.
BUT IT'S TWICE AS BAD
WITH ASAHINA
SINCE SHE HAS THIS PERFECTIONIST
STREAK A MILE WIDE.
IF THIS IS WHAT PICKING OUT
A TOILET SEAT COVER IS LIKE,
I DREAD WHAT THE REST OF THE DAY
HOLDS FOR ME.
- HERE.
- OH, THAT'S PERFECT!
BEAUTIFUL COLOR!
- YOU DON'T SOUND
LIKE YOU MEAN IT.
- I JUST WANT TO MAKE IT HOME
BY DINNER.
WE'VE BEEN SHOPPING HERE
FOR THREE HOURS,
AND I'VE REALIZED SOMETHING.
YOU'RE NOT A PERFECTIONIST,
LIKE I THOUGHT YOU WERE.
YOU'RE JUST VERY INDECISIVE.
- I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE I
SPEND MONEY ON THE RIGHT THINGS.
- OH, SURE.
- ANYWAY, I'M READY
TO GO HOME NOW.
ALL THE BUSTLE OF THE CITY'S
MAKING ME NERVOUS.
- WOULD YOU GIVE IT UP?
THIS CITY'S A COOL PLACE,
EVEN IF YOU WON'T ADMIT IT.
- I'M ALLOWED TO HAVE
WHATEVER FEELINGS I WANT.
- YOU JUST HAVEN'T GIVEN
THIS PLACE A CHANCE.
HOW ABOUT WE HAVE LUNCH, ON ME.
I KNOW JUST THE PLACE.
ONE BITE AND YOU'LL LOVE TOKYO.
- WHY ARE YOU DRAGGING ME DOWN
THIS DANK ALLEY?
- IT'S A SHORTCUT. JUST KEEP UP.
- THIS DOESN'T
IMPROVE MY OPINION.
- HERE WE ARE. THIS IS
THE BEST FOOD I'VE EVER HAD.
PINK ANGEL MASSAGE?
- SO THIS IS YOUR FAVORITE
PLACE? WOW. IT'S REALLY NICE.
- MAN! WHY'D THEY CLOSE?
THIS WAS A GREAT RESTAURANT.
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
- THEY GOT A GIRL HERE NAMED
SUZUKA. IT'S NOT YOU, IS IT?
- HAVE YOU GONE INSANE?
I'M GOING HOME.
- NO! WAIT! WE COULD FIND
ANOTHER PLACE NEARBY!
- NO!
- STOP RUNNING!
- WELL, STOP FOLLOWING ME!
- I PROMISE!
I'LL GET IT RIGHT THIS TIME!
I WON'T TAKE YOU
TO A MASSAGE PARLOR!
AWESOME.
( shouts )
- GEEZ.
YOU'VE GOT TO BE
THE MOST CLUMSY
AND LOUDMOUTHED
KNOW-IT-ALL EVER.
YOU GET ME TO GIVE IN,
THEN EVERY PLACE YOU
DRAG ME TO IS CLOSED.
YOU KNOW LESS ABOUT
THIS CITY THAN I DO.
AND SERIOUSLY, IF ANY OF THOSE
RESTAURANTS WERE GOOD,
THEY WOULD STILL BE IN BUSINESS.
- ( exclaims )
- WHY ARE YOU STOPPING?
- JUST GIVE ME
TWO SECONDS, OKAY?
- DON'T LEAVE ME ON THE STREET!
- DON'T WORRY,
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK!
- ( birds chirping )
- A SHRINE?
WHAT'S SOMETHING THIS NICE
DOING HERE?
IT'S SO NICE AND PEACEFUL.
I CAN SMELL THE EARTH
AND THE LEAVES.
-SORRY. THANKS FOR
WAITING FOR ME.
- WHERE DID YOU GO?
- AROUND THE CORNER.
WHAT DO YOU SAY WE TAKE
A WALK UP THE STAIRS?
- YOU PRAYING FOR SUCCESS?
- WELL, THAT'S WHAT
AN INARI SHRINE
IS SUPPOSED
TO HELP WITH, SO YEAH.
- WHY DON'T YOU GIVE IT A SHOT?
MAYBE IT'LL HELP YOU SET A
RECORD AND BECOME FAMOUS.
- I DON'T BELIEVE
IN THAT KIND OF STUFF.
- YOU KEEP TALKING LIKE THAT
AND YOU'LL BE PUNISHED.
- I HAD NO IDEA
YOU WERE RELIGIOUS.
YOU CAME UP HERE
JUST SO YOU COULD PRAY?
- YEAH, SORT OF.
HERE.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- MEAT AND POTATO CROQUETTE.
THAT CONVENIENCE
STORE BACK THERE
IS THE ONLY ONE THAT CARRIES IT.
THE STORE IS A FRANCHISE,
BUT THE MANAGER LIKES TO
ADD HIS SPECIAL FAVORITES.
AND, LUCKY FOR YOU,
THIS HAPPENS TO BE ONE OF THEM.
I EAT THESE RIGHT HERE
EVERY TIME I COME TO THE CITY,
- YOU'RE GONNA GET BUSTED EATING
LUNCH IN A PLACE LIKE THIS.
- ENOUGH OF YOUR WORRYING.
JUST HAVE A BITE.
- I KNOW I'M GONNA REGRET THIS.
THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
- I KNOW!
- OH, NO. IT'S NOT
THE FOOD ITSELF.
IT'S THE ATMOSPHERE UP HERE.
- ( laughs ) WHATEVER YOU SAY.
I KNOW ONLY ONE THING.
I LOVE TO PRAY AND EAT.
- WHEN YOU PRAYED JUST NOW,
WHAT EXACTLY WERE YOU
HOPING WOULD HAPPEN?
- THAT I'D HAVE A STROKE OF
GOOD LUCK, FOR A CHANGE.
- WHAT? BUT, YAMATO,
WHY WOULD YOU WISH FOR
SOMETHING SO GENERIC?
- WHO CARES?
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH
NOT HAVING A SPECIFIC GOAL.
MOST PEOPLE AREN'T BLESSED WITH
SELF-AWARENESS LIKE YOU ARE.
- WITH THAT ATTITUDE, NO PRAYERS
FOR SUCCESS ARE GONNA HELP.
DIDN'T YOU SAY
YOU WERE FROM HIROSHIMA?
- CLOSE. IT'S IN THE
COUNTRYSIDE,
JUST OUTSIDE HIROSHIMA.
- WHAT WAS IT THAT MADE
YOU DECIDE TO MOVE
SO FAR AWAY FROM YOUR HOME
TO START OFF HIGH SCHOOL?
- HMM. THERE WASN'T ONE THING
THAT DID IT.
I'VE JUST ALWAYS LIKED NEW
BEGINNINGS AND ENVIRONMENTS.
IT'S WHEN I FEEL LIKE I'M MAKING
THE MOST OUT OF MY LIFE.
IT KEEPS ME HAPPY
AND ON MY TOES.
- OH.
- I LOVE TOKYO. I THOUGHT THAT
LIVING HERE WOULD BE A BLAST.
BETTER THAN MOVING TO A CITY
ONLY HALF AS BIG AND
HALF AS FUN, RIGHT?
- I DIDN'T WANT
TO CHANGE MY LIFE.
I WANTED TO STAY IN SCHOOL
WITH THE SAME FRIENDS
I'VE ALWAYS HAD.
THAT'S ALL I WANTED.
I WAS ONLY JUMPING THE HIGH JUMP
FOR FUN UNTIL THE SCOUTS CAME.
THEN EVERYONE STARTED TELLING ME
I SHOULD GET OUT WHILE I COULD.
GO TO A GOOD SCHOOL.
I NEVER WANTED TO BE HERE.
THE WHOLE CITY IS OVERCROWDED.
AND THE PEOPLE
COULDN'T BE RUDER.
AND I HAVE
A VERY WEIRD NEIGHBOR.
BUT THAT WEIRD NEIGHBOR
HAS HELPED ME
TO BREAK MY HIGH JUMP RECORD
AND HE SHOWED ME A REALLY
NICE PLACE TO HAVE LUNCH TODAY.
IT MAY BE JUST A LITTLE BIT,
BUT I'M STARTING TO
LIKE IT HERE.
IN THE CITY.
- RIGHT. OF COURSE. THE CITY.
- WELL, I GUESS I OWE YOU
A HUGE THANK YOU
FOR SHOWING ME AROUND.
- WHY NOT? THANK ME, SURE.
- WE SHOULD HURRY BACK HOME. I'M
SURE YOUR AUNT IS WAITING ON US.
- RIGHT. WELL, HEY, WAIT UP!
- Ayano: CONGRATULATIONS,
SUZUKA AND YAMATO!
- THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR THIS!
- I'M SO EMBARRASSED!
- THANKS FOR HAVING ME, AYANO.
- WHAT ON EARTH
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- THE THREE OF YOU ARE GOING
TO THE SAME HIGH SCHOOL,
SO I FIGURED THIS WOULD BE FINE.
- THAT'S WHAT I SAID.
- IT'S SO CUTE THAT
YOU'RE STARTING HIGH SCHOOL.
I REMEMBER THE INNOCENT
DAYS OF MY YOUTH
LIKE THEY WERE YESTERDAY!
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU ACTUALLY HAD ANY
INNOCENT DAYS IN YOUR LIFE.
- WHAT DO YOU THINK I AM?
- Miho: WHY ARE YOU TWO
HERE ANYWAY?
- WE JUST WANTED
TO OFFER OUR REGARDS.
- THE MORE PEOPLE THE BETTER,
THAT'S WHAT I SAY.
- THE ONLY REASON YOU'RE HERE
IS TO GET A FREE MEAL
OFF MY MOTHER.
- I MADE PLENTY OF
FOOD TO GO AROUND.
YOU CAN HAVE AS
MUCH AS YOU LIKE.
- SO LET'S EAT.
- All: LET'S EAT!
- HERE'S SOME FOR YOU, GORO.
- I GOTTA SAY, THIS IS THE
BEST HOME COOKING EVER!
YOU COULD BE A
PROFESSIONAL CHEF!
- THANKS. YOU'RE ALWAYS WELCOME
TO DINNER. YOU KNOW THAT.
- I MIGHT TAKE YOU UP ON THAT.
- YEAH, I'LL BET.
- I FEEL STUPID.
I LEFT THE WINE BEHIND.
- GOT YA COVERED.
- AREN'T YOU JUST ON TOP
OF EVERYTHING?
- A RED WINE TO MATCH
THE COLOR OF YOUR VELVET LIPS.
- WHAT AN ASS.
- SAOTOME, MAYBE YOU SHOULD TRY
NOT TO DRINK TOO MUCH TONIGHT.
- LIKE YOU'RE ONE
TO TALK, MEGUMI.
SO, MEGUMI, AM I MISTAKEN OR
ARE YOU A GRAD SCHOOL STUDENT?
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- THEN YOU MUST BE VERY SMART.
MAYBE YOU COULD FIND
TIME IN YOUR SCHEDULE
TO TUTOR ME SOMETIME.
- I'M ALWAYS HAPPY TO HELP.
- WAY TO GO, MEGUMI. HE'S HOT.
AND HE SEEMS TO LIKE
MORE THAN YOUR BOOBS.
- STOP IT!
YOU'RE DRIVING ME CRAZY!
- WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
- YOU ALWAYS BRIGHTEN
THE ROOM, YASUNOBU.
- YEAH! LIKE A DEAD LIGHT BULB.
- YOU MIGHT WANT
TO STOP TALKING NOW.
- I LIKE CHEERFUL PEOPLE.
- Ayano: I THINK THAT'S
ENOUGH FUN FOR ONE NIGHT,
BOYS AND GIRLS.
THANKS FOR EVERYTHING.
- Yuka: I DON'T WANNA GO HOME.
LET'S HAVE A POST-PARTY PARTY!
- Yasunobu: GOOD IDEA.
- Megumi: HOW 'BOUT YOU, YAMATO?
- UM, NO THANKS.
I'LL HAVE TO PASS.
I WAS TIRED, MAN. WHY'D YOU DRAG
ME OUT HERE WITH YOU?
- BECAUSE MY NEW FRIEND YUKA
WOULD VERY MUCH LIKE
A BOX OF RICE CRACKERS.
- I DON'T GET IT. YOU'LL DO
ANYTHING A GIRL ASKS YOU TO.
- WELL, MAYBE YOU SHOULD
BE TAKING NOTES.
- SERIOUSLY? THE CRAP YOU
PULL JUST TO GET GIRLS
TO LIKE YOU AMAZES ME.
- COME ON, MAN. YOU KNOW
I DON'T SAY IT UNLESS I MEAN IT.
AND ANYWAY, NAME ME ANY GIRL
WHO DOESN'T LIKE SOME FLATTERY.
- I WONDER IF SOME KIND WORDS
MIGHT WORK ON ASAHINA.
SO GROW A PAIR ALREADY
AND GIVE THE GIRL A COMPLIMENT.
- NO, MAN. I CAN'T DO THAT!
- I KNOW.
SUCKS TO BE YOU. ( scoffs )
- WHAT! WHATEVER.
- THAT SUZUKA IS
ONE FINE LOOKING YOUNG LADY.
SO, WHY'D YOU TELL ME
SHE WAS FAT AND UGLY?
THERE SOME REASON YOU DIDN'T
TELL YOUR GOOD FRIEND
THE TRUTH ABOUT HER?
- NO. NOTHING SEEMS
TO COME TO MIND.
- OH, OKAY, GOOD THEN.
THAT MEANS I CAN ASK HER OUT.
I'VE ALWAYS HAD A THING
FOR ATHLETES.
- SINCE WHEN?
SHE'D NEVER GO OUT WITH YOU.
YOU'RE NOWHERE
NEAR HER TYPE!
- OH, YEAH? LET'S FIND OUT.
YO, SUZUKA!
- I THOUGHT YOU GUYS WERE
GONNA HAVE AN AFTER-PARTY.
- WE ARE. WE'RE JUST ON
A SNACK RUN. HOW ABOUT YOU?
ISN'T IT KINDA LATE
TO BE RUNNING?
NOT IF YOU'RE ME.
I MISSED SOME MILES TODAY
THAT I'M TRYING TO MAKE UP.
- WOW, YOU'RE REALLY DEDICATED.
I RESPECT THAT, BUT YOU
SHOULDN'T BE OUT HERE ALL ALONE.
LET ME WALK YOU HOME, OKAY?
- YOU SURE?
- OH, NO, I INSIST.
- HEY, WHAT ABOUT THE SNACKS WE
WERE GETTING?
- I THINK YOU CAN HANDLE IT.
COME ON, MAN,
HELP A BROTHER OUT.
- NO WAY! I'M WALKING ASAHINA
BACK HOME!
COME ON, LET'S GO.
- LET GO OF ME. I'M NOT A DOG!
YAMATO!
- SCORE ONE FOR YAMATO.
BEST OF LUCK TO YOU, BUDDY.
( chuckles ) YOU'LL NEED IT.
- YOU CAN LET GO OF MY ARM NOW!
I'M LOOSING CIRCULATION!
WHAT IS YOUR PROBLEM?
- IT'S... IT'S NOTHING.
- I KNOW. SUCKS TO BE YOU.
- I'M NOT GONNA MISS MY CHANCE.
I CAN DO THIS.
YOU KNOW SOMETHING, ASAHINA?
- WHAT?
- I WAS LOOKING
AT YOUR EARS EARLIER.
AND YOU KNOW, I THINK
THEY'RE REALLY NICE.
- ( scoffs )
- I MEAN THEY'RE
PERFECTLY SYMMETRICAL
AND THEY'RE MOUNTED AT
JUST THE RIGHT SPOTS
ON YOUR HEAD.
- ARE YOU HAVING
SOME KIND OF SEIZURE?
- WHAT? A SEIZURE?
NO, I'M TRYING TO GIVE YOU
A COMPLIMENT
BUT YOU'RE NOT
BEING NICE AT ALL!
- OH, WELL... MAYBE
THAT'S BECAUSE
I'M AN UGLY, FAT, OLD WOMAN
WITH A NASTY ATTITUDE!
- YOU'RE STILL STUCK ON THAT?
GET OVER IT!
- I'M NO WORSE THAN SOMEONE
WHO SPREADS THOSE LIES
IN THE FIRST PLACE!
- YOU'RE RIGHT, I'M SORRY.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
- THIS IS SO
FREAKIN' HUMILIATING.
( sighs ) YOU LOOK SO COOL
WHEN YOU'RE OUT THERE
DOING THE HIGH JUMP.
BUT THE SECOND
YOU OPEN YOUR MOUTH...
- WHAT?
DID YOU JUST TELL ME
THAT YOU THINK I'M COOL?
- YEAH. I WAS FASCINATED BY YOU
THE MOMENT I FIRST SAW YOU.
- NO ONE HAS EVER SAID
ANYTHING LIKE THAT TO ME.
SO THANKS I GUESS.
BUT, THAT'S JUST BECAUSE...
WELL, WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
YOU'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYONE HIGH JUMP BEFORE.
- YOU MIGHT JUST BE RIGHT
ABOUT THAT,
BUT I'M A PRETTY GOOD JUDGE
OF WHAT LOOKS GOOD
AND WHAT DOESN'T.
- YOU ARE? BECAUSE TO BE HONEST,
IT DOESN'T SEEM LIKE YOU PAY
MUCH ATTENTION TO ANYTHING.
- TRUST ME.
I KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING.
YOU LOOK GREAT OUT THERE!
REALLY! BEAUTIFUL! MAGNIFICENT!
- ( giggles )
- I SUPPOSE THAT WAS ALL
I NEEDED. THAT MOMENT.
I'M FEELING...
- WHAT?
- OH, SORRY, I WAS DAYDREAMING.
I'M FALLING IN LOVE
WITH YOU, ASAHINA.
BUT I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW TO SAY IT.
- ( theme song playing )
-♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ABOVE ♪
♪ NOW IS ALL WE HAVE ♪
♪ WITH A LITTLE FEELING
AND A LOT OF LOVE ♪
♪ WE TURN UP THE HEAT AND RUN ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- ♪ ALL MY LIFE HERE ON THE
GROUND ABOUT TO RUN AND NOW ♪
♪ I FIND I MUST
ASK MYSELF WHY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE SOMETHING IS STIRRING ♪
♪ I FEEL IT WHISPERING IN ME ♪
♪ SOME DAYS I WAKE UP ♪
♪ BUT MY HEART'S
STILL SLEEPING ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME
TO RUN AND TRY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME TO FLY ♪
♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ON HIGH ♪
♪ WITH OUR GOAL IN SIGHT ♪
♪ WE WILL RUN
WITH ALL OUR MIGHT ♪
♪ TOMORROW AND TODAY
WILL NEVER EVER PASS US BY ♪
♪ WE WILL NOT STOP NOW ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR HEART ALIVE
AND YOUR DREAM SURVIVES ♪
♪ AND YOU CROSS
THE FINISH LINE ♪
♪ LET IT GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- Yamato: ( sighs )
I'M SO THIRSTY.
THANKS FOR THE DRINK, ASAHINA.
- Suzuka: NO PROBLEM.
IT'S JUST WHAT I HAVE ON ME.
- WHAT IS IT?
- OH, IT'S A HONEY LEMON DRINK.
WITHOUT THE LEMON. OR HONEY.
- YOU MEAN WATER?