- ♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANT TO HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL
REWRITE THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- I DON'T HAVE A CLUE
WHY I'M DOING THIS,
OR WHAT I'LL SAY WHEN
I SEE ASAHINA.
I JUST KNOW THAT I HAVE TO GO
TO FIND HER.
I CAN'T GET HER OFF MY MIND.
AND IT'S DRIVING ME CRAZY.
( panting)
IT MUST BE
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE.
IT CAN'T BE THAT HOUSE, CAN IT?
IT IS?
THIS IS HER HOUSE?
IT'S MASSIVE.
HER FAMILY MUST BE LOADED.
MAYBE, I SHOULD THINK
OF WHAT I'LL SAY FIRST.
- Woman: EXCUSE ME,
MAY I HELP YOU?
AND WHO MIGHT YOU BE?
- OH, ME? I'M A FRIEND OF
ASAHINA'S FROM SCHOOL.
MY NAME'S YAMATO AKITSUKI.
- AND JUST WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE, YAMATO?
- I GUESS I'M NOT EXACTLY
SURE WHY I'M HERE.
ALL I KNOW IS THAT
IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT
THAT I TALK TO ASAHINA,
IF THAT'S OKAY.
- SO, DON'T TELL ME
YOU RAN ALL THE WAY HERE.
- YEAH.
- CHASING AFTER SUZUKA?
- I THINK I'LL JUST HEAD BACK.
- IT'S OKAY, I'LL TAKE YOU
TO HER.
AND YOU CAN
MEET KAZUKI, TOO.
SO YOU'RE TELLING ME THAT THE
TWO OF YOU WENT TO FANTASY LAND
AND THAT YOU CONFESSED YOU
HAD FEELINGS FOR SUZUKA.
- UM, YEAH, THAT'S IT.
- AND NOW YOU THINK THAT SHE
CAME BACK HERE TO GO ON A DATE.
THAT MUST MAGNIFY
YOUR SENSE OF REJECTION.
- ( laughs )
AIN'T THAT THE TRUTH.
( thinking) IT'S LIKE SHE'S
TORTURING A WOUNDED ANIMAL.
AND WHERE ARE WE GOING, ANYWAY?
WE'VE BEEN WALKING FOREVER.
EVEN IF SHE IS TAKING ME TO MEET
ASAHINA AND KAZUKI,
WHAT IN THE WORLD
AM I GOING TO SAY?
I REALLY DIDN'T THINK
THIS ONE THROUGH.
- HE WAS IN AN ACCIDENT.
A TRUCK SLAMMED INTO HIS
BUS WHEN HE WAS ON HIS WAY
TO A TOURNAMENT.
- YEAH. IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE I'VE GONE HOME TO SEE HIM.
- SHE CAME HOME
TO SEE KAZUKI, BUT HE'S GONE.
I KNOW THIS
MUST SEEM INSENSITIVE,
BUT THE LOOK ON
HER FACE, IT'S SO MATURE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN HER
LOOK SO BEAUTIFUL.
- KAZUKI...
HE WAS A YEAR AHEAD OF SUZUKA
AT THEIR JUNIOR HIGH,
AND HE WAS THE STAR
OF THE TRACK TEAM.
SUZUKA ADMIRED HIM
A GREAT DEAL.
SHE RESPECTED HIS DRIVE
AND DETERMINATION.
- ( gunshot fires )
- THEY CALLED HIM "KAZUKI TSUDA,
THE ROCKET STARTER."
AND I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYONE RUN
AS FAST AS HE COULD.
- DID YOU SAY, "ROCKET STARTER"?
- IT WAS A SILLY NICKNAME
THE NEIGHBORHOOD
KIDS CAME UP WITH FOR HIM.
YOU KNOW, YOU KIND OF
REMIND ME OF KAZUKI.
IT'S BEEN TWO YEARS
SINCE HE PASSED.
AND EVERY CHANCE SHE GETS,
SUZUKA COMES BACK
HERE TO VISIT HIM.
- I SHOULD GO.
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
- PLEASE DON'T TELL ASAHINA
THAT I CAME HERE TODAY.
- SUZUKA.
- WHAT'RE YOU DOING HERE?
- I THINK IT'S TIME WE
HAD A LITTLE TALK.
- OKAY.
- KAZUKI'S BEEN GONE
FOR OVER TWO YEARS NOW,
AND I'M STARTING TO THINK
IT'S TIME TO LET GO.
YOU SHOULD SPEND YOUR DAYS
OFF WITH YOUR FRIENDS,
LIKE A NORMAL HIGH
SCHOOL STUDENT.
GO SOMEWHERE FUN AND EXCITING.
MAYBE FANTASY LAND?
- I DON'T WANT TO GO
TO A PLACE LIKE THAT.
- SUZUKA.
WHY CAN'T YOU LET IT GO? PLEASE.
YOU KNOW, YOU KIND OF
REMIND ME OF KAZUKI.
- I COULD TELL
JUST BY LOOKING AT HIM.
HE'S DEFINITELY
YOUR TYPE, ASAHINA.
- I WAS JUST A REPLACEMENT.
- Man: THIS STOP, EBISU STATION.
- ASAHINA NEVER SAW ME
FOR WHO I AM.
SHE JUST SAW ME
AS A REMINDER OF KAZUKI.
I'M SUCH AN IDIOT.
( sighs )
- Miho: YAMATO.
- HMM?
- HOW DID IT GO?
SO, DID YOU TALK TO HER?
YOU BETTER HAVE, BECAUSE I SURE
WENT TO A WHOLE LOT OF TROUBLE.
I TRACKED DOWN
HER HOME ADDRESS FOR YOU.
- OH, YEAH?
WELL, THANKS FOR THAT.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- NOTHING. I JUST NEED TO GET
SOME REST, I THINK.
- BUT IT'S ALMOST TIME
FOR SUPPER.
WHAT'S WRONG?
- ( bell ringing )
- YOU CAN DO IT, COME ON.
- Suzune: KAZUKI'S BEEN GONE
FOR OVER TWO YEARS NOW,
AND I'M STARTING TO THINK
IT'S TIME TO LET GO.
- MAYBE SHE'S RIGHT.
BUT IT FEELS LIKE TIME HAS
STOPPED MOVING SINCE THEN.
- Man: ASAHINA!
LOOKS GOOD! I FEEL BETTER
ABOUT LEAVING KNOWING
THAT YOU'RE DOING SO WELL.
- THANKS, SENPAI.
- I THINK I'VE TAUGHT YOU
ALL THAT I CAN.
- WELL, I'M SURE YOU'LL DO GREAT
ON YOUR ENTRANCE EXAMS,
BUT GOOD LUCK.
AND THANKS AGAIN FOR EVERYTHING.
- I'M CONFIDENT THAT
WITH YOU HERE THE HIGH JUMP TEAM
WILL REMAIN ON
THE TOP OF THEIR GAME.
- THANKS.
- Kazuki: I'M NOT SO SURE
ABOUT THAT.
YOU SURE SHE'S AS GOOD
AS YOU THINK SHE IS?
- Suzuka: TSUDA SENPAI.
- YOU KNOW AS WELL
AS I DO THAT SUZI HERE
TENDS TO CHOKE UNDER PRESSURE.
AND I'M NOT SO SURE
HAVING HER AS THE LEADER
OF THE SQUAD IS A GOOD THING,
BUT I GUESS
WE'LL SEE SOON ENOUGH.
- I DON'T HAVE TO STAND HERE AND
TAKE THIS FROM SOMEONE WHO'S
NEVER WORKED HARD FOR
ANYTHING IN HIS WHOLE LIFE.
AND WHAT DO YOU KNOW ANYWAY?
YOU'RE JUST A SPRINTER.
AND MY NAME'S NOT SUZI. DOES
HE HAVE TO BE OUR NEW CAPTAIN?
THERE'S GOTTA BE SOMEONE
WHO'S MORE DESERVING THAN HIM.
MIYAMOTO SENPAI, MAYBE.
- BUT KAZUKI'S THE BEST ATHLETE
ON THE TEAM, BY FAR.
- THE MAN'S RIGHT.
- BIG DEAL. YOU JUST
GOT EXTREMELY LUCKY
GOING TO NATIONALS
TWO YEARS IN A ROW.
- ARE YOU JEALOUS? YOU HAVEN'T
EVEN MADE IT TO REGIONALS YET.
SO YOU'D BETTER DO AS
THE CAPTAIN TELLS YOU
AND GET ALONG WITH ME, OKAY?
- EVEN THOUGH I CAN'T STAND
THE SIGHT OF YOU,
IT WON'T BE A PROBLEM
IF YOU'RE RESPECTFUL ENOUGH.
- OH, REALLY?
- CALM DOWN, YOU TWO.
KAZUKI'S RIGHT.
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
FIND SOME WAY TO GET ALONG
AND STOP ARGUING ALL THE TIME.
- SURE. WE'LL FIGURE
SOMETHING OUT. RIGHT SUZI?
- STOP CALLING ME THAT.
( thinking ) REALLY. WHY IS
THIS GUY THE NEW TEAM CAPTAIN?
- Kazuki: GEEZ!
ALL I'M SAYING IS THAT PEOPLE
SHOULD BE ABLE TO HAVE FUN
WHILE THEY'RE PRACTICING.
YOU NEED TO LEARN HOW TO
LIGHTEN UP ONCE IN A WHILE.
- I DON'T NEED TO LIGHTEN UP,
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO NEEDS
TO LEARN HOW TO BE SERIOUS.
IT'S NOT THAT HARD!
EVERYTHING HAS TO BE A JOKE
WITH YOU, DOESN'T IT?
- NOT EVERYTHING.
- HAVE YOU NOTICED THAT
THEY'VE BEEN ARGUING
EVEN MORE THAN USUAL LATELY.
- YEAH, SHOULDN'T WE
DO SOMETHING, MIYAMOTO?
- NO, LEAVE 'EM ALONE.
WE NEED TO LET THEM WORK OUT
THEIR PROBLEMS ON THEIR OWN.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY
THEY'LL BE ABLE
TO RESOLVE THEIR DIFFERENCES.
- HEY, MIYACCHI! IT'S BEST
TO GRILL SAUSAGES, RIGHT?
- NO, IT'S DEFINITELY BEST
TO BOIL THEM.
- I DON'T KNOW IF THEY'RE
EVER GONNA LEARN
TO LIKE EACH OTHER. SERIOUSLY.
- UGH! WHY ARE YOU
SO HARDHEADED?
( thinking ) HE'D ARGUE WITH ME
EVEN IF I SAID THE SKY WAS BLUE.
- Kazuki: AWESOME.
WE FINALLY GOT IN
THE NEW SHIPMENT
OF STARTING BLOCKS TODAY.
- THAT'S WAY TOO MANY.
GREAT. HE CAN'T EVEN MANAGE
OUR BUDGET PROPERLY!
YET HE EASILY MADE HIS WAY
INTO THE NATIONAL TOURNAMENT
IN HIS SECOND YEAR
OF JUNIOR HIGH.
IT WAS MY FIRST YEAR AND
I DIDN'T EVEN MAKE IT
THROUGH THE REGIONALS.
MAN, I HATE THAT GUY.
BUT THAT WAS LAST YEAR.
NOW THIS YEAR'S MEET IS MY
CHANCE TO QUALIFY FOR NATIONALS.
- 'M SURPRISED WE'RE THE ONLY
ONES WHO MADE IT TO REGIONALS.
I FIGURED WE'D HAVE MORE
TEAMMATES HERE WITH US.
- I JUST GOT LUCKY.
I BARELY EVEN QUALIFIED.
BUT I THINK THAT YOU TWO
HAVE A GOOD CHANCE
OF MAKING IT TO THE NATIONALS
IF YOU APPLY YOURSELVES.
- WELL, I'M A SHOO-IN. I'M NOT
SO SURE ABOUT SUZI, THOUGH.
- SO ARROGANT.
- IT'S JUST LIKE
I'VE ALWAYS SAID.
YOU HAVE A TENDENCY TO CHOKE
WHEN YOU'RE UNDER PRESSURE.
AND I HATE TO BREAK IT TO YOU,
BUT ATHLETES THAT CAN'T
PERFORM WELL UNDER PRESSURE
WILL NEVER MAKE IT TO THE TOP.
- Announcer: NUMBER SIXTEEN.
SECOND ATTEMPT, FAILED.
- WHAT SHOULD I DO?
I CAN'T GET THE RIGHT TAKE OFF.
AND THE FORM ON MY JUMP
WAS TERRIBLE!
IF I DROP THE BAR AGAIN, I'LL BE
OUT OF THE PRELIMINARY.
- HEY, SUZUKA!
KEEP YOUR HEAD UP
AND DON'T GIVE UP YET.
YOU KNOW THAT YOU CAN
JUMP THAT HEIGHT EASILY.
- ( gasps ) TSUDA SENPAI?
OH MAN, YOU'RE HOPELESS!
YOU BETTER FIND YOUR RHYTHM
OR YOU'RE OUTTA HERE!
LIKE THIS.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
- ARGH! STOP IT ALREADY,
YOU'RE EMBARRASSING ME.
- I'M GONNA HAVE TO DISQUALIFY
YOU IF YOU DON'T BE QUIET.
- OH, I'M SORRY, SIR.
- ( thinking ) IDIOT.
HERE GOES.
- WOULD YOU MIND GETTING A
LITTLE CLOSER TOGETHER?
I CAN'T GET BOTH OF YOU
IN THE PICTURE.
- I'M NOT MOVING.
- YOU COULD SHOW
SOME APPRECIATION.
THE ONLY REASON YOU
MADE IT TO THE FINALS
IS BECAUSE I HELPED YOU.
- DON'T FLATTER YOURSELF,
I COULDA MADE THAT JUMP
EASILY WITHOUT YOUR HELP.
- BUT I DIDN'T HELP
YOU OUT IN THE FINALS
AND YOU ONLY MANAGED TO
COME IN AT AN EMBARRASSING
SIXTH PLACE.
- YOU ARE SO ARROGANT!
WHAT DOES AN IDIOT SPRINTER
LIKE YOU KNOW ABOUT HIGH JUMP?
- YOU'VE REALLY GOT SOME FIRE
IN THAT TONGUE OF YOURS,
DON'T YOU, SUZI?
- KNOCK IT OFF. I'M TRYING
TO TAKE A PICTURE HERE,
AND I DON'T HAVE
ALL DAY YOU KNOW.
- ALL RIGHT, FINE. LET'S DO IT.
- ( camera clicks )
- Suzuka: TSUDA SENPAI RAN
THE HUNDRED METERS
IN TEN POINT EIGHT TWO SECONDS.
THAT WAS THE BEST TIME
IN THE COUNTRY THAT YEAR.
AND HE WAS OFF TO
NATIONALS ONCE AGAIN.
AND THEN, ONE DAY...
- AND THAT'S IT.
- THANKS FOR STICKING AROUND
TO HELP OUT.
CLEANING GOES A LOT QUICKER
WITH AN EXTRA PAIR OF HANDS.
- OH, NO PROBLEM. SO TODAY WILL
BE MY LAST DAY OF PRACTICE HERE.
AFTER NATIONALS TOMORROW,
I'LL BE LEAVING AND WE WON'T
BE TEAMMATES ANYMORE.
I HOPE I GO OUT WITH A BANG
AND BRING BACK A GOLD MEDAL.
- I'M SURE YOU WILL.
YOU'VE GOT NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT. AFTER ALL,
YOUR TIME IN THE REGIONALS WAS
THE BEST IN THE WHOLE COUNTRY.
- THANKS, BUT WHAT'S WITH YOUR
NEWFOUND FAITH IN ME?
- IT'S NOT NEW...
- WELL, I APPRECIATE IT,
BUT IT'S NOT GOING TO BE EASY.
THIS IS THE NATIONALS
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
- SENPAI...
- I KNOW I TEND TO COME OFF
A BIT COCKY AT TIMES.
BUT BEFORE A RACE I'M THE
MOST NERVOUS PERSON
ON THE STARTING LINE, ACTUALLY.
AND ALL I WANT TO DO
IS FIND A PLACE TO HIDE.
- REALLY? I THOUGHT
YOU NEVER GOT NERVOUS.
- WELL THEN, YOU THOUGHT WRONG.
'CAUSE I'VE ALWAYS GOT
BUTTERFLIES BEFORE A RACE.
- HMM, I SEE.
- I WISH YOU COULD GO WITH ME.
I COULD USE A FRIENDLY FACE
ON THE SIDELINES.
- YOU'LL BE FINE. YOU
REALLY DON'T NEED ME
TO GO WITH YOU ANYWAY.
AND EVEN IF I DID GO, YOU'D
PROBABLY MAKE FUN OF ME
THE WHOLE TIME.
- LISTEN, SUZUKA.
I JUST WANTED TO SAY
THAT I'VE HAD A CRUSH ON YOU
EVER SINCE THE DAY WE MET.
I'M SORRY THAT I WAS
ALWAYS MEAN TO YOU.
I WANTED TO BE MYSELF AND ACT
NATURALLY AROUND YOU
BUT I COULDN'T.
SO, I MASKED IT
BEHIND THE CONSTANT BICKERING.
- IT'S OKAY.
I MEAN, I DID THE SAME.
- SO YOU DON'T REALLY HATE ME?
- NO, I DON'T HATE YOU.
I DON'T.
- BECAUSE I REALLY WANT TO
BE WITH YOU, SUZUKA.
- BUT YOU'RE GOING.
YOU'LL BE LEAVING SOON
AND THEN WHAT'LL WE DO?
- I DON'T KNOW, BUT WE CAN
FIGURE IT OUT.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO ANSWER ME NOW.
WAIT UNTIL I GET BACK
FROM NATIONALS,
WITH THE GOLD MEDAL OF COURSE.
LATER.
- I'VE NEVER EVEN THOUGHT
ABOUT HIM LIKE THAT.
I HAD NO IDEA THAT HE LIKED ME.
WHAT SHOULD I DO? I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO TELL HIM.
( sighs )
I DIDN'T KNOW EXACTLY
HOW I FELT ABOUT YOU.
NOT UNTIL YOU WERE ALREADY GONE
AND BY THEN IT WAS TOO LATE.
I WISH I HAD THE CHANCE
TO TELL YOU HOW I FELT.
TSUDA.
- THE METROPOLITAN TOURNAMENT'S
COMING UP TOMORROW
AND AKITSUKI STILL HASN'T
SHOWN UP FOR PRACTICE.
- WELL, CAPTAIN, I STILL HAVE
HIM ENTERED AS OUR TOP SPRINTER.
BUT I AM STARTING TO WORRY
ABOUT HIM. I WONDER WHERE HE IS.
- SENPAI, I DON'T MIND
TAKING A LOOK AROUND
TO SEE IF I CAN FIND HIM.
- OKAY, THANKS, HASHIBA.
- NO PROBLEM.
- ( bell ringing )
- HEY, MR. TRACK AND FIELD,
YOU GOOFIN' OFF AGAIN?
ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
- Miki: HEY, AKITSUKI.
- HMM?
JUST WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING IN HERE?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
AT PRACTICE.
- SORRY. I DON'T
FEEL LIKE GOING TODAY.
- COME ON! WOULD YOU
STOP BEING SO IRRESPONSIBLE?
YOU'RE REPRESENTING US
AT THE TOURNAMENT THIS WEEKEND.
- WHY DON'T YOU BACK OFF A BIT?
HE SAID HE DOESN'T WANT
TO GO TO PRACTICE.
- STAY OUT OF THIS.
LISTEN, IF YOU EVER HOPE
TO BE WITH SUZUKA
THEN YOU CAN'T GO
ON ACTING LIKE THIS.
I TOLD YOU THAT BEFORE.
AKITSUKI, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
MIYAMOTO SENPAI BELIEVES IN YOU.
THAT'S WHY HE ENTERED YOU
IN THE TOURNAMENT.
COME TO PRACTICE
AFTER SCHOOL, OKAY?
( sighs )
- ( doorbell ringing )
- HMM?
YES.
OH, ASAHINA?
- I CAME TO ASK YOU
IF YOU'RE QUITTING THE TEAM.
YOU'VE BEEN WORKING HARD
AND MAKING A LOT OF PROGRESS.
I WAS BEGINNING TO
THINK THAT MAYBE
YOU WERE TAKING THIS SERIOUSLY.
BUT NOW, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO THINK.
- WHY WOULD YOU START...
- JUST LEAVE ME ALONE.
WHAT? YOU ALWAYS WANTED ME
TO QUIT, DIDN'T YOU?
NOW I'M GIVING YOU
WHAT YOU WANTED.
- I SEE.
YOU CAN NEVER TAKE ANYTHING YOU
DO SERIOUSLY, CAN YOU, YAMATO?
YOU JOIN THE TEAM ON A WHIM,
THEN QUIT JUST AS EASILY.
YOU'RE JUST AN
IMPULSIVE LITTLE BOY.
- YOU'RE COMPLETELY RIGHT,
'CAUSE I'M NOTHING LIKE HIM.
BECAUSE I'M NOT KAZUKI, AM I?
WHAT WERE YOU DOING, ASAHINA?
JUST USING ME AS A WAY
TO PRETEND TO BE WITH HIM?
IS THAT ALL THAT I AM TO YOU?
I'M TIRED OF BEING COMPARED
TO SOME DEAD GUY.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
I GUESS THAT MAYBE I CROSSED
THE LINE BRINGING UP KAZUKI.
AND SHE LOOKED AT ME
WITH SUCH DISGUST.
- THIS DOESN'T LOOK GOOD.
I'M BEGINNING TO THINK THAT
AKITSUKI MIGHT NOT BE COMING.
HEY, ASAHINA, HAVE YOU
HEARD ANYTHING FROM HIM?
- NO, NOT REALLY.
- WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ABOVE ♪
♪ NOW IS ALL WE HAVE ♪
♪ WITH A LITTLE FEELING
AND A LOT OF LOVE ♪
♪ WE TURN UP THE HEAT AND RUN ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- ♪ ALL MY LIFE HERE ON THE
GROUND ABOUT TO RUN AND NOW ♪
♪ I FIND I MUST
ASK MYSELF WHY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE SOMETHING IS STIRRING ♪
♪ I FEEL IT WHISPERING IN ME ♪
♪ SOME DAYS I WAKE UP ♪
♪ BUT MY HEART'S
STILL SLEEPING ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME
TO RUN AND TRY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME TO FLY ♪
♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ON HIGH ♪
♪ WITH OUR GOAL IN SIGHT ♪
♪ WE WILL RUN
WITH ALL OUR MIGHT ♪
♪ TOMORROW AND TODAY
WILL NEVER EVER PASS US BY ♪
♪ WE WILL NOT STOP NOW ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR HEART ALIVE
AND KEEP SURVIVING ♪
♪ AND CROSS
THE FINISH LINE ♪
♪ LET IT GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- Yamato: THE CICADAS
ARE OUT EARLY.
THEY'RE CHIRPING,
AND IT'S ONLY JUNE.
I'M SUCH AN IDIOT, AREN'T I?
ALWAYS RUNNING MY BIG MOUTH.
- Suzuka: IT'S BEEN MUCH HOTTER
THAN USUAL THIS YEAR.
MAYBE THEY CAME OUT EARLY
THINKING IT WAS SUMMER ALREADY.
- HUH?
- JUST A THOUGHT.