♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- Suzuka: THAT MIGHT NOT BE THE
SAFEST SPOT TO SLEEP, GORO.
- ( meows )
- ARE YOU LEAVING ALREADY?
- HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
- SORRY, I HAVE AN EARLY
PRACTICE TODAY.
- THAT WAS ODD.
- Teacher: THE WAR OF 1812
WAS FOUGHT BETWEEN THE...
- ASAHINA'S BEEN A
BIT STANDOFFISH LATELY...
SHE'S ALWAYS LEAVING
EARLY AND COMING HOME LATE.
I HARDLY SEE HER ANYMORE.
AND WHEN I
DO SEE HER, SHE
BARELY NOTICES ME.
I THOUGHT THINGS WERE GOING
WELL. WHAT DID I DO WRONG?
THIS GIRL'S GIVING
ME A HEADACHE.
WHY DOES SHE HAVE TO
MAKE THINGS SO COMPLICATED?
- YOU MEAN TODAY?
- HUH?
- PLEASE, ASAHINA. WOULD YOU
COME WITH ME AFTER PRACTICE?
- IS THIS GUY ASKING HER OUT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
JUST THE TWO OF US?
- THAT'S RIGHT. JUST US.
- WHO DOES THIS GUY THINK HE IS?
HE SURE IS COMING ON STRONG...
THAT'S NOT GONNA WORK
WITH HER, PRETTY BOY...
HURRY UP AND REJECT
HIM, ASAHINA.
- Soichi: SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- SHE THINKS YOU'RE A MORON!
- SURE, WHY NOT?
- ( gasps )
- ( loud thud )
- WHY! I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE SAID YES
TO THAT GUY, JUST LIKE THAT!
IS SHE THE KIND OF GIRL WHO
WILL JUST GO ANYWHERE
WITH SOME GUY?
- YOU SHOULD CALM DOWN, DUDE.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO POP.
- SHUT UP!
WAIT. HOLD ON. I THINK I'M
IN THE MOOD FOR KARAOKE.
- EXCUSE ME?
- FOR SOME REASON I JUST
FEEL LIKE SCREAMING.
- OH BOY, THAT SOUNDS
LIKE TONS OF FUN.
- YOU'RE DAMN RIGHT IT DOES.
- Yasunobu: SAKURAI...
YOU WANNA JOIN US FOR
SOME KARAOKE OR WHAT?
- WHY'D YOU DO THAT?
I MEANT JUST US.
- OKAY, SURE.
- WELL, THE MORE THE MERRIER.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, YAMATO?
- BUT IF HONOKA'S THERE
I WON'T BE ABLE TO SCREAM
LIKE I WAS PLANNING TO.
- ♪ RAISE THE FLAG OF GLORY ♪
- ♪ THE CARP, THE CARP, THE
CARP OF HIROSHIMA THE CARP ♪
- Yasunobu:
HE SURE IS BELTING IT OUT.
MAN, I WISH HE'D
GIVE THE MIC TO ME.
- WE'RE GONNA GO ALL
THE WAY THIS YEAR!
- AMAZING, AKITSUKI... I NEVER
KNEW YOU COULD SING SO WELL.
- DECISIONS, DECISIONS...
- THAT HIT THE SPOT.
I WAS CRAVING SOME KARAOKE.
- THIS IS SO MUCH FUN!
I'M GLAD THAT WE CAME TOGETHER.
- WHAT'S THAT?
( groans )
- OH, WHAT'S THE
MATTER, AKITSUKI?
I HOPE THAT I DIDN'T SAY
ANYTHING TO MAKE YOU UPSET.
- IT'S NOTHING. I'M FINE.
- BUT, THAT'S MY...
THAT'S MY DRINK.
- HMM? WHAT'S THAT?
- OH, NOTHING. I DIDN'T
SAY ANYTHING.
OUR LIPS TOUCHED
THE SAME STRAW.
- HEY, SAKURAI... WHAT SONG
WOULD YOU LIKE TO HEAR ME SING?
- OH, ANYTHING'S FINE.
- THAT'S GREAT. GLAD YOU CARE.
- SO, I GUESS YOU'RE
REALLY THIRSTY?
- YEAH, JUST A BIT.
- THEN I'LL GO GET
TWO MORE DRINKS FOR US.
- FOR US?
I... I CAN'T... TAKE THIS!
( screams )
- OKAY, I THINK
I'VE PICKED A WINNER.
- LATER.
- WAIT, AKITSUKI,
I'LL GO WITH YOU.
- HOLD ON. I'M SINGING.
AND I CAN'T DO THAT
WITHOUT AN AUDIENCE.
YOU DON'T WANNA BE RUDE, DO YA?
- NO, I...
I GUESS I CAN STAY.
- ♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES STARE
OUT INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
- Honoka: THIS IS
AKITSUKI'S DRINK.
ANOTHER INDIRECT KISS!
- Yasunobu: HEY, ARE YOU
EVEN LISTENING TO ME?
- I WONDER IF
ASAHINA'S BACK YET.
I HAVE GOT TO GET
HER OFF OF MY MIND...
BUT I JUST CAN'T
SEEM TO THINK ABOUT
ANYTHING ELSE BUT HER.
- ( meows )
- HEY, THERE...
AREN'T YOU A PRETTY GIRL?
- ( meows )
- HEY, GORO... I DIDN'T
KNOW YOU HAD A GIRLFRIEND.
EVEN THE CAT HAS A GIRLFRIEND.
THAT'S JUST GREAT.
CONGRATULATIONS.
- Suzuka: I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU JUST SAID THAT.
- ( both laughing )
- ( mimics laughter )
OH, HE THINKS HE'S
JUST SO CLEVER.
I HOPE YOU LAUGH
UNTIL YOU PASS OUT.
- THAT'S THE ASAHINA I REMEMBER.
YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED A BIT.
- THAT'S NOT ENTIRELY TRUE.
- DON'T TELL ME THIS HAS
BEEN GOING ON FOR A WHILE...
( grunting )
( exclaims)
- YAMATO?
- HEY. STUPID CAT...
I DON'T WANNA MEET THIS DUDE.
- OH, YOU MUST BE
YAMATO AKITSUKI.
I'VE BEEN HEARING A LOT
ABOUT YOU FROM ASAHINA.
- REALLY? SHE CERTAINLY
HASN'T MENTIONED YOU.
I WONDER WHY.
- MY NAME'S SOICHI MIYAMOTO.
I'M A JUNIOR FROM
TRACK AND FIELD.
- HOW WOULD YOU LIKE
TO JOIN OUR TEAM?
- WHAT'S THAT?
- HE KNEW YOU AND
I ARE FRIENDS,
SO HE ASKED FOR AN INTRODUCTION.
HE WAS IMPRESSED WITH YOUR
TIME IN THE RACE THE OTHER DAY.
- SO THAT'S WHAT WAS...
GOING ON...
- I THOUGHT YOU
MIGHT FEEL WEIRD
IF I CAME TO SEE YOU ALONE,
SINCE WE'VE
NEVER MET BEFORE.
SO I ASKED ASAHINA
TO COME ALONG WITH ME.
SHE AND I HAVE
KNOWN EACH OTHER
SINCE JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL.
- ( laughs ) OH, YEAH, OKAY.
THAT MAKES PERFECT SENSE NOW.
IT'S NICE TO MEET
YOU, SOICHI. WELCOME!
- THANK YOU...
WILL YOU JOIN THE TEAM?
- NO, AFRAID NOT.
- ARE YOU SURE?
YOU HAVE THE TALENT
TO BECOME AN AMAZING SPRINTER.
- NO, I DON'T.
IT WAS A MISTAKE.
I PROBABLY JUST GOT
A LUCKY BREAK
WHEN I WON THAT RACE LAST WEEK.
- MAYBE THIS ISN'T A GOOD DAY.
I'LL ASK YOU AGAIN LATER.
- BUT, SENPAI...
- YA KNOW, I COULD TELL
JUST BY LOOKING AT HIM.
HE'S DEFINITELY YOUR
TYPE, ASAHINA.
- ( gasps )
WHAT IN THE WORLD
ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- ( chuckles )
I'LL SEE YOU LATER,
AKITSUKI. HAVE A
GOOD DAY, YOU TWO!
- SO I'M THE TYPE OF
GUY THAT YOU LIKE?
- UH...
MAYBE SHE DOES
LIKE ME AFTER ALL.
- ( Yamato groans )
- IN YOUR DREAMS, CREEP!
- I'M SO SORRY. ARE YOU OKAY?
- I THINK I'LL LIVE.
- ♪ STARTING LINE ♪
- ♪ TOGETHER WE'LL
REWRITE THE STORY ♪
- HMM. SO, YOU'RE ASKING
FOR MORE OF MY IMPECCABLE
INSIGHTS INTO WOMEN?
- I GUESS... I MUST BE
CRAZY OR SOMETHING...
BUT YOU'RE THE ONLY
ONE THAT I CAN ASK.
- SO, WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT'D SUZUKA DO
THAT'S GOT YOU SO UPSET?
IT'S NOT ABOUT HER. IT'S JUST
ABOUT GIRLS IN GENERAL.
- LOOK, DUDE,
I KNOW IT'S ABOUT HER.
AND FROM WHAT I CAN
TELL, SHE LIKES YOU.
- OH, YEAH, RIGHT!
YOU'VE GOT TO BE JOKING!
UH, DO YOU WANT SOME
OF MY CORNDOG?
- WHAT ARE YOU, FOUR?
ALL RIGHT, GIVE IT ME.
- HERE. I REALLY DON'T HAVE
A CLUE HOW WOMEN THINK...
AND I DON'T THINK I EVER WILL.
IT'S JUST NOT A SKILL I POSSESS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
- IF YOU'RE SO
WORRIED ABOUT IT,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST GO
AND ASK HER YOURSELF?
- HOW CAN I ASK HER
HOW SHE FEELS?
IF SHE LIKES ME OR NOT?
- ( thunder rumbling )
- UH, MUST BE A BLACKOUT.
- ( knock on door )
- Suzuka: YAMATO, ARE YOU
THERE? I'M COMING IN.
THE LIGHTS WENT OUT
SO I THOUGHT I'D COME BY.
YOU DON'T MIND, DO YOU?
- NO, I DON'T MIND.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- I'LL BE FINE. I THINK I JUST
NEED SOME COMPANY FOR A WHILE.
- NO, I UNDERSTAND.
WHAT'S THAT THING?
- IT'S AN AROMA CANDLE, SILLY.
- AROMA?
- DO YOU HAVE A LIGHTER
ANYWHERE, OR A MATCH?
- I THINK SO.
- Suzuka: SEE, SMELLS
NICE, RIGHT?
- YEAH. SURE.
- ( wind blowing )
- WOW, LISTEN...
IT'S COMING DOWN HARD.
- WHAT'S WRONG? DON'T TELL ME
THAT WIND SCARED YOU.
- WHAT? OF COURSE NOT.
HMM...
- YOU ARE SCARED, AREN'T YOU?
DON'T BE EMBARRASSED.
- DON'T BE SILLY.
- WHATEVER YOU SAY.
- ( lightning bolt )
- IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK...
I JUST FELL OVER.
- UM, IF YOU SAY SO.
- I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO GET
THE WRONG IDEA, THAT'S ALL.
- IT'S NOT THAT I'M SCARED.
I JUST DON'T LIKE IT.
- HUH?
- Suzuka: WHEN IT WOULD
STORM WHEN I WAS A KID,
IT WOULD KEEP ME UP AT NIGHT...
BUT I WASN'T ALONE,
BECAUSE MY SISTER WOULD
KEEP ME COMPANY.
- OH! YOU NEVER TOLD ME THAT
YOU HAD A SISTER, ASAHINA.
- YEAH. AND WE'VE
ALWAYS BEEN VERY CLOSE.
I MISS HER NOW
THAT I LIVE HERE IN TOKYO.
- YOU GREW UP IN
YOKOHAMA, RIGHT?
- UH-HUH, IN A LITTLE
TOWN OUTSIDE THE CITY.
BUT FROM CERTAIN SPOTS,
YOU COULD SEE THE BAY
BRIDGE, THE HARBOR,
AND THE DOWNTOWN SKYLINE.
IT WAS SO BEAUTIFUL THERE.
- IT'S COMPLETELY
OPPOSITE OUTSIDE HIROSHIMA.
WHERE I GREW UP IN THE COUNTRY,
YOU CAN'T SEE ANY LIGHTS
AFTER EIGHT AT NIGHT.
- NO WAY, REALLY?
- REALLY! BUT WE DID HAVE
TONS OF FIREFLIES.
AND IN THE SUMMERTIME
THEY WOULD ALL GATHER
IN HUGE SWARMS
AROUND THE NEARBY STREAMS.
- YOU HAVE TO COME AND
SEE IT SOMETIME.
- REALLY?
YOU KNOW, I'VE NEVER
SEEN A FIREFLY BEFORE.
- I'D LOVE TO SEE THEM.
- THEN SOMEDAY WE WILL.
WHAT AM I DOING? IT'S NOT
LIKE WE'RE GONNA TAKE
A WEEKEND TRIP TOGETHER. SHE'S
NOT EVEN MY GIRLFRIEND.
- ( thunder rumbling )
- LISTEN, ASAHINA?
- WHAT IS IT?
- REMEMBER THAT
DAY LAST WEEK
WHEN WE WALKED HOME IN THE RAIN?
- YEAH, I'VE ACTUALLY
BEEN MEANING TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT THAT DAY AS WELL.
- WHAT?
- IT'S JUST, I HAD TO JUMP
OUT OF THE WAY OF THE CAR.
- RIGHT, THE CAR...
I UNDERSTAND.
IS IT TRUE?
WHAT YOU TOLD ME EARLIER?
- HUH?
- THAT YOU FELT SO ALONE
WHEN YOU FIRST MOVED HERE?
- MMM-HMM.
- DO YOU STILL FEEL
THE SAME WAY NOW?
- NO, I FEEL DIFFERENTLY NOW.
- IS SHE GONNA SAY
SHE'S NOT LONELY BECAUSE OF ME?
- WHEN I LEFT HOME, I LEFT MY
FRIENDS AND FAMILY BEHIND.
BUT I HAD TO COME HERE.
AND I KNOW THAT THE MOVE
WAS THE BEST FOR ME.
NOW I JUST, HAVE
TO MAKE THE MOST
OF EVERY OPPORTUNITY
I HAVE HERE.
- GUESS I WAS WRONG.
- BUT I DO GET TO GO BACK
AND SEE MY FAMILY
FAIRLY REGULARLY.
- BECAUSE YOUR SISTER
GETS LONELY, I BET?
- THAT'S PART OF IT.
- ( lightning bolt )
- ( gasps )
- MY FOOT FELL ASLEEP.
- IF, THAT'S WHAT YOU SAY.
- YOU SURE GET
SCARED EASILY, ASAHINA.
- I TOLD YOU. I'M NOT SCARED.
AND BESIDES, YOUR HEART
IS RACING FASTER THAN MINE.
- ( exclaims ) THAT'S DIFFERENT.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- I DON'T KNOW...
IT'S BECAUSE I...
- WELL, THAT'S GOOD.
THE POWER'S FINALLY BACK ON.
- YEAH, IT IS.
- I GUESS I'LL BE
GOING THEN. THANKS,
AND SORRY IF I BOTHERED YOU.
- WAIT, ASAHINA.
- YES, WHAT IS IT?
- IT'S NOTHING. NEVER MIND.
- NIGHT THEN.
- ( door closes )
- I JUST WASTED A PERFECT
OPPORTUNITY
TO TELL HER HOW I FEEL.
YET AGAIN.
- Miho: MOM, CAN I
HAVE SOME MORE TEA?
- Ayano: SURE, MIHO.
WAIT JUST A MINUTE.
- SHE SURE LOOKS
GOOD THIS MORNING.
- YAMATO, WOULD
YOU LIKE SOME MORE?
- ( gasps ) YEAH, SURE.
- THAT'S YOUR SECOND
BOWL ALREADY. YOU KNOW,
YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T
EAT SO FAST.
- GEEZ, BOSSY. ANYWAY, I
HAVE TO TAKE OFF. SEE YA.
- WHAT ABOUT YOUR RICE, YAMATO?
- WHAT'S UP WITH HIM TODAY?
- I JUST DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO.
I FEEL SO AWKWARD WHENEVER
I TRY TO TALK TO HER.
( stomach growling )
OH...
I DON'T KNOW IF THIS
IS GONNA BE ENOUGH.
MAYBE I SHOULD GET TWO.
HOROSCOPES, HUH?
IT'S NONSENSE.
I'M NOT GONNA LET THE
STARS TELL ME HOW TO LIVE.
THE SIGN WITH THE BEST
LUCK THIS MONTH IS LEO?
I THINK I'M A LEO.
"YOU'LL ENJOY A CLOSE
RELATIONSHIP WITH SOMEONE
WHO HAS STRONGLY INFLUENCED
YOUR LIFE THIS MONTH." REALLY?
"WEARING BLUE UNDERWEAR
WILL DEFINITELY BRING
YOU GOOD LUCK, LEO."
I WONDER IF A
BLUE PATTERN COUNTS.
"IF YOU CONFESS, YOU WILL
GET YOUR DESIRED ANSWER."
CONFESS?
( laughing ) WHAT DO YOU
EVEN MEAN, "CONFESS?"
JUST COME OUT AND
SAY, "I LIKE YOU!"
- HEY, STOP THAT.
UNLESS YOU WANNA BUY IT.
- I'M SORRY.
- ( clock chiming )
- A HOROSCOPE? REALLY?
AND NOW YOU'RE GONNA
TELL SUZUKA EVERYTHING?
- I DIDN'T SAY I WAS GOING
TO TELL HER ANYTHING!
I'M JUST ASKING HOW
YOU WOULD TELL A GIRL
YOU'RE INTERESTED
IN HER! GEEZ!
- UH-HUH.
WELL, IF IT WAS ME AND
I LIKED SOME GIRL,
I'D PROBABLY ASK HER
TO GO OUT SOMETIME.
THAT WAY, SHE'LL GET THE HINT
AND YOU DON'T HAVE TO SAY IT.
- SO THAT'S IT?
I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND.
SO YOU WOULD ASK
SOMEONE YOU LIKED TO "GO OUT?"
WHAT DOES "GO OUT"
MEAN EXACTLY?
- WELL, IT MEANS SOMETHING
DIFFERENT FOR EVERYONE.
YOU COULD GO TO DINNER
OR THE MOVIES. OR SHOPPING.
- ( laughs) WHAT? BUT WE ALREADY
DO STUFF LIKE THAT ALL THE TIME!
- BUT WE'RE NOT TALKING
ABOUT YOU REMEMBER?
- EXCUSE ME?
- HMM?
IS IT OKAY IF I EAT
WITH YOU GUYS?
- SURE THING. HAVE A SEAT.
- THANKS.
HEY, WE'RE BOTH HAVING
THE SAME KIND OF NOODLES.
I LOVE UDON.
IT'S MY FAVORITE.
- WHAT'S THAT? OH, YEAH.
- IS SOMETHING WRONG?
CAN I DO ANYTHING?
- TELL ME SOMETHING, HONOKA...
HAVE YOU EVER TOLD A GUY YOU
LIKE HOW YOU FELT ABOUT HIM?
- I DON'T THINK SO.
- SAKURAI? I THINK YOU GOT
ENOUGH PEPPER ALREADY.
- AND DO YOU THINK THAT
THE TERM "GOING OUT"
MEANS YOU'RE A COUPLE?
OR DOES IT JUST MEAN
HANGING OUT AS FRIENDS?
- UH, "GOING OUT?"
- WELL, I'VE NEVER
BEEN ASKED OUT,
SO I DON'T UNDERSTAND
IT, EITHER.
- I SEE. WELL, THANKS.
SORRY TO BOTHER YOU.
- OH, YOU'RE LEAVING?
- YOU'RE NOT GONNA EAT THAT?
- WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
- ( panting ) OH, HOT!
- WATER.
- WHY'D YOU LET ME
DO THAT, HATTORI?
- I TRIED TO STOP YOU.
- ( whistle blows )
- Boy: OKAY, LAST LAP.
- WOW, ASAHINA.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYONE JUMP AS
GRACEFULLY AS YOU DO.
- Soichi: YOU MAKE IT
LOOK EASY, ASAHINA.
- THANK YOU.
- ( exclaims )
- WHAT'S HE DOING?
- IF GOING OUT MEANS EATING
TOGETHER OR GOING SHOPPING,
ASAHINA AND I ALREADY DO THAT.
IF I CONFESS AND
SHE REJECTS ME,
I WON'T BE ABLE TO DO THOSE
THINGS WITH HER ANYMORE.
I MEAN, I KNOW SHE
DOESN'T EXACTLY HATE ME...
THERE'S A CHANCE SHE
WON'T TURN ME DOWN,
BUT DOES THAT MEAN SHE
FEELS THE SAME WAY?
I GUESS I WON'T KNOW
UNLESS I ASK HER.
SO I HAVE TO CONFESS.
- WHO IS HE TALKING TO?
- I CAN'T DECIDE WHAT TO DO.
I DON'T WANT TO RUIN
OUR FRIENDSHIP.
- Suzuka: YAMATO!
I'VE BEEN LOOKING
FOR YOU EVERYWHERE.
- I THOUGHT YOU HAD PRACTICE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
- WE ALL GOT OUT EARLY TODAY.
AND I THOUGHT THAT
MAYBE WE COULD GO SHOPPING.
- SURE. LET'S GO.
I DON'T THINK I CAN JEOPARDIZE
WHAT I HAVE WITH HER.
IF MY CONFESSION
DOESN'T GO WELL...
- WHAT'S UP? YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU HAVE SOMETHING TO SAY.
- NO...
WELL, YES, I MEAN, MAYBE I DO.
I LIKE HER. I LIKE HER.
BUT I, I CAN'T DO IT.
SOMETIMES I THINK YOU
ONLY TAKE ME SHOPPING
TO CARRY YOUR BAGS.
YOU SHOULD AT
LEAST BUY ME A MEAL.
- IT'S A DEAL THEN.
YOU'LL GET THE BAGS
AND I'LL GET THE DINNER.
THAT'S NOT TOO MUCH TO ASK.
- WELL, COME ON ALREADY.
- OKAY.
I CAN'T TELL HER. NOT NOW.
WHEN THE TIME IS RIGHT,
I'LL KNOW IT.
IT JUST HASN'T HAPPENED YET.
AND I LIKE THINGS AS
THEY ARE, FOR NOW.
WE DON'T HAVE
TO BE "GOING OUT."
I JUST WANT TO BE WITH HER.
- SO, WHAT'S FOR DINNER?
- CROQUETTES...
I HOPE THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
- ALL RIGHT? I LOVE CROQUETTES,
YOU KNOW THAT!
- GOOD!
- I CAN'T FIND THE WORDS
TO DESCRIBE HOW I'M FEELING.
BUT AM I REALLY OKAY
WITH THIS? BECAUSE...
THE MORE I'M AROUND HER,
THE MORE I LIKE HER.
-( theme song playing )
-♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ABOVE ♪
♪ NOW IS ALL WE HAVE ♪
♪ WITH A LITTLE FEELING
AND A LOT OF LOVE ♪
♪ WE TURN UP THE HEAT AND RUN ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- ♪ ALL MY LIFE HERE ON THE
GROUND ABOUT TO RUN AND NOW ♪
♪ I FIND I MUST
ASK MYSELF WHY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE SOMETHING IS STIRRING ♪
♪ I FEEL IT WHISPERING IN ME ♪
♪ SOME DAYS I WAKE UP ♪
♪ BUT MY HEART'S
STILL SLEEPING ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME
TO RUN AND TRY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME TO FLY ♪
♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ON HIGH ♪
♪ WITH OUR GOAL IN SIGHT ♪
♪ WE WILL RUN
WITH ALL OUR MIGHT ♪
♪ TOMORROW AND TODAY
WILL NEVER EVER PASS US BY ♪
♪ WE WILL NOT STOP NOW ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR HEART ALIVE
AND YOUR DREAM SURVIVES ♪
♪ AND YOU CROSS
THE FINISH LINE ♪
♪ LET IT GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- ASAHINA AND I WENT TO
THE AMUSEMENT PARK TODAY.
WHEN I INVITED HER, SHE SAID,
"I GUESS I CAN GO WITH
YOU IF YOU WANT."
TO SOMEONE WHO
DOESN'T KNOW HER,
THEY'D THINK SHE
WASN'T INTERESTED,
BUT I COULD TELL THAT
SHE REALLY WANTED TO GO.
SHE JUST WOULDN'T SAY IT.
THAT GIRL'S SO WEIRD SOMETIMES.