-♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU
EVERYTHING WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS CLOSE
BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER
HOW FAR YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
( theme song ends )
- WELL, GOOD MORNING, ASAHINA.
- GOOD MORNING.
I THINK YOU GOT
SOME STRAY HAIRS
STICKING UPBACK THERE.
- UH...
- BUT I'D SAY THAT'S NORMAL.
- HEY, WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU TODAY?
NOT GET ENOUGH
SLEEP LAST NIGHT?
( sighs )
WHAT'S WITH HER?
- EVERYBODY GRAB A PARTNER
AND START STRETCHING.
- I'VE BEEN LOOKING
FORWARD TO TODAY
FOR A WHILE. IT'S
P.E. TEST TIME.
- REALLY? DUDE,
DON'T TELL ME
YOU TAKE ALL THIS
NONSENSE SERIOUSLY.
- ( laughing ) NOT REALLY,
BUT I WILL ADMIT
THAT I'M PRETTY
EXCITED ABOUT IT.
BECAUSE BACK IN JUNIOR HIGH,
I ALWAYS SCORED HIGHER IN
P.E. THAN ANYONE ELSE.
I JUST WANNA SEE
HOW I'LL DO HERE.
- WELL, I GUESS
WE SHOULD GET WARMED UP.
- WHAT DO YOU WANNA
START WITH THEN?
- HMM.
I DON'T KNOW.
HOW ABOUT THE LONG JUMP?
WE CAN GO OUTSIDE
AND GET SOME FRESH AIR.
- UH, HOW ABOUT WE TRY
THE VERTICAL JUMP INSTEAD?
THAT WAY,
WE DON'T HAVE TO WAIT IN LINE.
- GOOD CALL.
I LIKE THE WAY YOU THINK.
- HEY, DON'T GET
THE WRONG IDEA, YASUNOBU.
- WELL, YOU'RE LOOKING
AWFULLY LONELY
WARMING UP HERE ON YOUR OWN.
BETCHA'D HAVE MORE FUN
IF YAMATO AND I JOINED.
- THAT SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
- YEAH, THAT'S A GREAT IDEA!
- ALL RIGHT! THEY KNOW A GENIUS
WHEN THEY SEE ONE.
- OH, REALLY? WHERE IS HE?
- Yasunobu: ALL RIGHT, ACE.
WOW US WITH YOUR SKILLS, MR. TOP
ATHLETE FROM JUNIOR HIGH.
- OH! I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU WERE GOOD AT ATHLETICS.
- OH, YEAH. YAMATO WAS
QUITE THE ATHLETIC STUD
BACK HOME, WEREN'T YOU, BUD?
RIGHT?
- I DON'T KNOW. I THINK "STUD"
MIGHT BE PUSHING IT.
- I HOPE YOU CAN BACK THIS UP,
OR YOU'RE GONNA MAKE
A FOOL OF YOURSELF.
YOU DON'T WANT THAT TO HAPPEN,
DO YA?
- HERE I GO.
- I'LL MARK YOUR SCORE DOWN
FOR YOU, OKAY?
- HEY, YOU'RE JUST
KIDDING, RIGHT?
HE'S NOT REALLY A STAR
ATHLETE, IS HE?
- SURE, HE TOLD ME
HE EXCELLED IN EVERYTHING
EXCEPT FOR ONE EVENT.
- WHICH EVENT WAS THAT?
- I DON'T KNOW. BUT I'LL
FILL YOU IN WHEN I FIND OUT.
WELL, WE'LL KNOW SOON ENOUGH,
I SUPPOSE.
- ( grunting )
- 72.5 CENTIMETERS. GOOD JOB.
- ALL RIGHT! THAT'S
MY NEW PERSONAL BEST.
SEE, I TOLD YOU
THAT I WASN'T HALF BAD.
- WELL, IT WASN'T BAD, BUT WITH
AS MUCH AS YOU BUILT IT UP,
I GUESS I WAS EXPECTING
A LITTLE MORE OUT OF YOU.
- WHAT?
- ( grunting )
- WOW. SUZUKA GOT
84 CENTIMETERS.
- WHAT? SHE BEAT ME?
- WHAT ELSE WOULD YOU EXPECT
FROM THE HIGH JUMP GODDESS?
- I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE BEAT ME.
- HEY, LOOK.
I MADE SUZUKA'S MARK.
- WAY TO GO, HATTORI.
NOT BAD AT ALL.
- HMM.
- ( wind howling )
- ( grunting )
- NICE GOING, SUZUKA!
WHAT AN AMAZING JUMP!
- YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD, TOO.
FULL OF SURPRISES.
I'M IMPRESSED!
YOU SHOULD TRY OUT
FOR THE TRACK TEAM.
- WELL, THANKS, SAKURAI,
BUT I REALLY DON'T
THINK I'M GOOD ENOUGH.
I MEAN, TONS OF OTHER STUDENTS
ARE BETTER ATHLETES THAN I AM.
- I'M SURE THEY ARE.
BUT HE'S NOT ONE OF THEM.
COME ON, AKITSUKI, CHEER UP.
IT'S NOT SO BAD.
- I DON'T KNOW WHAT
I WAS EXPECTING FROM HIM.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE
HE'S HORRIBLE OR ANYTHING.
HE'S JUST YOUR AVERAGE GUY HERE.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG
WITH THAT, I GUESS.
- GIVE HIM A CHANCE.
THE COMPETITION'S STIFFER HERE,
AND HE'S JUST STARTED.
HE'LL COME AROUND.
- DON'T GIVE UP. THERE ARE STILL
PLENTY OF EVENTS LEFT.
- YEAH, BUT WHAT'S THE USE?
COMING UP NEXT
IS THE 50-METER SPRINT.
I DON'T STAND A CHANCE.
- COME ON. AT LEAST TRY.
- I WAS THE FASTEST KID
BACK IN MY ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
THEN, JUST TO SEE HOW I'D DO,
I DECIDED TO ENTER A RELAY
RACE AT THE CITY TOURNAMENT
THE SUMMER BEFORE
MY 7TH GRADE YEAR.
OUR SCHOOL NEVER EVEN
HAD ITS OWN TRACK TEAM.
WE ALMOST DIDN'T FIND
ENOUGH PEOPLE TO ENTER.
- REALLY? HOW DID IT TURN OUT?
- THEY PICKED ME TO RUN
THE ANCHOR POSITION FOR THE TEAM
AND WE CAME IN DEAD LAST
IN THE RACE.
SO SINCE THEN, I'VE NEVER RACED
SHORT DISTANCES.
I WOULD MAKE UP ANY
EXCUSE TO AVOID THEM.
THAT IS, UNTIL TODAY.
- HMM.
- I DON'T KNOW,
MAYBE I'LL JUST SKIP IT AGAIN.
- YOU CAN'T GIVE UP.
GIVE IT A SHOT.
- ( sighing )
( groaning )
- I JUST CAN'T BEAR
TO WATCH HIM ANYMORE.
- AW, CUT HIM SOME
SLACK, SUZUKA.
SHOW HIM A LITTLE SUPPORT
AND HE MIGHT SURPRISE YOU.
- I'M NOT TOTALLY SURE OF THAT.
HE'S RACING AGAINST KOBAYAKAWA.
- HE'S HERE ON
A TRACK SCHOLARSHIP, RIGHT?
THIS SHOULD BE INTERESTING.
- RUNNERS, ON YOUR MARK.
- HMM.
- HUH?
- YOU SEE THAT?
IT LOOKS LIKE YAMATO'S
USING THE ROCKET STARTER STANCE.
- HE'S PROBABLY THINKING THAT
IF HE USES BOTH OF HIS LEGS
TO KICK OFF,
IT'LL GIVE HIM AN EXTRA EDGE.
LIKE THAT'LL MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
- ALL RIGHT. HERE'S YOUR CHANCE
AT REDEMPTION. DON'T BLOW IT.
- GO, AKITSUKI! YOU CAN DO IT!
- WE'LL SEE SOON ENOUGH.
- GET SET.
- I JUST HAVE TO GIVE IT
ALL I GOT.
- NO WAY.
- ( panting )
- ( wind howling )
- I KNEW HE COULD DO IT.
- 5.93 SECONDS!
- SO, IS THAT LIKE
REALLY GOOD OR SOMETHING?
- OF COURSE THAT'S GOOD.
YOU JUST SET A SCHOOL RECORD.
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- WHY HAVEN'T I SEEN YOU BEFORE?
- YEAH, DID YOU JUST
TRANSFER IN?
- I TOLD YOU
HE WOULD SURPRISE YOU.
- WAIT A MINUTE! YOU'RE TELLING
ME YOU KNEW THIS WHOLE TIME?
- WELL, WHENEVER WE WERE KIDS
AND WE GOT IN TROUBLE,
HE NEVER GOT CAUGHT
'CAUSE HE WAS ALWAYS THE
QUICKEST TO MAKE HIS GETAWAY.
- BUT THEN WHAT HAPPENED
WITH THAT TOURNAMENT
HE TOLD ME ABOUT?
- I DON'T KNOW.
THAT WAS PROBABLY BECAUSE
OF THE REST OF THE TEAM.
I'M TELLING YOU,
THE KID'S GOT TALENT.
YOU SAW WHAT HE JUST DID.
HE TOTALLY SMOKED THAT GUY!
- HEY, ASAHINA. I THINK I'VE
FINALLY FOUND SOMETHING
THAT I'M GOOD AT.
- I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER SEEN
ANYONE RUN THAT FAST, AKITSUKI!
- REALLY?
WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK, HUH?
- IT WAS PRETTY FAST,
BUT I'VE SEEN FASTER.
LET'S GET GOING, SAKURAI.
WE NEED TO GET OURSELVES A
PLACE AT THE STARTING LINE.
- OH, OKAY.
- WHAT'S WITH HER?
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- AND I DON'T THINK
YOU EVER WILL, MY FRIEND.
BUT IF IT MAKES YOU FEEL BETTER,
I DO THINK YOU IMPRESSED HER.
- WOULD YOU STOP?
THAT'S NOT THE REASON WHY
I DECIDED TO RUN THE RACE.
ASAHINA.
- ( choking )
( coughing )
WHAT'S WRONG?
DO I HAVE SOMETHING ON MY FACE
OR WHAT?
- NO, IT'S NOTHING.
- HEY, YAMATO, I HEARD YOU RAN
AGAINST A KID TODAY
WHO GOT INTO SCHOOL
ON A SPRINTING SCHOLARSHIP,
AND YOU BEAT HIM.
THAT'S SO COOL. I'M IMPRESSED.
- YOU DIDN'T TELL ME.
WELL, I HEARD IT FROM HATTORI.
- ( laughing ) WHAT A BIG MOUTH!
I THINK I WAS MORE SURPRISED
THAN ANYONE ELSE.
I REALLY COULDN'T BELIEVE
IT HAPPENED, BUT I WON.
- AND GUESS WHAT. HATTORI SAID
HE BROKE THE SCHOOL RECORD.
- OH, REALLY?
IT WAS PRETTY AVERAGE.
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT,
ASAHINA? WHY CAN'T YOU JUST...
- I REALLY SHOULD BE GOING.
- WHAT WAS THAT ALL ABOUT?
- AH.
GREAT TIMING, ASAHINA.
GOOD MORNING.
- MORNING.
- IT'S A BEAUTIFUL DAY TODAY,
DON'T YOU THINK SO?
- YEAH, I GUESS.
- HMM.
HEY.
THAT GIRL IS INCREDIBLY STRANGE.
- GOOD MORNING, SUZUKA.
- GOOD MORNING, AYANO.
- THE NEWS SAID IT'S
SUPPOSED TO RAIN LATER.
DID YOU REMEMBER TO BRING AN
UMBRELLA WITH YOU?
- UH-HUH.
HAVE A GOOD DAY.
- ASAHINA, WAIT UP.
- BYE, YAMATO.
- HEY!
- HAVE FUN.
- SO WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
SUZUKA'S BEING WEIRD?
- IT'S THE STRANGEST THING.
I'LL CATCH HER STARING AT ME
AND THEN SHE'LL SAY SOMETHING
RUDE OUT OF NOWHERE.
I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT DID I DO WRONG?
- YOU IDIOT.
DON'T YOU KNOW ANYTHING?
THAT'S THE WAY A GIRL ACTS
WHEN SHE'S IN LOVE.
- IN LOVE?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- AH, YOU KNOW.
LIKE WHEN A GIRL CATCHES YOU
WHEN YOU'RE CHECKING HER OUT.
- I HADN'T THOUGHT OF IT
LIKE THAT.
- OF COURSE YOU HADN'T.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
I MAY NOT KNOW MUCH,
BUT I DEFINITELY KNOW
SOMETHING ABOUT WOMEN.
- RIGHT.
- AND I KNOW THAT YOU
SCORED A LOT OF POINTS
WITH HER YESTERDAY
WHEN YOU STEPPED UP
AND WON THAT RACE.
SERIOUSLY. I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYONE RUN THAT FAST.
- I DON'T KNOW, MAN. DO YOU
REALLY THINK SHE LIKES ME MORE,
JUST BECAUSE I WON
A STUPID RACE?
- I PERSONALLY GUARANTEE YOU
THAT SHE DOES.
SO, GOOD LUCK, DUDE.
- YOU GUARANTEE IT, HUH?
- ( wind howling )
- ( heavy rain )
- AND THE NEXT STEP IS YOU TAKE
THE SUM OF THE FACTORS OF X
TO THE THIRD AND Y TO THE THIRD.
ARE YOU FOLLOWING ME?
- DON'T YOU KNOW ANYTHING?
THAT'S THE WAY A GIRL
ACTS WHEN SHE'S IN LOVE.
- COULD HE BE RIGHT?
DOES SHE REALLY LIKE ME?
- ( chuckling )
- ( school bell ringing )
- AW, MAN. I'LL GET SOAKED
WALKING HOME IN THIS DOWNPOUR.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
IT SURE WOULD BE NICE
IF SOMEONE WOULD LET
ME SHARE THEIR UMBRELLA.
- SUZUKA!
- OH, HEY, MIKI.
- WE CAN'T PRACTICE OUTSIDE
TODAY BECAUSE OF THE RAIN.
WE'LL BE IN THE WEIGHT ROOM.
- I SEE.
THEN WEIGHT TRAINING IT IS.
- NOW WHAT?
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO GET HOME?
- AKITSUKI?
I GUESS YOU FORGOT
YOUR UMBRELLA?
WELL, I REMEMBERED MINE, SO
NOW WE CAN SHARE.
- OKAY.
- I'M AFRAID IF YOU
WALK HOME IN THE RAIN
YOU MIGHT GET SICK AGAIN.
- UM, THANKS. BUT I, UH,
HAVE SOMETHING TO DO
BEFORE I CAN LEAVE.
- THAT'S FINE. I CAN WAIT
IF YOU WANT ME TO.
- NO, THAT'S OKAY. I DON'T WANT
TO MAKE YOU WAIT FOR ME.
MAYBE I'LL JUST STAY HERE
TILL IT STOPS RAINING.
- I KNEW SAKURAI WOULD REMEMBER
TO BRING HER UMBRELLA.
HEY! WHAT WOULD
I DO WITHOUT YOU?
SEE, I'M ON MY WAY TO THIS PARTY
AND YOU KNOW HOW IT IS.
I CAN'T SHOW UP
WITH WET CLOTHES.
SO, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
WILL YOU WALK WITH ME
TO THE TRAIN STATION?
IT'S REALLY NOT
THAT FAR. I PROMISE.
- UM, WELL, UH...
- I'M GONNA BORROW YOUR
FRIEND FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
YOU DON'T MIND, DO YOU? LATER.
- LATER.
WHAT IN THE WORLD AM I DOING?
( sighing )
GEEZ, HOW LONG DOES IT TAKE
TO LIFT SOME WEIGHTS?
IT'S NOT LIKE
SHE NEEDS TO, ANYWAY.
SHE LOOKS PERFECT AS SHE IS NOW.
WHAT THE HELL AM I THINKING?
OH, FORGET IT, I'M LEAVING.
I'M TIRED OF WAITING
AROUND FOR HER.
ALL RIGHT, JUST ACT NATURAL.
WHAT AM I GONNA SAY
WHEN I SEE HER?
I SEEM TO HAVE FORGOTTEN
MY UMBRELLA, ASAHINA.
DO YOU MIND
SHARING YOURS WITH ME?
NO PRESSURE, IT'S UP TO YOU.
( laughing forcefully )
- WHAT'S HE DOING?
MAYBE HE'S A STALKER.
- OR JUST PLAIN CRAZY. DID YOU
HEAR HIM TALKING TO HIMSELF?
- MAYBE I SHOULD JUST GO HOME.
- LET'S GET OUTTA HERE.
I COULD WAIT
JUST A LITTLE LONGER, I GUESS.
- YAMATO?
- HELLO, ASAHINA.
- I THOUGHT YOU'D GONE HOME
A LONG TIME AGO.
- NO, IT'S JUST, I WAS HAVING
PROBLEMS WITH MY LOCKER.
- BUT IT'S OPEN.
- WELL, YOU SEE. I JUST GOT IT
TO OPEN UP A SECOND AGO.
( laughing forcefully )
- YOU FORGOT YOUR UMBRELLA
TODAY, DIDN'T YOU?
DO YOU WANNA SHARE MINE WITH ME?
- YEAH. I FORGOT
MY UMBRELLA TODAY.
THINK YOU CAN SHARE
YOURS WITH ME?
'COURSE, IT'S OKAY IF
YOU DON'T REALLY WANT TO.
( laughing forcefully )
REALLY?
- YEAH.
- ( raining heavily )
- ( wind howling )
- Yamato:
THE WIND'S STRONG TODAY.
- YEAH.
- IT SURE IS NICE TO TAKE A WALK
IN THE RAIN ONCE IN A WHILE.
- MM-HM.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
I CAN'T EVER READ THIS GIRL.
WHAT'S SHE THINKING?
MAYBE YASUNOBU WAS WRONG.
- I WANT TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
- WHAT?
- YOU... YOU'RE PRETTY FAST.
- YEAH, I GUESS.
- AND I KNOW THAT YOU
SCORED A LOT OF POINTS
WITH HER YESTERDAY
WHEN YOU STEPPED UP
AND WON THAT RACE.
- THEN AGAIN, MAYBE HE'S RIGHT.
I EVEN SURPRISED MYSELF
WHEN I WON.
- HMM.
- ( car revving )
- ASAHINA?
- ( wind howling )
-( theme song playing )
- ♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ABOVE ♪
♪ NOW IS ALL WE HAVE ♪
♪ WITH A LITTLE FEELING
AND A LOT OF LOVE ♪
♪ WE TURN UP THE HEAT AND RUN ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- ♪ ALL MY LIFE HERE ON THE
GROUND ABOUT TO RUN AND NOW ♪
♪ I FELT I MUST ASK MYSELF WHY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE SOMETHING IS STIRRING ♪
♪ I FEEL IT WHISPERING IN ME ♪
♪ SOME DAYS I WAKE UP ♪
♪ BUT MY HEART'S
STILL SLEEPING ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME
TO RUN AND TRY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME TO FLY ♪
♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ON HIGH ♪
♪ WITH OUR GOAL IN SIGHT ♪
♪ WE WILL RUN
WITH ALL OUR MIGHT ♪
♪ TOMORROW AND TODAY
WILL NEVER EVER PASS US BY ♪
♪ WE WILL NOT STOP NOW ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR HEART ALIVE
AND YOUR DREAM SURVIVES ♪
♪ AND YOU CROSS
THE FINISH LINE ♪
♪ LET IT GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- A WOMAN'S MIND IS A THING
OF MYSTERY TO ME.
I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT'S GOING ON UP THERE.
ASAHINA CAN BE ALL NICE
AND WARM,
THEN ON A DIME, SHE CAN CHANGE
AND BECOME DISTANT AND COLD.
- WHY DON'T YOU JUST
TALK TO HER, MAN?
INSTEAD OF SITTING HERE
WHINING ABOUT IT?