- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- WELL GOOD MORNING, YAMATO!
- OH, GOOD MORNING, AUNT AYANO.
HOW ARE YOU?
- GREAT. DO YOU HAVE TIME
TO EAT SOME BREAKFAST?
- I CAN'T, I'M RUNNING LATE,
BUT THANKS.
- ALL RIGHT. WELL HAVE A
GOOD DAY AT SCHOOL
AND PLEASE MAKE SURE
YOU EAT PLENTY FOR LUNCH, OKAY?
- OKAY, WELL, I BETTER
GET GOING NOW.
- WHERE'S SAKURAI? OH, NO.
- IT'S SAD, SHE USED TO COME BY
TO MEET HIM EVERY MORNING.
- THIS FEELS DIFFERENT.
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME SINCE I'VE
WALKED TO SCHOOL ALONE.
- AKITSUKI!
- IT REALLY HAPPENED.
WE BROKE UP.
- ( clock chiming )
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
( panting ) I WALKED TOO
SLOW AND NOW I'M LATE!
UH, HONOKA!
- GOOD MORNING.
- UH, GOOD MORNING.
- SO, UH...
- I THINK CLASS IS
ABOUT TO START!
- ( clock chiming )
- Yasunobu: WOW,
YOU GUYS BROKE UP?
- UM, YEAH.
- WHAT'D I TELL YA, MAN?
I GAVE YOU THE BEST ADVICE
YOU COULD EVER ASK FOR,
FREE OF CHARGE,
AND YOU JUST DIDN'T LISTEN,
DID YOU?
- I KNOW, AND YOU WERE
COMPLETELY RIGHT. I'M SORRY.
- HUH?
- Yamato: HONOKA WAS SUCH A
PATIENT AND GIVING PERSON.
SHE WOULD DO ANYTHING FOR ME.
THE ONLY THING
I EVER THOUGHT ABOUT
WAS THE WAY I FELT AND
WHAT I WANTED.
I WAS SUCH AN AWFUL BOYFRIEND.
- HEY, COME ON! DON'T BEAT
YOURSELF UP LIKE THAT.
LOOK, I'M SURE THERE ARE
PLENTY OF THINGS SAKURAI DID
THAT SHE'S REGRETTING NOW, TOO.
- NO WAY.
THIS WHOLE MESS IS MY FAULT!
- DON'T BE SO DRAMATIC, DUDE.
NO ONE'S EVER "RIGHT", "WRONG"
OR "AT FAULT" IN RELATIONSHIPS.
IN THIS CASE, I JUST THINK
YOU AND SAKURAI
ARE TWO DIFFERENT PEOPLE.
I GOT IT! WE NEED
TO HAVE A PARTY, MAN!
I'LL INVITE TONS OF HOT CHICKS
AND I'M SURE YOU'LL FIND ONE
THAT'S PERFECT FOR YOU,
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
- NO THANKS. I'M JUST NOT
IN THE MOOD RIGHT NOW.
- I SEE.
- Miki: HEY! AKITSUKI!
WHAT'S WRONG?
WHY DO YOU LOOK SO DOWN?
- WELL IF IT ISN'T THE
NOSIEST GIRL IN THE SCHOOL.
- I'M NOT TALKING TO YOU, AM I?
I THINK I KNOW WHAT
THIS IS ABOUT.
I BET SOMEONE GOT A ZERO ON
THEIR CHEMISTRY TEST,
DIDN'T THEY?
WELL, DON'T WORRY. I'M NOT
GOING TO GO TELLING EVERYONE.
BESIDES, GUESS WHAT I GOT
ON MINE? TWENTY! A TWENTY!
- UH, NO. IT'S NOT THAT.
- OH, COME ON! IT'S OKAY!
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
YOU'RE DUMBER THAN I THOUGHT!
- JUST STAY OUT OF IT, JERK!
THIS DOESN'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH YOU!
- YOU'RE ONE TO TALK!
YOU INTERRUPTED US!
THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH YOU!
- OH, YOU WERE TALKING DIRTY,
WEREN'T YOU?
- OH, PLEASE. WHAT DO YOU THINK
I AM, SOME KIND OF PERVERT? HUH?
- I HAPPEN TO KNOW THAT
YOU'RE A PERVERT!
- I DARE YOU TO SAY
THAT AGAIN, SLUG TRAIL.
- HEY! WAIT!
- JUST LEAVE HIM ALONE, NOSEY.
- I'M NOT NOSEY! I JUST WANNA
KNOW WHAT'S WRONG WITH HIM.
- OH REALLY?
- MMM-HMM. TOTALLY. SPILL IT.
- YEAH RIGHT. IN YOUR DREAMS.
- ( grunting )
YOU'RE SUCH A JERK!
- Yasunobu: OW! OW! OW!
YOU'RE HURTING ME!
- ( whistle blowing )
- Kinugasa: ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GET STARTED!
- All: YES, SIR!
- HEY, MANAGER!
BRING ME A TOWEL!
- ME TOO, PLEASE!
- SHE'S NOT HERE TODAY.
- HUH? WHY NOT?
- HEY AKITSUKI!
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHY
SAKURAI ISN'T HERE TODAY?
- UH, I, NO, SIR.
- YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHERE SHE IS, SERIOUSLY?
- BUT SHE IS YOUR
GIRLFRIEND, ISN'T SHE?
WHY WOULDN'T SHE TELL YOU?
- WELL, NO.
WE BROKE UP YESTERDAY.
- WHAT?
- All: YOU BROKE UP?
- UH, YEAH.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN? SO THAT'S
WHY SAKURAI ISN'T HERE!
- SO SHE JUST DOESN'T
WANNA BE AROUND YOU?
- REALLY, SWEET!
- THAT'S GREAT.
AND JUST BEFORE THE FALL
ROOKIE COMPETITION.
- OH NO. I FORGOT
ALL ABOUT THAT.
AND SHE'S BEEN SUCH
A BIG HELP TO US.
- THERE'S NOTHING
I CAN DO ABOUT IT.
- YOU'RE THE REASON OUR
MANAGER'S NOT HERE!
THANKS A LOT!
- LOOKS LIKE YOU'LL BE
DOING THE WASH
AND EVERYTHING ELSE
NOW, AKITSUKI!
- Boy: AW, THIS IS GREAT.
JUST WHAT WE NEED.
- BUT WAIT...
- OH, NO. AKITSUKI AND
SAKURAI BROKE UP.
- Suzuka: THAT'S WHAT
IT LOOKS LIKE.
- I KINDA FEEL SORRY FOR HIM.
I MEAN, THEY DIDN'T HAVE TO
BLAME HIM FOR EVERYTHING.
- WELL, IT'S HIS FAULT.
WHATEVER. MIKI, ARE
YOU GONNA STRETCH OR NOT?
- ( gasping )
SUZUKA! OW! THAT HURTS!
OKAY, THAT'S ENOUGH! SUZUKA!
- MAN, THEY WERE SO MEAN TO YOU!
I'M SURE YOU TWO
HAD YOUR REASONS.
I'M TOTALLY ON
YOUR SIDE, AKITSUKI.
- ( laughing ) WELL, I THINK
YOU MAY BE THE ONLY ONE.
SO THANKS, KOBAYASHI.
- HEY, DON'T MENTION IT, OKAY?
NO PROBLEM AT ALL.
- AND IT'S KOBAYAKAWA!
- OH, SORRY.
- ( laughing )
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT!
- THANKS.
- OKAY. I THINK I UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
I COULDN'T BELIEVE IT WHEN YOU
CALLED ME CRYING, THOUGH!
I WAS SO WORRIED ABOUT YOU!
- Honoka: I'M REALLY SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO LAY ALL
THIS ON YOU SO SUDDENLY.
- THAT'S OKAY. IT'S MY DAY OFF.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT. SERIOUSLY.
- AFTER WE BROKE UP I REALLY
THOUGHT THAT I'D BE OKAY.
BUT THEN WE RAN INTO EACH
OTHER TODAY
AND MY HEART COMPLETELY
SANK, NANA.
- SO YOU'RE SAYING
YOU'RE HAVING REGRETS?
ARE YOU SURE YOU WANTED TO
BREAK UP WITH HIM?
- WELL, NO. I DIDN'T WANT TO.
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE I REALLY HAVE
A CHOICE IN THIS SITUATION.
HE'LL ALWAYS HAVE
FEELINGS FOR ASAHINA.
- BUT CAN YOU REALLY BE SURE
ABOUT THAT?
I DON'T KNOW. DID HE EVER
ACTUALLY COME OUT AND SAY IT?
THAT HE CARES ABOUT SUZUKA,
LIKE, MORE THAN A FRIEND?
- NO. HE DIDN'T.
- WELL, THEN?
- WELL, THEN WHAT?
- LISTEN HONOKA, I KNOW YAMATO
HAS HIS ISSUES, BELIEVE ME.
BUT YOU'RE NOT PERFECT EITHER.
DON'T YOU THINK YOUR
INSECURITIES
MAY ALSO BE A PROBLEM?
AM I WRONG?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- ALL RIGHT, THAT'S ENOUGH!
NOW JUST LISTEN!
YOU'RE THINKING ABOUT
ASAHINA WAY TOO MUCH!
WELL, JUST...
IT MEANS YOU'RE WRONG.
AND I'M NOT THINKING ABOUT
ASAHINA ALL THE TIME
AND I HAVE PROOF.
I DON'T THINK ABOUT HER
WHEN WE WALK TO SCHOOL TOGETHER.
WHEN YOU COOK FOR ME.
AND I HONESTLY WASN'T THINKING
ABOUT HER WHEN I WENT SHOPPING
FOR YOUR BIRTHDAY PRESENT.
- MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
- YOU THINK?
- YEAH, THIS IS
PROBABLY MY FAULT.
I'M THE ONE WHO
BROKE UP WITH HIM.
I WOULDN'T HAVE REACTED
THE WAY THAT I DID
IF I WERE MORE CONFIDENT.
I GUESS IT'S MY OWN FAULT
THAT I'M HURTING THIS WAY NOW.
- HONOKA...
IT'LL BE OKAY!
COME ON! YOU'RE A SWEET,
ATTRACTIVE GIRL!
I'M SURE YOU'LL FIND
A NEW BOYFRIEND IN NO TIME!
- OH, NANA.
- OH, WHAT? I'M SERIOUS! THERE'S
TONS OF NICE GUYS OUT THERE!
AND I BET SOMEONE
ALREADY LIKES YOU!
- I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT.
- Nana: WELL, WE'LL JUST
HAVE TO FIND OUT THEN!
- ( both laughing )
- I'M SO TIRED, UGH...
- LOOKS LIKE SAKURAI DIDN'T
SHOW UP TODAY, EITHER. OH WELL.
- ALL RIGHT, WAKE UP, LADIES!
IT'S TIME TO START
RUNNING INTERVALS!
- All: OKAY.
- I'M REALLY NOT IN THE
MOOD FOR THIS TODAY.
- YEAH, ME NEITHER, MAN.
- UH...
- HEY! YOU'RE BACK!
- Boy 1: SHE'S BACK!
- Boy 2: HONOKA!
- Boy 3: HEY MANAGER!
- HEY GUYS! I'M SO SORRY
ABOUT YESTERDAY!
- SHE'S BACK.
- Soichi: IT'S FINE, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT IT. HAVE A SEAT!
- Boy 1: YEAH, TAKE A REST!
- Boy 2: DO YOU NEED A DRINK?
- Boy 3: I'M SO GLAD
YOU'RE BACK!
- Soichi: ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GET PRACTICE STARTED!
- All: ALL RIGHT!
- Kobayakawa: HERE.
- I, I HOPE YOU'RE FEELING
BETTER. - I AM. THANK YOU.
- WELCOME. I, I KNOW
IT'S BEEN HARD,
BUT IF YOU EVER WANNA
TALK, I'M HERE.
- WELL, THANK YOU.
THAT'S VERY SWEET.
- OH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
IT'S NOTHING REALLY.
- OKAY. WELL THERE IS SOMETHING
THAT'S BEEN ON MY MIND.
- YEAH, SURE.
- DO YOU THINK IT'S STRANGE TO
WANT TO GO OUT WITH SOMEONE
YOU JUST BROKE UP WITH?
I MEAN, IS THAT NORMAL?
- HUH! WHAT?
- IF WE WERE TO START DATING
AGAIN AT THIS POINT,
WE'D PROBABLY STILL FIGHT
OVER THE SAME THINGS.
BUT IF I TAKE SOME TIME TO WORK
ON MY INSECURITIES,
MAYBE SOMEDAY,
I'LL BE ABLE TO...
I'LL BE ABLE TO CONFESS
MY FEELINGS TO AKITSUKI AGAIN!
- 163 CENTIMETERS! ALL RIGHT!
- ON THE RELAY TEAM?
- THAT'S RIGHT. THE TWO OF YOU
HAD THE FASTEST TIMES
IN THE HUNDRED METER RACE TODAY.
I THINK YOU'D BE A GREAT
ADDITION TO THE TEAM.
- FASTEST? REALLY?
- BUT...
THIS IS ONLY MY FIRST YEAR
IN THE CLUB.
- WE NEED TO FIND THE FASTEST
RUNNERS ON THE TEAM FOR RELAY.
THAT'S AN ORDER, AKITSUKI.
FOR BOTH OF YOU.
- RIGHT! I'LL DO MY BEST!
- HEY, WAY TO GO, AKITSUKI!
- UH, WHAT?
- DO YOUR BEST!
- OKAY. THANKS.
- YEAH, UH, I'M GONNA WORK
REALLY HARD, TOO!
- UH, OKAY. GOOD LUCK, YOU TWO!
- RELAY PRACTICE STARTS RIGHT
AFTER REGULAR PRACTICE.
SO YOU'LL HAVE TO
STAY A LITTLE LATE.
- NO PROB!
- OKAY.
- THE RELAY TEAM?
- I KNOW! IT'S EXCITING,
ISN'T IT? HE'S AMAZING!
- IS HE?
- YA KNOW, I WAS
SO WORRIED ABOUT HIM
AFTER HE BROKE UP WITH SAKURAI.
YOU SHOULD'VE SEEN
HOW DEPRESSED HE WAS!
- Suzuka: WHATEVER.
I DON'T CARE HOW HE FEELS.
- WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOU, SUZUKA?
DID YOU TWO HAVE ANOTHER
FIGHT OR SOMETHING?
- THAT'S NOT IT...
IT'S JUST...
IT'S REALLY HARD FOR ME TO CARE
ABOUT SOMEONE AS IGNORANT
AS HE IS. THAT'S ALL.
- IGNORANT, HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I KNOW HE BROKE UP WITH
SAKURAI, BUT...
I WOULDN'T SAY THAT
MAKES HIM IGNORANT.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE REASON WAS.
- HE DUMPED HER BECAUSE
HE WAS ANNOYED WITH HER.
- WHAT? ARE YOU SURE?
DID HE REALLY MEAN THAT?
- WHY DON'T YOU GO
ASK HIM YOURSELF?
- HE SAID THAT?
- SEE YOU LATER, AKITSUKI!
- OKAY. BYE, KOBAYA... KAWA.
- LISTEN, WE MAY BE PARTNERS
IN RELAY,
BUT YOU'LL NEVER BEAT ME IN
THE HUNDRED METER!
- THAT'S RIGHT! ALSO...
( crying ) DAMN IT!
- NEVER MIND!
- WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH HIM?
- WE NEED TO TALK!
- WHAT ARE YOU STILL DOING HERE,
HASHIBA? IT'S SO LATE!
- I WAS WAITING FOR YOU!
- HUH?
- SO IS IT TRUE THAT YOU DUMPED
SAKURAI
BECAUSE YOU THOUGHT
SHE WAS ANNOYING?
- OH, GREAT. I BET I KNOW
WHERE YOU HEARD THAT.
- ASAHINA? RIGHT?
- DON'T EVEN TRY TO
BLOW THIS OFF. ANSWER ME!
- OKAY, YES.
IS THAT A PROBLEM?
- YOU'RE LYING.
IF SAKURAI WAS SO ANNOYING,
THEN WHY ARE YOU SO DEPRESSED?
AND IF YOU ACTUALLY DUMPED HER
LIKE YOU SAID YOU DID,
SHE WOULDN'T HAVE
SHOWN UP TO PRACTICE!
I CAN SEE RIGHT
THROUGH YOU, AKITSUKI!
- I'M NOT LYING!
- SEE YA!
- LISTEN TO ME!
I'M NOT GOING TO LEAVE YOU ALONE
UNTIL YOU TELL ME THE TRUTH.
- ALL RIGHT, FINE. SHE ACCUSED
ME OF STILL LIKING ASAHINA.
THEN WE HAD A HORRIBLE FIGHT.
- WHAT? YOU STILL HAVE
FEELINGS FOR SUZUKA?
- ( clock chiming )
- Yamato: NO. OF COURSE I DON'T.
I THINK I TRIED TOO HARD TO BE
THE PERFECT BOYFRIEND
AND WAS ONLY WORRIED ABOUT
HOW IT MADE ME LOOK.
I DIDN'T THINK ABOUT
HONOKA'S FEELINGS AT ALL.
I THINK BECAUSE OF THAT,
SHE FIGURED I MUST STILL
BE INTO ASAHINA.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU JUST
TELL SUZUKA THE TRUTH?
- BECAUSE. THAT'S TOO HARD.
I COULDN'T JUST SAY, "WE
BROKE UP BECAUSE OF YOU."
- YEAH, RIGHT. I SEE.
- ANYWAY, DO ME A FAVOR AND
DON'T SPEAK TO ASAHINA
ABOUT THIS, OKAY?
SHE'S ALREADY WORRIED ABOUT
THIS ENOUGH AS IT IS.
- AKITSUKI...
OKAY. I WON'T.
- GREAT THANKS.
I'M GONNA GO HOME NOW.
- WAIT! DON'T GO YET!
- WHY? WHAT'S WRONG?
- YOU HAVE TO BE HUNGRY
AFTER ALL THAT PRACTICE.
LET'S GO EAT SOMETHING
BEFORE WE GO HOME.
I'VE BEEN WANTING TO
TRY THIS PLACE FOR A LONG TIME!
BUT SINCE IT'S ON THE
BASEMENT FLOOR,
I DIDN'T WANT TO COME ALONE.
- I SEE. YOU COULD'VE
JUST ASKED ASAHINA.
WHY DID YOU HAVE TO
DRAG ME HERE WITH YOU?
IT'S NOT LIKE I FEEL
COMFORTABLE EITHER. GEEZ!
- ALL RIGHTY. IT LOOKS LIKE
IT'S READY TO GO.
SHOULD I TURN IT OVER NOW?
- Yamato: NO, YOU IDIOT!
CAN'T YOU SEE THAT
THE BATTER'S STILL RUNNY?
- Miki: BUT ISN'T IT
GOING TO BURN?
- NO. IF YOU FLIP IT TOO MUCH,
THE AIR BUBBLES ESCAPE AND IT
WON'T BE SOFT AND FLUFFY.
- Yamato: LOOK,
DON'T TOUCH IT, OKAY!
- YOU'RE SO ANNOYING! GEEZ!
ISN'T THIS SUPPOSED
TO BE KANSAI STYLE?
DO YOU THINK A BOY FROM
HIROSHIMA CAN HANDLE THIS?
- I'M A PRO! DON'T CHALLENGE ME!
- Miki: YEAH RIGHT.
GIMME YOUR SPATULA!
- Yamato: NO! WAIT!
DON'T BE STUPID!
- THERE WE GO!
AND IT'S PERFECTLY COOKED!
- QUIT PATTING IT LIKE THAT.
- OH DON'T WORRY, IT'S FINE.
- NOW IT'S TIME FOR THE
GREEN SEAWEED!
- WAIT!
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
DOING! PUT THE SAUCE ON FIRST!
- WHAT, SO YOU THINK
YOU'RE THE PANCAKE POLICE NOW?
- WHAT THE HECK IS
THE PANCAKE POLICE?
- Miki: SO, LET'S EAT, SHALL WE?
WHERE'S THE SAUCE?
- Yamato: HASHIBA!
- AKITSUKI! CAN YOU TELL ME IF
I STILL HAVE GREEN SEAWEED
IN MY TEETH?
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER HAD
SUCH BITTER OKONOMIYAKI.
EVEN THE WAITRESS
WAS STARING AT US.
- SERIOUSLY?
- HEY, LISTEN.
- WHAT IS IT NOW?
- NOTHING GOOD WILL EVER COME
FROM STRESSING OUT ABOUT IT.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- YOU KNOW...
WHENEVER YOU HAVE PROBLEMS LIKE
THIS, JUST EAT SOMETHING YUMMY.
YOU'LL BE SURPRISED HOW
MUCH IT CHEERS YOU UP!
- THANK YOU.
SHE WAS WORRIED ABOUT ME. THAT'S
WHY SHE TOOK ME OUT TO EAT.
- I'M SO SORRY. I DIDN'T
MEAN TO MAKE YOU WORRY.
- HUH?
- EVERYTHING'S FINE.
I THINK HONOKA'S OVER IT AND
SEEMS TO BE DOING WELL.
- BUT I'M...
- Miki: OH, I DIDN'T MEAN
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
I, UH, I HEARD YOU'VE BEEN
CHOSEN FOR THE RELAY TEAM.
JUST MAKE SURE
YOU GIVE IT YOUR ALL, OKAY?
- OH, YEAH. EXCEPT THAT...
IT DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT.
( sighing )
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- IT'S JUST, I ONLY JOINED
TRACK AND FIELD
BECAUSE ASAHINA WAS IN IT.
AND NOW THAT SHE HATES ME,
ALL THIS FEELS WRONG.
THERE'S REALLY NOT A
GOOD REASON FOR ME TO CONTINUE.
- WELL, UH...
- I FEEL GUILTY SINCE
THERE ARE KIDS
WHO ACTUALLY TAKE IT SERIOUSLY.
SO I THINK I SHOULD...
YOU KNOW...
- WELL, I'M PRETTY SURE
EVERYONE WAS ANNOYED WITH YOU
WHEN YOU STARTED.
- WHAT?
- YOU JOINED THE TEAM DURING
THE OFF SEASON,
YOU DIDN'T KEEP UP WITH
YOUR PRACTICES
AND YOU STILL GOT A REGULAR
SPOT IN THE COMPETITION
OVER SOME SENIORS!
AND YET, THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT MAKES YOU SPECIAL.
FOR SOME REASON, I HAVE HIGH
EXPECTATIONS FOR YOU.
I THINK YOU'RE GOING TO DO
AMAZING THINGS.
AND I REALLY THINK THAT
EVERYONE ELSE IS STARTING
TO SEE THE SAME THING AS I DO.
- WELL, I'M NOT SURE.
- IT'S THE TRUTH! AND YOU HAVE
THE RESPONSIBILITY
TO MEET OUR EXPECTATIONS.
THAT'S WHY YOU'RE
IN TRACK AND FIELD!
- UM, OKAY.
- SO STOP FEELING SORRY
FOR YOURSELF!
- C'MON, WE'D BETTER GET GOING.
- RIGHT, OKAY.
HAS ANYONE EVER TOLD YOU
THAT YOU ARE
AN UNREASONABLY NOSEY PERSON?
- I AM NOT!
- WELL THEN, I'M GONNA DO MY
BEST. YOU CONVINCED ME.
- ALL RIGHT!
LISTEN, UH, WHY DON'T WE
GO GET SOME DESSERT
BEFORE WE HEAD HOME?
AND THIS TIME IT'S ON YOU!
- HEY! WASN'T IT ON ME
THE LAST TIME?
- Miki: IS THAT RIGHT?
- Yamato: YES!
- Miki: OKAY,
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT THEN!
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WHEN I TURN AROUND ♪
♪ YOU'RE RIGHT THERE
NEXT TO ME ♪
♪ ON YOUR FACE A SMILE
SO COMFORTING AND FAMILIAR ♪
♪ THE CLOSER YOU BECAME
THE LESS THAT I COULD SEE ♪
♪ AND NOW I'M WONDERING
SO LOST AND ALL ALONE ♪
♪ PEOPLE CHANGE
A LITTLE AT A TIME ♪
♪ AND NOW I KNOW I'M CHANGING ♪
♪ WHEN I CALL YOUR NAME
SHOUT IT OUT INTO THE SKY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN I WILL FIND
THE LOVE I KEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'RE WITH ME
AND YOU TAKE MY HAND ♪
♪ SOMEHOW EVERYTHING
SEEMS TO WORK ITSELF OUT RIGHT ♪
♪ WHEN I SEE YOUR EYES
STARING BACK AT MINE ♪
♪ THERE INSIDE I FIND
A LOVE THAT NEVER DIES ♪
♪ TOGETHER I KNOW
WE'LL FIND A WAY ♪
♪ JUST YOU AND I ♪
- Yamato: HELLO?
- Miki: HELLO, AKITSUKI?
THIS IS HASHIBA.
- Yamato: HEY HASHIBA,
HOW'S IT GOING?
- Miki: WELL, I WAS JUST
WONDERING.
WERE YOU ABLE TO MAKE UP
WITH SUZUKA, YET?
- Yamato: UM, NO. NOT EXACTLY.
- Miki: ARE YOU TWO
FIGHTING AGAIN?