- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- Yamato: MY MOUTH IS SO DRY
I CAN BARELY SWALLOW.
I NEVER KNEW
IT WOULD BE THIS HARD.
MAYBE ASAHINA
WAS RIGHT ABOUT ME.
MAYBE I UNDERESTIMATED WHAT
IT TOOK TO BE ON THE TEAM,
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE WORKS OUT THIS
HARD EVERY DAY
AND THEN SHE SEEMS TO
BE TOTALLY FINE AFTERWARDS.
HUH? ASAHINA?
SHE'S STILL PRACTICING?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I'M THINKING.
I'M TRYING TO IMPRESS
HER WHEN SHE'S
THE STAR OF THE TRACK TEAM.
I WISH I COULD JUST BE
MYSELF AROUND HER.
BUT SHE ALWAYS MAKES ME
SO NERVOUS.
I FEEL LIKE THE CLOSER I GET TO
HER, THE FARTHER SHE SLIPS AWAY.
( sighs )
- ( door unlocks )
- HERE SHE COMES.
OH! ASAHINA!
YOU MUST BE LEAVING FOR
SCHOOL EARLY THIS MORNING?
- YEAH.
- WELL, WOULD YOU CARE FOR SOME
COMPANY DURING THE WALK?
- I WANNA WALK ALONE.
- FINE.
( sighs )
WHAT DID I DO TO MAKE HER
DESPISE ME SO MUCH?
I'M TRYING TO MAKE THINGS RIGHT.
- WE'RE CONSTANTLY WORKING TO
IMPROVE OURSELVES BY ONE SECOND,
BY ONE CENTIMETER.
DO YOU REALLY THINK YOU CAN
HANDLE IT, YAMATO?
- I JUST HAVE TO STICK THIS
OUT AND PROVE TO HER
THAT I'M SERIOUS.
- YOUR BUILD IS MORE ATHLETIC
THAN I EXPECTED, AKITSUKI.
A NICE SURPRISE.
- UH, HASHIBA, WHAT KIND OF
OUTFIT ARE YOU WEARING?
I MEAN, YOU'RE PRACTICALLY NUDE!
- ( exclaims ) THIS IS THE
UNIFORM FOR SPRINTERS!
- SORRY, I DIDN'T KNOW.
- AND IT'S NOT NICE TO TALK
ABOUT WHAT A GIRL'S WEARING.
WE'RE SENSITIVE ABOUT THAT.
- I SAID SORRY. SO WHY ARE YOU
WEARING THAT TODAY?
- OH, THAT'S RIGHT. I FORGOT YOU
WEREN'T ON THE TEAM WHEN WE HAD
THE MEETING AT THE
BEGINNING OF THE YEAR.
TODAY'S THE DAY THAT WE
DECIDE THE ENTRANTS FOR
THE TOKYO METROPOLITAN
TOURNAMENT IN TWO WEEKS.
- SO THAT'S WHY I WAS TOLD TO
BRING MY UNIFORM AND SPIKES.
- YEP, EXACTLY. ANYWAY, GOOD
LUCK WITH EVERYTHING TODAY.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED IT.
THE MEN'S SHORT DISTANCE HAS
A LOT OF STIFF COMPETITION.
- THANKS.
GOOD LUCK, RIGHT.
- ( gunshot )
- ( beeping )
- ELEVEN POINT
THREE NINE SECONDS.
EIGHTY-EIGHT SECONDS.
- YES!
( panting )
- EVERYONE'S SO TENSE.
I GOTTA TRY TO STAY LOOSE
AND NOT LET IT GET TO ME.
- Soichi: WHAT'S
WRONG, AKITSUKI?
- MIYAMOTO SENPAI.
- YOU LOOK A BIT DOWN.
- EVERYONE'S COMING IN AT
JUST OVER ELEVEN SECONDS.
I GUESS I'M WORRIED
I CAN'T KEEP UP.
- OH, YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
I'M SURE YOU CAN
COMPETE AT THEIR LEVEL.
- YOU REALLY THINK SO?
- ABSOLUTELY.
- GET SET.
- YOU'VE BEEN PRACTICING
REALLY HARD THE LAST TWO WEEKS.
- ( gunshot )
- SO QUIT WORRYING ABOUT IT!
I'M SURE YOU'RE GONNA DO GREAT.
- THANKS.
- NEXT, AKITSUKI AND KOBAYAKAWA.
- GO AND GIVE IT YOUR BEST SHOT.
- I HAVE TO DO WELL.
I CAN'T MAKE A FOOL OUT OF
MYSELF IN FRONT OF ASAHINA.
- YOU CAN DO IT, I
HAVE FAITH IN YOU.
- OH, THANKS.
- HUH? HE'S
A ROCKET STARTER? INTERESTING.
- YEAH.
AND HE GOT A GREAT TIME WHEN HE
USED THAT TECHNIQUE BEFORE.
- I SEE.
- ALL RIGHT. NOW, ON YOUR MARKS.
- LET'S GO.
( smirks )
- GREAT, SHE'S WATCHING.
NOW I HAVE TO DO WELL.
- SET.
- EVEN I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYONE
WHO CAN RUN AS FAST AS YOU CAN.
- YOU'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
I'M SURE YOU CAN COMPETE
AT THEIR LEVEL, AKITSUKI.
- I DON'T KNOW IF
THEY'RE RIGHT ABOUT ME.
THEIR EXPECTATIONS ARE SO HIGH.
- ( gunshot )
- I CAN'T TAKE IT!
- WHOA, AKITSUKI'S REALLY FAST.
- YOU'RE TELLING ME.
I HAD NO IDEA.
- HE'S STILL RIGHT BEHIND ME.
A HUNDRED METERS SEEMS SO FAR.
MY LEGS ARE GIVING OUT ON ME.
JUST A BIT FURTHER. I CAN'T LOSE
THIS HERE AT THE END.
- ( beeping )
- TEN POINT NINE EIGHT SECONDS!
- WHAT? THAT CAN'T BE RIGHT.
- IT IS. I SWEAR.
- WOW. THAT WAS AMAZING.
- I THINK I MIGHT HAVE
JUST BROKEN MY PREVIOUS RECORD.
- WHOA!
- YOU SURE FOUND US AN AMAZING
ROOKIE THERE, MIYAMOTO.
- I KNOW.
BUT I NEVER EXPECTED HIM
TO BE ANYWHERE NEAR
THIS GOOD SO SOON.
HE'S ALREADY FINISHING
IN THE TEN-SECOND RANGE.
- AKITSUKI, REMINDS YOU OF
SOMEONE, DOESN'T HE?
- YES, I HAD NOTICED
THE RESEMBLANCE.
AND I THINK ASAHINA
SEES IT, TOO.
- WAY TO GO, GRACE.
- ARE YOU OKAY, MAN?
- ( laughs )
- CONGRATULATIONS, AKITSUKI.
YOU HAD THE BEST TIME.
YOU'RE GOING
TO THE TOURNAMENT.
- MAN, TODAY FELT GOOD.
MAYBE ASAHINA WILL GIVE
ME MORE CREDIT.
ASAHINA.
HEY, DID YOU HEAR?
I RAN THE HUNDRED METERS
IN UNDER ELEVEN SECONDS?
I HAD THE BEST TIME
OUTTA MY GROUP.
PRETTY IMPRESSIVE,
DON'T YOU THINK?
- SURE.
- I WAS HOPING
FOR A BETTER REACTION.
- WHAT? WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO
DO? I THOUGHT YOU'D BE HAPPY.
- I AM . I AM HAPPY FOR YOU.
- OH, I SEE.
- THEN WHY? WHY DO YOU
HAVE TO BE SO COLD TO ME?
I EVEN GOT PICKED AS
THE TOP SPRINTER
FOR THE METROPOLITAN TOURNAMENT.
- YEAH, I HEARD.
- COULD YOU BE LESS EXCITED?
- SORRY, I THINK I'D BETTER
BE GETTING HOME NOW.
- WHA... HEY, WOULD YOU
JUST WAIT A MINUTE?
- JUST TELL ME WHAT IT IS
ABOUT ME THAT YOU DON'T LIKE.
'CAUSE I DON'T HAVE A CLUE.
- LET GO OF ME. THAT HURTS.
- IT'S JUST SOMETIMES,
I DESPISE BEING AROUND YOU.
AND I, I DON'T KNOW WHY,
IT'S JUST THE WAY IT IS.
- DESPISES YOU? THAT'S HARSH.
- YEAH. I KNOW. HARSH.
- I FEEL FOR YA.
DESPISE IS A STRONG WORD TO BE
THROWIN' AROUND. REALLY STRONG.
- YEAH.
- BUT AT LEAST SHE FEELS
ONE WAY OR THE OTHER.
I MEAN, SHE'S NOT INDIFFERENT.
BEING DESPISED IS MUCH BETTER
THAN JUST BEING TOLERATED.
- OH, REALLY?
- LOVE AND HATE ARE
VERY CLOSE EMOTIONS.
YOU MIGHT BE ABLE TO
TURN IT AROUND.
- YOU'RE JUST TRYING
TO MAKE ME FEEL BETTER.
- Miki: WHAT'S WITH
THE GLOOMY MOOD?
YOU GUYS ARE
ALWAYS SO SERIOUS?
SOMETHING WRONG WITH YOUR FOOD?
- HASHIBA! NO, NOTHING'S WRONG.
- WELL, ACTUALLY, YAMATO LIKES
SUZUKA BUT SHE TOLD HIM
THAT SHE DESPISES
BEING AROUND HIM.
- WHAT?
- DON'T TELL HER THAT.
- I THOUGHT WE COULD USE
A WOMAN'S OPINION ON THE MATTER.
I'M TRYING TO HELP YOU
OUT HERE, MAN. TRUST ME.
- HMM, I SEE.
AKITSUKI LIKES SUZUKA,
BUT SHE DOESN'T LIKE HIM.
AND I LIKE AKITSUKI, BUT HE'S SO
PREOCCUPIED WITH LIKING SUZUKA
THAT HE WON'T EVEN GIVE ME
THE TIME OF DAY.
- WHAT?
- WHO CARES ABOUT YOU?
THIS IS ABOUT HIM!
ANNOYING.
- WHAT? SHUT YOUR MOUTH.
- YOU SHUT YOURS.
PEOPLE WOULD PROBABLY LIKE YOU
A LOT BETTER IF YOU DID.
- OH, THAT'S ORIGINAL.
- COULD WE GET BACK
TO ME, PLEASE?
- OH, RIGHT, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
NOW BACK TO THE PROBLEM AT HAND.
HERE'S WHAT I THINK ABOUT IT.
IF SHE REALLY HATES
YOU THAT MUCH
THEN THERE'S NO POINT IN YOU
STAYING ON WITH
THE TRACK TEAM.
- WELL, MAYBE.
- YOU GOT INTO THIS WHOLE THING
TO MAKE HER LIKE YOU MORE.
AND THAT'S OBVIOUSLY
NOT WORKING.
- THAT'S HORRIBLE ADVICE, JERK.
HE CAN RUN THE HUNDRED METERS
IN THE TEN-SECOND RANGE!
HE'S GOT TALENT.
- I'M JUST SAYING, HE
DIDN'T HAVE ANY INTEREST
IN TRACK AND FIELD
TO BEGIN WITH.
AND IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF HE'S GREAT AT TRACK.
IF SUZUKA HATES HIM, THEN
ALL HIS SUCCESS IS MEANINGLESS.
- LISTEN TO ME.
IF HE QUIT NOW IT WOULD
ONLY MAKE SUZUKA HATE HIM
EVEN MORE THAN SHE ALREADY DOES.
TRUST ME. SHE'S MY BEST FRIEND.
I KNOW WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
- YOU THINK?
- OF COURSE. DON'T
LISTEN TO THIS SLACKER,
HIS ADVICE WILL ONLY GET
YOU INTO MORE TROUBLE.
- WHO'RE YOU CALLING
A SLACKER, DORK?
- WHY, YOU OF COURSE.
YOU'RE NOT IN ANY CLUBS,
YOU JUST HANG AROUND.
- BACK OFF PSYCHO,
I HAVE MY OWN GOALS!
AND WHAT ABOUT YOU?
WHAT KIND OF SPRINTER
GROWS HER HAIR THAT LONG?
- I WEAR IT LONG BECAUSE
AN ATHLETE I ADMIRE
WEARS HERS THIS WAY.
AND ANYWAY, LIKE
YOU'RE ONE TO TALK!
BUTTON UP YOUR SHIRT!
WHO ARE YOU TRYING TO ATTRACT?
- IT'S BECAUSE I'M HOT,
SLUG TRAIL.
- WELL, YOU LOOK SLOPPY.
- NOT AS SLOPPY AS YOUR HAIR!
- I DON'T THINK I'M GOING TO
QUIT THE TEAM, GUYS.
I'VE GOT NOTHING ELSE TO DO, SO
I MIGHT AS WELL STICK WITH IT.
I'LL JUST HAVE TO HANG IN THERE
AND HOPE THAT I CAN MANAGE
TO IMPRESS ASAHINA AGAIN.
- OH, THAT'S GREAT.
- I HOPE YOU'RE SURE.
- HEY, WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT?
- WE WERE JUST TRYING TO GIVE
YAMATO SOME ADVICE.
- YEAH, THAT'S IT.
LISTEN. CAN YOU HELP US OUT?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT HATTORI'S SHIRT?
HE SHOULD BUTTON IT, RIGHT?
- I...
- IT'S MY ONLY CHOICE.
I HAVE TO STICK WITH IT.
IF I KEEP GETTING BETTER
AND BETTER,
MAYBE ASAHINA WILL COME AROUND.
( grunting )
- THAT'S IMPRESSIVE. YOU'RE
LIFTING A LOT OF WEIGHT THERE.
YOU EVER CONSIDERED
TRYING THE SHOT PUT?
- NO THANKS. I THINK
I'LL STICK TO SPRINTING.
BUT I REALLY DON'T SEE
HOW WEIGHT TRAINING
IS GOING TO MAKE ME
RUN ANY FASTER.
- JUST TRUST ME.
WEIGHT TRAINING WILL HELP YOU
DEVELOP THAT EXPLOSIVE ENERGY
THAT YOU'RE GONNA NEED
IN A SHORT RACE.
THE STRONGER YOU ARE
THE FASTER YOU'LL BE.
- I SEE.
THEN I THINK I'LL DO A BIT
MORE TRAINING BY MYSELF
BEFORE I LEAVE.
- ALL RIGHT. JUST
DON'T OVERDO IT.
- SURE.
- HEY, AKITSUKI,
YOU MIND IF WE STAY AND
WORK OUT WITH YOU SOME MORE?
IT'LL RUIN OUR REPUTATION
IF A FRESHMAN STAYS LATER
THAN US UPPERCLASSMEN,
YOU KNOW.
- AND WE DON'T WANT THAT!
- THAT'S RIGHT.
- THERE'S NO WAY
I'M LEAVING YET.
- QUITE A CHANGE IN ATTITUDE
AROUND HERE, HUH?
- I SUPPOSE SO.
- AKITSUKI'S REALLY BEEN RAISING
EVERYONE'S SPIRITS.
HIS PRESENCE ON THE TEAM
HAS WORKED WONDERS FOR EVERYONE.
- LET'S GO AHEAD AND ADD
FIVE POUNDS TO EACH SIDE.
- YOU SURE YOU CAN HANDLE IT?
- YEAH. SURE.
- IT REMINDS ME OF THE WAY
THINGS USED TO BE...
BEFORE.
YOU SEE IT, DON'T YOU?
AKITSUKI. HE LOOKS
JUST LIKE KAZUKI.
OH, HEY. WAIT. ASAHINA.
- SORRY. I HAVE TO GET
BACK TO PRACTICE.
I HAVE A LOT TO WORK ON TODAY.
- OH. FINE.
( grunting )
( breathing heavily )
- WHAT'S WRONG, SUZUKA?
THAT HEIGHT ISN'T USUALLY
A PROBLEM FOR YOU.
ARE YOU NOT FEELING WELL?
- I'M FINE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
- OKAY. BUT IF THERE'S ANYTHING
YOU WANNA TALK ABOUT,
YOU KNOW I'M HERE.
- SORRY, BUT I NEED
SOME TIME TO MYSELF.
- YEAH, I UNDERSTAND.
YOU'VE BEEN THINKING
ABOUT AKITSUKI, HAVEN'T YOU?
- NO. I JUST NEED
TO GET SOME REST.
- I SEE.
- I FEEL TERRIBLE.
WHAT DOES HE KNOW?
- YOU SEE IT, DON'T
YOU? AKITSUKI.
HE LOOKS JUST LIKE KAZUKI.
- NO, HE DOESN'T!
THEY'RE NOTHING ALIKE.
- ( whistle blowing )
- Captain: THAT'S IT FOR TODAY!
- ALL RIGHT, WE'RE DONE!
- OH, MAN. I'M BEAT.
- I WANT YOU GUYS TO BE
COMPLETELY RESTED UP
FOR THE TOURNAMENT THIS WEEKEND.
- SO NO PRACTICE TOMORROW.
- All: YES!
- THEN THAT MEANS WE HAVE
A WHOLE DAY OFF TOMORROW.
- A DAY OFF, HUH?
I'VE GOTTA TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF THIS
AND FIX THINGS WITH ASAHINA.
BUT I HAVE NO IDEA
HOW TO DO THAT.
MAYBE WE COULD GO SHOPPING
FOR AUNT AYANO.
BUT I DOUBT SHE WOULD
GO WITH ME, THOUGH.
SHE HAS BEEN ACTING PRETTY COLD.
I'LL ASK HER ANYWAY, EVEN
THOUGH I KNOW SHE'LL SAY NO.
- Soichi: YOU'RE LEAVING?
- WHAT ARE THEY TALKING ABOUT?
- THE COMPETITION'S SOON.
SO I'M THINKING OF GOING HOME
THIS WEEKEND TO YOKOHAMA.
- YOKOHAMA?
- OH, AND TO KAZUKI.
- YEAH. IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE I'VE GONE HOME TO SEE HIM.
- KAZUKI?
- BE SURE TO PAY HIM MY RESPECTS
AND HAVE A SAFE TRIP.
- SURE.
- WHO'S KAZUKI?
- KAZUKI?
MAYBE IT'S HER BROTHER.
NAH.
SHE WOULDN'T MAKE THAT LONG TRIP
JUST TO SEE HER BROTHER.
MAYBE IT'S A GUY SHE USED
TO DATE, OR HAD A CRUSH ON.
( sighs ) EITHER WAY, IT'S
GOTTA BE SOMEONE SHE LIKES.
I'VE NEVER HEARD HER MENTION
ANY BOYS BEFORE.
BUT SHE MUST'VE HAD
A BOYFRIEND IN YOKOHAMA.
AND TOMORROW SHE'S USING HER
DAY OFF TO GO BACK AND SEE HIM.
OR HE COULD JUST BE A FRIEND.
BUT I DOUBT IT.
- YEAH. IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE I'VE GONE HOME TO SEE HIM.
I'M SORRY.
OR YOU'LL SERIOUSLY MAKE
A FOOL OF YOURSELF IF YOU JOIN
AND THEN QUIT WHEN IT
GETS TOO HARD.
SOMETIMES, I JUST DESPISE
BEING AROUND YOU.
- ASAHINA'S SAID
SOME MEAN THINGS BEFORE.
BUT NOTHING HURTS LIKE THIS.
LIKE KNOWING THAT SHE'S GOING
TO SEE SOMEONE ELSE.
- GOOD MORNING.
- WELL, GOOD MORNING, YAMATO.
- Ayano: DID YOU NOT SLEEP WELL?
YOU DON'T LOOK SO GOOD, YAMATO.
- OH, I'M FINE.
I DIDN'T GET A WINK
OF SLEEP LAST NIGHT.
I COULDN'T GET ASAHINA
OFF MY MIND.
- HERE, HAVE SOME TEA.
- OH, THANK YOU VERY MUCH, MIHO.
- WHERE'S ASAHINA? HAS SHE
NOT WOKEN UP YET THIS MORNING?
- NO, SHE ALREADY ATE,
AND THEN LEFT JUST A MINUTE AGO.
- SHE APPARENTLY NEEDED TO DO
SOMETHING BACK HOME.
- OH, I SEE.
- SO SHE DID GO SEE
THIS KAZUKI AFTER ALL.
I BET ASAHINA'S ARRIVING IN
YOKOHAMA RIGHT ABOUT NOW, GORO.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- ( meows )
- I NEVER UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
GORO, WAIT. WHERE DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOING? GET BACK HERE.
- ( meows )
- HEY, STOP IT.
I SAID GET BACK HERE.
- ( meows )
- YOU CAN'T GO IN THERE.
THAT'S ASAHINA'S ROOM. WAIT!
( grunting )
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU,
YOU STUPID CAT?
( exclaims )
IS THAT HIM?
- OH, AND TO KAZUKI.
- YEAH. IT'S BEEN A WHILE
SINCE I'VE SEEN HIM.
- ( heart beating )
- SO, THAT'S THE GUY.
THE GUY THAT ASAHINA LIKES.
- HERE YOU GO.
- THANK YOU.
- SEE YOU LATER.
- I HOPE YOU KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE DOING, YAMATO.
- I DON'T HAVE A CLUE.
- ( train whistling )
- I DON'T KNOW WHY...
BUT I JUST HAVE TO GO.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ABOVE ♪
♪ NOW IS ALL WE HAVE ♪
♪ WITH A LITTLE FEELING
AND A LOT OF LOVE ♪
♪ WE TURN UP THE HEAT AND RUN ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- ♪ ALL MY LIFE HERE ON THE
GROUND ABOUT TO RUN AND NOW ♪
♪ I FIND I MUST
ASK MYSELF WHY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE SOMETHING IS STIRRING ♪
♪ I FEEL IT WHISPERING IN ME ♪
♪ SOME DAYS I WAKE UP ♪
♪ BUT MY HEART'S
STILL SLEEPING ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME
TO RUN AND TRY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME TO FLY ♪
♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ON HIGH ♪
♪ WITH OUR GOAL IN SIGHT ♪
♪ WE WILL RUN
WITH ALL OUR MIGHT ♪
♪ TOMORROW AND TODAY
WILL NEVER EVER PASS US BY ♪
♪ WE WILL NOT STOP NOW ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR HEART ALIVE
AND YOUR DREAM SURVIVES ♪
♪ AND YOU CROSS
THE FINISH LINE ♪
♪ LET IT GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- Suzuka: ARE YOU QUITTING
THE TRACK TEAM?
JUST WHEN I THOUGHT YOU
WERE GETTING SERIOUS,
YOU LET ME DOWN.
- Yamato: YOU WANT ME
TO QUIT, DON'T YOU?
- I WANT YOU TO DO
WHAT YOU WANT TO DO.
STOP WORRYING ABOUT ME
ALL THE TIME.