- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART SKIP
THE BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEM
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING EVERYTHING
IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALL RIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOOD BYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- ALL RIGHT. RELAY.
I KNOW I CAN DO THIS.
HI!
- PLEASE DON'T
TALK TO ME, YAMATO.
- I NEED TO FOCUS BUT
I CAN'T STOP THINKING
ABOUT HOW MUCH SHE HATES ME.
- WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING, AKITSUKI?
YOU NEED TO WAKE UP!
YOU KEEP DROPPING THE BATON!
- UH, I'M SORRY.
- HEY, MIYAMOTO, I KNOW THIS GUY
MAY BE A FAST RUNNER BUT, UH,
HIS BATON WORK IS TERRIBLE!
- WOULD YOU GIVE HIM
A BREAK, SASAKI.
THIS IS HIS FIRST TIME
TO PRACTICE
WITH THE RELAY TEAM, OKAY?
- I UNDERSTAND THAT EVERYONE
HAS TO START SOMEWHERE,
SO I GUESS I CAN BE
A LITTLE MORE PATIENT.
BUT JUDGING BY HIS PROGRESS,
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE HE'S
ACTUALLY TAKING THIS SERIOUSLY.
I MEAN WERE YOU REALLY
TRYING YOUR BEST JUST THEN?
IT SURE DOESN'T SEEM LIKE IT...
- ALL RIGHT, THAT'S ENOUGH.
IT'S OBVIOUS TO ME THAT
HE'S TRYING HIS BEST.
- POOR AKITSUKI.
- ( bell chiming )
- I REALLY SUCK.
I WAS SO DETERMINED TO EXCEL
IN TRACK AND FIELD
AND NOW I'M JUST...
- AKITSUKI!
WHAT ARE YOU UP TO?
YOU JUST FINISH PRACTICING?
- UH, YEAH, WHAT ARE YOU
STILL DOING HERE?
- HAD SOME STUFF TO DO.
SO, HOW YOU DOING WITH RELAY?
- WELL, I KNOW
I'M HOLDING EVERYONE BACK.
I KEEP DROPPING
THE STUPID BATON.
I THINK THEY ALL HATE ME.
IT SUCKS BECAUSE THIS ISN'T
THE KIND OF THING
I CAN JUST PRACTICE ON MY OWN.
I REALLY FEEL BADLY ABOUT IT.
- WELL, IF YOU WANT...
I COULD HELP YOU.
I MEAN, SINCE I MADE SUCH A BIG
DEAL ABOUT YOU DOING YOUR BEST
THE OTHER DAY.
I MAY AS WELL DO MY PART TO MAKE
SURE YOU DON'T SCREW UP.
- OKAY. THAT SOUNDS PRETTY GOOD,
BUT I THINK
THE FIELD'S CLOSED SO...
- OH, DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT.
I KNOW OF ANOTHER PLACE
WE CAN GO THAT'LL WORK.
SO HURRY UP
AND GET READY, OKAY?
- OH, WOW.
A PARK?
- THAT'S RIGHT. HUGE, ISN'T IT?
I THOUGHT THIS ONE WOULD BE GOOD
SO THAT WE COULD HAVE THE
STRAIGHT COURSE TO PRACTICE ON.
- WAIT! WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHY ARE YOU STRIPPING?
- CALM DOWN. IT'S MY UNIFORM.
YOU'RE SUCH A DORK.
IF WE'RE GONNA PRACTICE
FOR THE MEET,
WE SHOULD DO IT UNDER
MEET CONDITIONS.
- BUT WHAT IF SOMEONE SEES US?
- OH, PLEASE. HURRY UP
AND TAKE YOUR CLOTHES OFF.
WE NEED TO GET BUSY.
- DON'T SAY IT LIKE THAT!
IT SOUNDS WEIRD!
- WELL, YOU'RE BEING WEIRD!
SEE, YOU'RE DOING
MUCH BETTER ALREADY.
LET'S GO ONE MORE ROUND
SO THAT IT ALL SINKS IN.
- RIGHT!
THIS IS IT. I'M GONNA DO IT.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU.
- WHAT HAPPENED? ALL YOU HAD TO
DO WAS GRAB THE BATON, AKITSUKI.
THE TIMING WAS PERFECT.
IT WAS RIGHT THERE.
- YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT. I'M SORRY.
- ( sighs )
WELL, I THINK WE BETTER
CALL IT A DAY.
- HUH?
- I'M GONNA GO GET US SOME
JUICE. I'LL BE RIGHT BACK, OKAY?
- I'M SO CONFUSED. WHAT IN
THE WORLD AM I DOING?
I FEEL LIKE I'M CONSTANTLY DOING
SOMETHING OR SAYING THINGS
JUST TO MAKE SOMEONE ELSE HAPPY.
I WANTED TO BE A GOOD BOYFRIEND
FOR HONOKA.
I'M PRACTICING LONG HOURS
FOR TRACK BECAUSE
HASHIBA BELIEVES IN ME.
BUT FOR SOME REASON I CAN'T SEEM
TO FULLY COMMIT TO ANYTHING.
I ONLY MAKE HALF AN EFFORT
AND I END UP LETTING
EVERYONE DOWN ANYWAY.
I HONESTLY HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT IT IS I WANT TO DO.
( exclaims ) THAT'S COLD!
- OH, GREAT. YOU WERE SULKING
AGAIN, WEREN'T YOU?
WHAT IS IT THIS TIME?
IS IT BECAUSE SENPAI
GOT MAD AT YOU?
- NO, THAT ISN'T IT. NOT REALLY.
- SO THEN WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- TO BE HONEST, I HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT I'M WORRIED ABOUT.
I'M SORRY. I KNOW THAT DOESN'T
MAKE ANY SENSE TO YOU.
I WISH I COULD EXPLAIN. REALLY.
- LET ME GUESS, I BET THIS HAS
SOMETHING TO DO WITH YOU
AND SUZUKA, DOESN'T IT?
DO YOU FEEL BAD ABOUT TELLING
HER SO MUCH INFORMATION?
LIKE ABOUT YOUR BREAKUP
WITH SAKURAI?
- NO, IT'S NOT THAT.
- ARE YOU SURE?
IT WOULD MAKE SENSE.
I MEAN, DIDN'T YOU BREAKUP
WITH HER BECAUSE OF SUZUKA?
AT LEAST, THAT'S WHAT I HEARD.
- NO. IT'S MOSTLY BECAUSE I JUST
JUMPED INTO THE RELATIONSHIP
WITHOUT EVEN THINKING.
- THEN WHY DIDN'T YOU JUST SAY
THAT IN THE FIRST PLACE?
WHY WOULD YOU SAY THAT
YOU BROKE UP WITH SAKURAI
BECAUSE SHE WAS ANNOYING?
SHE WAS REALLY HURT BY THAT!
AND ALL YOU DID WAS MAKE
SUZUKA ANGRY
BY USING THAT STUPID REASON
TO COVER UP THE TRUTH.
- YEAH, I KNOW! BUT, WHAT AM I
SUPPOSED TO DO ABOUT IT NOW?
JUST SAY, "SORRY, I LIED?"
- SEE. THAT IS WHY YOU WERE SAD.
WELL, NOW THAT I KNOW
I CAN HELP YOU CLEAR THIS UP.
I'LL JUST SAY, "AKITSUKI TOLD ME
NOT TO TELL YOU THIS, BUT... "
TRUST ME. SUZUKA WILL UNDERSTAND
IF SHE KNOWS THE TRUTH
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED.
I'M NOT EVEN GOING TO TELL HER
THAT WE TALKED TONIGHT,
SO DON'T WORRY.
- I GUESS... I MEAN, IF YOU DID
THAT THAT WOULD BE...
- OKAY. WE'LL SETTLE ALL OF THIS
TOMORROW, THEN.
- NO. JUST A MINUTE.
- OH, GREAT. NOW WHAT'S WRONG?
- DON'T TALK TO HER. I'LL DO IT.
- ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THAT?
- I MEAN, I KNOW ASAHINA'S JUST
GOING TO THINK THAT I'M LYING
AND I'M TRYING
TO COVER MY TRACKS.
IT'LL PROBABLY BE
REALLY EMBARRASSING,
BUT I HAVE TO
TAKE CARE OF THIS MYSELF.
BECAUSE I'LL JUST FEEL GUILTY
IF I DON'T.
- AKITSUKI...
- BUT, IT'S ALWAYS POSSIBLE THAT
AFTER I TELL HER THE TRUTH,
SHE'LL MAKE ME REGRET
SAYING ANYTHING AT ALL.
- THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
JUST DO WHAT YOU WANNA DO.
WHEN I ASKED YOU WHAT WAS WRONG,
YOU SAID YOU HAD NO IDEA
WHAT WAS BOTHERING YOU.
BUT IT'S OBVIOUS TO ME
THAT YOU JUST WANTED
TO MAKE UP WITH SUZUKA.
YOU SHOULD'VE JUST SAID THAT.
- YEAH. SHE'S RIGHT.
BECAUSE IT'S SO AWKWARD
BEING AROUND HER AT HOME!
- YEAH, I CAN UNDERSTAND THAT.
- I DON'T KNOW
WHY IT MATTERS SO MUCH,
BUT I CAN'T STAND THE FACT
THAT ASAHINA STILL HATES ME.
BUT, IF I SAY THAT TO HER
THEN SHE'LL JUST...
NO, I NEED TO GO ABOUT THIS
ANOTHER WAY.
IF SHE ANSWERS LIKE THAT,
THEN I COULD MAYBE ...
NO. FORGET IT.
- WHAT ARE YOU MUMBLING ABOUT
OVER THERE? EAT YOUR FOOD.
- ( screams ) IT'S HOPELESS!
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHICH WAY I GO
ABOUT THIS, I'M GOING TO FAIL!
- WELL, THAT WAS DRAMATIC.
SERIOUSLY, YAMATO,
WHY DOES IT ALWAYS SEEM LIKE YOU
HAVE SOME KIND
OF INCURABLE TRAUMA GOING
ON IN YOUR LIFE?
- ( sighs ) MAYBE IT WOULD BE
BETTER IF HASHIBA TALKED TO HER.
I DON'T KNOW.
- WHAT? YOU STILL HAVEN'T
TALKED TO HER, YET?
I KNEW THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
YOU SHOULD'VE JUST LET
ME TALK TO HER.
- BUT...
- WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
TALK TO WHO?
- THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
YOU. JUST EAT YOUR NOODLES.
- I GET IT. YAMATO'S SINGLE NOW,
AND SO YOU FIGURED YOU
WOULD JUMP ON THAT
BY PRETENDING
TO BE HELPFUL.
- WHAT? THAT'S RIDICULOUS
AND YOU KNOW IT!
- GEEZ! YAMATO!
HAVE I TAUGHT YOU NOTHING?
YOU'RE REALLY NOT SUPPOSED TO
REBOUND WITH YOUR FRIENDS.
- THAT'S ENOUGH! IT'S NOT TRUE!
WE'RE NOT AS DISTURBED AS YOU!
- HOW AM I DISTURBED?
I'M NOT THE ONE WHO'S TRYING
TO DATE MY FRIENDS.
- ( scoffs ) OH, LIKE YOU
HAVEN'T TRIED BEFORE?
- WHATEVER! YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT ME!
- THANK YOU!
- OH, I'M SORRY.
THINKING ABOUT IT ISN'T GOING TO
ACHIEVE ANYTHING.
I NEED TO JUST DO IT.
I'M SURE IF I GIVE HER
A CLEAR EXPLANATION,
SHE'LL UNDERSTAND.
- ( mewing )
- HI, GORO.
DID YOU JUST GET BACK?
- HEY! SORRY.
- FOR WHAT? HAVE YOU DONE
SOMETHING TO ME
AND I JUST HAVEN'T NOTICED IT?
- WHAT? NO!
IT'S NOTHING LIKE THAT!
LOOK, I TOLD YOU WHY I BROKE UP
WITH HONOKA, BUT
IT WASN'T THE TRUTH.
- WHY ARE YOU TELLING ME
ABOUT THIS NOW?
- I DIDN'T MEAN TO LIE.
THE TRUTH IS THERE WAS
ALWAYS SOMETHING WRONG
BETWEEN ME AND HONOKA.
WE FOUGHT ALL THE TIME
AND JUST REALIZED
WE WEREN'T
GETTING ALONG.
THAT'S ALL.
- IF THAT'S ALL, WHY DIDN'T YOU
JUST SAY SO IN THE FIRST PLACE?
WHY DID YOU HAVE TO MAKE UP
SUCH STUPID LIE?
IT DOESN'T SOUND LIKE
YOU HAVE ANYTHING TO HIDE.
- I KNOW.
- I DIDN'T WANNA TELL YOU THAT
THE REASON WE STARTED FIGHTING
IN THE FIRST PLACE WAS BECAUSE
SHE THOUGHT I STILL LIKED YOU.
THAT'S NOT THE ONLY REASON
WE BROKE UP, THOUGH.
DON'T THINK THAT.
THAT'S JUST HOW IT STARTED.
WE BROKE UP BECAUSE
I WAS CARELESS
AND I WASN'T TREATING HER RIGHT.
- OKAY, SO WHY DIDN'T YOU
TELL ME ALL THIS
WHEN I ASKED YOU ABOUT IT
THE FIRST TIME?
- BECAUSE I DIDN'T WANT YOU TO
FEEL GUILTY ABOUT IT, ASAHINA.
- WELL, I FEEL GUILTY.
YOU JUST TOLD ME I'M THE REASON
YOU BROKE UP WITH HER!
- SEE, THIS IS WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT!
THIS IS WHY I DIDN'T
WANT TO TELL YOU!
- THEN WHY ARE WE STANDING HERE
TALKING ABOUT IT?
WHAT'S THE POINT OF
EVEN BRINGING IT UP AGAIN?
- BECAUSE...
I CAN'T TAKE IT. I DON'T WANNA
FIGHT WITH YOU ANYMORE.
IT'S GETTING ANNOYING.
I CAN'T FOCUS ON THINGS.
I CAN'T EVEN PRACTICE
BECAUSE I'M TOO BUSY WORRYING
ABOUT HOW MAD YOU ARE AT ME.
- AND WHOSE FAULT IS THAT?
YOU BROUGHT THIS
ON YOURSELF, YOU KNOW.
YOU DIDN'T HAVE TO LIE.
- I KNOW THAT. AND I'M REALLY,
REALLY SORRY, OKAY?
I JUST DON'T WANT YOU
TO HATE ME.
- I DON'T GET IT.
- DON'T GET WHAT?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
ASAHINA! ASAHINA!
( sighs )
- ( door opens )
- ( groans ) DAMN IT!
I FEEL LIKE AN IDIOT.
IT JUST SOUNDED LIKE
I WAS MAKING EXCUSES.
I MESSED EVERYTHING UP.
I SHOULD'VE JUST LET HASHIBA
TALK TO HER FOR ME.
ASAHINA WOULD'VE
LISTENED TO HER.
I JUST MADE IT WORSE.
WHY DO I TRY?
( sighs ) THIS REALLY SUCKS!
- Miho: WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU LET
THIS MUCH LAUNDRY PILE UP!
I BET IT'S MOLDY!
- I'VE BEEN SO BUSY
WITH PRACTICE
THAT I HAVEN'T HAD
ANY TIME TO DO IT. GEEZ!
- SO YOU WERE JUST GOING TO WAIT
UNTIL YOU RAN COMPLETELY OUT
OF CLOTHES TO DO YOUR LAUNDRY?
- NO. I WAS JUST ON MY WAY
TO THE LAUNDROMAT.
GOODNESS, MIHO'S STARTING TO
SOUND EXACTLY LIKE HER MOTHER.
NAG, NAG, NAG. SERIOUSLY.
HEY, ASAHINA!
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE BOTH DOING
LAUNDRY TONIGHT, HUH?
- YEP.
- WITH ALL THESE PRACTICES
WE'RE HAVING,
IT'S EASY TO LET IT ALL PILE UP,
ISN'T IT?
- NO. I HARDLY EVER LET
MY LAUNDRY PILE UP.
- OH, SORRY.
- ( machine whirring )
- UH, HEY! I HAVE TWO MEAT AND
POTATO CROQUETTES HERE.
- WOULD YOU LIKE ONE, ASAHINA?
- NO THANKS.
- OH, OKAY.
OH, YEAH, GUESS WHAT? I WAS
THINKING ABOUT TRYING TO GROW
SOME CHERRY TOMATOES
OUTSIDE ON THE VERANDA!
IF I HAVE A GOOD CROP,
I'LL GIVE SOME TO YOU, OKAY?
- ( beeping )
- SINCE YOU HAVE SO MUCH TIME,
WHY DON'T YOU GO TO
THE CONVENIENCE STORE?
- I REALLY DON'T HAVE
THAT MUCH TIME LEFT.
BESIDES I HAVE
EVERYTHING I NEED.
- RIGHT.
- WHAT IS WRONG WITH HER?
WHY IS SHE IN SUCH A BAD MOOD?
IS IT BECAUSE SHE DOESN'T LIKE
BEING STUCK HERE WITH ME?
ASAHINA, DID YOU SEE?
YOUR LAUNDRY'S DONE.
IF YOU WAIT TOO LONG
TO TAKE IT OUT,
YOUR CLOTHES WILL GET WRINKLED.
SORRY.
- I CAN'T TAKE IT OUT.
LOOK, I JUST CAN'T TAKE IT OUT
WHILE YOU'RE HERE.
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND ANYTHING?
- UH, NOT THIS.
- YOU'RE SUCH AN IDIOT.
I CAN'T WANT TO TAKE IT OUT
BECAUSE MY UNDERWEAR'S IN THERE.
- OKAY. THAT MAKES SENSE NOW.
I GET IT! SHE JUST WANTED TO
TAKE HER UNDERWEAR OUT!
I'M SORRY I DIDN'T
CATCH THAT EARLIER.
UM, I GUESS I'M GOING TO
THE CONVENIENCE STORE THEN.
- HEY! WAIT JUST A MINUTE.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- I DECIDED I WANT IT.
THE CROQUETTE. I'M HUNGRY NOW
AND I CAN'T GO ANYWHERE,
SO JUST LEAVE IT HERE.
- SEE, YOU WANTED IT.
- IS THAT A PROBLEM?
- NO, NOT AT ALL.
( muffled ) WELL, I'LL SEE YOU
LATER. I HOPE YOU LIKE IT!
- HOLD ON! YOU CAN'T LEAVE YET!
- WHAT IS IT THIS TIME?
- I DON'T LIKE EATING BY MYSELF.
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
ESPECIALLY IN PLACES LIKE THIS.
STAY HERE AND EAT WITH ME.
- FIRST YOU WANT ME TO GO.
NOW YOU WANT ME TO STAY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND YOU, ASAHINA!
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHAT DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
EAT FIRST, THEN LEAVE!
- HEY! SHOULDN'T YOU BE A LITTLE
NICER WHEN YOU WANT
SOMEONE TO DO SOMETHING FOR YOU?
- JUST SAYIN'.
- I DON'T WANT IT, THEN!
- OH, COME ON! WHY ARE YOU
BEING LIKE THIS ASAHINA?
- LIKE WHAT?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH ME?
YOU NEED TO THINK ABOUT
HOW YOU'RE ACTING.
- WHAT'S GOING ON WITH HER?
- WOULD IT KILL YOU TO BE
- I ALWAYS THOUGHT
- A LITTLE MORE CONSIDERATE?
-SHE WAS SO MATURE, SO TOGETHER.
- YOUR TIMING IS TERRIBLE,
- BUT SHE'S SPOILED AND MOODY.
- NO IDEA ON TREATING GIRLS,
- SHE THROWS TANTRUMS
LIKE A CHILD.
- IT JUST PISSES ME OFF!
- YOU'RE JUST RUDE, YAMATO!
- THERE'S ABSOLUTELY NOTHING
CHARMING ABOUT HER ANYMORE.
- HEY! ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
HELLO? ANYONE THERE?
STOP DAYDREAMING!
- OKAY, WE FINISHED
OUR CROQUETTES.
I'M GOING TO THE STORE.
- ALL RIGHT.
WELL, TAKE YOUR TIME.
- YEAH, YEAH. I KNOW.
( sighs )
- ( phone ringing )
- HELLO?
- HOW'S IT GOING OVER THERE?
IT'S HASHIBA.
- OH, HI. HOW ARE YOU?
- GOOD. I WAS JUST WONDERING
HOW EVERYTHING WENT TODAY.
WERE YOU ABLE TO PATCH THINGS UP
WITH SUZUKA?
ACTUALLY, UM...
- OH, NO! DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
- NO, NOTHING LIKE THAT.
EVERYTHING IS FINE.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- YEAH! ABSOLUTELY! THANKS FOR
CHECKIN' ON ME, THOUGH.
- OKAY. I GUESS I'LL SEE YOU
TOMORROW THEN.
- OKAY, BYE!
- YOU DON'T REALLY SOUND
LIKE YOU'RE OKAY.
- WELL, I REALLY WISH I COULD
SAY THAT EVERYTHING WAS OKAY.
BUT I CAN'T. I MEAN, ASAHINA
WENT HOME WHEN SHE WAS DONE.
( sighs )
- ( phone ringing )
- WHAT NOW?
- HELLO?
- HI.
- UH, ASAHINA...
( groans )
OUCH!
- I'M SORRY. I WAS SO SURPRISED
I DROPPED THE PHONE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I'M NOT...
I WANTED TO SAY
I'M NOT MAD AT YOU ANYMORE!
SO JUST DON'T MESS UP
IN THE RELAY RACE, OKAY?
I DON'T WANT YOU TO LOSE
JUST BECAUSE YOU GOT
IN A FIGHT WITH ME.
GOOD NIGHT.
- I WON'T LOSE!
I'M GONNA CROSS THE FINISH LINE
WITH A HUGE LEAD!
( laughing ) JUST WATCH! I'LL
SHOW YOU, ASAHINA! I'M FAST!
YOU'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYONE AS FAST AS ME!
- Miho: HEY! YAMATO!
KEEP IT DOWN!
- THIS WILL BE THE GREATEST
RELAY RACE EVER!
JUST THEN I REALIZED.
IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT I SAY
OR WHAT SHE DOES,
I LIKE ASAHINA STILL.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ WHEN I TURN AROUND ♪
♪ YOU'RE RIGHT THERE
NEXT TO ME ♪
♪ ON YOUR FACE A SMILE
SO COMFORTING AND FAMILIAR ♪
♪ THE CLOSER YOU BECAME
THE LESS THAT I COULD SEE ♪
♪ AND NOW I'M WONDERING
SO LOST AND ALL ALONE ♪
♪ PEOPLE CHANGE
A LITTLE AT A TIME ♪
♪ AND NOW I KNOW I'M CHANGING ♪
♪ WHEN I CALL YOUR NAME
SHOUT IT OUT INTO THE SKY ♪
♪ THAT'S WHEN I WILL FIND
THE LOVE I KEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ WHEN YOU'RE WITH ME
AND YOU TAKE MY HAND ♪
♪ SOMEHOW EVERYTHING
SEEMS TO WORK ITSELF OUT RIGHT ♪
♪ WHEN I SEE YOUR EYES
STARING BACK AT MINE ♪
♪ THERE INSIDE I FIND
A LOVE THAT NEVER DIES ♪
♪ TOGETHER I KNOW
WE'LL FIND A WAY ♪
♪ JUST YOU AND I ♪
- Yamato: THIS IS IT!
I'VE DECIDED TO BECOME THE
NUMBER ONE SPRINTER IN JAPAN!
- Yasunobu: YOU'RE GONNA WHAT?
DUDE, ARE YOU FEELING OKAY?
- Yamato: YES, SHUT UP! IT'LL BE
A CHALLENGE, BUT I CAN DO IT.
I DON'T KNOW WHY,
BUT I FEEL LIKE I JUST HAVE TO!