♪ WATCHING AS YOUR EYES
STARE INTO THE DEEP BLUE SKY ♪
♪ I FEEL MY HEART
SKIP A BEAT WHEN YOU MOVE ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS KNOW
THE RIGHT THING TO SAY ♪
♪ YOUR FEELINGS
HIDDEN FAR AWAY ♪
♪ BREATHE A LITTLE SIGH ♪
♪ HOLD IT DEEP INSIDE ♪
♪ HIDING IN THE LIGHT ♪
♪ YOU ALWAYS SEEMED
SO SURE AND STRONG ♪
♪ BUT WE WERE WRONG ♪
♪ YOU WERE AFRAID ♪
♪ OF LOSING
EVERYTHING IN YOUR LIFE ♪
♪ I WANNA HOLD YOU
CLOSER TO MY HEART ♪
♪ I'LL CHASE AWAY
ALL OF YOUR FEARS ♪
♪ TELL YOU EVERYTHING
WILL BE ALRIGHT ♪
♪ STARTING LINE ♪
♪ TOGETHER WE'LL REWRITE
THIS STORY ♪
♪ AND TO OUR TEARS
WE ONLY SAY GOODBYE ♪
♪ AS WE REWRITE OUR FUTURES
IN THAT SKY ♪
♪ AND IN MY HEART ♪
♪ YOU'RE ALWAYS
CLOSE BESIDE ME ♪
♪ NO MATTER HOW FAR
YOU ARE AWAY ♪
♪ WE'LL ALWAYS BE ♪
♪ NEVER GO AWAY
ALWAYS STAY THIS CLOSE TO ME ♪
- COME ON, YASUNOBU. YOU COULD
AT LEAST TRY TO KEEP UP.
- I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU HAD TO DRAG ME
OUT OF BED AT EIGHT
ON A SUNDAY MORNING.
- 'CAUSE I DON'T WANNA
LIE AROUND MY ROOM ALL DAY
AND BE DEPRESSED. THAT'S WHY.
- THEN WHY DIDN'T YOU GO TO YOUR
TRACK MEET AND LET ME SLEEP?
IT IS TODAY, ISN'T IT?
- THAT'S THE LAST PLACE
I WANNA BE.
AFTER SHE SAID SUCH
HORRIBLE THINGS TO ME
AND EVEN SLAPPED ME.
I DON'T KNOW IF I EVER
WANT TO SEE ASAHINA AGAIN.
ALL RIGHT. LET'S GO
TO THAT KARAOKE PLACE.
- THERE'S NO WAY IT'S OPEN YET.
- I'M TIRED OF BEING
COMPARED TO SOME DEAD GUY.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
- BUT I, I WAS JUST
WORRIED ABOUT HIM.
- Reporter: HE'S HERE.
- OVER HERE!
- ARIMA, OVER HERE.
- Woman: HOW'RE YOU
FEELING TODAY?
- Man: FEEL LIKE BREAKING
ANY RECORDS? ( chuckles )
- WHAT'S THAT ALL ABOUT?
- OH, THAT'S
AKITSUKI'S COMPETITION.
EMERSON ARIMA, A SOPHOMORE
AT TOHTO UNIVERSITY
PREPARATORY ACADEMY.
HE'S THIS YEAR'S TOP
HIGH SCHOOL SPRINTER.
IN JUNIOR HIGH, HE WAS
ALWAYS OUTSHONE
BY KAZUKI AT THE
KANAGAWA PREFECTURE.
BUT SINCE HE'S
ENTERED HIGH SCHOOL,
HIS TALENT'S REALLY
BEGUN TO GROW.
- YEAH, I'VE HEARD OF HIM.
- IF KAZUKI WERE STILL ALIVE,
I'M SURE THEY'D BE EACH
OTHER'S STIFFEST COMPETITION.
- IF THINGS WERE DIFFERENT,
TSUDA SENPAI WOULD BE THE
ONE IN THE SPOTLIGHT
INSTEAD OF THAT GUY.
- WELL, YOU MAY BE RIGHT.
HOWEVER, WE'VE GOT AKITSUKI.
YOU REALLY SHOULDN'T
UNDERESTIMATE HIM.
- YOU DON'T HONESTLY THINK
HE'S STILL COMING, DO YOU?
I MEAN, REALLY.
HE'S SO IRRESPONSIBLE.
- WHY DO YOU GET SO ANGRY
EVERY TIME I BRING UP AKITSUKI?
- AND IF SENPAI WERE
STILL ALIVE TODAY,
THERE WOULD BE NO COMPETITION.
HE'D BEAT ARIMA EASILY.
A GUY LIKE ARIMA...
HE'S NOWHERE NEAR THE SAME
LEVEL AS TSUDA SENPAI.
- BE QUIET.
EVERYONE CAN HEAR YOU.
- I DON'T CARE WHO'S LISTENING.
- BUT...
- YOU DON'T SEEM TO KNOW
WHERE YOU'RE GOING,
SO LET ME PICK A DESTINATION.
- SURE. WAIT, WHERE?
- IF I TOLD YOU NOW,
IT'D RUIN THE SURPRISE.
- ( sighs )
- YOU BROUGHT ME
TO THE TRACK MEET?
- WELL, YOU WOULDN'T HAVE COME
IF I HAD TOLD YOU, RIGHT?
- NO, OF COURSE NOT.
- AND I'M NOT DOING THIS PURELY
OUTTA THE KINDNESS OF MY HEART.
THERE'S A LOTTA HOT GIRLS
IN THERE JUST MILLING ABOUT.
YOU CAN RUN OR NOT,
I DON'T REALLY CARE.
BUT I BET IF YOU DO, YOU'LL BE
A BABE MAGNET, YOU KNOW?
- SHUT UP.
AND I ALL READY TOLD YOU.
THERE'S REALLY NO REASON
FOR ME TO EVEN TRY ANYMORE.
- IS THAT SO?
THEN LET'S JUST HANG AROUND
A WHILE.
THERE ARE GIRLS
IN SHORT SHORTS IN THERE.
- HEY, YASUNOBU. LET GO OF ME.
I MEAN IT. I WANT TO GO HOME.
- HEY, THERE'S SUZUKA.
AND WE'RE JUST IN TIME TO SEE
SOME JERK MAKE A MOVE ON HER.
- HELLO THERE.
IT'S BEEN A WHILE, HASN'T IT?
- WHAT? CAN I HELP YOU
WITH SOMETHING?
- WOW, BACK OFF! I SEE
YOU'RE STILL THE SAME
AS YOU ALWAYS WERE.
- I'M SORRY,
BUT WHO ARE YOU AGAIN?
- YOU WERE ALWAYS WITH TSUDA
DURING PREFECTURAL COMPETITIONS,
WEREN'T YOU?
YOU GUYS SEEMED
TO BE REALLY CLOSE.
I ALWAYS WONDERED
IF YOU WERE DATING.
- MAN, TELL ME THIS ISN'T
PAINFUL FOR YOU TO WATCH.
- IT DOESN'T MATTER TO ME.
NOT AT ALL.
- IF YOU DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
ELSE TO SAY THEN LEAVE ME ALONE.
- NO, I'M NOT DONE
WITH YOU QUITE YET.
I OVERHEARD YOU EARLIER.
I BELIEVE YOU SAID I WASN'T
ON THE SAME LEVEL AS TSUDA.
AND BETWEEN YOU AND ME,
IT REALLY PISSED ME OFF.
- WELL THEN, I GUESS
THAT I'M SORRY.
FORGET I SAID ANYTHING.
- WELL, THAT WASN'T
MUCH OF AN APOLOGY.
YOU CAN'T EXPECT ME
TO ACCEPT THAT.
- YOU SURE ARE PERSISTENT.
YOU'RE JUST ANGRY BECAUSE
IT'S THE TRUTH.
- WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY TO ME?
IT DOESN'T MATTER
IF TSUDA'S ALIVE OR DEAD.
I'M THE NUMBER ONE SPRINTER.
- IF TSUDA SENPAI WERE ALIVE,
HE COULD BEAT YOU.
- HA. YOU'RE BEGINNING
TO SOUND LIKE A BROKEN RECORD.
"AW, IF TSUDA WERE ALIVE,
IF TSUDA WERE ALIVE."
WELL, LISTEN UP.
I HATE TO BREAK IT TO YOU,
BUT YOUR PRECIOUS
TSUDA SENPAI IS DEAD.
SO, AS YOU CAN
CLEARLY SEE, MY DEAR,
THERE'S NO WAY IN HELL THAT
I'M ON A LOWER LEVEL THAN TSUDA.
GIVE ME A BREAK.
- HEY, THAT GIRL'S
TALKING SMACK TO ARIMA.
- WHAT? WHAT THE HELL
IS SHE TALKING ABOUT?
- YOU NEED TO WATCH
YOUR MOUTH, LITTLE GIRL.
- APOLOGIZE IN FRONT
OF EVERYONE, NOW.
( chuckles ) MAYBE THEN,
WE'LL FORGIVE YOU.
- LET'S GO. IF WE STEP IN NOW,
WE'LL BE IN A LOT OF TROUBLE.
- SURE.
THERE'S NO REASON FOR ME
TO INTERVENE.
NONE AT ALL.
- HEY, HOLD UP.
- YA... YAMATO?
- WHAT'S THIS?
ARE YOU HERE TO APOLOGIZE
ON YOUR LITTLE GIRLFRIEND'S
BEHALF, MR. SPIKY HAIR?
- YOU DON'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO APOLOGIZE FOR, ASAHINA.
- WHAT WAS THAT?
PLEASE DON'T TELL ME
YOU AGREE WITH HER.
- IT DOESN'T MATTER TO ME
IF YOU'RE BETTER THAN KAZUKI.
BECAUSE I CAN RUN FASTER
THAN THE TWO OF YOU COMBINED.
- ( gasps )
- HUH?
- LOOK AT THIS STUPID PUNK.
CLEARLY, YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT YOU'RE SAYING.
DO YOU EVEN KNOW
WHO YOU'RE TALKING TO?
- YOU'RE WRONG.
I DO KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING.
AND THERE'S NO WAY I'M GOING
TO LOSE TO YOU TODAY.
- MAN, THIS GUY
MUST BE TOTALLY INSANE.
- YEAH, HE'S KIDDING
HIMSELF IF HE THINKS
HE CAN ACTUALLY BEAT ARIMA.
- YAMATO! ARE YOU CRAZY?
- THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
( sighs ) I'VE HAD ENOUGH.
- HEY, HOLD ON. WE'RE NOT DONE.
- SO, AM I TO UNDERSTAND
WE'LL BE COMPETING LATER
IN THE HUNDRED-METER
DASH? YOU'LL GET YOUR CHANCE
TO PROVE IF YOU'RE
FASTER THAN ME OR NOT.
( chuckles )
WHAT AN ASS.
- WHAT IN THE WORLD
WERE YOU THINKING, YAMATO?
WHY DID YOU SAY THOSE THINGS?
- BECAUSE I WAS PISSED OFF.
HE'S GOT SUCH A COCKY ATTITUDE.
- YOU DID ALL THAT
BECAUSE YOU WERE UPSET?
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU GONNA SAY
IF YOU LOSE TO THAT JERK LATER?
OR DID YOU NOT THINK
THAT FAR AHEAD?
- IF I LOSE THEN I SUPPOSE
I'LL OWE THE GUY AN APOLOGY,
WON'T I?
- WHY DO YOU ALWAYS
HAVE TO BE SO IMPETUOUS?
YOU SHOULD REALLY TRY
TO THINK BEFORE YOU SPEAK.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME, ASAHINA.
ALL I HAVE TO DO
IS WIN THE RACE.
I'M SURE I'LL BE
FINE. I JUST NEED TO BORROW
A UNIFORM AND SOME
SPIKES FROM SOMEONE FIRST.
- I'M NOT FINISHED!
I JUST DON'T GET HIM.
ALL THIS AFTER HE SAID
HE WAS QUITTING THE TEAM.
- ( grunts )
- THANKS FOR HELPING ME OUT,
HONOKA. I KNOW YOU MUST BE BUSY.
- OH, NO PROBLEM.
IT IS MY JOB AFTER ALL.
I'M JUST GLAD
YOU DECIDED TO COME.
I WAS WORRIED WHEN
YOU DIDN'T SHOW UP
TO PRACTICE FOR THREE DAYS.
- ( chuckles ) SORRY, SORRY.
I HAD A LOT OF STUFF GOING ON.
- THAT'S OKAY.
(thinking) I WAS SCARED
TO GO GET YOU.
BECAUSE I KNEW IF I WAS
TOO PERSISTENT,
YOU'D RESENT ME FOR IT.
- SO YOU CAME AFTER ALL.
- GEEZ, AKITSUKI, YOU SURE
HAVE A LOT OF NERVE.
- WHAT?
- I HEARD YOU PICKED A FIGHT
WITH TOHTO UNIVERSITY'S
ARIMA EMERSON EARLIER.
- BUT WHY WOULD YOU DO THAT?
- HE WAS PISSING ME OFF,
SO I HAD TO SAY SOMETHING.
- LIAR. YOU'RE NOT
THE TYPE TO FIGHT
OVER SOMETHING
THAT INSIGNIFICANT.
- BESIDES, I KNOW TONS OF GUYS
WHO ARE JUST LIKE ARIMA.
THEY'RE ALL BARK AND NO BITE.
BEATING HIM, NO PROBLEM.
- HMM.
- WHAT?
- I'M JUST WONDERING,
DID YOU PICK A FIGHT
BEFORE YOU FOUND OUT
ANYTHING ABOUT YOUR OPPONENT?
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
- ARIMA EMERSON
FROM TOHTO UNIVERSITY.
HIS BEST TIME FOR
THE HUNDRED METERS
IS TEN POINT FOUR SIX SECONDS.
HE'S CONSIDERED TO BE
THE NUMBER ONE
HIGH SCHOOL SPRINTER THIS YEAR.
- AND HE'S COMPETING
IN THIS TOURNAMENT?
- EXACTLY. THAT'S WHY
ALL THE REPORTERS
AND TV NETWORKS SHOWED UP.
NOW DO YOU WISH
YOU HADN'T PICKED A FIGHT?
- I DIDN'T KNOW HE COULD RUN
THAT FAST.
- ARE YOU WORRIED ABOUT YAMATO?
YOU'LL CATCH COLD IF YOU
DON'T PUT YOUR SWEATPANTS ON.
- I DIDN'T KNOW YOU
WERE HERE TODAY, HATTORI.
- YEAH.
IT SEEMS YAMATO IS GONNA
HAVE A SHOWDOWN WITH SOME GUY,
SO, I THOUGHT I'D STICK AROUND
TO WATCH.
- HE DOESN'T HAVE A CHANCE
AT WINNING.
THE GUY HE'S
GOING UP AGAINST
IS THE NUMBER ONE HIGH
SCHOOL SPRINTER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE PICKED
THAT RIDICULOUS FIGHT.
- YOU'RE RIGHT. YAMATO DOES
TEND TOWARDS THE RIDICULOUS.
ALWAYS ACTING BEFORE HE THINKS,
AND GETTING INTO TROUBLE.
AND NOW HE'S MANAGED
TO PISS OFF JAPAN'S
NUMBER ONE SPRINTER,
AND BECOME THE FOCUS
OF ALL HIS ANGER.
I'D HATE TO BE YAMATO RIGHT NOW.
- THIS IS THE LAST CALL FOR
THE HUNDRED-METER DASH.
ALL PARTICIPANTS MUST NOW
REPORT TO THE STARTING LINE.
- WE SHOULD GO.
THE RACE IS ABOUT TO START.
- BUT I...
- COME ON, IT'LL BE FINE.
MAYBE HE'LL EVEN MANAGE
TO PULL OFF AN UPSET AND
SURPRISE EVERYONE.
- IMPOSSIBLE.
- Man: NUMBER THIRTY-SIX,
YAMATO AKITSUKI.
OH, RIGHT HERE.
- HERE'S YOUR CHANCE, SPIKE,
DON'T BLOW IT.
AND WHEN YOU LOSE TO ME,
YOU'D BETTER KNEEL
AND APOLOGIZE.
- Crowd: YOU CAN DO IT, ARIMA.
WE BELIEVE IN YOU.
- YOU SO GOT THIS, DUDE!
- YEAH, YOU CAN BEAT
COMMANDER HAIRSPRAY!
- LOOK AT THE SIZE
OF THIS AUDIENCE.
- Yasunobu: HEY.
I BROUGHT SUZUKA TO WATCH,
SO DON'T EMBARRASS YOURSELF.
- ASAHINA?
- Referee: JUST ABOUT
READY TO BEGIN.
FIRST HEAT.
MAKE YOUR WAY
TO THE STARTING BLOCKS.
- I BET ARIMA WILL TAKE IT EASY
IN THESE PRELIMINARY ROUNDS
SO HE CAN SAVE ALL HIS
ENERGY FOR THE FINALS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- PROBABLY. HE DOESN'T HAVE ANY
COMPETITION IN THIS RACE ANYWAY.
- YEAH, THIS WILL BE MORE LIKE
A WARM UP FOR HIM THAN ANYTHING.
- LOOK AT THE OTHER SPRINTERS.
NO ONE SEEM TO BE PAYING
ANY ATTENTION TO YAMATO.
BUT I GUESS THAT'S NORMAL.
HE'S A COMPLETE UNKNOWN HERE.
- Soichi: AKITSUKI!
EVEN IF YOU FINISH SECOND,
YOU CAN STILL MAKE THE FINALS
DEPENDING ON YOUR TIME.
SO GIVE IT ALL YOU GOT.
- SECOND?
- NOW EVERYBODY
GET ON YOUR MARK.
- HERE GOES.
I'M FACING OFF AGAINST
THE TOP HIGH SCHOOL SPRINTER
IN MY FIRST PRELIMINARY RACE.
- YOU OWN THIS, ARIMA!
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT
THOSE OTHER GUYS!
THEY'RE NOTHING! COME ON, ARIMA,
YOU CAN DO IT! YOU CAN BEAT HIM!
- GO FOR IT! YEAH! ARIMA!
- OBVIOUSLY NOBODY
EXPECTS ME TO WIN.
- Yasunobu:
STAY FOCUSED, YAMATO.
- ASAHINA.
- DON'T LOOK AT ME LIKE THAT.
- Arima: A ROCKET STARTER?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA WIN EVEN IF
YOU DO COP A DEAD GUY'S STYLE.
- I MAY NOT HAVE WHAT IT TAKES
TO BEAT HIM NOW.
- GET SET.
- BUT I CAN'T FORGIVE SOMEONE...
...WHO MAKES ASAHINA CRY.
- ( sighs ) EVEN WITH
THE ROCKET START,
HE DOESN'T STAND A
CHANCE AGAINST ARIMA.
- GEEZ, THEY JUST STARTED
AND ARIMA'S ALL READY
OUT TO A HUGE LEAD.
- HMM, LOOKS LIKE
I'LL EASILY WIN,
EVEN IF I SLOW MY
PACE DOWN A BIT.
- DAMN IT. I CAN'T
CATCH UP TO HIM.
HE'S RIGHT THERE.
I JUST GOTTA PUSH HARDER.
I CAN'T LOSE TO THIS JERK.
- AKITSUKI ISN'T ON THE SAME
LEVEL AS ARIMA QUITE YET.
- YOU KNOW, I REALLY
THOUGHT HE'D FIND A WAY
TO PULL A WIN
OUT OF HIS ASS.
- LOOK AT THAT LOSER!
HE'S NOT EVEN IN THE
SAME LEAGUE AS ARIMA.
HE LOOKS SO DESPERATE.
- HE DOESN'T HAVE
A CHANCE IN HELL.
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
YOU IDIOT? RUN!
- ( all gasps )
- LOOK AT THAT,
THEY'RE NECK AND NECK.
- MAYBE HE WON'T LET ME DOWN.
- STOP SCREWING AROUND, ARIMA.
- TEACH HIM A LESSON.
- I'M NOT TOYING WITH HIM.
THIS GUY REALLY IS FAST.
- ASAHINA GAVE HIM THE BOOST HE
NEEDED TO CATCH UP WITH ARIMA.
- I DON'T BELIEVE THIS GUY.
- YOU CAN DO IT, AKITSUKI.
- YOU'VE ALMOST GOT HIM.
- Boy: ARIMA'S REGAINING
HIS LEAD.
- I CAN'T LOSE. NOT TO THIS GUY.
OF ALL PEOPLE,
I CAN'T LOSE TO HIM.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
I FEEL LIKE MY LEGS
ARE BUCKLING.
I CAN'T RUN ANY FURTHER.
- ALL RIGHT, FIRST PLACE.
- DUDE, YOU REALLY
SCARED US THERE.
- ( all cheering )
- ( panting )
- HIS PACE WAS TOO QUICK.
HE PUSHED HIMSELF TOO HARD
CHASING ARIMA.
HE DOESN'T HAVE
ENOUGH EXPERIENCE
AND HE SKIPPED PRACTICE
FOR THREE DAYS.
IT ALL ADDED UP, AND THAT'S WHY
HE COULDN'T WIN TODAY.
- NOW, HE KNOWS
NOT TO MESS WITH ARIMA.
MAYBE IN THE FUTURE,
HE'LL SHUT HIS BIG MOUTH.
- I KNOW, I KNOW.
YOU'RE WAITING
FOR YOUR APOLOGY.
- WAIT, YAMATO...
- I DON'T CARE ABOUT THAT.
- HUH?
YOU'RE ANNOYING ME.
TUCK YOUR TAIL BETWEEN YOUR
LEGS AND GET OUTTA HERE.
- BUT...
- WHAT, DID YOU NOT
UNDERSTAND ME?
I TOLD YOU TO GET OUT
OF MY SIGHT.
- NUMBER ONE SPRINTER, MY ASS!
THIS ISN'T THE LAST
YOU'LL BE SEEING OF ME, JERK.
I'LL BE BACK. YOU'LL SEE!
- HE RAN AWAY?
- THAT'S THE SIGN OF A TRUE
CHAMPION. ( laughs )
- DAMMIT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE MADE ME RUN
SUCH A HARD RACE IN THE PRELIMS.
- MY LEGS HURT.
I'M SUCH AN IDIOT.
WHY'D I HAVE TO SCREAM
AT HIM AND THEN RUN AWAY?
I MUST HAVE LOOKED SO PATHETIC.
AND I BET THAT ASAHINA
IS DISAPPOINTED IN ME, TOO.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- ( gasps ) ASAHINA.
I, UM... I'M OKAY.
- LET ME SEE YOUR LEGS.
- WHAT? MY LEGS?
WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
WHY IS SHE TAKING CARE
OF ME NOW?
( groans )
- YOU'LL BE FINE.
- DOES THIS MEAN THAT SHE
ISN'T ANGRY WITH ME ANYMORE?
SHE WAS CHEERING FOR ME
DURING THE RACE, BUT THEN...
I MADE SUCH A FOOL OF MYSELF
IN FRONT OF EVERYBODY.
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS FOR ME?
- JUST STAY STILL.
- SURE.
- ( Cicadas chirping )
- LISTEN. THE CICADAS ARE OUT.
EVEN THOUGH
IT'S ONLY JUNE. WEIRD.
I'M SUCH AN IDIOT, AREN'T I?
I RAN MY BIG MOUTH AT ARIMA,
THEN LOST THE RACE.
YOU MUST BE DISAPPOINTED IN ME.
- IT'S BEEN MUCH
HOTTER THAN USUAL.
MAYBE THE CICADAS CAME OUT EARLY
THINKING IT WAS SUMMER ALREADY.
JUST A THOUGHT.
- OH, YEAH. YOU'RE PROBABLY
RIGHT. ( chuckles )
- OKAY, ALL DONE.
- OH, THANKS, ASAHINA.
- YOU SKIPPED PRACTICE
FOR THREE DAYS.
- HUH?
- THE RACE. THAT'S WHY YOU LOST.
EVEN ATHLETES THAT
PRACTICE EVERY DAY,
SOMETIMES LOSE THEIR BALANCE,
JUST BEFORE THE FINISH LINE.
- YEAH.
- SO, YOU BETTER MAKE SURE
YOU SHOW UP TO PRACTICE
TOMORROW. YOU GOT IT?
- WHAT DOES THIS MEAN?
DOES SHE WANT ME
ON THE TEAM STILL?
WELL, REGARDLESS, I WAS GOING
TO SHOW UP TOMORROW, ANYWAY.
IT SURE IS HOT.
SUMMER'S ALMOST HERE.
- ( theme song playing )
- ♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ABOVE ♪
♪ NOW IS ALL WE HAVE ♪
♪ WITH A LITTLE FEELING
AND A LOT OF LOVE ♪
♪ WE TURN UP THE HEAT AND RUN ♪
♪ HERE WE GO ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- ♪ ALL MY LIFE HERE ON THE
GROUND ABOUT TO RUN AND NOW ♪
♪ I FIND I MUST
ASK MYSELF WHY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE SOMETHING IS STIRRING ♪
♪ I FEEL IT WHISPERING IN ME ♪
♪ SOMEDAYS I WAKE UP ♪
♪ BUT MY HEART'S
STILL SLEEPING ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME
TO RUN AND TRY ♪
♪ AND I KNOW IT'S TIME TO FLY ♪
♪ AND LIKE THE WIND
WE WILL RUN ♪
♪ THROUGH THESE SKIES ON HIGH ♪
♪ WITH OUR GOAL IN SIGHT ♪
♪ WE WILL RUN
WITH ALL OUR MIGHT ♪
♪ TOMORROW AND TODAY
WILL NEVER EVER PASS US BY ♪
♪ WE WILL NOT STOP NOW ♪
♪ KEEP YOUR HEART ALIVE
AND YOUR DREAM SURVIVES ♪
♪ AND YOU CROSS
THE FINISH LINE ♪
♪ LET IT GO! ♪
- ♪ YOU CAN RUN, YOU CAN STOP,
YOU CAN JUMP, YOU CAN CRAWL ♪
♪ YOU CAN LOSE, YOU CAN WIN ♪
♪ YOU CAN SING, YOU CAN SHOUT
TAKE A BREATH, LET IT OUT ♪
♪ LIVE IT UP EVERY DAY ♪
- Honoka: ASAHINA, I WANTED
TO TALK TO YOU.
YOU SEEM TO BE CLOSE
TO AKITSUKI.
- I WOULDN'T EXACTLY
CALL US CLOSE.
- OH, THEN IS IT OKAY?
- IS WHAT OKAY?
- IS IT OKAY IF I CONFESS
MY FEELINGS TO HIM?