Shit, it's dark in here.
I can't see a damn thing.
Where the hell is that bastard, anyway?
It's the middle of the day, and I still
have to feel my way around this hovel.
This had better be worth it.
Okay, if I remember correctly,
I'll find Dio over in that room.
Ugh! Disgusting.
This little lady must be one of Dio's leftovers.
Damn broads just throw themselves at the guy,
like having their blood drank is the latest bedroom craze.
The whole thing's nutty if you ask me,
though girls do tend to go for the bad boys.
But forget about that.
I've never seen so much gold in my life.
How'd he get all this?
Seems like this guy can have and do just about anything.
Hmm.
Hol Horse...
What is it?
It's master Dio.
Son of a bitch.
What is this?
Just lookin' at him is enough
to send chills down my spine.
Keep it together, Hol Horse.
Don't let him spook you.
He's nothin' to lose your cool over.
Yeah, he's not even that much stronger than you.
I'll ask you again.
Did you want something, Hol Horse?
Uh, well, yes, actually.
There's somethin' I thought you oughta know.
I received Intel that two of the nine great gods,
Mariah and Alessi, have been put out of commission.
And your point is?
Well, there's more.
We've got trouble comin'.
Turns out Joestar and his gang
will arrive in Cairo tomorrow,
and only three of the nine gods are left.
It seems you've misunderstood my question.
I want to know what you're going to do, Hol Horse.
Eh?!
You seem to have been caught rather off guard.
I simply wish to know when
you're going kill them, Hol Horse.
While it's true you've pledged your allegiance to me,
you have yet to adequately prove yourself in battle.
In this day and age, any
simpleton can deliver information.
Twice you've failed me, and here you are crawling back.
You couldn't know this, but my body once
belonged to a man by the name of Jonathan Joestar.
Jonathan was the grandfather of Joseph Joestar.
Look closely.
Notice how the left finger heals
at a slower rate than the right?
The left side of this body is weak,
which proves that it doesn't completely belong to me yet
and that I am not yet immortal.
I am ill-equipped to fight a
battle with Joestar and his friends.
Now then, if there is nothing else,
run along, and destroy my enemies on my behalf.
Failure will most assuredly
result in your untimely demise.
You're barkin' up the wrong tree, hoss.
As if threats are gonna make me
roll over and do whatever you want.
On your behalf, my ass.
I'm no fool. I'm smart enough to
throw in with whoever's strongest.
Everything I've said has been lip service.
I'd never swear my loyalty to you at the cost of my soul.
Rat bastard, you're not so tough, are you?
You're wide open.
Guess having another person's body
attached to your head has made you go soft.
This is perfect.
I don't have to fight Joseph and the other three,
not when I've got Dio in my crosshairs.
It'd be a hell of a lot easier to blow
his head to smithereens right here and now.
If I do, his treasure's mine for the takin'.
This'll be a piece of cake.
He doesn't know Emperor's aimed point-blank at his skull.
I could finish him off, and he'll be none the wiser.
Just one pull of the trigger,
and this nightmare will be over.
After all, Emperor was made for close-combat carnage.
I can do this. I can do this.
Is there a problem? You seem to be hesitating.
Eat lead, shit-bag!
I'm about to splatter your
brains all over the floor, Mr. Dio!
Are you positive you want to go through with shooting me?
Huh?
He's gone!
Fascinating.
As you prepared to fire, your breathing was relaxed.
You didn't even perspire.
You were composed.
Very impressive, Hol Horse.
This doesn't make a lick of sense.
I didn't even see him move.
There's no way in hell he could have creeped up behind
me without breaking a single one of those spider webs.
Fast or not, he shouldn't have been able to
sneak up to my rear without me noticing something.
Was that the power of Dio's stand,
the power of The World?
Ill-equipped? Yeah, right.
I-I finally understand, master Dio.
I've got no choice but to
pledge my eternal loyalty to you.
Y-you've got me beat.
Ladies and gentlemen, we sincerely hope
you've enjoyed today's flight from Aswan.
We'll be arriving on schedule at
Cairo international airport shortly.
Whoops! Snooze, you loose, buddy!
I hate to break it to you, cowboy,
but it looks like this is our cab now.
No hard feelings?
Huh? Don't tell me you're gonna
start cryin' like a baby! Hah!
Shit! What the hell?!
Giza Pronto, the mena house hotel.
I'm gonna open up this suitcase and let you out.
Unless you want some grade-a
pain, I suggest you keep calm.
We clear?
Huh? Did you, uh, say something just now, sir?
If I did, it sure the hell wasn't to
you. Now shut up, and drive the cab!
Ehh! Yes, sir.
Cut it out.
You know, if you weren't makin' such a damn racket,
I wouldn't have had to hogtie you and put
you on the plane like a piece of luggage!
Don't be a baby, Mondatta.
Your brother's got another month
in the hospital thanks to that bomb,
so you and I are partners.
Now make sure those big ears are
listening, 'cause here's what we're gonna do.
We're gonna use your book of
premonitions and my assassin gun
to stamp out Jotaro, Joseph, and the rest of those S.O.Bs!
Got that, Mondatta?!
I get that we haven't known each other long,
but from what I've gathered, you're afraid of
just about anyone that's not your brother, Zenyatta.
But don't you think this is the
perfect chance to avenge the guy?
You don't wanna be a yellow-bellied
coward forever, right? That's no good.
I'm out of options, too.
We've got no choice but to fight.
Time for us to get our revenge, Mondatta.
I'm gonna let you loose now, but you have to swear to me
you won't carry on with all that infernal hollering, okay?
See that, son?
I'm not so bad.
Now try and settle down, eh?
I don't need you gettin' sick on me,
'cause believe it or not, I'm
on your side in this whole mess.
So don't you worry.
Just relax for now.
Huh?
Sir, why do you have a puking kid?!
Shut up!
I see.
You got motion sickness from being on the plane.
Mondatta, I-let's be pals from here on.
How's that sound?
"I'm Mondatta.
"This is Hol Horse.
"He's mean, and I don't like him!
"While Mondatta was sleeping, Hol Horse
tied him up and stuffed him in a trunk.
"Mondatta was taken from his brother, Zenyatta.
"He was sad.
"But even though Mondatta was scared out of his mind,
"he wanted to avenge his brother,
"so he decided to work up his courage
and become partners with Hol Horse."
Hmm?
Oh, come on!
You won't even get near me?
Well, I guess you're tryin', which
is all I can ask for at this point.
And by the way, I gotta know.
Does your stand really predict the
future, or is that just some cockamamie rumor?
If that was all just a tall tale,
then I brought you here for nothin'.
I mean, even with it, your
brother got blown to high heaven.
Which is it, kid?! Are you a fraud?!
Hmm?
How'd a new comic appear on a
blank page from out of nowhere?
"While Mondatta and Hol Horse" were
walking through the outskirts of Cairo,
"they met a lady who was as pretty as the day was long.
Then Hol Horse jump-kicked the lady in the neck!"
Hmm?
"The pretty lady "was so overjoyed about the kick
that, "out of the blue, she gave Hol Horse her jewels.
Yahoo! We're rich!"
What the hell is this crap?!
You must think I was born last night!
You call this a prediction, Mondatta?!
There's just no way!
This crap has to be made up or somethin'.
I'm telling the truth.
My stand, Thoth, you just have to trust in its prophecies.
Th-th-they're 100...
They're 100% right every time.
They're right 100%?
You tryin' to pull the wool over my eyes?!
There's no way some lady's gonna give me
her jewels after jump-kickin' her in the neck.
You'd have to be off your
rocker to do somethin' like that.
Hmm?
Listen, Mondatta.
I am proud to say that I'm a
gentleman and a proper gentleman at that.
'Cause of that, I got girls all over the world.
I might tell a white lie now and
again, but I'd never haul off and hit one.
I respect all the ladies, the beauties,
the plain ones, and even the ugly ones.
There's no way your prediction will ever come to pass.
Come hell or high water, I swear I will never hit a woman.
She could pay me every dime, nickel, and quarter
she had. I still wouldn't put my hands on her.
It's 100% true, yes.
Hmph.
See there?
Your fancy prediction was wrong.
Huh?
Who the hell are you?!
What in the...
Th-there was a scorpion in your shawl!
This thing's sting is a death sentence.
What?!
You spotted that wretched creature before
it had a chance to crawl into my clothes.
If you hadn't killed it,
she would have been stung for sure.
You saved my life.
Oh, please, let me repay you.
Would my necklace be a sufficient reward?
It's yours.
Boy, this is my lucky day.
Mondatta and I are practically invincible.
We'll be the unstoppable duo!
I don't think I'm gonna be able to help you folks.
It's been my job to repair rooftops
in Cairo for around 40 years now,
and I can't say that I've ever seen a place like this.
From the looks of the building's design,
the thing was built over a hundred years ago,
give or take.
If I had to take a guess, based on the picture,
I'd say you'd find it somewhere south of here.
The buildings in Cairo get older
and older the farther south you travel.
Huh?
I'm sorry I don't have more to go on, Sonny.
No, don't worry about it.
Sorry to bother.
All right, understood. Thanks for the update.
I decided to make a call to Japan,
and my daughter's condition is much worse.
She's lost virtually all of her strength.
At best, she has three or four days left.
I can almost feel it.
It's like Dio's right on top of us.
I'd bet anything that he's hiding somewhere close by,
but where could he be, and how do we find him?
We should get moving.
We'll talk to everyone here until we find him.
Hmm. We've come this far.
We have to keep going.
Been a long time comin',
but it's time for our grand reunion.
I'm getting sick of those faces.
I never thought they'd get so
close to master Dio's mansion,
but they're on a collision course for his backyard.
And by the way, listen, Mondatta!
We need to chat about your latest prediction.
You sure it's 100% foolproof?
It's more than a little wacky.
They're not dumb enough to fall for this.
B-but my premonitions... ow!
"My premonitions are always 100% accurate."
Is that what you were gonna say?
Well, they are, yes.
Come on!
You really expect me to buy this load of baloney?
I think you've lost your touch, boy.
"'We found them!' shouted Hol Horse.
"'Joseph, Jotaro, Polnareff, and Avdol.
"Darn it, ' Hol Horse fumed.
"'They're a hop, skip, and a
jump "'away from master Dio's manor.
Those nosy buffoons'll each
get a bullet between the eyes.'"
"Hol Horse's mind was full of violent thoughts.
"'You're gonna pay for my brother!'
"Mondatta was beside himself with anger.
"But despite the pair wanting immediate payback,
Hol Horse couldn't use his
gun, the Emperor, in the market."
"'Now, Hol Horse, ' Mondatta instructed,
"'stick your fingers all the way up Polnareff's nose,
"'and then we'll win!
"'They're out cold from losing all that blood.
"'lucky you, Hol Horse.
This is your chance to finish them off for good.'"
Like hell I'm gonna buy that!
This is your big premonition?
Sticking my calloused fingers up
Polnareff's booger-infested nose?
The hell do you take me for? Well, speak, Mondatta!
The part about killing 'em sounds
good to me, but the rest of it...
You'd better not be planning anything funny, boy.
I mean, come on!
Even if I was supposed to stick
my fingers up Polnareff's nose,
I'd have to somehow get close enough to him to do it.
Instead of all that skullduggery,
I think we should go with the direct
approach and put a bullet in him with Emperor!
What do you say?
Y-you're not gonna be able to fire a bullet, yes.
E-even though you tried firing your stand,
fate wouldn't let you, yes.
You have to trust me, yes.
I know from personal experience,
I-If you try to go against the
comic, you'll suffer the consequences.
It's fate, I tell you. It's
100% up to the whims of fate, yes.
Hang on!
Your brother followed the comic and nearly died.
M-my brother was trying to save himself,
but he foolishly disguised himself
as Jotaro without thinking, yes.
If he had trusted what he read and not disguised himself,
then the real Jotaro would have been blown up, yes.
The premonition itself was correct, yes.
Then what now?
Hmm?
Wait! Where did Polnareff go?
Hey, kid, Polnareff left the herd.
Find out where he went.
Shit! It can't be.
Don't you move...
Unless you'd like to be lanced.
But... how the hell did you...
Imbecile! What exactly did you
think you were trying to pull just now?
If you know what's good for you,
keep your hands where I can see them.
I thought I noticed someone stalking
us like a desperate, starving hyena,
and wouldn't you know, I was lucky enough
to stumble across our old friend, Hol Horse.
It looks you're still trying to kill us,
which means you haven't learned your lesson yet.
Say, thanks for all the fun back in India.
You're very lucky Avdol survived our run-in,
'cause if he hadn't,
you, my friend, would already be dead.
You here alone, Hol Horse?
No way. A coward like you wouldn't come by himself.
I'm sure he's hiding out nearby, right?
Well, where's your partner?
Crap!
On the upside, though, he hasn't noticed Mondatta yet.
I still have a chance.
Shit!
He's gonna see the book and his fingers.
On your own, you're not much of a threat, Hol Horse,
but I'm well aware that you have a
special talent for picking allies.
If you've found someone to work with like
before, that could make you a dangerous obstacle.
Tell me, where did your partner go?
Out with it. Where is the other stand user?
Your fingers.
Mondatta, hide your fingers.
If he gets wise to where you are, it's all over.
You have to believe.
The reason you're in this situation
is because you tried using your gun.
Trust me. Believe in fate.
If you believe in the power of
fate, our victory is guaranteed, yes.
Hmm?
Huh?
I saw a hand go under the box,
which means my hunch was right.
What's the word, Polnareff?
Did you find the guy that was following us?
Oh, no, it's Avdol, and he's headed straight for us.
Believe, yes.
Put your faith in the book, and stick
your fingers up Polnareff's nose, yes!
Are you serious?
Damn it.
Hmm?
Hmm...
I've got no choice.
Fine. I'll do it!
You under the crate, show yourself!
Now, while he's looking the other way!
I know you're hiding under there!
What the hell?!
Hell, yeah!
"'Whoo-hoo! Everyone bled so much,
"'they all passed out! Lucky you, Hol Horse!
Now's your chance to finish them off!'"
So when is this so-called chance supposed to get here,
and what do I do 'til then?
Excuse me, Hol Horse.
Uh, what the hell are you doing?
You're not the only one who wants
to know the answer to that question.
I haven't the foggiest idea where to go from here.
What am I supposed to do?
Hey, what's the matter, Polnareff?
He's not answering back.
Something's off.
Shit! What now?!
They're on me like white on rice!
Damn it!
How the hell do I make the rest
of this stupid prediction come true?
This is crazy.
What am I supposed to do?!