What are you doing, Kakyoin?
I understand now.
I know now how to uncover the secret of Dio's stand.
What?
For Noriaki Kakyoin, Hierophant Green served
as a poignant reminder of a time long past.
It's Noriaki.
He doesn't attempt to socialize with the other children.
It's not that he's disliked, per se.
He just seems a bit too reserved.
As his teacher, I'm very concerned.
I'm ashamed to say it, but...
I'm afraid I don't understand it either.
I always had the same thoughts.
Life is full of interactions
where we meet all sorts of people,
but how often do those meetings involve deeper thinking?
How often do we make genuine human connections?
All of my classmates have address
books filled with their friends' names.
Each of them must have a book of 50, no, 100 names.
Mom has dad, and dad has mom.
But I have no one.
I'm sure rock stars and TV celebrities
have tens of thousands of friends.
But I have no one.
I'll never have any friends.
No one will ever understand me.
I'm the only one who can see Hierophant Green.
How am I supposed to truly relate to
someone if they can't see the real me?
It's impossible.
That's how I used to think about life
until I met Mr. Joestar, Jotaro, Polnareff, and Avdol.
Whenever I think about Avdol and Iggy,
it makes the hairs on the back of my neck stand on end.
I'm sure it's because they were
the first to treat me like a friend.
My friends and I were on a journey to defeat Dio,
and while it may have been short-lived,
they've understood me better than anyone.
Looking at Hierophant Green
was a revelation for Kakyoin.
I'll make Hierophant Green invisible
to everyone, like it used to be.
I'll use its invisibility to my advantage
and reveal Dio's secret before finishing him off for good!
Hey, Jotaro!
The truck is completely totaled.
Up there!
I can sense the old man and
Dio racing across the rooftops.
I've only dealt with Kakyoin and Joseph so far.
Interesting. They're attempting to strike from both sides,
which means Jotaro and Polnareff must be
waiting in the wings to attack me from behind.
How futile.
This is...
It's Kakyoin's Hierophant Green!
He turned it into a web?
Hmm?
So you've laid a...
That's right.
Anything that touches this web is instantly fired upon,
and you're surrounded for 20 meters on all sides.
You're done, Dio! I've snared you and
your stand, and I can sense your every move.
Now die!
20-meter-radius emerald splash!
You're a fool, Kakyoin.
With my stand, I have the ability to rule the world!
What can you do in the face of such overwhelming power?
All right, here it comes.
Behold, The World!
Huh? What?
Kakyoin!
He went flying through the air like a rag doll.
But how?!
Kakyoin!
I don't understand.
What just happened?
Did he really hit me?
I can't even move a single finger.
I can't speak, either.
It must have been a fatal blow.
It's 5:15,
which means that it's midnight back in Japan.
I wonder what mom and dad are doing right now.
Knowing them, I'm sure they're sound asleep.
I'm sorry for worrying you.
Despite his brief moment of reflection,
Noriaki Kakyoin's last thoughts were not of his parents.
His mind shifted and homed in on the
question weighing heaviest on his mind.
He had to find an answer before nothingness took hold.
I should be able to instantly sense any
movement within Hierophant Green's web,
but somehow Dio managed to destroy
the entire web in the blink of an eye,
and it wasn't one strand at a time.
It was instantaneous,
not even a split-second difference.
How did he shatter a 20-meter-radius area all at once?
How?
There wasn't even a slight delay.
What's his secret?
Damn it.
Kakyoin!
Shit. I've had enough of this!
Hermit purpl... eh?
Eh?
You're next on the chopping block, Joseph.
In order for Jonathan's body to become mine completely,
I must drink the blood of a Joestar, and I
think now's as good a time as any to partake.
Dio!
How did he destroy them all
without the slightest delay in time?
Time.
The time!
That's it.
Something as outlandish as that doesn't seem possible,
but there's no other explanation.
I have to find a way to tell the others.
They need to know the truth
behind such a terrifying ability.
If I can't tell Mr. Joestar what I've learned...
The friends I've come to love are going to die.
You're gonna pay for what you've done.
Just you wait!
I'm taking that body back in the name of granny Erina.
Erina? Ah, you mean that backwater shrew?
Nonsense.
I'm going to drink your blood, then eliminate you vermin.
Now, Joseph Joestar, die!
Huh?
Hmm?
That was my final emerald splash.
Make it count.
But why? That attack was utterly pointless.
Well, I suppose you're now just a dying
hero longing to make his Mark on the world. Heh.
As if! Kakyoin wouldn't waste the time
he has left with some meaningless attack.
Why'd he go after the clock?
Was it some kind of sign?
Was he trying to tell me something?
It's a message.
I don't have the strength to give you another.
Mr. Joestar...
You have to decipher it.
You have to let the others know.
Kakyoin.
Noriaki Kakyoin has died.
Hermit purple!
Now take this!
Hamon of the sun!
You old fool!
Out of all the stands I've seen, yours is the weakest!
No, you don't!
Kakyoin, why did you destroy the clock earlier?
Wait. You were trying to send me a message, weren't you?
But how does it relate to the clock tower?
That was Mr. Joestar!
And Dio's closing in.
Where the hell is Kakyoin?!
Could that be it, Kakyoin?
Did you figure out the secret of his
stand's ability in your dying moments?
You destroyed the clock with emerald splash...
But you aimed for the hands...
Which stopped the clock.
Huh?!
No way! That's impossible!
Dio's stand, The World, has the power to...
stop time whenever Dio commands it to!
Now die!
20-meter-radius emerald splash!
Behold, The World!
Now witness the power of the world.
That's right. I've caused time to stop for you,
which means you won't see or feel any of this.
Now die, Kakyoin!
You don't even realize you're about to die.
In a way, you're lucky.
You won't know what happened here,
only that you're dying.
I understand now, Kakyoin.
That's what you were trying to tell me in your message.
I'm not gonna waste this chance!
Freezing time is bad enough,
but Dio being able to move
around, too, is a deadly combo.
Unbelievable.
We might not have what it takes to beat it!
Just calm down. Calm down, and think.
I don't know the meaning of the word "panic."
There has to be a way to beat him,
and if anyone can find it, it's me.
He's gone.
Eh?
Say, what's the matter?
Aren't you gonna hit me, Dio?
Or don't you care about drinking my blood anymore?
You're running hamon through your body
to protect yourself, quite the strategy.
You've wrapped your body with Hermit Purple,
but you've infused it with hamon,
like a cloak of high-voltage wires.
Very clever.
A geriatric genius.
Well, it seems I'm not the only clever one.
It's just like you said.
I've been using this little trick to protect myself.
But thanks to Kakyoin's message,
I've learned something about your stand.
Dio, you can bring time to a standstill,
but there's a limit to the amount
of time you can use that power,
only three to four seconds, I'd say.
If you could do it for a longer period than that,
instead of chasing us around town all night, you
would have wiped us all out back at the mansion.
Tracking us down tells me everything that I need to know.
So you've finally figured it out.
That's an impressive accomplishment.
Ha! Congratulations.
You should congratulate Kakyoin.
He gave his life to give us a fighting chance.
So what? Am I supposed to care?
It doesn't matter if you know my stand's ability.
What can your pathetic hamon do against my power?!
Hermit Purple and hamon!
Idiot! I can kill you with or
without going through your hamon.
Hmm?
Eh?
Hey, what's with him?
I've heard of it raining men, but never old geezers!
Hey, what if he's Santa Claus?
The hell were you doin' on the roof?
Spying on the pretty girls below?
Old man.
It's Jotaro.
Stay back!
Mm?
You have to stay far away from me!
Jotaro. What good timing.
But he's staying outside of my stand's range,
so Joseph goes first.
Jotaro! Dio's stand, The World,
gives him the ability to control time!
Whatever you do, stay out of it's ran...
Once more, The World!
When I began using this power, I was only
able to freeze time for the blink of an eye.
That said, as my neck began the process of healing,
I found that I could stop time
for two seconds and even three.
Now I can stop time for five seconds.
Then again, time is stopped,
so from my perspective, it only feels like five seconds.
Soon, I'll be able to stop
time for a minute, then an hour,
and later, as long as I desire!
How amusing.
I'll have the ability to stop time to my heart's content!
Oh, I almost forgot.
He's covered himself with hamon for protection.
A hundred years ago, hamon was a concern.
Now, thanks to The World, it's
little more than an irritation.
Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda!
Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda!
Joseph, grandson of Jonathan, your demise is at hand!
One second left.
Zero.
Old man.
Run away.
G-get out of here, Jotaro.
Don't even try to fight.
Please keep your distance.
Stay far away from him.
He's invincible.
Come now. Don't worry.
At least he's joining Kakyoin.
Polnareff must be hiding around here somewhere,
though I guess it doesn't matter.
You're next, Jotaro.
Time to die.
Damn you.
Dio!
Oh, so you still want to fight?
It would appear pigheadedness runs in the family.
How ungrateful can you be?
You're blatantly ignoring your grandfather's wishes,
even after he gave his life to
tell you about the power of the world.
Surely his pathetic pleas
warranted a bit of consideration.
I have to move closer if I wanna
beat your sorry ass to a pulp.
Really?
Okay, then. By all means, come closer.
Ora!
You'll have to be faster.
My stand is more powerful than any other.
Even without the world's tremendous power and speed,
it would still outclass your pitiful Star Platinum.
Your stand has a lot in common with my Star Platinum.
We're not long-range fighters,
but we have incredible power and precision.
If I'm being honest, I've always had a desire to see how
much stronger the world is compared with Star Platinum,
but it seems pointless to compare them now.
Wait. Are you serious?
All you did was give me a love tap on the leg,
and you ripped my 20,000-yen pants.
For the life of me, I can't figure
out why you Joestars are so stubborn.
Fine. I shall accept your cheap provocation.
Let our comparison resume.
Ora! Ora!
Comparing our punching speed?
Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda!
Ora! Ora! Ora! Ora! Ora! Ora!...