Have your injuries improved any, Avdol?
They have. As relieved as I am,
I'm even more relieved knowing you're all right.
Yes, well, I'm fortunate there was
no significant damage to my cornea.
I'm expected to make a full recovery.
This takes me back to middle school.
During what should have been an ordinary game,
one of my classmates took a baseball to the eye.
He was good as new the next day,
and as it turned out, his eye
had only lost a bit of fluid.
Wait. Are you serious?
No!
I'll get these bandages off in no time,
and I'll catch up with you in a few days.
In 800 kilometers are Cairo and Dio.
Everyone, you must remain vigilant.
Now let's see.
What kind of language is this
hospital bill written in, anyway?
I guess it's supposed to be Arabic,
but, man, if this crap isn't confusing.
The zero is a five, the decimal
is a zero, and the seven is a six.
And what the heck is this
wormy-looking thingamajig supposed to be?
It's a four, so the amount we owe is...
46,350 Egyptian pounds?!
That's insane!
How adorable!
What kind of dog is he?
He's so funny-looking.
Look at that. Why in the world is he chewing gum?
He must be waiting for someone.
Such a good little doggie.
And here I thought Iggy was waiting for us outside.
Good grief.
Looks like he's a hit with the ladies.
Should we tell him doggies don't usually chew gum?
What a peculiar little puppy.
Hello there, ladies.
Hmm?
Here's a little bit of friendly advice for you girls.
Step away if you know what's good for you.
I know he comes across as a charming fur ball at first,
but deep in his soul, he harbors
an extreme hatred for people.
If you're not careful, when you least expect...
What the hell are you doing?!
Get off of me, you damn mutt!
Such a cutie!
Aww. You get along so well.
In your dreams! We don't get along at all!
Damn it, Iggy! Would you get the hell off of me?!
We'll catch you guys later.
See you, lovebirds.
Mr. Joestar, please help me!
Hey, hang on a minute, would you?!
What the hell?!
You nasty little mutt!
In ancient times, Egyptians were in the habit
of burying their dead on the west
bank of the Nile, where the sun sets.
That's the reason Egyptian cities
stand on the east side of the Nile.
On the West Side, however, you're likely to
find graves and mortuary temples scattered about.
But our enemies don't care about east or west.
They'll come from whatever direction is most advantageous.
Look, I know you didn't ask for my opinion,
but your cows are far too lethargic.
Although, they're strong. I'll give 'em that.
Hey, Chaka, move your ass, boy!
And would you stop dragging the rear already?!
What a disgrace.
Some man you are.
How are you my son?
Looks like your son and your cow have something in common.
Uh...
A sword?
What's something like this doing out here?
Hey, look! It's a sword!
Give me that!
Look at that. Must have been dropped.
I can't believe no one's come back to claim it.
Their loss is our gain, 'cause this
sword is probably worth a fortune.
Hey, what if the owner's still in the area?
Poor guy must be panicking right about now.
On the off chance it's some kind of fancy-schmancy
artifact, shouldn't we give it to the police?
You idiot, this sword could be
the end of all of our money troubles!
But I'm the one who found it.
It won't be worth a damn thing if it's blunt.
Pull it out so we can take a look.
Right!
What's wrong?
The damn thing won't budge.
Why the hell won't it come out?
That's weird.
Let me try it.
Take it.
You hold this end.
Right.
It's no use.
The blade hasn't moved a single centimeter.
Father, let me have a go.
Ah, shut up! If I can't free it,
what chance does an idiot like you have?!
Huh?!
M-my hand!
What happened to my hand?!
My hand, why is it spewing blood?!
How the hell did the sword cut me?!
We pulled on the damn thing,
but the blade wouldn't come out.
All I did was grab it by the hilt!
There's something strange about that sword.
Hey, uh, you think now's a good time for me to try?
You know what?! Fine!
Go ahead, and try it if you want!
It came out so easy.
I didn't put the slightest bit of effort into it.
What? I can hear it.
This makes no sense.
I can hear the blade ringing.
I'm by no means an expert when it
comes to swords or things of that nature,
but I don't think I've ever
encountered a blade this beautiful.
It's like a rare Japanese katana.
It glistens, like it's cloaked in ice-cold water.
We've been graced with an amazing discovery!
Hand it over, my boy!
A dolt like you has no business
wielding such a valuable treasure!
Oh, god!
Chaka, why?
Why would you do this to your own father?!
I don't know what happened!
You were standing behind me...
And before I knew it, the sword...
It's not my fault, I swear!
Why are you just standing there?!
We have to hurry and get him
to a doctor before it's too late!
This sword is evil!
It's almost as though the blade has a mind of its own!
Be calm.
Still your heart, Chaka.
Their deaths mean nothing, nothing whatsoever, Chaka.
Just... just who are you?
I can't see you, but I can hear your voice.
I am the stand of the god Anubis,
ruler of the underworld,
deity of embalming, and lord of the dead.
You have unsheathed me.
You are my flesh!
Thus you shall be my stand user.
You are a virtuoso.
So I shall make you master of the sword.
No one in the world is stronger than you.
You shall wield me, and you shall kill!
Father and that man deserved to die, so
they should be thrilled that I killed them.
I think I'll hack you to pieces while I'm on a roll.
Wait a minute, Chaka! You don't really wanna do this!
Please let me live, okay?! I don't wanna die!
How the hell did he do that?!
Somehow the cow's completely unharmed.
Slaughter Joseph.
Slice Polnareff.
Cleave Jotaro in two.
You are a fighting genius, a master of the sword.
No one in the world is a match for your blade, no one!
Kom ombo?
Come on. Do we really have time
to lounge around in this place?
Would you quit complaining?
They've been kind enough to allow us passage
on their ferry, so we must show our respect.
I don't know about you guys, but I'm
starving, so let's get something to eat.
Wow, you never stop, do you?
Here. This should tide you over for now.
You know damn well that's Iggy's!
Would you just take the gum, already?
Hey, where's the bathroom, huh?
Shall we look for it?
Hey, mister, over here!
Wanna buy some papyrus?
This papyrus is the original paper.
Want a piece of Egyptian history?
Here. Take a look. This is 100% bona fide papyrus!
Papyrus, huh?
I'll give you a good price.
Are you positive this is the real thing?
Of course, my friend. I'll have you know a famous
Egyptian craftsman drew this, so it's quite genuine.
Hmm.
This crap is fake, and you know it.
If this were actual papyrus, it wouldn't rip so easily.
I'm no fool.
You should try a little harder next time.
What the... for the love of...
Where'd Mr. Joestar and the others go?
Huh?
Was that Iggy?!
Why you... get back here, you little mutt!
Hey! What about my money?!
Stupid dog. He managed to get away.
Gotta say, if my hunch is correct,
then you've got a lot of balls, my friend.
Seems like you're planning to attack me
while we're in a crowd of innocent bystanders.
Guys like you are a rare breed.
Stand users don't usually show themselves,
let alone face their attacker head-on.
It's kind of noble.
I didn't think you guys had that trait.
Tell me your name.
My name is Chaka,
and my stand is known as Anubis,
the one true ruler of the underworld.
Now then, Jean Pierre Polnareff,
prepare to surrender your life to me.
You want me to surrender my life?
Man, oh, man, you sure don't mince words, do you, Chaka?
If nothing else, your confidence is
more impressive than your other companions.
Give me your best shot.
Let's see if your Anubis stand
is all it's cracked up to be.
Come out, chariot.
He's brandishing his sword, but is he really
planning to fight me with that instead of his stand?
Something's off.
His movements, his grip, his stance,
they're the dead giveaways of an amateur,
but that doesn't make sense.
I need to keep my distance from him.
What the hell is going on here?
His sword passed right through the pillar,
and if that wasn't enough,
he cut me without leaving even a single tear in my shirt.
If I hadn't stepped back when
I did, I would have been killed.
You bastard! Chariot!
Damn it!
Why don't you show yourself and face
me like a real fighter, you coward?!
Huh?
Merde.
This can't be happening.
I lost him.
He could be hiding behind any one of these pillars.
Judging from his attacks,
his sword can pass through solid objects.
And unfortunately for me, my chariot's
striking range is only about one meter.
Damn it. He's tougher than I thought he'd be.
I honestly can't believe this asshole is actually
giving me a run for my money in a sword fight.
But Mark my words.
You won't have the upper hand for long.
Hey, Chaka, are you listening?!
I've got a nice view, so let's see what you've got!
There's no way you can sneak up
on me if I'm not behind a pillar,
unless you're planning on popping out of the ground.
What the...
He's behind the pillar?!
My sword doesn't need to pass through objects!
With the power of this blade, I
can cut through the pillar itself!
Now die, Polnareff!
Man, that was a close one.
That technique is so secret that
not even Jotaro knows about it.
Silver chariot can launch its rapier.
The downside is I only get one shot.
If my opponent dodges, I'm history.
A last resort once I've exhausted my other options.
While it's true I didn't kill you,
I highly doubt you'll be
getting back up for another round.
Hmm?
That's peculiar.
How the heck did it get back into its scabbard?
Did it slip in by chance?
I didn't notice before, but now that I see it up close,
I fully appreciate the sword's beauty.
I have to unsheathe it.
Huh?
Hey, there, Polnareff.
Thought we'd lost you.
We were worried when you up and vanished by yourself.
We thought you'd been ambushed by the enemy.
Wait. Are you okay?
Huh?
Oh. Oh! It's you, Mr. Joestar.
I'm so fuzzy, I can't think straight.
Maybe it's from being tossed around
or my injuries are worse than I thought.
Polnareff, why are you squatting like that?
You didn't step in poop, did you?
Huh?
Polnareff, how did you come across that sword?
Did something happen out here?
Yeah.
I had a showdown with some dirtbag that attacked me.
What? An enemy stand user?!
It's all over now.
He said his stand was known as the god Anubis.
It was able to literally phase through objects
and cut them once it had a target in its crosshairs.
He was a strong foe.
"But despite his formidable power,"
"when all was said and done, he
was no match for the likes of me,"
Polnareff reassured himself.
He was using this sword as his weap...
Where did it go?
Where'd those rats come from,
and why are they making off with the sword?!
Get outta here!
Jeez, talk about creepy.
No one told me even the rats steal stuff in this place.
If you guys wanna steal something, steal some cheese.
That's unusual.
The sword's stuck in the scabbard.
It's jammed in here really tight.
Hey, Polnareff,
while I'm relieved that you're all right,
don't ever run off by yourself again. Got it?
It's dangerous.
The enemy will find a way to attack you
even if you're just alone for a few seconds.
Oh, crap, I forgot.
That's the sound of our ship taking off without us.
We need to hurry and get on board.
We're heading to Edfu today.
Wha... c-come on, guys. Wait for me!
Polnareff, so you decided to
bring the sword with you after all?
Yeah. I'm gonna turn it in to the police.
This thing is a dangerous weapon, you know.
Hmm. That's a good plan.
Anyone could pick it up at those
ruins, so we can't take any chances.
It's probably worth a small fortune.
Huh?
Quiet, Iggy. You can't make noise in here.
If you keep this up, we could get kicked out.
What the hell is wrong with that mutt, today?
Ah, well, since the damn dog won't shut up,
I guess I'll just take the sword to the cops now.
Polnareff, weren't you listening when
we told you not to go off on your own?
Seriously, we talked about this earlier.
Jotaro, tag along, and keep him out of trouble, would you?
Gotcha.
Hey, shouldn't our first stop
have been the police station?
Oh, take it easy, Jotaro.
A man's got to look his absolute best, as the saying goes.
Oh, before I forget,
old man, you mind putting this over there out of the way?
Sure.
That thing's a dangerous weapon.
All right, back to what I saying earlier.
I did a fair amount of rolling
around and ended up getting kinda dirty.
Make this face gorgeous again, Mr. Barber.
Will do.
Ow! Ow!
Hey, would you watch it?!
In case you haven't noticed, that razor's dull!
Come on, Mr. Barber! Sharpen that thing!
This is supposed to be the
most relaxing part of the haircut!
Oh, good grief. You're such a prima Donna.
You're right, sir. My apologies.
Mmm.
Oh. Mm, better.
Much better.
Now that's a shave, Mr. Barber.
That's what I'm talking about.
Thank you.
I'm glad to hear it.
Tres bien, barber.
Tres bien, man!
And now if you wouldn't mind getting under my chin.
Sure.
Right here...
Under your chin, yes?
Mm? Huh?
You did say under your chin, right, Polnareff?!
What the hell?!
Remember me, you fool?
I'm the Anubis stand, and this time, you're going to die!