They're about to exit the tunnel!
No! Not good! Darby's ahead
and by a full car length!
Our speed is about to be doubled.
It looks like I win!
No! The fact of the matter is I
still have more speed than you, Darby.
You're in for it now.
I can't believe what I'm seeing!
Kakyoin had enough power to spin his car around
and knock Darby's car clear off the racetrack!
He used his speed to his advantage.
He's out of there!
And Kakyoin's car is safely on the ground.
You did it!
The weaker car loses in a collision.
Giving up power to ram me will
prove to be a costly mistake.
Instead of gloating, you should have
paid more attention to my plan to stay behind
and knock you off course with a spin attack.
So you say,
though the same could also be said of you.
Losing power was not an accident.
You're so self-righteous.
In your hubris, you didn't realize I
planned for you to knock my car off course.
Everything rests on this.
Look closely. Do you see where my car is headed?
Ohh!
What?
He landed on the other side,
farther ahead, at that.
Impossible.
Yes, ordinarily.
Even at one's top speed, a move like the
one I just did usually would result in a crash.
You wouldn't make it by jumping over the curves,
but it's another story completely
if you're catapulted over them.
All I needed was your help.
From the moment we left the tunnel, my plan
was to get you to hit me by sacrificing my power.
That said, I think it's time we continued our race.
Don't you?
Don't let this guy get to you, Kakyoin!
Stay focused!
Kakyoin!
There.
Now his soul belongs to me.
The poor fool admitted defeat.
He finally realized that it
was pointless to continue racing.
Still, I must say, you, Kakyoin, are the
first opponent to ever make me perspire like this.
Given its source material, this doll will make a
most exquisite addition to my growing collection.
He was the very first opponent to
muster up the courage to conquer his fears
and resist cracking under such colossal pressure.
No. Kakyoin.
I will treasure his good company always.
Careful.
It would be in the best interest of all
involved for you to keep your emotions in check.
Harming me is out of the question.
You see, dying is something I simply
can't do if you want your friend back.
Slipping on a banana peel and hitting my head,
choking on gum, or even suffering a heart
attack from the shock of popping a bag of popcorn,
if any of those things sent me to heaven,
Kakyoin's soul would go, too.
What the... Hey, Jotaro, wait!
What's this?
Hey, Jotaro,
why the hell are you sitting down?
We should be kicking Geppetto's ass.
I'll play him next.
Old man,
have you ever actually played any of these games?
If not, the odds wouldn't be in your favor.
Stay out of it, old man.
This isn't your average game of gin rummy, after all.
We're playing baseball.
That's the game I choose to settle this once and for all.
As collateral, I'll bet my soul.
All right. Then I would like to bet Kakyoin's soul.
My stand Atum has released your arm.
You may thank me at your leisure.
Now that Kakyoin's soul is in my collection,
there's no longer reason for me to
keep your arm in my stand's clutches.
And suffice it to say I'd be at a bit of a
disadvantage if I faced you with my stand one-handed.
I'm well aware of your Star Platinum's
incredible speed and precision.
Really, out of all the games
you could have chosen to play...
it's unfortunate for you that we're playing my specialty.
Darby, just you wait.
The moment Jotaro wipes the floor with you,
I'll throttle the life out of your
pompous ass, and that is a promise.
"Oh! That's a baseball!"
Doesn't look like he's tampered with this game either.
You're good to go.
Before we begin, you'll need to pick your team.
Jaguars.
Jaguars!
Yes, I see. You've decided to go with
a team that has a strong offense, eh?
And two with a batting average over .400.
If that's how you're going to
play it, I'll choose the Red Dragons.
Red Dragons!
Offense or defense?
Go on. Take your pick.
Offense.
In that case,
the Jaguars will bat first.
Next, you can begin designing your own
players by drawing their faces on the screen.
This handsome devil is Star Platinum.
Now that we've gotten the preparations out of the way,
play ball?
Jaguars versus Red Dragons!
Play ball!
I've chosen number 15 as my pitcher.
January fifth is my birthday, you know.
Now, here we go.
The pitcher is winding up.
The first pitch.
What?!
Strike one.
Uh, hey, I don't get it.
What's wrong?
That was a pretty amateur move back there.
It's great that you swung the bat and
all, but it was before he even threw the ball!
Hmm?
Hey, what's this all about?
There's no need for you to practice your swing, is there?
Hang on. Jotaro, is this the very
first time you've ever played this?
In fact, have you ever played a video game in your life?
You answer me right now, Jotaro!
Relax. I already know how to play baseball.
I'll figure out the game controls as I go.
Huh?
W-What are you saying?!
In case you haven't noticed, your timing is totally off.
Your swings are pathetic.
Don't lie. This is your first time playing, isn't it?
Strike two.
And now you're actually swinging the
bat after the catcher has caught the ball.
You don't know what you're doing!
Damn it, Jotaro. I was right.
You don't know a video game from a hole in the ground.
Strike. Batter out.
Jotaro, it's time to get serious!
Stop trying to act cool, and use your blasted head!
You bet your soul on this game, so if you think you
can back out due to lack of experience, think again.
Good grief.
This is the worst pep talk I've ever heard.
You should be more encouraging.
Try something like, "it's only the first inning.
You can still make a comeback."
What the hell's going through that head of yours?
You can't possibly rely solely on Star
Platinum's reflexes to win this game, can you?
Think about it.
You don't know the first thing about video games.
How are you supposed to beat him?
What's your plan, Jotaro?
Answer me, damn it!
Do you have a way to beat this weirdo or not?
Jotaro...
Hmm?
Listen, if your strategy is to trick
me by pretending to be an amateur,
let me inform you that it isn't going to work.
I'd never be foolish enough to let my guard down.
Even if you were a helpless child, it wouldn't happen.
A soul is at stake.
Old man.
Eh? Huh?
Since you wanted to know, I don't have a plan.
However, if I did have one,
the only thing it would involve
would be knocking the nose straight off the face of
this condescending, over-inflated douche bag of a prick
taking up space beside me.
All I care about is getting Kakyoin's soul back.
I'll do whatever it takes.
You talk a big game,
but it's still the top of the
first inning, and you have one out.
The match is far from over.
And since you haven't played before, you should know
that if you fall more than 11 points behind, you lose.
Second batter, number 3.
Strike.
Damn, he's getting even worse.
That time, he swung the bat over 40
centimeters above the ball. How's he so bad?
Strike two.
What? It wasn't even close.
Strike three. You're out.
It's all over.
Jotaro's no match for someone like Darby.
This massacre is like being forced to
watch a group of high school baseball champs
go head-to-head with kids from the knitting club!
It's pathetic.
Strike one.
Strike two.
So it wasn't a bluff.
He really is a beginner. This is too easy.
In the same way a judo pro can Gauge his opponent's
skill simply by looking at the way he wears his gi,
I can read him like a book,
and chapter one is called,
"Jotaro, the video game novice."
All the same, I refuse to let my guard down.
I'm aware of the weaknesses of every batter in this game.
Next will be a low pitch to the outside.
I'll throw my best pitch,
the four-seam fast ball, and strike him out.
It's the first inning.
Two outs, two strikes, and no fouls.
Here comes my next pitch.
Go right ahead.
I've pretty much gotten the hang
of batting with the controller.
Wait. What did he just say?
I must have heard him wrong.
What does he mean, "got the hang of it"?
Surely, he couldn't have...
What is he talking about?
What does he mean?
What?!
Jotaro!
All right. I'm really starting to enjoy this game.
What in the... it can't be!
It's going! The ball is still going!
It just doesn't make sense.
What did he mean by, "got the hang of it"?
"Got the hang of it"? "Got the hang of it"?
He... he did it!
I don't know how, but he did it!
Home run!
Home run! It's a home run!
Jotaro, damn you.
Jotaro...
Did I really hear you correctly?
Say something. It sounded like you'd,
"pretty much gotten the hang of batting."
I don't feel like repeating myself.
He was a beginner when we started this game,
and yet he's claiming to have learned
proper swinging technique in only eight pitches.
Jotaro Kujo has all the speed
and dexterity of Star Platinum.
Now I know why master Dio finds him to
be problematic and why my brother lost.
Interesting.
I couldn't have asked for a more fitting opponent.
But as naturally gifted as you may be,
you made a critical mistake by revealing
your talents so early in the game,
a mistake that will cost you dearly.
Let's resume the game, Jotaro.
Yes, he did it!
That's my boy!
Another home run right out of the park!
Talk about a comeback.
Four runs in the first inning.
Looks like you've got this game in the bag, Jotaro.
Keep it up, and we'll be out of here in no time.
Hey, Darby, you'll just ignore me,
but I'll say it anyway, because I'm a nice guy.
I'm giving you an out.
All you have to do is return Kakyoin's soul
and take us to Dio of your own volition.
If you cooperate, no harm will befall you.
Huh?
For all his faults, my brother was a master gambler.
He made conning people into an art form.
You'd think his younger brother
would be perfect to practice on,
but you'd be wrong.
He never asked me to play one game of poker.
No, I was never asked to play any
games of the gambling persuasion.
Any guesses why?
When I was 15, I caught my brother putting
his oh-so-predictable moves on my girlfriend.
He was ten years older, but I beat him to a bloody pulp.
I broke his ribs and proceeded
to kick him until he spat blood.
The last thing my brother said to me was how sorry he was.
Any idea why?
Would you please cut to the chase already?
Even as kids, my brother had the good sense to
realize that he'd never have what it took to beat me.
The reason for that is about to become abundantly clear.
At this moment, you have a false sense
of confidence due to the home run you hit,
but deep down, you feel a sense of
unease, not unlike what my brother felt.
My prowess is beginning to worry you, isn't it?
Right now you're coming to a daunting conclusion
about the game's outcome, aren't you, Jotaro?
What the hell are you talking about?
Changing pitchers!
Number 15 is out, and number 77 is in.
77 is a power pitcher with a Max
pitch speed of 165 kilometers per hour.
Also, I'll tell you the pitch I'll throw.
Number 77 will throw a forkball,
and he'll throw it right down the middle.
What the hell?!
Why would he declare what he's throwing?!
A forkball is about to come barreling down center.
But will you believe me or not?
Jotaro, he's just spouting
nonsense to shake your confidence.
Do yourself a favor, and ignore everything he says.
Throw it, Darby.
Will you believe, or will you doubt?
I knew it. It's a fastball, and it's coming right at you.
Let's see. Is the ball going to change direction?
The suspense is driving me crazy!
You swung!
You bought his act and bet on the forkball!
It's still going. It actually is a fastball!
Oh, great. He hit the bottom of the ball.
Out.
First inning, three outs. Change.
Idiot. How could you?!
Leave it to a rookie for something like that.
I can't believe you swung for a forkball.
No.
He had already seen through me and
knew I would swing expecting a forkball,
so he switched it up to a fastball.
But he has a point, though.
Something's been gnawing at me ever
since we stepped foot in this mansion.
I'm not sure how, but he knew Star Platinum
would throw a right punch in our earlier skirmish.
What? Impossible!
Are you trying to tell me that he can read your mind?
No offense, Jotaro, but that's crazy talk.
Oh, would you look at that?
It's my turn at bat.
Eh?
This is going to be a home run.
Keep your eye on the birdie, as I'll be
hitting it into the left-field bleachers.
Old man, are you absolutely sure the
game and console haven't been tampered with?
Yeah, I'm positive it's clean,
and that's not all.
I haven't seen him make a single funny move either.
Then his secret weapon has to be that stand of his.
His stand doesn't just take souls.
It must have some other ability.
This'll be my target.
Now I'll get to the bottom of this.
Has he lost his mind?
He's going to try to hit the batter on purpose?
And where might you be aiming now, Jotaro,
an inside pitch?
Will you throw it high or low, perhaps?
Or maybe you're planning some kind of underhanded trick?
Well?
What the...
He pulled back when Jotaro threw the ball!
He predicted it.
He knew exactly what would happen. But how?
There's no way he could have seen that
pitch coming unless he read Jotaro's mind!
Home run!
That's one run.
Damn this bastard. We've faced all
kinds of opponents on this journey,
but never one who could read our minds.
If he really can read minds, then it
doesn't matter how clever we think we are.
We won't stand a snowball's chance in hell.
Jotaro, what are you going to do?
Why, that...
Damn, the punk's declaring another home run.
Let's see. Heh. An outside pitch?
Or maybe you're going to aim low?
Or something in the vein of a fastball?
Home run!
Four to two.
Damn. A person's body language
and the surrounding environment go a long way
toward helping predict an opponent's next move,
but there's no way to do it perfectly, and yet
his stand predicts Jotaro's pitch with 100% accuracy.
And technically he's not cheating.
Another home run!
It's four to three.
How are we supposed to stop
him from reading our minds? How?
At this rate, I'll be in the lead in no time.
Now what's next? An inside pitch, a
fastball, a high pitch, or maybe a curveball?
What's up your sleeve?
Huh?
Your hat...
You idiot.
Do you honestly take me for a
cheat like my ne'er-do-well brother?
Jotaro, you've got it wrong.
Hiding your face is useless.
I don't know what he's doing, but he's not
watching the reflection of the screen in your eyes.
I get that it's hard not to go there now,
but there's no way he can see what you're
pressing or what pitch you're choosing.
Trust me. I've been watching him the entire time.
That's not what's been going on here.
I only took off my hat, because I'm sweating,
no other reason.
Huh?
Could you throw your next pitch sometime this year?
But I'm not going to be sweating anymore.
I'll tell you my next pitch.
I'm throwing a high, outside fastball.
You're joking.
Jotaro, do you hear what you're saying right now?
Of course I do.
Finally starting to lose your hearing, old man?
Obviously I just told him my next pitch.
A high, outside fastball, that's how I'm gonna win.
Eh? Jotaro?
Will you believe me, or will you doubt me?
You're not too bright, are you?