Previously on "JoJo's Bizarre Adventure"...
Blast it!
Oh, no! The exit's blocked with ice,
and more's coming this way!
Shit!
It's starting to cover the whole tunnel.
I gotta find a way out of this deathtrap!
What?!
My paw!
I can't pry my paw loose!
Hmm.
All right, the sun is about to set.
Didn't "shades" say three hours?
Guess that cocky beggar had a bit more
trouble finding Dio's mansion than he thought.
Can't say I was expecting this to happen, though.
Right, Avdol?
I have a bad feeling.
Maybe it's better if he doesn't
find that accursed mansion.
Hmm?
You see,
maybe he hasn't come back,
because he did find it.
What are you saying?
It didn't occur to me until a moment ago, but a
stand user is likely to be guarding Dio's lair.
We may have put that beggar's life in grave danger,
if he hasn't already been killed.
What? Are you serious?
Son of a... I barely made it out of there,
and my... my leg is...
That ice caught my paw like a bear trap.
I'd be dead if I hadn't gnawed it off.
I-I think I'm gonna hide out here for a while.
If I'm down here long enough, maybe birdbrain'll go away.
After this is over, the Speedwagon
Foundation can make me an artificial leg.
But I'm still pissed as hell.
Damn that bird.
You're not getting away with this!
I'm gonna make you suffer for what you did to me.
Just you wait.
Wait. That sound.
Something out there dove into the water.
No way.
Birds have the capacity to dive under water.
Like humans and canines,
birds are reliant upon lungs for respiration,
but the average bird has five to six air sacs
stored away in its chest and stomach regions.
It's these pockets of air that give birds the ability
to remain conscious at altitudes of 6,000 to 7,000 meters,
a feat completely impossible for humans.
Even if it were to be strangled,
a bird can survive for several minutes
thanks to its internal air reserves.
With these advantages,
a bird can survive underwater much longer than a dog.
It sounds like something's headed straight for me.
But how? That's impossible!
I don't understand! What could
be coming after me down here?
Wait a sec.
Could it be?
It's that bird again.
But how can it survive underwater like this?
That bastard. Where'd it fly off to now?
It's closing in, but what's its plan?
More icicles? One, two, three.
Great. Three icicles are coming this way.
Suck on that, you frickin' coot!
Yes. I did it.
How do you like that?
The icicles are stopping the wall from leaking,
but at the rate they're spreading,
they're gonna cover everything!
No. What am I gonna do now?!
I know what it's doing.
It's focusing on freezing the water around me.
And it's cut my air pipes.
I-I don't think it's trying to suffocate me.
Its real plan is to Bury me alive.
It's no use. It's collapsing!
This bird is too powerful for me to hold it off!
And what's worse, I'm surrounded
by ice and freezing water!
Just my damn luck.
So much for finding a decent hiding
place to lay low in for a while.
No other choice.
I have to dig my way out.
Give me a break.
This stupid day has gone from bad to
horrifying in the worst possible way!
First, I lose my leg, and now some demon
bird wants me flattened into a frozen dinner!
Damn. I can't hold it off anymore.
I'm about to be crushed.
I need to dig myself out of here now!
Huh?
What is that?
It looks like someone dug a tunnel down here,
but why?
It's the bird!
It's getting ready to shoot another ice missile.
Damn it.
My stand is being held by the ice.
I can't defend myself,
and there's nowhere for me to escape!
Wait. That's it.
Either way you slice it, it's do-or-die time!
I'll let the dome break
and use the air pressure to catapult
me forward like a speeding bullet!
I got out of there alive.
That dumb bird didn't have to
die, but it left me no choice.
One of us had to go.
But it looks like this'll probably be the end for me.
I've been bleeding out for a while now.
I hardly have enough strength
in my body to keep myself afloat,
let alone make it back to shore,
which means I'm gonna drown.
Why is this happening?
I was supposed to live a trouble-free life.
Damn it. I messed up.
Thank goodness I found you.
As soon as I saw that little face and
those great big ears, I knew it was you.
It's that stupid bird's fault that you're
like this. It attacked you just like my dogs.
You're gonna pull through this.
The bird's gone, so there's nothing to worry about.
Try and hang on, all right? Keep fighting.
I'll patch you up right away.
The Bird: Pet Shop. Stand: Horus.
Status: Deceased.
Damn that mangy mutt. Where the hell did he run off to?
He's gotta stop pulling stunts like this.
I'm starting to get worried. He's been gone for a while.
That lousy flea bag.
Huh?
Jotaro, what's the matter?
There must be someone following us again.
Not quite,
but I thought I heard a voice,
like someone's calling out to us.
Hmm.
A voice?
Hmm?
It's Iggy!
Iggy!
What on earth happened?!
Look at that.
He's got injuries all over his body.
Hey, Iggy's missing his front leg, too!
You think he got run over by a car?
He's not the kind of dog that gets into car accidents.
You were attacked by the enemy, weren't you?
What's this?
It looks as though someone treated his wounds.
I have to say they did a great job.
But it wasn't Iggy that I heard.
Whoever was calling out to us was definitely human.
Huh?
Iggy did have a run-in with the enemy.
When we found him, he was half-dead in the arms of a boy,
so the Speedwagon foundation doctors saw to his wounds.
They did the same...
For my eyes.
It's you!
You're finally back!
It's Kakyoin!
Good to see you, Kakyoin! How's it going?
Kakyoin, tell me, how are your eyes treating you?
I'm glad you're all safe.
We missed you, pal.
So they were able to treat you?
Yes. I'm ready for action.
While it's true I'll have a few scars,
my eyesight is back to normal.
We're all really glad to hear that.
Jotaro.
Hmm?
Where do you think you're going, Iggy?
He may have been quite indifferent
toward humans and stands in the past,
but now it looks like he's trying to lead us somewhere.
I'm not aware of all the details
surrounding his encounter with the enemy stand,
but judging from his resolve, this is about revenge.
Maybe, but that still doesn't
explain where he's taking us.
Hang on, Iggy! Wait for us!
Hmm?
Huh?
I recognize that car.
It's the same fancy ride the beggar was driving.
C-could this wreckage mean that he...
But how?
What's strong enough to tear a hole
through a car like a piece of wet newspaper?
It would seem as though I was
right to be concerned about him.
He should have never been involved.
Is it possible this is the handiwork
of the stand user Iggy fought earlier?
All signs seem to point to that being the case.
Iggy!
Hmm?
What the hell's going on?
All of a sudden, I'm drenched in a cold sweat,
and there's this oppressive
feeling of doom roaming in the air.
I don't know about you guys,
but I am majorly creeped out.
Where exactly is Iggy trying to take us?
I know where he's going.
This feeling, it's all too familiar to me.
This aura is pure, unmitigated evil.
It's the mansion from the picture.
We've arrived.
Iggy, you were able to find it by yourself?
What lay before Jotaro and the others
was something more sinister than
anything they'd previously faced.
They would soon look upon the source of their predicament
and the very embodiment of evil.
The path that had led them here was long and arduous.
Foreign lands shrouded in mystery
and treacherous stand-using
assassins met them at every step.
Each battle was a struggle for survival
where the wrong move would spell out certain death.
There were tears, laughter, sadness, rage, and joy.
The journey affected them all.
Now nearly 50 days have passed
since the team departed Japan on their
quest to save the life of Jotaro's mother Holly.
Everything led to this.
The time had come to defeat Dio and end the
hundred-year curse afflicting the Joestar family.
Joseph was determined to save his daughter Holly,
and nothing and no one was going to stand in his way.
Kakyoin vowed to remain resolute.
He would defeat Dio not only to save Holly,
but to overcome his own weaknesses.
Avdol was steadfast in his conviction,
considering it his personal duty
to root out evil wherever it lurked.
Polnareff was determined to make the tyrant Dio suffer
for turning him into a puppet
and forcing him to betray his own principles.
Iggy's spirit was untamable.
He knew his life of turmoil
could be traced back to a single man
and was intent on making sure the bastard faced his wrath.
And so...
In other words,
if we beat the shit out of Dio in there,
this damn nightmare will be over once and for all.
That's right,
and the scent of evil confirms that he's here.
He's hiding inside the mansion like the coward he is.
It's hard to believe, but...
We've finally reached the end of this hellacious journey.
All right, men, you ready?
The gate's open as if they're inviting us in.
This is totally different from the situation yesterday.
Now that I think about it, if I can sense Dio,
then it stands to reason that he
has the ability to sense us, too.
If we try to enter the mansion guns blazing,
no doubt we'll be playing right into the enemy's hands.
Before we do anything, we need to think of a strategy.
Careful! The door is opening!
Everyone on guard!
Check it out.
What's with this weird corridor?
It must go on forever.
This can't be real, right?
It has to be some sort of trick or illusion.
Listen, Polnareff.
No matter what, don't go through the door.
Dio's probably got a couple more stand
users waiting in the wings to fight us.
Hey!
Something's coming this way!
Wait. Is that guy floating?
Is he a stand user or what?
Master Joestar...
Welcome to our abode.
We've been expecting you, sir.
I am the resident Butler of the mansion.