It's about time.
Hmm?
Hey, do you hear that noise, too?
They've arrived.
It's a helicopter!
Thanks for the update, captain obvious.
They're here from the Speedwagon foundation,
and they're looking for somewhere to land.
Speedwagon foundation?
Correct me if I'm wrong, but aren't they the
group that's looking after mom back in Japan?
They're old friends of yours, right?
Yep, that's them, all right.
So, what?
Are we taking a helicopter from here on out?
Not quite.
As much as I'd like to, the guys working
for the foundation aren't stand users,
so we'd be putting them in
harm's way if we hitched a ride.
Well, if they're not here to give
us a ride, what's the occasion, then?
They've brought us our new ally.
Tu rigoles! An ally?
I have to warn you, he's a bit of a handful,
which is the primary reason it took so long to fetch him.
Mr. Joestar!
You aren't seriously considering
taking him with us, are you?
His presence here would only hold us back.
So he might actually harm us?
Correct, so be careful.
Not so fast.
This new ally of ours, are you
saying that he's a stand user, too?
Yes, that's right, and his stand is
represented by the card known as the fool.
The fool?
Wait. The fool?
Sounds like a pretty stupid card if you want my opinion.
You should count your blessings that he's on our side.
You can't beat him.
I'd suggest watching your mouth
if you know what's good for you, Avdol.
It's true, Polnareff.
Now move your hand. You're hurting me.
Who died and made you the boss?!
Enough, you two.
The helicopter's here.
Mr. Joestar. Good to see you.
Thank you for bringing him here.
Must have been rough.
So which one of you is it?
Who's the stand user?
Hmm?
Well, are you gonna answer me or not?
Is it you?
No, sir. Neither of us is the user.
He's actually in the back.
In the back, huh?
I don't see anyone.
No, he's there.
Hey, hey, cut it out.
Come on. Quit joking around.
What's the deal? Is the guy really short or something?
Come out, come out wherever you are!
Hey, watch out!
Huh?
That's weird. What the hell is this stuff?
Please, be careful!
It was a rough copter ride, so he's in a foul mood!
Step away! I've already told you this guy is trouble.
Get back, Polnareff. You cannot beat him.
What's the big deal? All I'm doing is asking where he is.
Huh?
H-h-h-h-he's...
A dog.
Don't tell me this dog is...
Mm-hmm.
Yes, this dog possesses the stand of the fool.
His name is Iggy, and he's crazy about
ripping chunks of hair out of people's heads.
To be honest with you, I'm not sure where he's from,
but Avdol found him in New York after
none of the dogcatchers could wrangle him,
and it's thanks to Avdol that
he's not roaming the streets now.
Oh, there's something that I
probably should have mentioned.
When he's in the middle of ripping
out someone's hair, he likes to, uh...
Pass gas in their face.
It's a disgusting habit, really.
You little mutt! You're gonna pay for that!
Damn you!
Chariot!
Holy cow!
So that thing is the fool.
When we were in Singapore, we fought
an orangutan stand user, but this is...
Who does this stupid mutt think he is?!
Bastard. Don't make me turn you into dog meat!
What the hell? It turned into sand!
I can't cut him!
Damn it! His stand has solidified
and grabbed hold of my rapier!
Is that...
Yes, the dog's stand is made entirely out of sand.
Hmm. As simple as the design is, it's so
powerful, I'm not sure I could land a punch.
Guys!
What are you doing?! Help! Get this dog off of me!
I'm sorry, Polnareff, but if it's all
the same to you, I'd like to keep my hair.
You monster!
Did you happen to bring his favorite snack with you?
Of course I did.
He wouldn't have come with us otherwise.
For the love of god, stop! Help me!
The dog's sense of smell is simply incredible.
And that is?
It's coffee-flavored chewing gum,
and Iggy will do just about anything
to savor this tasty little morsel.
No, Mr. Avdol!
Quickly, hide the packet before he...
Blast it! He grabbed the whole thing!
He can't get enough of his
coffee-flavored gum, as you can see.
People, on the other hand, are
a different story, unfortunately.
The least he can do is take the wrapping off.
How is a gum-obsessed, feral dog supposed to help us?
Good grief.
Damn that little menace!
He's completely ruined my picturesque hair!
Petit con!
He'll be distracted while he's chewing his gum.
Let's get the supplies.
Here's the food and water you'll
be needing for your trip, sir.
Oh, thank you.
There are medical supplies and a change of clothes, too.
We also took the Liberty of buying
a new camera to use with your stand.
Yeah, I suppose it'll be a lot
easier than using a TV, right?
Oh, I know. Look sharp, men!
Hmm?
Fantastic. This is a perfect memento.
Avdol! Hurry up, and give the mutt the stupid gum!
Now, why in the world would I do that
when the two of you are already
such good friends, Polnareff?
Well, if that's everything,
I think we're going to be heading back now, Mr. Joestar.
Answer this before you leave.
It's regarding my daughter's condition.
And I want you to be straight with me.
How's my baby girl holding up?
Well, to be perfectly frank with you, sir,
it's not looking good right now.
She's rapidly losing strength, and
nothing seems to help her condition.
Our doctors at the Speedwagon foundation say
she has two weeks at best.
We're all out of time.
This is bullshit.
I also have some other information, sir.
Hmm?
Our investigators say that two days ago,
nine unidentified men and women
gathered in a building believed to be Dio's hideout.
Apparently they came and left together.
Dio has rounded up nine more people?!
We have no clue who they are.
The spy who reported this was killed shortly after,
and the mansion where they met has been vacated.
We've had no luck in locating these individuals.
We thought about tailing them,
but since our spies aren't stand users,
we decided it would be too dangerous.
So these people are stand users?!
Hold on.
Think about it for a minute.
That would be impossible.
Other than hol horse's stand, the emperor,
the only tarot card that still remains is the world.
I've been suspecting that one belongs to Dio,
but now I'm not sure. Avdol?
I... I don't know.
I just can't wrap my head around this.
Nine more stand users?
From what I can gather, it seems that Dio's
head hasn't been able to adjust to his new body yet.
But that monster would never run from us.
He's far too conceited for something like that.
He'll do everything within his
power to keep us out of Cairo.
Good freakin' grief.
We have to take out nine stand users in two weeks, huh?
Man, that is one hell of a whirlwind tour.
Have a safe trip, Mr. Joestar.
We await your return.
Thanks for your help. Look after my Holly.
That mutt...
So it sniffed out the great N'Doul from that far away?
So close.
What do you know? I almost caught it this time.
Just a bit more practice.
All of this because of the tsetse fly.
If not for those insects,
Joestar and his band of meddlers would
never have known master Dio was in Egypt.
Mr. Joestar, why are you letting him get away with this?
It's not fair he gets to be in the
back seat while we're stuck in the trunk!
And in case you didn't know,
it's not exactly spacious back here.
I'm gonna need a chiropractor!
Look, I know it's not ideal, but you'll just
have to wait until the gum runs out of flavor.
When it does, throw another stick of
gum into the trunk to lure him back there.
Then you can all switch seats with him.
All right, all right. Calm down already, flea bag.
Damn, you're annoying.
Whoa!
What the hell was that?!
Hey, quickly, look over there!
There! Do you see it?!
It's the helicopter!
The Speedwagon foundation helicopter went down.
I can't believe what I'm seeing.
There's no sign of an explosion or gunfire.
It seems like it just fell out
of the sky for no reason at all.
Could it be...
Careful, men!
I'd bet my life it was attacked by an enemy stand!
Over there, it's the pilot!
He's already dead.
Whatever happened to him... it wasn't pretty.
Eh, the poor bastard.
Approach carefully.
Whatever did this could still be hiding in there.
It's water.
There's no way all that water is just from his mouth.
It must be flowing from somewhere else.
It must be from his lungs.
And the fish would mean...
He drowned in the desert!
This is getting weirder and weirder!
What is going on?
H-hey!
We found the other guy over here!
He's alive!
Hang on! You have to talk to us!
Tell us what happened!
Wa...
Water.
What? Are you saying you need water?
Hurry, Polnareff, hand me the canteen!
Huh? Oh, yeah.
Here. You just hang in there.
Drink this.
Drink it slowly.
No!
The water attacked us!
What?!
Men, watch yourselves! It's a stand!
The enemy stand is inside the canteen!
Eh, damn it all.
They were just innocent bystanders.
What reason did it have to kill them?
Avdol, did you see what kind of stand we're dealing with?
I just saw the shape of a hand,
but I'd wager it's still inside the canteen.
I don't believe I saw it leave.
Who could the user be?
The foundation members informed us Dio
had a meeting with nine men and women.
Is it possible that one of them is the assassin?
Hey, I need you to find the stand user.
Yeah, I know. I'm already on it. That said...
I don't see anything around us, let alone the stand user.
When we duked it out with that sun stand, he
was hiding behind a mirror, but this time...
The enemy seems to be so far away that
we'll never be able to find him from here.
Polnareff, slice up the canteen, would you?
Why me?
Besides,
didn't you see what happened to the pilot?
His entire head got sucked
into that tiny, little container!
Think about it! If I so much
as poke a hole in that thing...
No way.
Why don't you slice it up, Kakyoin?
You're closer anyhow!
You can just use your emerald
splash and call it a day, can't you?!
Yes, but I don't want to.
Don't make me do something just
because you don't want to do it!
What the hell, man?! What's going on with you?!
I've said no, and that's final.
Well, like I said, I'm not gonna
attack the damn thing, either!
Hmm?
Th-that's the...
K-Kakyoin!
It's the water! The stand left the canteen
disguised as water and hid in the blood!
No, that's wrong!
The stand wasn't disguising itself as water at all!
I think the stand is the water!
No! It got Kakyoin!
It clawed out Kakyoin's eyes!
Polnareff, panicking isn't going to help anything!
Summon chariot for protection!
Damn it. It'll get Polnareff, too!
This doesn't make any sense.
Why would it go after the pilot's corpse?
It wasn't the corpse. The target was the watch.
It attacked the watch because of the alarm.
That's it! The stand stalks its victims by sound!
You're kidding.
Get out of there, Polnareff!
It's coming after you now!
Hurry, and get to the car!
It's so fast!
Faster, Polnareff!
I-it got me!
Hermit purple!
The stand disappeared into the ground!
I see now.
It detects sound through vibrations in the ground,
and it moves through the earth,
so there's no way to find it.
That puts us at a major disadvantage.
Since we can't see it, the stand has the ability to
attack from above or below at any moment it chooses.
To make things worse, the stand
user could be kilometers away.
So the prey has sought refuge atop the car.
Seems they've realized N'Doul is using the power of sound
to hunt them down one by one.
No matter.
It won't be long before they're all eliminated.
Hey, how's Kakyoin doing?
Not good. From the looks of
things he may have been blinded.
We have to get going.
He needs to see a doctor as soon as possible.
But if we try to move from this
spot, that stand will attack us.
We can't afford careless mistakes.
What the hell?!
Hmm? That sound...
It's the dog.
Interesting. It leapt out of
the car before I could attack.
It anticipated what my stand was going to do.
Seems like this dog is going to be quite the nuisance.
The tires are in the water!
Shit! What now?!
The whole car's about to be pulled in!
I can't hold him for long!
Everyone, we have to move to the back!
Hey, you good-for-nothing mongrel!
Aren't you supposed to be helping us or something?!
I see. That accursed dog is
too perceptive for his own good.
It knows I'm four kilometers west of Joestar's group.
What to do?
Perhaps I should do away with the dog right now.
Yeah, sleep while we fight to survive!
You're a bastard. You know that?
Never mind. The dog is of no concern.
Joestar and the others can't control that mongrel, anyway.
The mutt's harmless if all it does is nap.
Now for the kill.
Son of a bitch! The water's sharp
enough to slash through our front tires!
Move to the other side on the double!
If it's trying to do what I think it is,
then we're gonna need to hang on for our lives!