Everyone, hold on!
Yaah!
Oh, no!
It sunk into the sand.
We should all be all right as long as
we don't move and don't make a sound.
It's much too late to try hiding from me at this point.
I know where each of you landed. There's no escaping now.
Four... no, five steps.
I get it. You're walking quietly to avoid detection.
But you can't hide from me.
Tsk, tsk.
It appears these "steps" have thrown him for a loop.
Go ahead, you accursed water stand.
Just try to attack us,
because the moment you reveal yourself,
I'll vaporize you with the power of my magician's red.
He's here.
Hold on. What's this?
He only moved five steps forward.
How strange.
Why has he suddenly stopped moving?
Now!
Magician's red!
What?!
Avdol!
How can he be so...
So quick?
Avdol!
I have to admit that plan was
actually a stroke of brilliance.
I have to pay more attention
to their vibrations from now on.
Those weren't footsteps at all.
It would seem as though he threw some kind of metal rings.
And judging by these burns...
I'd say Avdol did the deed.
But c'est la vie.
Farewell...
Avdol.
Hmm? What's this?
Someone started running.
Jotaro, what are you doing?!
You know we can't just run around!
His stride says he's about 190...
No, 195 centimeters tall.
There's a youthfulness in his stride, so he's not Joseph.
It must be Jotaro then, but where exactly is he going?
It dove in!
I think it's going after Jotaro!
This can't be happening!
I'm grateful he's not attacking Avdol anymore, but...
Jotaro! He's catching up to you!
I hear Jotaro's star platinum is
the fiercest of the enemies' stands.
Master Dio will be beside himself with
joy if I take care of him here and now.
In the name of master Dio,
I'll use every fiber of my
being to finally vanquish Jotaro.
Hmm. If I heard correctly,
Jotaro just picked something up off the sand.
Let's see. What was at that location?
Last I checked, it was...
Wait. I remember!
The dog! Jotaro grabbed the dog, which means he knows!
I've finally figured you out, mutt.
I know you jumped out of the
car before the stand attacked it.
You can smell it, can't you?
You know where it's gonna be before it gets there.
Gah! Don't stop moving, Jotaro!
Now, Iggy, I think it's time for you to earn your keep.
Where's the stand coming from? Just show me, already.
Show me, or we die,
and how would you get your gum then?
Huh?
Iggy!
You've gotta be kidding me.
He can fly, too? Not so fast.
Go ahead, and pant all you want.
You're not getting out of this one.
Star platinum's as fast as they come.
If you're thinking of dropping me,
I'll snap your neck before you can blink.
What?
It's like he jumped and suddenly disappeared.
This is impossible.
They must have landed somewhere.
That's brilliant.
We can't move around, so to bypass that handicap,
Jotaro's using Iggy to find the stand user.
If we can find whoever's controlling the stand,
we might actually have a chance of defeating him.
He's vanished.
I can't hear Jotaro's footsteps.
Where is he? Where did he go?
Why can't I hear his footsteps?
Oh, no. They're flying lower and lower.
This isn't gonna end well.
It looks like the fool can't travel long distances.
The damn thing is gliding like a paper airplane!
My legs are about to touch the ground.
Hey, mutt,
quit tensing up like that.
You're starting to fart again.
For your sake, you better not let out a big one.
No choice.
We need to get more air,
and at this point, there's only one way to do it.
Ora!
That kick got us a lot closer to our destination for sure,
but the sound of it definitely gave away our strategy.
Now the user will know that
we're flying to avoid detection.
So that's why I wasn't able to locate them.
The dog's stand has the ability to fly.
But now I know what they're up to.
They're headed directly for me.
I have to eliminate Jotaro before he gets any closer!
His stand's on the move, and it's going after Jotaro!
He figured it out when Jotaro kicked off!
There's nothing we can do about it.
The only thing we can do now is trust Jotaro.
He's coming.
I know he was able to bring down a helicopter,
but he shouldn't be able to find our exact
location since Iggy's stand barely makes a sound.
I just have to get to the stand user
before landing, and it'll be lights out.
There he is.
The stand user's about 400 meters away.
And from the looks of things, our enemy is blind.
Damn it. Sand's falling from the sky.
Of course. The stand user must be trying to find us.
He's using the sand bouncing off
the wings like a submarine uses sonar.
Because of the falling sand, I can hear you now.
And I've discovered your exact location, Jotaro!
Time to die!
Star platinum!
Ora!
Star platinum's speed won't be of much use, I'm afraid!
If you can't tell where my attack is
coming from, then my stand has the advantage!
Here comes another!
Iggy...
Shit.
You damn mutt!
What a dog! He's dragging Jotaro right into my trap!
It seems like he'll do anything to save his own hide!
Even abandon his master!
Bastard.
Just you wait.
That's what you get for relying
on such a fickle creature, Jotaro.
Your end has come,
and now it's finally time
to put you out of your misery.
O...
Ora!
What's this?
It feels like he just threw something at me!
I can't make out what it is at that speed.
I tossed Iggy at you. Get a move on.
You'd better use your stand to defend yourselves, or else
you two are gonna be closer than you ever wanted to be.
Such insane velocity.
Damn it! It's going to hit me!
I can't believe it.
He actually threw the dog.
Blast it! I was so close to putting
an end to that wretch once and for all.
Huh?
No. I was so busy worrying about that damn dog,
I completely lost Jotaro's location.
Where? Where is he?
It's like he vanished, and he's staying absolutely still.
That must have been his plan.
Where the hell are you?
You can't hide forever.
Show yourself, Jotaro!
I'm right here.
I see.
I didn't realize you'd slink so close.
If I hadn't had the foresight to
protect myself with this water shield,
you would have already knocked me out from behind.
I suppose I should count myself
lucky it makes for such a good defense.
Given that we're now in such close proximity,
I no longer need this cane to hear you.
However, I will require its use when I return home.
Iggy. Iggy.
Iggy.
Iggy. Iggy. Iggy.
Iggy!
Ora!
It's hard to believe, but you
actually managed to knock off my hat.
You can relax a little. I was holding back.
You're not going to die.
What the?!
Why the hell would you use your stand to...
Explain. Why did you do it?!
Jotaro...
You... you thought you could...
You thought you could manipulate me
and force me to tell you information
regarding the other eight stand users, didn't you?
I'm very well aware...
That Joseph Joestar's hermit purple...
Can view into the minds of others.
You'll never get inside my head,
and I'll never tell you anything
that you could use against my master.
Dio.
I don't understand why you're so loyal to him.
Are you honestly telling me that you'd die for him?
Jotaro, you're right.
You don't understand.
Fear of death holds no place in my heart.
Because of the power of my stand,
I've always been able to live a life unencumbered
by such inconsequential fears like death.
I could always win any fight.
I could have and do whatever I wanted.
Killing and stealing were absolutely meaningless to me.
You should talk to the mutt about it.
I'm sure he knows how I feel.
Dio was the first person
who was able to look deep within
my soul and find something more.
He was the one who gave me a desire to live.
That glorious force of nature...
He was so strong, so wise, so beautiful.
He was the one and only person in my
life to ever see a purpose for my existence.
I waited such a long time for an opportunity to meet him.
I will gladly die for my master's sake.
But no matter what, I refuse to do
anything that would disappoint him.
And after all, evil or not,
a scoundrel needs someone to put his faith in.
I'll tell you this before I go.
You should know that my name is N'doul,
and my stand hails from Egypt,
the birthplace of the tarot.
It's referred to as one of the nine
gods of Egypt, Geb of the great ennead.
We call it the god of the earth.
Nine Egyptian gods?
What does that mean?!
Sorry, but I'll only tell you about my stand.
It's only fair, since you're
the one who ended up stopping me.
But info on my compatriots goes with me to my grave.
Dio brainwashes people like a cult leader.
Just who is this guy, exactly?
And what's this crap about the nine gods of Egypt?
It's all a mystery...
But for now, we just have to keep moving forward.
Hey, you don't have to be defensive.
It's not like I'm angry with you or anything.
Makes sense you'd be pissed.
I doubt you wanted to be dragged out into
the desert and forced into some human crap.
Your position must suck ass.
No one can blame you for being upset.
Iggy, here. You want some gum?
Would you calm down already?
I'm trying to apologize.
Take it.
Good grief.
That dog is a pain in the ass.
You can stay out here in the desert for all I care.
Iggy.
Hmm?
Huh. Well, what do you know?
You went back and fetched my hat for me.
Maybe you're not so bad after all.
Thanks.
You put gum in here?
You good-for-nothing, little...
You're no ordinary mutt.
Hey!
Jotaro!
Huh?
Are you all right?
Good grief.
Ah, sweet! Hey, there. Is that a
comic book you're reading, little man?
I've never seen one here.
So Egyptians read comics just like the rest of us.
You want some mini doughnuts?
Hey, mind if I see your comic book?
If you'll let me, I promise I'll be super careful with it.
I'm a comic book artist who's searching for inspiration.
Nothing gets me jazzed up more than
checking out rare books and comics.
Let me borrow it, and you can use my binoculars.
Hmm?
What the? How peculiar.
The story's about these two eerie-looking brothers?
I don't see the creator's name.
Wow!
These are all such bizarre drawings.
But this is fantastic print quality,
not to mention it's in full color!
"There once lived two brothers who got along very well."
"'My name is Zenyatta.'"
"'My name is Mondatta.'"
"Mondatta, the younger brother, was very shy"
"and wouldn't do anything unless Zenyatta was with him."
"He was always alone."
"One day, while his big brother Zenyatta was away,
"Mondatta met a kind traveler near the side of the road.
"He gave Mondatta yummy snacks
and let him use his binoculars.
Mondatta had more fun than he'd had in a long time."
"'Oh, it's 10:30!'"
"But unfortunately the very kind traveler
was impaled on a telephone
pole and died a horrific death."
Quite a weird comic you've got.
Is this comic especially popular in this place?
If you ask me, it's really strange.
The other pages are all blank.
It's like they forgot to print the rest.
Must be a dud.
But somehow I feel as though I have a
connection to it. It's totally pulled me in.
This is gonna sound crazy, but would it be
possible for me to buy this book from you?
It's not for sale!
Huh?
Are you deaf or somethin'?
My bro's book's not for sale!
Now get out of my sight.
This kid is your brother?
I won't tell you again!
Hey, what have I told you about talking to strangers?
There's lots of bad people roaming
the world these days, you know?
Last call!
The bus for Aswan is getting ready to depart!
That's us.
They're on their way to the hospital in Aswan to
drop off their friend and have his injuries treated.
Hmm?
Ah. You don't say?
If that's how it is,
we'll just have to wait for the next bus.