Before we get things started,
there's something I wanna check.
How about you go ahead and shuffle those cards?
And shuffled, they are.
What, pray tell, do you have in mind next?
Now draw a card from the deck.
Which one it is doesn't really
make a whole lot of difference,
but don't show anyone.
Very well.
And now I'll call it.
It's the six of hearts.
Next, I think I'll name the cards from the top down.
Five of spades, queen of diamonds,
Jack of spades, ace of hearts,
seven of diamonds, plus the six of clubs,
king of clubs, and two of diamonds.
He guessed them all!
And that's after D'arby shuffled the deck!
How did you do that?!
I could rattle off the entire deck if I wanted to.
Remember my request from earlier?
While you were shuffling the cards, Star
Platinum was busy memorizing their order in the deck.
Quite the interesting strategy.
That said, defeating your plan
is a simple matter of shuffling the cards in
a manner that obstructs your vision of them.
Are you that dense?
Cheating is gonna be damn near impossible
as long as you have me as an opponent.
Just somethin' I thought you should be aware of.
Okay.
The security seal.
An unbroken seal is an irrefutable confirmation
that the deck has not been tampered with in any way.
Well, there's only one joker here.
Don't see anything unusual.
It's a normal deck.
The page number is 538.
540. No, page 556.
I've still got it.
My ability to discern page
numbers by touch is as sharp as ever.
It's true that Jotaro's Star
Platinum has incredible visual prowess,
but I can remember the placement of
anything simply through the use of touch.
Shuffle them all you want. I still
know the exact location of every card.
Okay, open the game.
Looks like it's the ten of hearts.
I drew the seven of cubs.
Then it seems like I'll be dealing.
All right.
I need to shuffle so Star Platinum can't see.
If you would cut the deck...
Thank you, and now I'll deal.
One for Jotaro. One for me.
Huh? I-I don't understand!
What happened?!
Jotaro, his finger!
Why the devil would you use Star
Platinum to break D'arby's finger?
Like I said,
you're not gonna cheat while you're playing against me.
Huh? He tried to cheat?
But he was only dealing the cards, wasn't he?
I didn't notice him do anything suspicious.
That's what he wanted us to think, but
take a good look at the cards in his left hand.
Ahh! I see now!
The second card is sticking out.
That's the card he tried to deal me.
The entire time, he was pretending to deal the top card,
but the truth is he was dealing
me the second card from the top.
That being the case,
it means the top card would have gone to him.
If he'd gotten his hands on it,
the cheating bastard would have had a total of three tens.
This maneuver is known as the second deal,
a devious sleight-of-hand technique
involving the dealer throwing out
the second card in the deck,
instead of dealing the top card as one would expect.
When the technique is executed by a professional,
the cheat is almost undetectable to the naked eye.
And if that wasn't enough,
D'arby can discern the location
of every card in the deck by touch.
You brutish imbecile! How dare you break my finger?
I was playing nice with that attack.
You should count yourself lucky I didn't rip it off.
Ah, good grief.
I guess I can't let you cut the deck anymore.
Someone else is gonna do it from now on.
That boy on the hill looks up to the job.
Have it your way.
Hey, Avdol, ask him over.
Right away.
Most impressive.
Hmm?
Successful cheating requires the element of surprise,
and it takes more than sharp eyes to prevent that.
It appears I underestimated you,
as you saw through my second deal.
I'll accept my fractured finger as proper punishment.
But from here on, I'll devote my full
concentration to winning the game, Jotaro.
I've not done so since my
colossal gamble on may 17, 1986.
I was playing against a Japanese
man known as Shozo Mayama.
As the Victor, my spoils included
his eight Tokyo properties and his soul.
I will say this for Mayama.
Wealth didn't dull his gambler's instincts.
It's only fair that I warn you
I'm not here on behalf of lord Dio!
I am here due to the simple fact that I am a born gambler!
W-What do you think you're doing?
Those souls are Mr. Joestar's and Polnareff's!
I've done nothing more than split
their souls into six chips each.
I'm sure you know this, but in poker,
if you're on the verge of losing,
it's perfectly acceptable to fold.
However, if you use up all the chips for the ante,
there's no way to bet, and the game doesn't work.
To put it plainly, winning back six chips is the
equivalent of winning the soul of one of your friends.
Make sense?
All right then, Jotaro.
If you still want to play, you'll have
the opportunity to win back the chips,
but before that, I need to hear you say the words.
With pleasure.
I'll bet my soul on the game's outcome.
Okay.
Jotaro!
The pure white chips in front of you
are a physical representation of your soul.
Once I've procured all six of those chips,
your soul will be added to my collection.
For my opening action, I shall
bet one chip of Polnareff's soul.
Let's begin.
When beginning a new game of poker,
each player is dealt a total of five cards.
Players can improve their hand by swapping out cards.
Though it seems straightforward on the surface,
it's the betting aspect that makes poker
a game of determination and psychology.
Now then, what to do?
Ah, I think I'll raise.
Jotaro, you should bear in mind that
those six chips beside you are your soul.
Make sure you think carefully before making a move.
Eh?
Listen.
It's okay if you don't understand what's going on.
Don't worry yourself.
You just focus your attention on
cutting and dealing the cards, all right?
Uh, mm.
Give me three cards.
Would you look at that? Such a serious glare.
Behind it must be an outstanding hand.
I suppose I'll play it safe for
now and bet one more Polnareff.
Call, one.
If you don't fold, you'll need three
chips per game, at the very least.
All right, bring it on, Jotaro.
Two pair, with eights and nines.
Hmm.
That's too bad.
Two pair, Jacks and queens.
Oh, no!
My, that was a close one.
I was on the verge of a crushing defeat.
But as it stands...
H-he only has three left.
Jotaro, what are you...
Okay, next game. Deal the cards.
You should be careful what you wish for.
The next game may well be your last.
I'll change one card.
Huh?
What's the problem, Jotaro?
Hurry up, and check your hand so you can make
a decision as to whether you'll change or fold.
Hey, Jotaro?
No, it's fine.
These cards will do.
Wha?!
Eh?
So sorry. Come again?
There must be some confusion.
Perhaps I misheard you.
I could have sworn I heard you say, "these cards will do."
No, you heard right. I'm fine with these cards.
I'll play the round with this hand.
Obviously!
What I'm trying to ask is do you intend to play
those cards without so much as glancing at them?!
These cards will do.
Enough subterfuge!
Answer me!
How can you play a round with any sort of confidence
if you don't even look at the cards in your hand?!
Need a favor.
You in?
Favor?
Of course, but answer something first.
Why are you hellbent on not looking at your cards?
Damn it, Jotaro! I demand that you answer me!
Let's see now. Raise you another two.
And while I'm at it, I'll throw in Avdol's soul.
Argh! What?!
I admit you're an impressive opponent, D'arby.
Sure, you're no match for our stands physically,
but under pressure, you can
be amazingly calm and clever.
Suffice it to say, I'm not
much in terms of being a gambler.
It'd be easy for you to read me like a book,
so I could never defeat someone like you,
but I have the utmost confidence in Jotaro.
I don't know why he won't look at his cards,
but that's none of my concern.
If he asks for my soul, I won't
hesitate to put my life on the line.
My soul is in Jotaro's more than capable hands.
So that's how we're playing this.
It's become apparent that the two of you have
succumbed to the pressure of our little game.
You there, I believe you owe me another card.
Hurry, and deal me.
Y-yes, sir.
Hmm.
I dealt just as you asked, master D'arby.
His hand is worthless. There's no doubt about it.
My skills as a dealer never fail.
You've won. I know you have.
Jotaro's under the assumption
the boy has nothing to do with this,
but little does he know everyone in this cafe
and within sight of this place works for me...
Even the bartender and those men.
No matter what, I can't fail,
as my directive is to make sure Jotaro's hand is weak.
Still, not looking at the cards was a bold move.
He caught me by surprise, albeit briefly.
It's clearly a bluff. How dare he bluff against me?
Does the fool really think I'll lie down and fold?
Hah! Very well.
If that's your game,
I'll match you with six polnareffs, and...
I raise you Joseph's soul.
What do you think? 15 chips total.
What?! Hold on a minute!
That's not fair! How can you raise your
ante when Jotaro doesn't have any more chips?
He's out of chips, you say?
There's an easy way to fix that.
What do you mean?
Rectifying your chip conundrum is simple
as long as my stand has a written contract.
Once the deal is done, it'll
have carte Blanche to take a soul.
And exactly whose soul are you talking about?!
Kakyoin's in the hospital.
Why don't you simply bet his soul?
What?!
Panic, fool.
Show me your doubt and fear.
Let me see you lose that cool composure.
How dare he try to bluff me?
After I'm finished with him, that poker face
will be a contorted ball of anguish and misery.
Sounds like a plan.
I'll see your bet with Kakyoin's soul.
Wait! Jotaro, you can't!
Betting a man's soul without his knowledge is so uncouth!
Well, it is kinda selfish.
Hey, Jotaro, what did you just do?!
What did I just do? What do you mean by that?
You lit a cigare...
What's wrong with you?
Not feeling well or something?
Impertinent...
Why is he so confident?
Could he have...
Could he have used Star Platinum
to swap the cards without my knowing?
Stupid brat.
What are you thinking?
Don't look at me with that worried grimace
if Jotaro finds out you work for me, I'll murder you.
Compose yourself. I have four kings.
The only hands that could beat me are four aces,
a straight flush, or a joker-led five of a kind.
In order to get his mitts on any of those hands,
Jotaro would have to switch all five cards,
a challenge, indeed.
With Star Platinum's speed, there's a
chance he could have switched a card,
But five?
Could he really do that right under my nose? Impossible.
There's no way I could have missed him replacing all five.
I'm the great D'arby, the king of
games, master at the art of gambling.
I've had enough of this, Jotaro.
Your time has come.
He lit that cigarette to psych me out,
so now I know he's bluffing.
Ah, you're kidding me?!
You got a drink, too?!
When did you have a chance to...
You bastard! How dare you make fun of me?!
Let's finish this!
My hand is unbeata...
Hold it!
Why are you jumping the gun
when I haven't raised the pot yet?
Raise the pot?! No!
You don't have anything to raise it with!
That's where you're wrong.
I'll raise you with my mother's soul.
What?!
Are you out of your mind?!
Jotaro, why would you bet your mother's soul?!
The entire reason I came to Egypt in
the first place was to save my mother,
so if I end up losing here, she'll die anyway.
She won't mind if I bet her soul.
So then, D'arby, for your sake, I hope you have
something to bet that matches my mother's soul.
I know.
For your ante,
I want you to tell me the secret of Dio's stand.
Judging from his reaction,
he indeed knows Dio's secret.
Unfortunately for him,
Dio doesn't take treason sitting down.
If he tells us the information we want to know,
he's as good as dead.
Jotaro,
if you're confident enough to bet your mother's soul,
you're sure your hand will win, aren't you?
You wouldn't let us down, would you?
You've got the winning hand, right?
Jotaro?!
Come on!
Are you gonna call my bluff or fold?!
Decision time! Spit it out already!
D'arby!
I'll say it.
I'll say it, damn it!
I'll say it!
I'm the world's greatest gambler!
I can do this. I'll call!
Call, call, call, call, call,
call, call, call, call.
I'm going to call!
Ca...
C-c-c-c-c-ca... ca...
C-c...
I can't do it! I'm petrified!
I'm too terrified to say the words!
C-c-c-ca...
I... I can't... I can't breathe.
C-c-c-c...
Hmph.
Ca...
That's unbelievable!
His eyes rolled into the back of his head!
How is it possible for someone to
faint while they're on their feet?
He's completely lost it.
The pressure was too much.
Mr. Joestar and Polnareff's souls are
returning to their bodies! Thank heavens.
Mentally, he's already forfeited the game.
Deep down, he knew he had lost.
That's why the souls were released.
F-four kings?!
Are you telling me he had four kings all along?
Jotaro, I have to know what cards you
had in your hand to inspire such confidence.
Like I thought...
Your hand was shit, absolute shit!
Even with Star Platinum's incredible speed,
he wouldn't have been able to swap cards
in front of an expert gambler like D'arby.
It's a good thing my bluff and intimidation worked so well
with such a worthless hand.
Good grief. Had I known it was
this crappy, I would have freaked.
What? What do you mean you'd have freaked?!
Jotaro, don't tell me
that you bet our souls on that worthless hand!
Eh?
It would appear as though his
collection of souls has been released.
Come on, everyone! Let's play a game of mahjong!
Backgammon is a lot of fun, too!
Or we could play a game of
dice, even though I don't have any!
D'arby of the Osiris stand, retired.
I doubt that we'll be able to pry
Dio's secret out of him in this state.
That's true. He was a formidable opponent.
It's humbling to admit this, but he
almost took us all out singlehandedly.
The guy was a force to be reckoned with.
Indeed, he was a fierce adversary.
I feel like death warmed over.
Well, I guess we can't be the heroes in every episode.