Ponder this.
What walks on four legs in the morning,
two during midday, and three in the evening?
So goes the riddle of the Sphinx,
the legendary guardian of the pyramids.
The answer: Man.
Travelers who answer the riddle incorrectly
are devoured by the ravenous Sphinx.
Now 30,000 kilometers from Japan,
Jotaro and crew have finally
reached their destination, Cairo.
Cairo is massive.
It's in our best interest to
systematically search the city,
working our way toward the center.
We're finally here.
Jotaro and the others have reached Cairo.
However, before the team can reach Dio,
they must first navigate their way through
the many "sphinxes" that stand before them.
Hmm.
Very nice to meet you gentlemen.
What'll you have to drink?
There's something we'd like to ask you.
My associates and I are trying to locate this building.
Any idea where it is?
Joseph and the others were utterly exhausted.
They had been searching for the building in
the photograph ever since their arrival in Cairo.
Taken with Joseph's psychic photography,
the image revealed Dio's whereabouts.
Dio had recently moved to a new hideout,
and the Speedwagon foundation couldn't find him.
Where was Dio hiding?
Failure to locate him as soon as
possible would spell certain doom for Holly.
I'm sorry, stranger,
but this is a cafe.
You should order a drink before asking questions.
Then iced teas, four of 'em.
Hmm.
Never seen the place.
Cairo is a city of six million,
so there must be at least two or three million buildings.
How are we gonna find him?
We know he's here.
There must be someone who can help us.
This is the building, huh?
This picture doesn't tell me anything.
Sorry, man, but it doesn't look familiar.
I see. Sorry to bother you.
Let's go. We'll try somewhere else.
I happen to know where your little building is located.
To be honest with you, I'm quite familiar with it.
W-was that you?
Were you the one who said that?
Do you actually know where the building is?
Yes.
Huh?
The exact location of the building in question
is information readily available to me.
Are you serious? That's incredible!
What remarkable news!
Amazing! What are the odds that we would stumble
upon someone who knows exactly where the building is?
Well, don't keep us in suspense.
Where's it located?
Are you really expecting something for nothing?
Eh, yes, you bring up a good point.
My apologies. £10 for your help?
Now, then, where is it?
Hmm?
Thing is, I'm something of a gambling man.
I've been known to be a sucker for cheap thrills,
and some would even go so far as to say I'm an addict.
However, when all's said and done,
gambling's how I make my living.
Tell me, any of you boys like to gamble?
I'm not sure I fully understand
what you're trying to get at.
I thought I'd laid it out plainly.
If you don't like gambling, then say so.
For the last time, I have no
idea where you're going with this.
Oh, all right. What I'm asking is if you and
your friends would like to play a little game.
Win, and I'll tell you the location of your building.
It's as simple as that.
A bet?
Look, friend, I'm as lucky as the next guy, but I'm
afraid that we don't have time for poker right now.
If I throw in another £20, will you tell us?
No need to worry.
A bet can be anything, after all.
It won't take very long.
For example, take a look at that wall over there.
Do you see that cat?
So two pieces of dried fish.
Question is, which of the two will the cat eat first,
the right one or the left one?
I must say there's something
thrilling about its simplicity.
Hey!
I've had just about enough of your games,
so take the money, and tell us
what we wanna know, you bastard!
Take it down a notch, Polnareff.
That's not the way you ask someone for a favor.
Fine! If it'll make you shut up, I'll take the bet!
The cat'll choose the piece of fish on the right!
Okay. Now it's getting interesting.
I'll be placing my bet on the left.
Polnareff...
Say, Jotaro, are you getting a strange feeling from him?
I am. He might be an enemy stand user,
that, or he could just be a compulsive gambler.
If he does anything at all that seems suspicious,
you should immediately attack him with star platinum.
Understood.
Let's say I lose.
It's fairly obvious that I'll
owe you a hefty amount of money,
so would £100 do?
I've no use for money,
but what would you say to giving me your soul?
That should do just fine.
Huh?!
Ugh! Now the bastard thinks he's a comedian.
I wish we could get the hell out
of here and away from this freak.
Well?
Yeah, yeah, that's fine with me.
We'll do things your way.
Ah, it appears the cat has taken notice of the fish.
Like I thought.
Hah! He's going after the one on the right.
If I were a cat, I'd pick the bigger piece of meat,
and lucky for me, that's the one on the right!
And there you have it.
Our feline friend took the left, then the right, then ran.
I win this round, gentlemen.
Boy, you've outdone yourself this time, Polnareff.
I hope you're thrilled.
How exactly are we going to get the information
on the building's whereabouts out of him now?
Well, if there's nothing else, as
per our agreement, it's time to pay up.
Huh? Pay? With what?
Your soul, of course.
Surely you didn't forget about our wager, Polnareff.
I want your soul,
as I'm a stand user who prides himself on stealing them.
I find that it's far easier to take a
person's soul if they lose it in a bet,
which is when my stand's power
activates and collects what's mine.
What the hell?!
My god, what's happening?!
Polnareff!
Now, now, I wouldn't be so
quick to lash out if I were you.
I know you desperately want to kill me, but
if I die, Polnareff will meet the same end.
Polnareff!
No. No!
H-he has no pulse.
He's dead! Polnareff is dead!
Polnareff!
Have a look.
Polnareff's soul resides in this.
Now lord Dio has one less meddlesome
fool to interfere with his plans,
and what a fool he was.
Please allow me to introduce myself.
My name is D'arby, d-a-r-b-y.
There's an apostrophe after the "d."
Gambler, stealer of defeated souls,
and user of the Osiris stand.
I believe you've had the pleasure of meeting my cat.
What is this, you bastard?!
You call that a bet?
How dare you, you vile, cheating son of a...
A cheater, you say?
Have you considered Polnareff lost because he
lacked insight to consider all the possibilities?
Hear me out.
Gambling is nothing more than a simple
analogy for man's relationship with his brethren,
a dance of deception where the loser cries first.
Are you planning to kill me
with your own two hands, Avdol?
Go right ahead, if you don't mind
your friend's soul being lost forever.
The choice is completely up to you.
Know this. We're not just going to
let you waltz out of here in one piece.
Try to think back to September 22, 1984, 11:15 P.M.
Remember what you were doing during that time and date?
What does that even mean?!
I remember it quite clearly.
I was in California gambling against an American
that went by the name of Stephen Moor.
He said the same thing you just said a moment ago...
But now he's singing a more silent tune.
The chip below him is his father,
and the one next to him is his wife.
If you want Polnareff's soul back,
you have no choice but to continue our game.
How much is his life worth to you?
This man is evil incarnate.
So that's it. He wants to capture our souls.
So what's it gonna be?
You can leave if you're too scared to play.
I'll hold Polnareff here for safekeeping.
Why don't you fine gentlemen have
a drink and think things over a bit?
Care for a piece of chocolate?
Hmm?
What is this, Mr. Joestar?
What are you trying to accomplish?
I'm curious.
Do you have any idea what surface tension is, Barbie?
My name's D'arby. You know it's not Barbie.
And I assume you're referring to how the liquor
appears to almost overflow, but stays in the glass.
So is there a point to all this build-up?
We're playing a game.
The rules are simple: We take
turns dropping coins into the glass.
Whoever makes the liquor spill loses.
Old man...
Mr. Joestar, you're not going to...
Exactly right! I'm going to bet my soul!
Okay.
You've got to be kidding!
You can't go through with it, Mr. Joestar!
This man is a good-for-nothing cheater!
He won't cheat me this time
I decided on the rules myself, so I'll be fine.
Jotaro, you watch for funny business.
Okay.
Since you're so determined, I'll accept your conditions.
However, before we begin,
would you mind if I inspect the glass and coins?
Sure. Have at it.
You have the right to ensure
that I'm playing on the up and up.
Hmm. Hmm.
A question...
What guarantee do I have that you'll
return Polnareff's soul if you lose the game?
You've my word as a gambler that I'll keep my promise.
If I lose, I assure you that I will pay in full,
but I won't lose.
Well, in that case, you can go first.
Go ahead, and drop a coin in.
Please, stop!
Just leave everything to me.
The old coin-and-glass trick is one of my specialties.
Surface tension is a surprisingly strong force.
There's room for at least
eight or nine coins in the glass.
I just have to stay calm and
make sure my fingers don't shake.
Is it all right if I drop in
more than one coin at the same time?
As long as they all go in at once.
Well, then...
What? Five coins?!
Hey, that'll create a wave on the surface.
Quiet, please.
Take your hands off the table.
It looks like it's your turn.
It takes nerves of steel to put in five coins at once.
I think I'll go with one coin. It's too close to call.
Hmm?
Typical old man.
He's squeezing a cotton ball between his
finger and the coin to leak liquid into the glass.
So that's how he's gonna make the glass overflow.
And he told me to watch for cheating?
Clever bastard. Not bad.
The glass has reached its limit.
One more coin, and the booze will spill.
Victory is mine. Ha ha! It's like he said.
We'll see which dance partner cries first.
Ooh, man, that was a close one.
I thought it was gonna spill for sure.
Well, it's your turn. Good luck, Obi.
It's D'arby. Don't make me say it again.
I told you my name is D'arby. Understand?
Not Obi, not Barbie!
Hmm? Apologies.
He's screwing up his name on purpose to
get him riled up and throw off his game.
I gotta hand it to the old man. He's a natural.
So what do you say we keep playing?
I believe it's your turn to drop a coin in, D'arby.
The shadow makes it difficult to see from here.
I'll lower the coin in from the right side of the table.
Drop it in from whatever angle you'd like.
What he doesn't know is the glass is
already at its limit thanks to my little trick.
There's no way the liquid could take another coin.
Even the slightest touch will cause it to spill over.
You're probably thinking the glass has reached its limit,
that dropping in another coin would be impossible.
Well, you'd be wrong about that.
There's no way! How the hell did he do that?!
Why didn't it spill over?!
Your question's confusing.
What do you mean, why didn't it spill?
You saw the result with your own eyes.
As far as I know, he didn't do anything devious.
I was watching him with Star Platinum.
It's hard to believe, but he
dropped it in fair and square.
There's no doubt.
But how did he do it?
I'm positive I added enough liquid to the
glass that one more coin would make it spill.
I don't get it. There's no way it shouldn't have spilled.
What's going on?
Make your move. It's your turn, Joestar.
Hurry it up already,
or are you trying to wait until it evaporates?
No, no, this can't be happening.
Mr. Joestar!
Deep in his heart of hearts, Joestar
had already come to the realization
that he'd lost this game.
That's why his soul emerged so easily.
I, D'arby, have won this bet like all the others.
Polnareff, I... I failed you.
Holly, I'm so sorry, my beautiful
girl, but daddy's let you down.
Mr. Joestar!
Old man, no!
Two down.
Now let's continue where we left off,
that is unless you two have decided to abandon your
friends and slink away with your tails between your legs.
You bastard!
You don't get it, do you?
I keep trying to tell you that if you take my life,
your friends will die with me.
Damn you!
Avdol, stand down!
Hey, if you're gonna cause trouble,
then I'm gonna have to ask you to lea...
Shut your mouth, and stay out of this!
Right!
You've noticed it too late, Jotaro.
Eh, what? Something's wrong with the glass?
This is the reason the coin
didn't make the booze spill over.
If you look at the bottom of the glass, you'll
see that there's a tiny bit of chocolate on it.
He must have found a way to stick it on
when he was inspecting the glass and
coins at the very beginning of the game.
Surely you know the rules by now.
It doesn't count as cheating if
you never get caught in the act.
What? I don't understand.
How could a piece of chocolate
allow him to drop in an extra coin?
Well, at this point, it's melted,
but it used to be a solid chunk
stuck to the bottom of the glass,
just enough to slightly tilt the glass, but
not quite enough for us to notice the change.
Once the chocolate started to melt,
the glass came to be level with the table.
With the glass leveled out, the booze began to settle,
which made enough room for another coin.
W-What the hell?!
B-but that doesn't make any sense!
How could he have known the chocolate
would melt right when he needed it to?
He influenced things by using the sun.
It slipped my notice.
When he moved to the right side of the table, he
allowed the sun to shine directly onto the chocolate,
thereby melting it.
All right.
D'arby, get your cards, 'cause we're playin' my game.
Hope you're ready for some poker.
Eh?
Say what?!
Jotaro!
Interesting.
You couldn't have possibly known this,
but poker is my absolute favorite game.
Are you out of your mind?!
You're playing poker with a
man who outsmarted Mr. Joestar.
It's too dangerous!
Yeah, I know.
Even though he doesn't use physical strength,
he's the most dangerous stand user we've ever faced.
So now...
There's no turning back, and we're playing for keeps.