Ah, looks like new pages are appearing.
I wonder what'll happen next.
The brothers delayed their trip
and took a bus four hours later,
so they managed to avoid getting into an accident. Yippee!
What adventures awaited them now?
Once in Aswan, they made their discovery.
"Oh. There they are,
"the five bad guys," cried the brothers.
But the brothers wondered,
"what could they be talking about?"
The bad guys seemed so worried.
Hmm. I think that's them.
Little did they know they had drunk poison tea.
Brother, check it out.
Earth to big bro?
Huh?
So I just have to poison them.
Listen, little bro,
you and I are practically invincible together.
Between your clairvoyant comic stand
and my face stand's transformative ability,
no one can get in our way!
Those guys are as good as dead.
We possess the cards known as Thoth, the god of writing,
and Khnum, god of creation,
and together we are the bestest brothers ever!
It's here in this cafe.
Right at that table.
That's where those guys will drink their poison tea.
Yeah, my stand, Thoth, the god of writing,
has never been wrong about
anything when it comes to predictions.
Well, are they gonna pull through?
Luckily, Avdol's major arteries weren't
damaged, so he'll probably be released by tomorrow.
But, Kakyoin, on the other hand, has
serious injuries that need to be treated.
There's a chance he could go blind.
That's a raw deal.
I hate to say it, but if his condition doesn't
improve soon, we might have to leave him behind.
Hmm?
Hey, since there are so many cafes
nearby, how 'bout we get ourselves a drink?
That's a great idea.
Which one did you have in mind?
Hmm.
There you have it. The cigarette has spoken.
Hello, there.
Tell me, sirs, how may I be of service?
Well, tea sounds good right about now.
Same.
Right, so three teas.
Be back in a jiffy.
Actually, scratch that order, if you would.
Huh?
Hear me out.
We're in enemy territory here.
This is Dio's dominion, and since we don't know
when enemies will attack, we have to be cautious.
If we let our guard down even for
a second, someone could poison us.
From this point on, we're only
drinking from bottles and cans.
Come on. Are you serious?
Completely. Hey, there, you can forget
the tea, and bring us colas instead.
Huh?
Cola?!
That's right. Something wrong?
Not at all. Okay, three colas coming up.
Hmm?
I'll just go and grab them.
Oh, by the way, if you don't
mind, we'll open them ourselves,
and to make sure we're not
falling victim to any funny business,
give us the third, fourth, and
fifth ones from the far-right side.
Now they want unopened colas?
How am I supposed to put poison in those?
Was the prediction wrong? No, that can't be it.
My brother's comic is always right.
Damn it. I've got to get it together.
I just have to believe.
If I don't have absolute faith in
little bro, we won't stand a chance.
Yes, my predictions are foolproof, brother.
You in the apron, is this warm
cola your idea of a cold drink?
You must assume I'm a real halfwit or something
to think I'd pay for this excuse of a beverage.
Wait. What? The cola's really not cold?
Sorry about the hassle. The fridge is down, so...
Hey, don't you think you're being a little paranoid?
Let's say, for the sake of
argument, that guy was our enemy
and he was trying his damnedest to
slip a little poison into our drinks.
How would he have known to come to this exact cafe?
I mean, this city's not lacking in places to get a drink,
and I chose this one on a whim.
I'd understand if this were the
only cafe, but there are tons of 'em.
My point is we can't be too careful around here.
Well, if you're that worried,
let's go somewhere else then,
maybe the place across the street?
Mm.
Fire!
What do I do? My cafe is on fire!
Some fool left a burning cigarette
in the road, and it ignited the trash.
Oh, boy.
You know what?
I think we'll take those teas after all.
Yes, we did it.
Ah, zut alors.
What kind of jerk would toss
a lit cigarette near the trash?
Really, the nerve of some people.
Finally, they're drinking it.
Drink it. Drink it. Drink it until it's gone.
They drank it!
A dog just took my cake.
Who the hell brought a mangy mutt to a freakin' cafe?
Iggy.
Whose dog is this?!
Will somebody please get this dog outta here?!
Damn it, Iggy!
Get back here, you fleabag!
Damn it!
They were just about to swallow the poison.
Dumb mutt.
So what the hell's supposed to happen next?
Well, thing is the page hasn't appeared yet.
Also, while off, it wasn't entirely wrong. Be patient.
Thoth only has the ability to see the near future,
so Patience is key.
Next time, then.
When the next premonition is
revealed, we'll use it to destroy them.
This is what we were meant to do.
Together, we're the bestest brothers ever, baby.
"'We failed to kill them because of that darn
dog.'" "'we were so close, ' fumed the brothers."
"The brothers were beside themselves
with anger, "'cause their plan failed,
"but the brothers didn't give up,
"and soon they decided to follow
the three guys and their dog.
"While following them, they met a
man who had a very annoying face,
"the kind of face that was just begging to be hit.
In fact, it was the kind of face the brothers hated."
I must have hated that face in a past life,
and a face like that deserves a knuckle sandwich.
"Even though he was a perfectly nice man,
big bro punched him anyway."
"Thus, the man with the bad face ran away"...
"But fortunately for them," "he
dropped a wallet full of money."
"'Yay. We're rich. Whoopee!' cried Mondatta."
What a dumb-ass.
Yeah, thanks to that smarmy-faced fool, we're rich.
Huh? Hey, brother, check it out.
The new page is coming.
Oh.
"The brothers continued their pursuit.
"The bad guys got in their car and hurried over to the
hospital "to check on their friends Avdol and Kakyoin.
"But they had no idea Zenyatta had made a bomb,
"placed it an orange, and planted it in the car.
"Jotaro was blown into a million pieces.
"His head was split in two,
and his blood was splattered everywhere!"
L-I-I-look how clearly the pictures in the comic came in.
I see!
It's true that my stand, Thoth,
can only see the near future,
and most would see that as a disadvantage, but... heh...
Once the prediction has been printed, it can't
be changed, no matter what anybody does, not ever.
We're gonna blow Jotaro to smithereens.
The bomb will detonate three seconds
after he sticks his finger in to peel it.
It's destiny.
This is the end.
There's no way out.
Hmm?
Who the hell is in our car?!
Do you recognize this bozo?
What? Isn't it Jotaro?
No.
Jotaro said he was going straight to the hospital.
Be careful.
Damn it.
Don't let him get away!
You've gotta be kidding.
It's Joestar and Polnareff.
Whoever you are, come out this instant!
What he said! Out of the car!
Quit your stalling, and get out of there already!
Make it snappy.
Hey, hey, what's the matter with you two?
It was me. Couldn't you tell?
Oh.
Oh, so it was you, Jotaro.
My stand, Khnum, gives me the power of transformation.
I can alter my height, weight,
and scent however I see fit.
I even used my hair to recreate this hat.
Wait. I don't get it.
Last I heard, you said you were
going to head straight for the hospital.
Huh? I did?
Ah, the hospital. I forgot something,
so I decided to come and get it.
Oh, that's right. I left my wallet in the car.
Good grief.
Jotaro, where's your school uniform?
Uh, uniform?
What's he talking about?
What school uniform?
Nothin' personal, friend, but that's
not really a good look on you. Heh.
Uh, ah, my outfit.
I mean uniform.
Well, it's actually at the dry cleaners.
I took it in for a wash, but then
I realized I didn't have any money.
Yeah, that'll convince them. I'm in the clear.
That so? All right then.
You can go ahead and hop in the car. Time to go.
Huh?
Oh, no, not the car.
Then, that would mean.
No, i-it can't be.
If I get into the car with this face,
that means the real Jotaro
won't be the one getting blown up.
Instead, it'll be me!
Shit.
You know, it's a beautiful day out,
so I think I'll go ahead and walk...
We don't have time to wait
for you to walk there, Jotaro.
Things'll go a lot faster if you just
get in the car and ride over with us.
Brother, you have to get out of there now!
Crap, this is bad.
I've got to undo my Jotaro disguise before it's too late.
If I don't,
I'll be the one who gets blown to bits instead!
That's it.
I just need to throw it away.
I'll covertly get rid of this one
and put another one in the car later
so it can blow up the real Jotaro, thereby saving my ass.
I did it.
What a relief.
I'm safe.
Hey, what do you know? It's Iggy.
He's chasing our car.
He's got an orange in his mouth.
Did you steal that, Iggy?
It'll make a nice gift for Kakyoin and Avdol.
Hmm?
Wha...
Yow!
Come again?
Everything okay? Never thought
I'd hear you say something like that.
Oh, really? That's weird. "Yow"?
You know, "yow."
Actually, I was pointing out
that there's a "cyow" over there.
A cow?
Man, you sure are acting pretty peculiar today, Jotaro.
You're usually a lot cooler.
I hate to say this, but I've gotta wonder.
You're not really a fake, are you, Jotaro?
Hmm.
G-good grief, Polnareff. What the
hell are you even talking about, man?
By the way, are we at the hospital yet?
Hey, Jotaro, I'm super bored, so
how about you show me that trick again?
Hmm. A trick? Which one is that?
What's he talking about?
The one you taught me a while back.
You know, this one here.
Hey, you've gotten a bit better at that, Polnareff.
Oh, that's the trick you were talking about.
Thank goodness. I know how to do that one.
It's risky, but I can pull it off.
Why didn't you say so from the
beginning? That's an easy one.
All right. In that case, do the
one with five cigarettes, then.
F-five cigarettes?
Hurry it up already, would
you? I wanna see the trick again.
Why is this happening to me?
Damn that Jotaro, and damn his stupid party tricks!
But if I don't at least try to do it,
they'll really think something is up.
They're already becoming more
suspicious of me by the minute.
And Polnareff, loathsome idiot that he is,
is seconds away from setting off the bomb.
All right, fine. Damn it.
I'll do it!
Have it your way. Five cigarettes.
That's the way. Now come on. Do the trick.
All right, it's now or never.
I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna do the trick, damn it.
Here goes nothing!
Hot.
H-hot. Hot.
I did it!
Hot damn, I did it!
Ah!
There. Did you see that? I did it!
A man can do anything when his life is on the line.
Here.
Last time, you did this super cool move
where you drank a bottle of juice
without putting the cigarettes out.
Come on. Drink up.
Aw, you blew it!
Jotaro, are you all right? Oh, my god!
Brother! Brother! Please, little bro,
make that prediction go away right now!
Tear up that page!
Sorry, big bro, but the prediction can't be changed.
Hurry, and go back to your regular self.
If you can undo the disguise, the
real Jotaro will get blown up instead.
I believe in you, brother.
Jotaro, I know we've said this already,
but you're acting really weird today.
It's nothing.
I just feel a little under the weather is all.
Hmm.
Eh?
Crap. This couldn't get any worse.
I know their type. Since I've put them on guard,
they're gonna interrogate me and realize I'm an imposter.
If they figure me out, they'll kill me,
and if I don't undo my disguise, I'll
blow up just like the prophecy said.
Ah?
That's it. I'll just pretend I'm sick and
make them let me out of the car to relieve myself.
Brilliant.
Jotaro, I couldn't help but notice
the way you're clasping your hands.
Aha! Are you aware you've got your
left thumb on top of the others?!
Well, are you?!
Hmph!
Damn it. I wasn't prepared for this.
Does Jotaro have a weird tic that causes him
to clasp his hands with his right thumb on top?
Who even notices something like that?
What am I gonna do?
That just proves beyond a shadow of a
doubt that you were a woman in a past life!
And since, unlike you, I always put my right thumb
on top, it proves that I was a man in my past life.
Wow, now how about that?
I always put my left thumb on top, as well.
Sorry, Mr. Joestar, but that proves
you, too, were a woman in a past life.
Says you. How does it prove anything?
How do thumbs factor into reincarnation?
That's so stupid.
Now I really do feel sick.
These rabid lunatics are driving me up the wall.
All right, I'll tell them I've got a stomachache.
Jotaro, what do you say we find out which
one of us can eat an orange the fastest?
Say what?
Hey, maybe you...
Stop it! Don't do that, you idiot!
Whoa there! What the hell are you doing, Jotaro?
What's going on with you today, Jotaro?
Oh, it's nothing, guys.
But this isn't like you at all.
I just don't think it's good for
you to eat that particular orange.
What's the problem with it?
Well, it's obvious, isn't it?
Who knows where the heck Iggy found that thing?
For all we know, he could have dug it out of the gutter.
You should eat a different one.
Thanks for caring, but it doesn't look
bruised or dirty, so I think I'll be fine.
I'll eat this one, and you can have one of those.
I can't wait to see the look on your face when I win.
Ow! The pain!
Huh?!
Hey, what's wrong?
Please, stop the car. I have to go to the bathroom.
Come on. Stop the car! Hurry!
Does your stomach really hurt that bad?
I can't hold it anymore!
Let me out! Let me out! I'll go behind that rock!
The hospital's right there. Just hang on.
No, no, go on ahead without me.
I'll catch up once I'm done. Ohh!
Not so fast, Jotaro.
Take this. It's...
Yes!
I did it! I can't believe I did it!
I actually managed to get out
of that metal deathtrap alive!
I'll go behind that rock and undo my disguise.
He brought up a good point.
Who knows where Iggy found this orange?
For all we know, it could have been lying in the gutter.
Do you wanna eat it?
Nah. You can toss it.
Success!
Now I can use Khnum's powers to transform back to normal.
After that, they'll get what's comin' to 'em,
and the Zenyatta Mondatta brothers will have won again.
We win.
Uh...
Are you kidding me?!
Huh? Did you hear that sound?
Just forget it. It was probably construction.
Oh! Big bro, are you okay?
Speak to me.
Hey, little bro.
I think we lost this battle bad, really bad.
No, big brother.
No, no way.
Those wannabes haven't beaten me and my stand Thoth yet.
I-I'll destroy them all, brother,
by myself, if I have to.
No, don't.
Don't do this, brother.
These guys aren't some rookies
you can push around. You'll die.
I've already decided, and I can beat them on my own.
I know I can.
You were always so shy.
You've really grown up, little bro.
I'm gonna kill 'em all.
What does the book of Thoth say next?
Huh?
This is them, all right!
They're the ones who punched me and
purloined my wallet while they were at it.
All right, men, beat them to a bloody pulp,
and I'll make sure you're rewarded handsomely.
It's him again!
I'm scared, brother!
This doesn't look good for us!
"Despite his intense, yet short-lived, burst of bravery."
"Mondatta would have to wait
a while to avenge his brother."
"But try not to lose heart, Mondatta.
Life is full of wonderful ups and terrible downs."
Huh?
Well, if it isn't Jotaro.
Hmm?
Hey, what took so long?
Forget that.
How'd you take a dump behind that rock so fast?
Huh?
I can't believe you got here before us.
You even found time to go to the dry cleaners.
What the hell are you two talking about?
Hey,
it's an ambulance.
Someone must be hurt.
Ah, man, that's unfortunate.
Hmm? Oranges, huh?
I was just getting thirsty.
Think I'll take one.
Huh?
What's this?
That man's clothes...
You recognize him?
Nope, can't say that I do.
Right. Let's go find out how Avdol and Kakyoin are doing.
"And so the brothers" eventually gave up on their mission.
"The battle was over, and
after all the chaos and the pain,
Jotaro and the others were none the wiser."
Ba-dum-tss.