Hmm?
You did say under the chin, right, Polnareff?
What the hell?!
Remember me, you fool?
I'm the Anubis stand you fought earlier.
Merde! What do I do now?
Goodbye! I'm gonna shave your jaw clean off!
Hmm?
Who... who the hell are you, really?!
And what have you done with the barber?!
Wait. Could it possibly be that
the sword is actually the stand?
Could it be controlling the barber?
So the guy at Kom Ombo wasn't a real stand user!
Polnareff!
But in the end, it doesn't matter.
I'm still way out of your league, buddy.
What?! How are you so strong?!
If you must know, I took the Liberty of
learning chariot's moves during our last fight.
I won't lose twice to the same adversary.
Do you understand me?!
That's it. You can do it.
Ah, come on!
You can't give up now.
You've almost got it!
Oh?
Polnareff and Jotaro,
they should have returned by now.
Polnareff, what's going on?
The barber's a stand user?
Stay back, Jotaro!
Th-the sword is the stand!
Trust me. It's too dangerous to try using
Star Platinum's bare fists against this blade.
The sword's sharp enough to slice through them.
This barber isn't the stand user, he's just a puppet!
And that's not even the worst part!
The stand's even stronger than it was before!
Bastard!
Whoa, there!
Too much for you?
I suppose I should be grateful you've
shown me the limits of your defense.
Most kind of you.
Now, then, let's see if you have
what it takes to survive my next attack,
shall we, Polnareff?
Polnareff!
His powers keep increasing with every strike!
I can't keep parrying forever!
Sooner or later, he's gonna get me!
Huh?
Now!
Take this!
How in the...
In case you haven't realized the obvious,
I know all your moves.
It doesn't matter who my wielder is.
As long as I've done battle with you at least once,
I never, ever,
never, ever, never, ever,
never, ever lose twice!
I'm not gonna win this without my rapier.
Oh, no!
Jotaro, help me out here!
Star platinum.
Hmm?
Ora!
Think that finished him off?
No. That punch was shallow,
even though it took just about everything I had.
Hey, Khan.
Shit.
Are you all right?
This guy's strong.
It's been quite a while now since
we've seen a stand like this one.
It only relies on strength.
Not bad, Star Platinum.
The rumors of your speed were true.
But now that I've seen it, I can easily defeat it.
Hey, Khan, what's wrong with you?
Stay back!
Your friend is being controlled!
If you don't wanna get sliced to
ribbons, go back inside, and hide!
We're in major trouble, Jotaro.
The more we fight this stand, the faster it gets,
and its next attack
will probably be its fastest and strongest yet.
We have to be ready for whatever this
glorified butter knife throws at us!
Move, Polnareff!
I'm the one it's really after!
Get out of there, Jotaro!
Die!
Ora!
Ah?!
What? With his bare hands?!
Ora!
Amazing. For him to take that great of a risk...
Now it's become abundantly clear.
The true source of Star Platinum's
strength isn't its speed or precision.
It's Jotaro's nerves of steel
and ability to make quick decisions.
Yes.
Now I know it for sure.
Is he dead?
Hold on a second, Jotaro. He's just knocked out!
Whatever you do, don't touch that sword.
You snapped it in half,
but the stand's powers might still be lingering.
It controls anyone who touches it while unsheathed.
Let's get the blade back inside without touching the hilt.
Now what?
If someone draws it again, we're done for.
This damn thing has already learned all of our abilities.
I don't think we're gonna get any second chances.
Why not toss it into the river
to rust at the bottom of the Nile?
The Nile, huh?
That sounds like a great plan to me.
Hold it! This is the police!
This is perfect timing!
This guy needs a hospital! I have
multiple reports of a brawl at a barber shop!
What are you doing with that sword?!
Huh?
Hand this weapon over immediately!
Hey, stop it, would you?!
Don't pull it out!
Polnareff!
No, damn it.
His eyes, that stare...
Polnareff is being controlled by the sword's spell.
Hey, you there! You drew the sword!
I drew the sword, did I?
Hmph. Officer, you should really be
more careful with your accusations,
since you call yourself a servant of the law.
Take it easy! What are you doing?
I'm simply attacking the culprit who unsheathed the sword!
I don't know who you are or where you're hiding,
but I think it's safe to say
Polnareff is under your control.
Come to think of it,
I've never had to fight against Polnareff before.
Hmm?
And I can't pull punches with chariot as an opponent.
If I'm not smart about this,
I could end up killing Polnareff.
As I said before, at this point, I've already
witnessed Star Platinum's entire repertoire of moves,
and if I've done battle with you once before,
then I will never lose again!
Ora!
Hey, now.
En garde!
His speed,
it's incredible!
He's getting fast enough to outpace me!
I have to find a way to stop that sword.
I'll catch it again.
It sped up!
This time...
I'll take your head!
Wha...
Ora!
His speed and power are overwhelming.
Without a doubt,
this is the fastest stand I've ever faced.
At the rate I'm going, this won't end well.
I have to fight Polnareff with everything I've got,
or I'm dead.
So you head-butted the sword after
you realized you couldn't catch my blade.
Honestly I didn't think you were
capable of something like that.
I almost had you.
But now...
I've acquired that skill as well.
Jotaro...
I can tell that you're thinking the only way
to survive is to kill your friend, Polnareff.
Even if you wanted to, it's
naive to think it'd be that easy.
Take a close look, Jotaro.
What I'm about to show you will
put an end to this once and for all.
So, let's see...
If you can beat this, Jotaro!
Feast your eyes on the silver chariot and Anubis
two-sword technique!
Damn it.
This extra sword,
coupled with his accelerating speed,
even Star Platinum won't last long.
What's the matter? Are you
feeling a little tired, Jotaro?!
I'll stop him before he kills me.
Star finger!
Huh?
My right arm is as light as a feather now.
Interesting. I guess that was an option.
Didn't see that coming, did you?!
Round two! Armor release!
You fool! Your ridiculous, "or a,
or a," is no match for two swords
wielded by two master swordsmen!
Your stomach is wide open!
I've got you now!
I did it!
I win!
Master Dio, I've exterminated Jotaro!
I, Anubis, have finally put him down!
Victory is mine!
Just forget it.
You're not going to be able to pull out that blade.
Give up already! I'm not sure
your tiny brain has realized it,
but I've surpassed Star Platinum.
And now the final thrust.
The final thrust?
Yes, precisely!
Once I slice open your bowels, master Dio will rejoice!
Please, stop this.
Don't drive the blade any further.
It... it'll be murder.
Nice try, but you won't get any mercy from me!
I can't wait to spill your guts!
Ora!
What the devil?!
You're breaking me! I have to pull free!
No! Stop!
Maybe I'm wrong,
but weren't you saying something about slicing me open?
I told you it'd be murder,
but the murder I was talking about was yours, friend.
You're a pretty easy target
when the sword isn't moving around.
Damn it, what a pain in the ass.
This was the toughest opponent I've faced.
That last attack took everything
I had in me and then some.
Luckily it was just enough to defeat him before he
could learn it like he did the rest of our attacks.
This is new.
I've never been so exhausted.
I have to find Avdol and the old man.
W-What in the world just happened?
The sword didn't possess me like
it did all the other guys, did it?
Yeah, it did,
but it's over now.
Forgive me.
Just get the old man and Avdol.
I'm too tired to walk.
Huh?
Wow, it's so shiny.
Now I've learned that trick.
My original stand user was the sword
Smith who forged me 500 years ago.
He may have perished centuries ago,
but I survive as a stand with no master.
Master Dio liberated me from the
gloomy shadows of a dusty museum.
And speaking of master Dio, his stand,
the world, is far more powerful than I.
That's why I pledged my undying loyalty.
Jotaro, I swear on my life...
I will murder you!
I know your strength, your speed.
You won't see it coming until it's too late to stop it!
I'll stab you in the back!
Now die, Jotaro!
What just happened?!
Son of a... I missed!
I was tripped by a dog?!
Where the hell did that mutt come from?!
Hey, Iggy, what are you eating?
Wait a second. Is that a nasty, old sucker?
Eating right off the ground again, you filthy mutt.
You've gotta be kidding! It's the Nile river!
Aah! No, this can't be happening!
What did I do to deserve this cruel fate?!
If I fall into the river, I'm done for! I'll rust away!
Somebody stop me!
Aah! Oh?!
Aha! I'm heading for a wall!
The wall will stop me!
Lucky me!
What the... shit!
I was so panicked about falling into the water
that I accidentally phased right through the wall!
I'm gonna fall in!
Yes, it's a ship!
I'm saved!
If I wedge into those planks, that
guy's curiosity will make him pull me out,
and then I'll take over his pathetic mind!
Once I'm safely back on dry land,
I'll use his body to take revenge on Jotaro!
What?! A cow is on board?!
Stop thrashing around! Hey, calm down!
Would you cool it, you stupid cow?!
I know! I'll take over the cow's mind!
Then it'll be a cinch...
I'm not gonna make it in time!
Hey, over there!
That cow's really rockin' the boat, don't you think?
Oh, good grief. Who gives a damn?
Just go and get the old man and Avdol, will you?
Help me!
Hey! Yoo-hoo!
Oh, fishies, look down here!
Come on. Swim over to me!
Hey, wait! Where are you going?
Hey, Mr. Crab, it's a pleasure to meet you.
Would you mind doing me a favor and taking me ashore?
I'll give you something yummy.
Wait, Mr. Crab! You just can't leave me here!
I'll be rusted through in a couple of days.
Please, help me.
Don't leave me here!
I'm so alone!
Stupid mutt.
What are you staring at?
There's nothing to eat over there, flea bag.
Why, you stinkin' little...
Merde!
What the hell have you been eating?!
Come on, Polnareff.
To think all of that happened without us.
You fought the Anubis stand, huh?
That must have been rough, Jotaro.
Yeah, was.
That's the last time I ever go anywhere with him.
Stop it already, you stupid mutt!
Get the hell off my face!
The average tourist to Egypt is mostly
unaware of the country's rich ethnic diversity.
For example, take this Egyptian
man wearing the traditional jellabiya
or this Egyptian Nubian,
and here is a Bedouin from Egypt's desert region.
This gentleman hails from India.
And as a random example, here's another Egyptian citizen.
Hey! That fox has got some smokin'-hot
legs that are out of this world.
I can't keep my eyes off her.
Wow! Those puppies'll pull you right in, you know.