Just as I thought,
Joseph's blood suits me well.
It's like it was meant to be mine
from the very beginning.
It's far more intense than anything I've ever felt before!
This sensation is absolutely incredible!
A century ago, this body belonged to Jonathan Joestar,
and now these hands have feasted
on the blood of his grandson, Joseph!
But it was you, Jotaro, who so thoughtfully led me here.
Your ancestor must be rolling in his grave.
You Joestars have always been a nuisance,
so I think the time has come to put you self-righteous
cretins in your proper place, beneath my boot!
In the end, Jotaro,
it would appear that the Joestars' destiny
is to facilitate my ascension to perfection!
Why, you...
Old man.
You have to stay calm.
From here on, no matter what
Dio does to me, keep your cool.
Focus. Tempting as it may be, never
allow yourself to succumb to anger.
Don't worry about my fate, Jotaro.
I've accepted that it was meant to be.
Wait a sec.
That's his soul? But how?
Kakyoin deciphered the mystery of Dio's stand,
and I imparted that knowledge to you.
Had we attacked Dio together before learning his secret,
he would have been able to easily kill all of us.
You now have the ability to move while time is frozen,
but you only have two or three seconds.
Make sure you use that time wisely.
Remember what I told you, Jotaro.
You mustn't lose your head.
If you lose control, it'll only backfire.
Keep your emotions in check when you face off with Dio.
Jotaro...
It's been quite the journey, eh, my boy,
an unforgettable adventure.
Call me crazy.
But our time together was a lot of fun,
more fun than I've had in a long time.
That was real, right?
Hey!
What are you looking at, Jotaro?!
You bastard!
He's been sucked dry.
I know you said to keep my emotions in check,
but screw that! He just crossed the line!
There's not a person on the planet
who could stay calm after seeing that!
This fight has come to an end!
The World! Bring time to a halt!
One second, two seconds,
and three seconds.
Now four...
Five seconds. Interesting.
Six seconds. My, my.
This makes seven seconds.
My power grows exponentially!
I can stop time for even longer.
But as for you, Jotaro,
you wasted the opportunity you had to move.
Gambling on getting me two seconds
before time resumed was all for naught.
What a miscalculation.
I feel so marvelous, I could serenade the world!
The moment I've dreamed of for so long is finally upon us.
Eight seconds have passed.
I've been an immortal being for an entire century...
But never in my wildest dreams could I have
imagined I'd feel something this exhilarating!
The blood of the Joestars courses through my veins!
Damn it.
Guess you were right, after all, old man.
My stupid temper got me in a shit-ton of trouble.
For Christ's sake.
No, this isn't the end!
He still hasn't faced the full force of my rage!
Nine seconds total,
that's how long my power lasted just now.
Yes, perhaps nine seconds is the new
extent of my stand's extraordinary power.
You bastard.
Now to unleash all of my stand's power!
Jotaro, weren't you mumbling something about being angry?!
Is this all the power you possess?!
Muda!
And now I shall administer the killing blow!
Here it is, my final dance with time!
Nine more seconds, that's all you have left!
Prepare to die! The World!
One second.
Two seconds.
Three seconds.
Jotaro couldn't figure out why Dio had
suddenly vanished amidst the standstill...
Four seconds.
But he pushed the thoughts out of his mind.
No matter what sinister plot Dio was hatching,
no matter what unholy attack he attempted to unleash,
Jotaro had only two seconds to respond,
only two seconds to drive Star
Platinum's fists into Dio once and for all!
Five seconds.
I've had just about enough of this neon vampire.
The next time I see that goddamn face of his,
I'm gonna freakin' lose it and beat him into the ground.
Six seconds.
That's right, Dio.
Come and get it.
Seven seconds.
I'm going to roll all over you!
It's too late! Time to die!
Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda...
Ora! Ora! Ora! Ora...
Eight seconds!
I'll obliterate you!
Ora!
Nine seconds.
I did it.
It's over.
The world has defeated star platinum.
My stand is more powerful than his.
I am immortal.
I am everlasting.
Stand power!
Now there is incontrovertible proof that no
one on this miserable planet is stronger than me.
You loathsome humans,
I shall rule over your pathetic
species until the end of time.
Now bow before my wisdom and power!
Ten seconds!
Would you look at that?
I can stop time for ten seconds!
All right, now that I've defeated Jotaro, I
should inspect his lifeless body and drink his blood,
that is, if there's any blood left to savor.
This can't be.
My body's slowing down.
What's happening?
N-no. It's not that I'm slowing down.
For some reason, I can't move at all!
I don't get it.
This is impossible. I'm frozen.
Hey, Dio, it's been 11 seconds.
I guess that's your stand's limit, huh?
Eh, what?!
I stopped time at nine seconds,
and it's a good thing I did.
It gave me a chance to escape.
Good grief, you idiot.
Here's the thing.
Since you're frozen like that,
destroying you will only take a second!
Jotaro!
This is madness.
You can stop time, too?
Curse you! This whole act was a ruse to
waste my nine seconds, wasn't it, you bastard?
How does it feel, Dio? Tell me.
How's it feel having your archenemy tower
behind you while you stand frozen and helpless?
I suppose it's a lot like holding
your breath while underwater,
only someone's out to get you, and your air is
running out as you desperately swim for your life.
And then after finally reaching the surface
and taking a breath, you get pulled right back in.
Sound familiar?
But after everything you've done, Dio,
you're not gonna get any sympathy from me.
Ora!
Time is about to start moving again.
Compassion is something you're never gonna get from me.
I haven't got any kindness for your sorry undead ass,
though I gotta admit
you look pretty pathetic writhing on the ground in agony.
As much as I want to, killing you like this
would leave a pretty bad taste in my mouth.
I wonder how long it'll take for you to heal.
Three seconds? Four, maybe?
The very moment your legs are healed, Star
Platinum's headed your way to demolish you.
If this were the wild west, the hero would say,
"It's high noon. Now get off the ground, and
draw your piece, Dio. You're getting one shot."
This insignificant whelp,
how dare he mock me?!
Though I shouldn't be surprised.
Of course he would use this opportunity
to make such a human declaration.
You think like a true mortal,
cursed with a fleeting life destined for obscurity.
A bad taste in your mouth, you say?
What, are you afraid you'd regret killing me?
That reasoning is as pathetic as your species.
Your foolish honor will be your demise.
That is where you and I differ.
My vision is clear, and my
mind is focused on a single goal.
I want to dominate, nothing more, nothing less.
It's the only thing that will bring me fulfillment.
But how I go about doing that...
Doesn't matter in the slightest!
There! How about a little blood in your eyes?!
I win! Die!
Ora!
What the hell?!
It's impossible!
I am the immortal Dio!
I am Dio!
When the sun comes up, you'll be nothing but dust.
You only made one mistake, one that got you killed.
Dio, this whole thing might have ended differently, but...
You went and pissed me off.
Was it worth it?
This is Speedwagon Foundation, car two.
We're traveling northbound on the al-nil expressway,
and we've retrieved Dio's remains.
I repeat. We've retrieved Dio's remains.
Dio's body is showing cellular activity.
He must be exposed to sunlight immediately.
Proceed with extreme caution!
Roger.
Noriaki Kakyoin is dead.
His body is being transported now.
Jean Pierre Polnareff is unconscious.
The medical staff of car one has him.
Roger.
Car two, I have a question.
Why have you placed the remains of
Dio and Joseph Joestar in the same car?
Because it's not over yet.
Dio borrowed something from us...
Eh?
And we need to take it back from the bastard.
I'm not following your train of thought.
I need you to perform a blood
transfusion between the two bodies.
That's absurd!
You want us to transfuse Dio's blood into Mr. Joestar?
I see! You're trying to bring him back to life!
It hasn't been all that long since Dio drained his blood.
His upper half was destroyed in the fight,
but we'll take as much as we can.
If we hurry, I think we can make it.
Hey, car one, did you catch all that? Over.
Roger.
It's impossible! He doesn't even have a pulse.
Right!
Not to mention his heart has stopped, which means
we couldn't circulate his blood if we wanted to.
Don't give me that.
You could call everything we've
done on this journey impossible.
I'm tired of hearing words like "impossible" or "futile."
They all mean nothing to us.
You can do it if his heart's beating, right?
Well, you're in luck.
Huh?
Thanks to Dio, I've already had a bit of
practice with stopping and starting hearts.
Ora!
I hear a pulse.
Yes, you're right! His heart is beating!
We have to transfuse his blood into Mr. Joestar quickly!
We might just be able to pull this off!
Remarkable!
Take a look at his skin!
It's completely regaining all its color!
His skin is filling out!
My god! Brain activity, too!
I don't believe it.
His vitals are stable as well!
His eyes!
He opened his eyes!
We did it! He's back!
Old man?
You're a damn fool, Jotaro.
You have got to be kidding!
Hmm.
All you've done is resurrect yours truly!
Bastard!
Wait! Calm down, Jotaro!
It was a joke! I was just kidding!
There's no need to get violent!
I'm sorry!
I was just trying to have some fun!
You have my word, it's me!
I'm Joseph Joestar! I was born September 27th in 1920!
My wife's name is Suzie Q,
and I collect comics as a hobby!
I have a question for you.
Who's the leading actress in "Tarzan, the ape man"?
Bo Derek.
Okay, now answer this one.
Who sang "eat it," the spoof of "beat it"?
"Weird al" yankovic.
Good grief, it has to be you.
Who else would know pointless crap like that?
This is car two. Over!
It's amazing! Mr. Joestar is back with us!
He's come back from the brink of death!
It's a miracle! Over!
Hear that?
We've taken back everything you stole from us, Dio.
It's finally over.
Dio took something precious from all of us.
For a hundred years, he's taken whatever he wanted.
His appetite for power has been insatiable.
He's taken far too much. You realize that.
Yeah. He's taken things from us
that'll we'll never be able to get back.
The losses that we've endured on this
journey stretch as far as the planet itself.
But thanks to their sacrifices, we're here
to tell the tale and carry on in their stead.
Kakyoin, Iggy, Avdol...
It's over.
Passengers awaiting incoming flights,
please make your way to the boarding gate.
So you're really going back to France, Polnareff?
This may be a bit forward, but your family's gone.
Why don't you come back with me to New York?
Mr. Joestar, I know they're gone,
but France is the only home I've ever known.
It's filled with memories.
It's a place I must return to, no matter where I go.
But if you ever need anything, all you have
to do is call, and I'll be there in a heartbeat.
We're gonna miss you, buddy.
It wasn't easy, that's for damn sure,
but I had a hell of a time,
and I'm lucky to have been on
this adventure with you guys.
Hmm.
Remember, we're a team,
and that's never gonna change.
Calling all passengers for France
international airlines, flight 92 to Paris.
Please proceed to gate 18.
A bientot, you ornery bastard.
Live long and happy.
And you, his moody grandson, you'd better not forget me.
We'll meet again, that is, of course, if you
don't hate my guts by then, stubborn jackass!
We wouldn't be able to forget about
you, even if we wanted to, Polnareff.
You be well.
Au revoir.
Yeah.
See you later.
Holly!
How are you sitting up straight all of a sudden?
I'm feeling much better.
I'm not sure how to put it into words.
It's as if we could read each other's minds.
What?
Mom, I can feel that they're coming home to us!
Holly!
Papa and my Jotaro!
They're coming home!
Hmm?