Previously on "jojo's bizarre adventure"...
That's her! That woman there is the stand user!
Ooh!
I do appreciate your forwardness, but you need
to work on your approach, you naughty, naughty man.
Mwah!
Oh, my god!
I forgot to tell you. Whatever you do, it's imperative
that you refrain from touching any electrical outlets!
Eh?
I'm afraid I already did, Mr. Joestar.
What?!
If what I know about magnets is true,
we're being forced together!
Mr. Joestar, I really hate saying this, but...
Yeah, I know.
We've gotten ourselves into a world of trouble.
Hey! Wait a sec!
Damn it all.
Look! She's getting away! After her!
Blast it! Now my body's a magnet!
I can't believe we allowed
ourselves to play right into her hands!
Calm down, Avdol.
You getting hysterical isn't helping anything.
Focus on figuring out how to overpower this blasted stand.
Damn it! Now where did that woman run off to?!
I don't see her anywhere!
Well, we can't keep rolling in the dirt forever!
Why don't we try slowly standing up?
Give it a go.
Huh?
All right, we did it.
Now that we're upright, the next step
is to try pulling away from each other.
However, I think it's going to be easier said than done,
since the magnetic force that's currently
holding us together has been doubled.
But for now, let's use that fence to
try getting out of this predicament.
We can do it, Avdol! Get those stomach
muscles ready, and make sure you stay in sync!
Ready when you are, Mr. Joestar!
One, two! One, two!
One, two! One, two! One, two!
One, two!
Eh?
Mr. Joestar, this is one of the most
embarrassing things I've ever done.
What do you think you're looking at?!
Can't you see that we're just practicing our dance moves?
It's true!
What a perfect day for dancing outdoors!
Now run along! Get out of here, damn it!
There we go!
Almost got it, Avdol!
And one, and two.
We did it!
We made it, and we're still standing!
Yes, a remarkable feat.
Avdol, now that we've gotten over here,
do you think you can slide off me?
I think I might be able to.
All right.
Here's what we're gonna do, so listen carefully.
I'll hang on to the fence as
tightly as I can while you slide down.
Free yourself once you've gotten to the tip of my foot.
Do you see how our faces are stuck
together as opposed to the other way around?
Well, it's more than likely a sign that my
feet and your head should repel each other.
Yes, that makes a lot of sense.
That's the way, Avdol! Just keep moving!
Hmm.
Uh, hey, what's the matter with you, Avdol?
D-don't you think this position is a little...
This pose is highly suggestive, Mr. Joestar.
If anyone were to see us, they
would be inclined to think that...
Oh, come off it! No one's looking at us!
Hurry up, and slide off my...
Yaah!
Those little brats came back and brought their friends!
Why don't you take a hike?! There's nothing to see,
so knock it off with the staring, would you?!
I said beat it, you little ankle biters!
Get out of here! Take off!
Avdol, hurry up, and get off
me before this gets any worse.
I'm trying as hard as I can!
I can't believe this is happening to me!
The embarrassment!
All right, I'll be the one to move!
Mr. Joestar, please slow down!
Mr. Joestar, moving around like
that makes it seem as though we're...
Oh, no! It's that old hag again!
I come back expecting to find my handsome
man, and instead my eyes are assaulted with this?!
How dare you toy with the fragile gift
of a maiden's heart, you filthy cheater?!
For the love of god, hurry, Avdol!
She getting closer, and I can
already feel the tears coming!
Dirty, rotten scoundrel!
Help me! Oh, my god!
Please calm down! You've got it all wrong!
We did it!
We need to stay far apart from each other!
Your magnetic pull is getting more powerful by the second!
It serves you right, you damned fool!
You and your boy toy, go to hell!
What the...
There she is!
We found her.
Just look at her having her morning cigarette.
Avdol, try going after her from that side.
We can't let her get away from us this time.
She's cunning, so this may be a trap.
This can't be!
Mr. Joestar, it would appear as though
we've already fallen right into her trap!
Eh?
Hmm.
Ahh! They're railroad tracks!
And I don't think we're going
to be able to get off that easily!
Are you kidding me?!
It would seem...
That we're stuck together again!
Son of a bi... eh?
Mr. Joestar, something is coming.
That sound...
Oh, no, we have to get the hell
out of here as fast as we can!
Avdol, I need you to use magician's
red to burn through the tracks!
We need to get out of here!
But, Mr. Joestar, I don't think that would be...
Eh?
It's here! There's the train!
Hurry up, and melt those tracks!
I tried telling you, Mr. Joestar!
If I were to burn away these tracks...
The train would derail,
and innocent people would go tumbling to their deaths!
Shit!
That damn woman is pure, unadulterated evil!
I'm almost positive my vines would be able to hold her,
but at that distance, she's too far
out of range for them to even reach her,
so our best bet is me trying to pull us free
from the tracks using that post as an anchor.
I-it's no use!
The magnetic pull is even stronger than it was before!
Mr. Joestar, it's life or death!
You can't stop pulling, no matter what!
It's coming! You have to pull harder!
That didn't work!
I win.
I took care of them for you, lord Dio.
Now that that's done,
I'm going to do away with Jotaro and Polnareff.
Eh?
Good thinking, Avdol!
Only someone as clever as you would burn the
railroad tracks and dig a trench underneath!
You see, Mr. Joestar, unlike that earlier incident,
Mohammed Avdol does indeed have a decent modicum of class.
Doing things this way is a little more my style.
So you think you've outsmarted me?
You...
Obnoxious pieces of shit!
Magician's red!
Me, too! Hermit purple!
Now we've got you.
Unfortunately for you, young lady,
I've got to keep a grip on your neck until you pass out,
so you can count on being in the
hospital for at least a week or so.
I can't just let you and your
magnetic power run free, can I?
Hmm?
Are your imaginations running wild?
Sorry to disappoint, boys, but
my breasts aren't getting larger.
But there's no need to worry yourselves,
because your magnetism's growing even stronger.
And lucky for me I just happened
to stuff my bra with weapons.
Mr. Joestar, we have incoming!
Magician's red!
Your magnetism will keep intensifying,
well, at least until your
bodies are crushed to tiny pieces.
She's getting away again!
No, I don't think so. It's all part of her strategy.
She's moving farther away from us
in order to maintain a safe distance.
Remember, that woman's a stand user,
so she needs to stay close to her target.
If she gets too close to us, we'll be able to catch her,
but if she's too far out of range, her power won't work.
This magnetism is still just a stand.
The normal rules apply,
which means if she puts too much distance
between us, the magnetism should weaken.
So what should we do? If we don't get free,
the magnetic force will just continue to intensify.
Should we keep running until we're out of range?
That might be our best bet.
No way. We might be able to get away from her powers for
a short amount of time, but the stand would still prevail.
I've run away from fights before,
but I've only done so when running
was part of the overall strategy.
No matter how hopeless things look,
Joseph Joestar never throws in the towel.
The real showdown begins now!
Hmm?
I've drawn a map of the town.
Here's our current position,
and here's where the woman's going.
As long as she continues moving down this road,
she'll eventually loop around and head back this way.
We'll split up, and...
Right here is where we'll catch that witch.
It doesn't matter if she's a woman or not.
When we catch her, she's getting a taste of my boot!
Let's get going!
Check it out.
Oh, yeah. Someone's cut the rails.
Good. The locals are here.
I'm sure one of them will have the foresight
to notify the authorities about the tracks
before the next train arrives.
Come on!
Huh?
Something is definitely up.
Hey! Did you hear someone cut the rail line?!
What about all the trains?
Luckily they've stopped running, at least for now.
Someone actually cut the rail line?
People nowadays sure are sick, don't you think?
Who in their right mind would do something so terrible?
Major douche canoe.
Jotaro, you wanna know what I think?
Rotten people always get what's coming to 'em.
You Mark my words. They'll get theirs.
I saved three months' salary, all for this.
Will you marry me?
Oh, my!
Huh? What the?
Wait! Where did the...
The ring!
Those morons are getting closer to me,
but at this rate, they'll never catch me.
Huh?
Almost there. Almost there.
Hmm?
I must say you're looking a little weighted down.
But don't worry. The wild-goose chase ends here.
Interestingly enough, it would seem that the two
of us are more familiar with this town than you are.
You should take a look behind you.
You're now caught between us,
and there's nowhere for you to run.
It may have taken a while to get here,
but the tables have turned.
Hmm?
So you think I have nowhere to go?
You boys truly haven't realized it yet, have you?
You only thought you were hunting me, when
really I was luring you here the entire time!
Look up, idiots!
Huh?
High-voltage power lines!
Oh, no! The power lines are...
That's right.
Power lines are extremely magnetic!
I'm afraid you're going to fry this time, Joestar!
Magician's red!
Hermit purple!
Avdol might be able to defend himself
for now with his flames, but not you.
Time to die, Joestar.
My stand, the goddess bast is the perfect trap,
and it's also far more powerful than your hermit purple!
Hope you've said your prayers, because it's time to die!
Vile woman.
My flames will burn you and your evil alive!
My entire body is being pulled in another direction!
I... I can't resist!
My flames should be strong enough
to melt the steel without a problem,
but I can't defend myself from every attack,
and this weight is crushing me!
I can't hold it any longer!
Joseph Joestar, since you're going to die anyway,
I can confess that I find you to be quite a catch.
It's true that I only knew you for a short time,
but you were so clever and hilarious,
not to mention your experience
would make younger men green with envy,
plus you're very handsome.
I know that you and I are decades apart,
but if I'm being honest with myself,
you would have made a splendid lover.
Well, if that's how you truly feel about me,
then what do you say you give me a hand?
Hmm.
I've seen the light and realize that your stand is
way more powerful than mine could ever hope to be!
I can't hold it anymore!
Please! I'm begging you!
You have to turn off the magnetism!
Well, I suppose I could...
But, no, I don't think I will.
While you are exceptionally handsome,
you're nowhere near as good-looking as lord Dio.
So you're saying that you refuse
to turn off the power no matter what?
Exactly right.
Now don't you have some dying to do?
Even though I'm groveling to you?
I won't say it again, you idiot.
If that's how you're going to be,
then it's your loss, young lady.
What?!
Shit! Shit!
Weren't you listening to us earlier?
You've been caught between us the whole time.
Magnets are attracted to each other, you know.
It's too late to do anything about it now,
but getting between us was your biggest blunder.
There's no way she can hear you, Mr. Joestar.
She's already lost consciousness.
All the metal and magnetic force has crushed her,
and it's very likely that she's broken
more than a few bones in the process.
Hmm.
All right,
why don't we get that breakfast we were talking about?
Yes, a wonderful idea.
All this running around has made me rather hungry.
Is it really only 9 A.M.?
Damn, you pieces of shit...
Those two are taking forever!
As long as they've been in there, you'd think
they were putting on makeup and dressing for a gala.
And it's almost 9 A.M.
Hmm.
They may have run into an enemy on the way here.
You think we should see where they ran off to?
I guess. Ah, good grief.
It's time to go, Iggy.
Yeah, yeah, I know you're hungry.
You're not the only one, believe me.
Hmm.
Josef and Avdol are in the
middle of doing battle with Mariah,
so I, Alessi, shall take on the great
honor of killing Jotaro and Polnareff.