You've finally come out, Dio.
A job well done, Polnareff.
You managed to avenge your sister,
but what's most impressive is that
you also found the time to track me down.
I'll gladly kill you to celebrate,
but I think we should start with this first.
I'll give you a chance to rethink.
Descend now, and not only will you live,
you'll be given the chance to serve me again.
Or you could choose to rise forth.
However, you'd be ascending to your doom.
When the two of us first met,
fear consumed me like a curse.
It gave your evil carte Blanche
to manipulate me like a puppet.
That fear was the beginning of a
futile existence with no end in sight.
It was a fate worse than death,
a wretched life devoid of any
desire other than doing your bidding.
But that fear has been eradicated,
leaving only the burning will to fight.
I've spent 45 days traveling
with Mr. Joestar and the others,
and in honor of those who died on
that journey, I'll never fear you again.
My, aren't we confident?
Climb these stairs, and put that bravado to the test.
Quite the interesting decision, Polnareff.
You've backed down after all.
Is that your clever way of telling
me you want your former life back?
What in the hell?!
But I went up the stairs.
I'm sure. What happened?
Problem? You seem to be shaken, Polnareff.
But why is that? Could the winds of fear
have extinguished your burning resolve?
Perhaps the only steps you took were in your mind,
and in actuality fear overrode your consciousness,
wrestling control from your brain,
causing you to descend down the stairs.
No way!
I'm positive I just walked up those stairs.
What?
Is he doing this with his stand?
No! It couldn't be.
Dio's stand is...
The World?!
What am I supposed to do now?
I'm curious, Polnareff.
Have you ever wondered what the human soul desires most?
Peace of mind.
Subconsciously, all humans wish to overcome their fears.
They seek fame, money, and dominance of others,
all to obtain a sense of everlasting security.
What a farce.
They create bonds as a means of self-preservation.
They say they wish to help others
purely for the sake of love and justice,
but it's only to settle their feeble minds.
Humanity's greatest desire is to latch on to serenity.
So why? Why refuse to serve me?
What greater serenity is there?
Return to me, and all I speak of will be yours.
You don't want to challenge me.
There's just no point in running
headlong into a meaningless death.
You deserve much more.
No, am I seriously letting him draw me back in?
You're a talented stand user.
It would be a shame to kill you.
Turn your back on Joestar, and live as my right hand.
I promise you unending peace starting now.
I have to resist.
Avdol, Iggy, I need your courage.
Cut the bullshit, Dio!
I've already stared death in the eye!
And I'll gladly do it again
if it helps uncover your stand's abilities!
How disappointing.
Hmm.
Time to meet your end, Polnareff!
So that's your stand, The World! Bring it!
Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda!
Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda! Muda!
Huh?
Mm?
It's Mr. Joestar!
There's no need to worry, Polnareff.
Dio!
That was Dio!
After him!
I have to tell you something first!
It was only out in the open for a
moment or two, but I saw him use his stand.
Uh, well, I didn't actually see it,
but I did feel it in a manner of speaking.
It's complicated, but here's the long and short of it.
I was heading up the stairs to beat the life out of
that bastard when suddenly I was back where I started.
Believe me, I know what I'm
saying doesn't make any sense at all.
I can't wrap my head around what happened either.
I feel like I'm losing my mind over here.
I'm sure he wasn't using any sort of hypnosis.
I'd say super speed, but there's no way.
All I know is that I sensed something utterly terrifying.
Hey, where are Iggy and Avdol?
They didn't make it.
They're both dead.
They died trying to save me.
Is that so?
We should go.
Look, Mr. Joestar. The sun is setting.
Let's hurry.
Yeah, you're right.
All right, out with it!
What's waiting for us upstairs?
The... the towers!
There's also another room at the top!
It's where lord Dio dwells during the day!
Is there another staircase to the tower?
No, this is the only set of stairs that leads there.
In that case, lead the way.
Ora!
So that's him.
The two of us have never met,
but I've known about this monster
for longer than I care to remember.
How could I not know this fiend?
The thought of him has been burned into
my mind ever since the day I was born.
Same for Jotaro.
We'd hoped this day would never come,
that we'd never have to face Dio,
but as Joestars, we knew we'd
eventually have to destroy him.
I have no regrets.
I came on this journey of my own free will,
so I can live with whatever happens from here on out.
I've never seen things more clearly.
It's like a light of clarity has washed over me.
My friends are that light, while Dio is darkness.
My body may be broken and
battered, but the fear has vanished.
Virtue and light has purified my soul.
We'll attack the moment Dio steps out of the coffin.
Stay at the ready.
We don't know what tricks he has up his sleeves.
It's time, loser.
Open the coffin.
Whatever happens, lord Dio, you
have to know I never betrayed you.
I only led these degenerates here, because I
knew you had the power to easily dispose of them!
As certain as a man wetting himself when
pissing in the wind, your victory is assured.
You are all-powerful.
Please don't be angry with me!
Enough of the groveling!
Open the damn coffin!
Please, I'm begging you,
give these bastards a cruel and horrifying end...
Lord Dio!
Get ready, everyone.
Huh?
Why?
I don't know what's going on.
How'd I get in here? I was just opening the coffin!
What the hell?! How did he...
My eyes were locked on loser boy the entire time.
Did anyone else see him get in the coffin?
Wait! Did someone put him in there without us knowing?
No, I was watching him just like you were.
He's opening the coffin one
second, and the next, he's inside it.
You're right, Polnareff,
but I don't believe it's a mind trick,
and it's not super speed either.
Good grief.
Is he playing games with us?
Get out of here!
Damn you!
What are you doing?! Come on!
Let me go!
Okay, what was that feeling back there?
The ominous presence it was
giving off was far more powerful
than any stand our group has ever encountered before!
It was like knowing a bulldozer is coming after
you just from the sound of its roaring engine!
Yeah, I sensed it, too, an insane lust to kill us.
It felt like somebody shoving an icicle up my ass!
If we hadn't escaped when we did, whatever
that was would have killed us for sure!
Damn it! Just look at the sun.
It's almost gone below the horizon.
Dio will have the advantage in the dark.
Hang on.
Come again?! Please don't tell me you guys
are planning to run away and hide until dawn.
Listen to me, Mr. Joestar. I'm finishing this.
There's no way I'm packing up and heading for the hills.
You're right. We have to see this through to the end.
I wanna get this over with as much as you do,
but the tide of battle has turned.
While not up close, we've faced his stand, The World,
but we still have no idea what its powers are.
We're fighting blind here. Think of it this way.
It's like mountain climbing without knowing the route.
If we try to fight Dio right now, we'll all die.
That fact is as inevitable as burping
after knocking back a couple of colas.
Dio would be a fool not to come racing after us,
but he only has until sunrise to kill us.
In the meantime, we need to learn the extent of
his stand's power and find a way to put him down.
If we can just hold out until then...
No way! I'm not going back on my word!
Avdol and Iggy died because of my weakness!
I have to kill Dio.
I'll go to hell and back to do it,
but what I won't do is run away from my obligation!
No! Come back, Polnareff!
Forget it. He's not gonna listen.
Jotaro, what do you think we should do now?
He went down there to fight Dio.
As we retreat, we'll also be fighting him,
which means we'll be attacking from both sides at once.
Hey, buddy,
let us buy this truck off you. What do you say?
The hell is wrong with you?!
This baby's my bread and butter! No way I'd...
It's all yours.
Buckle up, Kakyoin.
There you are, Dio.
Think I'll just run 'til dawn?
You've crossed the wrong Frenchmen.
I'll settle this on my own if I have to.
So what if I don't know how Dio's stand works?
I'll just find another way to defeat him.
He's dead.
Hold it, Polnareff.
I had them let you go, 'cause convincing
stubborn guys like you is a pain in the ass,
but the old man and Kakyoin insisted I
stay close and watch your back, so here I am.
Jotaro!
Oh, good grief.
The automobile,
such impressive power and speed.
When I was young, all we had
were shabby horse-drawn carriages.
Don't move! What do you think you're doing?
This car belongs to U.S. senator Mr. Wilson
Phillips, and touching it results in a beat-down!
Huh?
What the hell is wrong with you?!
Hmm.
My, my.
Young people these days are so full of piss and vinegar.
Time's are a-changin'.
Eh?
Why would you?!
Stop talking now, and proceed to the front seat.
It's time to drive.
Just who the hell are you, sicko?!
After I'm finished with you, you'll rue
the day you ever barged into my vehicle!
Yeah, this is unforgivable.
No one gets away with doing something like this to me.
I was valedictorian in both high school and college,
not to mention captain of the college wrestling team.
Even after graduation, people respected me.
That's how I became a politician.
I own a villa on a thousand-acre plot of land in Hawaii,
my gorgeous model of a wife is 25 years
younger, and I pay more taxes than anyone else!
I've destroyed every enemy who's ever stood
in my way, and someday I'll become president!
I'm the senator Wilson Phillips, damn it!
Listen to me, you punk band reject!
I'm gonna make sure you rot in
prison for the rest of your miser...
Hear this, as I won't repeat it.
Drive the car.
This psychopath's gonna kill me.
I have to get the hell out of this car.
If I don't, I'm a goner!
Someone, help me!
Huh?
What the hell?!
What was that?!
I'm positive I jumped out of the car, so
what the hell am I doing back in the car?!
I don't get it! What's going on?!
Your job is to catch up to that truck.
Fail to do so, and you die.
Uh, yes, sir!
How am I still in the car?
Of course. That's it. I'm a senator.
What can't I do?
Yes, it makes total sense now.
I still sense Dio's sinister blood lust.
Its presence is overwhelming.
He's coming for us.
You can bet your ass he's on our trail.
Are you saying that Dio somehow
knows our precise location?
Not quite. He stole the body of
my grandfather, Jonathan Joestar.
I can sense his body, but I can't
tell if he's nearby or far away.
I have a general feeling, but I
don't know exactly where he is.
It's like when we got to Cairo and, while I
knew he was here, I couldn't pinpoint his lair.
Lucky for us, the same thing goes for Dio.
All he knows is that we're nearby,
but he's unable to tell the difference between us,
and he probably doesn't know we've
separated, which is good for now.
Why the hell isn't this working?
Cars always start up when they
do this kind of thing in movies.
Seems like there's a traffic jam.
I'm sorry, sir. The evening
commute is always bumper to bumper.
Move it.
Uh, but we're stuck here. There's just too much traffic.
Have you forgotten there's a sidewalk? Use it.
The sidewalk?
B-but it's covered with people heading home from work.
And your point? Go.
Yes, sir.
Faster.
Yes, sir!
Okay, it's running.
Hurry up, and get on, Polnareff.
Oh. Yeah.
Oh, the things I do for you!
But I've done everything you've
asked, so you'll spare my life, right?
There's no need to kill a helpless senator!
Wrong.
I have to be dreaming.
What other explanation is there?
As if a senator like me could be killed.
Whoo-hoo-hoo! It's just a dream!
Found you.
Now get closer. We need to catch up to them.
I can't use the world if I'm this far away.
Look. Here he comes.
You see that car? That's Dio's ride.
Kakyoin!
Hmm. It's Kakyoin's...
Take this, Dio!
Emerald splash!
Unbelievable!
He deflected my attack with a flick of a finger.
He barely moved.
But how do you like this?!
He even dodged the concentrated splash? Damn it!
When did he bring out his stand?
How could I have missed that?!
Well, that's a shame. He's too far away now.
My punch seems to have thrown
him out of the world's range.
What's happening?!
And what precisely would I gain
by explaining this situation to you?
Pay attention to the road, and drive.
Be careful, Kakyoin!
You were way too close to it,
Please, forgive me. I didn't mean...
It was only a few months ago when Dio asked me
if I was "really going to vomit out of fear."
That monster had the audacity to tell me I should relax.
Bastard, never again.
I'll never lose to you again.
Are you all right, Kakyoin?
Did you catch a glimpse of the world?
Yes, I saw it
when I attacked Dio from ten meters away.
If I had gotten any closer, I would have been done for.
But we know one thing for certain.
His stand holds a power more horrific
than we could have ever imagined.
However, we know two things about it.
First, his stand doesn't have the reach of
my Hierophant Green or your Hermit Purple.
It's a close-range power stand, like Star Platinum,
and has a range of about ten meters.
Second, it attacked with its fist, so it
doesn't use projectile weapons, like bullets.
That being said, if we can sneak
up on him and get within range,
we just might have a chance of finishing him off.
We have to figure out his secret.
Even so, we have to exercise extreme
caution when approaching this bastard.
Hold on.
Why'd his car suddenly stop?
Incoming! We're about to be hit!
Mr. Joestar!
What are you doing, Kakyoin?
I understand now.
I know now how to uncover the secret of Dio's stand.