What is that?
Weren't Avdol's flames
supposed to be able to sense anything?
Avdol, where are you?!
Avdol...
Has been reduced to nothingness.
You were arrogant enough
to believe you could defeat lord Dio.
Allow me to demonstrate just how wrong you were.
You'll fall in line one by one
as I scatter your atomic fragments
across the recesses of the void.
It can't be.
I don't believe you.
Avdol's not dead.
Don't you lie to me!
W-What?!
I never would have imagined Polnareff's
stand could attack this swiftly from so far away.
An amazing feat, to be sure.
Over here.
I want you to look at me when I kill you.
Hmm?
All right,
now I'm sure something fishy's going on.
Ever since we escaped the mirage,
I've heard the sounds of a battle.
Blast it. Avdol and Polnareff are out there.
Hmm?
Mm.
Damn that guy. I know I hit the
bastard, but it wasn't enough to kill him.
He just swallowed himself again
so he could hide in that abyss.
Damn that guy and his stand.
Avdol, how could you do that?
How could you break the one rule you gave us?
Polnareff, Iggy, you have to get out of here now!
You told us we had to watch our own backs,
that you wouldn't save us, even if we were in danger.
You liar.
You've been meddling in other people's business
ever since the moment we set foot in India.
Damn it, Avdol!
Why couldn't you just leave me alone
and mind your own freaking business?!
If I hadn't ducked, I'd be a dead man right now.
It's like fate is telling me to carry on.
This must be Avdol's way of knocking some sense into me.
It's way too dangerous in here.
Let's get moving!
Come on, Iggy. We have to make it upstairs!
Don't fall behind!
Look up ahead!
It's the exit! We're almost there!
But I won't just turn tail and run away.
Avdol sacrificed himself for us, and
I'll repay that debt, no matter what!
He believed we had the power to
put an end to Dio once and for all.
I can't betray his faith in us by letting him down.
That is not an option.
I refuse to take the easy way out like some common coward.
I'm gonna see this fight through to the bitter end!
The only place I'm running to is Dio's shadow den!
So up the stairs we go!
I expected him to dash out the door.
Pity.
Impressive. He managed a hit.
It seems Polnareff's mental fortitude
gives him the ability to conquer his fears
in the face of imminent death.
You will soon be joining Avdol. Rest assured.
Your strength pales in comparison to
the harbinger of death that is my stand.
If what he says is true,
his stand's jaws are the
gateway to an alternate dimension,
a dark, unimaginable abyss,
one that allows him to move through our
realm without leaving any trace of himself.
But how does he do it?
And how the heck am I supposed to beat him?
No, no, no! He's cut us off!
He's nearby.
But where exactly?
Iggy, I need you to watch my back,
and don't worry. I'll do the same for you.
Okay, if he wants to reach us, then he's
gonna have to come out of that other realm.
This is good. He has to come out
from the dark beyond at some point.
When he does, I'll take my chance
and attack him with everything I've got.
All right, come at me, you demented pinball!
I'll slice you in two!
Now I'm pissed off, so my chariot's even faster!
I may have lost Avdol,
but it'll be a cold day in hell before I let you get away.
Huh?
Eh?
What the hell?!
He... he was hiding under my foot?
Chario...
Aah! My foot!
Now you can't run away.
I got your foot so that you can't hide anymore.
Eat silver.
I'll pass.
Mr. Joestar, a brawl's under way.
Avdol and Polnareff.
Sounds like they came in after us and
wound up getting themselves into a fight.
Come on, you two! We have to find them ASAP!
You've managed to hide amid the chaos, Polnareff.
How futile. You couldn't have gone far with that injury,
which means you're hiding beneath the rubble.
By now, you must have realized
you're helpless against me.
You shall meet your end by my hand.
Now then, where could you be, Polnareff?
That's quite the ruckus, Cool Ice.
L-lord Dio.
Please be careful, my lord.
I believe Polnareff and that
four-legged rodent are still hiding nearby.
Allow me to handle the situation.
You mustn't trouble yourself with such nonsense, master.
A fake Dio made from the fool. We got him.
You'd think I'd feel guilty about
attacking from behind like a coward,
and you'd be wrong,
because you pulled the same shit on Avdol.
This is the death you deserve.
Now, Iggy! Crucify him.
Now Iggy! Crucify him!
Make him pay for what he did.
End his life in the same merciless way he did Avdol's.
Send him straight to hell!
You're kidding?!
He knows. But how?!
Because the windows to my left are
letting in the light from the sun.
Lord Dio would never enter this room during the day.
You'll suffer a thousand deaths for your deception.
Iggy.
I made a vow to lord Dio that
I would kill you interlopers.
He entrusted me with that honor.
Lord Dio's a man of his word.
He would never descend to the second floor for any reason.
No. He's gonna kill Iggy.
He's about to be swallowed by the abyss!
Now die, you filthy, pathetic dog.
Your incorrigible ruse forced
me to destroy lord Dio's likeness!
D-did he really just hit him?
He didn't use the void.
Instead of killing Iggy, he went in for a punch!
Do you know what you've done?
I don't care if it was a fake.
You forced me to destroy a figure in the form of lord Dio,
and you must answer for that crime.
Your life is mine now!
I will kick you to death!
My dark abyss could swallow you whole in an instant,
but a quick death wouldn't satiate my fury.
This whole mess,
it's all your fault!
This is what happens to those who anger me.
Have you learned your lesson yet?!
How 'bout it? Is this better?
Tell me! Is it? Is it?! Is it?!
Stop it! Leave him alone!
It's like Cool Ice's brain has melted.
Is he really going bat-shit because he
destroyed some pile of sand that looked like Dio?
From over here, his soul is the murky abyss.
It's a bottomless black hole that obliterates
any and every thing that gets in its way.
I was warned about the humans.
Lord Dio said the resolve in their
hearts must never be underestimated.
But you, you're just a flea-bitten stray.
You've never known resolve,
and you certainly know nothing of pride.
Yeah? Grin at this!
Leave him alone.
You like that? Do you?!
What did I say?
Come on! Your suffering's just begun.
Cool Ice! You're dealing with me now!
I'm ending this, Polnareff.
Damn it.
He's gone!
But more importantly, Iggy,
our plan to trick Cool Ice may have fallen through,
but your sand might have just saved us.
Thanks to you, I think I found a way to find the bastard.
Yeah, that's him, all right.
I can see him moving around.
Guess your stand power is a double-edged sword.
When you move, your stand has no choice
but to absorb everything in your path.
So choke on a mouthful of this,
and get over here, you piece of shit.
As soon as you come out from behind
your stand's putrid teeth to attack me,
I'll turn the tables and finish you off.
Bull's-eye! Yeah, eat that!
Well, would you look at that?
I found your weakness, Cool Ice.
Any attempt to pinpoint my location leaves you vulnerable,
which is probably a tad inconvenient, since you
can't see me without emerging from your dark dimension.
It's over.
Now suck on my sword and burn in hell, fils de pute!
Hurry up, and die.
W-What? How are you still alive?
I skewered your throat and brainstem.
Would you die, already?!
No way you're getting out of it.
Hurry up, and die!
Stop making me repeat myself. Die!
I cannot die.
My mission is far too important to feel any pain.
I will not rest until I kill you.
I'll swallow Iggy, the Joestars,
and anyone else who gets in my way.
Only after your deaths will I allow myself to die.
Bastard!
There's a good boy.
You knew to withdraw your sword.
I also know that you're about to die.
This is the one,
the vile arm you used to stab me.
Knock it off!
Damn it!
I had no choice but to shove him away.
No!
Y-you're not going anywhere!
Did I get him? Ah, where'd he go now?
Shit. He got my leg. I can't move.
But I can't think about the pain right now.
I was so close.
I almost managed to land a killing blow,
but he got away.
This guy is different, fueled by pure vengeance.
And he's not just nuts.
His devotion to Dio is all-consuming.
But I won't let him get the upper hand.
You said you couldn't die yet?
Well, I can't die until I kill you!
Okay, here he comes.
Take this!
Shit, it's no use.
His stand just obliterated the tip of my sword,
though it probably wouldn't
matter, even if it were intact.
It's impossible to attack him
when he's hidden in the abyss.
If I so much as touch that thing, it'll swallow me whole.
Great, now he's absorbing the building at random. Merde!
That's clever. He knows full well
I'll go after him if he shows himself,
so he's blindly attacking to
prevent me from fighting back.
He's not messing around.
At this rate, he's gonna hit me for sure.
I should pull back chariot and think of a plan.
Damn. This isn't good.
Iggy's not gonna last long if he keeps losing blood.
From the state he's in, I'd say his
broken ribs must have punctured his lungs.
And just when I thought this couldn't get any worse.
Why the hell is he devouring the walls?
Wait a second. I'm starting to think I was all wrong.
This isn't random.
It was all part of his plan from the beginning.
He's been drawing circles around me,
and with every lap, he's getting closer and closer.
The odds are stacked against me,
but I have to do something.
He's closing in.
He still doesn't know our location,
but with that rolling ball of death
hurtling toward us, it doesn't matter.
He's got us right where he wants us.
There's no way I'm gonna be able to
dodge an attack from him with this bum leg.
I-I've got to try to escape through the floor.
I don't have enough time to tunnel through!
He's coming straight for us!
Somehow, I dodged it.
Not out of the woods. He's closing in on
me like a needle on an old record player.
I only have about five more rounds before he
makes his way back here and finishes me off for good.
So, the million-dollar question
is how do I dodge with this injured leg?
If I had it my way, I'd just pick option two,
but I can't count on that.
They only entered the mansion 10 minutes before us.
As much as I'd love for them to swoop in out of thin
air and save the day like some American comic book hero,
wishful thinking's not gonna save me now.
There's no point hoping for an out-of-the-blue rescue.
For all I know, the others might be
in the middle of a fight themselves.
All right then.
Option one's our only choice.
Okay, chariot, I need you to pull me
out of the circle as fast as you can.
What are you doing?
Pull me faster, chariot!
I-it's no use.
What do you know?
The answer ended up being option three.
Life's a bitch.
Silver chariot is a finesse-orientated
stand that fights with a saber.
It simply doesn't have the power to pull my body weight,
especially when I'm injured.
I'm done for.
You're holding on by a thread.
Stay down, you stupid mutt.
If you keep moving or try using your stand's power,
your broken ribs will sink
deeper into your lungs and kill you.
Hey, you can drop the tough guy act, you idiot.
The only thing this will accomplish
is you dying right along with me.
Just you wait. I'm the one who's gonna save you.
You have to live on to tell Mr. Joestar
and the others about this bastard.
You have to defeat him in my stead.
Avdol might have saved me,
but you sure as hell better not!
If we all die here, then what was the point of this?
One more loop, and its lights out.
So it's number three.
Life can be a bitch sometimes.
We both wanted to win.
Guess he wanted it more.
Au revoir, Iggy.