[music playing in japanese]
-Ichigo and his
friends have set out
for Sosouke Aizen's
fortress, Las Noches,
in order to save Orihime.
But they are dragged
into the Menos forest
by Runuganga, the guardian
of the White Sand.
In the forest,
Rukia is separated
from Ichigo and the others.
She is saved by a mysterious
Soul Reaper named Ashido.
CEO Long ago, Ashido followed
Hollows into the Menos Forest
where he fought Hollows
by himself for centuries.
-Go!
Save your friend.
[gasps]
[roars]
-Ashido!
-Ichigo and his friends are able
to successfully make their way
back to the surface
with Ashido's help,
and they finally
make to Las Noches.
-Your friends have
entered Hueco Mundo.
-Why would they come here?
-Why, you ask?
They have come to save you.
Why else would they
choose to come here?
They have no other reasons.
[roars]
-So they came here
just to save me?
-Yes, that's right.
But that no longer has
any meaning for you.
By wearing these clothes,
you are no longer
the person you once used to be.
You are one of us now,
in body and in spirit.
That is reality, Orihime Inoue.
[crack]
-Yes.
-Tell me, who does your body
and spirit belong to now?
I want to hear you
say it out loud.
-They-- they belong to Lord
Aizen and are for his purpose
and use.
[explosion]
-Did we make it through?
-Looks like it.
Wind is passing through.
-Hey!
What are you doing?
ICHIGO AND RENJI: Huh?
-The entrance to
the palace is just
a three-day walk
in that direction.
-Look, Nell.
This isn't a visit
to a friend's house.
We're not just going to walk
in through the front door.
-We also don't have the
time to walk for three days.
-Aww.
-Nell.
-Huh?
-Thank you for
bringing us this far,
but I'm afraid this is
where it has to end.
If you involve yourselves
with us anymore,
you'll most likely wind
up being seen as traitors.
And so, this is goodbye.
-Augh.
-See ya.
[footsteps]
-(GASPING) W- Wait!
Ichigo!
[piano music]
[footsteps]
-Ichigo!
From the moment [? that ruru ?]
got the swords together,
out fate was sealed because
we were labeled as traitors!
No, it may have even
been long before then.
Lord Aizen may have already
known, and if that's the case,
he'll never forgive
us for helping you.
And even if Lord
Aizen does forgive us,
the Espada would definitely
never forgive us. (GASPING)
Nell is not saying that Nell
wants you to take us with you.
Nell is just telling you this
so you don't worry about us.
The last thing Nell
wants is for you
to worry about Nell
and her friends!
And Nell is also
not saying that Nell
wants you to take us with you.
-So, when she says don't worry--
-What she really means
is, please worry.
-No, the last thing
Nell wants is for Ichigo
to worry about her poor
little body being crushed
by Lord Aizen and the Espada.
Nell will be perfectly
fine without Ichigo
looking after her--
-Fine!
Just be quiet, OK?
[crying]
-What the hell?
-Her voice is getting
fainter and fainter.
It almost sounds like she
fell underground or something.
-What do you mean,
fell underground?
How could that happen?
-Ichigo, wait!
[crying]
-Nell!
-Aahhh!
-That hurts!
-Watch where you're going, huh?
-Give me a break!
You're the ones who ran into me.
-What are you fools doing here?
-Yeah, and where's Nell?
-I don't know.
We heard her
screaming so we came
in here looking for Nell, too.
-Yeah, what he said.
-Huh?
Then where could she
have disappeared to?
-Ichigo, look.
-(GASPS) What the hell is that?
-You mean the
floor fell through?
-No, it's probably an
air shaft or something
that was built into the floor.
It looks to me like she fell
through when she ran by here.
-Damn, that kid
sure is a handful.
Why the hell does Hueco
Mundo have so many holes
lying around all over the place?
-Nell!
-You OK down there?
-So what now?
-It's not like we can
just leave her alone
down there to fend for herself.
-You've got to be kidding.
These guys are becoming
a real pain in the butt.
-You can say that again.
-Let's do this.
-(CRYING) Ichigo!
You big idiot!
Piece of garbage!
-(GASPING) Why did you come?
Nell doesn't really want
you to take her away anyway.
-Do you have any idea
how annoying you are?
Stay here.
I don't need you hanging around.
-(CRYING) You pretended
to come and save Nell.
But you just came
to pick on Nell.
-All right, already.
I get it.
Stop crying.
Would you give me a break?
I'll take you with me, OK?
You better now?
[crying]
-Come on, you've
got to be kidding.
What are you crying about now?
-What are they doing down there?
-Some kind of weird
comedy routine.
[crumbling]
-What's that?
-Huh?
-I hear it coming from above us.
-Uh oh!
[moaning in terror]
-Everyone, jump!
-OK, just blow your
nose and let's go.
-Ichigo!
Run!
-Hey, wait!
[yelling]
[thump]
-Hey, Nell!
You're safe!
-I'm glad you're OK.
-I wanna play, too!
-Get off me!
This nonsense has got to stop.
[crash]
-Whoa, that was close.
You know what I'm talking about?
-Whew!
You said it, brother.
-Ichigo, are you all right?
[rubble shfting]
-What idiots.
-Come on.
Let's find a way out here.
-Yeah, I'm with you.
-Let's see if there's a
staircase around or something
around here.
-Hey, you guys!
Wait!
-It sure is dark down here.
-Yeah, I know.
It's a good thing I'm here.
-Why?
-It's not like there's anything
you can do about it, is there?
-Well, you see, when
slightly tweaked a bit,
Kido can be used like this.
[ yelling Kido chant]
[music box music playing]
-(SARCASTICALLY) Wow.
That's a pretty small
light you've got there.
So, do you use it to help
you find the bathroom
in the middle of the night?
-You're a fool.
This happened because
he tried to look
cool by using [? ine shokai ?]
even though he's not
good at it.
-Well, don't worry about it.
We'll just use that red hair of
yours to guide our way tonight.
I even wrote a song
about it once, something
about a red-haired
Soul Reaper guiding
Santa's sleigh on a
foggy Christmas Eve.
-Ha ha, very funny.
[footsteps]
-Hmm.
What kind of place
is this, anyway?
I mean, do you
know if this place
was even here before Aizen came?
-Hmm.
The building above was
built by Lord Aizen,
but Nell doesn't know about
the basement part down here.
-Most likely this area was
part of an older building.
It's probably not used anymore.
-Well, I don't care either way.
Let's go upstairs
as soon as possible.
-Huh?
Hold on a second!
I saw a light.
-Huh?
I didn't see anything.
-I'll go check it out.
-I'll go, too!
-Hey, wait for us!
[labored breathing]
-Huh?
Where's the light?
-What the heck is it?
-This has got to be the exit.
The materials used to
make it are different.
Everything from
this point on must
be the newly built building.
In other words, it's not
abandoned like this area is.
Instead, it's being used now.
But we should try to be
cautious from this point on.
We don't know what--
-Uryu.
Move aside, will ya?
[kring]
[roars]
[explosion]
-Ah!
There are the stairs.
-Mmm.
It's another door.
Ichigo, you should
try to be more--
-All we gotta do is smash
through the wall and move on.
Nnngh!
[explosions]
-Huh.
We finally came to a
decent-looking place this time.
[flames crackling]
-The crossroad.
-How do we decide which
door to go through?
[shuddering walls]
-Mmph.
-Nell.
Sorry, but it looks
like we'll have
to part ways here after all.
The spiritual pressure
is too strong.
There's no way you guys
will be able to withstand it
from this point on.
I can't even imagine what
might be facing us ahead.
[thudding]
-There are five paths.
-We have to check
each one, starting
with the ones on the ends.
-No, let's each go down a
separate path at the same time.
-Mmm.
-That's just crazy!
I mean, we're talking
about Espada here!
If we all stand
together as one unit,
we'll have a better
chance against them!
Think about it. if
we become separated--
-Enough!
It's insulting to a warrior
be concerned about his life
while he's out in
the battlefield.
-Ehnghn.
-Ichigo, you say that because
you're worried about me,
but that's just not like you.
I didn't come here so
you could worry about me.
Believe me, I can take care of
myself, even without your help.
-Mmph.
(SIGHING) All right, then.
We'll go down separate paths.
-Good.
But before we do that, I
think we should probably
do a charm together.
-A charm?
-That's right.
It's a ritual that
the 13th Court Guard
Squad has used over
the years and it's
chanted before a big battle.
It's fallen out of use.
And to be honest,
there aren't many squad
that still do it anymore.
But I figure it's a good thing
to do at a time like this.
Come on, join hands.
Let's go.
If I can do it,
you can do it, too.
[sighs]
[hands smacking]
-As we approach the
crucial battlegrounds,
believe that our blades
will not shatter!
Believe that our
resolve will not weaken!
Though our paths may
diverge, our iron hearts
will remain together!
Swear that though the land
itself may break asunder,
we will come back here alive!
[guitar music]
[footsteps]
[piano music]
-Hey, they left!
You know what I'm talking about?
-So what should we do?
-Uhhhh, forget about it.
If we turn back now,
it'll still be dangerous.
[whimpering]
-Where are you going, Nell?
-Ichigo!
Nell is going after Ichigo!
-What?
Going after him?
-Nell had-- Nell had fun.
Nell had lots and lots of fun!
Nell still-- Nell
still wants to stay
with Ichigo and the others!
-What?
-Nell!
-All right!
Then we're going, too.
-Yeah!
Let's do it!
-Uhhh.
-Ehhh.
-Huh.
-There's only one problem.
Which way did Nell go?
[fire crackling]
-They belong to Lord Aizen, and
are for his purpose and use.
-She only hesitated
for an instant.
She didn't flinch
at my question.
She's a brave girl.
[footsteps]
-Hey.
Tell me, how's our
little pet doing today?
-Nnoitra.
-I know that Lord Aizen
decided to leave you
in charge of that
girl, Urukiora.
How wonderful.
Hmm.
Have you disciplined her yet?
-Mmph.
How vulgar.
[thump]
-Don't get so touchy!
I'm simply asking if things are
going OK in there, that's all.
Well?
-You're curious.
Don't worry yourself over
such trifling matters.
-Hmm?
Actually, what I meant
to say it was at the girl
was under Lord
Aizen's spell long
before she came to Hueco Mundo.
-His Kioka Suigetsu, huh?
-Of course not.
There's no need to use it
for something like this.
He placed her in several
psychological cages
when they brought her here,
which she won't escape from.
He ordered her to
surrender, and made
her unable to refuse by offering
to spare her friends' lives.
Afterwards, he gave
her a 12-hour reprieve
and allowed her to say
goodbye to one of her friends
on the condition that no
one else could see her.
-And you call that a cage?
-By giving her a
reprieve and allowing
her to say goodbye to a friend
in such a tense situation,
she'll mistakenly believe that
we've shown her some sympathy
and we are on her side,
which will eventually
weaken her will.
But in truth, her
friends' lives were not
actually at risk at all
during that 12-hour reprieve.
Furthermore, even though
she was forced to surrender,
by allowing her to choose
someone to say goodbye to,
she'd get the idea that
she had done so by.
Choice and by making to
return to the rendezvous
before taking her to
Hueco Mundo ensured
that she bought into
our plan completely.
The idea that she chose
us was etched even deeper
into her mind, and gradually she
will lose the will to run away.
Even you can understand that.
-Huh?
-The genius of the plan
is that by allowing
her to say goodbye to
one and only one person
without anyone
else knowing means
that she'd most likely leave
evidence behind of having
said goodbye to that person.
-So what of it?
If she left evidence
behind with a friend,
then we have completely failed!
-Quite the opposite.
The evidence of
having said goodbye
becomes undeniable
proof to our enemies
that she was
completely free to do
what she wanted until
the time she surrendered.
[spanish guitar music]
-In other words, the
stronger the evidence
was, the more her
friends would be
inclined to think that she
willfully betrayed them,
and that she wasn't, in
fact, taken against her will.
Though, that last part
wasn't a complete success.
But it is safe to say that
the Soul Society won't
be getting involved.
-Hmm.
That sure was well thought out.
I guess that's to
be expected when
you consider it's Lord Aizen.
-What do you mean,
well thought out?
This is a game of
strategy to Lord Aizen.
He would have had a
solution whether she
played into it or not.
But in any case,
right now that girl
does not have the
strength to run away.
She doesn't have the strength
or the will to defy us.
-I'm glad you've come, Orihime.
Sorry to call you
here on short notice.
There's something very important
that I'd like to show you.
[gasps]
-Loly, Menoly, leave us.
-Huh?
But, sir!
We can't leave you alone
with someone like her.
LOLY AND MENOLY: Excuse us, sir!
-That girl!
What is up with her?
-Now then.
This is what I wanted
to show you, Orihime.
[whoosh]
[clicking]
-(GASPING) What
is this sensation?
Could this be the--
-You can sense it, can't you?
You know that it's the Hogyoku.
But you may not know this.
Its sleep has been
recently disrupted.
It will awaken soon.
Without the Hogyoku, it is
impossible to transform Hollows
into Arrancars or
to create the Oken.
I've chosen to show this
to you for one reason--
to prove that I trust you.
You have a phenomenal power.
You can negate things
that have happened
and possess the ability
to wipe out entire events.
This is an incredible
power, a power
that is very useful to me.
Orihime, you'll use your
power for me, won't you?
-(GASPING) I don't think
he showed me the Hogyoku
because he trusts me, but at
least I know where the Hogyoku
is now.
And my power, it's true.
I can negate things
that have happened
and wipe out entire events.
Thank you, Ichigo,
for coming to save me.
But now I know what
I have to do here.
It's something
that only I can do.
I have to use my power to
erase the Hogyoku's existence!
[chuckles]
[footsteps]
[labored breathing]
[music playing in japanese]
-Renji, have you ever
done that chant before?
-No.
I suggested it to my
Captain several times,
but for some reason
he always ignores me.
-Rukia, ask him to do it for me.
-(SIGHING) Well--
You really think
Byakua would do that?