It's your call.
I'm Kugo.
Kugo Ginjo.
[Uryu]
He's fast! No ordinary
human can move that fast!
I don't see any changes in
the reishi surrounding him.
So then how is he able to
accelerate like that?!
Huh?
What was that?
A light?!
Hm?
[gasp]
- Oh!
- Look at that guy!
- Messed up!
- What happened?
- Did you see it?
[ambulence driving off]
I suppose there's no point
in worrying about stuff.
[Keigo]
Oh well, it's just
you and me today.
Hey, if it bugs you
that much I'll leave.
No! Don't do that!
Guess I'm just wonderin'
if Ichigo's okay.
I'm sure he's okay.
Something must've
just come up for him
at the last minute.
"Come up"...?
[Keigo]
You mean like that big
fight he had with the gang
who came looking for him
or when he got kidnapped
by that crazy boss of his?
Fighting, having a job.
He sure is living the
teen life big time.
What the?! Getting
kidnapped's his job?!
That's "living the life"?!?
Sounds more like
planning an
early death!
Hm?
Huh? What is it?
I've got this feeling
somebody's following us.
"Following us"? Why
in the world would
anyone be after us?
We're not Ichigo!
Look out! Move!!
Hnh?
Waagh!
Aah! Aaaah! Ahhhh!
That sure
was close.
I think I
peed my
pants.
Damn! Hey are you
kids all right?!
Just barely.
You moron!!
[construction worker]
Who did that?!
Watch what you're doing!
Thanks a lot,
Tatsuki.
Hey, were you by chance
following us just now?
What? "Following you"?
What're you talking about?
I just happened
to be walking by.
From what I saw, someone
just tried to drop a
steel beam on you.
You think it was
done on purpose?!
Don't scare us like that!
[Riruka]
Aaaw, did you blow it?
You brought him food and
he still turned you down?
That sucks!
But that's what you get
for being so cagey and
not showing me what that
Ichigo guy looks like!
I'd have to
agree, sir.
What are you two
doing here?
I thought I told you all to
stay and wait at the club.
Oh, you said that?!
Hey we're in this together,
you're not the boss of us!
Neither of us are here
to take orders from you.
First of all, you
have no persuasive
skills to speak of!
I should handle this one!
I'll persuade him in no time!
As I recall it was
Mr. Ginjo who persuaded
us to work for him.
Why don't you shut up!
You're the only one he
persuaded, Giriko!
He's not running things and
I'm not working for him,
Are we clear?!
And besides--
[gasp]
Put a sock in it.
I've heard enough.
[snarl]
Let's go.
Hanging on to the
past isn't my style.
So I'm through.
Hey Ichigo, guess what?!
Hm?
Check it out!!
It's the very first
test I took this year!
And I scored a 95
percent on it!
Aren't I awesome?!
That is awesome!
Way to go!
You should go and show Dad!
He'll be thrilled!!
Uhh..
Speaking of Dad, do
you know where he is?
I dunno.
When I woke up this
morning, he was gone and
he hasn't come back.
Oh yeah? Well I'm gonna
go relax in my room.
Oh, hey wait.
Hm? What d'ya need, Yuzu?
Uh.
[Yuzu]
It's nothing.
Never mind.
Hmm...
My cheeks are still red.
My whole plan was to
give him that bread and
then ask him a question;
I didn't expect him to
invite me to come in.
So come on in.
I mean, when he put
it that way, how
could I say no?!
Wanna come in?
And then he took me up to
his room, and told me to
take home what I wanted!
He is so sweet! So sweet!
The sweetest!
S - W - E - E--
Agh!
Uhh...
Sorry about
that, Brother!
[gasp]
So, hey.
Yeah?
I'm wondering, has
anything happened
to you recently?
[sip]
Not really. Why would you ask
something like that?
I just know it.
You're keeping something
from me, aren't you Ichigo?
[Ringtone]
You'll be fine.
Um-hm-hm!
That scared me!
Who'd call this late?
Oh, it's Uryu.
Hey! What's up, Uryu?
Huh?
Oh, hello.
Uh-huh? What?!
Where's Ichigo?
His room. I called
him but he said
he'll eat later.
Oh yeah?
In his room?
Y'know boys at his age.
All of them are just pervos.
Don't say that!
I don't like
talking about stuff
like that okay?
And besides, Ichigo isn't
that kind of boy at all!
Yea, yeah.
Listen, Yuzu, you'll be
better off once you drop
those ridiculous notions
you have about our brother.
I mean, he's a typical
boy, like all the rest.
He's not some anime
character.
So, of course, he's going
to be doing things--
I don't think that about him
and I don't care anymore!
I'm done talking to you!
Huh? Hey wait!
I didn't mean it
like that, Yuzu!
I was just teasing you!
Oh yeah?! Well just for that,
you can do the dishes tonight!
[slam]
Oh boy, Ichigo
must've given her
the brush off again.
I guess I better have
him go smooth things
over with her.
[slam]
Hm? Yuzu?
Ichigo! Hey,
where're you going?!
Hold up a sec!
Ichigo!
Uryu!
Ah! Oh, Ichigo!
[panting]
Orihime! So you're
already here.
Where's Chad?
He didn't pick up
when I phoned him.
He's probably still working
at his construction job.
[Uryu]
So he even gave Ichigo
a call? Really?
That was unnecessary.
Uryu.
You're so predictable.
You speak like an adult,
but it's still just talk.
I thought I wasn't supposed
to be allowed visitors here.
Couldn't my condition get
even worse from having
people come see me?
Don't be foolish.
Who do you think
operated on you?
Your wounds won't
get worse from
having visitors.
You're an amateur who
was slashed by an enemy
and nearly died.
You're not in any position to
be telling your doctor what
he should and shouldn't do.
[sigh]
Wait! He was what?!
An enemy cut you down?!
What's he talking
about, Uryu?!
It's none of your business.
Of course this is my business!
You were attacked
and almost killed!
Listen if you can't handle
this thing yourself, then
we'll have to do something
about it together!
Say something!
Sharing any
information is vital.
Don't you let my
efforts go to waste.
No one asked for
your opinion!
Hngghh!
Oh dear. That was close.
If you had yelled a few
more decibels higher,
you may have ripped all
of your sutures apart.
[wincing in pain]
Uryu...
I'm sorry Orihime,
there isn't anything I
can say to you right now.
Please go home.
Okay.
Ichigo?
Huh? Oh! I bet you've
gotta be pretty exhausted
by now, Orihime.
I'll walk
you home.
What?! No, but I...
Uh really?!
Ah!
Perhaps I'd better
drive her back myself.
And you should go home now.
I recall how your dad can be.
He'd probably give me
grief if he knew I had
you out this late.
I understand.
Thank you.
Ah!
Bye Ichigo! See you in
the morning at school!
Calm down, you
shouldn't be yelling
in a hospital.
Oh! I'm sorry!
Ichigo doesn't seem like
he'll be much help, so
I'll tell you this instead.
Uryu wasn't attacked
by a Hollow.
Huh?
But it wasn't by a
Soul Reaper, either.
I found residual
Spiritual Pressure
on his wounds.
And to be frank, I'm not
sure if I can call it
"Spiritual Pressure."
It was a kind of energy
signature unlike anything
I've ever come across.
What does that mean?
Don't ask me.
I have told you everything
that I know about this.
My thinking is that even
Uryu doesn't know a thing
about who attacked him.
So you see, it's not that
he didn't want to tell
you what happened to him.
It's just that he
had nothing to tell.
I see.
One thing is clear though.
Someone is targeting you kids.
Any thoughts who
might've done this?
No.
This is just my
hypothesis but...
Whoever attacked him possesses
some power we know nothing
about. This enemy is probably,
A human.
Someone who is less
like a Soul Reaper,
And more like you and Sado.
Since Uryu is a Quincy,
he would generally fall
into that category as well.
Assuming that the
attacker was human and
had been targeting individuals
with unique abilities,
It's logical that the
next person in line
could be Sado or you.
Ah!
[Ryuken]
Be careful.
Hey wait! Hold up
Rukia, I said wait!
Don't you understand
the meaning of "wait"?!
What do you want?
"What do I want"?
Do I have to want something
just to talk to you?
You fool, don't stop me for
something as trivial as that.
Besides...
Hnh?
Who are you anyway?
What the?
It seems that things aren't
going as we had planned.
Well that's all right.
Let's try a different
approach.
[Ichigo]
Morning guys.
[sigh]
Umm. What's up you two?
Hurry up and start
eating, c'mon.
Oh sure!
I've got an idea! What do
you say we go shopping
after school today?
Didn't you say there were
some things you wanted?
'Kay.
Go bowling?
Yeah! This is our last
year together, right?
College entrance exams and stuff
are just around the corner,
so this might be our
only chance to go and
have some real fun!
I don't see why you're
trying so hard to create
happy memories for us.
Let's just do what
we always do.
You don't get it, do you?
Who knows what might
happen to us!
Live for today!
I mean, just
yesterday--
Uhh...
Um-um.
What happened?
Uh... Just yesterday...
This uh...
He thought some hot girl was
following him, but instead it
turned out it was Tatsuki.
Right! True story but
funny, huh? Ha ha ha ha!
Yeah, funny.
Sorry guys, but I
promised to take my
sisters shopping today.
See ya later.
It's best we don't
tell him, right?
I think so.
Huh?
Yuzu!
Hey, Ichigo!
Where's Karin?
She's running a little
late, so she said for
us to go ahead.
Mh.
I see! Well then,
shall we get going?
Mm... Sure.
Huh?
Isn't that...?
It's that punk from
the other day!
Why's he
looking at us?
[labored breathing]
[Tatsuki]
Ichigo!
Weren't you with
Keigo and Mizuiro?
I was but I left, 'cause
I'd made plans to hang
out with my sisters.
Hello there.
So what's up,
Tatsuki?
Oh, hey!
I told them that we'd try and
meet up later, but I can't
seem to reach them now.
They're just
not answering.
Maybe their phone's
out of range or their
battery's dead.
I'm hoping that's
all it is.
But after
what happened
yesterday...
Hnh?! Yesterday?
What are you
talking about?
So they didn't tell you
what happened to them?
Hm?
[creepy breathing]
You're telling me
they got attacked
by someone?!
What? I don't
know! But...
What are you
waiting for,
Ichigo?
[gasp]
Yuzu...!
They're your friends, right?
Then go and help them!
Sorry about
this, Yuzu.
Let's go!
Uh, right!
Dammit! I can't
reach them either!
Hey Tatsuki,
let's split up!
You go check the area
over by the bowling
alley. Got it?
Right!
I'll go and check
out where they were
attacked yesterday.
It's the high-rise
construction site
on Third street!
Got it!
Keigo! Mizuiro!
[gasp]
Look out!!
Huh?
[Ichigo]
So, you did this?!
Why'd you go after
these guys?!
If you wanted revenge
then attack me!
Me, "Revenge"?
It's not about that.
I was just asked by
someone to do this!
Asked by someone?!
That's right!
Agh!
Dagh!
Damn! If I didn't
have to hold this up!
But you do!
You're stuck here!
I'm gonna take down your friends
one after the other!
Gaagh!
And when they're gone,
then I'll get your family!
Hnh!? You what?!
Heh.
No way in hell!
Raaagh!
[panting]
Who was it?
Answer me!
[gasp]
Who're you?
Wait!
[chuckle]
Hey! Hold it!
Dammit.
[Ryuken]
Let him go.
Ryuken?
I'm glad he sensed my Spiritual
Pressure and decided to leave.
Uh, why're
you here?
Just walking by.
That guy.
Who was he?
Probably some punk
just looking to
get into a fight.
That's not
what happened!
Those guys, did they
attack your son?
These two
will be okay.
They're unconscious,
but they're not
seriously injured.
Just to be safe I'll call
an ambulance for them.
As for you, don't get
involved any further.
Tch! I have to!
I can help out!
Then let me ask
you something.
Just what can you do?
What's going on here, dammit!
I'm not understanding
any of this!
Damn it!
Isn't there anything
I can do to stop it?!
Here's some advice.
Act now while
you can.
That's if you want to
protect your family.
[recorded female voice]
You have reached X-cution.
This card number is
currently unregistered.
Are you a new member?
If so, please say your name now.
Ichigo... Kurosaki.
Thank you.
Mister Ichigo Kurosaki.
We have been
expecting your call.
Welcome to
X-cution.
[Ichigo]
Uryu's dad!
How's Uryu doing?
[Ryuken]
It's not your concern.
And don't address me
as "dad."
[Ichigo]
Then Uryu's father...?
[Ryuken]
Don't address
me as "father"!
[Uryu]
Ryuken!
Who cares about that?!
[Ryuken]
Uryu, it's okay for you to
address me as "Daddy."
[Uryu]
No way!