[grunting]
[roaring]
Not bad...
The power you just displayed...
It's a lot
closer to the power that
you once possessed.
[gasping]
Uh!
Invaders must die.
What the hell's this?!
I get it.
You don't want me coming
in contact with Ichigo
Kurosaki when his powers
are still incomplete.
Especially since he is so very
close to perfecting them...
That right... Yukio?
Hey!...What just
happened?!
Where the hell am I?! Let
me out! Now!!
[gasping]
No-Not this time!
[grunting]
Mm.
Looks like I'm
too late.
With Ichigo's powers so close
to being fully formed,
you saved him from coming
in contact with me.
But you made a mistake...
Why wouldn't you have confined
me in your console instead?
I thought of that, but I didn't have
enough battery life to hold you as well.
And besides, the truth is, that
wasn't why I saved Kurosaki anyway.
Hey. You hear that down
there?
Huh?
Looks like we've attracted a crowd,
the police, fire department...
Those explosions we made
do attract attention.
TV news choppers might
even be here soon.
This is turning into big
pain for us, but isn't
all of this posing a
problem for you, too?
The Love Gun?
That's right! And you know
exactly what it can do!
'Cause you're the one
who made it!
Hurry up and get lost,
will you?
As you know, I'm not so
calm in these situations.
It's time to get going, Mr.
Tsukishima.
But if you're thinking
you want to make a scene
instead, then I'd suggest you
stay here and go for it.
Hm.
Uh--
All right, you win.
I'll see you again,
Riruka.
Hmm.
We should get going as well.
We'll take Ichigo and Jackie.
[groaning in pain]
Huh?!
[groaning]
Chad! What's wrong?!
What is it?!
[knocking]
Come in.
Hi Uryu.
Thank you for coming on short notice.
I appreciate you making the time.
Oh, don't mention
it. How are you feeling?
A lot better,
thanks.
That's good. So
then, what's up?
Well...
I need your help with my wounds I
want you to heal them right now.
Oh?
Sure, that's not a
problem, but why now?
Things have changed. Ichigo has made
contact with the guy who did this to me.
[gasping]
His Spiritual Pressure's a lot different
than it was before, but it was
definitely Ichigo's. I'm not sure
what suddenly caused it to change,
but I do know that I can't spend
anymore time sitting here.
You felt it too, right
Orihime?
Um, yes, I have.
But Ichigo hasn't exactly
said anything to me about
it, so I've just been
trying to give him space.
But I--
I've got this feeling that
the person who attacked
you, was the same presence
I sensed around Ichigo.
And I think... that's the same
person who attacked me as well.
What did you say?!
There. He's done
loading.
Where am I?
Our other hideout. But compared
to where we were-it's a rathole.
Hey, now. Make statements like that
and I'll stop buying you nice things.
You don't even help out, but you
sure do complain a lot. Don't ya?
You know it's gonna be
my money that'll end
up paying to repair our
last hideout, right?
Sorry.
You had a lot to do with
those two explosions.
So now should I rebuild it all from
scratch? Or go ahead and fix it up
the way it was, I sure wish
someone would chip in.
Maybe you should take
that up with Chad.
When he wakes up, I will.
Hey Chad!
Hold it!! Isn't anybody gonna
thank me for looking after them?!
Uh!
Actually, Chad and Jackie's
injuries were nothing.
You don't have to get
all theatrical on us.
Know what? I bet if we just wait
a sec they'll wake right up.
[lightly grunting]
Chad!
How you feelin', Chad?
You all right?
Uh--
Chad?
Wha--uh, yeah.
I'm okay.
It's nothing serious.
That's good.
So what about that guy,
Tsukishima?
Looks like he's retreated...
for now, anyway.
Is something bothering
you?
Kind of.
If he had really wanted
to put it to us in that
situation, all he'd of had
to do was keep fighting.
Especially with the kind
of power he possesses.
Riruka was well inside of
Tsushima's attack radius, and
he could've cut down Yukio
easily, if he had meant to.
Was the reason he didn't
attack them because he
was actually only interested
in you as a target?
Or... Did he have some other
reason for acting the way he did?
You're overthinking
this.
Tsushima already knows full
well the nature of my powers.
He's quite aware that
he couldn't attack me
while I was holding that
terminal in my hand.
Or he wouldn't have another
chance of fighting Ichigo again.
That makes sense... Hm?
Kutsuzawa, how'd it go?
Everything has been
smoothed over.
The police, fire department,
reporters and neighbors have been
reassured and calmed down and
they've all gone back home.
Excellent work.
All right, then. I'll
start working on an
estimate. Man, what a
headache this is gonna be.
Wait a sec Yukio.
Huh?
You stay here and help
Ichigo work on his training.
What?! Why would I do
that?!
There's nothing I can
do to help him!
Besides-this thing's
almost dead!
I asked you because I know you can assist
him. Just use it with the cord plugged in.
After what I just went through-I
don't wanna help out!
Stop whining and
listen to me!
I don't know exactly how Tsukishima
found our hideout, but it's
reasonable to assume that he
traced our Spiritual Pressure.
And if that's what made
it easy for him...
Your Fullbring, which we know has the power
to completely block Spiritual Pressure
is essential to Ichigo's
training and survival.
Do you understand?
Fine. I'll do it.
We are talking about
fighting, right?
Yeah, we are. After all, that's what
seems to work the best for you.
All right. But I already
defeated Jackie.
So who will I up against
this time around?
Hm. That
would be me.
Mm.
That's strange.
You and I were attacked by
the same person but based
on the extent of your
injuries versus mine...
I'd say, that suggests an enemy
with different capabilities...
Maybe. Oh, did you
notice a sweet smell?
A sweet smell?
Let me try to remember... was it honey?
Could that have been it?
Oh! And another thing!
His weapon looked a lot like a Zanpakuto,
but he said it was called a Fullbring.
Did the person who attacked you
mention something like that as well?
Sorry. Unfortunately, I didn't have
the time to ask him any questions.
But until I just heard you mention
it, I had been assuming that the
sword he used was some
type of Zanpakuto.
Uh--
Hnh?
Hi, Chad!
Orihime.
Hey, were you at the
hospital?
Yeah, I was just there
healing Uryu's wounds.
I see. How'd it go?
He seems to be doing much better, but I'd
say he still needs more time to rest.
It's weird. They don't seem
to be the kind of injuries
sustained by an ordinary
Spirit Energy attack.
Interesting. Glad we met up. I've been
wanting to ask you how Uryu was doing.
You can tell me more as
we walk.
Huh?!! Whoa-Wait-Hold on
Chad! Where are we going?
To go help Ichigo.
From here on, Ichigo's training
will require your powers!
Oh!
Okay, let's get
started...
So, uh, this is the exact same place
as I was being held in earlier.
That's right.
This is Yukio's Fullbring.
It's called Invaders Must Die.
He can capture a target
in another dimension
and then control it
on his game screen.
But no worries, I've already
told him not to interfere.
So have you ever fantasized
about being inside a game?
What? No.
Come on, admit it. Every kid's thought of
it, it's nothing to be embarrassed about...
I've never obsessed about it
but I have had the thought.
Really? Well I've never had
that thought, not even once.
Then why'd you make me
say it?
Well, whether you had
that thought or not
doesn't really make much
of a difference, here.
So then why didja make me
say it?!
You know, this could be quite a bit
different than what you imagined it to be.
I'm guessing you're kind
of surprised that this
is what being inside
of a game feels like.
Well yeah. It's definitely a lot emptier
than I expected it to be in here.
Emptier? Fine, then.
Huh?!
You want livelier,
huh? So, how's that?
It's like a game from
the early 90's.
Yukio, there's no need
to dress things up here.
Hmph.
Uh--
So now that you've entered this
game space for your training,
we'll be using rules
that work for a game.
And so, what does
that mean?
Don't worry, we won't make it too
complicated. It's all pretty simple.
Yukio! Can you give us a
life gauge?
Um-hm! Do you want it matched
to your current health?
No, make it an even six
for each of us.
Okay.
Nice. There we go.
So it's game over when those
6 life signs are gone, huh?
Exactly.
So do you need an
explanation of game over?
Are you kidding me?
I think I've got it.
When it's game over for
you, I'll have a "You
Die" icon appear for
you to let you know.
That's very clever.
Ready?
Sure.
Cross of Scaffold!
Three... two... one.
[screaming]
Hm?
What is this?
Chad! Who's that girl?!
This is Orihime.
Oh, her! You're
the one.
Uh!
Oh! Well, hi there!
Mm.
Orihime,
this is Riruka.
Pleased to meet you.
Chad told me about you. He says that
you can heal people's wounds quickly.
So why'd you come here? To help
Ichigo after he takes a beating?!
[grunting]
[roaring]
Come on, Riruka...
That's right.
You realize what you'll be doing-right?
If you go healing his injuries,
that just means he's going
to get injured even more.
He'll keep fighting, keep getting
hurt, and suffer over and over again.
I know.
So you're worried for
Ichigo, too, aren't you?
[gasping]
Huh?! Uh-- no,
I'm not!
Hey!
He can't help it, you
know?
Uh--
But, I had to face up to his stubborn-ness
and get past it a long time ago.
Uh!
If Ichigo ever needs my help to
do what he's decided to do...
Regardless of what it is, I would
use all of my power to help him.
Oh?
And what would happen if
Ichigo were to suffer a really
terrible injury that he
could never recover from?
Nothing. Because I won't
ever let that happen.
It doesn't matter how
bad the injury is...
I will heal all his
wounds completely!
[groaning]
[gasping]
[grunting]
He swings that huge sword as
though it weighs nothing!
[grunting]
[gasping]
Hnh!-I see you!
[grunting]
You certainly have improved quite
a bit at managing your Fullbring.
And yet...
[gasping]
You still have a
long way to go!
Um!
I say! Hello there.
Kugo. We have a visitor.
I'm letting her in.
Huh?!
Ah! So the healer is
finally here!
Oh! Hi there-How do you do, sir?
It's such a pleasure!
Skip the greetings. You're just in time to
do a job. Now, hurry up and go heal him.
[gasping]
Ichigo!
[struggling]
Come on.
How stupid.
So the next'll be the
last of it-right?
Now, Isshin... you're
sure about this?
Well, sure I'm sure! How many
times are you gonna ask me?!
A father can rob his son
of his future. It's
only right that I verify
numerous times that
you're really
certain.
I know that. So I'm telling you to stop
asking me before I change my mind.
Hm. Well, I suppose
you're right.
Let's move on to our final step, then.
Shall we?
Okay, just place your Spirit
Energy in here and it's all done.
Whenever
you're ready.
Right.
Our next episode will be
a New Years special.
Wow, looks like a cavalcade
of Soul Reapers.
Who knows?
I can pretty much tell
from what we're seeing.
You don't really believe what's being
shown is going to be in the show, do you?
What?! It's not?!
That, is a secret.
Wait!-It is?!?