[theme music]
Sosuke Aizen had
kidnapped Orihime Inoue
and taken her to Hueco Mundo.
The Soul Society assumed Sosuke
was using her for her ability
to reject phenomena, in
order to restore the Hogyoku.
So they sent the captains
of the 13 Court Guard squads
to rescue her.
However, in truth,
Orihime was merely
bait to lure them closer.
Sosuke's actual plan was to
wipe out the enriched spirit
zone of Karkura Town.
This would allow him
to create the Oken
and eventually take over
the entire Soul Society.
Sosuke sealed off the
gateway to Hueco Mundo,
trapping Ichigo and the others.
Then, along with Gin
Ichimaru and Kaname Tosen,
he set out to
invade Karkura Town.
But Head Captain Yamamoto
saw right through the plan.
He ordered Kisuke Urahara
to ready the remaining
captains for the showdown.
Kisuke created a device
called the Tenkai Kecchu.
It acted as a huge Senkaimon,
surrounding Karkura Town.
And with it, the
Soul Society was
able to build a replica
of the entire town
and switch places
with the real thing.
YAMAMOTO: Excellent.
It seems we made
it here in time.
-Made it in time?
Now, why would you think
to say something like that?
I'm well aware that
what lies beneath you
is not Karkura Town.
This may come as a surprise,
but that means nothing to me.
If Karkura Town is now
inside the Soul Society,
we'll just kill you right
here and create the Oken
within the Soul Society.
It is that simple.
Until then, I shall
leave Las Noches
under your care, Ulquiorra.
-Sir.
-[gasp]
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): I
know what my job is.
It's to protect my friends.
[gasping]
-[scream]
[gasp]
[roar]
-[whimper]
[groaning]
-Huh?
EIKICHIRO: Little
lady, you all right?
Whoo, boy.
Looks like that spiritual
pressure got him good.
Man, I'm telling you, the
spiritual pressure around here
is all kinds of crazy.
In fact, if you and me don't
get that heck out of here,
we could wind up bugging out,
just like that gang of freaks.
Oh, and by the way, I can
see your panties, FYI.
-Huh?
OH!
-[laughs]
-Mister, who are you, anyway?
-Huh?
Who, me?
-Mhm.
--[sigh] Well, the
name's Eikichiro Saido.
Just a small-time Soul
Reaper who recently got put
in charge of this district.
-So you're small time, then?
-Oh, ouch.
Never mind.
Listen, missy, if you stick
around here much longer,
you're going to end up
deader than those monsters.
So do me a favor and
get lost, will ya?
Oh, brother.
Mm.
Looks like some pretty rough
business is about to go down.
Well, good or bad, it'll
be interesting to see
how this thing turns out.
-His spiritual
pressure is monstrous,
just like I remember it.
-If you're so scared, then
why don't you run away?
Coward.
-So I assume our first priority
is going after the leader.
-Not quite.
Sosuke's powers
are very special.
If we have any chance
of attacking him,
we have to beat those
around him first.
-Jushiro, among
those three Espadas,
which one do you figure
is the strongest?
-Hard to say.
Sosuke is the one who knows.
-The problem is, while
we're fighting the Espadas,
there's no guarantee whatsoever
that Sosuke and his men
won't get in the way.
-You're right.
-All right.
You should stand back.
All things in the
universe turn to ashes.
Ryujin Jakka!
-Take cover, Jushiro.
-Right.
-Huh?
[shout]
YAMAMOTO: Jokaku Enjo.
We are safe.
This wall of flames are to
keep Sosuke and his cohorts
at bay for quite some time.
Now then, we shall
show them no mercy.
End them at once!
-The Head Captain's
rather drastic.
-It just goes to show
you how seriously old man
Yama's treating this threat.
-[gasp]
-Sosuke.
ICHIMARU: Whoo!
I'm Sure is toasty in here.
The Head Captain went a little
overboard, don't you think?
Well, Captain, Aizen?
What's going to
be our next move?
We can't have any fun while
we're stuck in this furnace.
-We wait.
This battle will come
to an end without us
having to lift a finger.
You'll see.
-Are you afraid?
You're useless to
Lord Aizen now.
There is no one
here to protect you.
You are alone.
It's over.
You will die here.
You will die all by yourself,
with no one to witness it.
So I want to know, how
frightened are you?
-I am not at all.
You see, now I know that my
friends came to rescue me.
So right now, my heart--
my heart is with them.
[roaring]
ULQUIORRA: What nonsense.
You're not scared because your
friends have come for you?
You can't be serious.
You really think
they can save you?
-Absolutely.
-Getsuga Tensho!
ORIHIME: When I was told
they were coming here
to get me, at
first, I was happy.
But it also made me sad.
After all, the
reason I came here
was so I could protect them.
I thought, why did
they have to come?
Didn't they realize
what I was trying to do?
But then, when I
felt Rukia's pain,
and when I saw Ichigo
fighting with all his might,
I finally realized
none of that mattered.
But still, I couldn't bear
to see Ichigo get hurt.
I desperately wanted
everyone to be safe.
And that's when it hit me.
They must have felt the
same way that I did.
I mean, if one of them suddenly
went missing like I did,
there's no question I would do
the exact same thing for them.
-[grunt]
[gasp]
-You must be the
intruder, Ichigo Kurosaki.
-[groaning]
-I am Rudborrn, the
captain of the Exequias.
And I am here to
claim your life.
Your life now belongs to me.
You will go no further.
-Sorry, pal.
But I really don't have the time
to waste on some horned freak,
OK?
-That is fine.
I do not have any time
to waste on you either.
[fighting noises]
-Damn it.
How many of them are there?
[shouting]
-[laughs] Yeah!
Want some more?
-What?
Renji!
-Heh.
-El Directo!
[shouting]
-Hey, Chad!
-You fools, letting a minor
obstacle ruin our mission.
RUKIA: Tsugi no mai, Hakuren!
-Rukia!
-Idiot!
Save the heartwarming
reunion for later.
Now get going, Ichigo.
-I'm on it.
-Oh, that guy.
He still needs a babysitter.
RUDBORNN: You honestly
thought you could best me
with those feeble powers?
You are nothing more
than a small nuisance.
-Ridiculous.
No matter what you think, the
fate of you and your friends
is already decided.
Even if they do
manage to find you,
it will not change the fact
that you are going to die.
There's no turning
back from that now.
Sharing your
feelings with someone
when you're on
the verge of death
brings some sort of
comfort to you humans.
It's an instinct to help
minimize your fear and sorrow.
But in reality, it is impossible
to know another's emotions.
Empathy is simply a
meaningless human delusion.
ORIHIME: That may be true.
It might be impossible to feel
exactly what someone else is
feeling.
But when people truly
care about each other,
their hearts grow
so close, you can't
tell the difference
between them.
Please don't die!
Don't die, Ichigo!
You don't have to win, but you
don't have to fight for me.
Just don't get hurt.
I couldn't bear it.
That's what it
must mean when they
say two people are of one heart.
-Your heart, you say.
You humans always
toss around that word
so casually, as
if it's something
you can hold in the
palm of your hand.
But my eyes can see everything.
Nothing exists that I can't see.
So if I can't see
it, it's not real.
That is what I believe.
Tell me, what is a heart?
If I tore a whole in your
chest, would I see it?
If I split open your
skull, would it be there?
[gasp]
[rumbling]
[theme music]
RENJI: Roar, Zabimaru!
CHAD: El Directo!
RUKIA: Hakuren!
ICHIGO: Whoa, guys!
Want to take it down a notch?
RENJI: We haven't been
on the show in forever!
We got to make our mark.
[laughter]
ICHIGO: I kind of feel
sorry for the Exequias now.