[theme music]
-Ha!
-Zeige dich, Dalk.
-Shall I deal with them?
[laughter]
[screams over radio]
-What is happening there?
Report at once!
-Dammit.
I told them to wait.
We've got to help them.
[gasp]
-Oh, no.
-Are you all right?
-What happened here?
-My apologies, captain.
I failed.
I thought that we
could capture him,
but-- but then his
Doll took us out.
-It's all right.
Don't worry.
I'll call for help.
Just rest.
The Ryoka's probably close by.
Let's move.
Based on his fighting
style, it seems likely
that this Bount was
the same one that Izuru
fought in the world
of the living.
If so, he's very powerful.
Be careful.
-Yes, sir!
-Captain Hitsugaya!
Rangiku!
-Renji.
-Well, what's going on?
Are we having a party here?
-Renji.
How did you find us?
-We followed the Bounts'
spiritual pressure.
-The Bounts' spiritual pressure?
-Ah, that's right.
That's this little
one's special ability.
-Yes.
That is my job, and I do it
quite well, if I say so myself.
-What is the meaning of this?
-Weren't you told about
Kurodo here, Captain?
He's one of the mod-souls
Ichigo and the others
used in the world of the
living to track the Bounts.
-Pleased to meet you, Captain.
-That's a mod-soul?
I have heard of them,
but why would one
take a form like that?
-Well, that would take a
while to explain, you see.
-Have Ichigo and the others
actually found such things
to be useful?
-Yes.
He isn't quite as
worthless as he looks.
-Why, what a thing to say!
-All right, then.
Lieutenant, I'll need
to borrow your mod-soul.
-Huh?
-You're going to
carry Kurodo, Captain?
-Don't we look just fabulous?
-Well, that might not be
such a bad combination.
-No.
Not me.
-You'll be carrying it.
-Aw.
That's no fun.
-Uh, I'm happy to lend
it to you, Captain,
but then what will I do?
-I need you to
stay here and take
care of my injured men, Renji.
-Again I'm getting
left out of the fight.
-You'll get your
chance soon enough.
-Well, what do you know?
It looks like I'm back to being
carried by a real lady again.
That's a definite improvement
over being bounced around
by some rough riding brute.
-Just what are you saying?
-Oh, a little
jealous now, are we?
-Are we on the
Bount's trail now?
-Yes.
In fact, I'm certain of it.
-Then what should we do?
-Surround him.
We don't know how much they've
learned about the Soul Society
in the time they've
been here, but it's
safe to assume that we still
know it better than they do.
-Understood.
Squad 10, calling all units.
The targeted Bount has been
tracked to Northern District
2, center street number two.
Target is currently on the
move, believed heading south.
Groups one and two are to
reverse direction at once
and proceed through
Eastern District 6.
Groups three and four are
to reroute and close off
all connecting roads.
All other teams
converge on the target.
-The noose is getting
tighter and tighter.
-Well, what do we do?
-Oh, my!
Something's changed!
-What is it?
-Its spiritual
pressure just weakened.
-Really?
Then which direction is he in?
-It's that way!
-Toward Eastern District 7.
-Wait.
Did the spiritual pressure
disappear completely?
-No.
It's still moving, but it
suddenly became weaker.
-Hm.
What could he be up to?
[sigh]
-Why are we walking
down here in this sewer?
I'm likely to rust.
-If we lay low here,
it'll buy us some time.
-Oh, but I'm still
not satisfied.
I want to cut loose.
To fight, and kill, and maim.
-You'll have to wait.
Right now we have to
find out where Kariya is.
We don't dare leave him
alone for very long.
-My, what an interesting
thing to say.
-What do you mean?
-It sounds like you
don't trust Kariya.
-Something like that.
-Did you quarrel?
-I'm afraid it's a
little more complicated.
-What's the conflict, then?
-We have different
points of view.
Hide.
-Huh?
-Keep your eyes open.
-Check over there!
-I don't see them.
-Hm.
Even down here,
we can't get away.
-What are we going to do?
Just keep hiding from them?
-No.
We have to break
through somehow.
The only way is to attack.
-Was I right?
-Yes.
The Bount seems to be using
the underground passages.
-Ah, you truly are a
captain, despite your size.
Because you take notice of
things others would overlook.
-He'll surface when he
realizes that we're on to him.
If I could only track him while
he's still in the underpass.
-All units in the
Western Districts
report to the
underpass for backup.
-Unit Three responding.
-Understood.
-Changing course to
the northwestern roads
to provide backup.
-Ha ha!
-We've encountered
the Ryoka's doll.
RANGIKU (OVER RADIO):
What's your location?
-Western District 6,
street number three.
The middle of the third
block from the north.
-Good.
Try and lure the target
out into a wider area,
then wait for backup.
-Let's go.
Right.
[shouting]
-Ah.
A little mayhem was
just what I needed.
Although they were
pretty worthless.
-Hm.
-Unit Three,
respond immediately.
-The spiritual pressure
has disappeared again.
It looks like yet
another battle has
ended, and with
us as the losers.
Enough of your
useless commentary.
-Sorry.
-Send this to all units.
No rash attacks upon
the Ryoka or his Doll.
Report in and stand
by for backup.
-This is Unit Six.
We've arrived at Southern
District street number four.
RANGIKU (OVER RADIO):
Any sign of the Ryoka?
-Negative.
-There it is again!
I'm getting a strong Bount
spiritual pressure signal.
-From where?
-Well, it's somewhere around
the area of Southern District,
and maybe street number four.
-Are you positive?
But that's the group I was
just communicating with.
Unit Six, the
target is confirmed.
Right there, in your vicinity.
-Understood.
He's close now, men.
Keep your eyes open.
-Yeah.
-Unit Six requesting
immediate backup
at Southern street number four.
-Have you noticed?
Each team has a butterfly
for communication.
All right, Dalk.
I want you to destroy them all.
All at the same time.
-Aw.
Poor things.
But very well, I'll try.
[gasp]
-Captain.
The hell butterflies.
-What's wrong?
MAN (OVER RADIO: Lieutenant!
The hell butterflies are-- argh!
-Oh, no!
It looks like the
Bount has figured
out our means of communication,
and has cut it off!
-I've lost contact with all
of the patrols, Captain.
-Lieutenant!
Come in, Lieutenant!
-Ah.
Hello there, boys.
Do you want to play?
-Now, Dalk.
-Here goes!
-Oh!
What a disaster!
-Hey!
He's alive.
-This one's still
breathing, too.
-This one, also.
And this one's still alive, too.
I imagine we ought to be
glad he let them live,
instead of killing them.
But I wonder why?
-Take care of them.
-But Captain--
-Listen, mod-soul.
Tell me, where is his
spiritual pressure?
-It-- it's headed this way!
-I thought so.
-Captain.
What are you going to do?
He knew that we were
operating in group in concert
with each other.
This has been his
plan all along.
To defeat all of the
suborindates one by one,
and then wait for the
commander to come out.
-Are you planning
to face him alone?
-That's right.
Take care of the
wounded, Rangiku.
-I understand, sir.
Please, be careful.
-And good luck.
-Are you the captain?
-Yes.
You injured my men.
-I did hold back, though.
I try not to hurt young
people, if it can be avoided.
-I suppose I should
thank you for that, then.
But it doesn't mean
I'll go easy on you.
So get ready.
-Very well, then.
Zeige deke, Dalk.
-Oh, my.
Hello there.
What a cute little boy.
Are you here to play with me?
You simply are impatient.
Oh!
You've scarred me, you
horrid little brat.
[scream]
-Ha.
You're pretty good.
But you shouldn't
have done that.
Like any disobedient
child, you must
be captured and
severely punished!
-Rain over the frosted heavens.
Hyorinmaru!
-Bring it on!
Ha ha Ha ha!
Looks like I caught you.
Huh?
What's this?
It's-- it's cold!
[scream]
-No, Dalk!
Dalk.
You must return.
It's dangerous to
separate and reassemble
when you're still frozen.
-Don't worry, I'm all right.
I can still fight.
I'll deal with the cold somehow.
-No, Dalk.
Stop.
-That's it!
-That ought to teach you
not to ignore me, boy!
Ha ha ha!
[scream]
-Dalk, pull back.
-No, I can't quit now.
Don't worry, I can
handle this by myself.
Don't you know, Soul Reaper?
No hunk of snow and ice can
defeat my burning heart!
-No, Dalk!
[laughter]
[scream]
-Dalk!
No!
Dalk!
-I'm sorry.
I was defeated.
-It's all right.
You fought bravely, Dalk.
-Thank you.
I'm glad you're
with me to the end.
-It's different
from the reports.
-What is?
-Well, I was told that
a Bount disappears
as soon as he loses
his Doll in a battle.
Not true?
-Hmph.
-What?
-Each member of our tribe
has had his own role to play.
Mine was to train the young, to
grow into full fledged Bounts
as soon as possible.
There were those who grew
up well, and those who,
for whatever reason, didn't.
Something from long
ago just came to me.
-What is all of this about?
And why the hell
are you rambling
instead of answering
my question?
-Yes.
I heard you.
The reason I haven't
collapsed yet is simply this.
I'm still here because
Dalk isn't dead.
-What?
What's that?
-This is Dalk.
This is her core.
Her essence lives on
within this blade of steel.
As a captain of the 13
Court Guards Squads,
you are everything I expected.
In order to get past you, I will
have to use my full strength.
I have something I
must do, and nothing
will stop me from pursuing it.
If you persist on
standing in my way,
I will have no choice
but to eliminate you.
-I'm not about to let you go.
-Quite a bit of
Dalk's power remains
concentrated in this axe blade.
I'm going to add my
spiritual pressure to it.
Then I'm going to
strike you down.
Let's go, my Dalk.
-What's this?
[shouting]
-This spiritual pressure.
I guess this is where the
battle begins for real.
In that case, I'd better
start getting serious as well.
Bankai!
Daiguren Hyorinmaru.
-I expected no less from a
captain of the 13 Court Guard
Squads.
Still, I have absolutely no
intention of losing to you yet!
[shouting]
-Damn!
Do you still plan to fight?
-I have no choice but to
keep going after Kariya.
[shouting]
-Your body won't be
able to withstand
all the reishi you've absorbed.
-Then I'll have to finish this
now before it breaks down.
Let's do it, Dalk.
[shouting]
-Huh?
-So this is the end.
I guess I'm the loser.
-What were you planning to
do when you found Kariya?
-There wouldn't have been
anything I could have done.
But in any case, that dispute's
between no one but me and him.
-Where did you think you were
going to go once all of this
was over?
-To a future where
there would be no wars.
[theme music]
MAN: Ikkaku!
We've finally
received our orders
to search for the Bounts!
IKKAKU: About time!
UYRU: Um--
IKKAKU: Let's cut loose!
MAN: We can do whatever we want
to the Bounts we catch, right?
IKKAKU: Yeah!
It's first come, first served!
URYU: Hello?
MAN: I'm going to
get them first!
IKKAKU: What?
URYU: Do you think
I should let them
know that there's
only one Bount left?
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers.
I haven't shown up much lately.
I'm sorry, but I must go.
-Oh!
Kon!
-Forgive me and forget me, baby.
-Don't go!
-I've got places I've gotta go.
I can't be sippin' tea in a
tea house at a time like this.
But I will always remember
the wonderful days
I've spent here
with you as-- ah!