[Toshiro]
That Rangiku is getting
to be too much.
She's always putting off her
duties to go out and have fun.
[Rangiku]
I want to wish all of
you, a Happy New Year!
[group]
Happy New Year!
Hunh! I swear,
she is such a...
Hey! What the?!!!
And good health
to all of us!
[giggling girls]
Are you kidding me?!
Now listen up, everyone!
Let the Women's Soul Reaper
Association New Year's
celebration party begin!
Let's start with our
Chairperson passing out cash
gifts for the New Year.
[all]
Thank you very much!
[Rangiku]
This envelope is
just the cutest!
I should say so,
but, a giraffe??
A cat.
Oh! Lady Yoruichi!
[Yachiru]
Here!
The envelope for you
has a bear on it,
Captain Soi Fon!
Oh! Uhh.
And I will pass out
my Squad's New Year's
cards as well!
Excuse me, but aren't
New Year's cards
usually mailed instead?
[Kenpachi] [deadpan]
Happy New Year.
[nervous laughing]
It's so different!
[Toshiro]
So! Here you are!
Hm?!
Huh?
[Rangiku]
Is something wrong, Captain?
Yes, everything is, Rangiku.
I realize it's New Year's,
but you mustn't neglect your
duties as a Soul Reaper--
Lieutenant! Hey!
Why'd you send out these
cards for New Years??!
They are disgraceful
and so inappropriate!
Please retrieve each and
every one of these hideous
cards immediately,
and replace them with
something beautiful
and more tasteful.
Huh?... "More tasteful"?!?
[Rangiku]
Oh... Like this one?
Uhh, well uh...
Not like that one.
Rangiku, look.
the thing is,
[Nanao]
Just a minute.
Ut!
New Year's card designs are
chosen by whoever sends them.
Hey, I was talking
to my subordinate--
She's totally right.
I mean Squad 7's card has
Captain Komamura's photo on it.
And it's not even
the Year of the Dog.
[Toshiro]
He doesn't even believe
in the Chinese Zodiac!
[Yachiru]
What are you talking about?
It's the year of the cat, see?
[Toshiro]
No! It's definitely not!
Oh no! This is...
Lady Yoruichi's card!
What's the
matter, Captain?
Yoruichi, there's a New Year's
card for you as well.
[Yoruichi]
Okay!
Let's take a look then.
Oh!
I forgot to send a
card to Soi Fon.
[Nemu]
I'll tell you what
I would prefer.
[Toshiro]
Are you crazy?!
You can't hand out
pictures like that!
I know I would prefer if
I wasn't quite so tall...
[Isane]
Nobody asked you about your
hang-up about being so tall!
Captain, this is a
really weird dynamic.
Can you explain why
these ladies keep changing
the subject on us?
No, I've got no clue.
However you must
agree that they are
mixing too much play
with their work.
I think that is fairly obvious!
[Nanao]
I don't appreciate
what you just said!
Hm!?
Huh?
Hunh?
Comments like yours that tend to
trivialize women are absolutely
unacceptable here, Captain!
[Toshiro]
Tell that to the guys
who said it and not me!
Let's review the facts.
This started because you
made some narrow-minded
comments over a small thing
like New Year's cards!
Hah! Majoring in
minor things,
Look who's talking?!
Don't go there, Ikkaku.
You can't win a battle
of wits with women.
What was that?!
Are you saying women
just enjoy arguing?
Hey I never even said
anything to you!
Yes you did! You said I
was hung-up about being
tall, so see; you're the
ones who want to argue!
[Shuhei]
Well then that's it!
We'll have to settle this
thing once and for all!
Hm!?
Huh?
Hunh?
[Toshiro]
Izuru! Shuhei!
As a man, I have my share
of pride to uphold here.
What now... ?
Then it's on.
It's so on!!
[all growling]
Now, now, everybody.
Calm down.
This will be a match to
the finish, the women
versus the men in:
The First Annual
Men vs Women:
New Years Whacky
Karuta Card Tournament!
And this way, no one from our
squads will get unnecessarily
killed or disemboweled!
Why karuta?
And why am I
in this too?
All right then, let's begin!
Wait-Hold on!
Aren't you going to
explain the rules?
It's regular karuta.
Verses in a 5-7-5
syllable format!
Okay, here's the first card!
It's early morning,
The Third Seat Madarame
The year's first sunrise!
Here!
Hrg.
The New Year has come
And Third Seat Madarame
Stacks up large rice cakes.
[Nanao]
Found it!
[growl]
He hit the jackpot
The Third Seat Madarame
Pachinko ball face.
Hold on!
What's with these cards?!
Knock it off!! I've got the
feeling you're picking on me!
And that third card, very funny!
What's with the pachinko balls?!
They've got nothing
at all to do with
New Year's at all!
You are ejected for arguing
with the game judge!
A red card!!?!
What kinda rule is that?!
I've never even heard
of that one!
I just made it now.
Year of the Rabbit
Of course, even doggies, too,
wear cute rabbit ears.
Hmm.
It's there!
Haaa!
[Isane]
Hee-e!
I got it!
Not fair! She's taller!
And has a longer reach
than I do!
Stop whining.
Greeting the New Year
saying prayers for long life
for the Head Captain.
[Rangiku]
Hunnh.
It starts with
"Greeting the New Year,"
so to match it I
need a "Gree".
gree... gree... ?
Where is it? Let's see...
"Gree"...
Augh!
Whoa!
Eeww!
Outrageous... Disgraceful...
[Izuru]
That's not fair!
Using your "secret weapons"
to make Shuhei bleed...
So you'd do that to win?!
Hey it's not my fault
that he got a nosebleed!
Festive New Year's broth
with freshly pounded rice cakes
Gegetsuburi.
Ah!
Since it's come to this!
Raise your head! Wabisuke!
Ah!
Got it!
That wasn't right!
That move was
going too far!
Well Judge!
Wasn't that move illegal?!
Well, uh...
[Yachiru]
Zabimaru, was that the
year of the monkey, or
the year of the snake?
Did you hear us!??
And that wasn't even
close to the right form!
Za... za...
za... Huh?
Waaah!!
I found it.
Worthy of display
Beautiful and radiant
You and New Year's day.
Ha-ahh!
Bakudo Number Four!
Hainawa!!
I got it!
Hado Number Thirty One!
Shakkaho!!
All right. Now let's
get back to the game.
Now you've done it.
Now we're even.
Why... is... this happening...?
Putting up a kite
is so much easier with
a good pair of shades.
Oh no you don't!
Hado Number Thirty!
Shitotsusansen!
Okay! Now!
Huh?! It's gone!
[Isane]
Got it!
What?!
So then that other
one was a decoy??
You are an idiot.
It's time to
step things up!
[Izuru]
Hado Number
Fifty Eight! Tenran!
[Nanao]
Bakudo Number
Sixty Two!
Hyapporankan!
[Yumichika]
Bloom! Fujikujaku!
[sigh] That's it.
I'm not even gonna bother.
[panting]
Poor, poor Yoruichi!
[Yachiru]
The black cat card is
eligible for a big
Zodiac Consolation prize!
That black cat card,
is Lady Yoruichi's!
And I want it!
Hey! Wait a second, whoa!
Hold back a second will ya??!
I won't let you have it!!
[massive explosion]
[dumbfounded]
A-aahh...
[wistful sigh]
Happy! Happy!!
Happy!!
Uh Captain, I've
been thinking...
Wasn't there something you
came here to see me about?
[sigh]
[Toshiro]
Yes, there was.
I wanted to wish you
a Happy New Year.
Hello brother. I want to
wish you a Happy New Year.
I will try to stay happy this
year and always do my best.
The first-of-the-New Year
shrine visit.
[sigh] I wonder how
everyone else is spending
their New Year's?
[Ichigo]
Hey! Slow down, Wait up!
Your New Year's gift money's
not gonna disappear and the
store won't close for hours,
so slow down will ya?!
[giggles] Oh C'mon, keep up!
Hold on! How come I'm the one
stuck carrying all this?!
Because you're a guy!
I'd say you're probably
strong enough to carry those
game consoles all day long.
Besides, I have to save up my
energy so I'll be ready to play
them as soon as we get home!
That's great, you're wearing
me out, so you can beat me!!
Uh-huh!
Well I get to
pick the game!!
No!
I wanna do the one
that's racing through
the candy first!
Quit whining!
No!
Ah?
There's a surprise!
So that's how Uryu spends
time with his family.
That's nice. I guess
everyone spends time with
their families on New Years.
I bet that same kind of
family bonding is probably
going on at Tatsuki's too.
It wouldn't be right for me
to bother them or intrude.
Ah! I've gotta stop
being so down!
Hey! It's a New Year!
Time for a new start!
Happy New Year!
[yawn]
What was that big
yawn about Renji?
You already bored
with the New Year?
It's not that, I
just feel worn out.
Last night Tetsuzaemon and
the guys took me out to a party
and kept me out really late.
I bet Ichigo would get a
big kick out of seeing
you so wiped out.
I bet he would. Let's hurry
up and finish this New Year's
greetings tour, so I can get
back home and sleep...
Hey. Orihime.
Oh, hey you two,
great to see you!
Happy New Year,
All the best!
Thanks. Happy
New Year.
Yeah, Happy
So what'cha doing,
just walking around?
I thought I might make a New
Year's shrine visit.
A shrine visit?
Yup. But it was too
crowded, so I figured I'd
maybe do it another day.
So are you two on
your way to a shrine?
Not us. We came here to the
World of the Living to share
our New Year's greetings.
That sounds great, I've
been meeting up with a
lot of people today.
So tell me-Which of our friends
have you already visited?
Hm! Let's see, there was
Ichigo, Uryu, and some
of my school friends,
But I really shouldn't say
"I met up with them" because
we didn't really talk, I only
saw them from a distance.
Ah! So Ichigo's in the area?
C'mon, let's hurry and
get these New Year's
greetings over with.
You wanna tag
along with us?
No thanks, I
think I'll pass.
Huh?
Everybody's spending time
with their families today.
I don't think it would be right
to interrupt their special
holiday time together.
So that's what you do
for New Year's in the
World of the Living?
Oh, we do all kinds of
things! Some people
spend it alone, like me.
[chuckle]
Oh, I see.
[yawn]
Okay, well let's
get going. C'mon!
You're coming with us.
Hunh!? Wait! But I!
[yawn]
Huh?
[group of kids]
Yoisho!
[Jinta]
Again!
-Yoisho!
-Again!
I should've known
we'd come here.
Hey there, what's up guys.
A most Happy New Year to
all of you!
Thanks and a Happy New
Year to all of you, too!
What are you pounding
with that big hammer?
We're pounding out
some mochi together.
We're just doing
something kinda festive
to celebrate New Year's.
You wanna try
pounding some out?
Oh! I'd love to
try doing that!
[sigh]
Here I go!
And why am I
doing this?!!
Hammer it, Ururu!
Yosho!
Yaaiaaiaiaiaa!
Oh! Almost!
Whaddya mean "almost"?!
It sounds like you actually
wanted me to get hit!
Aren't you supposed to be
aiming for the mochi?!
This time...
Hey! I'm not mochi! Stop it!
Yoisho!
Yes!
Auughhh!!!!
Nice shot!
C'mon! Don't wimp out!
When you hit it back,
give it a little more heat!
D'aagh!
That one had
some real heat.
You suck, Renji.
Just shut up!
I'm too sleep-deprived
to play this game well!
[Ururu]
Okay, face-painting time!
[Renji]
W-Whoa! That's a big brush!
[Rukia]
So, how'd you do with
Ururu's face painting?
I got pretty inked up,
just like you!
Although, we got off pretty
easy compared to Renji.
Go on, laugh.
You don't look so bad.
Well I sure don't look good!
Now that you've all had
a chance to wash up,
You'll wanna change.
So I brought you these clothes.
Those are...
Wow! Cute kimonos!
Today I had the perfect
New Year's experience.
The only thing left is a
New Year's shrine visit.
A visit to a shrine?
Well we could stop at
one on the way home.
Yeah well, you
can count me out.
[Tessai]
stop what you're doing!!!
What did I do?!
Now you listen to this, Renji!
Red sea bream is not just a
fish, it is very special!
It holds legendary place
in our New Year's feast.
Long ago, tales were
told of the custom of
"staring at the sea bream"
and refraining from
eating sea bream on
New Year's day!
[sigh]
Okay okay, I hear
what you're sayin'.
[steamed]
Rrrr!
[Tessai]
I said "stop that!"
[Renji] [getting beat up]
Ow! Damn it! What'd you hit me
for?! That hurt! Oww! Geez
Kid! Watch where you hit me!
Oh man! This whole New Year's
thing really sucks.
I would've stayed in bed
if I'd known New Year's
was gonna be like this.
You really mean that?
What?!
I haven't enjoyed my New Year's
this much in a long time!
Well I'm certainly glad
you had a good time...
But how come I always
end up getting the short
end of the stick?
I mean isn't New Year's...
meant to be a time when we
all get to mellow out?
I can see how that
might sound good.
But New Year's is no fun
if you're all by yourself.
Huh?
Orihime...
[Tessai]
The ozoni is ready now!
Wow it's ready!
C'mon, let's go eat!
Sure.
You too, Renji! Come on!
[Renji]
What?
[Kisuke]
Well! See you around
Rukia, Orihime.
Great seeing you
and Happy New Year.
And as for the kimono,
just give it back
next time.
Thank you very much for all
the fun, and Happy New Year.
And thank you Rukia.
Well I guess I'll be
heading home now.
[Rukia]
Wait Orihime.
Hm?
Didn't you want to
go visit the shrine?
Well, I feel like it's
too late for that.
By now there's probably no one
there, so I don't think it
would be all that much fun.
Come on, you
never know.
No, the vendors are
probably all gone, so
it'll be empty and boring.
Let's go anyway.
Uh! Okay!
It's just like I said,
there's no one's here.
But we came all this way,
So let's say our prayers
before we leave.
Even though it's
just the two of us.
[Ichigo]
Wait. You'd better
include us, too.
Huh?
You're all here!
Hey there you two!
Happy New Year, Orihime.
Hi Ichigo!
I thought I'd see you
earlier today. I mean
you could've at least
called one of us.
Um-hm.
Hi Uryu!
And hi Chad!
Well Happy New Year Orihime.
Good to see you.
Yeah, Happy New Year.
You guys made it just in time.
Never thought I'd have
to work so hard at the
start of a New Year.
Thanks you guys.
Ngeh, Alright, we're
done here, let's end
this, so I can go home
and get some sleep.
Can't admit
it, can you?
Shut up!
[Orihime]
I pray that we can all share
another wonderful year together.
[Rukia]
Ichigo!
[Ichigo]
You look small, Ruki--
Oh! It's you
again, Ruki-ruki.
Then this must be
a dream!
[Rukia]
This is not a dream!
And I'm not Rukiruki either!
[Ichigo]
Ow! Don't poke me.
[Rukia]
Now let's go!
[Ichigo]
Go where?
[Rukia]
The castle.
[Ichigo]
And do what?
[Rukia]
Play Monsters.