[music playing]
[theme music]
NARRATOR: In order
to save Orihime,
who has been abducted
by the Arrancars,
Ichigo, Uryu, and
Chad have snuck
into the Hollow
World, Hueco Mundo.
After making it
through the Garganta,
Ichigo and his friends
were confronted
by the guardians of Underground
Path 22, a place where
intruders are intercepted.
They crushed the Arrancars
standing in their way,
and set off for Aizen's
palace, Las Noches.
-It has to be that Las Noches
place those guys talked about.
That thing's enormous.
-I'm not actually sure
how far away it is.
-The way this place works, we'll
be dragged into another flight
if don't move fast.
-Huh?
[roar]
[crying]
-A human?
-No way.
There can't be another
human living here.
That's impossible.
[creatures laughing]
-My brother!
[gasping]
-It hurts!
It hurts!
The tip!
The tip is poking me!
-Stop that!
Leave them alone!
-Hm?
-What'd we do to you?
Stop picking on us, will ya?
Why don't you just
leave us alone?
-A mask?
Then are-- are you a Hollow?
-Please leave us alone.
We're really sorry!
We never thought our
game of eternal tag
would cause such a
misunderstanding.
It'll never happen again.
-You mean you play a
game called Eternal Tag?
-Unfortunately there's nothing
else to do here in Hueco Mundo
to pass the time.
-Eternal Tag?
But you were crying while you
were running away from them.
-Sure!
Nel is a masochist,
and it's no fun for Nel
unless Nel is chased to the
point where Nel starts to cry.
-Why are you teaching this
kid words like masochist?
-Wait, I'm confused.
Nel is your name, right?
-That's right!
Nel is an Arrancar, and
Nel's full name is Nel Tu!
-An Arrancar?
-Nel sure is.
-Oh, and these are
Nel's brothers.
-I'm Nel's older
brother, Pesche.
-I'm the oldest
brother, Dondochakka.
-Brother?
-And this guy right
here is our pet.
His name is Bawabawa.
-Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
-You have a question?
-Since when do Arrancars
all of a sudden
have siblings and pets?
-What do you mean?
Arrancars have always had those.
-When I met Nel, she
was so cute that I
decided to become
a big brother, you
know what I'm talking about?
-Yep, same here.
-But that means you're not
really siblings at all.
-Huh?
-But if these guys aren't my
siblings, what are they then?
-Not her brother?
What are you talking about?
-No way!
-I mean, what am
I talking about?
Sure.
You guys could
definitely be siblings.
-This is all so bizarre.
Are you sure you guys
are really Arrancars?
-Hey, what are
you trying to say?
Can't you see this here?
A beautifully cracked
Arrancar mask.
-It's just that you seem
different from the Arrancars
that came to the
world of the living.
-Oh, but of course we do.
The Arrancars who went to
the world of the living
are called Numeros.
-Numeros?
Wait, what are they?
-Numeros are the guys who are
even stronger than the Menos
Grande.
That is, before they
turned into Arrancars.
All the Numeros
can be identified
by two digit numbers,
and they serve directly
under the Espada.
-They sure have it good.
-You're telling me.
It just ain't right.
-Numeros are combat experts.
They're an elite fighting force.
There's no comparison to them
and garbage bugs like us.
-Garbage bugs?
-You have some
nerve, telling us we
don't look like
Arrancars when you
look even less like
Arrancars than we do.
You don't have a mask, and
you wear a black kimono.
You're dressed more like a--
-A Soule Reaper, you
know what I mean?
-Yeah, like a Soul Reaper.
[wind blowing]
-What is it?
-What are you guys, anyway?
-Ichigo Kurosaki,
substitute Soul Reaper.
-Uryu Ishida.
I am a Quincy.
-Yasutora Saro.
And I'm human.
[screaming]
-A Soul Reaper?
-A Quincy and a human?
-What are we going to do?
-Do you know what this means?
-You're the bad guys!
-You mean, you didn't have any
idea at all who we really were?
-That's right!
Because you didn't
say who you were.
-You should have told
us from the start.
-Bad guys.
I can't believe it.
-This is terrible.
Nel is sure the, the bad
guys are going to kill us!
-Uh huh.
-No.
We're not going to kill you.
-Wow, I wasn't
expecting this at all.
-Who knew there were
Arrancars like this.
-We're in big trouble.
-We're gonna die.
-Nel thinks we really
should try to kill
the bad guys before
they try to kill us.
-Yeah, but I don't think
there's anyway we can beat them.
-We have to.
Soul Reapers are the bad guys.
-That's right.
Let's invite them to play
a game of Eternal Tag.
And while we're pretending
to play, we jump them,
and then we run for it.
-Now that's a good idea!
-Yeah, maybe this
way we can beat them!
-Yeah.
-What is it now?
-Oh Mr. Soul Reapear,
if you're not bad guys,
then play with us!
-Huh?
-OK, here we go.
Let's start!
On your mark, get ready, tag!
You're it.
-What?
-Come on.
It's a game of Eternal Tag.
-Hey!
Come back here.
[laughter]
-Try to catch Nel.
And then try to beat
Nel up and make Nel cry!
-Why you little--
-Let's go!
-I'm on it!
-What are you guys doing?
-This is a game of Eternal Tag!
-We're going to tag
you good, so get ready!
[laughter]
-Wow.
Ichigo sure got his
Zanpakuto stolen easily.
-Do you think he wanted to
play Eternal Tag with them?
[heavy breathing]
-Why is he chasing us too?
-That's what I want to know.
-Looks like we've
got new players,
know what I'm talking about?
-This is the best way
to play Eternal Tag.
The more people you have,
the more fun it gets.
Just like Rock, Paper, Scissors!
-What are you talking about?
Rock, Paper, Scissors is not
more fun with more people.
This isn't exactly fun, either!
[yelling]
[laughter]
-Oh man.
That was close.
[groaning]
-Hey, can you stand?
-Wow.
Nel can't believe you save her.
-Of course I did.
You would have been squashed
under that giant Arrancar.
You OK?
Are you hurt anywhere?
-Nel's fine.
-That's good.
You should try to
be more careful.
Well, we've got
to get going now.
Later.
[music playing]
-Hey!
Are you running away?
-Huh?
-You're just going to run
away, after what you did to us?
-What?
Look, we're in a hurry.
We can't stay and play with you.
Go run around with your
friends and play some more tag.
-That's so mean!
You were just toying
with Nel's feelings,
but you should have
just killed Nel instead.
It would have been much less
painful for Nel that way.
-Why does this crap
always happen to me?
-Since you asked for death,
I shall grant you your wish.
-Something's coming.
-What the hell?
That's huge.
-It's Runuganga, the
guardian of the white sand.
-I was just informed only
moments ago by Las Noches
that we had intruders.
I never would have
guessed they had
you measly garbage
bugs acting as spies.
Unforgivable.
I'm going to turn you
all into desert sand.
-It's not like that.
You've got it all wrong.
You see, actually we were--
-Stand aside.
-Wha--?
-This guy doesn't look like
he wants to play around.
All right, let's go, monster!
Getsuga Tensho!
Now he's toast.
-I can't believe he did that.
-That was a blatant
sneak attack!
That's cheating!
He's a bad guy!
-Shut up.
After all, I just
saved you, didn't I?
Anyway, I swung at him head on.
It wasn't a sneak attack.
-Ichigo!
-He's back.
-He's what?
-You won't even confess to
attempting a sneak attack.
For this, you intruders
must be punished.
-What are you trying
to pull on us?
It wasn't a sneak attack.
And how are you able to
regenerate yourself so fast?
What's the deal with
this guy anyway?
-Can't you figure it out?
Runuganga is obviously
made out of sand.
-You don't have to
be so calm about it.
He's after you, too, you know?
Don't just stand around like
it's just another game of tag!
-No more talk!
How ill-mannered you are.
[music playing]
-Give me your hand!
-How persistent you are.
I'm going to finish
you off, all at once!
[music playing]
-Idiots.
It's useless.
Fools!
Did you think you could defeat
me with such a weak attack?
-This is impossible.
-Ichigo.
Let's combine attacks.
-We'll wipe this guy
out without a trace.
-Right.
Getsuga Tensho!
-Ginrei Kojako!
-El Directo!
[music playing]
-So did we do it?
I'm not really sure.
-He, he's coming!
-An ant-lion pit!
-Oh no!
-Grab my hand.
Don't let go of
me, you got that?
-Nel won't let go.
-Dammit.
Isn't there something
we can do about this?
-It seems impossible.
-I just can't find a
way to attack this guy.
-Hey Nel, does this guy have any
weaknesses I should know about?
-Well, he does
have one weakness.
But Nel can't tell a bad
guy like you what it is.
-You little!
Don't you realize that
you're being sucked in, too?
Come on, tell me!
-It's water!
-Water?
-That's right.
Water.
-Water?
-Water.
In a desert, huh?
-Where are we going to
find water around here?
-There isn't any.
It's impossible.
That's why Runuganga
is invincible.
That's why he guards the palace.
[runuganga laughing]
-I'm going to swallow you
all up in one fell swoop.
[growling]
-Dammit.
[gasping]
[crashing]
-Rukia!
Renji!
[music playing]
-Reporting.
The spiritual pressure's of both
Sixth Squad Lieutenant Renji
Abarai, and Thirteenth
Squad member Rukia Kuchiki,
have disappeared
from their barracks.
Currently our Second
Division, the patrol core,
have spread their search to
all corners of the seireitei.
-Those fools.
[crying]
-More Soul Reapers.
More of the bad guys.
-Rukia!
Renji!
You guys are here.
-Hey!
Easy!
-Are you all right, Ichigo?
-No, I'm not.
-You idiot!
Why did you go off on
your own to Hueco Mundo?
Why couldn't you have
just waited for us
to come back and help you?
-Because.
I had no idea if
you were actually
going to come back and--
-Of course we were!
No matter what!
Renji and I were
planning on coming back
from the very beginning.
Why didn't you wait for us?
Why couldn't you trust us?
I thought we were supposed
to be your friends, Ichigo.
-Yeah.
You're right.
-Well, as long as
you understand now.
Please don't ever make me
confirm something as silly
as this, ever again.
That aside, who are they?
-Huh?
What kind of rude
question is that?
Nel Tu!
-Dondochakka!
-Pesche Guatiche!
-And together we're--
[interposing voices]
-You're not on the same page.
-We talked about this before!
We're the Nel-Don-Pe
Phantom Thieves!
-I told you that I would
only accept The Great Desert
Brothers!
-I want Three Brothers in
the name, or forget about it.
-Well, you get the idea.
You know, they're all Hollows.
-What idea am I supposed to get?
-Oh no!
Bawabawa is crying.
-It's all right, Bawabawa.
We haven't forgotten about you!
-Right!
Including Bawabawa, together
the four of us are--
[interposing voices]
-It's time for you
guys to be quiet now.
Are you ready to get going?
Come on.
-All right, Ichigo.
-They're leaving?
-Forget about it.
-Hey!
Hold up a sec!
Itsigo!
-Hey, it's not Itsigo!
-If you'll wait for us, Nel
will guide you to Las Noches.
[wind blowing]
-Uh, why is she staring
at you like that?
-I don't know.
-May I ask you what your
relationship is with Itsigo?
-What?
-You're pretty popular
with the ladies!
-Just shut up.
Hey, by the way, where did
you guys get those cloaks?
Did you pick them up somewhere?
-They're gifts.
I was told that Hueco Mundo's
deserts have a pretty rough
terrain, and you
need protection.
-Who said that.
-My brother did.
-Then, does that
mean that Byakuya
sent you guys all the
way here to find me?
-Well, actually,
it was Kisuke who
opened up the Garganta for us.
But it was my Captain who
got us through the world
of the living.
-My brother said, the
only order received
was the one to bring us
back to the Soul Society.
-I never received
any orders concerning
what to do with you
after I brought you back.
Do whatever you like.
-See?
-Yeah, I see.
Byakuya did that, huh?
Sure has gotten
rather soft lately.
-He also said that it must
be unpleasant for the enemy
to have that dingy
boy wandering around.
-That bastard!
-Ichigo!
What are you doing,
punching our ride?
-That's right!
Don't pick on Bawabawa.
If you want to pick on
someone, please pick on Nel!
-Ah!
Enough!
-Oh man, what is it now?
[music playing]
[theme music]
-Hey, don't I get a cloak?
-Sorry, my brother
only gave me two.
-There's only enough
for us, Ichigo.
Are you jealous?
-He actually didn't want
to give you one, either.
But he reluctantly gave one
to you because I asked him to.
-Damn.
-Yeah, that sounds like Byakuya.