[theme music]
-Central 46-- it gets its
name from the 40 sages and six
judges who've been gathered
from across the Soul Society.
It is the highest
judicial system
that exists within
the Soul Society.
When a soul reaper is
charged with a crime,
whether it occurred in the
Soul Society or the world
of the living, it is here
that they are judged.
Once a verdict is
handed down, Central 46
then designates who will
execute the sentence--
the stealth force, or the
13 court guard squads.
Once they declare their
verdict, it is absolute.
No one, not even a captain,
can appeal their decision.
That is the function
of Central 46.
-Eh.
[gasps]
-What?
I can't believe what I'm seeing.
How could something
like this happen?
TOSHIRO (VOICE OVER) : This
blood is completely dry.
It's already blackened, and
even started to crack and flake.
This obviously didn't
happen yesterday,
or the day before that.
The question is when?
The last time
Central 46 operated
normally was just before
Renji was defeated.
After that, martial
law was declared
and the Central
Underground Assembly Hall
was locked down completely.
No one was allowed
to enter or leave.
The defense system was
engaged, sealing all entrances,
and there was no
sign of forced entry
when we got here-- that means
they were killed before then.
If that's the case, all the
judgments and decisions that
have come from Central 46 since
that time, they were fake.
But who could have
pulled this off, Gin?
Even he's not capable
of doing this by itself,
so there must have been
others who helped him.
-Captain Hitsugaya, I
figured I'd find you here.
-Izuru.
Are you the one
responsible for this?
After him, Rangiku, come on!
-Uh.
-It's no use running.
Answer me, Izuru, are
you responsible for what
happened back there?
-No.
I was merely allowed in from
the inside before you arrived.
My role was to unlock
the doors from the inside
so you could get into the
Underground Assembly Hall.
-Who gave you those orders?
Who was it?
-It's no secret.
Central 46 gave the order.
-Then where is
the official seal?
Show me, damn it!
-Instead of chasing me,
asking pointless questions
about orders and official
seals, shouldn't you
be more concerned
about protecting Momo?
-What are you talking about?
She's perfectly safe.
She's--
-Not in the Squat 10 barracks,
if that's what you're thinking.
-You put a force field around
the room Momo was sleeping in,
didn't you?
A Kiyomo, a high
level force field
that repels attacks
from the outside,
so you left her there
thinking she'd be safe.
But that force field is meant
to keep people out, not in.
Momo was a master of Kido.
Breaking a force field like that
would be child's play for her.
And she could put a force
field around herself
to hide her spiritual
pressure while moving about.
You didn't even notice, did you?
She's been right behind you,
following you the entire time.
-Rangiku, can I
leave this to you?
-I've got it.
[grunts]
-Uh.
What, you tired of running?
-You don't know, do you Rangiku?
You've no idea.
-About what?
-About what my Zanpakuto can do.
-Perhaps that's
because you've never
told anyone exactly what it is.
-I'm afraid that's not true.
There are some-- both Renji
and Momo know its power,
but that's neither
here nor there.
Now I plan on telling you, too.
Raise your head, Wabisuke.
-How dare you?
-Good reflexes, impressive.
-What are you doing?
Are you completely insane?
Uh!
Listen, Izuru, I don't know
what Dean said to you but--
-Tell me, how many attacks
so far, about seven?
-Uh!
[crash]
-Whatever my sword cuts
becomes twice as heavy.
It doubles with each
strike and continues
doing so indefinitely,
until finally the person I
fight can no longer
lift the weight.
They kneel helplessly
on the ground,
head bowed down as if they
were in penitence-- thus
the name Wabisuke,
the penitent one.
I can help you with the math.
If your sword weighed
16 ounces, that
multiplied by 2 to the seventh
power would be 128 pounds.
That's going to make
running with it difficult.
-So what?
If it gets too heavy, then
I'll just have to drop it.
Izuru, tell me, what exactly
do you want to do with her?
Roar.
Haineko!
-Uh.
-What in the world do
you want to do with me?
Where is it that you want to go?
-What, what happened here?
Everyone in Central 46, they're
all dead, every one of them.
Toshiro was here, but he
was surprised somehow.
Izuru was here, too,
but then for some reason
Toshiro followed
him away from here.
None of this makes any sense.
If Toshiro killed
Captain Aizen, does that
mean that he's the
one who did this, too?
But, why would he be
surprised to see Izuru here,
unless, unless it was Izuru.
So if Hitsugaya didn't do
this, what about Captain Aizen?
-Welcome Momo.
What a pleasure to see you.
-Captain Ichimaru, what
are you doing here?
-Just come with me.
-Momo.
-But, this is the Seijotokyorin.
These are the living
quarters of Central 46.
I don't understand-- why
would you bring me here?
Captain Ichimaru, please.
-So, how many times have you
visited this place, Momo?
-I never have, I'm not allowed.
This area is completely
off-limits to me.
This is the first time.
-There's someone here
I'd like you to meet.
-Who would want to
meet me, and why?
-You'll see.
-But--
-No need to be shy.
Look behind you.
-Behind me?
[footsteps]
[gasps]
Captain Aizen.
-I've missed seeing you, Momo.
-Captain Aizen, I
don't believe it.
Is it really you?
Ah, all this time I
thought you were dead.
-I know you did, and I'm sorry.
-You really are alive,
aren't you, Captain Aizen.
And I thought that,
I thought that--
[crying]
I didn't know what to think.
-I'm sorry.
I can see that I've
caused you pain.
MOMO (VOICE OVER): Oh,
Captain Aizen's hand,
it's so warm and comforting.
-Come in and talk until
you've calmed down.
You're welcome to stay
here as long as you like.
MOMO (VOICE OVER): He's the
same as always-- even his scent.
I always feel as if
he cleanses my soul.
It really is Captain Aizen.
It is.
[crying]
MOMO (VOICE OVER): When
I thought you were dead,
I'd lost all hope.
Life had no meaning without you.
I didn't think I could go on.
But I was wrong, it was a lie.
I should have seen it.
I should have known you
wouldn't die, Captain Aizen.
I should have known that you
would never die and leave me
behind.
[crying]
-You've become so thin.
I'm sorry, Momo.
I'm sorry my actions
caused you so much pain.
But you understand,
don't you, Momo?
You're the only one
who could understand.
There was a task that
needed to be handled.
In order to do that, I
had to fake my own death.
-It's all right.
Everything's all right.
None of that makes
any difference now,
as long as you're alive and
back home where you belong.
-Thank you, Momo.
I'm a fortunate man to
have you as a subordinate.
Thank you, Momo.
From the bottom of my heart,
thank you-- and goodbye.
[stab]
[gasping]
-What have you done?
Why?
[thud]
-Let's go, Gin.
-Yes.
As you wish, Captain Aizen.
-Uh.
[breathing heavily]
-Hey, Toshiro.
-What is this?
Captain Aizen.
Are you alive, or
is this some trick?
-No trick, this is
really me, Toshiro.
Excuse me a minute.
Gin, he's returned
sooner than we expected.
I hope you have an explanation.
-Sorry, sir.
Izuru must not have been
able to keep him occupied.
-What's going on here?
What are you two talking about?
-Nothing, really.
We were just discussing
the finer points
of strategy-- the breaking down
of an enemy's fighting power,
to be specific.
-Enemy, I see.
[grunting]
Tell me where Momo is!
-That's a good question.
[grunts]
[boom]
-Momo, no.
-Huh, found her.
Guess I shouldn't have
left her lying around.
I apologize.
I really didn't plan on
surprising you this way.
No, I should have chopped her
into little pieces, then hidden
them away where
you'd never find her.
-Aizen, Ichimaru, how long
have you worked together?
Did Gin help conspire
to fake your death?
-He joined me long before that.
Gin's been with me from
the very beginning.
From the moment
I became captain,
there was no one better
suited to be my lieutenant.
-So all this time you've been
lying to everyone-- Momo,
me, the 13 Court Guard Squads,
all the other Soul Reapers,
everyone!
[grunts]
You deceived us!
-Well, I had never
thought of it that way.
It's just, it
became very obvious
that no one was capable
of understanding.
My true identity
was beyond them.
-True identity?
Momo, Momo looked up to you.
She joined the 13
Court Guard Squad
so she could be closer to you.
She believed in you, and
everything you represented.
So much so, that she was
willing to risk her life
to become your lieutenant!
-Of course I knew,
that's the quality
that made her easy to
control-- her blind admiration.
That and her abilities made
her the perfect candidate
to be my subordinate.
This is a lesson you
might want to take
to heart as well, Toshiro.
[laughs]
Admiration is a state furthest
away from understanding.
[gasps]
Bankai.
[shouting]
[breathing heavily]
No, Aizen, you've talked enough.
Time to die.
-Ha, you shouldn't be
making such strong remarks,
it only makes you look weak.
[yells]
[whoosh]
[laughing]
[grunts]
[crash]
-This isn't possible.
-What a beautiful sight.
It's the wrong
season, but I rather
like seeing ice
this time of year.
-Captain Aizen--
no, that's wrong.
After what I've
witnessed, it wouldn't
be right to call you
captain any longer.
Sosuke Aizen, your
title is high traitor.
-Well, hello, Captain Unohana.
I have to admit that
your arrival is not
completely unexpected.
I knew you'd figure out
that I was staying here.
-It was the only explanation.
Seijotokyorin had been declared
totally off-limits to everyone.
This location was
perfectly suited for you
to carry out the
plans you had in mind.
You needed to hide away
in complete isolation
after you staged your own
death with that exquisitely
designed corpse doll.
And what better place in
all of the Seireitei for you
to go completely undetected?
That was your plan
at least, wasn't it?
-Not quite.
Some of that is true, but
you did make two mistakes.
Let me clear things up for you.
First of all, I have no
need to hide from anyone--
that's not what I came here for.
And secondly, what
you're looking at here
is not a corpse doll.
[gasps]
-But, when did he--
-When did I what?
I've been standing here
holding it the whole time.
It's been right in
front of you, you simply
weren't able to see it.
That's because I didn't allow
you to see it until just now.
-Wha, what do you mean?
-You'll soon understand.
I'm going to release
my Zanpakuto.
Shatter, Kyoka Suigetsu.
[gasping]
This is my Zanpakuto,
Kyoka Suigetsu.
Its ability is perfect hypnosis.
-Impossible.
It couldn't change.
Kyoka Suigetsu has always been
a running water type Zanpakuto.
It uses the diffused
reflection of mist
to confuse enemies into
attacking each other.
You yourself explained to
us exactly how it worked,
Captain Aizen.
And we saw it with our own eyes.
You specifically gathered
all the lieutenants together
because you wanted
to demonstrate it!
I see now.
Your demonstration was
actually the hypnosis ritual.
-You're catching on quickly.
Complete hypnosis
controls all five senses,
and is able to cause every
dimension of a target,
including its form, shape,
mass, feel and smell, even
its vocal patterns in the way it
tastes, to perfectly replicate
that of an enemy.
In other words, it
is possible for me
to make a fly appear
to be a dragon,
or a marsh, a flowerbed.
And all I need to do to activate
it is simply show my enemies
my Zanpakuto's Kanzen
Saimin release.
[breathing heavily]
The power of my Zanpakuto
is limited only by my mind,
because whoever lays
their eyes on it,
even once, will be hypnotized
into doing my bidding
whenever I release
my Kyoka Suigetsu.
-Even once?
But, uh.
-I see you've figured it out.
Very good.
You see, whoever lays their
eyes on it falls under my spell.
So unfortunately,
those who can't see
will never be under my power.
In other words, Kaname Tosen
was always my subordinate.
-Captain Tosen, what's wrong?
Please let me by,
I'm in a hurry.
[whoosh]
What the hell's going on?
-I want to commend you, Unohana.
You examined my body
far more thoroughly
than any of the others.
That you felt even a
bit of suspicion while
under the influence
of my hypnotic spell,
I find most remarkable.
I congratulate you,
and bid you farewell.
I don't think I'll ever
see any of you again.
-Wait!
Unh!
[coughing]
-What the hell was
that all about?
But this is Sokyoku Hill.
-Welcome, Renji.
-Captain Aizen,
how did-- What the?
[inaudible]
What, what's going on?
-Leave Rukia where she
is, Renji, and back away.
[gasps]
[theme music]
-The next episode, I plan to
divulge my true intentions
with an entertaining
dinner show.
There's still time
to buy tickets,
but it's first
come, first served.
-I'm making a special
guest appearance.
-Don't be late.
-You're not an actor, and
there's not going to be a show!