[music playing]
NARRATOR: After
several failed attempts
to assassinate Rurichiyo
Kasumioji, her retainer,
Gyokaku Kumoi, formed an
assassination squad headed
by Hanzunu Qui, Gyokaku gave
each member of the squad
a mysterious weapon called
Bakkoto and sent them
to the World of the Living
to complete their assignment.
-Here I come, Ichigo Kurasaki!
-Bankai!
NARRATOR: Rukia suffered
several injuries in the fight
against the
assassin, Jinai Doko,
who was armed with a strange
Bakkoto called the Retsu Rai.
But thanks to
Kenryu's help, she was
able to use her Kido to
hold Jinai at bay, at least
temporarily.
[growling]
[explosion]
-Amazing!
I can feel the power
welling up inside me!
So this is the power
of the Bakkoto!
(LAUGHS MANIACALLY)
[gasps]
[clang]
[laughter]
NARRATOR: Meanwhile,
Uryu had been fighting
the assassin, Kuzu Ryu
and found himself trapped
inside a mist released by
Kuzu Ryu's Bakkoto, Shiragiri.
-Shiragiri.
Mugen Kairo.
[blast]
-(GRUNTING) Where is he?
[laughter]
-Over there!
How is he-- Huh?
-[laughing] Over here!
-Some sort of illusion?
[slashing]
-Nngh!
-(LAUGHNG DIABOLICALLY) How
long do you think you can run?
NARRATOR: At the same
time, Chad was caught up
in a fierce battle with
the assessin, Genga,
who was armed with his own
Bakkoto named Kakuyoku.
[zapping]
-Feast your eyes on the
true power of my Kakuyoku!
(ROARING)
[blast]
[growls]
-Nnngh.
There's no sign of his presence.
Hmm.
-Heh.
You're mine.
(ROARING)
[maniacal laughter]
-He's a lot faster
than I had realized.
I've to find a way to
keep him from attacking.
[clang]
[yelling]
[kring]
-What?
Nnngh!
[slashing]
-The finishing blow!
[kring]
-Nnngh!
-Impossible!
-You're done.
[shrieks]
-(LAUGHING MANIACALLY)
Not so fast, missy.
My Bakkoto, Retsu Rai, is much
more powerful than you imagine!
(SHRIEKING)
-What is he--
[blast]
-(LAUGHING MANIACALLY) Haiyah!
[clanging]
[shrieking]
[yells]
[thud]
-What's THE matter, girl?
You done already?
[gasping]
-Lady Kuchiki!
-Kenryu, you must
go and help her.
She's hurt!
-Right!
-Going somewhere?
-Huh?
[maniacal laughter]
[whimpering]
-Lady Rurichiyo!
I warned you.
Take the princess to safety!
-Not so fast!
[slashing]
-Nnngh!
-Kenryu!
-Haiyah!
-(WHIMPERING) Kenryu!
-Damn it!
We're in trouble.
If we don't find a way to
do something about his speed
and those blades on his
back, we're gonna lose!
[crunch]
-(GASPING) That's it!
Hadou Number 33, Sokatsui!
[blast]
-Aaugh!
Damn it!
-Sokatsui!
-Aahhh!
-Aaahh! (LAUGHS)
-Sokatsui!
Sokatsui!
-Iieeh!
You're becoming a pain!
Time to step things up.
(SHRIEKING)
[kring]
-Some no mae!
Tsukishiro!
[ice crackling]
-I don't believe this!
You're really in for it now!
(GROWLING)
-Freeze!
Bakkuro Number Four!
Ai no wa.
-What's going on?
-Bakkuro Number One!
Sai!
-Aaahh!
You think you're so clever!
[chiming]
-Tsukinomae Hakurun!
[blast]
[wailing]
-(BREATHING HEAVILY) I did it.
[explosion]
-Get the princess out of here!
-I won't forgive you for that!
The fact is, I'm a
lot stronger than you
think! (LAUGHING
MANIACALLY) Huh?
(WAILING) What is this thing?
I'm burning up inside!
[flames crackling]
[clang]
-What happened?
He completely disintegrated!
-How did he do that?
He scattered his
spiritual pressure
so I can't figure
out where he is.
Eh?
[hailing]
-Hmm.
Huh?
-Nnngh.
-What's that sword
you're holding?
-Seele Schneider,
a special blade
for Quincies, the
only one we carry.
-Interesting.
I've never heard of Quincies
using a sword before.
-Think about it.
I may have other weapons
you've never heard of as well.
-I doubt that.
-Hmm.
Very strange.
This mist has definitely
been created with Reishi.
So if that's the case,
why is the concentration
of Reishi weakening?
I have to test it.
Nnngh!
[sizzling]
-All right.
Nnngh!
Huh?
[clink]
-There's something wrong here.
He shouldn't be able to move
this fast, even with Flash
Step and his sword.
Even though I cut into
it with Seele Schneider,
I wasn't able to damage it.
Did he repair it with
Reishi from the mist?
That can't be, otherwise
I'd be able to absorb them
just as easily.
Impossible!
But it's the only explanation.
Has he actually
merged with the mist?
[slash]
-Nnngh!
(GRUNTING) I was right!
-So, you finally
figured it out, did you?
This mist is my body.
(LAUGHING) But now that
your leg is wounded,
you can't use Hiranjaku anymore.
There's no way you can escape
from my Shiragiri's Mugen
Kairo!
Ha ha!
I was wondering what
you'd try to do.
[blast]
-It's useless.
-Nnngh!
-If you're trying to attack
the moment I physically
materialize, you're
wasting your time.
How much longer can
you hold out, Quincy?
-Long enough!
I figured that would
be your next move.
[blast]
-What?
What the hell is this?
-Sprenger!
-Nnngh.
-It's a Quincy Zaikon I drew
with my Seele Schneider.
-How did you do that?
-It was all thanks to you.
-What?
-I purposely created openings
in five different directions.
The five points of the symbol.
And when you attacked
each of those openings,
it enabled me to
set up the barrier.
You're a fool, Quincy!
This isn't enough to stop me!
-You're not going anywhere.
-What are you doing?
-Blowing you to bits.
-Are you insane?
There's no way you
can escape the blast!
You're going to blow
yourself up as well.
-That may be, but you'll
get the worst of it.
[blast]
[wailing]
Aaaugh.
Damn.
[explosion]
[zap]
[labored breathing]
-Lady Rurichiyo,
are you injured?
-I am fine, but I'm
afraid Enryu is-- Enryu!
-Please don't worry, Princess.
Enryu is even tougher
than he appears.
-But what about you, Kenryu?
You suffered injuries as well.
We must take care of them.
-That blade the
assassin was using.
He called it a Bakkoto.
[swish]
-Hold it right there!
Wait!
Why was that blade so important?
[clang]
-Nnngh.
[diabolical laughter]
-It came from inside the wall?
-(LAUGHING)
Surprised you, right?
It's the power of
my Bakkoto Kakuyoku.
[blast]
[grunting]
-I'm trapped.
-(LAUGHING) What's your hurry?
Running isn't going
to get you anywhere.
-Then I'll just have
to destroy this wall.
-Too late.
-Aaugh!
[smashing]
-There's no way you can break
down this wall without turning
your back to me, and
that leaves you exposed.
(LAUGHING) Huh?
-There might be another way.
(ROARING)
[blast]
[yelling]
-Aaugh.
Stupid me.
I forgot about your strength.
Let me tell you,
that move's not going
to work on me a second time.
-Doesn't really matter.
You can go for it, but you're
not surrounding me again.
-We'll see about that.
[blast]
[grunting]
-So, that's your
battle strategy, is it?
You plan to destroy my walls?
Well, I'd like to see you try!
(ROARS)
[explosions]
[roaring]
[slashing]
[blast]
-(LABORED BREATHING)
So damned tough.
You must have a
weakness somewhere.
-(LABORED BREATHING)
My thoughts, as well.
[chuckles]
-What's so funny?
-Nothing.
I just never thought
I'd meet a man like you
in the World of the Living.
I joined up with Nukii because
I wanted to possess this katana.
and the first time
I use it, I end up
facing an opponent
who's so strong I'm
forced to draw out
its full power.
What luck!
Is it any wonder I'm laughing?
-Listen, that
blade is dangerous.
It's pulling the life
force out of you.
-Believe me, I'm
well aware of that.
But before I defeat
you and lay it down,
I want to see the full
extent of its power.
One way or another, this
will be my final attack.
-I understand.
In that case, I'll meet you
with everything I've got.
Brazo Izquierdo del Diablo.
-(CHUCKLING) It appears you were
still hiding your true power
from me.
-Afraid so.
-That's all right.
It won't matter ultimately.
I'm ready.
(ROARING
[blast]
[roaring]
-Kakuyoku, give me your power!
(ROARING)
[blast]
[grunting]
[sizzling]
-La Muerte.
[explosion]
-(LABORED BREATHING) Aaugh.
Chad!
[chuckling]
-Keh.
Damn it, Chad's down, too.
I see.
You couldn't beat
me so your thugs
are going after all
of my friends now.
-So what of it?
-You jerk!
In the heat of battle, those
warriors who lose their temper
die.
-Shut up!
[clang]
-Aha!
[grunting]
-Nice move.
-We already have all your
little tricks figured out!
[shattering]
-I told you when we
fought before, I never
fall for the same move twice.
That Zanpakuto uses the light
reflected from its mirror
to press the attack.
So once the mirror is
broken, the fight is over.
-Don't be so sure, kid.
-What?
[blast]
-Aaaugh!
-As I told you before,
depending on the spirit
energy of its
wielder, this katana
can become infinitely powerful.
[grunting]
[yelling]
[music playing]
-Lady Kuchiki, are you hurt?
-I'm fine, Kenryu.
But I'm afraid your
house has been ruined.
-Fortunately, we have
homeowners' insurance
for incidents like these.
No matter what
happens, we're covered.
-Where did you buy such a thing?
-At Urahara's shop.
-I'm not sure that was wise.