[theme music]
-The Head Captain has issued
a level one security order.
What good will it do for us if
the Punishment Force can't even
apprehend a single Ryoka?
[laughter]
-Well, Ritz.
Now let it fly.
MAN: Captain!
MAN: What's he done?
-Who did that?
-Has he lost his mind?
[groaning]
-Hold him down!
-Bastard!
-Grab him!
-What is this?
What was that you threw?
[shouting]
-What's he doing?
MAN: He's lost his mind.
-It was poisoned.
The Bounts must be behind this.
-What's wrong with you?
-MAN: He's dead.
MAN: How did that happen?
MAN: Captain, you
need to recover.
-Calm down.
One of the Bounts has the power
to control a person's mind.
I doubt this guy had any
idea what he was doing.
-How could the Bounts do that?
-It's possible that when he came
into contact with the Bount,
the Bount was able to
penetrate his mind.
(THINKING) If that's the
case, there may be others.
Did anybody else come in
contact with the Bount?
-There were a number of us
on patrol in the Higeshinejo
district when--
[groaning]
-Careful!
-What are you doing?
-Get him!
-Protect the captain!
-Captain, let us handle him.
-You shouldn't be fighting
wounded like this.
-(THINKING) How many of
them have been possessed?
-This doesn't make any sense.
One minute I can sense the
Bounts' spiritual pressure,
and then it
completely disappears.
-Yeah.
We've got to figure out
what it is they're up to.
-Do you have any ideas?
-All I know is when I get a hold
of those Bounts, I'm gonna--
-Whoa!
Ah!
[groan]
-Man, what the
hell are you doin'?
-Ichigo.
These guys look
like Soul Reapers,
but they smell like Bounts.
RITZ: Ichigo Kurosaki.
It's time for you to die!
-You mean they're all Dolls?
That Bount Mabashi has a
Doll that controls minds.
These poor guys didn't
know what hit 'em.
-What's wrong with you guys?
Back off!
-They're acting
exactly like Rukia
did when she was being
controlled by that Bount.
-Damit.
[groaning]
[shouting]
[laughter]
-Excellent, Ritz.
Keep up the good work, until
every one of them is dead.
Ah!
This strong spiritual pressure.
Interesting.
-Are you sure?
-Yes, sir.
Some Soul Reapers have fallen
into the hands of the Bounts,
and they've begun
attacking their own men.
-How is that possible?
-One of the Bounts has a
Doll that can enter the body
and control the mind.
I know it for a fact because
I encountered this Bount
in the world of the living.
-Hm.
Is there a way to
regain control?
-The Doll enters the body,
so it's difficult to get to.
While they're alive.
-(THINKING) If I can defeat
the one controlling the Dolls,
it should bring the men who are
being possessed back to normal.
I've got to find that Bount.
Is someone here?
You're a Bount.
[laughter]
-I sensed a strong
spiritual pressure,
so I thought I'd take a look.
-Ha.
I've found the
captain, haven't I?
You look a little
worse for wear.
You haven't been poisoned
by a Bitto, have you?
-So this is your doing.
-If I just let a living soul
sit after harvesting it,
it becomes rancid.
-What?
-Don't worry.
You won't suffer long.
Oh, please.
Don't give me that look.
The poison is fatal,
and there's no antidote.
[grunting]
-Ha!
-Heh, heh.
I figured you'd put up a fight.
That's too bad.
You should try not
to move so much.
It makes the poison
spread faster.
-(THINKING) If I drag this
out, I won't stand a chance.
In that case-- Sting
all enemies to death.
Suzumebachi.
Not so fast!
-Damn you.
Ah!
Ha.
So this is the homonka
I've heard so much about.
It's very impressive.
I'm supposed to die if you hit
me in the same place twice,
right?
Ha ha ha.
If you want to finish me off,
then you'd better do it soon.
You don't have very
much time left.
So I'll just keep my
distance and relax
while I watch you die.
-You psychopath.
-Just die already,
and get it over with.
-Wait!
-Shuhei.
-Huh?
-It's just like you said.
This Doll, or whatever it
is that's controlling them,
has completely fused
with their bodies.
-Yes.
Which means they'll
probably be the same
when they regain consciousness.
-We'll move them to the Squad
4 barracks for observation.
-Uh, what?
-Then Captain Unohana
can examine them.
She'll know best.
If anyone can help these men
in their present condition,
it's her.
I just hope it's not too late.
-Let's get them over to the
treatment room on the double.
MEN: Yes, sir!
UNOHANA: So, Squad
7 Captain Komamura
instructed you to bring
all these men here?
-Yes, ma'am.
We were forced to
knock them unconscious.
We don't know how many
others have been infected,
but we're hoping
you can discover
how to make them normal again.
-This is amazing.
-Have you discovered something?
-Something inside
him is not only
controlling his mind, but his
entire nervous system as well.
It's impossible to
remove the dolls
while the men are fighting.
-There must be
something we can do.
-Right now, all we can
do is suppress the Dolls.
Bring anyone who is being
controlled by a Doll here.
Now we must bind them
before they wake up.
-Right.
-The procedure isn't
foolproof, and I'm not
certain of the outcome,
but we've got to try.
Make the preparations.
-Yes, ma'am.
-The pain.
It's unbearable.
It's so dark.
I can't see.
I have to do something.
But what?
I never thought that I
could be this helpless.
What should I do?
Save me, Yoruichi.
Of course.
That's it!
[crunch]
[screaming]
-Yah!
-Captain, no!
-I'll handle this one.
You just worry about yourself.
All right.
This ends here!
-We're out of beds in here!
You two, move that patient
into the next room!
Let's go!
Hurry it up!
-Captain.
Is he--
-What's going on?
Some other Ritz's aren't
responding to orders.
They must have knocked them out.
The only way they
wouldn't respond
is if the host bodies had
been knocked unconscious.
It's all pointless, though.
They can knock out as
many men as they want,
because with my increased power,
I can create unlimited Ritz's.
You know what to do, Ritz.
RITZ: Understood.
-This is almost too easy.
Probably about time I check
in on that little Soul Reaper.
Just in case she hasn't
discovered it yet,
I'm going to teach her the
true meaning of despair.
-That's what happens
when you get me mad!
-It's time to use Bakudo one!
Sai!
[shouting]
-Renji, that was magnificent!
Who would have guessed you
were able to fight using Kido?
-Yeah, well, I couldn't
use Zabimuru right here,
so I thought that-- hm?
What do you mean, who
would have guessed?
You're making fun
of me, aren't you?
-What are you talking about?
-I'm talking about the fact
that my ability to use Kido
should be no surprise.
I am a lieutenant, you know?
-Right.
-There you are.
Ha ha ha ha.
So, this is where you've
been keeping yourself.
Are you still breathing?
Clinging to that
last bit of life?
I had planned on staying hidden
away until you were dead.
But then--
-Why didn't you?
Why did you come back?
-I realized that the Soul
Reapers had discovered a way
to incapacitate my precious
little Ritz's one by one.
Then I thought,
maybe if I hit them
with someone really strong,
who they can't knock out.
Right?
-You want me.
I'm your victim.
-It's nothing personal, you see.
It's just that I can't bear the
thought of Ritz being harmed.
Don't tell me
you're still trying
to figure out how to
get in that second hit?
You'd give anything to
kill me, wouldn't you?
Well, you can just forget it!
Ah, ha ha ha!
MAN: Hold it!
MABASHI: The Punishment Force.
-Captain.
Are you all right?
MABASHI: So, there are
still a few of you left.
-You're gonna pay for this.
-Your captain is in
danger, so you valiantly
rush to her rescue.
I find that touching.
-Don't you worry, Captain.
We're going to get you
to the treatment room.
-He sounds so sincere.
But is he really a
friend, or an enemy?
-You bastard.
-Ritz, now!
[groaning]
-Yes!
-Oh, what a pity.
Your men were all set to
whisk you away to safety.
But now they belong to Ritz.
Hold her down.
-What's wrong with you?
Let me go.
-Tell me, how does it feel
to have your own subordinates
controlling you?
-You're insane.
-Even though you're
unable to move a muscle,
your tongue works just fine.
I'm going to possess you.
Then I'm going to have Ritz
send you to your grave.
-I'll kill you.
-I don't think so.
Ritz, now!
-Yes!
-It's somehow ironic, isn't it?
Now, farewell, my dear captain.
-I am going to take
good care of you!
[shouting]
-What the--
[groaning]
-Homonka's second strike.
-You little witch.
How'd you do it?
You should be
completely paralyzed.
-Just who the hell do you
think you're dealing with?
My body has already
completely counter-acted
that poison of yours.
-How can that be?
-I've studied all the
disciplines of the Punishment
Force since I was a child.
Including poison.
And over the years, I've
developed a resistance
to nearly every poison there is.
For those poisons I've
never encountered,
there's only one way to
neutralize them successfully.
And that is to fight
poison with poison.
Using Suzumebachi.
-Why did you pretend as
if you were paralyzed?
-I had to draw you in close.
In order to return my
subordinates to normal,
I had to make myself the
bait to lure you back.
I was willing to risk
everything for them.
[groaning]
-This is where it ends.
-You think I'll
give up that easily?
Ritz, now!
RITZ: Your wish is my command.
-You forget that
I still have Ritz.
I'll finish you off this time!
What's wrong?
You're so terrified, you
can't move, aren't you?
Aren't you?
-You're pitiful.
-Damn you!
Kill her!
Destroy her, Ritz!
RITZ: Yes!
Yes!
MABASHI: No!
What?
No, Ritz!
Not me!
Get away from me!
What are you doing?
Dammit, Ritz!
I told you to get her!
-Yes, I understand.
-No, Ritz!
Why are you doing this?
[scream]
-You've obviously
forgotten that your Doll
is a double edged sword.
I learned what happens
when you become
too weak The Doll
senses the weakness,
and then turns on the master.
[scream]
-Help me, please!
Ritz, no!
[scream]
-It's useless.
Suzumebachi's poison will
consume your entire body
within a matter of seconds.
[screaming]
-What the hell just happened?
-They just passed out.
-The Doll's presence
has vanished.
It's completely disappeared.
-Hm.
-What the-- will someone tell
me what's going on around here?
-I guess the Bount controlling
them must've been defeated.
Everything's going
to be all right.
-Mabashi's spiritual
pressure has disappeared.
Can't say I'm surprised.
I always knew he didn't
have what it takes.
So long, loser.
-Heh, heh.
Now it's Mabashi's spiritual
pressure that's disappeared.
It looks like the enemy is
putting up a good fight.
Why don't you quit playing
these hide and seek
games, and come out?
I much prefer
talking face to face.
-Hm.
So you knew I was
there, did you?
I tried to copy you and
hide my spiritual presence.
[laughter]
-Even if you hid your
spiritual pressure,
there's no way to conceal
your lust for blood.
I can smell it in the air.
-My apologies.
But it has nothing
to do with you.
I was looking for Ichinose.
You don't know
where he is, do you?
-It's hard to say.
Perhaps he's dead.
His spiritual pressure
disappeared quite a while ago,
so I assumed one of your
cohorts had done the deed.
-Aw.
I was hoping to have
that honor myself.
But since I can't
have him, I suppose
I'll just have to
make do with you.
You understand.
it's the price you have
to pay for humiliating me.
-If I must, I must.
But don't make the mistake
of underestimating me.
You might just be
in for a surprise,
because I have been given
a very specific job.
To send all the
captains to their grave.
[theme music]
VOICEOVER: Baura, the
alternate dimensional monster,
has suddenly appeared.
Konjiki Ashisogi Jizo, the
guardian beast, fights back.
Two giant monsters clash
in a Soul Society Showdown,
coming soon!
VOICEOVER: How rude.
My zanpakuto is not a monster.
VOICEOVER: It's close enough.
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers.
VOICEOVER: Golden!
-I guess there's nobody here.
-The place is completely empty.
Kenny, aren't you going to
look for the Bounts, too?
-Not interested.
Just because you run around
chasing after something doesn't
mean you're ever
going to find it.
Besides, there's only one
person I want to slash,
and that is Ichigo!
-What the hell?
Why'd it get so cold?