Hyaaahh!
I may have actually
reached my limit.
My limit as a Soul
Reaper, that is.
When I said 'since the
beginning,' I meant I've known
about you since you were born.
What?!
The moment you were born,
I knew you were a special case.
The reason is, because
you're a human, and--
Tch.
You talk too much, Aizen.
Dad, Is that... you?
Hey, Say something!
Dad?
What the heo~llll!!
Hmph.
Keeping his distance.
A wise decision.
Must be in their blood.
You've been watching
for quite a long time.
Haven't you, Gin?
You shouldn't assume I've
just been watching. I just
didn't think you needed my
assistance with him yet.
I see.
Eeeyaah!
It's been a while
since I fought you,
hasn't it?
This time, I won't
be holding back.
Hyaaargh!
Heyaah!
Raikoho!
It's been a while,
my young friend,
since I've crossed
swords with you.
Do you remember the
last time we fought?
It seems like it was
only yesterday.
[Gin]
Ahh. Not good.
Unh!
Aughh!
Unacceptable.
Being the "guardian" of the
gate doesn't mean you're
supposed to open the gate.
A gate-keeper who loses isn't
When a gatekeeper
loses,
It means... Death!
When I cut off Jidanbo's arm,
you got very upset.
Without any hesitation,
you rushed in and attacked me.
You wanna tell me just what the
hell you think you're doing?!
Impale him! Shinso!
I remember thinking,
that as an opponent,
you were extremely
interesting.
Sorry, pal, but I
don't remember.
Huh?
Nice try, but you're a liar.
Hold on, was that
supposed to be an insult?
Take it however you want.
And I'm not saying I've
forgotten crossing
swords with you.
I just have no concept of
what was in your heart.
Whenever I face someone in
battle, I have some idea of
what they're thinking.
Don't get me wrong,
I'm not able to
read their minds.
But during the battles,
I can usually tell why
they're really fighting,
what they want out of me,
and if they think they're
stronger than I am.
But after so many battles now,
I've come to realize
that the stronger my opponent
is, the easier it is for me
to understand their heart.
Well, my friend, you're quite
the poet, aren't you?
Don't change the subject.
With you, it's an entirely
different matter.
Despite how much I
try to read you,
almost nothing comes through.
Even in the midst of the fight,
You weren't completely engaged.
I don't know what you were
thinking about, but it wasn't
the battle with me.
Know something? At first,
I thought you were an
interesting kid.
But the fact is,
you're actually
kind of creepy.
I don't think you should be
calling anybody creepy.
Fascinating, you
throw everything back
at your opponent.
I see why
Captain Aizen is
interested in you.
My Zanpakuto Shinso,
Do you know how far my
blade can extend?
I have no idea.
The length of a hundred
swords, actually.
When I was just a young boy,
people were very impressed.
They said I carried around
a hundred-bladed weapon.
I'm not interested
in your tricks.
Really? Do you have any
idea how far this blade
can extend in Bankai?
Can't say I do, but I didn't
come here for a quiz.
You mean you're not even going
to venture a guess? That's
really a shame. How boring.
Well, I'm going to tell you
anyway, and I'll explain it in
measurements you can understand.
It can extend to
thirteen kilometers.
That must be hard
for you to imagine.
It seems impossible, right?
Tell you what.
I'll demonstrate it for you.
All thirteen kilometers of it.
Bankai...
Kamishininoyari!
Why do you look
so surprised?
Don't you think one Bankai,
is capable of
stopping another?
HaaaaAAA!
You know, the more time I spend
with you, the creepier you get.
Unh... Uh?
Gin...!
That was pretty scary.
But it was also enlightening.
I'd better deal with you
while I'm still able.
Otherwise, things may
get troublesome.
[gasp]
When did his blade suddenly
shrink back down?! Did I get
distracted somehow, and miss it?
No! I never took my attention
away from his sword.
There's no way I wouldn't have
seen that huge blade contract!
[gasp]
Now then, what should I
do to finish you off,
once and for all?
You easily stopped my Bankai.
Guess I have no choice but
to engage you, one on one.
I must say, that's
an impressive sword
you have there.
I feel like mine could
break at any moment.
Well, I'm all for that!
In fact, here, let me
help you!
If my hunch is correct, he only
shrunk that sword to make it
easier to handle.
He hasn't ended his Bankai.
I have to watch his every
move! He's fast. And if he
points the tip of his sword
at me, I could be dead!
He's vulnerable up close!
So, just as I thought.
Huh?
The most frightening thing
about your Bankai is not its
length, and it's not its
destructive force, either.
It's the speed you're
able to contract.
I was thinking about
what you said,
Telling me the length of your
blade served no purpose.
In fact, not telling me
about it would have been
to your advantage.
Similarly, swinging your
sword and slicing up the
town served no purpose.
Attacking me head-on
would have made much more
sense, strategy-wise.
I think you showed me those
things to distract me. Keep me
from noticing how fast your
contraction speed really was.
Am I wrong?
Not bad.
He figured out my strategy
from my first attack, and was
able to apply that knowledge
to dodge my second attack.
That's frightening.
And the chances are,
he'll improve as the
battle goes on.
But he's still got
a long way to go.
Well, since you figured it
out, I guess I have no choice.
I'll tell you how fast
Kamishininoyari can
extend itself.
[claps]
Mm?
Did you hear that?
It's five hundred
times that speed.
[gasp]
The truth of the matter is,
Kamishininoyari isn't the
longest Zanpakuto.
But it is the
fastest Zanpukuto.
Now that you know that,
you realize you have no
chance of winning.
HYAAAAH!
What's wrong, Aizen?
Is it my imagination, or
are you getting slower?
Perhaps you've reached
your limit.
Well now that I think about it,
you may be right about my speed.
I may have actually
reached my limit.
My limit as a Soul
Reaper, that is.
What are you saying?
That my soul is about
to be re-structured.
Not so fast.
What makes you think
that's happening?
The Hogyoku is finally
responding. It's beginning
to understand my thoughts.
I have to concentrate!
Come on...
Ignore the attacks where
he's swinging his sword,
and pay attention when
he makes a thrust!
Don't let him point
that blade at you!
You're not getting away.
[chuckles]
You're awfully jumpy.
What's the problem?
Gah!
You bastard!
I swear I'm gonna
break that sword
of yours!
You're welcome to try,
of course, but don't
get your hopes up.
I may have actually
reached my limit.
My limit as a Soul
Reaper, that is.
What makes you think
that's happening?
The Hogyoku is
finally responding.
I can feel that it's beginning
to understand my thoughts.
That's nonsense!
You can dismiss
it if you like.
But I'm telling you, the
Hogyoku has a will of its own.
Yeah right It's a mass
of energy, not a being.
I understand your
skepticism.
Even I had no idea the
Hogyoku had its own will.
until I became its master,
that is, and was able to
feel it.
Tell me what you think the
Hogyoku's ultimate power is?
You may believe it is
the power to dominate
two opposing forces,
the balance between
Hollows and Soul Reapers.
You'd be wrong.
The Hogyoku's true power,
is the ability to manifest
the desires of those around it.
I'm surprised you
haven't seen that.
What are you talking about?
I guess I have to spell it out
for you.
All the amazing things
that happened to Ichigo
Kurosaki, Rukia Kuchiki,
and Kisuke Urahara,
were simply the result of
manipulation by the Hogyoku.
They were all manifested by
the Hogyoku's will.
What the hell do you mean?
Kisuke Urahara
mistakenly believed that
the Hogyoku's power
was the ability to control the
boundary between Hollows and
Soul Reapers.
As its creator, this is what
he desired its powers to be.
Rukia Kuchiki, in her desire to
bring Ichigo Kurosaki into the
fold, passed along all of her
Spirit Energy to him.
She lost her Soul Reaper
powers because she was still
suffering from the pain of
killing Kaien Shiba.
Yasutora Sado and Orihime Inoue
developed special powers
because, deep in their hearts,
they hated the fact that they
remained helpless, while their
friends were manifesting such
incredible abilities.
I've known about the Hogyoku's
true power for some time now.
[gasp]
I suppose it's incorrect to say
that I know everything about it.
To be accurate, I know that its
power was not the ability to
control the boundary between
Hollows and Soul Reapers,
as Kisuke Urahara
felt it was.
He misinterpreted.
If that was really its
power, the results would
have been different.
Shinji Hirako and the other
Visoreds would never have
become complete Visoreds.
The Hollowfication of
Shinji Hirako and the other
Visoreds was really nothing
more than an experiment.
It was a confirmation of
the Hogyoku's powers.
And in the end, it turned
out to be quite successful.
The activation of the Hogyoku's
power eventually turned Shinji
Hirako and the other Visoreds
into complete Visoreds.
They wouldn't be what
they are today, without
that manipulation.
And armed with my suspicions
about the Hogyoku's power,
I had Rukia Kuchiki
approach Ichigo Kurosaki
with the idea that he could
become a Soul Reaper.
If there were limits to the
Hogyoku's power, this would
help identify them.
It turns out the Hogyoku has
the power to manifest the
desires of those around it.
But if the target does not
have the power to achieve
those desires, nothing
significant happens.
It's a very interesting dynamic,
filled with subtleties.
It can help guide you to
your goals, but can't
achieve them for you.
Most creatures aren't
strong enough to take
advantage of this gift.
They're able to achieve their
petty wishes, but don't have the
vision or force of will to go
after their larger desires.
Aizen, you bastard!
That was a very nice move there.
Fascinating just how effective
sheer luck can be.
You're stupid to
think that was luck!
I--Ichigo?
What is it?!
Leave me alone!
I'm just getting warmed up!
I'll defeat him soon!
I don't want you to interfere!
Sorry about all this,
Captain Aizen. I hope
I didn't interrupt
your conversation.
It's all right.
I had pretty much finished
explaining myself.
Hey, what the
hell is that Dad?!
What's going on?!
Why are you
asking me?!
I had no idea what was going
on when you came flying in,
and as of this moment, I
still have no idea!
Hey, what kind of
answer is that?!
You're the one who's
been fighting the guy!
Didn't you pay attention?!
That's not my job,
smart-ass!
If you want to know
what's going on, why
don't you get him to
explain it to you!
It doesn't matter if you
understand what it is.
You can't escape its influence.
You're feeling it now, even as
you try to resist its will.
It has the power to destroy
the wall that separates
those beings who are gods,
from those who are not!
[gasp]
So you've come.
Kisuke Urahara.
[Gin]
You and your father
are very much alike.
[Ichigo]
Are you nuts? No way!
[Isshin]
I absolutely agree!
My son is nowhere near
as good a warrior as I am!
[Gin]
See? That's what
I'm talking about!
[Ichigo & Isshin]
Yeah, right!
[Gin]
[exasperated sigh]