[theme song]
NARRATOR: Although
Kenryu and the others
had tried to shield Princess
Rurichiyo from the truth,
she was still able to
discern Gyokaku Kumoi's
sinister intentions.
Rurichiyo returned home
to the Kasumioji palace.
Ichigo and Rukia followed,
and attempted a rescue
during her arranged wedding.
But they soon discovered they
had walked into Kumoi's trap
and that the bride
was an imposter.
They were immediately surrounded
by Soi Fon and her squad.
Thanks to some unexpected help
from Rurichiyo's fiance, Shu
Kannogi, they managed to escape.
But now, Ichigo is a wanted man.
-Any sign of them?
-No, sir.
We're searching
the entire complex.
-There's no one in here.
-I'll look over here.
-I'll check the east corridor.
-You check that room.
-Are you all right, Ichigo?
-Yeah.
It's really just a scratch.
-Wow.
I never had any idea that places
like this existed underground.
-Sorry.
I'm sure this makes
you uncomfortable.
-Oh, I'm fine.
Don't worry about it.
The important thing is we
have to find Rurichiyo.
-I understand.
But we are wanted, and Soul
Reapers are looking for us.
If we go out now, we're
as good as captured.
-Right.
-Keeping that in mind, we
still have to look for her.
Any idea where she is?
-The truth is, I've
never even walked around
outside the palace grounds.
I've seen a bit of the world
while riding through town,
though.
-I can't believe it.
Are all you nobles like this?
-Not everyone.
I heard that Rurichiyo
used to sneak out
every once in a while.
But I was too scared
to go with her.
-You shouldn't be
so hard on yourself.
-Look, she couldn't have
been taken very far.
She's probably somewhere
inside the Kasumioji palace.
Should we try breaking in again?
-But even Sir Kenryu
couldn't pull that off.
How are we going
to manage eluding
all of those guards on our own?
-Shu, you may not know
the world outside,
but you know the layout
of the palace, right?
-For the most part.
But it's so big, I
haven't seen all of it.
-You'll have to give
it your best shot.
-Right.
-Captain, Groups Three and Four
have been searching the palace
grounds, but haven't
found them yet.
-Groups One and Two
have just returned.
Groups Five and Six have
headed out to take their place.
-Very well then.
Keep me updated
on their progress.
-Right.
SOI FON (VOICEOVER):
Why did he do this?
-Sorry.
Can you give me just a second?
-Captain.
-Mm?
-Squad Three has just reported.
I have their information.
-Were they are
able to find them?
-They've disappeared completely.
No trace.
-Is that so?
-I've been thinking about those
two guys Kenryu and Enryu.
Do think we should
have handed them over
to the Kasumioji Clan?
Maybe we should have kept
them in custody ourselves.
Captain?
-Mm?
-Is everything all right?
-Yes.
I'm fine.
Those two men are no
longer our concern.
The head captain made
it perfectly clear to us
that we're to allow
the nobles to take
care of their own affairs.
Our mission is to go out
and capture Ichigo Kurosaki,
and that's all.
I'm going to lead the
punishment force myself.
You're in charge here.
-Yes, Captain.
-We'll determine the truth
once he's in custody.
-Squad Three has been
ordered to remain on standby.
Groups should go get
their meals one at a time.
-Right, sir.
Group one, move out for chow.
-How's everything going?
-Welcome back, Captain Amagai.
Things are fine here.
-Good.
Squad Two seemed to have
everything under control.
I'm taking a quick break.
-You're in time for dinner.
It appears we'll be out
here for quite a while.
-Our adversaries are well
trained and very smart.
We have to be patient.
Let me ask you.
-Hm?
-How has Makoto
been acting lately?
-He's done nothing
out of the ordinary.
-All right.
I have to say I'm
relieved to hear that.
It never feels good to have
suspicions about your comrades.
-Of course.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Captain Amagai!
Are you coming down
here for dinner?
-I am!
[cheering]
-Huh?
-Have the emergency repairs to
the walls been completed yet?
-Yes sir.
-Those bandits may try to
break in again any time.
Let's double the number
of men on the watch.
-Yes.
Right away.
-I can't believe they
managed to escape.
The 13 Court Guard Squads
were absolutely useless.
-Master Kumoi?
It's time for Lady
Rurichiyo's dinner.
Is she in her room?
-The princess was traumatized
by today's events.
She took to her bed.
She needs her rest.
She isn't up to eating a meal.
-But my lord!
-Imagine how the
princess must feel.
Her wedding completely ruined.
-Of course.
I'm so sorry, sir.
-I certainly hadn't
counted on Shu Kannogi
being taken hostage.
But that's unimportant.
Bottom line is the princess
is still in my hands.
-The princess has been spotted?
-Yes, sir.
She's passed through the
Senkaimon and is on her way
here.
But we're keeping a close
eye on the precipice world.
-Have you completed
all the preparations?
-Yes, sir.
-Why don't we gather
in the grand hall?
Everyone, come and
join the princess.
We will celebrate her
return with a toast.
[cheering]
-I wonder why there
are no guards on duty.
-Huh?
-[laughing]
-I am really back.
I have returned to my true home.
The sky seems so small
when I look at it now.
Huh?
[gasp] Help me, someone!
Anyone!
[muffled screaming]
-Whoever you are,
tell me, how long
do you plan on keeping me
locked up in this place?
-You'll be released
in a little while,
after I take care of that
substitute Soul Reaper
who's here looking for you.
-Huh?
-Hm.
-Ichigo.
He followed me here.
-He must be a fool.
I was told he made a
mess of your wedding,
and turned the 13 Court
Guard Squads against him.
-What is it you're after?
-You're in no position to
be asking any questions.
-Is Kumoi paying you to do this?
-You have such a simple mind.
I'm not a fool who can be led
around by the promise of money.
I am here for a
different reason.
-I guess you must be.
Otherwise, you
wouldn't be so afraid.
-Afraid?
What are you talking about?
-Do not deny it.
I may not know much about
the world out there,
but it is obvious
to me that you are
deathly afraid of something.
It is written all over your
face, and it is in your voice.
-Stop talking!
It's no matter, Princess.
You won't have to be
brave for much longer.
-There's the man.
How you doing,
Third Seat Kibune?
-Huh?
-You're the last person
I expected to see.
Why are you out here so late?
-Have you been drinking?
-Huh?
You mean you can tell?
-We're supposed to be
on emergency alert.
-Sorry about that.
I only had a little bit of sake.
Do you mind keeping this
between the two of us?
-Hm.
-And if you do,
Third Seat Kibune,
I promise I'll keep my mouth
shut about what you were doing
out here in the
middle of the night.
-Hm?
You saw where I was coming from?
-Captain Amagai, something
urgent has come up.
Third Seat Kibune is missing.
-Excuse me?
-There's more, Captain.
One of our squad members has
been missing since last night
as well.
-It can't be coincidental.
-I don't think so.
From what I've learned,
some of our squad members
apparently snuck out and
had a small drinking party
last night.
Halfway through the
evening, one of the men
thought he saw Third Seat
Kibune and ran after him.
The other men said
he never came back.
-He's been missing for hours and
nobody's seen any trace of him?
-Right, Captain.
-Hm.
Izuru, I want you to take
over the search for Makoto.
I'll go find that
substitute Soul Reaper
and find him as
quickly as possible.
-Understood, Captain.
-I have a bad
feeling about this.
-I leave the search
under your command.
Something wrong?
-Captain, how are you going
to handle this problem?
-What are you talking about?
-Ichigo and Rukia, of course.
There has to be some kind of
explanation for their actions!
They'd never do something like
this without a good reason!
-And what if they did?
I have no sympathy
for anyone who
chooses to defy orders that
come from the Soul Society.
-But your sister.
-I stand by what I said.
I expect you to personally
head up the search parties.
-You're putting me in
charge of everything
relating to this search?
Understood, sir.
I'll take command of
Squad Six and begin
to conduct a thorough
sweep immediately.
-Huh?
What's wrong?
-Shh.
-I'm sensing it as well.
Someone's coming this way.
-You're right.
-Have we been found?
-They haven't
discovered us yet, but--
-It's just a matter of time now.
-Come on.
MALE SPEAKER
(OFFSCREEN): I thought
I heard someone
moving over there!
-Damn!
They noticed us!
-Hurry!
[shouting]
-Go get them!
-Don't let them get away.
-Catch up to them!
Cut them off!
-If Anatura were here,
we wouldn't have to run!
He knows all the escape routes!
-Quit complaining.
-Damn.
It's a dead end.
-Ichigo.
This way.
We can get to the
surface from here.
-Guess we have no choice.
-What's the matter?
-What a surprise.
I must say we never thought
we'd run into you here.
-We were set up.
-You're mistaken.
It was just a coincidence.
-How very convenient.
Who are you, anyway?
-The captain of Squad Three,
of the 13 Court Guard Squads.
I'm Shusuke Amagai.
-The captain of Squad Three?
-He must be the new guy they
recently appointed to the post.
-That explains it.
It's no wonder I
don't recognize him.
-What bad luck.
We might have been
able to get out of this
if we were dealing
with a captain who
happened to know us.
-You must be Ichigo Kurosaki?
-That's right.
-I see.
I'm afraid I have to arrest you.
-Captain, can I speak to you?
I'm Rukia Kuchiki of Squad 13.
Is there any way
you might consider
hearing our side of the story?
-I'll tell you what.
If you come quietly and let us
take you to our holding cell,
I'd be willing to listen.
-But that's not--
-Rukia, you take care of Shu.
-Stand down!
I've heard a lot about this
substitute Soul Reaper's
abilities.
I'd like to see them myself.
I'm ordering you
not to interfere.
--[laughs] You may come
to regret that order.
-What's wrong, kid?
Is that all you got?
-You move pretty fast,
considering how big you are.
-I have a bit of
exper-- Guess I better
stop holding back if
I want to defeat you.
Sever, Raika!
The real battle
is about to start.
-So let it.
I'm ready for you.
-Ichigo!
-[growling]
-Your power is very impressive.
-Is this the best
you can come up with,
substitute Soul Reaper?
-Getsuga Tensho!
-OK, kid, that wasn't bad.
-Stop this!
-Sir Shu, don't!
-Shu!
-No!
Stop, please!
-Young man, why are you
defending the very people who
ruined your wedding ceremony and
then proceeded to kidnap you?
What, have you lost your mind?
-No, you don't
understand, Captain!
You've got all wrong!
I went with these people
of my own free will.
-Hm?
-Please, Captain.
I'm begging you, just
hear what I have to say.
-Shu.
-These people came
here to try and save
Princess Rurichiyo's life.
Believe me.
That's why I went with them.
I've always wanted
to help the princess,
but everything I tried
ended in failure.
What they showed
me opened my eyes
about what's really going
on and who's responsible.
The Kasumioji Clan is
in terrible trouble,
but with their help, we
have a chance to save it!
-Oh, Sir Shu.
-Oh, boy.
-Captain, please help us find
Rurichiyo before they kill her!
[crying]
-All right, fine.
I'll listen to what
they have to say.
After hearing the
sincerity in your voice,
I have to give you the
benefit of the doubt.
Put away your swords, everyone.
-Thank you, Captain Amagai.
-Upheaval amongst the
Kasumioji Clan, you say?
So, you were hired to be
bodyguards for the princess,
right?
-Yeah.
-Uh-huh.
That makes things clearer.
But not easier.
We weren't ordered to
investigate the Kasumioji Clan.
It seems that the
head captain doesn't
want to stick his nose
into their affairs.
He doesn't want
to mess with them.
He's made it pretty clear.
It's outside our jurisdiction.
At the very least, we will need
to find some solid evidence
as a basis to justify
our initial involvement.
-There is one starting
point, and that's the Bakoto.
-The Bakoto?
-That's the name they give
to the weapons they're using.
-We've all had to face them,
and they're definitely illegal.
I believe at the
very least, they're
much too powerful for
one clan to possess.
-Huh.
So before we captured you, what
was going to be your next move?
-We were searching for
the real Rurichiyo.
The girl who was involved in
the wedding ceremony was a fake.
-First we wanted to
rescue the princess,
then expose Kumoi as a criminal.
It will be easier to
accomplish that now
that Sir Shu is helping us.
-I understand.
Now that I've got
the whole story,
I've decided we will help
you rescue the princess.
-Are you sure about that?
-Captain!
-It's all right, men.
Trust me on this.
I'm convinced they've
been telling us the truth.
-You're a man of great insight.
Thank you for your
faith, Captain.
-Don't mention it.
I have a few issues of my
own that need to be resolved,
and it seems to me that siding
with you will take care of them
much more quickly than
attempting to work them out
alone.
Go to Lieutenant Kira and
tell him about all of this.
-Yes, sir.
SHU (VOICEOVER): Thank goodness.
Hang on, Rurichiyo.
We're coming.
We're coming to save you.
[theme song]
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Whenever
I come to the Soul Society,
I always feel like
I'm running away.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): That's silly.
By the way, we need to
find a place to hide.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Oh, great.
What about your house.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): Impossible.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Why?
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): Because
my older brother's there.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Oh, yeah.
That would be bad.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): Very bad.