[theme music]
CHILD: There it is!
CHILD: Gotcha!
[humming]
-All done.
What do you think?
Your new outfit is
all ready, Bostov.
See?
Isn't it just the cutest
little thing ever?
Wow, I just thought
of something else.
Some colorful embroidery.
Huh?
I'll use blue.
No, red.
Aw.
Since there's no red,
guess I'll use yellow.
Aw.
This is awful.
I hate it when I don't have
the thread that I need.
Don't worry, Bostov.
I'm gona buy some new thread
for your outfit right now.
I'll be right back.
[humming]
-Kon here.
Day 175.
As if it wasn't
humiliating enough
having to live as a stupid stuff
animal trapped in this house,
now I'm supposed to wear that?
After all the endless
hours I've been
forced to actually play house
with the other stuffed animals?
I can't take it!
I'm outta here!
I what the hell?
My hands!
Ah!
I've been stitched
into a threesome
with stupid and stupider!
How dare that human
do this to me?
[scream]
-The spirits are
always with you--
-I heard that the squishy
bug drinking juice,
it'll make you really sick.
-Wow, I guess I shouldn't
have done that then, huh?
-Damn you kids!
You totally messed
up my catch phrase.
Once again, the spirits
are-- [mumbling].
-Customer parking only here
in front of the clinic.
Move that pile of junk.
-Hey, it's Karakura Red!
Long time no see.
-Not nearly long enough.
What do you want, Don Kanonji?
-Oh, now is that any way to talk
to a friend, a comrade in arms
who fought with you side
by side for peace and love
in the free world?
-It's the middle of the day.
Aren't you supposed
to be working?
-Hey, now!
It may look like I'm unemployed,
but I can explain, kid.
You see, TV shows are
taped weeks in advance,
so right now I'm
just on vacation.
The fact is, the
network can't wait
to renew my contract
for another season.
Wah, ha ha ha!
-That's funny.
I heard you were
getting cancelled.
-Huh?
-I hear your ratings
have been really bad.
-Not so loud!
If I lose one more sponsor,
I'll be back to selling
used cars at midnight on cable!
Never mind all that.
I've come to enlist you in
a special training session!
-Oh, brother.
What does that mean?
-I'll tell ya!
We need to train like crazy to
protect this happy little town
from the bad spirits that
even now are threatening!
Whoa!
Almost lost my head there.
Come on, Karakura Red.
Let's start with
some jumping jacks!
Wah, ha ha ha!
Wah, ha ha--
-What's this really all about?
-Huh?
Damn.
It's painful to
admit, but it's true.
I, Don Kanonji, have seen my
popularity dropping lately.
But anyone who thinks they've
seen the last of Don Kanonji
has another thing comin'!
I'll do whatever it takes
to revive this show,
and I knwo just what I need to
grab the hearts of my audience.
We all know everyone wants a
hero, so now all I have to do
is bring back the
Karakura Superheroes!
-Waste of time, if you ask me.
-Huh?
Ah!
Hold on!
No, wait!
Please!
Don't go!
I need you!
I'm begging you, Karakura Red!
Please don't abandon me!
Not now, in my time of need!
Please!
-Ha ha!
On these wings of
freedom I shall now
take flight, and soar
far away from here.
Ah, they're freakin' heavy!
All right, fine, so I'm not
soaring so much as I'm walking.
The point is, I'm
getting out of this-- ah!
Damn, I've been spotted!
-Hello, there.
[mumbling]
-I'm a robot.
-Look, a silver dollar!
-That's mine!
Where?
Ah!
-You are not a plain old
stuff animal, are you?
-Well, sure I am.
Look.
You just wind me up,
and I dance around
like any other cheap toy--
-You're an evil
spirit, aren't you?
-(THINKING) Oh, crap!
I've had about enough of this!
I'm Bostov, a stupid sailor
suit wearing prisoner
of a little girl, sewn together
with these two yahoos, Buri
and Puri.
Now's my chance!
-Oh, no you don't!
Come back here!
Hold it there, bad spirit.
I'm curious about you.
Hm?
-What are you doing, you freak?
I'm no rose.
I-- ah, your nose breath!
-Well, you certainly
have a strange odor,
but it's not awful.
I think I've got it.
You're not an evil spirit.
You're just a weird spirit.
-Who are you calling
weird, you reject
from hell's marching band?
-As every TV action fan
knows, no team of superheroes
can be complete
without a mascot.
This walking, stalking
stuffed animal
could be just the thing
to put the Karakura
superheroes over the top!
Wah, ha ha ha!
-Whatever the hell
you're planning for me,
you can forget about it.
-Oh, good heavens.
Did I say all of that out loud?
It must be old age kicking in.
I hardly even know my
own name, much less
what I'm blabbering about.
-What are you blabbering about?
-I'll tell you!
How would you like to
become an actual hero?
-A hero?
For real?
-Yes.
A hero of justice.
-A hero of justice, huh?
Ha ha.
-Oh, you're the best!
Wow!
-This must be heaven, squeezed
by so many lovely marshmallows!
-So, what do you say?
Do you think you're
ready to join
the superheroes of justice?
-My name is Kon, also
known as Karakura King!
-Wah, ha ha ha!
-Welcome aboard, new member.
-Hi!
-Huh?
-Don Kanonji!
Wah, ha ha ha ha ha ha!
-Wah, ha ha ha ha!
Everybody!
Wah, ha ha ha ha!
Oh, it has little a
while, sister of Ichigo.
-Are you here to do a
Spirit Hunter episode?
-Oh, no.
I'm here recruiting
the latest member
for my team of superheroes.
-Really?
Who is that?
-Let me introduce you.
Here he is, the newest member
of the Karakura Superheroes,
Karakura King!
-Huh?
You mean this stuffed animal?
-Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Tell me this isn't happening.
-Hm.
You sure look a lot
like a friend of mine.
Nice to meet ya.
-N-nice to meet you, too.
-You even talk.
That's amazing!
-How about you, Karakura Yellow?
You'll join up too, right?
-Absolutely!
Yes, sir!
Affirmative!
Oh?
Hey, I have a new outfit I made
for Bostov's boyfriend that
might be just right.
What do you think,
Karakura King?
-Huh?
You've got to be kidding me.
All this time I've been
wearing frilly dresses,
I could have been dressed
like a bad ass superhero?
I wish I knew she could
make outfits like this.
Oh!
-How do I look?
-You look so cool,
Karakura King!
It fits perfectly!
-That makes one
member and a mascot.
If only I could pull the rest
of them out of the ground,
just like a bunch of taters!
-What's a bunch of taters?
-Did I say that out loud, too?
I gotta watch that.
Never mind.
Everything is OK!
Wah, ha ha ha!
-There it is.
-So Karin turned you down, huh?
-Yes, but it doesn't matter.
I think we go left here.
-OK.
-Wah!
-Uh-oh!
I forgot she didn't
know I could walk.
Oh, well.
If she hasn't recognized
me by now, she won't.
-I have never seen a
stuffed animal that walks.
-What did you expect
of the Karakura King?
-Amazing!
-Hey, I can jump rope
double dutch, too.
-Even more amazing!
All my friend Bostov ever
does is sit around in my room
and sleep all the time.
But for the most part, I think I
know what she's dreaming about.
She thinks about having a
boyfriend, or pretty girls'
clothes.
-Girls without
clothes, you mean.
-Soon my heroic team
will be complete,
and my resurrection can begin!
-That's right!
Whatever he just said!
-Look out!
-Huh?
Wah!
-What's the big idea?
-Hey, there's still
more tash up here!
Huh?
Why'd you throw trash
on those people?
-I know this place.
-So what kind of training?
-I'm glad you asked
that question.
You should join us!
-I love how you talk.
Oh?
-You've gotta be kidding!
The last time I helped you guys,
I was grounded for six months!
-Oh, please?
-I've got nothing
against you, Yuzu.
But you?
I'll never take
orders from you again!
-Oh?
-Got that?
-For sure?
-Somehow I know I'm going
to regret this, but OK.
Karakura Red, here we go again!
-Jinta, remember what Tessai
does when you goof off?
[screaming]
-You're right.
I never want to feel that again.
-It'll be OK if we do
it together, though.
-Huh?
-And we'll Be doing something
to help out our neighborhood.
Right?
-Oh, all right, all right, I'll
do it, I'll do it, I'll do it!
-Ururu, you're joining, too.
Then if we get in trouble,
we'll both get it equally.
-I don't know.
-Please, Ururu?
It'll be fun.
OK?
-All right.
KON (THINKING): What kind of
a nightmare superhero team
is this?
A goofball in a clown suit,
a psycho runt, a space cadet?
and a monster
disguised as a girl?
You guys have got
to be kidding me!
I can't work with these losers.
I'm outta here.
Wah!
-And just where do you
think you're going?
-Let's start training.
You wouldn't want to miss
out on that, now, would you?
-No!
Of course not!
I was just about to
suggest that, myself!
-All right!
Let's get this training
session started!
-Karakura King, are you ready?
-What is this supposed to
be training me for, exactly?
-10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5,
4, 3, 2, 1, blast off!
-Ah!
-First exercise successful!
-We did it!
-Good job!
-Now what am I learning?
-Learning to be fabulous!
-What does that have
to do with anything?
I'm a superhero, not
a giant wedding cake!
-Karakura King,a big
and beautiful thing!
-Song and dance?
-Karakura King, a big
and beautiful thing.
-Wha's this string?
-Oh, you shouldn't
pull on that yet.
-You should have said
that before I pulled.
-You shouldn't have
pulled before you asked.
-Huh?
Ah!
This is not training!
This is torture!
Why does everything
happen to me?
-Marvelous!
-A failure.
-Oh, really?
You think so?
-It would have been a
lot prettier at night.
-I get blown up, and
that's all you care about?
I don't have to put
up with this abuse!
I'm through with your training!
-Hey!
-Wait, Karakura King!
-See ya, losers!
-This headache.
it must be about to
rain, or something.
Yuzu?
Not here.
Where'd she go?
-Rukia, where are you?
Please come back.
I need you to hold me and
save me from these monsters.
You don't know the
horrors they're
putting me through here.
Come home, Rukia!
Huh?
No.
No!
No, no, no, no!
-Karakura King!
-Karakura King?
Where did he go?
-Hm.
Disaster, crisis!
Spine-tingling suspense.
Just when things were
going along so well,
fate has reared its
ugly head with the loss
my super team's lovable mascot.
My perfect plan lies in ruins!
What will I do?
-Have you guys noticed?
-He keeps talking to himself?
-A lot.
-Huh?
I'm not about to give
up on the King yet.
-But we haven't found a
trace of him anywhere.
-If only he'd give us a sign.
KON: Help me!
-There he is!
-Help!
Help!
It's got me!
-That is one big, bad spirit!
-Whoa, it's a hollow!
-Way to go, Karakura King!
-Huh?
What are you
talking about, girl?
-Karakura King can fly, too.
Isn't he just the coolest?
DON KANONJI: Oh, I forgot.
You can't see him, can you?
Well, it doesn't matter.
With big trouble
brewing and dark
clouds gathering on the horizon.
But when evil rears
its ugly head,
there's only one thing to do.
And Don Kanonji is
just the man to do it!
I love the sound
of my own voice!
So, the first mission for
the newly reformed Karakura
Superheroes is to save
the Karakura King!
-Yes, sir!
-All right!
-Help me!
Ah!
Don't eat me!
Don't eat me, please!
I'm not very tasty.
I'm just full of
cotton on the inside.
-Ha, ha, ha.
Oh, I have no intention
of eating you.
-What is this?
You mean you can actually talk?
-Of course I can.
-Well, what are you planning
to do with me, then?
-I'm going to take you back
home with me and give you good
lovin'.
-I think that might be
worse than getting eaten!
-Come on, my little
flat faced lion.
-No, no!
No, let me go!
-You don't have to do
so afraid, little one.
I'm a professional, you know?
-Oh, I can't believe it's really
going to end like this for me.
Goodbye, my fair Rukia.
Goodbye, my sweet Orihime.
Farewell to all
the beautiful girls
I never had a chance to meet!
-Aw.
-Please make it painless.
-Hold it right there!
-What?
-Oh, good!
About time you
came to rescue me!
[shouting]
-This is a rescue?
-The spirits are
always with you!
Wah, ha ha ha ha ha!
-The burning heart is
the flame of justice!
Burning eternal
fire, Karakura Red!
-I'm Karakura Pink.
-Um, I, oh, right.
Introductions.
Well, I'm Yellow.
And there's Karakura King!
-How ridiculous you are.
And so foolish, to think you
could stop the love affair
I've begun.
Little flat face
is all mine now.
-Oh, no!
It's even changed
my name already!
-Anyone who messes with
my love life gets sliced!
-I don't understand.
What's happening?
-Yuzu, no!
Get away!
-She can't see the Hollow.
-Well, look here.
A willing victmi?
-Where-- where did everyone go?
-Do you want to taste my claw?
-Run away!
-Tear at flesh, my claw!
-Yuzu!
-Karakura Yellow!
-Huh?
Hey, Karin!
-That was close.
No wonder I've been
having headaches.
-Well, Karakura Red.
You've come to
join us after all.
-Hey, I'm Karakura Red!
-Don't tell me you guys
are still doing that stuff
and calling yourselves
those silly names.
-Listen, I joined
because there were
people who needed our help.
-What's with Karakura King?
-Stealthy.
-Isn't that Yuzu's Bostov doll?
-No, that's Karakura King.
Karakura King needs
our help, Karin.
And you're just
the one to do it.
-You don't know what
you're asking for.
-But where are
you my lover lion?
Wait for me!
My swetheart!
Oh, don't leave me, my love.
-All right!
Then I'll go take care
of this monster myself!
-Huh?
Oh, no you don't!
-Wait, you guys!
-What do you think you're doing?
-I'm not about to leave
this all up to you!
-You've got some
nerve, mocking me!
-You're the one who put Yuzu
in danger in the first place.
-Oh, shut up, shut up, shut up!
-What would you know about it?
You're just a girl!
-Oh, no you didn't!
-Oh, yes I did!
-Argh!
-Wait, flat face!
-Huh?
[screaming]
-Leave him alone!
He's mine!
-Just get away from
me, all of you!
-Now I've got you!
-You stay out of this!
-I told you to let
me handle this!
-Let you mess it up, you mean!
-That's your job, clown!
-How dare you call me clown!
-You little twerp!
-Look who's talking, wannabe!
-Shut up, stupid!
-You're stupid!
-Oh, yeah?
Well, you're stupid
for calling me stupid.
Oh, really?
-Stupid!
-And you're even stupider for--
-Silence, both of you!
Enough of your bickering!
I've had it with you
annoying creatures.
I'm going to release my
twister and destroy you!
-Whoa!
A typhoon!
-What did I do to deserve this?
-Yuzu!
Take my hand!
-They're all falling
right into the center.
-I'm spinning and swirling!
I'm getting sucked in!
Oh, wow.
I guess I'm all
right, after all.
-The Hollow is
down at the center.
I've got to throw a
really powerful attack.
-Huh?
What now?
[mumbling] What
have you done to me?
-Do it, Ururu!
-Huh?
What are you gonna do?
-Karakura Storm Serve!
-Ah!
-Now it's our turn, Karin!
Home run!
-I got it!
-Yah!
-Goal kick!
-Why me?
-Huh?
This technique!
I think they're using the
legendary Karakura Ultimate
Buster Attack!
Yow!
-I guess this is the end for me.
I can see eternity
reaching out to suck me in.
-How humiliating to
have it end this way!
-Where is everyone?
-Up there.
-Huh?
-Wah, ha ha ha ha ha!
-Listen here, you pervert!
You put me down right
now, you hear me?
-Is, is this heaven?
If it is, then are you an angel?
Oh.
Obviously not.
-Are you gonna be all
right, Karakura King?
-Well, I'm alive, if
that's what you mean.
-Thank goodness.
For a minute there, I thought
you sacrificed yourself
to save all the rest of us.
-Oh, yeah.
That was my plan right
from the beginning.
Sure.
-Now you see the
impressive results
of all our hard training!
Magnificent!
Wah, ha ha ha ha ha!
The spirits are always with you!
Yeah!
[cheering]
-All right.
Welcome to a special
edition report,
in which I, Don Kanonji, join
the legendary superheroes
of Karakura town
on a brave mission
into the uncharted wilderness!
Shock and suspense!
-Shock and suspense!
-Huh?
Hey, Karin!
Take a look at what's on
the television right now.
It's you!
-Huh?
What the-- When
did he shoot this?
-Oh, the joy of it.
Here you see one of the
tortured evil spirits
that can never rest!
-I wonder how Karakura
King is doing?
Huh?
-But don't be sad, Bostov.
I haven't forgotten you.
I'm making you a
brand new outfit
so you'll be even prettier.
-(THINKING) Oh, joy.
I can hardly wait.
[theme music]
-Wah, ha ha ha ha!
For all of you plagued
by bad spirits,
we, the Karakura Superheroes,
can take care of your problems
right away!
Call now to take advantage of
our no money down, interest
free offer!
MAN: Next episode, we're
getting back to our main story!