The Zanpakuto... Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined
by its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper and
dies with its Soul Reaper.
That is the existence
of a Zanpakuto.
Afternoon, Lieutenant
Ise. How about some
tea?
Have I been here that
long? Sorry for taking
over your desk like this.
Oh, I don't mind. To me,
these temporary quarters
feel like I've gone off
to camp. I know it's
kinda silly, but to tell
you the truth, I'm sort
of enjoying it.
I know what you mean.
Oh! I meant to tell
you--- Lieutenant
Hinamori brought in some
cookies she baked herself!
Do they look like the
normal kind you'd eat?
Of course, is
something wrong?
Not at all. I just had
a silly flashback.
Well... They sure look
like normal cookies to
me! See?
Well, that's a relief.
Let me get you your tea.
Huh? Now that's weird.
Is something the matter?
I can't seem to find any
of the tea leaves.
That is weird---I just
bought some the other
day.
I have to tell you,
Lieutenant, there's been
a whole lot of things
that have been reported
missing lately. Rice
and soybean paste, to
start with...
Captain Kyoraku was
saying his secret stash
of sake disappeared the
other day.
Hanamaru is... My
Hanamaru is missing!
I'm afraid this is all
we've got. This is the
clearest image caught by
the surveillance cameras.
Not really much help, is
it? It could be anything.
We were unable to get any
clearer images, but
according to what we
could make out, the
intruder snuck into the
barracks and stole four
chickens. Hanamaru, Hanae,
Hanakichi, and Hanaemon.
Why do we have chickens?
Ever since the Muramasa
incident, Squad Four has
been so busy, its members
barely have time to go
home between one shift
and another.
So they've tried to
become more
self-sufficient. They now
raise chickens, and
they've started growing a
vegetable garden on the
grounds of their
barracks.
Their tomatoes and eggs
are delicious, I can tell
you that.
It's a group effort---I
was in charge of raising
the chickens..
They were all perfectly
fine as of yesterday.
The fence around the coop
was secure, and there
weren't any holes dug
underneath it. If we're
to assume the culprit
stole the chickens by
opening the entrance
door, then it can't be
the work of a
simple-minded predator.
The timing of this
incident is so unusual,
I'm wondering if it could
be connected with the
rash of recent thefts at
the barracks?
Do you suppose this could
be the work of one of the
Sword Beasts?
Captain Unohana... What
are your thoughts?
I'm afraid we can't
eliminate the possibility
But the truth of the
matter is, we don't have
enough information yet to
make any kind of
conclusion.
I traced the footsteps
found on the scene, and
confirmed that the
alleged culprit escaped
by accessing the
underground waterway.
The reason we've
assembled this unit is,
we need you to identify
the thief who escaped
through the underground
waterway, track him down,
and take him into custody.
Uh-huh. And tell me how that
affects me. Why was I summoned
here?
Oh, that's an easy one to
answer. From what we've
been able to determine,
the thief may in fact be
a Sword Beast.
So just to be safe, we
want you to protect
everyone.
Well... It'll be a good
way to pass the time.
I suppose.
Sorry to involve you,
Nanao...
But I'm depending on
you to get the job done.
Yes! I understand completely,
sir. My team and I are ready
to go!
Are you having any
trouble tracking them?
No. See for yourself.
So this is their present
position in real time?
Yes sir. But if you
don't mind my saying...
Conducting a search while
mapping the underground
waterway is a lot for
them to handle.
I wonder if we're being
too ambitious here.
Why waste the
opportunity? Truly,
it's killing two birds
with one stone.
But it's kind of dangerous,
will they be okay?
Oh... I wouldn't worry,
I'm sure they'll be fine.
This place sure has a
creepy feel about it.
You're right about that.
I've been hearing scary
stories about this place, ever
since I was a little kid...
Oh? What sort of
stories?
Well, stories about
how people down here
have died.
Or worse, how people
who have come down and
gone missing.
They even talk about
people being trapped here
while working on extending
the waterway!
They say, when conditions
are right, you can hear
their voices calling for
help.
Terrific, that's a good
one!
Maybe our thief is one of
those people who's been
stuck down here all this
time.
Ridiculous!
Those ghost stories are
told to scare little
children.
Everyone knows there's no
such thing as ghosts in
the Soul Society...
What's wrong?!
[screaming]
Something touched my
neck! I can feel it!
Was it an enemy?
Oh, it's okay
Lieutenant.
Don't worry. That was
just a drop of water.
Look there.. Up in the
ceiling...
Water seeps down through
the rock in quite a few
places.
You were spooked by a
water droplet. I never
noticed it before, but
you're kind of a
scaredy-cat, aren't you,
Lieutenant?
What was that?! I just
bumped into something!
What just happened?!
You set off a booby trap!
Someone tried to wipe
us out!
You're right. It
appears someone doesn't
want us down here. We're
unwelcome guests.
That means the enemy's
nearby, and watching us.
From this point on, we'll
have to proceed with
caution.
How come you stopped?
Look. That spot in the
floor is definitely a trap.
It might be a hole or it
might be a land mine.
I have to say, though,
putting it smack in the
middle of the path is a
pretty amateurish move.
I've got it. We just have
to walk along the edge
and avoid stepping on
that spot.
Wait, wait, wait! Don't
do it!
Well look at
that! Nothing happened!
I thought I'd get blown
to pieces!
You imbecile!
Because of your reckless
behavior, you might have
just killed us all!
I'm so sorry.
Well, nothing happened
this time, you were
just lucky!
Be quiet, everybody!
What's happening?
Anyone else hear that?
What are you talking
about?
The sound of water.
You mean like those
little drips you talked
about before?
No, it's bigger! It
seems more like rushing
water. I hope it's not
headed this way.
I guess that answers your
question! Run for it!!!
It must have been a
time-delay trap! It
tricked us into thinking
nothing happened, so we
had no chance to escape!
Thanks for explaining!
Now I'll feel a lot better
about things if I drown!
So is everyone all right?
Could you define 'all
right'?
Damn! What is this
place?
I don't know. It seems we
got swept along for quite
a ways, though. We could
be anywhere.
Oh, that's just great,
you're lost! I thought
you were supposed to know
your way around down here.
I know my way around some
of it! But I've never had
a chance to come this far!
This part of it is
all new to me!
So here we float.
Doesn't look to me like
we're going to accomplish
our mission.
Who cares about the
mission? We'll be lucky
if we all get out of here
alive!
I blame you. You were
supposed to be our guide
and you turn out to be
useless!
Ikkaku!
What's going on?!
Third Seat Madarame!
[awkward laughing]
That's a pretty good
joke, Ikkaku...
But not really appropriate,
you know what I mean? Don't
you agree with me, Lieutenant
Ise?
Ikkaku, hold on! I'm
coming to save you! I'll
be there in a minute!
Don't do it! Stay away!
I'm gonna try and figure
something out!
Meanwhile, you all have
to get out of here!
Ikkaku!
Third Seat Madarame!
What were we just
attacked by?
I can't believe it! This
can't be! Ikkaku went and
sacrificed himself just to
save us!
Don't worry...
A Zanpakuto and its
master have separate
bodies... but they both
share one heart.
Trust me, he's not dead.
Thanks, Hozukimaru.
Wait a minute. Do you
smell something?
What?
I do smell it. Where's
it coming from?
Who's been camping here?
Wait a minute!
It can't be!
Did somebody make
kabobs with my chickens?!
Wait. I recognize this
sake...
This bottle was stolen
from my captain!
It has the name 'Shunsui'
on it!
So what are you telling
me? That all these things are
items that the thief stole
from the barracks?
Yes, it would seem so.
Hey, come back here, you
little thief!
You're not getting away.
Hanataro!
Seventh Seat Yamada!
Help us head him off!
He's the thief!
But I... What am I
supposed to...?
I am so sorry!
Why are you apologizing,
all of a sudden?
I want to see what you
look like. Lift up your
head and show us your
face.
Wait a minute, you're---!
Do you know him, Yamada?
'Fraid not. How 'bout
you?
Stop confusing us with
inappropriate reactions!
Sorry for misleading you.
But since you brought up
the subject, I have to
admit, there's something
awfully familiar about him.
Hey, you!
Tell us what you did with
Ikkaku!
I'm... sorry!
Don't play dumb with us,
we're not buying it! Who are
you and why are you here?!
I'm sorry!
Cut it out! Can't you
say anything but I'm sorry?!
I'm really sorry!
That is enough of that!
You'd better come clean
with us, or things are
gonna get ugly for you!
Ikkaku!
What just happened?!
It's about time you
showed yourself!
That's a huge Sword
Beast! You're responsible
for this! Don't even try
to deny it!
I'm sorry!
You protect the others.
I'll take care of that
beast.
Right.
Don't worry,
Ikakku. This guy's about
to be sashimi!
Bankai!
Ryumon Hozikimaru!
Huh?! What happened?
Did I miss?!
What the hell?
Let go of me, you
overgrown octopus!
Hado Number Thirty-One!
Shakkaho!
He threw him like a rag
doll!
Seventh Seat Yamada! We
need your help! You'll
have to fight, too!
What?
You're a Soul
Reaper! What's the
matter with you?! Get
on your feet and attack
this monster with your
Zanpakuto!
Well, I would Lieutenant,
but my Zanpakuto is mainly
used for healing, and so I...
What are you saying?
I thought I wouldn't need
it for this search, so I
guess I... I kinda left
it back at the barracks.
You're kidding.
Lieutenant Ise!
What now?
How do I fight without a
weapon? This is horrible!
What do I do?!
Wait! What are you doing?!
Stop that! You're going to
cripple Ikkaku!
I don't know why this is
happening, but suddenly,
I feel great!!
What?! Hold on. I know
that Zanpakuto. Are you--?
Fill up! Vermillion
Hisagomaru!
So, from what I
understand, you're saying
the thief was
the manifested form of Seventh
Seat Yamada's Zanpakuto. Are
you absolutely sure about that?
Yes sir.
Wait! If you knew that,
then why didn't you say
so at the time?
Sorry. He looked so
different that I didn't
recognize him at first.
Hmm... I guess that's not
such an unusual story for
you, Seventh Seat Yamada.
According to Hisagomaru,
he was manifested by
Muramasa, just like all
of the other Zanpakuto.
However, he had no
complaints against his
master, and when he
realized what had
happened, he immediately
tried to return to sword
form. Despite his best efforts,
he was unable to do so.
Eventually, he got
depressed. He thought his
master had rejected him,
and he went to live like
a hermit in the
underground waterway.
That's where we found
him, and told him what
was really going on.
What?! You mean the
reason I'm not able to
return to my original
form isn't because my
master hates me?!
That's right. As you
can see, we've all been
affected.
None of us have been
able to return to our
original form.
All this time, I thought
it was something I did!
Are you all right?
Oh sure. It was just such
a relief, my body went
limp for a second!
So, did you ever find
out about those grilled
chicken kabobs?
What? Those aren't mine!
I could never kill
something, then eat it!
Then where did that
chicken come from?
They were prepared dishes
from the camp kitchen.
Your chickens are right
here!
Ah! Hanamaru! Hanae!
Hanakichi! And Hanaemon!
So why did you take the
chickens in the first
place?
After my master had rejected
me, I decided I was going to
live alone. But I was
still lonely, and I
wanted some company...
Hisagomaru...
It's all right. I can
promise you, you're not
alone.
You have me now, and I
swear to you, I'll always
be your partner!
Master!
Hisagomaru.
Hisagomaru!
Hold on a minute...
Something in all this
isn't clear to me...
Where is Hisagomaru,
the one who was at the
center of your little
drama?
Well...You see...
We kinda... got
separated.
He took one turn. We took
another, and we couldn't
find him again.
Where did everybody go?
Captain Unohana, my
Itegumo has manifested
itself, as well.
I know that.
And it refuses to be
ignored!
I see that.
Why does it only get to
appear in previews for
the next episode?
We don't have any control
over that.
It's not fair! Hisagomaru
got a whole episode!