[theme music]
[gasping]
-Zabimaru?
-How long are you
going to lie there?
-Lazy scumbag.
-We haven't seen each
other in all this time,
and that's the kind of
greeting I get from you?
Your manners certainly do
leave something to be desired.
-I'm recovered and
ready to fight again.
Now I'm just waiting for you.
It's time you did your part.
-That's right.
Now get out of that bed and get
healed so we can fight again.
I want to take on that
Zangetsu one more time.
-And this time, I guarantee--
-We're going to win.
-You idiot.
You must have been brain
damaged in that battle.
-Huh?
-He's no longer the
one I must fight.
-He's not?
Well then.
Who is it?
Who will you fight now?
[gasp]
[music playing]
-So you leave me no choice.
Before you become
too full of yourself,
I shall show you the
difference between us.
[gasp]
-The gap in power you
could never hope to bridge,
not even if you had
1,000 years of training.
-Run, Ichigo, run!
-Scatter.
-Yoruichi.
-It's been a long time, Byakuya.
-Yoruichi Shihoin.
-Do you know who that is?
I've never seen her before.
-No, but, I have heard
that name somewhere.
She's the--
-The former Commander in
charge of the Stealth Force.
And Ex-general of the 1st
Division Punishment Force.
Yoruichi Shihoin.
I haven't seen your
face in awhile.
You've been in hiding
for over 100 years.
I thought you were dead.
-Yoruichi.
You came here to rescue
me, I realize that.
I appreciate it.
But at the moment, I
need you to step aside
so I can beat this guy.
-Beat him?
You think you can beat this guy?
You are a fool.
-What?
What are you doing, Yoruichi?
-It's a drug, isn't it?
A powerful anaesthetic,
maybe goten or hoten,
forced directly into his
body to try to save him.
What do you intend to
do with him, Yoruichi?
-Ukitake.
-Don't waste your time
trying to help him.
Neither of you will
ever escape from here.
-My, just listen to you, talking
like such a big shot now,
Byakuya.
And yet, I don't
believe you've ever
beaten me, even once, at
a game of tag, have you?
-Shall we give it another try?
[music playing]
[flash step]
-Did you really think
you could escape,
with a flash step that slow?
[flash step]
-Did you really think
you could capture me,
with a flash step
that predictable?
Three days.
In three days I shall make
this boy stronger than you.
Until then, consider the fight
between you two postponed.
Feel free to give
chase if you wish,
but Yoruichi Shihoin
is not about to be
caught by the likes of you.
[flash step]
-So you're letting
them get away?
Hey!
Byakuya, where are you going?
I thought you came
to capture the Ryoka?
-I've lost interest.
Do whatever you want with them.
-Typical.
He does whatever he feels like.
-Rukia!
What's the matter?
-Once Byakuya left, the
tension drained out of her.
I can't blame her.
Hey!
Kiyone, Sentaro,
get down here, now!
-At your service, Captain.
What are your orders?
-I had a feeling you
two were following me.
How long were you there?
-We arrived just
in time to witness
you stop Captain Kuchiki
from swinging his sword,
and to hear you tell him
his behavior was dangerous,
my Captain.
-So you've been hear
right from the start.
Didn't I tell you to stay
away til this was resolved?
-Forgive me, sir.
It's just that I respect you
so much that I was compelled
to follow, in case
something happened,
and you needed my
assistance, sir!
-No way!
What are you talking
about, Sentaro?
Captain!
I'm the one with the
greatest respect for you.
In fact, I'd say I love you!
I-- Let's just say
I respect you a lot.
-What?
Why do you always have
to horn in on my action?
I respected him first.
And I respect him
way more than you.
-Huh?
Why don't you just
shut up, you moron!
-Why don't you make
me, you blockhead?
-You want to fight?
Let's go.
-Enough.
-Kiyone, we need to get medical
attention for this wounded man.
I'm afraid he's in bad shape.
-Yes, sir.
-Have Squad Force send an
advanced relief squad at once.
Sentaro, I want you
to take care of Rukia.
Carry her back to
her prison cell.
-Right.
Move it.
-No, no I can't!
I can't let you put
Rukia back in that cell.
-Get out of the way
now, booger face!
You think I want to put her
back in that damn place?
Orders are orders,
and that's that.
I'm sorry, Rukia.
But Captain Ukitake will
appeal to the top brass
on your behalf.
And we'll get you
out of there, soon.
-Huh?
-Until then, please be patient.
-What are you talking
about, Sentaro?
I'm much more concerned
about her than you are,
and I'm the one who's
going to get her out.
Now listen.
The Captain and I
will do everything
we can to see that you are
released as soon as possible.
-Ah, why do you have to copy
everything I say, you airhead?
I out to kick your
bony little butt.
-Go ahead and try.
-I would.
But I've been given
orders, and so have you!
-You shut up!
I was on my way to
Squad Four already!
-Um, um sir?
-You probably want to know why
I'm helping you, don't you?
-Yes, sir.
-It's only logical, really.
We still don't know
who killed Aizen,
and you troublemakers
are certainly
prime suspects, and an
important source of information.
Wouldn't want to kill you
until we've investigated.
There's one other reason.
Though your efforts may have
been clumsy, the fact is, you
and your friend here were trying
to save one of my officers.
Honor would never let me stand
by idly and watch you die.
[wind blowing]
[shouting]
-Sir!
No Ryoka back there either, sir!
-Very well.
This area is secure, then.
Hey there, you men go and
search the Higashi Nijo area.
And look sharp now, these
Ryoka are damn sneaky.
Thank you for reporting in.
Come to think of it though,
I've never seen the two of you
before.
Are you new here?
-Yes, sir.
We just joined up this last
term, as a matter of fact.
I'm Orihime, at
your service, sir!
-And I'm Uryu.
I'm glad we could
be of help, sir.
-Mm.
Mm.
You know, you should come over
to my place tonight, my dear.
-Huh?
-Yes, it would be
quite an honor.
At least for you, that is.
No doubt you've
heard of me before.
I'm Toshimori Umesada,
and this year I
made 15th season on
a 20 seat Squad Nine.
I'm not one to boast,
but I'm clearly
going places in my squad.
So what do you say, my dear?
I'll treat you good, and--
-At a time like this,
with Ryoka on the loose
and a wartime alert
having been issued,
I hardly think a seat Officer
would dare take the time
to be propositioning women, sir.
-Why you-- What?
How dare you lecture me
about proper conduct,
you insolent slug!
-Umesada, sir!
This sector is clear, sir.
Awaiting further orders, sir.
-Grr.
Figures.
You're lucky duty calls.
But when this is
over, I'll be back
to take your
insubordinate head off.
-Yeah, right.
Threaten away, because by
the time you come back,
I'll be long gone.
-Thank you for defending me.
-It was nothing.
I did it because
I can't stand it
when pigs like him act that way.
-But it all worked
out so perfectly.
-Well, I guess it's
true, I did kind of--
-My whole plan is working great.
Am I a genius, or what?
-You sure are.
-Are you crazy?
Steal Soul Reaper's clothes?
-Sh!
Not so loud, they'll hear us.
Anyway, it's not
stealing, it's borrowing.
Haven't you noticed, we don't
look that different from Soul
Reapers, except for the
clothes we're wearing?
So why don't we just fix that.
If everyone thinks
we're Soul Reapers,
too, just think how much easier
we'll be able to get around.
-Well, you do have a point.
-I think someone's coming!
-But how do we--
-Get ready!
When I say go, we jump.
OK?
Ready?
Go!
-Uh, sorry.
I didn't hear you say you go.
-Orihime, listen.
-Huh?
Oh, sorry.
Here are your clothes.
-No, it isn't that.
I was just-- I was
going to tell you
that I think what you did
out there just now was really
amazing.
You knocked out those two
without using your spirit
energy.
-Oh, thank you!
I learned some
karate from Tatsuki.
She told me I was
pretty good at it.
In fact, she said I was
about at the yellow belt
level, whatever that means.
-Is that what she said?
-Well, we better hurry
up and get changed.
-Ah!
Orihime, wait, wait, wait!
You can't do that!
Please put your shirt back down.
-That's right.
Sorry Uryu.
I was thinking I was
with Tatsuki again.
And I forgot boys and
girls aren't really
supposed to change clothes
in front of each other.
-That's right.
So now-
-So you use the dressing room.
Then you can have your privacy.
-Isn't it supposed to
be the other way around?
-Are you OK in there, Uryu?
Hurry up!
-I'll be right out.
-All right, then.
Those two Soul Reapers said
we should head this way
to get to the tower
where Rukia's being held.
I'm sure by now the others
all headed that way as well.
And if I know Ichigo, he's
so determined he's probably
already there.
-Hm.
Well then.
We'd better get moving, right?
You know how Ichigo always has
to rush into things all alone.
We need to there and help him,
before he screws everything up.
-Right.
So, what squad should we say
we're from if anyone asks us?
-Good question.
-We have to be ready to answer
right away, if we get stopped.
-Yeah, you're right about that.
[music playing]
-I guess that's
what happens when
you don't fight for 100 years.
You get so out of shape, that
after just a few dozen flash
steps, you're exhausted.
I can't remember
ever feeling so weak.
[deep breathing]
-Hey, Ichigo, how
are you feeling?
-Where am I?
Why did you do that?
Why was I the only
one you brought back?
I was the only one with half a
chance of surviving back there.
And now thanks to you,
Ganju and Hanataro and rukia
will be killed.
Damn you.
-Don't be so vain.
You had no chance of surviving.
None of you defeated Byakuya.
Stop thrashing around.
Do you want to open
up those wounds again?
-Why don't you go to hell?
-One person was all I could
carry and still get away
from Byakuya.
-Then why, why didn't you
take Rukia, instead of me?
-I could have.
But Rukia wouldn't have a chance
of defeating Byakuya any more
than the rest of them
back there would have.
You alone have the ability to do
that, given the right training.
So I brought you
back here with me,
in order to give
you that training.
Besides, I'm sure the others
are safe with Captain Ukitake
there.
He's Rukia's superior,
and a very decent man.
Even though Ganju's an intruder,
and Hanataro a traitor,
he wouldn't kill someone
who tried to save Rukia.
So don't worry
about them, Ichigo.
Stay here and regain
your strength.
You're no match for
Byakuya right now.
But I am going to train
you, so you will be.
And then you're going to
go back and rescue everyone
with your own hands.
How is the pain?
-It's still there, but a
lot better than before.
-We won't be able to wait
for you to heal completely.
You're just going to have to
ignore the pain, and do this.
-Fine.
What is this place?
Looks kind of familiar somehow.
-You are the very first
outsider I've ever brought here.
It is pretty
impressive, isn't it?
-Huh.
Oh well.
Time is short, right?
So let's get this
show on the road.
-Fine.
All right, then.
Let me start by
asking you a question.
I assume that by now,
you must have noticed
that your Zanpakuto is always
in it's released form, correct?
-It's released form?
That's what Kenpachi Zaraki
told me about his Zanpakuto.
I guess that's why
it's shape is so
different from other
people's swords,
and why it never
transformed, even
when I tried calling
out its name.
-Hm.
So you really didn't
know after all, did you?
Then I assume you also
didn't know that Zangetsu
can be released
to another level.
-Huh?
-Not just Zangetsu, of course.
All Zanpakuto swords have a
second level of soul release,
beyond the initial one.
That first level
is called Shikai.
The second level
is called Bankai.
Before any Soul Reaper
can become a captain,
he or she must have mastered
both of these Zanpakuto
releases.
-Both?
-That's right.
Except for one, every squad
captain of the Court Guard
has always had to
first master Bankai.
-Which one?
-Kenpachi Zaraki.
As far as I know, in all
the vast history of the Soul
Society, Kenpachi
is the only one
ever to become Captain without
first achieving Bankai.
Certainly he is the first to
attain that rank, without even
knowing the name
of the Zanpakuto.
It shows how greatly the
13 Court Guard squads
value and respect his
fighting abilities.
I'm sure you can appreciate that
more than anyone, having fought
him yourself, and
survived to tell about it.
The power difference
between levels
varies, depending on
the fighters ability
and discipline.
But, in general, it's accepted
that with a Bankai release,
a fighter's power
increases by 5 to 10 times.
-That much?
-Now do you see what
I'm talking about?
To gain this advantage,
it's not uncommon for even
a strong fighter to have
to train for over 10 years
to achieve it.
-What are you saying?
I don't have that kind of time!
-I know, I know.
Don't panic.
There is another way.
It's going to be rather
dangerous, Ichigo,
but I plan to use a completely
different method here.
You will master Bankai
in only three days.
-Three days.
[theme song]
-So Uryu, what squad shall
we say we're from anyway?
-Doe each squad have it's
own unique characteristic?
-I'm sure they do.
Like a squad that loves flowers.
Or a musical squad.
Or a squad that
tells great jokes!
-Orihime, you don't
really understand
what Soul Reapers are
all about, do you?