The Zanpakuto. Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined
by its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper and
dies with its Soul
Reaper.
That is the existence of
a Zanpakuto.
Let's have some fun!
Byakuya Kuchiki!
Scatter.
That doesn't appear to
work.
And that
doesn't either.
Yeah, go on, run! Looks
like your speed's only
good for running away!
That's laughable.
Scatter.
That's very impressive.
Captain!
Byakuya!
Rukia! Wait, it's too
dangerous out there!
Byakuya!
Outta my way!!!
You will not get past me!
Getsugatensho!
I don't want you to
bother me any further...
If I have to face you
again, I will have no
other choice, I will be
forced to take your life.
[laughing]
Take my life?! You've
got to be kidding.
Go right ahead!
Try, if you dare!
I've always wanted to
have a big sword fight
with you to the death.
You're finally onboard!
Come at me with that
spirit...
I'm ready to take you on,
Byakuya Kuchiki!
Very well. I see you
leave me no option.
[baby crying]
What the hell?
Byakuya!
Rukia! Wait!
Let go, Renji! I must
do what I can to stop
my brother!
Look out!
What is that?
Byakuya!
It's you!
Damn.
What the-?!
W-wait!
Is your only
plan to run away?!
Shucks! You dodged
that one nicely.
You couldn't dodge my
attack, so you decided
to sacrifice your arm
instead.
You get credit for quick
thinking, but you've just
given me more targets!
So! What should I
aim for this time?
I don't understand this.
Our speed should be equal,
and yet...
Are you wondering why you
can't keep up with me?
What?
You, the fastest Soul
Reaper in the Soul Society,
and I, your Zanpakuto,
are almost perfectly
equal in speed.
But--
While my attacks on you
are scoring direct hits,
your attacks keep on
missing me.
Oh dear, what will you
do now?!
Your fear is written all
over your face.
So you see, I understand
why you feel completely
hopeless.
Too bad! I wonder what
it'll take for you to
strike me!
I know you've never fought
with an adversary that's
this much smaller than you.
When two combatants are
equal in speed,
the one who is smaller,
in this case, me, always
has the advantage.
That's just common
sense.
Your biased perception is
clouding your judgment.
Just as in your
relationship with
Yoruichi.
You resent her when she's
not around, but will do
anything for her when
she is.
There is no middle ground
with you.
What would you know about
Lady Yoruichi?!
I know everything!
After all, I was your
Zanpakuto, remember?
Yoruichi's the one
holding you back! She's
the real problem here.
What's with that look on
your face?
Oh, no, I've
upset you!
Stop!
You can't quite
get me, can you?
[laughing]
Your attacks never work,
do they?
Time to deliver the
finishing blow!
You're not really
thinking you can you keep
up with my moves, are you?
Now, where should I
make the final strike?
Right...
... there! Nice
knowing you!
W-What?!
This can't be!
How--?!
I concentrated the energy
of Shunko around the Homonka
mark you aimed for.
A sword cannot penetrate
that.
I'm sorry, but I do not
rely solely on my Zanpakuto.
That is the way in
which I was trained.
To be at this level.
Damn it!
[laughing]
Huh?!
Found you! Hide
and seek time!
Oh...
I see you!
I found you again! Yay!
Let's play tag!
Hey wait!
Gotcha!
Oh!
Hey. Next time just
keep your ass out of
my battle.
Because of your interference,
Byakuya had the chance to
get away from me.
So how are you planning
on making it up to me?
Huh? Well?!
What the--??
That is my Zanpakuto.
And I will not allow you
to do whatever you please
with it.
It is my duty to
administer the punishment
to it for betraying its
master.
Damn you.
I must go.
It looks like you've
really been beaten up.
Lady Yoruichi.
What is it, Soi Fon?
Please! Not that! Stop!
Let go! I'm begging--
Why are you protesting
treatment? Your body
has been infused with
a deadly poison.
You must be treated
immediately or you'll
die.
I don't need that stuff!
I've already heard that
your treatments don't
really work!
My goodness! Who would
have told you such a
vicious lie?
Uryu! He told me!
Oh, that Quincy. I knew I
should have rebuilt him too!
That would have kept him
from spreading such
ridiculous rumors!
"Too"? Did you just say
"too"?
That means you have the
intention to rebuild me
as well!
You talk too much as
well!
I'm thinking since I'm
treating you anyway, I
could rebuild you without
an extra charge.
You should be grateful!
I should be thrilled
about being injected with
something harmful?!
Nemu!
Huh?? What?! Hey! No!
Don't! Wait!
Please, Ichigo,
calm down.
Keep him still, Nemu.
Hey!
I don't care what you do
to Ichigo, as long as
he's still able to fight
me when you're done.
Kenpachi! Don't just
sit there! Stop him,
will you?!
Why should I?
I don't care if you get
turned into a machine or
a fire-breathing monster.
As long as I can still
have fun fighting with
you.
You jerk!
You hang in there, Icchi!
Hey hold on, how come the
poison isn't affecting the
two of you?!
Oh, good question.
We held our breath and
didn't breathe in the
poison, so we're doing
a-okay!
Well that's rather
strange.
That poison is supposed to
be capable of entering your
body whether you inhale
it or not...
Well, maybe it doesn't
work on idiots.
I bet there's
another reason.
I'll bet that Captain
Zaraki's Spirit Energy
repelled the poison.
Captain Kyoraku! And
Captain Ukitake!
Sorry about showing
up so late, Ichigo.
So are you all
right, then?
Captain Kurotsuchi...
Our thanks for tending to
everyone.
Now that Squad Four's
arrived, we'll take care
of things from here on.
Great-I'm saved!
Please be quiet.
Hey! Come on! Let me go!
It isn't easy to treat
a victim of my poison, if
you are not familiar with
it.
Please rest assured.
We successfully treated
Isane and the others who
were exposed to the
poison during Ashisogijizo's
attack.
We have already analyzed
its contents.
That was unwarranted!
Next time, I'll create a poison
that even you will be unable to
analyze and treat so quickly,
Captain Unohana.
Well I have that to look
forward to.
Uh, are they having an
argument?
Captain Unohana. Did you
say that Ashisogijizo
attacked?
Yes. Before coming here,
Konjiki Ashisogijizo
infiltrated the Seireitei.
Hado Number Thirty One!
Shakkaho!
[squeaking]
Damn it! It's catching
up to us!
Momo!
I'm sorry. I think the
poison has taken effect!
I think... you must just
be over tired.
I'm glad you're
all safe--
Momo!
What's
happening?!
Rangiku!
They've been poisoned!
Isane! Damn it!!
Fortunately, Ashisogijizo
conducted its rampage
relatively close to our
Squad Four barracks.
All four of them are
being treated there now.
Thanks to our effective
treatment, their lives
aren't in danger.
After a week or so of bed
rest, they should be fully
recovered.
That's good to know.
Captain Unohana!
Lieutenant Kira was
discovered near a
collapsed building.
We found Third Seat
Madarame near the
courtyard!
And Fifth Seat
Ayasegawa in the
forest! They were
unconscious!
I understand.
In that case I will
look after the wounded
here. Please go and help
out the others.
Yes ma'am!
Say, Captain Kurotsuchi.
Your Zanpakuto. Was it
really such a wise
decision to break it?
Yes it was. It was more
important for me to
recover Ashisogijizo
to understand the secret
behind the brainwashing of
the Zanpakuto.
Wait. So earlier you
forced it to submit?
Hardly. It simply
self-destructed.
It was the same as when
that ruffian took action
and broke Wabisuke.
Then it's lost...
forever.
Enough talk! I broke
my own Zanpakuto in order
to discover vital new
information.
[chuckling]
You ask too many
questions.
You don't think losing
your own sword just to
conduct an experiment, is
too big a price to pay?
Oh, of course not!
[laughing]
It's a good thing
you're on our side.
Rukia. Are you okay?
I'm sorry that I
have you so concerned.
It's fine. Relax.
Right.
S you tried but you
couldn't stop Byakuya?
Yes.
I don't understand. Just
what exactly is he
intending to do?
Good work.
Are you heading to the
World of the Living?
Follow me.
All right then. I
guess I'll get going.
Where are you going,
Captain Zaraki?
You know where. I'm going
to go find Byakuya so we
can finish our fight.
Sounds like great fun,
Kenny!
You won't find him just
searching blindly.
Yoruichi!
Yoruichi Shihoin, you're
back?
They really did a number
on this place.
So, do you know where
I'm gonna be able to
find those rebel bastards?
I don't!
What?!
But I have discovered
where they're holding
the Head Captain.
So, do you
wanna go?
It's here.
Renji, do you know where
my broken Sodenoshirayuki
is?
Hey! Zabimaru is missing
too.
Oh, Captain Kurotsuchi
took them both. He said
he's going to repair them.
Oh, that's nice...
What?! We've gotta get
them back before he
rebuilds them!
Sodenoshirayuki!