[Izuru] Wait, did you say a
Special New Year's issue?
That's right!
It'll show the Soul
Reapers conquering their
Squads' differences to
welcome the New Year!
[cheering]
The next Seireitei bulletin
will be all about unity!
Hmm.
Right.
We'll hold a non-competitive Soul Reaper
event unlike anything they've ever seen!
And I thoughtfully decided
to put you in charge of it!
Huh? Why choose me for that!?
If you pull this off, I'll
give you a huge credit as the
chief planner of the whole
thing and a big editor byline!
Eh... Huh?
It's set, then!
Do a good job, Izuru!
Uhhh...
That's weird, I don't recall ever
saying "Yes" to taking this job.
Shuhei can be so
pushy sometimes.
Well I'm just gonna
turn it down!
[Momo]
Turn what down?
Hm!
Whoa! Hi there, Momo!!
Boy, you really
look surprised.
What's going on?
Oh! It's uh, nothing.
So what were you saying you
were going to turn down?
Um... Well,
I was just...
Is it that serious?
You can tell me!
No, actually...
What an opportunity!
Why're you turning it down?
Well I--
Having the Squads put aside their
differences and get along is a great idea!
Well, it is, but--
Shuhei has given you this important
task because he trusts you!
That must make you feel like you're
pretty important, doesn't it?
Well I don't think
that's why he picked--
Hey now don't be shy!
You can do it!
You... You think so?
Um-hm!
[Nanao] Momo! We have to go!
Oh! I'll be right there!
Gotta go now, but good
luck with everything!
[giggle]
All right then.
I'll do it!
[Izuru] All right, so to celebrate the
New Year and bring us closer together,
you'll all be flying
kites. Have fun.
Ready, and... !
[bang]
Fly kites!
This is such a
lovely idea!
Momo said she'd
be a little late.
Hope I can make this more
exciting before she gets here.
Captain, everyone else's
kites are flying so high!
But our kite isn't
doing nearly as well.
That's because you
made ours look like a
butterfly instead of
doing what I suggested,
which was to build more
of a conventional design.
Hey!
Whose kite is that?
Huh?
What exactlydo you think
you're doing, Shuhei?
Kite flying!
Is there a problem?
Well, aren't we supposed to
be the HOSTS of this event?
Don't forget this event's aim is to
have everybody get along, even us.
Hm. I guess you're right,
but it'd be really great if
you'd help make sure everyone
flying their kites has a good time.
That's what
I'm here for!
D'ooh!
[Shuhei] Whoa! It's
really getting up there.
Hey!
[Ikkaku]
Whoa! He-ey!!!
Hisagi,
you bastard!
Oh, sorry pal! I'll
untangle 'em right now.
[Ikkaku]
Aaah! You broke my kite string!
You did that on purpose,
didn't you, jerk?!
Don't be silly, it snapped because
your string was too weak.
What was that!?!
I think what you're
really trying to say here
is that Squad Eleven is weak!
Is that it?!
Hey please guys,
let's calm down!
I won't stand for that either! he insulted
Squad Eleven's pride, plain and simple!
He was just talking
about a kite!
Well if that's the case, then why don't we
see whose kite flies higher, Yours or mine!
Let's go for it.
I'm Ready when you are.
Rrrgh!
All right,
let's do this!
Right!
Wait! Hold on you two!
let's just relax!!
You said you'd help things go smoothly
but now you've started an argument!
What? I'm helping by kicking
things up a notch! Don't worry.
Check out those two!
Sentaro! Our Captain will always
be number one, isn't that right?!
He sure will be!
Huh?!
What a pain, but since
Captain Soi Fon might
yell at me I'd better
win this thing.
Huhh?!
See? I've really livened
things up around here!
This can't be happening...
[Rangiku] Out of my way!!
Coming through!
Huh?
I'm giving kite-flying
my best shot!
I felt that shot...
[Shunsui] Are you
having fun down there?
Hnh?
Captain Kyoraku!
What a nice
relaxing time.
So then the two of
you aren't competing?
We're just not like
those pushy barbarians.
Oh man, tht's
music to my ears.
[all laugh]
[Marechiyo] Watch this, Madame Butterfly!
Cat kite bumping maneuver!
[Rangiku] Hey! What're
you doing to our kite?!
For starters, I'm gonna take out the
easy-to-knock-down women's kites first!
Rrrgh!
Marechiyo! You're nothing but
a cheap shotting bully!!
No I'm smart! All women are naturally
weaker, so it's a no brainer!
[Nanao] Hado Number Thirty-One!
Shakkaho!!
Wha-aa?
[Marechiyo] Oh no! The
Captain's gonna kill me!
[Nanao] Soyouthinkwomenare
tooweak,andeasyprey.
I can't believe you're stupid
enough to say that out loud!
You'll pay for your insults!
Way to go! Do it! Blast away!
Shakkaho!
[Kiyone]
Wow! It survived that blast!
Never mess with
Squad Thirteen!
That kite's made of fireproof
materials imported
straight from America!
It's a juggernaut!
Nice going, Sentaro!
[both]
Ah ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Wait a sec, what kind of
warped thinking would
prompt someone to make
a kite like that?
[bunch of guys cheering]
Yahhh!
Huh? What the hell?!
Oh yeah!
[proud laughing]
All right ya bastards,
let's let er' rip!
This is the Squad Eleven
Captain's kite!!
This kite-flying is becoming
quite a heated contest.
[Soi Fon] No you
don't, Madarame!
Hnh?!
Your lousy kite will
be no match for mine!
You'll never beat our
"True Lady Yoruichi" kite!
No-ooo!!
Now I'll... claw your...
eyes out!
It's no use... It's gotten
completely out of control... !
[Momo]
[scream]
Hey, that voice!
Is that Momo?!
What's going on, Izuru?! Why is
everyone fighting in a kite contest?!
Get me down from
here! Help!!
How the hell did Momo
get strung up there?!
I can explain it!
Momo showed up late for the event but
was ready to join in on the fun.
That's when she became an innocent
victim in the kite battle
between the Punishment
Force and Squad Eleven.
To add to her usual bad luck,
the rope that she grabbed
was attached to the kite
and before she knew it,
she was yanked skyward,
so that's how she got up there!
Noooo!
Thank you so much
for the info.
But we've gotta find a way to get
Momo down and back on the ground!
[Toshiro]
Bankai!
Hnh?!
Hyaah!
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!!
Hey! If that's how they're gonna play,
let's zap Ikkaku's kite together!
Hado Number Fifty-Eight!
[both]
Tenran!!
I'm coming to save y!
[Momo]
Aaahhh!
Shiro!!
Yahhhh!
Uh oh! Captain?!
What just happened?
Huh? Wait,what
was that wind?
Hey over there!
Don't get distracted!
Who me?!
[Yachiru] Go, Baldy go! Go, Meow-Meow!
Do your best, you two!
Why?! Why won't anyone
just listen to me?
Raise your
head, Izuru!
Unh? Was that a joke?
Don't worry. I have a plan!
Use this secret weapon and you
can bring an end to all of this!
Uh? So! That'll do it?!
It's about time we settle this
contest once and for all!
No problem, I'll send your kite crashing
down with the next hit and we'll be done!
Haaaaaa!
[together]
Pull!
I'll stop you both myself!
I have to end this mess.
Raise your head!
Wabisuke!!
Huh!?
Unh?!
Uh??
Huwaaaaaa!
Isn't that
where...?
I sure
hope not!
Guess I m.
[Yamamoto]
Ahem!
Hnh? Yahh!
Uh...
Are you insane?!?
[Yamamoto] You ruined
my New Year's meal!
I'm going to burn
you into ashes!
[Izuru]
Yaaaagh!
[all]
Yaaaaaa!
[Shuhei]
Extra, extra!
Seireitei bulletin!
New years issue!
I'm such a loser.
Heh...
[Rukia]
Sorry to make you wait, Renji.
[Renji]
No problem. Have a seat.
So, what is it you
wanted to see me about?
Hm.
Why don't you try
having a drink first!
Uh!
Isn't that bottle from
the World of the Living?!
Ah, don't be
so uptight.
[gulp]
Ahh!
Renji!
I asked you here, because I've
been asked to perform a dance.
I bet you're having trouble
getting the steps down,
so that's why you wanted
to talk to me, right?
I've already learned the
choreography but...
Here's what you
need to know.
The Celebration Dance is a
dance that Hisana once did.
And you must perform it perfectly, so
as not to embarrass the Kuchiki Clan.
I've been told that my sister
danced it quite beautifully.
I don't think I could
ever match her level.
Uh, in that case maybe I'm not
the one you want to talk to.
Uh!
But what the hell!
Why don't you show me this
dance of yours anyway.
You want to
see me dance?!
If I don't see it, how can tell
if you're good or bad at it?
I suppose you're right.
Whaddya think?
That was pretty
strange looking.
What?!
How dare you call it "strange-looking"
after asking me to show it to you!
Getting angry's not
gonna help anything!
Didn't you think it
was strange looking?
Uh... Yeah, I guess
I thought that too.
Hey, wow, cool! That sure is
one expensive looking kimono.
Yeah, it sure is!
This piece was painstakingly
made especially
for this dance over a
long period of time!
Hm!
Well if you get
the dance right,
there's really no need to
wear something that fancy.
Huh?
Rukia, what is this?
Oh, that's a book I've been reading
on dance for beginners. So?
I've got it!
All right, c'mon Rukia,
we're going out.
No, I have to
rehearse my dance!
[Renji]
Never mind that!
[Rukia]
Wait Renji, hey!
[Renji] Don't worry!
This won't take long!
We've come with
a request!
Okay Renji, what're we
doing at Squad Eleven?
You'll see. I've decided
I want to get stronger.
Whaaaa!
Quit your pathetic
slacking off, damn it!!
Listen up,
you guys!
[moaning]
There are no holiday
breaks for fighting!
If I catch you resting, I'll kill
you and toss you in the river!
So, what are you guys
doing around here?
Come on, let's get in
on the fun, Rukia!
And why would
we do that?!
Fighting both of you?
That'll be fun!
[Kenpachi beating up
Rukia and Renji]
[Renji]
Hellooo!
So what have you got planned
to do here at Squad Ten?!
Never you mind.
Just indulge me.
Oh hi, what brings
the two of you here?
Captain Hitsugaya's
not here right now.
My! If I do say, You look especially
ravishing today, Lieutenant!
Huh?! Why're you talking
like that, Renji?
Did you come over here just to
make fun of me or something?
Why no!
Not at all!
It's just that Rukia here wants to learn
the secret of your feminine charms!
Isn't that
right, Rukia?
Uh...!
Hmm?
Wait, um! That's
not really true.
Well now, I understand, so your
femininity finally woke up huh!
It's not that! I...
Oh come on,
let's get started!
Hrrgh.
Hey wait! After all I
went through to help!
I won't put up with you
wasting my time with games!
So how did
THAT look?
[quickly]
Oh that was great.
What??
Don't say anything if you
weren't even watching me!
What exactly are you doing
on the floor, anyway?
What does it look like? I'm
practicing my New Year's calligraphy.
Why don't you go do
that at your own place!
Hey wait a minute, why
don't you give it a try?
Huh?
Doing calligraphy will calm your mind
and that'll help your concentration,
which might just
improve your dancing!
It could do that?
Maybe! It sure wouldn't
hurt you to try it!
Hm!
Okay, look I'm all done!
Great! so tell me, does
your mind feel calmer now?
It does!
Hey by the way,
what time is it?
It's about
seven o'clock.
It's seven?! It's
that late already?!
Calm down Rukia! Don't
get so freaked out!
"Calm down"?! Because of your idea I've
wasted even more of my precious time!
That's not fair! I've tried to
help you and all you can say is--
Enough!
Just go home.
[frustrated]
But Rukia, I was
just trying to--
I said, go home!
Hey, hear me out!
Whoaa!
Oof!
Heh heh!
Are you all right Rukia?
Uahh...
Yeah, I'm fine...
[gasp]
The kimono...
D'ahh! I...
Uhh... Oh no...
I- I'm so sorry, Rukia!
I'll pay whatever it costs...
This piece was painstakingly made, just for
this dance, over a long period of time!
[soft]
Augh.
I need you
to leave.
Rukia...
Just get out!!
[soft sobs]
Agh!
Master
Byakuya!
What is it?
Well, it's
about, uh...
Hm?
Unh.
Where am I?
It's been awhile Rukia.
Kaien! It's you!
I came here today to
see how you were doing.
Oh Kaien! Please help
me to understand--
Just hold it.
Don't say a word.
Right now, you're like,
"The boy at the temple gate,
a candle in the wind"!
Huh?
You know the
old proverbs:
"A cornered rat
cannot repent."
"Nothing ventured is
worth two in the bush."
"Out of sight,
can fall from trees."
Am I right?
Um, okay...
Wait! There's more of them!
Fear is greater
without consent.
In one ear and
nail the other.
Even a worm has a
god who will save it.
Don't ever forget
what I have said!!
Please don't go, Kaien! I need your advice!
What should I do?!
When you know that your
toes are tired, always
put a chili pepper in your socks!
So long!
Wha!? Wait, Kaien!!
Ahh!
Whoaa!
Kaieennnn!
[gasp]
Uhh.
A dream. Huh?
That was a really
strange dream.
Uh?
[door closes]
Brother!
Hisana wore that very kimono when she
performed at the Celebration Dance.
And you should wear it as well, when
you dance at this year's ceremony.
You mean that?
However, It's not the
kimono that matters.
What's more important, is the
attitude you have during the dance.
YouknowwhatI
meanbythat.
Therewassomeoneelse whotoldyouthesame
thingwaybeforeIdid.
Come on, let's get in
on the fun, Rukia!
You look
ravishing today!
Doing calligraphy will calm
your mind and help you focus.
Now I understand, that's why Renji
did all those things with me.
Rukia, there's still time
before the ceremony.
Use it wisely for
your practice.
And do not forget that you will be
representing the entire Kuchiki Clan.
Thank you very
much, Brother!
[Hanataro]
Hello!
Oh, why hello
Hanataro!
It's been
quite a while.
I was sent here today in order to
pay Lieutenant Abarai a visit.
Oh really? You're
here to see Renji?
Yes, is something
the matter?
No, it's just that Renji hasn't come
out of his room since yesterday.
I understand.
In that case,
Can you please
give this to him?
Sure, I'll see
he gets it.
Great. Then
I'll be going.
It's pretty rare for Renji
to get a letter sent to him.
Wonder who
it's from?
Oh!
[Rukia] "Dear Renji, On January 10th, I
will be performing the Celebration Dance."
"I'dreallylikeyouto
comeandseemeperform."
"P.S. And Renji,"
"Thank you."
[Renji] Rukia! Your dancing
has improved so much!
[Rukia] Really?! My feet were warm
and that made it easier to perform.
[Renji] I'm sure that's
thanks to my advice!
[Rukia] Kaien was right all along!
I kept a chili pepper in my socks!
[Renji]
What about my advice?
[Rukia]
Thank you so much, Kaien!