[theme music]
-You've never seen such
a fighting technique
before, have you?
It's unique because
it combines elements
of both Hakudo and Kido.
It's something I created myself.
You should feel
privileged, actually.
This technique has only
been perfected recently,
so you're the first victim of
it in actual combat conditions.
It doesn't even have a name yet.
-Wrong.
It has a name.
-What did you just say?
-It's called Shunko.
[music playing]
-The fact is I
really didn't want
to have to resort to using
this technique against you.
You better be careful, Sui-Feng,
because to tell you the truth,
even I can't control
this technique very well.
-[laughing] I guess you're
wondering why I never showed
you this technique
before, Sui-Feng.
Is that it?
I didn't want to
tell you because I
knew it was too dangerous.
-[shouting]
YORUICHI (OFFSCREEN): Stop.
You are not ready to use
this technique yet, Sui-Feng.
SUI-FENG (VOICE OVER): She-- she
used a Hanki Sosai against me.
She canceled mine
out by crushing
it the Kido of the same
quality and strength,
but with opposite spin.
And yet she did it so
quickly and effortlessly.
It shouldn't have
been so easy, not
against my Kido
speed and pressure.
Tell me why.
I should have
surpassed you by now!
I'm stronger than you!
Why are you still standing?
I should have the power by now.
A century of isolation should
have made you weaker than me.
How can you be dominating me?
It's not right.
Why are you standing
there in front of me
as if you were my master?
How can it be that you
still prevail over me!
Tell me the answer, Yoruichi!
-Look up there, Shaolin.
Do you see her?
There, the Princess
of the Shihoin Clan.
She's the one who
will someday become
the Commander of the
Punishment Force.
You will serve her, as all
of us in the Feng Clan do.
We devote everything
of ourselves to her.
-Everything?
-Everything.
That is our fate
and our obligation,
and it is now yours as well.
From this day on, you
have a new name, Sui-Feng.
You will live only
to serve that lady.
SUI-FENG (VOICE
OVER): I remember
the first time I met her.
It was like meeting a goddess.
For generations, the Feng Clan
has been a low-ranking house,
its members making their living
as executioners and assassins.
For us, strength is everything.
Any clan member who can not make
it into the Punishment Force
is cast out by the family.
-I give up!
-You should go back
to doing drudge work.
SUI-FENG (VOICE
OVER): I just knew
I wanted to become stronger,
stronger than anyone.
Force leader.
-You there.
What's your name?
-My-- my name is
Sui-Feng, Commander.
-Not bad.
SUI-FENG (VOICE OVER): From
that day on, she was my idol.
I worshipped her.
She was everything
I wanted to be.
Then seven years after I
joined the Force came the day
I was named to the Commander's
personal guard squad.
Sui-Feng reporting
for duty, Commander.
-Ah, you've already heard
about your promotion, I see.
-Yes.
And I assure you,
Commander, that am ready.
I won't hesitate to lay
down my life for you
if the occasion should--
-Oh, don't be so formal.
Stop with the "Commander" stuff.
Just address me with
something simple.
How about Miss Yoruichi?
-Commander, that's impossible!
I could never show such
disrespect for you.
So, instead of that, would
it be acceptable if I just
call you Lady Yoruichi instead?
-Ah!
How'd you get to be so uptight?
It doesn't matter.
Call me whatever you want.
I didn't have you transferred
over here for your manners.
I wanted you for your skill.
What we call each other
isn't very important.
Are you prepared to work
hard here, Sui-Feng?
-Yes!
INSTRUCTOR (VOICE OVER): You
will give your life for her,
Sui-Feng.
You live only to
serve the Commander.
SUI-FENG (VOICE OVER): Yes, sir.
I live only to
serve Lady Yoruichi.
I accepted that
without hesitation.
I was happy.
-How have you been
doing, Sui-Feng?
Are you getting used to your
role here with the Force?
-Uh, yes, Commander.
I am.
-Hmm.
What is that buzzing
sound I'm hearing?
Buzz buzz.
Buzz-- ah-ha!
Oh, I thought it was
a bee, but it was just
all those thoughts
inside of your head.
-I-- I suppose.
-And I thought we were through
with a "Commander" stuff.
-Yes.
I forgot.
-Hmm?
-Um, Lady Yoruichi, I meant.
-See?
That was easy.
Come on, follow me!
-What?
Hey, wait a minute!
-When I tell you
to come with me,
I expect you to
run, and run fast.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Hmm.
You're going to be fine.
SUI-FENG (VOICE OVER): I
was happy to serve her.
Even in the middle of battle,
I was filled with happiness.
-OK, let's pull out.
SUI-FENG (OFFSCREEN): Please
forgive me, Lady Yoruichi.
-Hmm?
-I'm here to protect you.
It's not supposed to be
the other way around.
-Hah!
We work together.
It's not about who did what.
-But I wasn't strong enough.
-Look, if I say it's
OK, then it's OK.
Do you understand?
-Yes, but Commander--
-Hmm?
-I mean, yes, I understand.
Thank you, Lady Yoruichi.
-Well, good.
-How can I protect Lady
Yoruichi when I can't even
defend myself?
I must do better!
-Sui-Feng, listen to me.
I'll teach you the
way to wield a sword.
When you're ready, you'll
step in, like this.
You're just thinking too much.
Relax Sui-Feng.
You're doing fine.
-No, I'm not.
I'm not good enough,
and I'll never be.
I don't have anywhere near
enough skill or strength
to protect you, Lady Yoruichi.
I-- I'm lacking in
every single way.
-That's enough for now.
-Lady Yoruichi?
-You know what?
You're just like I was.
I've even caught myself thinking
of you as my little sister
sometimes.
-That's such a beautiful
thing for you to tell me,
Lady, Yoruichi, but
I don't deserve it.
-That's enough of such talk.
Hey, did you notice there's
a full moon out tonight?
-Yes.
[music playing]
I swear I will always be by
your side to protect you.
You can count on it.
-So it's a promise, then?
SUI-FENG (VOICE
OVER): I was so happy.
I couldn't have guessed
was about to happen.
SUI-FENG (VOICE OVER):
It happened so suddenly.
You disappeared without a trace,
without any warning at all.
JOHN (VOICE OVER):
YORUICHI (VOICE OVER):
So it's a promise, then?
SUI-FENG (VOICE OVER):
It was such a betrayal
from a person I had
devote myself to,
someone I had worshipped
like a goddess.
You lied.
Ah!
You lied to me!
You promise me we would
always be together!
I was so hurt and angry I
came to hate and curse you!
I vowed to make myself
stronger than you
so I could catch you and
defeat you with my own hands!
I can never forgive
what you did, Yoruichi.
There could be no
forgiveness for the way
you betrayed my
trust and devotion.
Not ever!
[music playing]
Tell me why.
Help me understand.
Why didn't you take me with you?
I would have gone
anywhere with you.
You must have known that.
[sobbing] Oh, Lady Yoruichi.
YORUICHI (VOICE OVER): You
have gotten much stronger
since the last time
I saw you, Sui-Feng.
-[crying]
TETSUZAEMON
(OFFSCREEN): That was
some wild lighting
just now, wasn't it?
-Good thing we weren't holding
our swords up in the air.
We probably would have been
struck dead by it, huh?
-You idiot.
That wasn't any
ordinary lightning.
That was Kido.
It's fired at specific targets.
It doesn't just
strike random objects.
Do you mean to tell me you
still can't use Kido at all?
-Shut up!
I don't have any interest
in that Kido crap,
and I never have.
I'm not like you.
I wasn't born a
jack of all trades
with all those built-in
talents like Kido.
-As usual, you're
wrong because I
wasn't born a jack of
all trades, either.
Everybody knows that you're more
likely to be made a lieutenant
if you're well-balanced
and not limited
to excelling in just one skill.
That's why I worked hard and
became a jack of all trades,
so that I could be
made a lieutenant.
-I gotta say, it doesn't sound
like much fun, if you ask me.
-Lazy fool.
A real man always
strives to improve
and to rise through the ranks.
-Don't give me that old line.
You're really only doing it to
please your mother, aren't you?
-Shut up!
Why would I go to
all the trouble
of making lieutenant just
to please that old hag?
Huh?
Oh, no!
We're all out of sake!
-Ah!
What the hell do you mean
we're all out of sake?
We wouldn't be if
you didn't always
hog more than your share!
-Take it easy.
It's only natural that
sake should disappear.
-Don't make it sound
like it just evaporated.
It's gone because you
drank it all, you big pig.
How we'll just have to
settle this the usual way.
-Fine.
-[both] Rock, paper, scissors!
Again!
And again!
-Ha ha!
I win again!
I'll take the high ground.
-Again?
That's not fair!
-Hey, it's not my fault you
suck at rock, paper, scissors.
[explosions]
I thought I felt
something unusual.
Who do you suppose that is
fighting with Captain Kuchiki
up with at Sokyoku?
Strange spiritual pressure.
-That's Ichigo, no doubt.
-Ichigo?
-Ichigo, the Ryoka.
I fought him too, and I'd
know that spiritual pressure
anywhere.
-Ryoka?
Is that right?
Impressive.
He's that strong?
-Forget him.
It's just you and me.
-Huh?
-Take your stance and let's
settle this thing now.
-You understand what's at stake?
The loser has to
go get more sake!
-And the winner gets to
stay here and do nothing.
-Bring it on, chrome dome!
-Fine, mama's boy!
[music playing]
-I see you have
mastered the Flash Step,
but don't think it
will change anything.
It won't.
-What's all this casual
analysis of my powers?
You said talk was
useless, but now here you
are taking it easy on me.
I thought you were
going to kill me.
Didn't you say you
intended to cut me down?
You haven't even put a
scratch on me yet, Byakuya.
Does your silence mean that
this is all you've got?
Huh.
I don't believe it.
Show your Bankai, Byakuya!
Come on!
I heard what you said.
You told me you were going to
kill me first and then execute
Rukia with your own hands.
-So I did.
-I will not allow that!
I'm going to defeat
you, Byakuya.
I'm willing to risk
everything, and I'm
going to crush you until
there's nothing left.
You act as if there's some
reason it has to be this way.
You say I wouldn't understand.
Well, you got that right.
I can't even imagine
what kind of monster
would actually threaten
to murder his own sister.
But I promise you, you'll
never say such a thing
in front of Rukia again.
Release your Bankai now, or
I'll kill you where you stand,
Byakuya!
-What an empty threat.
All your boasting and bragging
will not change my mind,
and it will not change
Rukia's fate, nor your own.
You want my Bankai?
Careful what you ask for, fool.
You will die, but
it's a thousand years
too soon for you to
die by my Bankai.
Scatter.
Senbonzakura.
[music playing]
What is that light that I saw?
Is this the true power of your
Zanpakuto, Ichigo Kurosaki?
-That's right.
When I swing my sword, all
of my spiritual pressure
is absorbed by Zanpakuto.
Then it gets released again
in a super high density
beam that gives it an
incredibly amplified swing.
That's Zangetsu's power.
You know, the funny
thing is I never actually
aimed it at anything before.
Until just now, I wasn't
really sure how to fire it.
Kisuke Urahara told me, I can
only teach you the stances.
Now I finally know
what he meant.
He was telling me that there
was only one who could really
teach me how to use Zangetsu,
and that was Zangetsu himself!
-At last you are able to
fire a shot at will, Ichigo,
so I shall tell you.
The destructive
power of an attack
is a thousand times
greater when you
know its name than
when you do not.
Hear this and
remember well, Ichigo.
The name of that attack is--
-Is Getsuga Tensho.
I'll say it once more.
Attack with your Bankai now!
I'm going to destroy you
completely this time!
[theme music]
TETSUZAEMON (VOICE
OVER): All right!
Now that the fight between
the women is finally decided,
we'll show you an even better
fight between some cool guys.
IKKAKU (VOICE OVER):
Here I come, Tetsuzaemon.
TETSUZAEMON (VOICE OVER): Yeah!
IKKAKU (VOICE OVER):
Sorry to interrupt
when you were
getting all excited,
but we don't want to see your
unbearably grungy battle.
We're moving onto the next one!
TETSUZAEMON (VOICE
OVER): What did you say?