The Zanpakuto. Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined
by its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper and
dies with its Soul
Reaper.
That is the existence
of a Zanpakuto.
Hey look at that, you
guys--it's a frog!
Ooow. What's wrong
with you? That hurt!
Zip it, alright, we
don't have time to go
chasing frogs.
Yeah I got it, I was just
looking, OK?!
Listen, I only dragged
you two to the World of
the Living because I
thought you'd help me
capture those Sword
Beasts quicker. Stop
fooling around. Let's go.
Yeah, yeah, we know.
All right, what is it
you want now?
You forgetting something?
You'll probably have to
cut me loose if we're
splitting up.
You gonna behave?
Sure, no sweat. I'll
be on my best behavior.
It's close!
Let's go!
Hehe.
Now roar, Zabimaru!
Now, Roar---
That all you got?
Not by a long shot!
You're not getting
away!
He's fast, I'll give
him that much.
Yeah, but Snake is over
in that direction. He's
finished!
Damn.
Coming your way, Snake!
Hey monkey! You're
not gonna believe it! I
caught a fish the size
of-
Uhh---
Out of the way!
Damn it! What the hell
were you thinking back
there?!
It doesn't matter, he's
injured now.
He couldn't have gotten
far.
Honestly--Every time I
unchain you, it's the
same thing.
You know where this
behavior will get you.
Come on, he's
gettin' away.
Right.
What's her problem? I mean,
it's not everyday I get to be
on my own. Why can't I have a
little fun?
He's injured. In that
case, I can handle him
by myself.
Hey!
Dammit, they
found me.
So how about it?
You wanna give up?
I'm finally able to
choose my own path.
I won't give up my
freedom now!
Goin' solo, huh? Is
freedom really all it's
cracked up to be?
Damn straight. Being on
your own is great, kid.
You can roam wherever you
want, when you want.
It's a miracle
creatures like you and I
have even gotten a taste
of it!
A miracle?
Yup, that's right.
Come on, look the other
way, will you? As long
as I'm on the loose,
you get to be your own
man, right?
Once you capture me, it's
right back on the leash.
You know where this
behavior will get you.
Wait!
Damn it, he got away
again!
What's the matter, why
were you just standing
here?!
Well, umm--
Don't tell me you just
let him get away...
Just shut up, okay? I
didn't let him escape.
I'm sorry, Snake. I don't
wanna do this, but it's time.
Hold on a minute!
I've been thinking
about it, and I'm not
so sure I wanna spend all
my time on the end of
that chain anymore!
You've been a hinderance since
the moment you were let loose,
now enough is enough, you hear
me?
I'm sorry, have I
been slowing you down?
What are you chomping at
the bit for? You wanna
finish this mission and
go back to being a regular
Zanpakuto?! You've gotta be
kidding me!
I'm finally able to choose
my own path. I won't give
up my freedom now!
I'm finally able to exercise
a little free will!
I don't wanna be bound to
you anymore, I'm done!
You little-!
Leave it.
Give him a little space.
Oh man, I am so over
those two. I think
it's time for me to
strike out on my own-
Wait a minute, if
I'm on my own...
That's right! I can do
anything that pops into
my head now! All right!
Okay, what's the first
thing I wanna do as a
free snake?
I've always wanted to
stuff my face without
being told to mind my
manners!
It's a dream
come true!
What do you think
you're doing?
Can I help you?
Uh, I think
maybe you can.
For starters, why don't you
pay for that food you're
about to wolf down?
Huh? Uh, what's the big
deal? I just wanted a
snack.
Now, beat it, girl, unless
you want me to beat you!
Excuse me sir! There's
a kid back here who's
trying to eat without
paying!
Pipe down. Renji and Monkey
will have my tail in a sling
if I get in trouble here!
What's going on?
This little weirdo is
getting into the rice
balls back here.
What little weirdo?
Huh?
Big jerk. What was
her problem, anyway?
Being your own boss is
awesome!
I should have broken away
ages ago--Monkey never lets
me have fun like this. I can
do whatever I want to, now.
[stomach growling]
Excuse me. One chicken
breast, please--and some
of your eggs.
Right. One breast, and a
carton of eggs, coming
up!
Hey! Give me that chicken
leg and some eggs!
Thank you very much!
And what can I get for
you today?
Hey! Old man! I said I
wanted a chicken leg and
eggs!
For you, pretty lady?
No problem.
Hey, lady, what are you,
blind? I was here first,
what are you cutting in
line for?!
... two breasts
as well...
You got it!
What gives here? Can't
these two even see me?
But then... how was
she able to?
Oh, is that so?
[stomach growling]
Looks a little thick for
soft serve.
What is that?
Man, I don't know what I'm
lookin' at, but it looks
absolutely delicious!
Karin, are you okay?
What's wrong?
Uh. Well, it's that
kid I saw back at the
store.
Hmm? From
the store?
Yeah! The weirdo in the
goofy outfit, remember?
Goofy outfit, huh?
Hmm. Where is he?
Oh, am I the only one
who can see him?
Hey.
Oh, great, that kid again.
You're just a kid
yourself.
Shut up, I am not
a kid, okay?!
Hey Karin, who are you
talking to?
A weird little boy in a
goofy suit.
What the?! Who are you
calling weird!? And
anyway, you're more
of a kid than I am!
Hi there! Pleased to
meet you, Mister weird
little boy!
Hey! I'm over here!
Are you hungry or
something? You're
drooling all over
the place.
I'm not drooling, all
right? And it's none of
your business if I am,
anyway.
Okay, never mind, then.
Let's go, Yuzu.
Man, that girl's
a piece of work.
What? Oh, like I would
ever eat any of that!
That rice can sit there
and rot! I don't need
that jerk to give me
anything!
Hey!
What is it?
Well, I um...
thought that--
You want some more rice
balls?
What?! 'Course not!
Who'd want any of that
garbage?!
Please! I didn't even
touch the first one!
You might wanna work on
your story there, or at
least clean your face up
a bit.
Hey! Are you talking to
that boy in the goofy suit
again? Maybe he needs a little
more food in his stomach...
What for? I didn't know
ghosts even felt hunger!
Who said I was a ghost?
I'm actually a Zanpakuto.
A Zanpakuto?
Really...
Hey, I've got a
great idea, Karin.
Why doesn't the weird
little boy come stay at
our house for a while?
What's the matter?
Still worried about Snake
being on his own?
No, I know he'll
be okay.
So what is it then?
Gallivanting about,
acting like a Sword Beast
out there. It's pathetic.
You don't really
believe that.
Renji!
Ichigo!
I thought I was picking
up your Spiritual Pressure.
What are you guys doin' here?
Oh, you've probably heard
about it. Those Sword Beasts
are still on the loose...
I see you've got
Zabimaru with you.
That's weird. Isn't
she usually paired up
with that little snake kid?
He ran off. But he's
probably still in the
area somewhere.
Sorry for the wait!
Easy does it now, it's
hot, so you'd better
try to drink it slow?
Hello! I'm sitting
over here!
So my dad and my brother
aren't around the house
right now...
But if they come back
I'm gonna need you to
find a place to hide for
a bit.
I'm pretty sure Ichigo
will be able to see you,
just like I can.
Who's Ichigo?
The brother I was
mentioning.
Sounds pretty crowded to
me, are they always around?
Yeah, sure, what's
wrong with that?
Man, that's lame. I
prefer to fly solo. I
can do anything I want
on my own.
Anything except buying
lunch I guess.
And for the record,
there's nothing cool
about being on your own.
Oh, please! I'm my own
man! It's like the coolest
thing, ever!
Sure. So, um... Where
are your mother and
father, anyway?
I never had any.
Oh?
Well of course I don't!
Why would I have a mother
or father?! I'm a Zanpakuto!
Sorry... guess I
don't understand.
Here. I found some pudding
in the fridge you can have.
It's actually our brother's,
but I know how hungry you are.
I said I was over here!
Why is it always so
difficult for you to
figure out where I am?
Whoa, that was good! That
was the most delicious thing
I've ever tasted!
By the way, I don't think
you ever told us your name.
It's Zabimaru. What do
you two go by?
I'm Karin... and
my sister--
Hi, I'm Yuzu!
Got it, Karin and Yuzu.
All right! So do you
guys wanna play a board
game or something? Come
on!
Hey, yeah, still
over here!
Ah forget it, I can't do
this!
What? You're kidding
me, right?
Huh, maybe--
What the heck's the
point to all this? I
don't get it.
You know what, maybe
games and ghosts just
don't mix.
How many times do I have
to tell you, I'm not a
ghost!
So the rice cooker...
Seems to be all the rage
these days, right?
And I always have to buy
the latest and greatest,
you know? I buy everything--
You think this is more
his speed?
Seems like it.
He's so funny, we should
have popped on the TV
from the start.
Amazing.
Boy, this thing is cool,
how does it even work?
I'm home!
What ? Is everyone
sleeping in the living
room tonight?
No, please, I'm stuffed,
I can't eat anymore...
Hey...
What?
What the hell are you
doing in my living room,
kid?
Sorry, who are you?
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Substitute Soul Reaper?
Forget it. Look, I don't
what you're doing in my
house,
but Renji and the others
are worried about you.
Wait a minute, how do you
know about Renji?!
Doesn't matter, you're
his Zanpakuto, right?
They don't know where
you are right now.
Shouldn't you head back?
Buzz off, pal! It's none
of your damn business!
What's going on?
You should have never
brought me to your stupid
house! I hate you!
Hey!
Wait!
Karin!
Dammit! Everyone's
ganging up on me!
How's it going?
It's you.
I can't help but notice
you're still on your own.
How is your newfound
freedom suiting you?
Thanks to you, I was
able to buy some time and
recuperate.
Now all I have to do is
track each of you down,
one by one, and finish
you off.
That was your plan from
the beginning.
Not that it matters
though, I can handle you
alone.
Zabimaru!
Now, roar!
Sorry, were you aiming at
me?
All right, not bad.
Watch this.
You really don't wanna
underestimate me!!
What is this?!
What did I tell you?
I'm more than equipped
to deal with you, pal.
Damn you!
Zabimaru!
It's her!
Karin!
Oh don't worry too
much, your little friend
here is fine for the
moment.
But if you don't
abandon your attack, the
girl will die. Do I make
myself clear?
Dammit.
Little fool!
Well, at least you
learned how to stand on
your own two feet before
the end...
Truthfully, you should be
thanking me.
You're a stubborn one,
huh?
But no one's gonna rob
me of my freedom, I
don't care who you are.
Who the hell needs a
master to bow down to?!
Or Friends?!
You know, I actually
feel sorry for you.
Why be alone? Having
friends around you is
a privilege.
Hah, that's funny, kid.
Die!
Thanks for keeping him
busy, Snake. I think we
can handle this guy from
here. Right?
It may have taken some
time, but when all is
said and done it looks
like cutting you loose
was actually a good call.
Wouldn't you agree?
Karin!
There you are.
She's okay. She's
just had a long day.
Thanks a lot, kid.
Wait, you're going?
Do me a favor. I
don't want you telling
Karin or Yuzu anything
about me.
It's better that way.
What's wrong?
Where's Zabimaru?
What happened?
I thought you were gonna
sleep out here all night.
Ichigo, where's
Zabimaru?!
What are you talking
about?
Forget it.
Ready to go?
Yeah, I'm good.
After all, I'm a
Zanpakuto, right?
Besides, Monkey would be
heartbroken if she didn't
have me around!
Ha. Dream on,
snakeboy.
Let's go home.
Hey Yuzu, what happened
to the pudding I left in
the fridge?
Huh? W-well---
Oh, uh... I think
dad ate it.
What?! I'm gonna pound
the beard right off his
face!
K-Karin?!
Ah don't sweat it.
Dad's been wanting some
father and son time,
anyway.