[theme music]
NARRATOR: Sosuke Aizen had
entered the World of the Living
and aimed to destroy Karakura
Town's enriched spirit zone.
The Soul Reapers devised a
plan to stop his assault.
They set up a Tenkai
Kecchu around the perimeter
of Karakura Town and replaced
the entire town with a replica.
Ikkaku Madarame, Izuru
Kira, Yumichika Ayasegawa,
and Shuhei Hisagi
were dispatched
to defend the pillars.
Each of them fought
a deadly member
of Barragan's Fracciones.
Yumichika faced off against
Charlotte Chuhlhourne.
It quickly became personal,
devolving into a bizarre beauty
pageant.
Charlotte trumpeted
his own good looks,
while Yumichika claimed
he was better looking.
CHARLOTTE: A princess
always gets her way.
It may not be fair, but
that's the way things are.
-This blackness-- what is it?
-Rosa Blanca, the sentence
of the white rose.
Your enveloped in this
briar, covered with black.
This is your fate.
You will die here,
unseen by anyone,
smothered in white petals.
YUMICHIKA: Completely
unseen by anyone?
-That's right.
YUMICHIKA: No one can
see in here at all?
In that case, thank you.
-Huh?
YUMICHIKA: Tear in
frenzy, Ruri'iro Kujaku!
CHARLOTTE: [gasp]
[whimper]
What is all this?
-The final act.
The flowers are feasting
on your life force.
All the spirit
energy you radiate
is being stolen and
absorbed into these buds.
Do you understand?
The moment those
flowers bloom will
be the moment your life
ends, Charlotte, Chuhlhourne.
-No!
-Now I'll enjoy some
of your spirit energy.
Thank you very much.
CHARLOTTE: [groan]
You-- you're so sly,
hiding it all this time.
Such an incredible technique.
I guess that was your
Zanpakuto's second form,
your Bankai?
Huh?
-Not quite.
That wasn't a Bankai.
You see, my Zanpakuto's actual
name is Ruri'iro Kujako.
My sword is a little particular.
It actually has
a favorite color.
It simply adores
the color sapphire,
and it despises
the color lavender.
The name Fuji-- well, it
roughly translates to lavender.
My sword absolutely
loathes that name.
So it never fully releases
when I address is as such.
-But why?
Why would you do that?
YUMICHIKA: Among the
13 Court Guard Squads,
my Squad, Number 11, has by
far the strongest fighters.
Everyone who serves
under Captain Zaraki
is a bloodthirsty warrior
who lives to fight.
Each squad member would
prefer to die in battle.
This mindset eventually led to
an unspoken rule between us,
that our Zanpakuto would only
be the direct combat type.
Kido-type Zanpakuto are seen
as disgraceful and pathetic.
You'd be considered a
coward just for having one.
Naturally, I don't
want anyone in Squad 11
to know my sword's
abilities, especially Ikkaku
and the captain.
So now you can understand
why when you hid me
away behind that rose
bush, I thanked you.
In fact, if you hadn't
used that technique,
there's no way I could have
used this sword at all,
despite the consequences.
-Even if it meant that
you would lost to me?
-Yes, even then.
Even if it meant my life.
-Your resolve is truly stunning.
[bang]
-[shout]
What gives?
Aren't you going
to draw that sword?
-This is the only weapon I need.
-Is that so?
-I'm aware of how
dense your Hierro is.
-Oh, so you fought against
an Arrancar before, have you?
-Yeah.
So, big fella, why don't
you tell me your name?
-Why on earth would
I tell you that?
I have no need to reveal my
name to some lowly weakling who
I'm about to destroy.
-Ha.
Fine, keep it to yourself.
See if I care.
But I'm Captain Zaraki's
third seat, Ikkaku Madarame.
Personally, I think it's polite
to tell a person your name
before you kill them.
But then, that's just my style!
-Huh?
[grunting]
-I don't get it.
-Don't get what?
-Earlier I thought
you told me you
were going to battle with all
the power of a lieutenant.
But right now, I'd
peg your strength
at the level of a
fifth seat, if that.
So what's really going on?
-Exacta!
You got it.
-Hm?
I got what?
-As you just said, my
current power level
is exactly that of one
of your fifth seats.
It pleases me that
you guessed correctly,
but I should have expected
as much from lieutenant.
So, you pass.
-What?
FINDORR: That was a test.
I wanted to see whether or
not you could accurately
gauge my power level.
Because otherwise, what would
be the point of engaging you
at a more potent
lieutenant level.
It's a waste if you can't
tell the difference.
-I don't like what
you're implying.
If I take what you're
saying at face value,
it sounds like you're
claiming you could somehow
fight with the strength
of a lieutenant
if that's what you wanted to do.
-Exacta.
I was at a fifth seat's level.
But now--
-[gasp]
-Did his attack
just get stronger?
-Now I'm at a fourth seat.
Third seat.
-[grunt] Stop playing!
-We're almost at the same level.
Get ready, 'cause now,
I'm at lieutenant.
-Bakudo Number 39, Enkosen!
ABIRAMA: [laughs]
-What the--?
ABIRAMA: Finished already?
That was pathetic, Izuru Kira!
But up against my Aguila,
it's not surprising.
These aren't ordinary
wings, you know.
They're wings of steel,
heavier than boulders.
Anything in their path
will be obliterated!
-Wings of steel, you say?
-Hm.
-That's a pretty good name.
Makes 'em sound strong.
However, it doesn't change the
fact that they're still wings.
-Huh?
Another strange spell?
-Hado Number 58, Tenran!
-So you thought if
they're just wings,
then a tornado might
mess them up, huh?
You're going to have
try harder than that!
Heh.
-His speed and power
are tough to deal with.
But if I can lure him into
a narrow space-- Hado Number
31, Shakkaho!
-He's letting me
know his position?
An obvious trap.
-Your move now.
-Quit trying to confuse
me, you damn rat!
Devorar Pluma!
-Those things can
pierce cement walls?
-There you are.
Damn it.
That little pest is
hiding behind everything.
IZURU (VOICEOVER):
It doesn't look
like he's running out
of feathers, which
means they're
regenerating instantly.
They must regrow from
where he shoots them.
In which case--
-All this running around.
He's probably buying time while
he things up some kind of plan.
[laugh] Not going to happen.
-[shout]
-What?
What is that bizarre power!
-[shout]
Where'd you run
off to this time?
What's wrong?
Get your legs crushed?
Was I too fast for you?
Pathetic.
I wasn't even going
at my full speed.
IZURU: I should thank you.
-What?
-Your long range attacks
were pretty tough to handle.
In fact, this whole
time I've been
trying to figure out how to
draw you into close combat.
You see, my Zanpakuto
only works on objects
connected to my opponent.
-What the hell are
you talking about?
What do you think that
weird-looking sword of yours
can actually cut?
What?
No!
[shout]
Damn it.
What is this?
My wings can't move.
IZURU: My blade doubles the
weight of anything it hits.
A second strike doubles
the weight again,
and a third doubles
it once more.
Now you've felt the power
of my Zanpakuto Wabisuke.
Now raise your head, Wabisuke.
Moments ago, as
you attacked me, I
managed to hit your wings
a total of four times.
If you weren't just
bragging, and your wings
are really heavier
than boulders,
there's no way can fly anymore.
-You bastard!
You're fighting dirty.
A true warrior doesn't
pull tricks like that.
-Fighting dirty?
Oh, forgive me, but weren't you
the one shouting and screaming,
trying to get me to lose my
cool before the fight began?
If that's how a true warrior
is supposed to behave,
then I must not
understand the concept.
Squad Three's symbol
is the marigold,
a flower which
represents despair.
That in essence is the crux
of how my squad fights.
Battles aren't supposed
to be heroic affairs.
They're not supposed
to be fun or exciting.
To us, every battle is
filled with despair.
They are dark,
horrifying, grisly.
We should fear warfare,
avoid it always, and whenever
possible, choose
the path of peace.
Which is why I
believe my Zanpakuto,
Wabisuke upholds Squad
Three's dreams philosophy
better than any other
weapon in the Soul Society.
Every time it strikes an
enemy, he becomes heavier,
eventually collapsing
to his knees.
It's as if my blade
compels him to bow his head
and beg for forgiveness.
Wabisuke means to apologize.
-[grunt] [laughs]
-Hm?
What do you find funny?
-What the hell are
you talking about?
Despair?
Fear fighting?
Avoid battle?
I'll say to you what
you said before.
I must not understand
your concept.
[growl]
If you ask me, a battle is
all about pushing yourself,
relishing it, so you
can crush your enemy!
It's supposed to
be exhilarating!
Your feeble technique
can't break me.
In the end, I won't be the
one bowing my head in apology.
It will be you.
Devorar Pluma!
[shout]
-Huh?
[grunt]
[groan] How?
-I knew your fate was sealed
the moment my sword rendered
even one of your wings useless.
No matter how hard it
tries to take to the air,
a bird who can't
fly is easy prey.
-[groan]
-I believe you asked what
exactly this weird looking
sword of mine could cut.
Isn't that right?
-Wait.
Please, don't.
-A true warrior would never
beg someone for his life.
Farewell, warrior of the sky.
Promise me that you'll
never forgive me.
[theme music]
FINDORR: Lieutenant,
say silk 10 times fast.
SHUHEI: Silk, silk, silk, silk,
silk, silk, silk, silk, silk.
FINDORR: What do cows drink?
SHUHEI: Milk!
FINDORR: No es exacto.
The correct answer is water.
SHUHEI: Aw!