Enrage!! Ira!!!
[grunting]
Shut up!
Ulquiorra...!
Pick it up. Let's
finish this battle now.
The entity fighting you
earlier was a Hollowfied
being with no consciousness.
It was not
really me.
If we're going to
settle this fight,
I have to be in the same
condition as you, or we
won't be evenly matched.
I am fine with it. If
that is what you want,
that is what you will get.
[gasping]
So this is how it ends.
Kill me, Ichigo.
I can't
do it.
What are you saying?
I don't want to,
not like this.
It's wrong.
This is not the way I
want to defeat you!
To the very end...
you just won't do
what I want.
And just when I was
finally becoming...
...a little bit intrigued
with the way you people
behave.
So let me ask you again,
girl...
Are you afraid of me?
No, I'm not afraid.
I understand.
I see now...
In the palm of my hand...
...is a heart.
Huh!
[gasping]
Hey, do you guys feel
that? That Spiritual
Pressure... it's gone.
So does that mean
Ichigo won?
Aw, man! Right after I
got done killing all of
these guys,
I've been planning on
goin' to help out
Ulquiorra!
And then he just goes
and dies on me.
You three won't be
enough to satisfy me!
So I wasted all this
time eating, sleeping
and storing up my Spirit
energy for a real fight!
All to kill you leftover
punks! I won't even come
close to using all of my
energy!
Looks like he got bigger
again. What the hell's
going on with him?
He's definitely changed
since I fought him in the
World of the Living...
Do you see that?
Take a look at
his shoulder...
He's number ten.
So before this... did
you guys experience going
up against an Espada?
We did...
I won't ask how
it ended for you...
I didn't exactly do
so well, either.
I'm sure your fights
were equally as tough.
Nevertheless, however
we did it, we managed to
overcome all the Espadas
we faced.
And at number ten, this
guy is the weakest of
them all.
There's no reason to be
intimidated by his
size....
Let's take him out! Then
we'll go pick up Ichigo!
What was that? What are
you three mumbling about
down there?
You really think that I
can be taken out by tiny
insects like you?
That's right. I
certainly hope you're
ready for this!
Don't make me laugh.
Enrage!! Ira!!!
[grunting]
Mm!
[roaring]
Uh!
Damn! He just grew
10 times bigger!
What's happening?
His number's changing!!
There's no way!
What now?
How can this be? What
happened to his number?!
It's a zero?!
Did someone tell you that
the ten Espadas were numbered
for their strength from one
through ten?
They're not?!
Espadas are actually
numbered from zero to
nine.
I'm the only Espada
capable of changing
his number
by accumulating power
and going into full
release state!
Espada Zero! I am Yammy
Riyalgo!
Look out!
Roar! Zabimaru!!
[grunting]
Shut up!
Renji!!
Now, dance, Sodenoshirayuki!
Somenomai Tsukishiro!
[growling]
Oh no!
[grunting]
[yelling]
You stupid human!
Hah!
La Muerte!
What?!
You got him?!
Uh! Not good!
Let's face it, you
guys are garbage!
He's a monster!
What's the problem? Is
that all you've got?
Save it! The real battle
starts now!
Bankai!!
Hihio Zabimaru!
No matter how hard
you try, it's useless!
Ridiculous.
Huh?!
What's this?!
[growling]
Rukia! Chad!
Now!
Right!
Dance! Sodenoshirayuki!
Tsuginomai Hakuren!
Brazo Derecho del
Gigante.
[yelling]
[growling]
You should't
be so confident!
[roaring]
Watch out!!
[grunting]
[groaning]
[gasping]
Hm!
How can he be...
completely unharmed?!
Your pathetic efforts to
hurt me will never work!
Uh!
[gasping]
As powerful as you are,
you're still just the
third strongest?
As powerful as
I am, you say...
I don't recall showing
you the full extent of
my power just yet.
[gasping]
Bankai!
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!
So is that
all you've got?
[struggling]
Dammit!
How pitiful.
Ola Azul.
[gasping]
[struggling]
Dammit.
How pitiful.
Ola Azul.
[gasping]
Mmmm...
This can't...
be happening.
[panting]
They're not doing
so well.
Hmm...
Hmmm!
You're quite agile, my
friend. And you're very
strong, that's for sure!
I'd say the same!
You dodged my sword
attacks, and kept your
hat and composure.
You're surprising. Much
more so than I've been.
Ola Azul!
Enough!
[grunting]
[grunting and panting]
[groaning]
This battle is no
contest...
All your techniques, and
you can't even make me
budge from this spot!
Uh!
Hmph.
Now then... I wonder which
of you I should split in
half first?
Uh, Captain?
What is it?
Uh, isn't it about
time now?
Time for what?
Don't play dumb! I'm
talking about the
Gentei Kaijo!!
Come on! We've held
back long enough. It's
about time we use Gentei
Kaijo, 'cause with that
you'll blow this old
geezer away!!
What's that? Oh, really?
You have some tricks up
your sleeve, huh?
Damn right, you
old goat!
We use Gentai Kaijo, and
you'll be gone in two
seconds, get it?!
Sounds intriguing.
Go on, try it.
Hey-I don't think
we're asking for your
permission to do it!
Right, Captain?!
I can't.
Huh?!
The Spirit Restriction
Seal.
When a Soul Reaper
captain passes through the
Senkaimon, it's automatically
sealed onto our bodies.
The purpose of this
restriction is to limit
our Spirit Energy from
exerting too much
influence. That way our
immense Spirit Energy doesn't
end up affecting spirits in
the World of the Living.
The Gentei Kaijo removes
that Spirit Restriction
Seal and releases our
full Spirit Energy.
However, there are
exceptions to this.
Before passing through
the Senkaimon gate, the
automatic seal function
can be bypassed.
So, then... what's
that mean?
It means this time, we
entered the World of the
Living without getting a
Spirit Restriction Seal.
Take a look. There's no
seal anywhere on your
body, is there?
Uh?! Uh! Oh?!
There isn't
one... so...
You want Gentei Kaijo...
But you see, we are already
in an unrestricted state.
What?!! So you mean
we've been fighting at
full-strength all this
time?!
That is all we've got?!
Naah! What the hell are
we gonna do?!
So that means...
So, is that it?
This is the extent of a
Captain's strength?
It's hard to believe...
Apache and the others
were beaten by this.
I will end this here.
I will crush you.
And make sure you will
not have the will to get
up again...
You will be broken
into pieces.
Hunt. Tiburon!
Uh!
So that's her
Resurrection...
From appearances, there's
not as much of a change as
I had expected.
But taking her lightly
could lead to my death.
I must stay focused.
[gasping]
You are powerless.
Your ice dragon is
drowned by a single
strike from a shark.
Captain get outta there!
Izuru!
Continue giving
treatment.
But sir--
Listen to me. You must
trust the captain's
abilities.
Yes, sir.
You are next...
I will avenge those three
you burned.
You will suffer.
How can you still be
alive?
After your sword release
I didn't think that your
speed and range would
increase so quickly.
But I took a
few precautions.
An illusion?
Made of ice?
I can only use a move
like this once, so I held
off using it until I knew
it would have the maximum
effect on our battle.
Our strength is not...
to be underestimated.
Now I know what happened!
What is it, Izuru?
Rangiku tried to dump
some of her work on
Captain Hitsugaya once,
but didn't get any
response from him, so she
ended up doing the work
herself. I remember hearing
her complain about it.
He used that ice
illusion?
Guess it was the best way
to avoid Rangiku.