[theme music]
[music playing]
-Your the fourth?
-Ichigo Kurosaki,
it's pointless.
You cannot defeat me.
Even if you were lucky
enough to succeed,
there are three
Espada ranked above me
who are much stronger than I.
Try as many times as you like.
The results will
always be the same.
It appears that I have
grossly overestimated you.
Your development didn't
meet my expectations.
[roaring]
-A waste of time.
Oh, no!
That weapon's
about to disappear.
[roaring]
-Renji!
-Don't stand around
doing nothing!
Find some way to defeat him!
I always thought
your specialty was
finding the enemy's weak spots.
Now would be a good
time to prove it!
There must be some way to
turn this fight around!
-I do have a way
to beat these guys.
You want to try it?
-Hmm!
Sure, I'm in.
But first, I got a
little favor to ask.
See if you can manage
not to screw this up.
-Don't worry, it'll work as long
as you don't make any mistakes.
Renji.
-Hmm?
-Tell me, how many
seconds can you stall him?
-20 seconds would
be a generous guess.
I'm sorry it can't be longer.
-I understand.
That's more than enough.
Let's go!
-Everyone stay back.
No one interfere with us.
This should be
fascinating, an opportunity
to see with these two pathetic
creatures and their puny brains
are capable of in their
wretched condition.
-Ahhhh!
Uhhhhhh!
Ahhhh-- oh!
Wait a second.
That doesn't hurt at all.
That knucklehead Uryu,
going off on his own.
How can I play the
goofy comedic character
without a straight man?
Take a look at what I just did!
I fell on my butt because
I was always like this,
not because I was playing dumb.
I'm a natural comedian!
[growling]
I seemed to have fallen
into the middle of something
very strange.
I don't know what's
going on, but nobody here
looks to friendly.
Is this bad?
It isn't good.
I definitely think it's bad!
That's-- Dondochakka!
He must have come down
here with Renji, but what
the heck happened to him?
Could he have ended up
in that amusing pose
just because he got
mixed up in this battle?
Damn it!
That idiot is officially
not my friend anymore.
I'm going to cry! [sobbing]
But still, I found him.
I can't leave him
stuck in there.
Please nobody notice me.
Please!
-Did you hear a
rustling sound just now?
-Come to think of it, I did.
-It's all right, Pesche.
You can do this.
No one will notice you at all.
Huh!
Not that people don't notice me.
I have a sparkling personality.
--[together] Could it
have been a cockroach?
-Cockroach!
-Oh, no!
Those cockroaches
scare me to death.
-But you're as big as a house.
FRACCION: It doesn't
matter how big I am.
They can fly!
-Flap flap flap flap flap!
FRACCION: And their
antenna, they move!
-Twitchy twitchy.
FRACCION: And their
butts, they're all shiny.
I hate 'em!
Disgusting cockroaches!
-Be quiet!
This is not the
time for whining.
-They haven't noticed me at all.
That's kind of
disappointing when
you stop to think about it.
I'm feeling neglected.
Maybe if they
notice me a little,
I mean, just a tiny little bit.
[sigh]
-Ah!
Pesche!
-You got out by yourself!
-Wha-- wha-- wha--
where are you, Pesche?
Oh, Pesche, did you
come here to save me?
It was terrible!
-Yeah!
Shhh!
-Oh, the horror!
I was terrified.
Terrified, Pesche!
-Stupid Dondochekka,
hold down the volume.
If they discover us, they'll
squash us like cockroaches.
Be quiet!
-[sobbing]
-Shut up!
I'm telling you to shut up!
That was your last warning.
How was that, buddy boy?
Hurts a bit, doesn't it?
I'm an expert on butts.
Mine just about cracked in
half a little while ago.
If it had broken, I'd give
you one butt cheek. [laughing]
One butt cheek!
-Pesche, it might be a
good idea to try quiet.
-[together] Noooooo!
-Don't kill us!
-Nice!
Huh?
What was that?
-I was wondering what
you were planning to do.
As I expected, brute force
is your only options.
What a fool.
What do you think you're doing?
Unfortunately for you, I'm
not into this sort of thing.
-A ring of heat beyond all
of the seas in reverse.
Take steps--
-What's that?
Talking to yourself now?
Huh!
-There's no doubt there's a
big difference in strength
between you and me
with only my Shikai.
Frankly, I don't
think I have a chance
of winning the fight,
not when we're so close.
But I think
nonetheless that even
if the difference in
our powers is great
and there is no comparison
in our strength,
you're going to
find it pretty damn
painful if you get
hit point blank.
I was always lousy at Kido.
I would get scolded
for losing control
and having my spells explode.
You're pretty arrogant.
Let's find out for sure
who's tougher, you or me.
Hado 31 Shakkaho!
-Ahhhhh!
[coughing]
Damn you!
You lousy Soul Reaper!
Do you know who
you're dealing with?
Huh?
-Exactly as planned.
When Rengi attached,
you moved away from him
to maintain the
distance between you.
You don't like it when your
enemies get too close, do you?
You like to keep a
clear view, right?
If you are attacked
you, change your stance,
and you have a
habit of moving just
beyond the reach of your enemy.
Good defense, so far.
-And if I do, so what?
You seem to enjoy
creeping up on people
and attacking them when
their backs are turned.
Tell me, do you think
you've won, Quincy?
-Yes , that's
exactly what I think.
-Impossible!
Your weapons!
I thought I sealed away
all of your spirit energy.
-That just means
that there are things
in this world that you don't
know about, doesn't it?
Shall I explain your
situation in a manner that's
easier for you to understand?
Esta terminado.
It's over.
Szayelaporro grunts.
[music playing]
-Ahhhhhh!
[screaming]
-Ohhhhhhh!
-Wha-- what was that
technique you used, Uryu?
-It's called Sprenger.
It destroys everything
within the pentagram
that I drew with a combination
of the Ginto and the Seele
Schneider.
Seele Schneider has the ability
to store Reishi in its hilt.
It absorbs Reishi
that is released
by an enemy in a fight.
I can use that Reishi to
temporarily reform blades edge.
I used it to draw
a Quincy Zeichen.
Then by adding a drop of
the compressed spirit energy
from my Ginto, I can
create a giant explosion
within the pentagram.
It's powerful, but
it's difficult to use
because casting it
takes a long time.
I can't use it for
one-on-one battles,
and it can't be done without
help from someone you trust.
--[chuckling] Flatter
me all you like,
I'm not listening
to a single word.
-It's true, Renji.
I'm very grateful.
-Damn you.
-Huh?
-That bastard!
[chatter]
-Damn you.
Damn, damn damn!
-You survived our attack.
How is it possible that
you're still standing up?
-Yes, of course, I told you.
I'm one step ahead of you.
I've analyzed every
detail, every aspect
of your spiritual pressure.
Even if I've never
seen the attack before
and the technique
is new to me, it
is still your particular
spiritual Reishi.
I can disperse the impact
and reduce the damage.
Reduce the damage-- the damage--
the damage-- the damage!
Reduce the damage,
you ignorant clowns!
Reduce the damage!
[music playing]
-Ah!
-Lumina!
Lumina!
-Be quiet.
Don't make such a big fuss.
I'll create a new Lumina later.
-Yes, OK.
Is something wrong?
You both look a bit surprised.
Don't remember?
As I told you before,
I don't mean to brag,
but my eight
Fracciones are unique.
Essentially, they are living
medicine designed in order
to help me heal.
When I'm injured, I can
recover by eating one of them.
That is why they exist.
-Awful!
How could he?
-You're a monster.
-Actually, I prefer to
be called brilliant.
-Hold on!
Where are you going?
-Where am I going?
I'm going to change my clothes.
Put yourself in my
shoes for a second.
Do you expect me to fight
in this ragged attire?
-That's it!
-Hold on.
Think about it for a moment.
I have to change because you
tore my clothes to shreds
I want you to wait in this
very spot and to do so quietly.
Do your best to organize those
tiny little brains of yours.
Concentrate very hard, and see
what your inferior intellects
are capable of.
Perhaps you can find
a more viable plan.
While I'm changing,
e can be sure
that I'll be considering
the myriad grotesque
ways to kill you.
[music playing]
-Ichigo?
Ichigo?
[music playing]
-[crying]
Ichigo!
[sobbing]
Don't die, Ichigo!
Ichigo!
-Hey, kid beat it!
-It's really you, Master
Grimmjow Jaegerjaquez Espada
Number 6.
[music playing]
-I figured things
would to be like this.
-No!
Please stop it!
-Ichigo!
-You know what I
brought you here to do.
Now heal!
[music playing]
-What's the meaning of this?
-Ichigo!
Ichigo was only to protect
Nel, and he took a hit
from nasty Cero.
And it wasn't just that.
He was trying his bestest to
keep Nel from getting hurt
and took a horrible kick.
Nel was just a burden on Ichigo.
Nel only got in the way!
If Nel wasn't around,
Ichigo would be all right.
It's only because Nel's here!
These bad things
only happened to him
because he tried to save Nel.
It's all Nel's doing that
Ichigo has gone away.
You've got to save him, please!
[sobbing]
-Quiet!
If you keep on crying
like that, you'll
be picking your teeth
up off the ground.
That clear to you, kid?
-[gulp]
-You can stop all
your damn noise.
He's going to be healed, anyway.
[music playing]
ORIHIME (VOICEOVER):
There's an incredible amount
of spirit energy swirling
around Ichigo's wounds.
I can't reject it.
I don't understand.
Who wold do such a thing?
-It was Ulquiorra.
-Who did this?
-Grimmjow.
-He's got a style of fighting
that is his, and his alone.
It's very particular to
him, like a signature.
But I doubt he's aware of it.
-I see.
GRIMMJOW: When he finds
prey who catch his eye,
he stabs them in the same
spot where his own hole is.
I'm going to teach him something
about the nature of punishment
for taking someone else's prey.
[music playing]
-It's Nel and Orihime.
-Ichigo!
-Shut your mouth, girl!
If you have time to make a fuss,
then just heal him already!
-What the-- Grimmjow!
Why are you with Orihime?
-Shut up, Ichigo.
She's healing you, all right?
And when you're
completely healed,
you and I are going
one-on-one, Soul Reaper.
-It can't be true.
Is that the only reason
you want him to heal?
-Quit all your complaining.
If it wasn't for me letting you
save his life, he'd be dead.
Now get to work!
Hurry!
Ulquiorra will
catch on to what's
happening sooner or
later and come back.
And before he does-- uh!
[music playing]
[theme music]
MALE SPEAKER: Szayelaporro, I
didn't know you healed yourself
by eating those things.
SZAYELAPORRO: Care to try some?
I've prepared Fraccion in
a variety of ways, Western
Japanese, and Chinese
styles, all my favorites.
MALE SPEAKER: Yes,
yes, count me in!
I want to eat a
curry flavored one!
MALE SPEAKER: Oh,
give it a rest.