[theme music]
-Such a narrow sky.
What is that?
The sky is glowing.
-It hit the membrane.
-Yes.
And it looks like it's
being held there, somehow.
-How can it have crashed
into the membrane,
and yet not have been destroyed?
It would take a body of
unimaginable spirit power
to survive.
[grunts]
-[screaming]
-Oh!
-[grunt]
-[moan]
-We must stick together.
Because anyone
who gets separated
will be blown away
by the explosion.
[screaming]
-Grab the person closest
to you, and hold on tight.
Then don't let go,
no matter what.
-Oh, great.
-What do you mean
by that, dandelion?
-[screaming]
-I'll sit here on your shoulder.
-Sure no problem.
-[screaming]
-Uryu.
-[grunt]
-[whimper]
-What are you doing?
[screaming]
Why'd you do that?
-Oh, Chad, no!
-You'll be blown away!
Come on!
-Grab onto me!
-Orihime!
-Damn.
The intruders have
split into four.
-Which one is the strongest?
That's the one I have to find.
-Hold on to me, Uryu.
Hinagiku, Baigon, Lily.
Santen Kesshun, I reject.
-Hey, what's your problem?
-Shut up!
Stay back.
[growling] Turn to sand.
Seppa!
[explosion]
[gagging and coughing]
-Thanks to your goofy spell,
we're safe for the moment.
-How'd all this sand
get in here? [coughing]
-Your skill did this.
So shut up already.
-[growling] You know, you
got a hell of a lot of nerve,
kicking the guy who
just saved your life.
-Saved my life?
I only said we were saved.
You got that?
-Woohoo!
What luck.
-Can you believe this?
First we skip out on
our boring guard duty.
And then these two fall
right into our hands.
-(SINGING) Lucky, lucky me.
Today I'm lucky.
However, you, on the other
hand most certainly aren't.
-Yeah?
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
This hole is huge.
How is this possible?
-And there's no
one in the crater.
So that must mean that
they're still alive.
Go find them!
-Right.
Come on!
-Let's go.
-Move on.
-OK.
So what now?
[panting]
-It's coming.
Now get ready.
[explosion]
-What?
It disappeared.
Damn.
Find him.
-It looks like
I'm on my own now,
and something tells me it
just might be better this way.
-Wait.
This is all no good, Ichigo.
Can't you see?
It's not Poo-san,
it's Pee-tan, silly.
They sound alike,
but they're not.
-Uh, Orihime.
-Oh, come on now, Ichigo.
-Orihime!
Oh!
-Ow!
-Careful.
Close-quarters combat.
[giggling] Oh, hi.
It's only you.
-Are you all right, Orihime?
-Yeah.
I'm fine.
-That's good.
It appears as though we have
landed in an unpopulated area.
-How lucky!
-Careful, Orihime.
I'm afraid you may have
injured your arm in the fall.
Once I realized you were
hurt, I administered first aid
with the bandages I had.
But unfortunately, I didn't
have any painkillers with me.
-I see.
So you did this?
Uh, thank you.
You keep bandages on hand?
Look, I'm fine, you see.
-Forgive me.
I, uh, know that you
were protecting me.
If it weren't for
me, then you probably
never would have gotten hurt.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN):
You think so?
Oh, don't blame yourself.
I mean, I'm such a klutz.
I probably would have
gotten hurt, anyway.
But you already knew
that, didn't you?
Besides if you weren't there
with that first aid kid,
I could have fainted from
extreme loss of blood,
and gone into a state of
shock, and died right here.
Does that sound weird?
-No.
Let's just get going.
We made a lot of
noise when we landed.
I'm sure it won't be long
before we attract a crowd.
-Right.
-(SINGING) Who is lucky?
I am lucky.
None so lucky but me.
That's right.
I said me.
Lucky, lucky, lucky, lucky,
lucky, lucky, lucky, lucky,
lucky, lucky, lucky,
lucky, lucky me.
-Eh?
-Ugh.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
What are you doing?
-You fools!
Come on.
Couldn't you see that I
doing my lucky dance for you
both while I was waiting
for you to come crawling out
of your stinking
sand box to fight me?
And why are you two gaping at
me like a couple of idiots?
Unbelievable.
-What the hell's with him.
-Wait a minute.
-Hmm?
Oh, come on.
-Listen to me.
I'm going to make a run
for it, first chance I get.
-So now you're going to run?
What are you, some
kind of little pansy?
-These guys have too
much spirit energy
for an amateur soul
reaper like you.
Don't you understand
anything, you damn idiot?
IKKAKU (OFFSCREEN): Hey, what
are those two arguing about?
-Well, it could be
they're both scared out o
their minds to fight us.
So then, why don't we just
let them take their time
and argue about it?
But then again, if we
let them take too long
some of the other soul
reapers may show up.
And then they will
steal our glory.
Yeah, that's true.
I got it.
We'll set a time limit.
That will give me a
chance to do another one
of my pre-fight dances.
So you two can have enough
time to make your decision--
GANJU (OFFSCREEN): If you
want to fight, be my guest.
-Aw, you two have a falling out?
-Something like that.
-He really shouldn't
have run away.
Get him.
-Right.
I'm on it.
-Oh great, just as I expected.
One of them's after me.
Crap.
IKKAKU (OFFSCREEN): Hey.
-Hmm?
-So tell me, why didn't you
run away like your friend?
He obviously ran
because he sensed
that our powers are far
superior to his own.
You know, if you ask me,
I think your friend made
a pretty wise decision.
-If your power really
is greater than mine,
it would be useless to run.
You'd catch me for sure.
But if, on the other
hand, my power is greater,
then I'll just defeat
you, and be on my way.
At least that's
the way I see it.
-Is that so?
I guess you're not
stupid after all.
[roaring] (THINKING)
He dodged it.
He moves well.
-[roaring]
-(THINKING) His sheath?
-[ROARING
-[roaring]
-At least tell me your name.
-Ichigo Kurosaki.
-Ichigo, that's a good name?
-You think so?
No one's ever told
me that before.
-Yeah.
They say that guys with
Ichi in their names
are overflowing with
talent and good looks.
At least that's what I've heard.
I'm third seed
assistant adjutant,
Squad 11, Ikkaku Madarame.
Well, Ichi, what
say we be friends?
-Ain't gonna happen.
-[panting]
[music playing]
-[chuckling]
-[roaring]
[panting]
[growling]
Damn it.
This guy sure is persistent.
Come on.
Doesn't he ever get tired?
-Hah.
What beastly running.
Up in front of you.
-Turn into sand now.
Seppa.
-Hmm.
That is one unusual skill.
So that's how you made
that crater back there.
But it's a skill
that could backfire.
-Seppa.
-Look out ahead.
-[panting] [roaring]
[gasp] [wailing]
Holy smokes.
That pit is huge.
-Welcome.
This is the old
execution ground.
Long ago, we'd bring hollows
that we captured here.
We'd throw them down into that
pit to fight with criminals,
and watch the spectacle
from up there.
-So what you're saying is that
soul reapers are supremely
twisted, aren't they?
-Ah, but not as
twisted as your face.
GANJU (OFFSCREEN): I pity you.
-Pretty?
I'm flattered that even
a brute as awkward as you
can somehow recognize my
dazzling handsomeness.
-I said pity, not pretty.
-I realize that.
I've simply made a
witty, humorous joke.
Besides, that twisted
form of execution
is no longer performed here.
These days, those who fall into
this pit can never get out.
I think that's enough chasing
around and prattle for now.
It's time.
I will let to you choose.
Will you die by my sword, or
will you fall into that hole,
and die?
So which will it be?
Aw.
You're angry, I know.
Turn, and let me see your
face, no matter how it looks.
I love to witness the
agony on one's face
when forced to choose
how he's going to die.
[chuckling]
-You are a cruel
bastard, no matter
how you try to disguise it.
IKKAKU (OFFSCREEN):
I don't get it.
Sure there's some
distance between us.
But only a novice
unfamiliar with fighting
would allow a hand to leave
his sword during a match.
-Why don't you just shut
your trap, all right?
I got blood in my eyes.
So I just stopped
to wipe it away.
-Even shallow wounds above
the eye bleed profusely.
Therefore, you must
stop the bleeding.
You can't just wipe it away.
-Hey, that's not fair.
You have a special ointment
to stop your bleeding.
-It is too fair.
It's called being
prepared, you idiot.
Instead of
complaining, you should
be applauding my
professionalism.
-Eh.
-Heh.
You sure are one strange guy.
You behave like a greenhorn.
And you don't look
like much of a fighter.
But you have excellent reflexes.
-[roaring]
-And fierce attacks.
One could even say the
sum of your movements
are nearly close
to matching mine.
You shouldn't look so angry.
I'm complimenting you.
You're too good to be
dismissed as merely
a greenhorn with
natural abilities.
There's something
about the way you move.
Who is your master, Ichigo?
-Truth is, I only
trained for 10 days.
So I don't know if I can
really call him my master.
But there is a man who taught
me the skills to fight.
-Who is he?
-It's Kisuke Urahara.
IKKAKU (OFFSCREEN): I see
So he was your master.
In that case, it would
be rude to kill you
without giving it my all.
Extend Hozukimaru.
Now is not the time to
look surprised, Ichigo.
(SHOUTING) Let's go!
No mistakes.
-That's right.
-[laughing]
-A spear's reach is long.
I know that much.
I won't misread it.
-You're wrong.
-An opening.
-[roaring]
-Split apart, Hozukimaru.
-Now turn around, and face me.
I want to see the
expression on your face
in your last moments of life.
Each time I see such
things, my beauty grows.
-Maybe it's time you've
got beautiful on your owns.
-Huh?
-Wretch!
What do you see now?
Become sand now!
-Just what do you think you're
doing to one as beautiful
as me?
Help.
I'm falling!
-[chuckling] Well, what a shame.
Talk about digging
your own grave.
But I guess some
people actually do it.
-[shouting]
-How insignificant.
Huh?
Whoa!
-[laughing] Gotcha.
-What?
It's some kind of trick.
What is that sphere?
-[laughing] Goods thing I
brought a spare with me.
This is no average cannon ball.
It was originally developed
by my sister, Kukaku Shiba.
Even more importantly,
you zanpakuto
can't easily shatter it.
-Too bad.
You've underestimated me.
Just so you know,
I'm the fifth seed
of Squad 11's strongest
squad in the soul society.
And if you think that I'm
just an ordinary soul reaper,
then you're sadly mistaken.
Bloom for me, Fuji Kujaku.
Watch as I break
your Reishukaku core.
I'll shatter it
with a single blow.
What?
-Oh, yeah.
I've got some news for you.
This bomb my sister
made, it's unstable
when its concentration of
spirit power is broken.
-Huh?
-[chuckling]
[explosion]
-[roaring]
[grunting]
-Idiot.
-Heh.
Clever strategy, wasn't it.
Still, all things considered,
your one tough bastard.
-Don't even tell me
that for one minute,
you thought that was
enough to kill me off.
Now I'm really mad.
And you're going to pay.
-Hah.
Can't hear you.
Seppa.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN): Aha!
Running away again?
-You can kiss my ass.
-An ugly thought.
That's truly ugly.
-Remember I warned
you not to misread it.
Hozukimaru is not a spear.
It is a three-part pole.
Does it hurt?
You probably can't hold
a sword with that hand.
I'm a man with a
generous spirit.
Normally, I would have
taken you in alive.
But I'm afraid, in
this case I won't
receive any credit
unless I kill you.
-Fine.
-Now what?
You're not serious, are you?
-Dead serious.
-[roaring]
-Don't talk as if
our fight is over.
You still haven't
seen what I can do.
Now it's my turn, Ikkaku.
-Those are certainly some
mighty brave words, greenhorn.
[music playing]
IKKAKU (OFFSCREEN): You're
pretty good, Ichigo.
But the real battle starts now.
And it's too late to come
crying with apologies.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
Hey, that's my line.
Fight!
MALE SPEAKER
(OFFSCREEN): Hit it.
Cover it.
Rock, paper, scissors.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): No,
not that kind of battle.