Mnnnhhh.
A successful
procedure!
We did it, Karin!
My name is Franken-Ichigo.
I was on the brink of death
after battling Hollows.
But I have been rebuilt,
and brought back to life!
I wandered about aimlessly
for hours, and as I emerged
from within the dark forest,
a castle appeared before me.
Huh? What is this place?
Hm? Huh?
What's going on here?
[sigh] Not again.
[Rukia]
Ichigo!
Huh?
Oh! Rukiruki!
Who?
One night, I had a dream.
I awoke in a desert to
find I had become an
Arabian thief and--
Uhh, It's not
important.
All you really need to know is,
this whole thing's a dream.
So you think you're in the
middle of a daydream?
That's what you're saying?
I don't see why you're
even bringing that up.
What difference does it
make, when I'm already
inside a dream?!
Ouch! What the hell
are you doing?!
That really hurt!
You're not dreaming!
It was time for our
scheduled meeting,
but as usual, you
didn't show up!
So I had to come
and get you!
What meeting?
You dummy!
G'ahh!
All right then,
let's see if you can
forget about this!
Ut! Agh! Egh!
Hey, cut that out!
Move it! We're going
back to the castle!
All right, I'm going!
So you can stop
poking me, Rukiruki!
It's not Rukiruki!
I'm Rukia!
Now speed it up!
That thing's really sharp,
in case you didn't know!
Sorry we're late.
[frustrated sigh]
Huh?
[Ichigo]
Rangiku... Toshiro... Uryu...
Orihime... and, who are you?
Relax. Relax.
This is nothing
but a stupid dream.
What are you mumbling
to yourself about?
Hurry up and
take your seat!
Yeah, whatever.
[slurrrp]
Hey Uryu, What
in the world are
you drinking?
Have you gone blind?
It's a bottle of milk!
Shouldn't you be
drinking blood
or something?
You're supposed to
be Dracula, right?
What do you mean? Blood is
the same color as a Soul
Reaper's Spirit Ribbon,
I would never drink that!
That makes sense,
but why drink milk?
Augh!
As you can see, I'm both
Dracula and a Quincy! It's
only natural that I take
pride in the color white...
[dizzy]
Nnh...
Hey, what's wrong, Uryu?
The truth is, I'm a
little anemic because
I can't drink blood.
Try not to get me so
worked up, willya?
You're an idiot,
you know that?
[Rangiku]
Take it easy!
It happens all
the time, right?
Yeah!
Huh?
[Ichigo]
So Rangiku is a witch.
And Orihime is
a-- well, what is
she, a pumpkin?
A pumpkin ghost?
Ha ha ha! You're all
patched together!
You look really weird!
Geh!
Come on, I don't look
as weird as you!
Ignore him, Orihime.
The fact is, he's been
acting extremely strange
since I brought him here.
There's nothing
wrong with me.
And by the way, what
kind of monster are you
supposed to be, Rukia?
S'cuse me?
You can't tell?
I happen to be a succubus.
Huh? What the
heck's a succubus?
[Uryu] [still weak]
Allow me to explain.
Huh?
Hm?
They're dream demons.
The kind of demons
that ruin men.
They appear as lovely
women, with bat wings
on their backs.
In many cases, they target
men ahead of time, and
attack them in their sleep.
Once the men have no
way to escape, they
proceed to seduce them.
And then they go and
suck out their life energy.
Ungh!
Hey, Rukia.
Come to think of it, you
are a succubus and you've
been jabbing at me with
your fork the whole time.
What's the deal?
Forget it! I've known
you a long time.
Why would I seduce you?
I only use my skills
on certain people.
They have to be both
noble and beautiful
to get my attention!
For example, someone
like my older brother.
Hmpf...
[Renji]
Oh will you stop already?
You're making my ears bleed.
Hm?
Mmh.
That voice.
Is that you in
there, Renji?
I didn't recognize you
inside that mummy outfit.
Wrong.
Eh?
I'm not a mummy.
I'm a pirate.
Huh?
Once upon a time not that
long ago, I was a pirate
who sailed the Seven Seas!
Back then, I was afraid
of nothing. I believed
the world was my oyster.
But I was constantly
being harassed by
my arch-enemies,
Team Seaweed!
Let's get 'em, boys!
Pine!!
Seaweed Zone Defense!
Seaweed! Seaweed!
A fierce firefight broke
out between our two ships,
until finally...
Now that you're at my mercy,
shall I tell you the
difference between you and I?
It's class!
Ungh.
I carry the wounds on my
body from that day, and
that's why I look like this!
Hold on.
So you're telling me that
you're not a monster?
And what's Team Seaweed?
I've never heard of it!
[Toshiro]
I hate to interrupt...
but aren't we all gathered
here to have a meeting?
A meeting? What are you
talking about, Toshiro?
My name's not Toshiro!
It's Wolfman Hitsugaya!
Egh.
And the bottom line is,
we couldn't start on
time because you didn't
show up, as usual!
Don't get so upset.
It's all right,
Captain.
I mean, we haven't all
introduced ourselves yet.
And anyway, the meeting's
only about the hunters,
isn't that right?
What hunters?
[grumble]
It's no big
deal, really.
We just have to find a
way to get rid of them
as quickly as possible!
[growl]
Try not to get so
stressed out, Captain!
Otherwise, your fur will
start falling out again!
Rangiku!
Hey, don't shoot
the messenger!
Here, why don't we
use this to ease
your stress! Fetch!
[barks and yips]
[sigh]
[panting]
Wow! Good dog,
Captain, good dog!
Stop it!
I'm not a dog!
Shake? Come on!
Woof.
Good job!
Attaboy!
Weren't you listening?!
I'm not a dog!
Here you go!
Once more...
Fetch!
Ruff!
So. What is this
meeting regarding the
hunters all about?
If you insist, I suppose
I'll have to explain it.
We're back to you again?!
Recently,
we received word,
that mysterious monster
hunters have been spotted,
prowling through this area.
It appears the two of them are
not here to kill monsters, but
are instead, looking for a
certain secret treasure.
Treasure?
Yes. And the secret treasure
they're looking for is...
priceless.
It's a legendary jewel that
will force us monsters to
return to our original
forms as human beings!
It's called the
'Snow Crystal'!
Wait just a minute!
I know that shape.
I recognize it! Yeah!
Anyway, long story short.
They plan to use the Snow
Crystal to cleanse the world
of every last monster.
That's their
ultimate objective.
Question! Where would
a person look for this
'whatever-you-call-it'
crystal?
Here.
It is kept under lock and key on
the top floor of this castle.
So if we use that on
ourselves, We'll all
turn back into human
beings, right?
Yes, that is correct.
And that is why we must
protect the Snow Crystal
from falling into the
wrong hands, at all coss.
Hm?
Hold on, there!
Just where are you
going, Ichigo?
To the top floor,
if you must know.
Egh! You're not
planning to steal
the jewel, are you?
Damn right, I am!
I'm gonna use that jewel
to turn myself back
into a human being!
At that point, I should be able
to wake up from this dream!
What kind of stupid plan have
you got up your sleeve?!
Come to your senses,
will you?!
Nngh... Blood...
Need more blood...
Once you wake up from
this dream, your anemia
will be gone, too!
See ya!
We have a situation, everyone!
Hm?
Huh?
Just look outside!
Something's coming!
Who's that?
It's my Dad!
It's Ryuken!
Huh?
Hey Dad!
Ryuken!
Sorry Ichigo.
It's only polite,
go first.
There's no need to be polite,
Uryu! You go ahead and talk,
if you're ready!
Grr! Well all right,
fine then!
[clears throat]
Ahem!
Hey, Ryuken!
Calling your father
by his first name.
You haven't changed at all.
That's not important.
Why do you have the
powers of a monster hunter?
Why are you asking such
a foolish question?
Really?
Just accept the fact.
The truth of the matter is,
whether you like it or not,
I am the only man who is
allowed to call himself,
the last Monster Hunter.
Excuse me, but I'm
a Hunter, as well!
Then how 'bout getting out
there and doing your job?!
Hey, hey, take
it easyyyyyo~!
Now then, prepare
yourself, Uryu!
You leave me no choice
but to fight you!
Rukia. Orihime. Momo.
You three return to the castle
and protect the crystal!
[all 3]
Right!
The rest of us will make a stand
and stop them here.
Wait a minute.
Where's Ichigo?
Ah!
[all in unison]
Oh crap! He's going after
the crystal himself!
[Ichigo]
Heh ha ha ha ha!
Yeah, right, Like I'm gonna
waste my time fighting hunters!
I'm gonna go in there, get
the Snow Crystal, and wake
up from this stupid dream!
Huh?
Dad!
Son! This is it.
I won't allow you to lay a
hand on the Snow Crystal.
Huhh?
Wait a minute!
What the hell?
I thought you came here to
steal the Snow Crystal,
not protect it!
Ha ha ha ha!
Don't sweat the
details, kid.
Well just forget it!
The Snow Crystal is
mine, Dad!
And you can't stop me from
waking up back in reality!
Raaaaa!
Yaaaaah!
This is a useless
exercise, Uryu!
I know you don't have
the energy to shoot a
full volley of arrows!
Damn it all! I knew I should
have started drinking blood!
And there's one more thing.
You probably think the
maximum number of Spirit
Arrows I can shoot in a
volley is 1200, don't you?
Actually,
It's twelve hundred...
...and one!
What?!
Yee!
[Renji]
Extend, Zabitai!
Hm?
Got it!
Let me help you
out a bit, Uryu.
Dgh.
Damn! All I really want to do
is wake up from this dream!
Tell me something, Dad.
Why do I have to fight you?!
Ah ha ha ha!
Oh, come on, Ichigo!
Isn't it obvious, yet?
As the saying goes: The Lion,
the King of Beasts, shoves its
cubs off the highest cliff to
test their worthiness!
Now then, Ichigo, Crawl
back up and prove that
you can surpass me!
Why the hell are you spouting
all this nonsense. dad?
You want me to fight you so
I can prove I can fight?!
[Toshiro]
We finally found you, Ichigo!
You bastard! How could
you betray us like this?!
You were planning to snatch
the crystal for yourself this
whole time, weren't you?!
Uhh!
Wait, you've got it all wrong!
I mean, just look!
You see this hunter?!
I'm in the middle of
fighting him now!
Huh?
You're having...
a family squabble?
Yaaaahhh!
Yaahhhhh!
Renji! Uryu!
I have to say, when
it comes down to it,
you guys are all talk
and no substance!
Egh!
Damn it! We can't defend
ourselves against him!
If you absolutely
refuse to tell me where
the crystal is, then
you leave me no choice.
I'll have to get
rid of you first.
After that, I'll just
find it on my own.
Come on, Uryu!
Isn't there
anything we can do?
There is!
Huh?
Hey! What's going on?!
What the hell is this?!
Hikotsu... Houtai!
Huh?
Huuagh!
Hey, what's the big idea!
Stop it!
Panpuru! Pinpuru!
Hainek, kon!
Waaagh!
[coughing]
Ban...kai!
Daiurufu Hyorinmaru!
Ha!
Huaaghh!!
I anticipated
this situation.
So I placed Sprenger
inside the courtyard
in case I needed it.
Looks like it paid off.
It's over, Monster Hunters.
And as for you, Ichigo, your
noble sacrifice allowed us to
earn a great victory today.
Rest in peace, my friend.
[gasp]
Huh?
Huhh?
[Hollow groan]
[choked gasps]
Ichigo!
Are you all right?
Man, that was close!
If I hadn't been wearing
my mask, I would have been
wiped out, right along
with those other two guys!
Hey, Uryu, what was up
with that land mine?!
Are you nuts?!
What do you mean?
I carefully
explained it all at
today's meeting.
You have yourself to
blame for missing it.
What? I couldn't
help it!
'Course not!
I'm sure you'd lose
your head if it wasn't
sewn onto your body!
You know what?
You may be
right about that!
[laughing]
[Isshin & Ryuken]
Very funny, but
the joke is over!
Huh?
What the--?!
...Hell?
[faints]
Now you kids have
really done it!
You little bastards!
[in unison]
You won't get away with this!
[all screaming]
Yeeahhahhhhhh!
Raaaahhh!!
[Orihime]
Pumpkin... Pumpkin...
Pumpkin... Pumpkin!
What do you think, Orihime?
Will this do the job for now?
Oh yes. The barrier
has become much,
much stronger.
Huh?
[panting]
[panting and barking]
[Renji]
What are we gonna do?!
There's nowhere else to run!
[Ichigo]
Damn! We'll have to
fight them again!
[Rangiku]
Fight? Did you already
forget that we didn't stand
a chance back there?
[Uryu]
We don't have a choice!
It's just not worth
risking everyone's lives.
It sucks, but
we'll have to hand
over the crystal.
Mmm.
Urgh!
Orihime! Where's the
crystal right now?
Hm? Right over there,
of course.
Okay!
What?
[Renji]
Hey, Ichigo!
It's no use!
I can't hold them
back any longer!
Hwaaah!
That's it, then!
This is as far as
you go, you
pathetic monsters!
[fright squeal]
Eyaaahh!
Okay, spill it!
Where have you guys
hidden the crystal?
Hmph! Someone's
a petty thief!
Which one of you is it?
I'll tell you,
it wasn't me!
I would never pull
such a trick!
I didn't do it!
It wasn't
me, either!
Or me, honest!
Hmph.
Looks like you
have your answer.
Nobody knows about this crystal.
Maybe the thing never
existed to begin with!
That ridiculous!
You don't know if
it's true or not!
And I'm warning you
now, These people
here are my friends!
I'll protect them
against any attack!
You fool! You think you're
actually able to defeat us?
It's no longer a matter
of whether I think I
can defeat you.
The bottom line is, I can
no longer allow you to
hurt any of my friends.
That means I have to defeat you!
Great, Ichigo.
I see you're reckless as always.
Uryu!
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm not doing this to try
and help you.
This is my fight, too,
and I'm not gonna run away.
That's a good enough
reason to join forces.
Ready to show 'em
what we've got?
Hm.
Let's do it!
[both attack growl]
Huaaaahhh!
What is this?!
Huh! I can see now that
beating scum like you
isn't going to make us
very much money!
So... That's the way it goes!
Huh?! What does that mean?!
See ya!
Where are
you going?!
[all others]
Hey! We won! Yeah!
Huh?
[Ryuken]
Friends, huh? That foolish boy
never learns from his mistakes.
[Isshin]
Ah, stop being so hard on him.
At least you got to see how much
your precious son has matured.
Yeah. If you say so.
You're too much!
You won't admit
you're proud of him!
Hey! Wait for me!
[relieved sigh]
What the hell was
that all about?
Yeah, really.
And we still
don't know where
the crystal is!
Hmm.
Right! And without it,
I can't go back!
Go back to what?
Finally, I'm out! Hey!
Rukia!
Wait a minute,
did you hide
the crystal?
What are you talking about?
Don't you understand it yet?
A succubus is a demon
who shows you dreams.
In other words, my young friend,
I am the Snow Crystal!
I don't understand.
And besides,
I hate to
inform you,
this doesn't even happen
to be your dream!
Then whose is it?
Ow!
What did you do that for!
GYAHHHHH!
[gasps]
Ichigo!
What's going on?!
Fur?!
[Rukia]
Farewell, Ichigo!
Raaaghh!
Beast!!
What a dream!
Wow. That was really scary.
Oh! It was me.
Heh heh...
[Isshin]
Good episode to celebrate
our 10-year anniversary.
Our sons have matured.
[Ryuken]
I'm not so sure.
I wore this outfit,
thinking it was my son's design.
But I must have been
mistaken, or else he hasn't
improved his skills.
It doesn't look
right at all!
[Isshin]
Oh. I designed that.
[Ryuken]
I have to go change.