[theme music]
-What are you trying
to do, poison us?
This crap wouldn't
pass for dog food!
-I only bring what
they tell me to, sir.
-We're the patients here.
Bring us some better food.
-Yeah!
-What's with all the noise?
What's up?
-Squad 11 agian.
-Now it's the food
they don't like.
-Huh?
-You maggots don't know
who you're dealing with.
-Do you men have some
complaints about the way
you're being treated?
-Ah!
-Sorry about that.
-Oh, hello there, captain.
-We didn't realize you
were standing right there.
-Obviously you're feeling
better if you're up and able
to criticize.
Just the same, you would
do well to remember
that you are in my
care now, and that I
am in charge of everything
that goes on here.
As such, well you
ar eunder this roof,
the members of my squad four
have your lives completely
in their hands.
-Sorry!
We're sorry!
-It won't happen again!
-Wow.
I wonder why they're acting
as if I'm some kind of ghost.
Huh?
-Urgh!
-Just like that.
All right, who's next?
-Uh--
-Aw, come on!
Don't tell me not one
of you has the nerve!
-Well, in that case, I'll take
you on, if no one else will,
Ikkaku.
-Ichigo.
Well, you've got guts,
I'll give you that.
But can you handle it?
Aren't you still in recovery?
-Both of us had
serious injuries.
When you say recovery, it
sounds like I have some disease.
-Recovery just means
getting over something.
You could use it for
either, you simpleton.
-Cannot!
-OK, if it's not recovery,
then what word do you use?
-Well, I'd use--
look, I don't now!
-Ha!
I knew it!
You're all brawn and
no brain, Ichigo.
-Me?
Nothing goes into
your bald, shiny head.
It just bounces off!
-Ha!
Let's fight, and the
winner is the smarter one!
-You got it, Ikkaku!
There's nothing I
can't beat you at!
-Hey.
Eh?
-Good morning, captain, sir.
-Huh?
What are you doing, Ichigo?
-Ichi!
How are you?
KENPACHI (OFFSCREEN):
Have your wounds healed?
-Well, yeah.
And in fact, I was
just about to-- eh?
-I see.
That is good news,
because it means you
and I can fight again!
-Whoa!
-Heh, heh, heh.
Huh?
Hey, that's the wrong guy.
-I'm never fighting
you again, you--
-Kenny, look!
He's getting away!
-Hey, Ichigo!
Come back here and fight me!
-Such a commotion.
Those guys need to
relax, if you ask me.
-At least with Ichigo in squad
11, things are never boring.
-True.
Now that you mention it, you've
been around a lot lately, too.
What happened to
Captain Komamura?
-Well, I wish I knew.
Lately it seems like the captain
just wants to be left alone.
-Friend of Kaname Tosen.
You whose name I do not know.
What would you have done?
What would you have
said to stop him?
-Wha--?
Captain Komamura.
Do you think he'll come back?
Or is Captain Tosen
gone for good?
-He'll be back.
But we must find a way to
open his eyes to the truth.
-I wouldn't have minded being
your captive be little longer.
So long, Rangiku.
Maybe next time.
-That's the thing I
hate most about you.
So stupid.
-Talking about yourself?
-Ah!
Don't sneak up on me like that.
You scared me so bad I
almost popped out of my robe.
-What if you had?
-Then I'd have been exposed.
-Which I doubt would bother you.
Anyway, you have a guest.
-Hm?
Izuru.
-I need to talk to you.
-Hm.
I have some sweet buns here.
Help yourself.
And sake, of course!
-Huh?
-No.
No more, Rangiku.
-No wimping out!
-Rangiku, back there
I was a little--
-Forget it.
-I just wanted to
say I was sorry.
-Don't worry.
It's OK.
-Yeah?
-Though it's true you came
at me with full force.
Didn't you?
And to think you
thought you hurt me
when you barely
laid a hit on me!
But don't feel bad.
The fact that you came to
visit, that makes it all right.
Really.
-Yeah?
-Sitting down face to face
and talking about things
might not solve everything,
but if we don't do it,
we'll never understand
each other at all.
You know what I mean?
-I think so.
I guess you're right,
as usual, Rangiku.
-Captain?
Before you go, could you talked
to her for a few moments?
She's waiting.
She's waiting for someone
who's closer to her
than I am to sit and talk to
her, just for a little while.
-Unfortunately, right
now I don't have anything
to say to her.
-Right now?
-If you'll excuse me.
-Finally finished.
Since we can't go back to the
world of the living dressed
like soul reapers, I've made
new clothes for all of us.
Pretty nice, huh?
-Yeah, but it's sort
of different, isn't it?
You changed something.
URYU (OFFSCREEN): Yeah.
It's better, huh?
As for you, Orihime,
I couldn't duplicate
the design your old
shirt had, so instead I
did this one with some
lace down one side,
then sewed these flowers
here at the bottom.
What do you think?
-Uh, yeah.
Cute.
-I'm glad you like it.
I also made this one for Rukia.
I made it kind of
like the one she
was wearing when she came
to our world the first time.
-Yeah, this is great!
Whoa.
-You're, uh, better at making
clothes for girls than guys,
aren't you, Uryu?
-What?
-Hey, I know.
I'm gonna take Rukia her dress
and show it to her right now.
-Uh-- so, what do you say, Chad?
Why don't you try that
on and see how it fits?
[giggling]
-Uryu's not a bad designer.
I think Rukia's really
going to like this.
She's been so depressed lately.
But now, when she sees
this, it'll cheer her up.
It's strange Uryu made
something so pretty for Rukia.
I wonder why he went
to so much trouble.
This can only mean that Urye
is secretly in love with Rukia.
It's cool that I
noticed it, though.
Only 15 years old and
already, my female intuition
is razor sharp!
Rukia!
I have something for you!
Rukia?
-Man, my feet are killing me.
That crazy Kenpachi
must've chased me
for hours trying
to fight me again.
That guy is totally insane.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): Ichigo!
-Orihime?
What are you doing Here And
what's with those clothes?
-There's something wrong.
I can't find Rukia.
-Huh?
-Renji.
Why are you here?
-I'm here because
you're my captain.
-You probably wish I were dead.
I imagine that's what
you're thinking now.
-No, you're wrong.
If you were to die, then
what motivation would
I have to get stronger?
And in fact, captain--
[footsteps]
-Renji!
-What the hell?
How dare you charge
in here like that.
I was just about ready to
say something really cool,
and you totally
ruined the moment!
-Sorry.
How was I supposed to know?
Hey have you seen Rukia
around anywhere lately?
-What?
You better not have
lost Rukia again.
-No.
No.
I just thought you might
know where she was.
-What's going on, Ichigo?
So, what did you find out?
-How did you get
all the way up here?
No way.
Sorry to barge in
on you, Byakuya.
Later, Renji.
-We'll be going, now.
-Wonder what the hell
those two are up to.
-What is it?
Is something wrong, sir?
-Just that-- well,
I certainly hope
this Ichigo doesn't
intend to keep
calling me by my first name.
I find his lack of
respect disturbing.
-Huh?
-Where are we going, Ichigo?
Did Renji give you some idea
where to look for Rukia?
-Well, sort of.
If she's not with
Renji, then there's
only one other place to look.
-Ow!
Stop it, Kukaku!
I can't take it!
-Quit your whining and
give me 1,000 more!
- --cracked my spine!
Come on!
How about I give
you 50 of them now,
and the rest of them later?
Hah!
Still got injuries from
fighting so heroically before.
-Hah!
That's not exactly what I heard.
I heard you were nowhere
near the front lines,
and in fact, you
were practically
useless the whole second
half of the fight.
-What?
Lies!
Who told you that?
-Now I'm going to make you sorry
that you came back and lied.
You shame the Shiba name!
-Ah!
-Huh?
Yeah?
What do you want?
-Hm?
Oh, Rukia!
It's her, Kukaku!
It's the person this
whole thing was all about.
She's the one Ichigo came here
and risked his life to save!
-I know who she is.
Rukia Kuchiki, the soul reaper
who killed our brother Kaien.
I know who you are.
Now, what did you come here for?
-I'm sorry.
-I know who you are.
Now, what did you come here for?
-I'm sorry.
I-- I know I should
have come sooner.
I wanted to, but I was a coward.
I should've apologized to
you the first chance I got.
The longer I waited, the
harder it seemed to become,
until I ran.
I ran and I'm sorry.
-Stop.
That's enough.
What is this?
The world's longest apology?
-I'm, um-- I'm so sorry-- oh!
-Enough, I said!
-Oh!
I, um, uh--
-It's all right.
I mean it.
Anyway, I already heard the
whole story from Ukitake.
I know that Kaien's
death wasn't your fault.
And I know that
ever since that day,
you've been carrying more than
your share of guilt over it.
So long ago I
decided in my heart
that if you said just
one word of apology,
I would forgive you.
-(THINKING) Of course.
She knew Kaien,
better than anyone.
She knows what he
would have wanted.
All this time I was
only thinking of myself,
when she's the one
who was hurt the most
by the loss of her brother.
Thank you.
I'm just so sorry I--
-Enough apologizing.
-Um, OK.
I'm sorry-- Wait.
I mean, thank you.
-Ah-ha.
I thought I'd find you here.
-Ichigo?
Orihime?
-Sorry to interrupt
your little chat,
but right now we should
probably head back
and try to get some
rest before tomorrow.
In the morning they're
going to open a gate for us
to return to our world.
And you're still not
back to full health.
-I have to tell you something.
It's only right that you
be the first to know.
-Uh-huh?
-I've decided, Ichigo, to
stay here in the Soul Society.
-Well, that's fine.
Good for you.
-Huh?
-Well, it sounds like
you've made up your mind,
so there's not much else to say.
If you've decided that
you want to stay here,
then that's what you should do.
(THINKING) Looking at her
now, I remember exactly why
I wanted to save her
in the first place.
-Hmph!
Ichigo, you finally
showed up, huh?
-Well, I, uh-- I mean--
-Hello again, Kukaku.
-So you're checking out and
leaving in the morning, huh?
Then stay and have
dinner with us tonight!
-Well, thanks.
I would, but I don't
know if I can--
-Not this again.
The correct answer is yes,
I'd love to stay for dinner.
-You know, I was thinking
dinner tonight would be great.
Thank you.
-No, no, that was great.
-Hey!
Rukia!
Where the hell
could she have gone?
-Orihime!
Orihime, where'd
you disappear to?
-Ichigo!
Come out and fight
me, you bastard!
-Too much free time
on their hands.
-What happened here?
-No, no more sake.
-That was close.
I almost died!
-How?
What happened?
-I can't breathe if I lie
face down because of my boobs!
Don't you know what
the feels like?
-I don't.
-Well, you should
have more sympathy.
It's not easy being a
girl and being beautiful.
-Oh, shut up.
-This is the official
Senkaimon for your departure
from the Soul Society.
It incorporates a
reishi [inaudible]
made specifically for you.
Ichigo.
-Yeah?
-This is for you.
-Hm?
What's this thing?
-A substitute soul reaper badge.
-Huh?
-Over the centuries, there
have been a few other instances
where substitute soul reapers
have been deemed useful.
They too were given this badges
as proof of their status.
You can use it to
become a soul reaper
whenever you wish to do so.
Of course, such a mere
token can never really
repay you for what
you have done here.
-It's all right.
The reason I did it all
is because I wanted to.
But I'll gladly accept this.
It's an honor.
Thank you.
-(THINKING) This man
is truly exceptional.
-There's something
here for you too,
Rukia, that Uryu made for you.
-Oh.
But since I'm staying here, I
won't need a dress like that.
-Rukia, you have got
to wear this dress!
-All right, then, I will.
-It is time.
-Well, see you around, Rukia.
-Yeah.
Thank you, Ichigo.
-That's my line.
Thank you, Rukia.
Thanks to you, now it
will finally stop raining.
-Aw.
Ichi's spiritual pressure
just disappeared.
-Yeah.
-Why didn't you go see them off?
-What for?
-Well, do you think you're
ever going to see him again?
-Someday, yes.
-Huh?
-You heard what old
man Yamamoto said.
This fight isn't over.
Not by a long shot.
Ichigo and I will meet again.
Besides, we're a
lot alike, he and I.
-Kenny, you've learned you
don't have to win every fight.
-Don't patronize me.
-What the hell, Yoruichi?
If this is the
official gate, then why
do we have to run for our
lives through it, just
like the last time?
URYU (OFFSCREEN):
We each need a hell
butterfly to clear
the gate safely!
Only soul reapers
can handle them.
Relax!
We're almost at the exit!
[screaming]
-I'm locked on target.
Fire one.
[screaming]
-There's the pitch, and
here comes the swing!
Jinta home run!
-[inaudible] catch!
-My, my.
Welcome back, everyone.
-Urahara.
But how?
-It's good to see you
again, young Ichigo.
I imagine by now you've
heard the truth about me.
-I have.
-Words cannot express
how sorry I am.
-Stop.
It's all right.
I'm not mad about it anymore.
Look, you really didn't
do anything wrong.
I'm not sure what
your motivation was,
but the fact is you helped
all of us become stronger,
and in the end, you
probably saved our lives.
For that, we're thankful.
So please don't apologize.
-OK.
-But I do want to
ask you one question.
Why didn't you just
tell me the truth?
Did you think I would
get scared and run away?
-Exactly right!
-Now, that just pisses me off.
-You were taking it so well.
I wasn't expecting
an elbow in the face.
-One other thing.
I want you to apologize
to Rukia when you see her.
And know she will say
the same thing I'd say.
Will you do that for me?
-Hm.
Yes.
-Mr. Urahara, do you suppose you
could drop me off around here?
-Of course.
Consider it done.
-See you later, Uryu.
I'll be sure to call you
if anything big comes up.
-What are you talking about?
-Hm?
-Have you forgotten, Ichigo?
You are a soul reaper,
and I am a Quincy.
The next time you and I
meet, we'll be enemies.
-He's a stubborn guy.
-Yeah, that's for sure.
-But that stubborn streak is one
of Uryu's best chatacteristics.
-You really think so?
-Yeah.
It's true.
-No way.
Man, you guys are more
understanding than I am.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): Well,
this is my stop, guys.
Goodbye!
-Shall I drop you off
at your house, Ichigo?
-Yeah.
That would be great.
Actually, I think I'll
get off right here.
-Wait a second.
-See ya.
Thanks for the ride.
-Ichigo!
-Hm.
-What's wrong, Yoruichi?
-Hm?
I was just thinking.
This has been quite a
long journey, hasn't it?
-It has.
-Tell me something, Kisuke.
-What?
-What are you going to do now?
-That's a good question.
It feels like we've
won a big victory,
but in fact, this all started
after we suffered a big defeat.
So really, all we've done is
get things back to normal.
To win this thing
for good, we're
going to have to count on
Ichigo and the others even more.
I'm afraid the battle
has just begun.
-Then I guess for
you and me, there'll
be no dying
peacefully of old age.
-Probably not.
But that really can't
be helped, I guess.
-Yoruichi and the boss sure
are a couple of odd ducks,
aren't they?
-They look like a
cat and a man to me.
-It's just an expression-- ow!
-Ow!
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): I'm home.
[theme music]
-Give me some suggestions
for the next episode.
MAN (OFFSCREEN): Dr. Kurosaki's
serious medical drama!
MAN (OFFSCREEN): Kon's
steamy and suggestive diary.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): How
about a horror mystery?
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
You're all wrong.
MAN (OFFSCREEN): Who's left?
MAN (OFFSCREEN): Wasn't it
someone you know, Ichigo?
-I don't know.
Aw, time's up!
MAN (OFFSCREEN): That
sure is nostalgic.