The Zanpakuto. Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined by
its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper and
dies with its Soul
Reaper.
That is the existence of
a Zanpakuto.
Stay out of our way.
Brother, why?!
Hey, c'mon now! Aren't
you going to finish them
off?
It sure looks to me like
you were having fun, right?
What are you all doing
here?
Is that any way to greet
us? Muramasa said to lend
you two a hand, so we all
came to help with things.
Beat those Soul Reapers
to death-Do it now!
Get going, Rukia! I'll
stay here and hold them off!
As weak as you are?
Don't be ridiculous!
Go!
Enough chitchat! Your
lives will soon be over!
And there will be two
less Soul Reapers to--
What the hell is this?!
Don't move!
No one move!
Hey!-Up here!
You're gonna beat who
to death?
Damn bastards!
Rukia! You all right?
Byakuya.
Well it looks like these
guys have us completely
surrounded.
After all that commotion
it's not too surprising. They
were bound to discover us.
Byakuya Kuchiki and you
six Zanpakuto... We are
here to take you into
custody.
Is that so? But there are
so many of us gathered in
one spot.
Are you sure you wouldn't
rather fight us?
What was that?!
If that's your wish, we
will oblige you. We are
ready to go at any time.
Don't let them
get to you!
We'll start by forming
a perimeter so they can't
escape from the area.
After that, we can take
them on one at a time.
Ha! o~ Why make it all so
damn complicated?
If we're gonna do this, then
let's just do it! None of us
are going to run away and hide
like cowards!
He's right, what are we
waiting for?
Hold your ground! And
do not let them escape
the boundaries of the
Squad Six barracks!
Anyone with a death wish,
come on, come at me! It'd
be my pleasure to cut you
down with my blade!
What?!
Sorry. I can't just
stand back and let you
run wild any longer.
Is that right?
All right. This time,
there's no one to get
in between us.
How about we finish what
we started the other day?
Ha. So you want to
settle the score?
I'm not gonna hold
anything back.
Then we might have fun!
Halt!
Thank you, Tenken.
Two against one? Fine
with me.
It's been a while. How
are you doing?
Oh, not bad. And you're
looking well.
Well, only thanks to you.
I was able to get away from
the cause of my stress.
Hold on. I haven't
identified myself. How
did you know it was me?
Oh, I could tell
immediately. The moment
I laid eyes on you I felt
disgusted.
Fujikujaku.
Do you mind not calling
me that name? It offends me.
My real name is
Ruriirokujaku.
If you insist on calling
me otherwise, I'll kill
you.
Well okay then, give it
your best shot.
Rukia! Renji!
Don't worry about me.
I'm okay, but Renji's
worn out.
It's not that bad.
Well you can stand down
now. I'm gonna bring
these guys to their
senses.
Leave him to me. You
return to Muramasa.
Very well then.
Byakuya!
Stand back!
I will not let you
through.
What do you want?
Captain. I'm not finished
talking with you just yet.
You still don't
understand that it's
useless?
I'm gonna stop you even
if it means giving my life!
Easy Renji!
Hmph.
We don't want to give
you the impression that
we have nothing left.
Yeah, that's right. In
fact, we haven't even
begun to get serious yet.
Thanks guys, I appreciate
it.
Scatter.
Not gonna happen!
Shikai isn't enough? In
that case...
Bankai!
Getsugatensho!!!
Hmph.
Say, you look pretty good
holding that sword.
Huh?
And that feather on your
face... it's probably
faux, but still it's a
nice look.
I hadn't gotten the
chance to really check
you out, but so far I am
loving your style.
What're you talking
about?!
Now, if you would make
the effort to coordinate
with genuine accessories,
I think you'd come
across even better.
Then again, you don't
want to overdo it and
look trashy or cheap.
Is there a point to any
of this?
I've got it! My
feathers are the real
thing. How about I give
you one of these?
Forget it, they're
ugly.
Also, it might be nice to
add a few extra flourishes
to your uniform.
Fabulous!
Hey!
Huh, but how to
compliment your lovely
complexion? Hmmm.
Cut it out will you!!
You're mocking me, and
I do not appreciate it!!
Hmph. I don't know
what you mean.
Well you look hideous.
Your face is the absolute
worst.
Whatever, be as insulting
as you like, it doesn't
matter to me at all.
Do you have any idea why
I took the trouble of
choosing this location,
far from everyone else
for our battle?
I assume it's because
you don't want anyone
else to see my powers.
Exactly right.
That confidence... you
might come to regret it.
I never regret anything.
That's just the way
that I do battle...
Fujikujaku.
I told you, if you keep
calling me by that name,
I will destroy you.
Looking for somebody?
Well done. As I'd
expect from the leader of
the Stealth Force.
What's the matter?
It's been bothering me
for a while now... But
whose Zanpakuto are you?
I am Gonryomaru!
Sorry, never heard of
you.
My name is Gonryomaru!
The Zanpakuto of Squad
One lieutenant, Chojiro
Sasakibe!
Ah! So you're his
sword!
You're so boring, I
couldn't tell.
What?! How dare
you! Huh?
Don't worry, Tenken.
I'm all right. Chojiro is
the one to blame for all of
this
for not having a
presence in his
own squad.
Oh I see, so that's the
reason you betrayed your
master?
Shut up!
Well that's pretty stupid.
Not that it'll matter in
a couple of seconds.
When I immobilize you, you
can say whatever you want
to your master.
I won't go down that
easy.
What is this?
What's the matter? For someone
who talks a big game, all you're
doing is running away, coward!
What was that? A
coward?
Damn right! Last time, you
couldn't beat me either so
you just ran away! That makes
you a true coward!
Battles are waged,
according to the specific
situation.
I don't consider
pulling back cowardice.
Forcing a fight you
cannot win, that's
just foolish.
Man, you sure do talk
a lot of nonsense.
Whatever. This time
I'll slice you to bits
before you can run.
I'm finding it hard to
believe you're really
Shuhei's Zanpakuto.
What?
Well if that's the truth,
I have to assume Shuhei must
have been suppressing his
negative energy without
even realizing it.
You're a manifestation
of his stress. His darkest
impulses. Isn't that right?
What the hell are you
saying?! You think
I'm stress!?
Am I wrong?
Don't mess with me!
Hado number Thirty One:
Shakkaho!
See, Shuhei has always
had my back, no matter
what. So I owe it to him
to get his revenge.
Damn you.
I'm not finished with
you yet!
Extend! Hozukimaru!
Huh?
Oh. So you've
regained your Shikai
then, partner?
Uh-huh!
What's wrong? Don't
tell me you're outta
gas already.
You're weaker than you
were the last time around.
Not even close. You think
I've been giving it a
hundred percent?
Oh yeah. I do remember
you being sort-of slow to
get going.
Fine then, how about
I light a fire under you
right now!
What's the matter? Is
that all you've got?
Bankai.
Don't push your luck,
partner.
So you've finally
gotten serious.
Then the real fight
starts now!
Over here!
Damn!
And I've got plenty
more!
Come on. That all you
got?
No, you idiot. Now I'm
just getting warmed up.
Your spirit is impressive.
But still, you're gonna need
more than that to take me down.
Go on, cling to your
silly stubbornness, but
in head-to-head battles
you'll always get crushed.
What'd you say?
If you're gonna act
like a badass, you
should probably have the
skill to back it up.
Bastard!
I warned you and you
still fell short. Are
you stupid or something?
Heh. You're the
stupid one.
That right?
How did you--?
What you said about me
before... you're right,
I am pretty stubborn.
But still, I'll stick
to the way I do things.
I'll fight the way I
always do and still tear
you apart!
Because when you get
right down to it, a man's
not a man if he can't be
himself in battle!
Now you're talkin', partner.
Go on, give it your best shot
and defeat me!
You don't have to tell
me twice!
You, you're pretty good.
Just what I expected from
my own Zanpakuto.
Same here. That's why
I'm at full strength.
Hmph.
Huh?
What are
you up to?
This is the end. I
won't back away past
this line.
Hozukimaru, I'll take
all your force and send
it right back at you!
That's a promise!
You realize how
powerful this attack
is going to be, right?
That sounds perfect.
Come at me, Hozukimaru!
I am the Third Seat of
Zaraki's Squad.
Ikkaku Madarame!
Pretty good, partner.
Yah you're damn right.
Heh. I told you,
didn't I?
Lieutenant Iba!
Oh, Lieutenant Kotetsu.
What's the situation?
Captain Soi Fon and the
others are fighting at
the Squad Six barracks.
We've gotten reports that the
Stealth Force has the enemy
surrounded and is preventing
them from escaping.
I see. Then I suppose
we should hurry to their
position and give them
some backup.
I agree. Apparently, there
are many fighters who have
been wounded already.
What the---
what's wrong?
Over there!
What is that?
After Shuhei, Marechiyo,
Rangiku, Momo, it'll
be my turn!!
Bring it on, Zanpakuto!
Tetsuzaemon, what was
your Zanpakuto's name
again?
Come at me Zanpakuto!!
You forgot didn't you?
Come on, Zanpakuto, fight
me!!