Your only option is to
attack me from where you
stand.
Kick about, Los Lobos!
And that counter attack
packed a real punch. Damn.
I'm impressed.
Why thank you, Captain.
I went through all the
trouble of a sword
release.
You can at least show
me what I want... your
Bankai.
Cero Metralleta.
It's no use
running away!
Hey! Hold on, wait a
second!
You had your chance!
When fired like this,
even a Cero blast should
be enough to destroy you,
right?
I dunno, isn't that
kinda like cheating?!
Seems fair to me.
What's wrong? Have
you had enough, Captain?
Maybe it's time you
show me... your Bankai.
Looks like I
don't have a choice.
[panting]
Damn it. I must have
taken too much damage.
Are you all right,
Captain!
I'm fine!
Huh?!
Oh, come on! Why can't
you just accept somebody
trying to be kind to you?
What did you just say?
Uh?! That wasn't
me, ma'am!
Must've been the wind.
But that guy was scary,
wasn't he, Captain?
Um, Captain?
We're done with
that, now.
Sogyonokotowari.
[gasping]
Jushiro?
What the hell? Did
he shoot... a Cero?
That was definitely a
Cero.
Hey, what gives?
There's no use arguing.
We're basically up
against two of them.
There's nothing
cowardly in accepting
my help.
I got the sense you
weren't planning on
using your Bankai.
Actually, I was just
about to.
No. You
shouldn't.
Hm??!
It's too risky. Your
Bankai shouldn't be
used where it could
be seen.
Not to mention, against
an enemy like this...
my attacks will be more
effective.
Hey you.
Huh?
Not you.
You, the captain with
the white hair.
Oh, me?!
Yeah...
How did you manage to
fire that Cero just now?
Well, I can't really say.
If you shoot at us again,
there's a good chance
you'll find out.
That sounds fair.
Guess I'll try that!
Hey wait-Hold on! He's
trying to set a trap for
you!
Isn't it pretty obvious?!
He wants you to shoot at
him! Hey, come on!
Are you listening
to me?!
Just shut up.
See! He fired back at us,
just like I thought he
would! Would you listen
to me?!
Now I get it.
You have the ability to
absorb an enemy's attack
and send it directly back
to where it came from.
But that's not
all, is it?
Those five talismans
hanging from that cord
adjust the speed and
pressure of the technique
when it returns, which
throws off your
opponent...
It complicates your
enemy's timing and disrupts
their defense.
You may have the
appearance of a
gentleman...
... but you've got some
pretty nasty skills,
don't you?
Amazing! I never thought
you'd figure out that much
from just three attacks!
Thanks for the compliment.
I'm pleased to know that
your ability isn't some
mindless trick that only
reflects your enemy's
attacks back at them.
But since you absorb the
attacks before sending
them back,
there has to be a limit as
to how much you can take in.
If I fired hundreds of
shots at you at the same
time, you couldn't
return all of them.
Looks like you're
acting out of
character... Captain!
You don't know me well
enough to speak about
my character.
I'd have to say my
biggest characteristic,
is being completely
uncharacteristic.
Uh! And all this time I
thought you and I were
alike!
I've got you!
Not quite.
So, you're staying at
close range where I can
shoot you. In that case...
Now you can't get to me
from this side.
Your only option is to
attack me from where you
stand.
Hm!
Uh!
Hm! You're
really good!
Huh.
Oh, you guys are actually
trying to hustle me, aren't
you? Was that your plan?
He never promised to
fight you alone.
Jushiro, how are you
holding up, old buddy?
Heh, never
felt better.
You bastards!
Two on one's unfair!
Attack him one at a time!
What are you talking
about?! There are two
of you as well! You're
helping him.
A kid like you shouldn't
be involved in this thing.
Will you give it a rest,
old man?
I've really had
it with you.
I want this guy dead
right now, Stark!
Okay, okay! I want to get
this over with quickly as
well, but--
This time, I'll see to
it from the start that
he won't get near us.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
[gasping]
What? A Garganta?!
It's huge! What the
hell is going on up
there?
Hmmm...
It can't be.
No, not now.
A Garganta?
Reinforcements?
Are you trying to tell me
there are more of them coming
over here to help these
Espadas attack us?
Well, now, that's
not a pleasant thought.
What the--?
Who is that?
He's one creepy
looking fella,
that's for sure.
Aaaaa.
Wonderweiss.
Haaauuhhh.
Whoa.
Hey look! Now something
else is coming out.
Captain! What's
going on?!
What?!
Uh! You're
kidding me.
Aaaa-oouh-ah.
Hmm.
That's the eye...
from before.
Ahhh! Captain, let's
get out of here before--
Just shut up.
[gasping]
What on earth...
is that?!
Auuww?
[gasping]
[grunting]
Heaaaa!
Aaaaa... Uh?
Sorry.
Aaa-aauuh.
The fact that Wonderweiss
is here means one thing.
Lord Aizen cannot wait
any longer.
Shunsui! Jushiro!!
[screaming]
[gasping]
He's back!
Impossible!
Uh... Captain?!
Captain Komamura.
Hm?
We'll be fine here.
Please sir, go.
Are you sure?
You must go!
I know your presence here
is keeping us safe, Captain!
But our survival means
nothing, if everyone is
wiped out because you
stay with us!!
Aaaaahhh-oooh-ahh.
Hmm?
That's rather a foul
stench... as always.
Agreed.
This must be what people
refer to as the stench of
death.
Yes, the stench of death
is quite fitting here.
It's a perfect
description...
... of what's about
to happen before us.
Uh!
This is it.
We're finished!!
Not so fast.
[gasping]
Heh!
Rose...!
I'm on it, everyone
get back!
Good! Now I gotcha!
[roaring]
Bakudo Number
Ninety-Nine...!
...Restrict!
Shin... ji...
Let go of me!
[gagging]
[gasping]
[screaming]
Hold on a minute...!
...Kaname!
He's actually quite...
loyal.
As a matter of fact,
Kaname was just loyally
following my orders.
You, of all people, can
understand that, so
please don't hold it
against him...
...Captain Hirako.
Sosu... ke...!
Sosuke!
What's happening to me?
[gasping]
Sosuke!! What's
going on?!
I suppose, when it comes
right down to it, that
you owe your friends here
an apology. Because you
were chosen by me, they
ended up on the ground as
casualties, through no
fault of their own...
[struggling]
As we thought... it
appears that an agitated
state helps to accelerate
the Hollowfication process.
Hollowfication?
What have you
done to us?
I see no reason to
explain, Captain.
[struggling]
I believe it's time
to finish you off...
...Dear Captain Hirako.
In the end, I hope you'll
remember one thing...
Any betrayal you can see
is trivial.
What is truly frightening,
and much more lethal, is
the betrayal you cannot see.
Goodbye...
I must commend you---You
people have provided
wonderful research
material.
[screaming]
It's been awhile,
hasn't it?
Sosuke...
Aaaah!
Damn! He's
still screaming.
Sorry Izuru, I could no
longer hold back my
instinctual urges.
Captain Komamura?
[barking]
[screaming]
Stop that!