[music playing]
[clanking]
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Attention, red alert.
Red alert.
Intruders detected
in West Rukon.
This is not a drill.
Repeat, red alert.
Breach detected in West Rukon.
-Wait a second.
What the hell is going on?
-Don't look now, but that
section we just came through
is collapsing on us.
I'm running as fast as I can.
But I still don't think we're
going to make it through.
-Quit looking behind you,
and concentrate your efforts
on running.
If the restrictive
current swallows you up,
then it's all over.
-[panting]
-[inaudible].
I knew that stupid outfit of
his was going to get him caught.
-Hold it.
You musn't do that, Ichigo.
The restrictive current
entangles the spiritual body.
If you reveal yourself
using you zanpakuto,
it'll swallow you too.
-[screaming]
-[grunting]
-Thanks for that, Chad.
-Let's go.
-Whoa!
What do you think you're doing?
Hey!
Put me down, will you?
I can run on my own!
I, I don't mean to bother
you while you're running,
but something else is coming.
Ah!
Yoruichi, what is that?
-It's the cleaner.
It comes through
here every seven days
to clear out the passage way.
And it's just our bad luck
that today is the day.
Don't look back at it.
That'll only slow you down.
Just keep running, or it
will crush you to powder.
Go, go!
We're almost to the exit.
-Guys, we're not
going to make it!
-[speaking japanese]
-[screaming]
[explosion]
-Oh.
Hey, is everyone all right?
[giggling]
-Ichigo, the way
you landed showed
tremendous artistic flair.
-Gee, thanks a lot.
-Unh.
I knew it would be rough
getting through that gate.
But I had no idea it would take
such a toll on my equipment.
I wasn't expecting to have
to use my spare cape so soon.
-Aw, man.
Don't tell me he brought
a change of clothes.
-Guys, isn't this great?
We all made it.
And everyone's OK.
-It's not great.
We were lucky.
-My eye.
-I told you not to expose your
spiritual powers in there.
We're fortunate that
the cleaner only
make contact with
the shield area.
If it had even touched any part
of the six flowers themselves,
you'd all be dead now.
-I, I didn't know.
-Hey, lighten up.
How was Orihime
supposed to know that?
And anyway, if it hadn't
been for her quick thinking,
we wouldn't have made it through
that gate in the first place.
-I don't think any
of you appreciate
how serious the
situation really is.
-Listen.
Doesn't it seem awfully
quiet around here?
-Yeah.
Is this place really
the soul society?
-Yes.
And the specific area we're in
is called the Rukon district.
It's here in the Rukon
district that souls
come to live when they first
arrive in the soul society.
As a matter of fact, it's
right on the perimeter
of the Seireitei, where
soul reapers live.
It's the poorest
section, but also
the one with the
greatest freedom.
And it has the
largest population
of souls within
the soul society.
-If that's true, then
where is everybody?
-Hey, look at those
buildings over there.
Why do they look so different
from everywhere else?
-Just forget about that.
-I know.
I bet that's the Seirei--
whatever you mentioned,
where all the soul reapers live.
-Uh!
-All right, you soul reapers.
Here I come.
-Wait!
Stop, you idiot.
You can't run up to
the gate like that.
You'll be killed!
-Huh?
[crashing]
[coughing]
-[coughing]
-Well, well, it's
been a long time
since anyone tried to pass
through the spirit gates
without a travel permit.
And I don't get many
guests these days.
So welcome to you, little man.
[laughing]
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
So the intruders
have landed outside
the Hakudo gate.
-But as long as
they're on that side,
there's no need for us to
get involved in the matter.
-I agree.
Because on the other side,
they all have to deal with--
-[roaring]
-Jidanbo.
-[laughing] Whenever
you are ready,
give it all all you've got.
And good luck.
-He's a leviathan.
What kind of creature do
you suppose he is, anyway?
He's way too big to
be a human being.
-He is known simply as Jidanbo.
He was chosen from among
the very best warriors
the soul society has.
His task is to guard
the Hakuto gate, one
of four entrances that
make up the spirit gate.
-He's the guard?
If we intend to get
through this gate,
it looks like we have no
choice but to defeat him.
YORUICHI (OFFSCREEN): Yes.
But that will not be an
easy task, I'm afraid.
In the 300 years Jidanbo
has served at this post,
countless invaders have tried.
But not a single one has ever
broken through the Hakuto gate.
Jidanbo has become a legend
of power and strength.
-How in the world
are we supposed
to defeat something like that?
YORUICHI (OFFSCREEN): That's
where your intelligence
and creativity come in.
The first thing we need
to do is to have a meeting
to decide on a strategy.
Ichigo, let's start
with-- [screaming].
No!
Chad!
Orihime!
Come back here, both of you!
Have you lost your minds?
-(THINKING) We're coming
to help you, Ichigo.
Hang on.
We'll fight him together.
[panting]
-[growling] [roaring]
[screaming]
-He's not only huge.
He's insane.
-You two need some
work on your manners.
What are you, country
bumpkins, or something?
We're civilized in this city.
Here are the rules.
Rule number one,
always wash your hands
before you sit down to eat.
Rule number two, don't eat food
that's fallen on the floor.
Rule three, battles in the city
are always fought one on one.
The kid with the
spiky orange hair
was the first to approach
and challenge me.
So you shall be
my first opponent.
Then I'll come back
to deal with you two.
This won't take long, promise.
-Oh.
CHAD (OFFSCREEN): Orihime.
-Oh?
-I'm going to wait for
the right opportunity,
and then punch a big
hole through this wall.
As soon as it's open, you
aim Subaki at the big guy
through the opening.
-What was that?
Don't tell me you two are still
plotting schemes over there.
-Even his ears are powerful.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Orihime,
Chad, are you there?
-Ichigo, yes, we're here.
Are you all right?
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Yeah.
I'm still alive and kicking.
-We're coming to help you.
Just wait right there.
-Yeah, well, here's
the thing, Orihime.
I actually want you and Chad
to just stay put, and let
me handle this by myself.
-What?
Ichigo, this is too big a job
for even you to handle alone.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Don't worry.
Just wait for me over there.
It'll be OK.
-I refuse to do that.
-Yeah, tell him.
-Ichigo, we can't
afford to wait around.
Instead of wasting time
battling the guard individually,
we've got to attack together,
and get past this gate.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
You're here too, Uryu?
-I've been here the whole time.
It's just like you
to waste energy
with stupid comments, Ichigo.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Oh, shut up.
You're giving me a headache.
-Can you defeat him?
-Probably.
URYU (OFFSCREEN): Probably?
What's wrong with you?
Don't you understand
this is a life and death
situation we're in here?
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Look, don't
worry about it, all right?
-How can I not worry, Ichigo?
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
Listen, I'll tell you
all an interesting little story.
Remember when I was training
with Mister [inaudible]?
He said it was going to take
me 10 days for my soul reaper
powers to be
completely restored.
But as it turned out, it
only took me five days.
So what do you think I did
for those other five day?
-Knowing you,
probably goofing off.
-I fought with him the
whole time, for so long,
nonstop, for five
days and nights.
He and I battled each
other one on one.
URYU (OFFSCREEN): I see.
And you learned all his
fighting techniques, right?
-Wrong again.
URYU (OFFSCREEN): So
what's your point, then.
I didn't learn a single thing
from him about fighting.
But in those long hours, I
gained tremendous strength
and stamina.
[music playing]
-You done making speeches yet?
-Look, pal, I never
asked you to wait.
So you could have attacked
at any time, right?
-So you are a country
bumpkin after all.
Didn't your folks
teach you any manners?
When someone is polite
enough to wait for you,
you should always say thank you.
-[screaming]
-This can't be good.
-Huh?
Who are you, spiky head?
-I'm no expert, but
isn't it also bad
manners to attack before
your opponent is ready?
-[grumbling] [laughing]
-He's laughing.
-You're gutsy.
I'll give you that, spiky head.
I can't remember the
last time someone was
able to stop the
thrust of my axe.
This is going to be fun.
For once, I'll be able to
give it everything I have.
Of all the intruders who have
tried to get past this gate,
there have only been
two who have come along
before you who were powerful
enough to stop my first thrust.
But that is where
the story ends.
Because neither they
nor you could ever
hope (SHOUTING) to fend
off my second thrust.
[roaring]
Are you still standing?
I guess I get to keep trying
my attacks on you, then.
See how you like this.
Jidan ten-strike festival.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven--
-What in the world is he doing?
-7, 8, 12, 9, 6-- wait.
I've never had to
count this high before.
But I must be at 10 by now.
So it's time to finish this.
[roaring]
-[whimpering]
-[grunting]
-[sighing] Got him, I think.
What?
That's impossible.
How can you still be standing
after that attack, spiky head?
-I agree.
It does seem impossible.
-But he's still all right.
-(THINKING) Now I understand.
What Ichigo gained
from his training
wasn't fighting skills.
And it wasn't just strength
and stamina, either.
-Ichigo has spiritual
power far beyond that
of most soul reapers.
But he has a long way to go.
Because he's still inexperienced
at wielding that great power.
-(THINKING) So before, when he
confronted other soul reapers,
the only thing that Ichigo
was lacking was experience.
And now that he's gained that--
-Are you finished, gate keeper?
CHAD (OFFSCREEN):
(THINKING) I have a feeling.
-Because if you are,
then it's my turn now.
CHAD (OFFSCREEN):
(THINKING) He's
going to be so
powerful, it's scary.
-I'm not done.
I'm not done.
I just have to bring
out some more weaponry.
-He's got another axe!
My ultimate attack!
[shouting] See if you
can withstand the Jidan
banzai-strike festival.
-Sorry, pal.
But I'm going to
destroy your axes.
[shout]
-[grunting]
[moaning] What, what was that?
-Wow.
If I hadn't seen it, I
wouldn't have believed it.
Ichigo just sent
that giant flying.
-[grunting] [chuckling] Whoa,
you almost caught me that
time.
I can't believe I slipped
and fell on my behind.
It's been a long time
since that happened.
What's that weird
look on your face for?
I bet you think you're the one
who sent me flying backwards,
don't you?
[chuckling] You should
really know better than that.
But it's typical of
a country bumpkin
like you to believe
that a gatekeeper like
me could be blown
away so easily.
All I have to do is
make one more swing
with my mighty axe and-- oh!
-Huh.
It appears Jidanbo's mighty axes
have been modified somewhat.
-Wow.
A single blow, and
he got them both.
-Well, are you going to say
something, or just stand there?
-(WHIMPERING) My axes.
My axes, ruined!
Why did you have to do it?
Why did you have
to-- Why did you
have to destroy my
beautiful babies?
Why?
[sobbing]
-(THINKING) This giant is such
a big tough guy on the outside.
But on the inside--
-(THINKING) He's more
like a little boy.
-[sobbing]
-Look, I'm sorry about
your axes, and everything.
But, hey, I couldn't let you
keep swinging them at me.
Although I guess I could have
just destroyed one of them,
and let you keep the other one.
My bad.
-No, you not bad.
Even though you my enemy.
You care.
Instead of thinking of
your quest, and your desire
to get through the
gate, you're actually
concerned for you
opponent and his axes.
What a good person you
are, my spiky headed enemy.
What a generous heart you have.
-Well, it's only natural
to want to console someone
who cries so much, even
if they are really big.
-I know.
I'm acting like a big baby.
All that crying and moaning
over a couple of old axes.
I'm nothing but an
embarrassment as a man.
[pouting] I'm a total loser.
-Huh?
-(SHOUTING) A total loser!
You beat me not only as a
warrior and gate keeper.
You have defeated me
as a man, as well.
It has been 300
years since I became
the keeper of the Hakudo gate.
And in all those years, never
have I lost a challenge,
or allowed anyone
to pass this way.
I thought the day
would never come.
But you are the first man
to defeat me. [sniffling]
Therefore I, Jidanbo,
hereby grant you passage
through the Hakudo gate.
-Huh?
Whoa, cool.
URYU (OFFSCREEN): You're
allowing all of us to pass?
-That's right.
I was decisively defeated
in battle by your leader.
As a result, I have no right
to stop anyone in your group.
-What?
Whoever said anything about
Ichigo being our leader?
Absolutely not!
-It's no big deal, but why
are you so upset, Uryu?
-So your name is
Ichigo, huh spiky head?
-That's right.
I'm Ichigo Kurosaki.
That's a pretty cute
name for someone
who seems to take himself so
seriously, don't you think?
-My name is not cute!
Ichi means number one.
And go stands for guardian.
And that's what I am!
-[chuckling] Yeah, whatever.
You take care now.
I don't know why you
were so determined
to pass through this gate.
But those will meet on the
other side are all very strong.
-I'm aware of that.
-Very well.
As long as you think you know
what you're getting into.
Now stand back.
And I'll open the gate for you.
[grunting] This is
not going to be easy.
It's been closed a long time.
[grunting]
-Oh!
-[grunting] [roaring]
-Amazing.
-I never thought anyone could
lift something so heavy.
-Jidanbo, what is it?
Why are you frozen like that?
Something wrong?
-[stuttering]
-Who is that?
-That is none other
than the captain
of Squad Three, Gin Ichimaru.
-[chuckling]
[music playing]
URYU (OFFSCREEN): A mysterious
wild boar gang attacks.
And it seems that
the only one who
can stop this dangerous
bunch is Ichigo.
-Ha!
-And so we leave
it to you, Ichigo.
Don't let everyone down.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN): Right.
Vroom, vroom, vroom.
Hey, don't run away, you guys.