The Zanpakuto, Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined by
its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper and
dies with its Soul Reaper.
That is the existence of
a Zanpakuto.
Impressive.
Enlisting him will
be no easy task.
You're not too bad.
I am not here to play
with you.
Now prove to me that you
are Ichigo Kurosaki's true
power. Don't waste anymore
of my time.
Let's have some fun.
Damn it. What now? Why
the hell do these two have
to do this in my inner world?!
Our Zanpakuto can be lost
forever?
Yes, they can.
Under normal
circumstances, a broken
Zanpakuto would regenerate
once its master fully heals.
However, our Zanpakuto
have left our bodies and
now exist as an entity
that is completely
independent from us.
Meaning, the rules may
have changed from what
they once were.
Let me get this straight,
Jushiro. You're thinking that
killing those manifestations
could lead to us losing
our Zanpakuto?
Hmmm...
While that thought sounds
pretty logical, we have no
actual proof. I would sure hate
to jump to the wrong conclusion.
Well, that's true...
However...
The thing that worries me the
most, is if we were to confront
our Zanpakuto with such a
question in mind,
would we even stand
a chance against them?
Ready, Renji?
Hm, not good. I gotta say,
monkey, I thought he'd be much
better than that. Pretty weak.
There's no need for that
attitude. We can't have him
throwing in the towel just yet.
Hey! Look! He got up!
He's standing up!
Knock it off! Don't
overreact, you little
brat.
Oww! You don't have to
hit me you fat-assed
freak!
Why, you-- shut the
heck up, you pervo!
Shut it! I said shut
it or I'll shut it for
you!
That's enough, you two!
Don't argue with each other
like that! I'm the one you're
fighting here.
You really don't
understand anything, do
you?
What's that?
Here's the deal. We feel
like we're just wasting our
time battling against a
weakling like you.
Boom! There ya you go!
The big-assed broad said
it!
I told you two to stop it
already!
What's with you? You
keep calling me names and
treating me like I'm
second rate. What's
behind the two of you
acting like that?!
There's a lot
behind it.
It's our true instinct.
What the hell's that
mean? Now you're not
making any sense.
We don't want to
be weak.
Hm!?
As he said, we refuse to
be weak. We want to be
stronger.
And we've grown tired
of your weakness. We now
wish to leave you. And
that is all.
That's it! Just
keep talkin'!
Roar! Zabimaru!
Uh!??
So just how do you intend
to fight us? Well, Renji?
So the only defense left
for you is running away?!
Damn! He's anticipating
almost every move I make!
Do you think it's wise
to rest in a spot that's
so open for attack?
So you run away and hide
then attack me from the
shadows? You fight just as
dirty as you look!
Fight dirty?
What's wrong with that?
Does it matter in a life
or death situation?
I prefer to look my
opponent in the eye.
You think I care how you
fight!?
I am a Zanpakuto whose
sole aim is to harvest as
many lives as I can.
I have no interest in
how my master fights.
I was under the impression
that you and I had an
understanding.
Through communication,
we formed a relationship
where we were a synergistic
unit.
I can't say I know
about other Zanpakuto!
But I know who I am. I
exist to reap lives! That
was the only thing I was
responsible for in this
relationship.
Is that so? Then you
have left me no choice.
If killing you means losing
my Zanpakuto, then so be it.
I just realized
something. I don't
like you!
That's fine with me...
I feel the same...
His speed.
His power.
This feels so good. It's
been quite a while since I've
used my power without holding
back.
He acts on pure instinct.
There are no mistakes.
He is overpowering
him!
Come on out,
Zanpakuto!
I know there's more to
you than that!
Impressive. I didn't
anticipate that you would
be so capable.
It's true. You are
a hollow.
Thanks to Zangetsu being
released from Ichigo
Kurosaki, you were left
to run free inside of him.
If you're his Inner
Hollow, that helps
explain the strange
transformation that
Ichigo went through at
that time.
Am I right?
And so what if you
are?
I have one more thing to
say...
Now that I know the
secret behind your tricks,
it's clear there's no need
for me to waste anymore time.
Zanpakuto and Soul Reapers
come together through
communication and synergy.
But now I see there are
exceptions to this. Like
you. Some forces must remain
suppressed.
You are a very interesting
subject.
Hey! I let you speak
your mind and you go
putting me down like
that?!
Did you just say that he's
been keeping me suppressed?
Am I wrong?
Oh yeah, dead wrong!
Then explain it to me.
Now, why should I do
that for you?
Besides, what's got you
so interested in Ichigo?
You're sure curious about
us both! So what's your
game here?
You'll know in time.
Oh yeah?
Well I don't know or care
what you're planning, but
listen up...
You won't get your way!
Not with me here.
I'll devour Ichigo and then
take control of this body!
You see, that is
my true instinct.
I see.
So you're saying you
intend to stand in my
way. I have no choice,
then.
I'll wipe you out from
this existence.
Nice try!
Roar!
Hey, you coward!
Hm? Wow. Weakling, coward.
What the hell have I done to
earn all of these fancy
nicknames you're giving me?
I call you a coward because
you are one. It's the only
way to describe you.
I've had enough.
I quit.
Hey!
You still need to remain
focused.
And why should I?!...
Even with all we've done
to get him to fight us,
he won't get serious!...
This whole thing is no
fun at all!
Have you forgotten that
we know everything about
you?
Like that the time you
gave up something that
was very dear to you.
We saw how desperately
you tried to get it back.
You fought for it, then.
Yet in spite of what you
did, you still don't have
confidence in yourself.
Perhaps killing your
precious friend and
holding her severed head
in front of your face
will finally get you to
be serious? Will that force
you to take this seriously?
Bastard!
We can see you're
angry... But we also
know just why you can't
find the guts to kill us.
And that's why I say
you're weak.
Well! I think you've
finally gone and done it.
It doesn't matter. He wasn't
even half the man we had
wanted him to be.
Let's go, he's
hopeless.
Hold it! Where do you
think you're going?
Looks like he still
wants to fight.
You're not leaving until
you've beaten me.
We're through with you. You
do not have the will to
fight us.
We know you better than
anyone, right?
Let's say you fight
us and you defeat us.
You will have won, but
what if beating us means
you'd lose your own
power? But what if that
I bet that's the explanation
for why you're afraid to attack
us. Isn't that right?
Unfortunately, we don't
know what would happen
either.
We now exist completely
separate from you. So I
wouldn't be surprised if
we are
now capable of dying,
just like you Soul
Reapers.
Renji. You refuse to
make the decision to
destroy your Zanpakuto.
In other words,
You cannot bring yourself
to destroy us... Am I wrong?
Can you really blame me
for calling you a weakling?
True strength is not
just about having the
ability to fight.
What's the matter? That
all you got?
You know, with you fighting
that slow, your chances of
getting to me aren't that
good!
Yes, I'm aware. But
not concerned.
Not sure what you have
up your sleeve, but--
What's this?!
Can't move!
What's the matter? That
all you got?
D-damn you! Shut up!
This is what happened
to me.
What is that?
Could that be...
how he--
You are nothing but a
hollow.
You do not possess the
power that I am seeking.
Therefore, you are expendable.
It hurts. What am I
gonna do?
I am too weak.
Is this the end
for me?
All this time... what
have I been doing?!
Do something!
After all this time, my
own Zanpakuto has deserted
me! What should I do?!
It hurts. It really
hurts. I think I
understand now.
The pain is not coming
from my injuries. It
is my life force as a
whole that is diminished.
He's beat. So what now?
Go ahead. Just
finish him off.
So in the end, I didn't
change at all. I kept
boasting about becoming
stronger, but all I did
was move forward without
actually thinking. Is
that it?
What about Ichigo?
Ichigo has told me, the only
reason he fights is to protect
others. That's what makes
him strong!
But what about me? What do
I have? What do I fight for?
Damn you.
That's it. I can't just let
you take what you want.
Hmm... he escaped my
spell in such a short
time. How is this possible?
Why are you protecting
me? Why would you do that
for me?!
Do you really
need to ask?
It's who I am. And
obviously you're a
part of me. It's as
simple as that.
Oh great, more
of your arrogance.
Now that Zangetsu has
disappeared, I don't
know what you plan on
doing with me .
And I don't know what
to do with myself either.
But one thing must be
done.
And done now. You
know that, right?
You're such a pain
in the ass.
What an interesting sight,
this is. You're choosing to
protect the hollow?
What the hell's so strange?
So what if he's a hollow?
All that matters at this
moment is that he's a part
of me.
I'm good with that because
I'm the guy in charge here.
But I don't intend to let
you get away with whatever
the hell you want.
Ichigo Kurosaki. Just
what exactly are you?
What you described is
hardly the relationship between
a Soul Reaper and a Hollow.
Listen to
me, Muramasa.
You're wrong
about one thing.
You haven't realized this, but
I'm not a Soul Reaper. I'm
a human!
You intend to push me out
of this world by using your
own will?
I must say...
you are unusual.
Huh?
Where were we?
You may have been right
about me being weak. I
had forgotten.
But my mindset's
different now. I don't
have the time to waste
arguing about stupid
things like that.
Stupid, you say?
I only want to become
stronger. That's all.
I will regain control.
I will find a way reunite
with Zangetsu.
Even if I have to
destroy him.
There is still someone
that I must surpass in
battle.
That is why I have this
goal to become even
stronger!
Facing the two of you is
what reminded me of that!
This is a choice that
I've made.
And I know in order to
achieve that goal...
I can't afford to
lose! I must win!
Roar! Zabimaru!
Come on!
What are you doing?
You just said to "Roar,
Zabimaru."Isn't that
right, Snake Boy?
Yeah-you told us, so we
roared. Want us to roar
again?
No!
[roaring]
Please
shut up!!!