Mmh...
Ah!
How are you feeling?
Where am I?
A candy store called
Urahara's Shop.
You can relax.
You'll be safe here.
Hngh.
Ah! You still
need rest.
Hey! You looked like you
were having a nightmare.
Are you okay Nozomi?
Hel-lo? Are you even listening?!
What are you?
Oh! That's right!
You've never seen me
like this before, have you?
It's me, Kon!
But back to you.
So, why were those guys after
you, anyway? What did you do?
Oh, yeah. Before we
get to that, you were
a Soul Reaper, right?
You should've said so!
Not to brag, but I do know
a thing or two about that!
How lame.
Yeah, that's
right, lame.
Wait, what?!
Hey, I'm not in this form
by choice, you know!
I'm a Mod Soul; when I can't
use Ichigo's body, there's
nothing I can do about it!
A Mod Soul?
Yeah. That's right.
What? What're
you staring at?!
Look, just answer my
questions and tell me
what happened, okay?!
Then my loyal servants
just might be able to
help you out!
[shattering crash]
[Kon]
Yeaaghh!
Ngh... egh.. hrg...
Watch it,
pervert.
You jerk!
Why did you do that?!
That's enough, Kon.
But what was that for?!
All I did was ask her
some questions!
If she doesn't want to talk
about it, then there's no use
trying to force her to, okay?
[sigh]
Yeah, I guess so.
Hey, Ichigo.
How much longer are you going
to keep everyone waiting?
Come on, already!
Yeah, okay. One sec.
All right! Let's go!
Strategy meeting,
here we come!
No. You stay here with
Nozomi and the others.
What?!
They're still
looking for her.
We must take steps
to keep her safe.
Yeah but...
It's a vital assignment.
We need you.
Awwh.
Well, I guess I can handle
all the important jobs,
just like usual.
Let's go, Ichigo.
[proud chuckling]
Yeah.
Be careful, guys!
Hmm?
Is something wrong?
[Inaba]
Thank you,
everyone.
I appreciate you
all gathering here.
I know you have very
busy schedules.
Enough formalities.
What's the plan?
What are we going
to do now?!
I've already sealed off the
Precipice World and rendered
communications impossible.
Now we must strengthen and
unify ourselves before
they can formulate a
strategy and return here.
Also, there are still a few
captains who haven't yet
been replaced with a Reigai.
And what about
the Head Captain?
I have a plan in mind for him,
don't you worry about that.
Of course, I will
need everyone's
help to achieve it.
To tell you the truth,
I don't care about that.
Whatever you ask of us,
I'll do it.
So how
about it?
Hurry up and let
me fight myself!
Eugh.
It's so revolting!
Barbarians are
just so eager to
turn to violence.
What?!
Not that I care whom a barbarian
chooses to fight, of course.
But don't go carving them
up too much, all right?
They're important you know.
They are my test subjects,
after all.
What are your thoughts,
Captain Kuchiki?
Only one can lead
the Kuchiki clan.
And that will be me.
Of course it will.
All your wishes will
soon be granted.
Just as soon as we
capture that girl.
And then, with our own hands,
we will be able to reshape
the world into what it
should rightfully be.
But so much trouble
for just one girl.
[gasp]
Heh...
All right, let's begin our Soul
Reaper impostor crisis meeting.
If it's okay,
I'll lead this one.
[Ichigo]
Wait!
Hmm?
[frustrated]
Gghh...
What? What's wrong, Ichigo?
You really need to ask?!
Why're we all
crammed in my room?!
Oh calm down!
[Mayuri]
Enough with the interruptions!
Get on with it, already!
Ugh.
The mastermind behind
this is Kageroza Inaba,
Seventh Seat in Squad Twelve.
A section chief in the
Department of Research
and Development.
He oversees research regarding
the Precipice World.
It's safe to say he knows
all there is to know about it.
[Mayuri]
Everything that's been
happening. has been planned
entirely by Kageroza.
He manipulated time in the
Precipice World so the
Cleaner would find us.
And we'd be confined there.
He also sent back Reigai
versions of us captains
to the Soul Society.
If he's left unchecked, all the
Thirteen Court Guard Squads
will be under his control.
Rrgh, it's very aggravating!
This Kageroza.
He lured me to the Soul Society
by manipulating the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads.
That was when he
tried to capture Nozomi.
I mean what the hell
could he be planning to
use that girl for, anyway?
[Rukia]
My guess is,
That girl is carrying
around some kind of secret.
It's something big.
It could be that what he
wants is something he's
hidden... in her body.
[gasp]
I won't let him.
I'll never let that
ever happen again!
[Kisuke]
Are you guys finding
everything all right?
[Orihime]
Yes, we are, Kisuke.
Thank you so much for letting
us use your barbecue stuff.
and for getting us
all this food, too!
No problem! Don't mention it.
I plan to come enjoy it myself!
Eehh??
I don't get it. Why are we
having a barbecue, again?
Well, it appears to me
that you're even dumber
than Ichigo is.
Hmm? Hey,
watch it!
You've seen how withdrawn
that girl Nozomi is.
Well, this is Orihime's way
of trying to cheer her up.
Clearly, she's
been though a lot.
Aah...
Okay I get it, but should
we really be doing this in
the middle of a crisis?
Actually, if our
party's successful,
she might finally open up
and help us understand
what's going on around here.
Gotcha.
Whew!
Come on, everyone!
Let's get started on this!
Uryu, could you cut
the vegetables?
And Chad, get the
fire started, okay?
[Uryu]
Got it!
[Chad]
[sffirmative grunt]
Huh?
I get it!
Hey! What, you
goofing off already?
Oh. That's right. Sorry.
Guess this is your
welcome party.
Anyway, I really want you
to tell me the truth.
And I'll help you
any way that I can.
Even if you don't want to
tell the others, you can
still tell me, you know!
'Cause I mean, after all,
I was the one who saved
your life!
Uh?
Uuhh...
Huh?
Hey, what is that? That thing
you're holding right there?
Oh, it's just chili powder!
Why do you have a
can of chili powder?
Oh, of course! I get it!
You don't know what
chili powder is, do you?
Admit it: I'm right!
Tell you what,
I'll teach you
what it is!
But let me warn you, it's
seriously spicy stuff if
you eat it straight.
Exactly! If you put it in your
mouth like that, you'll see-
It's hot!
Ah! My mouth is on fire!
Aahh! That's hot, too!
Hot! Hot! Hot! Hot!
Yaahhh!
Huh... Hrk?
What is this?!
Don't you get it?
Your stupid goofing around has
defiled the proud Quincy Cross!
But that's a
shiitake mushroom!!
(woozy reax)
I worked hard on that
shiitake, So eat it with the
respect that it deserves!
Uh, yes, sir...
You guys!
Nozomi just ran away!
What?! She's gone?!
Huh?
[Orihime]
Nozomi!
Hey, Nozomi!
Any luck?
No.
Where are you, Nozomi?!
Oh, man. This is hopeless!
Where the heck did that girl
run off to this time?!
Huh?
Nozomi!
Hey, hold on!
Wait for me!
We've been looking for you!
[stepped on]
Hnngh!
H'awww...
Wait, Nozomi.
Where do you think
you're going?!
Come have barbecue with us!
It's great!
No, thanks.
Aw, don't be like that.
Let's go back!
Everyone made
all that food,
and just for you!
C'mon, Nozomi!
Come back with me.
You know, everybody's
really worried about you!
Not my problem.
Huh??
Hrrgh! What is
wrong with you?!
We're only trying
to cheer you up!
We just thought that you'd
be scared because those
guys are coming after you!
How is that not your problem?!
Is this how you repay
other people's kindness?!
[panting]
Not my problem.
Dgh!
[growling]
Hey there, what are you doing?
What?!
[embarrassed]
Oh! Rangiku! Hi.
So... What's going on here?
You gotta hear
this, Rangiku!
That girl is stuck-up and
violent, she just runs off on
her own, and she doesn't
listen to anyone but herself!
I mean, we're trying
to look after her,
but she's totally
ungrateful!
Even I've had it with her,
and you know how calm I am!
Oh...
Whatever's going on,
it sure seems you're
having trouble, huh?
Hmm?
Hmm!
You know what, why
don't you let me
handle this one?
What...?
I know how difficult
girls her age can be.
We'll talk, girl
to girl. 'Kay?
What, seriously?!
Boy, would that help!
Oh, No, wait.
Everyone else is
looking for Nozomi, too...
Which means if I come back
without her, they'll just
get on my case again!
It'll be fine! I'm sure I
can convince her to come
back in just a little bit.
[grumble]
I don't know; I'm a man.
And a man must
keep his promises.
Come on.
Huh?
Let me handle this.
Pretty please?
All right, she's all yours!
Come on, Nozomi,
let's take a walk
and talk, okay?
Come along.
[stretching]
Aaahhh!
Such a relief that's over! Whew!
You know, if that girl were a
little more open and friendly,
she'd might even be cute.
[giddy]
But boy, that Rangiku,
she's...
Just let me handle this.
Pretty please?
OohhOOooOOohh!!
Rangiku...
What about me, Kon?
What?! Rangiku!?
But...! Rangiku,
why're you-?!
Where's Nozomi?!
What's that?
What do you mean?
I haven't seen her!
What...?
[gasp]
Oh!
Kon? What're
you doing here?
I thought you were
looking for--
Wha?
What's with him?
Damn it! This is all my fault!
I let her out of my sight.
It's a vital assignment.
We need you.
Rrgh!
[Nozomi]
[struggling] Let me go!
I said let me go!
[gasp]
Now, then.
We'll talk more on
the other side.
Eyagh!
Foolish girl!
Now you've done it!
You came back!
I'm sorry I took so long!
I saw through your disguise
right from the very start!
Stay out of this, got it? Ugh.
Stop, you impostor!
Damn you!
Run, Nozomi!
Impostor, huh?
[choking]
I'm no impostor!
From here on out,
we're going to be...
...the real ones!
Ah! Are
you--?!
Ngh!
Nozomi, hurry.
get out of here!
I'll defeat the impostor.
No problem.
You fool!
You can't stop her!
Nozomi...
I'm so sorry, I left
you alone like that.
You're sorry?
Rrrhyaaahh!
Well, that was weak.
Agh!
Did you think you could
defeat me with chili powder?
You underestimated me.
Now then. Shall we go, Nozomi?
[chuckle]
No! Stop!
But first...
You must be punished
for being a bad girl!
[gasp]
Huh?
[Kon]
Ichigo!
[Renji]
Don't move.
It's time to give it up,
you impostor!
[Rangiku]
Hmm.
Uh!
So this is my
impostor, huh?
She's quite a
good-looking woman.
Hmph. But no match
for the original.
Tch.
Growl...
Haineko!
Damn it. She got away.
Nozomi!
I'm glad you're okay.
Of course, it was all
thanks to my awesome and
timely assistance.
Where's the thanks?!
Ha ha ha ha!
Ulp!
Hey!
What're you talking about?
This all started 'cause
you took your eyes off
her in the first place!
Uuh--
What made you think it was
a good idea to leave her?!
Wasn't Rukia clear enough?!
Well, I...
It's just that...
I, uh...
Pervert.
No, I! I'm not a--!
Hey, Ichigo!
You too, Nozomi!
The food is all ready!
Here, I'll bring it
over to them for you!
That Kon.
Look, don't worry
about it, Nozomi.
Uh?
From here on, we'll protect you.
Are all of you
really this stupid?
Yeah, maybe!
[Kon]
Nozomi...
Have a shish-kebab!
It's tasty!
C'mon, try it!
[chuckling]
[Kisuke]
This sure is a mess.
[Mayuri]
Indeed. Two Marechiyo Omaedas
means twice the fried rice
cracker consumption.
[Kisuke]
[sigh]
Uh huh...
[Mayuri]
Two Rangiku Matsumotos means two
Soul Reapers who won't do work,
Uh-huh, uh-huh...
while two Kenpachi Zarakis
means double the destruction!
Enough!