[theme music]
-Excuse me, guard?
-Yeah?
What do you want?
[gasp]
GUARD (VOICE OVER):
Sweet flowers?
[music playing]
AIZEN (VOICE OVER): If you
are reading this letter,
then I am probably
no longer alive.
There is no one in Seireitei
whom I trust as much as you,
so I've written you
this letter to document
the truth I've uncovered.
MOMO (VOICE OVER): When I first
read the Captain's letter,
I couldn't believe my eyes.
How could something like
that possibly be true?
I didn't want to believe
it, but know I know.
It is true.
Everything he wrote was true.
The one who murdered Captain
Aizen, it was-- [sobbing]
[wind blowing]
-Eat.
If you can faint from
hunger, then that obviously
means that you have it, right?
The power.
-So you have it, too?
-Yes, just like you.
My name is Gin.
I'm pleased to meet you.
-Gin?
What a strange name.
-So your finally awake.
-Captain, I-- what are
you doing here in my room?
-Better take a
look around, idiot.
You're in the office,
not your room.
Since you're awake,
you can take over.
I'm completely exhausted.
-Maybe if you hadn't done all
the paperwork for Squad 5's
takeover yourself, you
wouldn't be so exhausted.
-Be quiet and just
finish it off, will you?
-It seems like you've
left out a few things.
What about all the details of--
-Didn't I tell
you to keep quiet?
RANGIKU (OFFSCREEN): I, uh--
I've been asleep a long time,
haven't I?
HITSUGAYA (OFFSCREEN):
Don't worry about it.
You have a classmate who's
fighting with your junior.
That can't be easy for you.
RANGIKU (VOICE
OVER): My classmate?
Captain, do you honestly
think he could have done it?
Was Gin really capable of that?
KOKICHIRO (OFFSCREEN):
Excuse me, sir.
I am Kokichiro Takezoe,
Squad 10, 7th Seat.
I'm looking for Captain
Hitsugaya and Lieutenant
Matsumoto.
May I come in?
-Yes.
What do you want?
-Sir, I beg your pardon, but
this is an urgent matter.
There's been an incident
at the prison that
requires your
immediate attention.
Sir, Lieutenant Abarai and
Lieutenant Hinamori, as well as
Lieutenant Kira, sir.
All of them have vanished
from their cells.
-Please forgive me, sir.
It all happened so quickly.
Lieutenant Hinamori
called out to me,
and when I turned
around, I was blinded
by ant intense white light.
That's all I remember.
When I woke up,
they were all gone.
I have no excuse, sir.
-It was Hakufuku.
-Hakufuku?
-I should've remembered that
Momo was a master of Kido.
If we had been serious about
wanting to restrain her,
we would have made
certain that we
sealed her spiritual
pressure, but we didn't even
think of taking that action.
We had no reason
because none of us
actually believed she would
ever take things this far.
-It's not as if she were being
threatened with execution,
so why would--
-There's only one explanation
that makes any sense.
-Huh?
-Rangiku.
-Yes?
-You're to go home.
That's an order.
I only hope I'm in
time to save Momo.
HITSUGAYA (VOICE OVER): Momo,
don't do anything stupid!
YORUICHI (VOICE OVER): He's now
able to maintain his stance,
even when his sword breaks.
Hurry, Ichigo.
You're running out of time.
-That was number 51.
[music playing]
-This time for sure!
[yelling]
-Remember, never take
your eyes off the enemy.
That makes number 52.
-Damn it.
I almost had the
bastard that time.
YORUICHI (VOICE OVER):
Ichigo, at the exact moment
of impact, you adjusted
to the enemy speed
and were able to
deflect his blade.
Then without missing a
beat, you instantaneously
countered with your
own unique attack.
It's obvious that you
no longer rely solely
on the power of Zanjutsu.
He's absorbing it with amazing
speed at an incredible level.
Kisuke, you were
absolutely right.
The boy truly is--
-Ah-- ah-choo!
Oh!
-That's not good.
Have you caught a cold, boss?
-No, I'm sure there's probably
just a pretty girl talking
about me somewhere.
-Somehow I find that
hard to believe.
-I'm sorry, did
you say something?
-No, no.
Uh, nothing.
You know, I just happen to
have a little remedy that'll
knock that cold right out.
-Uh, remedy?
Are you nuts?
This expired two years ago!
TESSAI (OFFSCREEN): It's
nicely aged like a fine wine.
KISUKE (OFFSCREEN): No, no!
I'm not going to swallow that.
TESSAI (OFFSCREEN): Yeah!
KISUKE (OFFSCREEN): No, no!
No, stop!
TESSAI (OFFSCREEN):
Drink, drink.
Don't be a baby.
TESSAI (OFFSCREEN): Get
that stuff away from me!
What are you, some
kind of witch doctor?
Get away!
-Damn it!
Still not it!
ICHIGO (VOICE OVER):
I have to do this.
I got to if I want
to save Rukia!
AIZEN (VOICE OVER):
What purpose does it
serve to have Rukia
Kuchiki executed?
And why do they keep moving
up the date of the execution?
In my search for the
answers to these questions,
I came upon the truth.
I want you to have
it in my place.
[music playing]
MOMO (VOICE OVER):
Captain Aizen!
-He's been able to fight with
that once sword for over five
minutes now without breaking it.
But still, everything
must come to an end.
-Here it goes!
[yelling]
Huh?
Uh--
-You've done enough fighting.
Rest now.
Put your sword down.
Day one is over.
-This way, sir.
-It can't be.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): I had no
idea it was night already.
Man, this place is
so disorienting.
I never know what time it is.
Huh?
What's with this hot spring?
My scars healing like crazy!
This is freaking awesome!
What'll it do if I drink it?
YORUICHI (OFFSCREEN): Ichigo.
-Hmm?
-How's the water?
Everything all right?
[mumbling]
-Nice, huh?
I'm glad to hear it.
[mumbling]
-In fact, it sounds so
good I think I'll join you.
-Yahhh!
[coughing] Are you nuts!
What are you doing?
YORUICHI (OFFSCREEN): Why?
What do you mean?
Is something wrong?
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
Yeah, something's wrong!
You just took your pants off!
YORUICHI (OFFSCREEN):
What's the big deal?
Come on, loosen up, Ichigo.
Don't be so old fashioned.
You're such a prude.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Cut--
cut it out, will you?
Stop making fun of me!
Ah, no!
Don't come in!
No, no!
-I don't know what you're
getting so worked up about.
-Uh--
-What?
Are you a little disappointed?
Come on, be honest.
You are, aren't you?
You little pervert.
-I am going to drown you!
[music playing]
-Hey, this place looks familiar.
-How's that?
-I've been thinking
about it for a while now,
and I finally figured out
what it reminds me of.
It looks like the training
room under Uda Harashah.
-You picked up on that, huh?
We tried to model that
place after this one
when we built it.
-You built this place?
YORUICHI (OFFSCREEN): Yeah.
When Kisuke and I were kids,
we needed a place to play,
so we snuck off and
built this place.
It was our own little
secret hideout.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
Secret hideout?
this place is huge!
How'd you ever keep it a secret?
-It's a very long story.
Back when the two
of us were kids,
we used to play here
almost every day.
When we got older, he joined
the 13th Court Guard Squad
and I joined the Stealth
Force, but we'd still
come here to hone our skills.
-Wait a minute, Yoruichi.
You mean you two used to-- yaaa!
You scared the hell out of me!
Can't you even cross your legs?
YORUICHI (OFFSCREEN): I
always get the same reaction.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
Yeah, just tell me more
about Mr. Hat-and-Clogs.
The truth, now.
The guy's really a
Soul Reaper, isn't he?
-Mm-hum.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
I always wondered
how he knew so much
about the Soul Society,
not to mention the fact
that he had a Zanpakuto.
I want to know, Yoruichi.
I want to know the truth
about the guy who trained me.
-All right, then.
He's the former
Captain of Squad 12
of the 13 Court Guard
Squads In addition to that,
he's the one who
conceived and founded
the Department of
Research and Development
and served as its first Chief.
-Are you serious?
I had no idea Mr. Hat-and-Clogs
was such a hot shot.
[music playing]
-I figured as much.
KISUKE (OFFSCREEN):
That stuff was horrible!
You trying to kill me?
Oh!
-Don't worry, I've
got a remedy that'll
take care of that
stomach of yours.
I'll get some from the guard.
Sit tight.
I'll be right back.
KISUKE (OFFSCREEN): That's it!
Oh, you really are trying
to kill me, aren't you?
Ohh!
-I wonder about those guys.
HITSUGAYA (OFFSCREEN):
I suspected
I'd find you together.
-Captain Hitsugaya!
I--
-Hmm.
I figured you were behind
this, because out of the three,
Izuru's was the
only cell that had
been opened from the outside.
If you didn't want
to get caught,
you should have
been more careful.
That was careless
even for you, Gin.
-It's funny that
you would accuse me
of being careless when
the fact of the matter
is I left him that way on
purpose so that you'd know.
-It's a good thing I
arrived before Momo.
I'll kill you before
she gets here.
Your blood will be on my hands.
Momo, no!
-I found you just in time.
I'm glad I'm not too late.
-Don't do this, Momo!
You're no match for him.
You'll just wind up dead.
Now stand back and
let me handle this!
What do you think you're doing?
-I'm about to take
revenge for Captain Aizen.
Why, Toshiro?
Why did you kill him?
There's no need to pretend.
I know everything.
The Captain wrote it all down.
It's here in this letter.
AIZEN (VOICE OVER):
Momo, the true purpose
for this execution is not
to kill Rukia Kuchiki.
She's merely a pawn in
a much larger scheme.
The execution was
contrived in order
to steal a certain object,
an object of great value,
the Sokyoku.
The Sokyoku's seal is broken
only for an execution.
In that one blade lies the
destructive power of a million
Zanpakuto.
It possess the defensive
ability to block
Zanpakuto of equal power.
More importantly,
when a Soul reaper
is crucified and then
stabbed with Sokyoku,
the blade's power grows
exponentially dozens of times
over.
The one who plotted
this execution
plans to use this power
to destroy the Seireitei.
Once that's done, they intend
to obliterate the entire Soul
Society as well.
-He wrote it down, the
name of the person,
the one who intended
to do all of this.
Toshiro Hitsugaya.
The letter goes on to say--
AIZEN (VOICE OVER): I have
no choice but to confront him
about this, so
I've called him out
to the sacred
Eastern Wall tonight.
I must do whatever
it takes to stop him.
-"If I cannot persuade him
to abandon this evil plan,
then I'm resolved to fight him.
If I should die,
then it's up to you.
You must find a way to
accomplish what I could not,
kill him and save the Seireitei.
Please, this is
my final request.
I ask not as the
Captain of Squad 5,
but merely as a humble man.
Please, I beg of you--"
-Momo, let's not--
-[yelling]
-Don't be a fool!
Think about what you're saying!
If he dies, he wants you
to risk your life as well?
Do you honestly believe
Captain Aizen would say that?
The Captain Aizen
I know would never
be stupid enough to face
unbeatable odds alone,
and if he did, he
certainly wasn't
a coward who would ask
his men to bail him out
because he couldn't
get the job done!
-I know.
But the Captain wrote
it all in his letter.
He did!
And I know it was
his handwriting.
I recognized it.
I didn't want to believe
it either, but it's true!
And this is what he wanted me
to do, so I'm going to do it!
I can't do it.
I can't!
[sobbing] I'm so confused.
I don't know what to do anymore.
I don't know what
to do, little Shiro.
-Momo, you can't.
-[screaming]
HITSUGAYA (VOICE OVER):
I can't reason with her.
No matter what I say, it
just doesn't get through.
She's too upset to
think rationally,
but I know I'm right.
Aizen would never write
a letter like that.
Someone must have forged
it so that Momo and I would
try to kill each other.
[music playing]
Of course.
Damn him!
Only one person is
capable of doing all this,
and now you'll pay!
[music playing]
Momo!
-Oh, my.
Who's have thought the Squad
10 Captain could be so cruel?
The girl was obviously suffering
from emotional distress,
so why'd you have to hit to
poor little thing so hard?
-Gin.
GIN (VOICE OVER): The
warning certainly came
at a convenient time for you.
-What exactly are
you after, Gin?
HITSUGAYA (VOICE OVER): The
words you spoke that day,
they're etched into my memory.
GIN (VOICE OVER):
You're always the same.
You need to stop and
listen more often.
You wouldn't want to
miss the last alarm, now.
It won't be long before you'll
never be able to hear it again.
-So Aizen wasn't enough for you.
You couldn't be happy until
you'd hurt Momo as well.
You slid your lies into
her mind like a dagger
and twisted them until they were
so painful that her hands bled
from gripping her sword so hard.
-I'm sorry, I'm afraid
I don't follow you.
-I gave you a warning.
I told you that if
you never hurt Mom,
I would kill you myself!
-This will never do.
If you insist on drawing your
sword in a place like this,
then I'm afraid you leave me no
other choice than to stop you.
[music playing]
[theme music]
TESSAI (VOICE OVER): Boss,
you got to trust me this time.
I've got the perfect cure.
It's all natural.
KISUKE (VOICE OVER):
Uh, no thanks.
I'm feeling much better.
TESSAI (VOICE OVER):
I read about it
in the back of a manga.
It's the latest
Chinese medicine.
I got it mail order.
KISUKE (VOICE OVER): Look, I
don't know if I trust that.
I--
TESSAI (VOICE OVER): It says
it'll cure what ails you.