[theme song]
-After Izuru Kira
defeated Makoto Kibune,
Renji delivered Makoto's
bakoto to Head Captain Yamamoto
to convince him of
Gyokaku Kumoi's treason.
The head captain then commanded
the 13 Court Guard Squads
to storm the Kasumioji
Clan's palace
to find further evidence.
Kumoi instructed his
band of assassins
to hold off the Soul
Reapers as he attempted
to make his escape,
but Yoruichi's actions
prevented him from getting away.
Having taken Rurichiyo
as his hostage,
Kumoi found himself
cornered and decided
that threatening to kill the
princess was his only way out.
-[laughing]
-Stop it!
-Huh?
-It's Captain Amagai.
-What's going on here?
What did you just do?
-You've been most
helpful, Soul Reaper.
-What do you mean,
I've been helpful?
-Ichigo!
-Rurichiyo!
-See you around.
-What the hell did he just do?
-I have never seen
a Kido like that.
It's like he used a technique
to relocate while completely
suppressing his
spiritual pressure.
-So?
-So it's not good.
There's no way for
us to follow him.
-We've got to find him!
He's got Rurichiyo!
-What brings you here?
Well, Captain?
You arrive here announced with
the Rurichiyo Clan's princess
in tow and look rather serious.
State your business.
-I thought you would know.
Though now that I think of
it, I suppose you wouldn't.
You would probably
never even dream
that someone in the Soul
Society would come here
with the intention
of killing you.
-You want to kill me?
-Tell me, for what reason?
-For Shin'etsu Kisaragi.
-Shin'etsu?
-Don't tell me you've
forgotten about him.
So now I've come here from hell
on Shin'etsu Kisaragi's behalf
to vanquish you.
Bloom in glory, Benishidare!
-Damn.
I thought I'd suppressed
my spiritual pressure.
Just what I would expect from
the princess's guardians.
But your efforts are in vain.
-Silence!
Benishidare, Sange!
-Princess!
Quickly, run!
-That won't work.
-[yelling] [inaudible]!
-What?
-[groan]
-Princess!
-Kenryu!
-You're finally safe now,
with nothing to fear.
-Princess!
-Thank goodness.
-Hi!
-Oh, Enryu!
This is great.
Now I know what your
voice sounds like.
There's no need to blush.
You have a fine voice.
-Pardon me, princess, but
we must be on our way.
-Right.
Of course.
-[scream]
-Oh, no, Enryu!
-Shusuke.
Just what are you
intending to do with that?
-Allow me to show you.
I now hold the bakoto's core.
Until now, all the battles
were with the intent
of allowing this core to
absorb the spiritual energy
of the strong.
But the time has come
to take this core
and feed it to my bakoto.
Witness a display
of its true power.
-So that's what you were
up to all this time.
You were after the
bakoto as well.
-That's correct.
-You are foolish!
Now all things in the
universe turn to ashes!
Ryujin Jakka!
Prepare yourself,
Shusuke Amagai!
-[yells]
-How did you-- explain this!
What have you done?
-The strength to cancel
the power of Soul Reapers.
My bakoto possesses
that ability.
As long as this
bakoto is functioning,
all of your zanpakutos will be
rendered powerless and useless.
All except for my
zanpakuto Raika.
Bankai!
Raika Goen Kaku!
[yelling]
-Are you all right?
Kenryu?
Enryu?
-Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
-So you're still alive.
-[growl]
-Don't give me that
look, unless you
want to be the first to die.
-Shusuke, leave them be.
You said your purpose in
coming here was to kill me.
Those three have
nothing to do with it.
They are innocent.
-They're innocent?
You're dead wrong.
You're not the only one who will
feel the sting of my revenge!
I'll kill the heir to
the Kasumioji Clan!
None of you will live!
Now perish!
-Rurichiyo!
-Huh?
-[growling]
-Ichigo!
-Sorry I was late again.
-Explain.
How did you find us?
-Kenryu somehow left
behind a Hell Butterfly.
-So it made it in time.
-What's up?
What's keeping you
from fighting him?
-He's already tried
to, but he can't,
because my bakoto cancels out
the power of Soul Reapers.
-What?
-His flame attack
has no effect on me.
[laughing]
-So, Shusuke.
I don't want to believe it, but
you're our enemy, aren't you?
Who the hell are you?
[sounds of fighting]
-Byakuya, are you done here?
-The lieutenants are
mopping up what's
left of the enemy forces.
-And your squad?
-We've taken control
of the bakoto workshop.
Captain Soi Fon is protecting
the site as we speak.
-More importantly,
where is Shusuke Amagai?
-Shusuke?
He entered the compound
when Ikkaku and others first
stormed in.
But come to think of it,
I haven't seen him since.
-Where is he?
-Why are you so
concerned about him?
-He orchestrated this entire
incident to gain power.
-What?
YORUICHI (VOICEOVER):
Allow me to explain.
Kisuke contacted me and
requested I thoroughly
examine the ongoing
confusion regarding
the logistics of
the Soul Society.
I began looking into
every aspect I could,
and while doing that, I
uncovered information that
revealed the Kasumioji
Clan's dark side.
I found out that Kumoi was
the first to create a bakoto.
He applied the clan's secret
techniques developed over
centuries for the royal
family, and continued
to produce superior weaponry.
The bakoto allows its bearer
to gain strength and fighting
power far beyond its bearer's
abilities, but wielding it
can be fatal.
-We're not certain of
where Shusuke first
learned of the
bakoto's existence,
but once he learned
of it, he approached
Kumoi with the express
purpose of having it.
-He set into motion
his own grand plan
knowing that his
possession of the bakoto
was the key element
to it succeeding.
-To make that happen, he knew
he must become a squad captain
so he would have complete
knowledge of the movements
of both the Soul Reapers
and the Soul Society.
-And so Shusuke connived a
plan to become a captain,
knowing that would
advance his plan.
Right after he became
a captain, an incident
occurred in which a
restrictive current shutdown
request was ignored.
By discreetly
voiding that request,
Shusuke created a chance to
show off his powers to his squad
and won their confidence.
He then met with the other
captains, gaining their trust,
and advocated cooperation
between their squads
and established training
exercises to create unity.
But his real reason
for doing that
was to analyze the fighting
ability of each squad.
As he think carefully prepared
to put his plan in motion,
an unexpected
windfall came to him.
-Ichigo Kurosaki?
-Correct.
Originally, he intended to
take even more time to make
his move, but
Ichigo's intervention
caused upheaval for
the Soul Society.
He fanned Gyokaku
Kumoi's ambitious nature,
and by overstating the conflict,
he plunged the Soul Society
into utter confusion and chaos.
He then used the Kasumioji
Clan's assassin squad
to make things worse,
and hand picked
his third seat, Makoto
Kibune, to wreak havoc.
-But I heard when they
fought, Lieutenant Kira
succeeded in defeating
Third Seat Kibune.
-Izuru?
-Makoto's defeat was
the first instance
in which Shusuke's plan
suffered a setback.
Apparently, Amagai
didn't foresee
Izuru winning that battle.
-Guess he underestimated
Izuru's tenacity.
-We know Shusuke Amagai went
to all kinds of extremes
with this, but for what?
-I have an idea why.
-Shin'etsu Kisaragi?
Enlighten me as to how it
is that you know that name.
-To me, that name is special.
You see, that was the
name of my father.
-That's right.
My father was
Shin'etsu Kisaragi.
My father was the Soul
Reaper that you murdered.
-Head Captain
Yamamoto killed him?
-Hey, old man, is there
anything to what he's saying?
-He speaks the truth.
Indeed, I did kill a soul
reaper whose name was
Shin'etsu Kisaragi.
-[yelling]
-I remember that time and place,
but how did you find out I
killed your father?
-He lived for several hours
after you left him for dead
in the field.
That last day, my father
had been acting strangely,
so I decided to go
looking for him.
-Father?
AMAGAI (VOICEOVER):
I knew my father
trained with his
zanpakuto in that field.
-Father?
Father, no!
Not you!
Why?
Father, please open your eyes!
Please don't die!
-With his dying
breath, he told me.
He said it clearly.
He said that you
had cut him down.
-That can't be.
-Old man?
-It is true.
He killed his
subordinate, my father!
-Several years after his
death, I changed my name,
enlisted in the 13
Court Guard Squads,
and lied that I was
from the Rukon district.
I did it to find out the
truth about my father's death.
I gathered many facts.
And then I recalled a word.
The bakoto.
That was the last word
my father ever spoke.
What was a bakoto?
Why did my father need
me to hear that word?
It took years for
me to understand,
but slowly, it all
fell into place.
Somehow, my father had stumbled
onto the bakoto's existence,
and it appears he was trying
to unmask its mystery.
So to learn the truth
about the bakoto,
he infiltrated
the Kasumioji Clan
and found himself
in over his head.
-You were an accomplice of the
Kasumioji Clan in those days.
You were also involved in
the bakoto's development.
My father was quite
aware of your actions,
so you decided that
you had to silence him!
In the years that
followed, there
were many more suspicious
decisions and activities
sponsored by the Kasumioji Clan,
but you refused to interfere.
I saw it all, and
swore I'd make you pay.
Through all those years,
as I was training myself,
all I could think about
was seeing you crushed.
Then I aligned myself
with the Kasumioji Clan
and was given the bakoto.
My prominent service in the
expedition unit was noticed.
That led to me being
promoted to Captain,
creating this long
sought after opportunity.
My time is now!
I will avenge my father!
[growl]
-I know you.
-Yes, you're Shu Kannogi.
Rurichiyo Kasumioji
is betrothed to you.
-And all of you are Soul
Reaper squad captains, right?
-Yes, we are.
Why have you come here alone?
-I'm here to beg you to
help Ichigo and the others.
-What?
-Ichigo and Rukia are
trying to catch up
with Rurichiyo and
Captain Amagai, who's
gone after the Head Captain.
-[growling]
-Stay out of my way, Ichigo!
Enough!
-Knock it off!
I've been here the
whole time, and I
heard all of your completely
self-centered nonsense!
-Every word I said
was the truth!
-I'm not arguing that what
you said was the truth.
Your selfish, destructive
actions have ripped apart a lot
of innocent people's lives,
including Rurichiyo's.
Where's the justice in that?
-Ichigo.
-She's been threatened
so many times
that her life's just an
endless, terrifying nightmare.
She wants to be free
to live her life!
Get your revenge, but
leave her out of it.
Don't involve other
people in your business!
-You just don't get it!
You cannot save her!
Don't act like an idiot!
Move it!
-I don't think you
understand what's going on.
You say you want me to move?
Well, you're gonna
have to make me do it!
[theme song]
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
What's up, Yoruichi?
Why didn't you tell
us you were here, too?
YORUICHI (VOICEOVER):
[laughs] Sorry,
but I'm all about
working secretly
undercover behind the scenes.
Want to know why?
I like seeing that surprised
look on everyone's face
when I show up so unexpectedly.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
Just for that?
YORUICHI (VOICEOVER):
Just for that.