The reason is, because
you're a human and--
Your Spirit Energy
works very well.
I'm very pleased.
You've matured
splendidly.
Just the way I wanted you to.
Eh? What?!
The truth is, Ichigo Kurosaki,
All of the battles you've
fought up to now,
were simply a
part of my plan.
Eh heh, heh heh heh.
Who the hell are you?
Hirako, answer me!
[gasp]
What do you see? Tell me.
Try and, guess, if ya can?
A Hollow mask!
Yes. A Zanpakuto,
and a Hollow mask.
You get it now?
You see, I'm a Visored.
You're one of us, Ichigo.
You do not belong with them.
You have got to know that you do
not belong with them at all.
Lord Aizen.
It appears Shinji Hirako
has made contact with
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I see.
What's your next move?
Let's see.
Contact Ulquiorra.
Let's have him go to
the World of the Living.
Yes sir!
So Captain.
I see that you're
still quite cautious.
Bankai!!
Tensa Zangetsu.
[Ulquiorra]
The orange hair,
The black Bankai,
There's no doubt about it.
This is our target, Yammy,
he's the one.
So he saved us the trouble
of searching for him, hah!
Que Suerute!
Hmm?
Auuggghh!
[panting]
Damn! You little runt!
I can't believe you need
your Zanpakuto to deal
with a runt like this.
Shut up and
stay back!
That's a Zanpakuto?
I should have known!
His sword is a Zanpakuto!
The cracked Hollow mask...
the hole in his chest and
the Zanpakuto...
I knew I felt something
odd about their
Spiritual Pressure!
[Ichigo]
Who are these guys!?
Are they visoreds!?
Like Shinji and me?
Huuuah!
Damn it, I can't move my body!
I rejected you, so now
you wanna get in my
way and sabotage me?!
Damn it!
Time for you to disappear!
Hey there!
Sorry I couldn't get
here sooner, Ichigo.
You know how it is.
[Ulquiorra]
we've completed
our mission here.
It's time we deliver our
report to Lord Aizen.
I'll tell him the Soul
Reaper he's interested in
has no value whatsoever.
He's not even worth killing.
[Shinji]
Good job finding
this place, Ichigo.
My, so serious?
[chuckles]
Ah hah hah hah hah!
I wonder what that means?
Wait! Have you finally
decided to join us?
I'm sort of impressed
you found our hideout.
RrrraAAAAHHH!
Impossible!
[panting]
GrrrraAAAHH!!
He finally mastered
Hollowfication.
He's developed quickly.
I suppose that's to be expected.
Lord Aizen.
Yes, what is it?
Sir. I've made sure
everything is ready.
I see.
So this is it.
Sir?
Nothing.
It's not
important.
I will leave the
rest to Ulquiorra.
[Ichigo]
Get up...
Get up!
I have to get up!
I promise... I will...
I will protect you!!
Impossible!
With his bare hand?!
[animal roar]
Graaahh!!!
You said all of the
battles I fought,
were planned by you?!
What exactly,
do you mean
by that?
I just asked you what you
meant, now answer me!
Your voice.
Nh?
You don't have to
raise your voice.
There's no need for that.
There's nothing to
be surprised about.
Allow me to explain.
I made a conscious
decision about you.
I decided to actively
assist your development,
because I believed that
you would be a great
research subject.
That is all I am saying.
[gasp]
Didn't you ever think
it was strange?
You had never seen or even
heard of Hollows until you
met Rukia Kuchiki,
And yet, within a few days
after meeting her, you found
yourself attacked by one.
How do you suppose a Menos
Grande was drawn to that
Quincy's bait which could only
attract low-level Hollows?
Once you started getting
used to fighting as a Soul
Reaper, a very significant
event occurred.
Do you think it was a
coincidence that Rukia
Kuchiki's previously
undetected Spiritual Pressure
was suddenly detected and
reported to the Soul Society?
You battled Renji Abarai,
Kenpachi Zaraki,
Byakuya Kuchiki.
Don't you find it strange that
against all these highly trained
and formidable warriors,
your power was somehow
comparable to theirs?
I was in control of
all those events.
[gasp]
You thought all that
happened by chance?
Hold on.
You thought that attack
was simply your fate?
Wait...
Your victories weren't
because of your hard work.
Grrahh!
Don't disappoint me.
By this point, your
power should be much
greater than this.
So now do you
believe what I've
just told you?
Of course I don't!
Well, It's the truth.
You're lying!
You planned all of my battles??
All of them were your doing?!
You controlled them!?
You really expect me
to believe all that?!
You said before that when
you first found Rukia,
it was after she went
missing in the World of
the Living! Remember?
And yet now you say that
you knew about me since
the time I met her?!
That doesn't make any sense!
I knew you'd say that.
You heard what I said
and called me a liar.
Now you refuse to believe
what I've shared.
Your mind may not want to
accept these revelations.
But inside you there's
a voice saying,
"Accept it- It's the truth."
Soon you'll know.
Time will help.
I feel sorry about
your confusion.
But this world's never really
been about truth or lies.
In this world, there's
only one thing that's
worth knowing;
Hard facts.
Despite this
universal truth,
people misguidedly
choose to only accept
the facts that appeal to
their way of thinking.
They're so limited, they can
only accept the truths that
are comfortable for them.
So, this is simply
about wanting to hang on
to your personal power.
Realizing things may not have
been as we accepted them to be
unsettles us; it's overwhelming.
Are you absolutely sure
that you know the truth?
Do you know who stationed
Rukia Kuchiki in the
World of the Living?
Or who endowed Renji Abarai's
gear with the ability to detect
Spiritual Pressure?
And then, who was it that added
the information on your
whereabouts to that report that
was sent to the Lieutenants?
You think I wasn't able to
find where the Hogyoku was
for over a hundred years?
Do you really find that
completely believable?
Aizen. One thing.
I want to ask you.
You said that you
believed that I would be
a great research subject.
Why did you think that?
What did you base that
thinking on?
You're claiming you saw me
when I met Rukia. So tell me,
When the hell did I become
a project for you?!
Since the beginning.
Stop with that nonsense.
Listen to me.
I'm saying from
when you were born.
When I said "since the
beginning", I meant I've known
about you since you were born.
What?!
The moment you were born,
I knew you were a special case.
The reason is, because
you're a human, and--
Tch.
You talk too much... Aizen.
The reason is, because
you're a human, and--
"I'm human and" what?
The rest of what he said was
drowned out by the noise.
I thought I'd lost my
chance to hear it.
But I was wrong.
I never needed to
hear his words.
Because right before my eyes,
the answer soon appeared.
Dad? Is that...you?
Hey! Say something.
Dad?
Haiigh!
What the hellll!!!!
Hmph.
Keeping his distance.
A wise decision.
Must be in their blood.
[muffled shouting]
Shut up! I know what
you want to ask!
Be quiet or I'll--
[gasping inhale]
I know that I have to
be quiet, you idiot!
I was yelling to you
I couldn't breathe!
Oh! S-Sorry!
[rubbing off pain grunt]
Mmh. You're not imaging this.
I'm really here.
Yeah, so it seems.
We'll talk later.
There's gotta be a ton
of things you want to
ask me about. But to
tell the truth there's--
No, not really.
Hm?!
There's nothing I wanna ask.
You probably had your reasons
for not telling me
about everything.
You had problems you
didn't want to talk about.
There's no good
way for me to ask
you about them.
And I don't want to rip your
heart out with questions
right now. I'm sure one day
we'll get around to it.
I can wait.
Until you feel like
telling me about it all.
Whenever you decide
that the time is right.
You can choose when we'll have
our little conversation.
Sounds like you've matured.
Seems you've learned to be
more patient.
Guess I have.
I guess you could say
somebody else has taught me a
lot of good habits that have
changed me for the better.
Thanks for hitting me
so hard up there, dad.
I feel like...
I've finally
come back home.
Heh. Ichigo,
I didn't hit you,
I head-butted you.
Hitting or head-butting,
What's the difference?
Way to ruin the mood, old man.
They hid their pressures.
And have created a pretty
powerful barrier.
You've been watching for quite
a long time, haven't you, Gin?
You shouldn't assume
I've just been watching.
I just didn't think you needed
my assistance with him yet.
I see.
[battle shout]
T'heeeyaaahh!
Huh?
[gasp]
It's been a while since
I've fought you hasn't it?
This time, I won't
be holding back.
[Isshin]
Say Ichigo! You sure you
don't want to ask me?
[Ichigo]
Yeah.
[Isshin]
You sure?
[Ichigo]
Yeah.
[Isshin]
Really? You don't want
to know what happened in
your daddy's past?
[Ichigo]
I said I'm fine!
[Isshin]
Aw really?! Come on,
are you like SURE sure?
[Ichigo]
You want me to
ask, don't you?