Believe me, I do not want
to have to kill you...
How dare you!
Welcome Sosuke,
To the inverted world.
Suzumushi Hyakushiki.
Grillado Grillo!
At last, I can see...
I can see..!!
Heh.
Yah hah hah hah!
I can see, Sajin!
I can see, I can see!
So that is the sky!
So this is blood!
And so that is what
you look like, Sajin.
You're not how I imagined.
You're much, much uglier.
Heh.
When? When did you
become like this?
You seem shocked by my new
form... Preparing to give up?
So I'm ugly to you?
Well. I remember you telling
me once just how much you
personally were disgusted by
what you saw in the mirror.
Did it bother you to hear
those words coming from me?
That's not it.
Then what is it?
I pity you.
Why's that?
Before this, your vision
was unobstructed.
Now it seems you
are truly blind.
Your words have no meaning.
I can see clearly now.
See for yourself!
So explain this!
What are you
witnessing now?!
Is my attack the attack
of someone stumbling
around in the dark?!
What is your answer
to that, Sajin!??
Ngyahh.
What's wrong?
I thought you could see
things better than I could?
Your sword has a most
interesting shape.
Nice huh? You can't borrow it.
We'll see. I don't sense
anything different here.
Didn't you tell me
before that it takes
over a person's senses?
What are you talking about?
The change is already in effect.
Mmh?
Ohh... What is that?
Do you smell
something good?
[gasp]
It's too late to
hold your breath.
Heh. Welcome, Sosuke,
...to the inverted world.
Kaname...
Believe me, I don't want
to have to kill you...
But I can tell now that
you've lost your ability to
see the world as it is...
I'm forced to kill you
in the name of justice!
Did you say, "justice"?
How dare you!
You have lost the true vision
you had as a Soul Reaper.
You know I am telling
you the truth.
(Sl. Straining CT Exhale)
All those years, even though
you were blind, you always
had a way of understanding
things, and seeing reality.
You saw the dark and the
light in others and you
fought as a warrior, as
if you had perfect sight!
You're so sure of yourself,
But you know nothing about me!
What changed you?!
What was it that made you
decide to close your eyes to
the world before you?!
Silence!
You show me disrespect!
Now I can clearly see
how ugly you really are!
Raaghh!
I told you, you may
now possess sight,
Yet it appears you are
now more blind than ever.
You refuse to see the
essence of my being.
My true essence is far beyond
my physical appearance, Instead
I ask you to look further.
Gaze deeply...
Into my heart....
"Into your heart"?
Don't act as if you
understand my life.
Your heart?
What heart is that?
Ridiculous.
I'll give you one last
chance to understand!
Where is my heart?!
Can you see it?
I'm curious, Why did
you choose to become
a soul reaper?
To repay a debt of
gratitude to the one
who saved my life.
Repaying a debt.
That sounds like you.
And what about
you, Kaname?
Me?... Well...
It's For justice.
I dedicated my life to
this all because of her.
She loved this world,
So I became a Soul Reaper
to bring justice to it.
I couldn't sit by and watch
the justice she fought for
just simply disappear.
When she died, I decided I had
to carry on her heart's desire.
That's why I did it,
She is why I became
a Soul Reaper.
Kaname...
At that time, I noted,
There was something you
didn't say that made an
impression on me.
You talked a lot
about how she felt,
how she loved the world.
But you never called it...
the world YOU love.
That was when I realized,
your heart is filled with
hate for this world...
I fully understood
your feelings.
In fact, I would have
felt the same way.
Anyone would feel like that
if they had lost a loved one.
I was glad to know that
you had real feelings,
and weren't some saint
who could say that he
still loved the world
in spite of what had
happened to your
dearest companion.
That was the reason I
decided to reach out
and become your friend.
If you knew sadness,
I would embrace it.
If you went astray,
I would guide you.
If you make a mistake,
I will forgive you.
When you had nowhere to turn,
I would be your refuge.
I wanted to help, all so
that this man who could
no longer love the world,
might love it again.
Los Nueve Aspectos.
Kaname...
Shall we end this now,
what do you say?
Mmgh.
Justice... isn't something
that's seen with your eyes.
Justice Is something mere words
can't completely describe.
[Sajin]
Forgive me, Tetsuzaemon...
Forgive me, Shuhei...
Forgive me, Kaname....
I cannot kill you.
I know you too well.
That's enough. You're not
really Captain Tosen anymore.
Before this, when you
couldn't see, you could have
easily dodged my attack.
Reap...Kazeshini!
[choking]
[younger Kaname]
Why isn't that man
going to be executed?!
I need to speak to the
central 46! Right now!
I beg you!
Why?
How did it come to this?
Welcome Sosuke...
to the inverted world.
Here we have the
power of Sakanade.
It completely reverses your
opponent's sense of direction
and acts like a puzzle game
changing which way you move.
Yes... funny isn't it?
You probably haven't
played any video games.
Have you?!
This is quite interesting.
Everything is reversed.
Up is down.
And left is right.
Did you honestly think
that I wouldn't notice?
[gasp]
I'd say it appears
you didn't notice.
Up and down, left and right,
and front and back are all
reversed.
The way you turned and
where you just attacked
from, are also reversed.
Hmm.
All those changes in
direction and damage
coming at you from
every single angle.
So why don't you
ask yourself,
can you really fight while
reversing everything
inside your head?
No one can do that.
It's impossible.
Whether you're a Soul Reaper,
an Espada, or a human,
the sense most used
in battle is sight.
We all fight based on
visual information.
But once I employ Sakanade,
it becomes almost impossible
to fight based on sight.
So you're left with reacting
reflexively to my attacks,
but you have to think
twice before every move.
Heh.
What a challenge.
Even with your fast
reaction time, how will you
counteract your reflexes?
The more conditioned you are,
the greater chance you'll fail!
Over here!
What's wrong Sosuke?!
You look quite confused!
I've got you!
Not too bad, Sosuke.
Even though everything
is reversed for you,
you still somehow managed to
dodge almost all of my
triple bluffed attacks.
You are quite impressive.
But.
It ends here.
You are through, Sosuke!
Nh!
So that's it...?
Your whole strategy was nothing
more than an optical illusion.
How did you...?!
You talked about how when
warriors battle, they rely
mainly on their sight.
Have you forgotten that
you are no exception in
this situation?
Wh-What do you mean, Sosuke?
Please... don't act so
surprised, Shinji.
Your ability is nowhere
near my level of power, one
which takes control of all
five of your senses.
So instead of me being
beaten by this visual
effect, it was you.
If I can change your
senses even a little,
the rest is easy.
Rrgh.
Yours was a parlor trick.
It's quite a far cry from
my ability to control all
five senses.
It was child's play
for me, Shinji Hirako.
[Kaname]
Who is this...This woman?
How strange...
This wasn't how it was
supposed to happen.
Who is she?
I can't see.
I can't see anything.
Not a thing.
Nothing.
Agh...
Sajin...
Shuhei...
Don't speak. Your Hollow
powers are allowing you
to breathe, but your
throat's been torn open.
You don't need to
talk right now.
It's better that you
save your strength.
Kaname, you said
something before
our battle began.
You mentioned to me that
you knew someday, we would
cross our swords in combat.
To be honest,
As we were fighting,
I found myself feeling
the same thing.
Shuhei probably had
the same thought.
Our relationship
has been all too
superficial
until now.
Even as friends,
it was our fate to
fight each other.
And by fighting,
We've come to a greater
understanding between us.
I can't ask you
not to hate me,
I know you'll probably
hold a grudge after
what's happened,
Just don't allow your
hunger for revenge to
change who you truly are.
I feel just as you
must've felt when you
lost your friend.
If we were to lose you,
it would leave a hole
in my heart.
I thank you, Sajin.
Shuhei, let me have
a look at your face.
Because of my Hollowfication,
I'm still able to see.
I want to see your face
while I still have the
chance to remember it.
Captain...
Hungh!
Captain!
Captain!!
Aizen!!!
I won't forgive you Aizen!!
[Soi Fon]
Huh, They're finally settling
the score down there.
[snoring]
[Soi Fon]
Ugh! Wake up, Marechiyo!
[Marechiyo]
Captain Soi Fon,
I've defeated Sosuke Aizen!
[Soi Fon]
Quit dreaming!
He's still alive!
[Marechiyo]
There you go with
the lies, Captain.