[theme music]
-[grunting in pain]
[explosion]
-[screaming]
-(THINKING) He got me.
What was that just now?
What was it, [inaudible]?
Damn it.
It hurts.
My body feels heavy.
I can't move my legs.
I can't lift my arms.
Damn it.
Have I lost?
Damn.
[screaming] Rukia.
[gasping]
-[gasping]
-[labored breathing]
[music playing]
-(THINKING) When she left, I
was the one who didn't go after
her.
RENJI NARRATING: Hanging
Dog, the 78th district
in South Rukon.
To the North, South, East, and
West, Rukon has 80 districts.
District One has the
highest standard of living.
So to be poor kids
like us, living
in a place like
the 78th district,
well, that made us pretty
much the lowest of the low.
-Get out of here,
you street rats.
-Hey.
Watch it, you old grouch.
RENJI NARRATING: Every
day was a challenge.
And it wasn't the
kind of place where
grownups cut you slack,
just because you're a kid.
-Aah!
I said beat it!
-All right, all right.
-Come on.
RENJI NARRATING:
But we did whatever
we had to do to survive.
-OK, let's do it.
-Hey!
I'm going to beat the
living daylights out of you!
Ow!
-Take that you old goat.
Go, grab whatever you can.
-This is water.
-This one's candy.
-Why you thieving
little bastards.
-All right.
Let's get out of here, guys!
-[screaming]
-Put that stuff down, you
worthless street vermin,
or I'm going to pound
you all into jelly.
-This is bad, Renji.
I think he's really
pissed off this time.
-Then you better just
shut up, and keep running.
-Oh, you think you can outrun
me, you thieving little punks.
Just wait.
You've got another thing coming.
RENJI NARRATING: Life
was hard in that town.
And we hated every minute of it.
-[screaming] You maggots are
going to be sorry you messed
with me!
Now I've got you,
you little brats!
[screaming]
-Huh?
-[moaning] I'll kill
you-- [inaudible].
-Now follow me.
Hurry!
-Hey, wait.
Who the hell are you?
-You want to stand
around asking question?
Or you want to get away?
-Let's go.
-Good call.
RENJI NARRATING: It was
on those mean streets
that I first met Rukia.
RENJI (OFFSCREEN): Here.
-What do you got in the bag?
-I divided up all
the stuff we got.
Here.
This is your portion.
-Thank you.
-See, it's rock candy.
-Rock candy?
RENJI (OFFSCREEN):
You're kidding, right?
Don't tell me you've
never even heard of it.
Try it.
It's sweet.
-OK.
CHILD (OFFSCREEN): Give it back.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
That's my [inaudible].
-No, it's mine.
Give me back my candy.
-You want it back?
Then take it back, you shrimp.
Ow!
[crying]
MALE SPEAKER
(OFFSCREEN): Oh, great.
Now look what you've done.
If you'd have let
me have it, I might
have given you some,
you stupid kid.
[crying]
-Cut out the crying,
you little baby.
It was just a little candy.
It would have been
wasted on you, anyway.
You don't have an
ounce of spirit energy.
So what good are you?
Now just shut up already.
-Hey.
-Huh?
-What kind of a pathetic creep
steals from a little kid?
-Why you.
I'll teach you to mind
your own business.
Whoa!
-We may not get hungry.
But we can all smell,
and we can all taste.
You got that?
We're all the same.
And happiness should be
shared with every one of us.
If we hurt each
other, than we're
no better than those
horrible grown ups.
Agreed?
-Mhmm.
CHILD (OFFSCREEN):
Wow, she's tough.
-[whimpering]
-Don't cry little one.
Here, take this.
-Huh?
Oh!
RENJI NARRATING: I knew
she wanted it for herself.
But she give it
away, just like that.
That's the way she was.
But it's not like she was soft.
Rukia was tougher
than most men I know.
She didn't take any
crap from anyone.
She even kind of
talked like a man.
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN): Hey, Renji.
-Huh?
-Watcha doing?
Did you come looking for me?
-Um, no, I, I just-- [scoffing]
why would I be looking for you?
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN):
[giggling] You're so weird.
[laughing]
-How dare you laugh at me?
-[laughing]
-You're the weird one.
You got a lot of
nerve, you know that?
I'm going to be a
soul reaper someday--
-It didn't matter
what she was doing.
There was something
classy about Rukia.
-Stop laughing at me.
[panting]
RENJI (OFFSCREEN):
Rukia, what's the matter?
-Nothing.
I'm right behind you.
-Whoa.
Look at that rickshaw.
-That's the coolest
one I've ever seen.
It must belong to
someone famous.
-Check it out--
red leather seats
-It's so shiny you can
see your face in it.
-Whoa.
Look at that.
-Can you believe he's going
to become a soul reaper?
I remember when he was
still just a skinny kid
in the neighborhood.
-Yeah.
Now he's the local hero.
-I'm going to be a
soul reaper, too.
-Oh, yeah, sure.
You don't have a chance.
Soul reapers have to have
a ton of spirit energy.
MALE SPEAKER
(OFFSCREEN): He's right.
The three of us
put together don't
have enough spirit
energy for that.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Ah, I can dream, can't I?
-Argh!
Get your sticky fingers
off that paint job.
-Thank you, sir.
I'll be on my way now.
-Hey, look!
He's about to come outside.
-We're all rooting for you.
You can do it.
[applause and praise]
-Hey, Rukia, are you OK?
What's wrong?
What happened to you?
-What's the matter
with your friend?
I imagine you must be weak
from hunger, aren't you?
-No.
Why would you think that?
-Feeling hunger in
this world where
no one is supposed
to get hungry,
I was also confused
about it at first, too.
But it's a reality that we
all have to accept eventually.
I think what happened just
now is that your body felt
my spiritual pressure
when I passed by you,
and it instantly used
up all your energy.
Here, why don't you
eat some of these.
That should help to
restore your strength.
-Oh, thank you.
-[roaring]
[clapping]
-That's awesome, Renji.
You're going to get to be a
soul reaper someday for sure!
-You're damn right!
-Huh?
-[giggling]
-Whoa, yours is even
bigger than Renji's.
-Amazing, Rukia.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Rukia, you when Renji are both
going to become
soul reapers, huh?
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN): Nah, I
wouldn't worry about that.
I'm not going to go
anywhere, you guys?
-Really?
-We're going to keep this
gang together forever.
-Excellent!
-That's fantastic!
-Right, Renji?
-Uh, sure.
Why not?
-Yay.
We're going to be
friends forever!
-Forever!
[giggling]
RENJI NARRATING: With
or without spirit
energy didn't seem to
matter so much back then.
At least it didn't to Rukia.
We may have lived among
the lowest of the low,
but she always shined.
-Uh!
Renji, there's one
coming your way.
-OK.
I got it!
[grunting]
-Hey, you're just going to scare
all the fish away doing that.
-Aah!
-Now what are you doing?
Trying to make friends
with them down there?
-[gasping] No, I'm OK.
Thanks for asking.
-They're flowers.
-Flowers?
Ha!
Hey, check this
one out, you guys.
Am I talented or what?
If you've got that fire ready,
then we'll cook this baby up.
-Yeah.
-[giggling]
-Why are you just
standing around?
Get the fire ready.
-Whoa!
-Hey!
-Come on.
-Day after day, night after
night, we were always together.
And so, though we didn't
realize it at the time,
we had become a family.
That was what we had to do.
It's how we survived.
But we knew it was
still no kind of a life.
We were still pathetic
people, living pathetic lives
in a terrible, ugly place.
All the grownups were
either thieves or murderers.
And all the kids
were delinquents.
And to get out of life,
well, there was only one way.
-Renji.
I think we should
become soul reapers.
If we do that, then we can
live in the [inaudible].
I've had enough, lived in
this ugly place too long.
RENJI NARRATING: Each of us
came to this merciless town
on their own.
Each one of us had
struggled alone,
until finally we had come
together out of necessity.
In order to survive,
we became a family.
But in the end, that
cruel place had still
proven to be too
much for us, to much
for any makeshift
family of kids.
It had been 10 years
since Rukia had come.
And now we looked around.
And all the rest of
our friends were gone.
Yes, let's becomes soul reapers.
Shortly after the day we
made that fateful decision,
we both entered the
soul reaper academy.
We quickly learned we were
different from the rest
of the spoiled brats
from noble families.
-Yes, yes, I know that one.
Let me give the answer, sir.
I know it.
-I'm glad to hear it.
And in the future, if I need a
substitute, I'll think of you.
But as I am not
dead yet, I'll do
the explaining in
this classroom.
And you'll do the listening,
if you don't mind, young man.
-What a total loser.
You'd think it's his first
time in a real classroom.
-Well, honestly,
what do you expect?
You know where he's from, right?
He's just district 78 trash.
-All right, quiet down.
Let's move on to the
next problem now, class.
-Renji.
-I, I was just studying.
I have lots of
extra work because
of this advanced placement
class I've been promoted to.
So I don't have much time
to hang around, like you do.
I've got so much work to do.
-About the other
students, I know
they were making
fun of you earlier.
But I liked your eagerness.
-Uh, oh?
-Keep it up.
Don't let a bunch
of stuffed shirts
keep you from being yourself.
You got it?
-What?
What do you mean, be myself?
-You know what I mean, Renji.
Most of the other students
here come from nobility.
They don't understand
the kind of existence
we had back in Hanging Dog.
So they'll never accept us.
And that's something
we can never change.
-That's true.
RENJI NARRATING: So even
though we had left the Rukongai
behind, and it made
it into the academy,
there was still a huge
gap between us and them.
I swore then and
there I would make
them eat their words, somehow.
[panting]
-[screaming]
-Oh, sorry about that!
[panting] Rukia, guess
what just happened.
I passed the second exam.
Isn't that great?
Now if I pass the next
one I-- (THINKING)
Those are [inaudible].
What are nobles doing here?
-Well, it would seem
our deliberations
have been interrupted.
Take a few days, and
consider the situation.
We are looking forward to
hearing a favorable answer.
-(THINKING) This amazing
spiritual pressure.
It's so strong.
I can't even look into his eyes.
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN): Renji.
-Oh, uh, Rukia,
how are you doing?
You had some pretty important
looking visitors there, huh?
Sorry to interrupt.
So tell me, what was
that all about anyway?
Oh, so it's a secret, huh?
-That was the Kuchiki
family, Renji.
They want to adopt
me as their daughter.
They said that they're
going to let me graduate
right away, and
then, after that,
they can make
arrangements to put me
straight into one of the
13 court guard squads.
Renji, I don't know what to do.
-Ah!
Rukia, what do you mean?
Of course you know what to do.
You say yes, Rukia.
This is fantastic!
Don't you see?
You're in.
The Kuchikis are a
powerful noble family.
And now you're going to
become one them. [laughing]
You're going to live
the rest of your life
in luxury, Rukia,
wearing fine clothes.
Hey, I wonder what nobles eat.
[laughing] Man, I'm jealous.
And not only that--
[laughing] wow!
You're going to get to
graduate immediately.
This is wonderful
news, Rukia. [laughing]
-You think so?
-I'm practically
speechless. [laughing]
-Thank you.
RENJI NARRATING:
Rukia had finally
found a family, a real family.
And I knew I must not interfere.
That's what I had to
keep telling myself.
[gasping]
But now that I
think back, I think
I was just scared to lose her,
to lose the only family I ever
had.
Not only that, I didn't
want to face the fact
that I'm nothing more
than a stray dog.
And I'm so sick of it.
All I do is bark
wildly at the moon.
I don't have the guts
to actually bite.
[moaning]
-[panting]
-All this time I've been
blaming you for the fact
that Rukia has been imprisoned.
Every time I thought of
you it made my blood boil.
But I was wrong.
It wasn't you.
It was me from the start,
because I didn't stop Rukia
from going to the Kuchikis.
I didn't want her to go.
But I never imagined
that if she did,
she'd end up being a
condemned criminal.
I thought she would
find happiness.
I really believed that.
How could I have ever known?
And I wanted so badly to
surpass Captain Kuchiki
for taking Rukia from me.
From that first day I
saw him, I pursued him.
I trained with only
that thought in mind.
But even to this day, not once
have I been able to beat him.
He's just too strong.
As much as I wanted to, I
just didn't have the strength
to get Rukia back that way.
So Ichigo, now I'm swallowing
my shame and my pride.
And I'm asking you
to save Rukia. [gasp]
will you promise?
[gasp] I'm begging you.
Will you save her?
[weeping and gasping]
-Yes.
RENJI NARRATING: Light a fire
to the fang that cannot be
reached, so that I do
not have to see the star,
so that I do not
slit this throat.
[music playing]
-I am this century's premier
spiritualist [inaudible].
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN): Huh?
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN): This
positively reeks of bad things.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
What about the fight?
That definitely smells
like bad spirits.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
And my injury?
And Renji?
MALE SPEAKER
(OFFSCREEN): You kids
watching at home, just
you wait. [laughing]
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Hey, what's the deal here?