[music playing]
[theme music]
NARRATOR: Ichigo
and his friends,
still undergoing intense
training and preparation
for the showdown this winter,
were forced into action
when Aizen's elite group of
Arrancars suddenly appeared.
Captain Hitsugaya's
advanced troops and Ichigo
stood against the Arrancars,
but they ran into trouble
fighting the Espada.
However, Aizen's
true goal was to take
Orihime Inoue to Hueco Mundo.
Orihime gives in to
Ulquiorra's threats,
and agrees to go to Hueco Mundo.
She is then given 12 hours to
say goodbye to only one person.
And so Orihime goes to Ichigo.
-Thank you, Ichigo.
[music playing]
Goodbye.
[gasping]
-What was that?
Damn, that hurt.
That has got to be
the worst possible way
to wake up in the morning.
My freaking head.
I'm such an idiot.
It's healed.
Who did this?
The spiritual pressure.
-It was probably Orihime Inoue.
Come immediately, Ichigo.
It's an emergency.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
-Rukia.
What's this?
Why is everyone standing
here, in Orihime's room?
And where is she, anyway?
-Well.
-What is the status?
-Sir.
We have regulated
the spiritual wave.
-Fine.
Put me through.
Ukitake?
I was looking for
the head captain.
-I had him switch to me.
-And your reason?
-Because I'm the last person
who saw Orihime Inoue.
Before she went
through the Senkaimon,
to return to the
world of the living.
Judging by your
reaction, it doesn't
appear as though she's arrived
there safely, as I had hoped.
-What's the meaning
of this, Jushiro?
Where exactly did
she disappear to?
Do you know anything?
-I'll give you my assessment.
The two guards I had
sent with her when
she went through the
Senkaimon came back alive.
According to them, it's
likely that Orihime Inoue
has either been
abducted, or killed.
By the Arrancars.
-Killed?
-Captain Ukitake.
I believe you're
jumping to conclusions.
-I understand.
I don't want to
believe it, either.
I'm simply stating the worst
possible scenario there is.
We think it more
likely, however,
that Orihime Inoue was
attacked by an Arrancar.
And then disappeared with him.
-Are you kidding me?
Is that really all you have?
Orihime has disappeared.
You say that there's no proof,
and that she might be dead.
Well
Take a look at this.
I was seriously injured
in yesterday's battle.
No one here could
heal my wounds.
But when I woke up
this morning, it
was already completely healed.
And not only that,
but on my wrist,
there's still some of
Orihime's spiritual pressure!
Are you still just going
to stand there and tell me
that she might be dead?
-I see.
That is most unfortunate.
-Unfortunate?
Wait, what do you mean by that?
If what you say is
true, then it would
be safe to assume that
Orihime Inoue is indeed alive.
But at the same time,
unfortunately, it also
means that this is
an act of betrayal.
-Act of betrayal?
-If you had been
abducted, she would not
have had the time to
visit you while you slept.
In other words, the fact
that she healed your wounds
before disappearing can
only mean one thing,
that Orihime Inoue had
actually volunteered
to go along with the Arrancar.
Of her own free will.
-You better take that back!
-Stop.
You'll just end up
worsening your position
if you say anything else.
Sir!
I understand what you're
saying, Head Captain Yamamoto.
Therefore, as a member
of the advanced troops,
and because I am the
lieutenant of Squad Six,
I will head over to Hueco Mundo
to bring the traitor, Orihime
Inoue back to her senses.
-Renji.
-Hm.
-You must not.
-What?
-With this new
information, we now
know that the Arrancars
are ready for battle.
All members of Captain
Hitsugaya's advanced troops
are to return immediately,
and defend the Soul Society.
-Are you saying that
Orihime is to be
abandoned by us, Head Captain?
-Exactly.
We cannot risk the safety of the
entire world just to go chasing
after one simple human.
-Unfortunately, Head Captain,
with all due respect,
I can't follow that order.
-Unfortunate indeed.
I thought that
this might happen,
so I'm glad that I
have prepared for it.
[music playing]
-Captain Kuchiki.
-All right, now.
I want you all to head on back.
-Don't fight us.
We have been ordered to take
you back by force, if necessary.
-All right, then.
In that case, I'm not
going to ask the Soul
Society to help me
get Orihime back.
However, the least
you can do is tell me
how I can get into Hueco Mundo.
After all, she's
still my friend.
So I'll just go save her myself.
-Ichigo.
-You must not.
-Why is he saying that?
-We are going to need your
help in this battle, Ichigo
Kurosaki.
I won't allow you to plot
your own course of action
and die for nothing.
Stand by until you
receive orders.
That is all for now.
[music playing]
-All right, let's go.
-Ichigo.
[music playing]
I'm sorry.
[city noises]
-Hey, Orihime!
Oh, I'm sorry.
MUSIC PLAYING]
Orihime.
[music playing]
[crying]
Where did you go, Orihime?
[music playing]
-Shinji!
This was on the ground outside.
-What is it?
-I have no idea.
-Don't pick up things if you
don't know what they are.
-But it was just sitting
there, all alone.
Right in front of our place.
I had to pick it up.
Oh!
What are those?
-Bandages?
From Ichigo?
Why would he go through
the trouble to send this?
-Why bandages?
Huh?
How come?
Why bandages?
Why?
Why, why, why, why bandages?
-That guy's an idiot.
-What should we do
to cheer him up?
-Let's bring him dinner.
-And what about some ice cream?
-No, before that he'll get
a big bear hug from me.
Ready, set, let's Ichigo!
How unfortunate, I missed.
-Oh, that's too bad.
-Hey, Ichigo.
-Look, why don't you
have some dinner.
Otherwise Yuzu won't be
able to clear the table.
-I'm sorry.
I don't really feel
like eating today.
-But Yuzu prepared all
of your favorite dishes!
You have to.
-I'm sorry, Yuzu.
-Oh, it's all right.
Don't worry about it.
I'll put it in the
refrigerator, and you
can eat it when you feel hungry.
All right, let's go.
Come on dad, you too!
-Huh?
Oh, OK.
-That is amazing, Ichigo!
You just apologized three whole
times, a new national record
for being pathetic!
What's wrong?
You're acting all gloomy again.
I know what it is,
you're constipated.
Well, believe me, there's
plenty of other things
to get down in the
dumps about, if you'll
pardon the expression.
Oh, you want to
fight, is that it?
-Sorry, but could
you move, please?
-Sorry.
Sorry!
Hey, wait.
You're acting like you're
completely out of it.
Oh, you're palm reading, huh?
Let me take a look at mine!
-Well, well, Ichigo.
It's been awhile since I've
seen you last, hasn't it.
I was sad, thinking
you didn't want
to graduate with the
rest of your class.
You haven't been hospitalized
due to an accident, have you?
-Amazing.
-What do you have to say?
-Oh, she's pounding him.
-Well, say something
for yourself.
-You changed your hairstyle.
-Yes, I did!
Thanks for noticing.
But I changed it
three weeks ago!
-Oh boy.
That has got to hurt.
-I know.
[bells ringing]
-Ichigo, Ichigo,
Ichigo, Ichigo, Ichigo!
Hey, it sure has been
a long time, huh?
-It really has been awhile.
What have you been doing
during the month you took off?
We were worried about you.
You didn't even answer
your text messages.
-Oh yeah, sorry about that.
I was a little busy.
-What are you doing Mizuiro?
-Oh, I almost forgot!
I was able to get some tickets
for a premiere screening,
if you'd like to come with me.
They're for Bad Shield 2.
-When is it?
-Oh, it's for the
5th of December.
-Yeah, it sounds good.
I think I should
be back by then.
-Huh?
-Thank you, Mizuiro.
-He'll be back by then?
-Ichigo!
-Huh?
Tatsuki.
What is it?
Tell me what's wrong.
-It's Orihime.
She disappeared.
She's not at home, or anywhere.
Her entire presence
has disappeared.
-Huh?
-It's true.
I've been looking all
over the city for her.
But I can find her.
She's gone.
But you know.
You know where she
went, don't you?
Admit it!
-What do you mean by that?
Why would I know?
Besides, are you even sure
she really disappeared?
Why don't you just try
looking for her again?
-Cut it out!
I've always been
able to sense her.
But her presence
has disappeared.
I can't sense her nearby.
For awhile now, I could
only faintly sense her.
It was as if she was on the
other side of some wall.
But yesterday she suddenly
vanished without a trace.
And you know something
about this, don't you?
I know you do!
-Just cut it out.
I told you already,
I don't know.
-Yes you do.
And don't think I
don't know, either.
I've seen you.
When you wear that
black robe, and you
go around fighting
monsters, as well
as other strange people
wearing the same get up.
Ichigo, I've had it
with all the lies.
Tell me the truth.
What are you trying to hide?
-Listen, it's none
of your business.
-Tatsuki, what the?
Have you completely
lost your mind?
-Are you all right?
-What do you think I am?
I want to know.
What am I?
Am I someone who
even matters to you?
Do you consider me your friend?
Are you really my friend?
I save you all those times
when you were getting beat up.
How many times did I find you
crying, and tried to help you?
Just cut it out!
Stop trying to hide
things from me.
You idiot.
-Ichigo.
-Sorry.
Keigo.
Mizuiro.
Take care of Tatsuki.
And do yourself a favor,
and just stay away from me.
-You idiot.
You idiot!
[music playing]
-Hey, welcome back.
I've been waiting for you
to show up here, Ichigo.
-Oh yeah, what made
you think that?
-Because you thought
I would know a way
to get into Hueco Mundo.
And you would have been correct.
Come inside, Ichigo.
I've made some preparations.
I was afraid.
Afraid that Aizen would
go after Orihime's power.
So I left her out
of this battle.
But I was too late.
Taking her feelings
into consideration,
it was my mistake
to leave her out.
I shall do anything I can in
order to try and help you.
-You sure about that?
I mean, after all,
you'd be going
against the Soul
Society's decision.
-Look, I'm here because I
went against their rules
in the first place.
-Well, you sure are
a sad sight, Ichigo.
[music playing]
-Hey, Uryu.
Wait a minute, what
are you doing here?
-Isn't it obvious?
We're going to Hueco Mundo.
-But Chad.
-Kisuke already gave
us all of the details.
We're going with you.
-Yeah.
-You can't.
Look, I appreciate your concern.
Both of you.
But you're just
not strong enough.
-Ichigo!
Now do you think that I'm
still not strong enough?
Believe in us.
-Chad.
-Don't take this on by yourself.
This is what friends are for.
-All right!
Are we all set?
It looks like everybody's
ready, finally.
[theme music]
CONE: Ready, Ichigo?
There are terrifying Hollows
waiting for you in Hueco Mundo!
Brace yourself, and be careful!
-I will!
Hey, Cone!
Why don't you come
with us to Hueco Mundo?
CONE: Sorry, I can't.
Someone's got to stay and
protect the girls of this town.
-Gee, how brave of you, Cone.