Hado Number 91, Senjukotentaiho!
Wha-? What in the world...
...is that?
Tell you what.
I'll demonstrate it for you.
All thirteen kilometers of it.
Bankai,
Kamishininoyari.
Hyahhh!
What's wrong, Aizen?
Is it my imagination,
or are you getting slower?
Perhaps you've
reached your limit.
Well now that I think about it,
you may be right about my speed.
I may have actually
reached my limit.
My limit as a Soul
Reaper, that is.
That was a very nice move there.
Fascinating just how effective
sheer luck can be.
You're stupid to
think that was luck!
Sorry about all this, Captain
Aizen. I hope I didn't interrupt
your conversation.
It's all right.
I had pretty much finished
explaining myself.
It doesn't matter if you
understand what it is.
You can't escape its influence.
You're feeling it now, even as
you try to resist its will.
It has the power to destroy
the wall that separates those
beings who are gods...
...from those who are not!
So you've come,
Kisuke Urahara!
Where did he come from?
Well now, it's been
a while, Aizen.
A hundred years or so?
Since we last crossed paths,
You seem to have adopted
quite an interesting look.
As you know, everything in
the process of evolving
tends to look ugly.
An odd response.
Who said anything about ugly?
I see. You've fused
yourself with the
Hogyoku haven't you?
I wouldn't say 'fused'.
It's more along the
lines of 'subjugated'.
I've Subjugated the Hogyoku
you could not control.
You're right, my friend.
I couldn't control it...
at the time.
At the time?
That's a very interesting
remark, Kisuke. Except,
I don't believe there's even
the slightest shred of truth
behind what you're implying.
I'll prove it.
[gasp]
Get out of there, Kisuke!
I'm certain that if you had the
power to control the Hogyoku,
you would have done so by now.
[baloon inflate & pop]
[gasp]
Rikujokoro!
Hmh.
Now that I think about it,
Yammy's battle records
contained an entry that
listed such an item.
Wah-ha ha ha ha!
I'll tell you what that was!
It's called a Bala!
A Bala is a projectile
of spiritual energy!
It's not as
strong as a Cero.
Doesn't need the power,
It's twenty times faster!
[sing-song]
Lord Aizen'll
be terribly ma-ad!
Huh???
Rrgh!
Alive?! But how?!
You're asking if
I'm still alive?
Is that it?
The answer is right here.
Huh?
What??
A portable gigai!
Very good.
I let my guard down,
never figuring you'd
resort to such trickery.
So what is it you're planning
to do now, after trying to tie
me up with such a weak Bakudo?
Such a weak Bakudo, really?
Well then, let's see
how many you can take.
Bakudo Number 63!
Sajosabaku!
Bakudo Number 79!
Kuyoshibari!
Beyond the end of a
thousand hands, the hand
of darkness, out of reach.
The archer in heaven
that goes unseen.
Road that lights the way.
Wind that ignites the embers.
Converge where I point.
Bullets of light, bodies
of eight, rays of nine,
paths of heaven,
treasures of speed,
wheels of immensity,
and cannons of gray.
The bow is drawn
and fades in light.
Really, do you think I'd
let you use such a Kido?
I can easily break free.
Too late!
Hado Number 91,
Senjukotentaiho!
That's incredible!
That's too bad, Aizen.
When you went and
embedded the Hogyoku,
It appears you really did let
your guard down, and now,
you have to pay the price.
Exactly as I thought.
[gasp]
Too slow!
I did let my guard down. But at
this point, there's no longer
any reason to be on guard.
I can feel the power.
Back in the Soul Society,
I realized that no-one could
compare to my capabilities.
But now that I have
subjugated the Hogyoku,
I have surpassed even that
performance potential!
No matter what you attack
me with, it will fall short.
At this point, I have
no intention of dodging
any of your Kido, even
at the nineties level.
You've got it wrong.
Standing up to my Kido
isn't what I meant by
'letting your guard down'.
The old you would have never
attempted to attack me twice,
without first thoroughly
thinking it through.
What's happening?
You've been sealed.
I've sealed all the
outlets for Spirit Energy.
You know, the ones that
are on the wrists of
every Soul Reaper.
[gasp]
With no outlet for the energy,
you'll be incinerated
from the inside by your
own Spirit Energy.
[fright breaths]
Did you defeat him?!
It's not over yet.
It would be child's
play if that were all
it took to defeat him.
We could laugh him off as
some kind of odd monster.
He'll break out of
that trap in no time.
Wh---?
What in the world...
is that?
You used a nineties-level
Kido as a decoy to lure
me into attacking.
And you used a spell you
developed, to incinerate
me from the inside.
It was a bold plan,
and it almost worked.
If it hadn't been me who
subjugated the Hogyoku,
this battle would probably
have been over by now.
But unfortunately for you,
the Hogyoku you created,
exceeds even your ability
to understand it.
As a result, the technique you
created in anticipation of
battling me, is a failure.
It has no effect on me.
Your spell didn't work,
so now you're coming at
me with your sword?
As you wish.
Rgh!
Rrraah!
What nonsense is this?
Do you really think
these chains will hold me?
Hyahhh!
You...!
...Yoruichi!
HaaaAAAA!
Did it work?
Is he unconscious?
Look out, Yoruichi!
Get out of there!
What's the matter?
You're not done
already, are you?
You'd better make your
next move quickly.
I plan to crush your
compatriots, one at a time.
Until none of them
are left standing.
The number of methods you
contrived to defeat me,
are proof of your imagination
and strength of will.
At the same time, they
represent the desperation
you're feeling as you try to
overcome my superior power.
As you're about to find out,
there's no way you can stop me.
But feel free to mount
your next attack.
Kisuke Urahara,
Yoruichi Shihoin,
and of course,
Isshin Kurosaki.
Well, this presents
a problem.
Hm?
This iron armor was
specially constructed,
and made for use
against Hierro.
I didn't think it could
be destroyed so easily.
Hmm, what are you saying?
From your tone, you're
implying that it's my fault.
No! You're not to blame,
I didn't mean it like that.
Yes you did, mister!
You're trying to say
it's my fault, because
I let my guard down!
Huh??
Well, listen to me!
You didn't put enough thought
into this armor when you
originally constructed it!
Which means it's all your fault
for not being imaginative
enough when you conceived of it
in the first place
!
Okay, I get it!
It's all my fault!
Take it easy!
[Aizen]
I see.
Hm?
You overlook the fact that
your leg still remains intact
after being hit by me.
It proves they are special.
You're talking
about my legs?
[snort]
Huh?! What's so
funny, smart-ass?!
Dammit, you
hurt my nose!
There's no need
to make a scene.
It's meaningless to argue
over whether or not the
armor is adequate.
If a single swing was enough
to make one piece disappear,
then three more swings
should be enough to
destroy it completely.
He took the bait.
Just like you thought.
Are you good to go?
Who do you think you're
dealing with here?
All I have to do is
hit him with something
besides my left leg.
Huh??
Don't lose your balance!
Gh!
Hyaahh!
[Gin]
Watch yourself.
Your back and neck
are wide open.
Psyched you out,
didn't I?
I was just
messing with you.
How 'bout we take
a little break?
What?! What are you
talking about?!
Take a load off.
Let's watch the action.
Haaaa!
It's useless.
You're wasting your time.
[Gin]
They won't defeat him.
I've been working
with Captain Aizen
for a long time now.
But I've never seen him
as effective as this.
Of course I didn't know he
had fused with the Hogyoku,
which may have given him a
whole new level of power.
You probably don't realize
it yet, but there's nothing
you can do to stop him.
He's going to kill all of
you, no matter what you do.
It's only a matter of time.
There's no way I'm
gonna let that happen.
That's no surprise. It's pretty
much what I figured you'd say.
There's no telling what
Aizen's capable of.
And he probably doesn't
need you, either, now
that he's this powerful.
Well, I have to admit,
I wasn't expecting you
to say that.
In fact, the way you said it,
leads me to believe you
may not be expecting to
survive this battle.
Maybe somewhere
deep inside of you,
you've given up any
hope of being able
to win this fight.
Huh?
My, my.
Truly pathetic.
I was hoping you'd
be better than that.
but I guess you really
are just a kid.
You're weak inside.
I couldn't possibly let
Captain Aizen waste his time,
fighting a coward like you.
What're you doing?!
Kamishininoyari,
Buto!
[Ichigo]
That was so fast!
Kamishininoyari,
Butorenjin!
Hyaaaaaa!
Captain... Ichimaru.
Huh?
[Izuru]
Rangiku...?
Gin!
Yaaah!
Way too soft.
I'll be the one...
...who'll stop you!
[battle shouts]
[Yoruichi]
We'll have to move
to our final plan!
[Ichigo]
You mean you still
have one more ?!
[Yoruichi]
I'll have to get rid
of all my armor!
[Ichigo]
Huh?
[Yoruichi]
And after that, I have to get
rid of any clothing I'm wearing!
I call it 'Operation
Sex Appeal'!
[Ichigo]
Yaahahh! Put
everything back on!
[Yoruichi]
This is more effective on
my allies than my opponent!