It won't be long now.
[Toshiro]
[heavy injured breaths]
Apparently, this is the place.
Kenpachi?
Hey.
Looks like we're the
only two left to
carry on this fight.
That's not bad,
all things
considered.
We don't know if the
others were defeated yet.
We may still have help.
[Kageroza]
He he he he he!
[chuckles]
There you are.
What's so damn funny?
We've wiped out most
of your invading army.
And now that we've
tracked you down,
we're gonna crush your
invasion plans for good!
But first, Kageroza Inaba,
We need answers.
Just exactly who in
the hell are you?!
Heh! He doesn't want
to answer that.
Well, it doesn't really matter,
one way or the other.
There's only one thing
that matters to me.
Are you strong enough
to fight me, or not?!
[chuckles] Well,
how disappointing.
After all you've gone through,
you still don't realize.
You don't have any
chance of victory.
[Rukia]
What's the situation?
I'm scanning everywhere,
but I still can't get a
reading on Ichigo.
Give us the bottom line.
Does that mean he's dead?
I'm afraid I just
can't tell you for
sure, at this point.
Come on, you guys!
You know he's okay!
That bastard, Ichigo,
wouldn't die on us!
He's too
tricky for that!
He'll probably just show up
here, and have no explanation
for where he's been!
You know what I mean? Eh?
It's okay,
take it easy.
What?!
Yeah, it's written all
over your face, pal.
You're more worried than
anybody else in the room!
Shut up! Who says I'm
worried about Ichigo?
Well I'm not, so
get out of my face!
Dahg!
Ichigo makes it to the Soul
Society, then disappears
into the Precipice World?
[Renji & Kon fighting]
This has got to be
Kageroza's doing!
But how?
Despite all our interactions
and confrontations, we know
very little about Kageroza.
With the exception
of Nozomi.
All of her actions up till
now suggest that she may
have better insight into how
Kageroza thinks.
Once I return and I
have retrieved Nozomi,
Then I will be able to
completely show all of
you my true power.
What in the world did
Kageroza mean by that?
Does it have to do with
the secret this girl is
hiding from us?
If so, then what is it?
Go mad,
Raiku!
What's going on with this guy?
I don't sense any Spirit Energy
at all from his Shikai!
Until the moment when we
actually cross swords,
We'll have no way of knowing
exactly how strong he is!
I don't know how you're
hiding your Spirit
Energy, Kageroza.
But try your best to
make this fun for me!
Hold it, Kenpachi!
Rgh!
He's so impetuous!
Hyoryusenbi!
Sorry, Kenpachi, but
I'm not gonna let
you do this alone.
Whatever. But if
I kill him first,
we're done here!
Hyaaah!
Raagh!
What's the matter,
scientist?
Don't tell me you showed up
here just so we could kill you!
That would be
pretty stupid!
Wait. Am I still alive?
Ahg!
[Kagerosa]
I bid you farewell...
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Waagh!
What? Is this the
Precipice World?
Ah!
[gasp]
I'm...passing out.
Who are you?
Hey, Mr. Scientist.
I have to say, it was pretty
daring of you to confront
the two of us by yourself,
but I don't think you've
got what it takes!
You're not letting me
have any fun, are ya?
[Kenpachi]
I don't know if this is supposed
to be your true strength,
but if this is all you've
got and you aren't gonna
take me seriously,
I guess I'll have to
kill you right now
and be done with it!
Kenpachi, wait!
[Toshiro]
He's planning to trap you!
[gasp]
Guncho Tsurara!
I see. You were evading
us, in order to use that
technique of yours.
I almost forgot that
you're a specialist on
the Precipice World.
You create portals where
they shouldn't exist,
and seal your opponents
into the Precipice
World that lies beyond.
Obviously, that's the
power of your Zanpakuto.
You're able to
manipulate space.
Here I thought you possessed
some awesome power, but it
turns out to be a cheap trick!
How
boring is that?
Now that we've been alerted
to your sneak attack,
that technique won't
work on us again!
He he he he he!
Hrraahh!
You're so predictable!
He was the decoy?
Huh?
Hyoryu...senbi!
Apparently, you do
have some skills!
Hyaah!
He he he! I could say
the same about you,
Captain Hitsugaya!
And what is that
supposed to mean?
You apparently thought I
would make the Precipice
World appear again.
So you switched your
tactics instantly,
...to a long-range attack.
[panting]
Do you mean that
as a compliment?
Or are you just
making fun of me?
Heh heh heh! I guess
you'll have to figure that
one out for yourself.
Yes. I manipulate space.
And as you said,
that is the extent of my
Zanpakuto's capabilities.
But that, my friend, is
a very powerful weapon.
No matter how much you change
your attacks, they mean nothing
if they cannot reach me.
Yes, I suppose not.
Guncho Tsurara!
[gasp]
Yaaahh!
Where did you get the idea we
wouldn't be able to reach you?!
[Toshiro]
Hyaaaa!
It was all about setting
everything up for this
one last strike!
Yaaah!
Ha-HAH!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
[Toshiro]
Hyaaaa!
It was all about setting
everything up for this
one last strike!
Heh heh heh!
What a coincidence!
I was setting you up, as well.
For this!
What?!
Eagh!
What just... happened?
That was definitely
my Guncho Tsurara,
but that's
impossible!
Space manipulation.
That was how you described
my powers, wasn't it?
Well, you were certainly
correct, but you made
one grievous error.
My abilities are not limited
to simply manipulating one
small dimension such as the
Precipice World.
It would be more accurate to say
that I can manipulate all space.
What?
My Zanpakuto actually
affects space itself.
It records it and
re-creates it.
When you two captains were
attacking me earlier,
I used it to re-create
the Precipice World,
in an attempt to trap
and neutralize you.
But as I watched the details
and patterns of your attacks,
I also had it
record a new space.
So do you understand
my power now?
[shattering]
Huh?
[Kenpachi]
Heh! No, I don't. It still
sounds like a silly trick!
And if you can't fight without
resorting to cheap tricks,
then I have no
more use for you!
You're an eyesore!
And I'll put you out
of your misery!
Ha!
Quit screwin' around, bastard!
Huuh??
What the hell?
Careful, Captain.
You ended up
attacking yourself.
[chuckle]
So, you can even re-create
a Zanpakuto attack?
What will you do now?
It's useless!
Hyaaah!
Heh heh!
I can see now how your
Zanpakuto actually works!
You spin it to the right when
you want to record space.
And you spin it to the
left to re-create space.
If I prevent you from spinning
it to the right to record,
you're powerless!
It's all over!
Heh-heh!
Hngh!
I can re-create the last
recorded space, not once,
But as many times as I
need to, for strategic
advantage.
[light-headed gasp]
[panting]
Heh heh heh!
Huh?
So this is where
you've been hiding!
Hm! Well, well, if it
isn't Captain Soi Fon!
Truthfully, I never
thought you'd make it
out of that barrier.
Ugh! I have to give you credit,
you bastard, for deciding to
seal me in there, first!
Naturally. With you out of the
way, I would have free reign
over the Punishment Force.
[Yoruichi]
You certainly went through
a lot of trouble.
[Kageroza]
Yoruichi Shihoin.
Kageroza Inaba,
we finally meet.
It's about time you
showed yourself.
I was beginning
to worry.
I searched everywhere,
but I just couldn't
seem to find you.
Now I know why.
Believe me, it was hard work,
rescuing Soi Fon and the others,
without you realizing it.
I apologize for putting you
through all that trouble.
But I'm afraid it had to
be done, in order to make
sure everything was
brought under my control.
Oh please, you truly
believe you have the power
for such an accomplishment?
You're a very silly man.
Do you presume that such a
thing is beyond my capability?
Am I wrong?
Hrrrghh.
Don't underestimate my power,
Yoruichi Shihoin!
There are others who have
made the same mistake,
But they're no longer
around to oppose me!
In that case, it would be a big
mistake to underestimate your
adversaries!
Eh?
Huh??
[chuckle]
I don't believe it.
Byakuya! You're alive!
[Byakuya]
Yet you still won't give up.
There's only one head
of the Kuchiki Clan.
There can't be two.
Bankai.
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Senbonzakura
Kageyoshi.
I have been a witness to
the pride exhibited by you
and all the other Reigai.
As I said, there can
only be one head of
the Kuchiki Clan.
We, the Thirteen Court Guard
Squads, will uphold our duty and
honor, to destroy your
ambitions.
Prepare yourself.
[Soi Fon]
There is no way for
you to escape!
[Toshiro]
This is the
end, Kageroza.
[chuckles]
[Yoruichi]
What's so funny?
[Kageroza]
The idea that you think you
have me cornered, with so
few of you surrounding me.
I commend you originals
for fighting so well
against my Reigai army.
You all did better than I
originally anticipated.
But regardless, it won't
be enough to defeat me.
Your madness is going
to end here and now!
Heh.
[Kisuke]
[gasp]
What is it?
I've just located Ichigo's
Spiritual Pressure!
Really?!
Where is he?!
Okay everyone,
let's go.
You got it.
[Kon]
Now you're talking!
Hang on, Ichigo!
Come on.
You too, Nozomi.
[giggle]
So that's what
he meant!
[Toshiro]
In numbers alone, we're equal...
[Yoruichi]
But because none of
them are injured,
they have the advantage.
[Kenpachi]
Ha! Who cares?
Bring it on!
It's finally getting
interesting around here!
This will be your finale.
Scatter,
Senbonzakura!
Hee hee heeee!
Eh?
Bankai.
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
[gasps]
Now is our chance!
Attack!
Shunko!
Not so fast!
Agh!
Take this! Sennen Hyoro!
Shunko from his
Zanpakuto?!
He said earlier,
he can copy
whatever we do!
[Toshiro]
We need you two to stop
his counter-attack!
[Yoruichi]
On it! Soi Fon!
[Soi Fon]
Ready!
[in unison]
Time to end this!
It's useless!
Hyaah!
We'll cancel
the Kido...
...by spinning
in reverse!
[Both]
Hankisosai!
Hyaah!
Eyagh!
Ungh...
Why are you still
fighting us?
Look, your master
has been defeated.
[gasp]
Yaah!
Ht!
Ngh!
Agh!
Egh!
Heh!
That was fine
teamwork, everyone.
But as I told you,
if you were smart,
you would have been
paying attention!
[panting]
You have absolutely no chance
for victory, and maybe now,
you'll understand why!
[Kageroza]
G'augh!
What the...?
Heh heh! What's the
matter, Mr. Know-It-All?
Agh!
How dare you attack me!
Oh my, surely you of all people
would have noticed by now?
I changed places with
my double a while ago.
[Soi Fon]
Kageroza! Why didn't you
ever create a Reigai of
Lady Yoruichi?
[Kageroza]
Because of what happened
when she passed through
the Senkaimon.
[meow]
[Kageroza]
She took the form of a cat, so I
could only create a cat Reigai.
[Soi Fon]
She has a cat double?!
[meow]
[Kageroza]
Unfortunately, yes.