[MUSIC - BEAT CRUSADERS,
"TONIGHT, TONIGHT, TONIGHT"]
-Hm.
Welcome, substitute Soul Reaper.
ICHIGO: I take it your
the leader of the Bounts.
You invited us, so here we are.
-Huh.
-Ichigo.
-Yeah.
-Now then, my name
is Jin Kariya.
Pleased to meet you,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
-[grunt] How the hell
did you know my name?
-I make it my business.
Would I be correct in
assuming the lady next to you
is the Soul Reaper
Rukia Kuchiki?
RIRIN: (WHISPERING) Rukia.
-Is something wrong?
You all look as if you're
surprised to see us.
That would mean you're
afraid, because surprise
is the same as fear.
-What did you say?
-Take it easy.
He's just saying that
to get under your skin.
-Ichigo's right.
Let them say what they want.
It means nothing. [laughs]
-We're not falling for it.
-No, but this is bad.
This is really bad.
Bad, bad, bad.
That man is definitely scary.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): Those eyes.
What a repulsive glare.
RUKIA: Ichigo, you've
got to be careful.
ICHIGO: I know.
We've come here
to take back Uryu.
-I have no intention of
returning your friend.
We need the Quincy, so
I'm afraid you'll just
have to live without him.
-Get over it.
I don't care how
much you need him.
It's not what Uryu wants.
-Oh, really?
So what do you plan to do?
-Give him back to us.
Or we're going to take him back.
-You think you can?
ICHIGO: Definitely.
Rukia.
-All right.
Zeige Dich, Fried!
-You're not leaving.
-Sorry, no snakes allowed.
-How dare you?
-Ichigo, are you all right?
ICHIGO: Don't worry about me.
Just take care of Uryu.
-Be careful!
-So it's seven against one, huh?
-Don't know much
about us, do you?
We Bounts are very independent.
We're far too proud
and free spirited
to ever fight in a
group, especially
against a substitute
Soul Reaper.
I can easily handle you myself.
ICHIGO: Oh, really?
-You don't think I'm capable.
I'll tell you what, then.
Master Kariya, in order
to prove my point,
would you remove your crest?
-What's this about?
-A Bount needs his crest in
order to call out his doll.
Without our dolls, we're
basically powerless
and have no other means
to defend ourselves.
KARIYA: Take your time, Utagawa.
I'm going to enjoy
watching this.
-Feel better now?
You see if any of the other
Bounts breaks the rules
and tries to attack you.
Then you can go after
our leader Kariya,
and he'll be
completely defenseless.
He is powerless.
He can neither attack
you nor protect himself.
-Look, I don't know what kind
of game you're playing here,
but I'm going to cut you down.
-What kind of defense is that?
-[grunts]
UTAGAWA: I've got you.
-Do you really think Ichigo
will be all right back
there by himself?
-Ichigo's not an idiot.
He knows all he has to
do is buy enough time
for us to find Uryu and
get him out of here.
-Even so, I think we're
grossly unprepared to do battle
with these Bounts.
We know next to
nothing about them.
If we were to gather
more information
and carefully analyze it
to make a cohesive plan--
-Will you shut up?
If he wants to analyze, he
can do it while he's fighting.
And if you're really
worried about him,
then you should have been
thinking about a strategy
long ago, instead of
waiting until now.
-You don't have to
get so nasty about it.
I was just trying to express
my anxiety over the fact
that we stranded him there.
-Stop!
If you had a brain
in your head, we'd
realize that we can
use Noba's ability
to get us to Ichigo
whenever we want.
KURODO: Oh!
-It also means that
once we find Uryu,
we can use Noba's
space-warping ability
to get us out of this mansion.
You are able to use your
ability in here, aren't you?
-No a problem.
-You know, I'm still here.
And I resent the fact that
you act as if you're all
coming up with brilliant
ideas and trying
to make me look like an idiot.
I think it's very rude.
RUKIA: Did it feel as if most
of the Bounts in this mansion
are concentrated in
that room back there?
RIRIN: Yeah, but I think
sense one in the back.
They probably left him
there to guard Uryu.
-Huh?
Who's there?
A Soul Reaper?
-You are partially
right about that.
You thought you felt the
presence of another Bount.
But the Bount you
sensed is not a guard,
but a traitor who is being
held with the Quincy.
-You mean the Bount
who saved Uryu?
MAKI: That's right.
-What's your story?
What could the Bounts
possibly offer you?
-You probably
haven't heard of me.
I served with Squad 11.
Maki Ichinose.
-Really?
You were in Squad 11?
-Yes.
Back before Kenpachi
Zaraki was captain.
-So you ran away from
the Soul Society?
All right, then.
What are you doing here?
-Some other time.
-What?
-No way!
-[grunt]
-[shout]
-That's your strategy?
Create a hallucination,
then teleport and attack
from behind?
Not a bad idea, I suppose.
But it's just a childish trick.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): He's
strong-- very strong.
-You're a Soul
Reaper, aren't you?
-Squad 13.
Rukia Kuchiki.
-What are you doing
running around in a Gigai?
And why don't you have
your Zanpakuto with you?
-Due to some unfortunate
circumstances,
I can't use it-- although
I've got Hado 33.
Sokatsui!
-Chant discard?
Your skilled in throwing spells
without uttering the chant.
-It's obvious you're
familiar with the technique.
So why do you act surprised?
-Chant discard weakens
the power of Kido.
What's surprising is that
you have this much power,
and yet you aren't
using your true power.
I can't quite put
my finger on it,
but I sense that this isn't
your true power, is it?
-I wish I could lie to you
and say that it wasn't.
But the truth is, that was
the full extent of my power.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): At
least in my current state.
My powers haven't
fully returned.
MAKI: Whatever.
RUKIA: Why would a Soul Reaper
want to help the Bounts?
-Good question.
Tell me, do you
know how to become
a captain of the 13
Court Guard Squads?
RUKIA: What?
-You know.
The same method
Kenpachi Zaraki used
when he made his name famous
throughout the Soul Society.
He didn't earn it with
intelligence or cunning-- not
Zaraki.
He became captain using nothing
but his physical strength.
He crushed the
vision the captain
and I had created and discarded
it like a fleeting dream.
Everything-- everything was
destroyed in that instant!
I refused to follow Kenpachi
Zaraki like the other squad
members.
I had seen him for what he was.
RUKIA: So you left, and
you ran away forever.
-I wandered around,
disillusioned and heartless,
until he gave me
a reason to live.
Jin Kariya-- because
of him, I was
able to pick up my Zanpakuto and
find something worth fighting.
I now have a purpose again.
I will stand by him--
he who lives eternally,
he who is searching
for what lies
beyond by breaking
all laws of nature.
Once more, I plan
to lay everything
I have on the line for this man.
-So you're willing
to help him, knowing
full well what he plans to do?
-I think we've wasted
enough time with talk.
I'm sorry, but there's no way
I'm going to allow you to pass.
-[gasp] That spiritual pressure.
Ichigo and the
others must be here.
Open up!
Open the door!
URYU (VOICEOVER): Ichigo,
don't do anything crazy.
[gasping]
YOSHINO (VOICEOVER): I
might have to get out.
[grunting]
-[laughs]
-That old trick?
Are you making snakes
come out of walls again?
-[grunt]
-Fried!
-No matter how sharp your sword
is, it'll never caught Fried!
-Who cares about it, anyway?
Why should I waste
my time with that
snake when I can
attack you directly?
-How will you do that?
-Like this, you jerk?
-That's Flash Step.
-[gasp]
-I'll cut you
deeper next to time.
-I have to admit, I'm impressed.
-How sloppy of you.
I don't see why
I should give you
my strength if you're
going to be so weak.
-No need to worry.
Have you made all
of the preparation?
-Of course.
-Just let me know when you're
done talking over there.
UTAGAWA: Thank you.
I think we're finished.
-[gasp]
-[laughs]
ICHIGO: What?
What the hell is this?
FRIED: Snake Net.
-Damn it.
-No one has survived
Fried's absolute barrier.
You can run if you want, but
it's just a matter of time.
-[grunts]
-You wouldn't happen to be
familiar with the term spinal
flexion, would you?
It's the kind of
thing that happens
when you touch
something hot and react
even before the signal has
time to reach your brain.
ICHIGO: So what's your point?
-I just thought you'd like to
know the physics behind Snake
Net.
If you try to approach
me with a Flash Step,
it's as if Fried
intercepts the impulse
and reacts even before you do.
FRIED: You can't
escape anywhere.
-It's a secret technique.
How do you know
about the Flash Step?
KARIYA: I was certain
the Soul Society would
interfere at some point.
It seems they've
always got their noses
in other people's business.
So it was only natural
that I learned as much
about Soul Reapers as possible.
ICHIGO: What?
UTAGAWA: If you two
are done discussing
things-- continue Fried.
-I understand.
-[grunts]
-It's useless.
-[shouts]
-It's over.
-How uneventful.
Hm.
Please forgive
me, Master Kariya.
It appears as though
I accidentally
damaged your mansion.
-Don't worry about it.
-What?
Done already?
-Heh.
A little sloppy,
don't you think?
UTAGAWA: What shall I do now?
Would you like me to
track down the others?
KARIYA: I've left
them to Ichinose.
UTAGAWA: Hm.
Ichinose, huh?
-But we have other
guests, whom I
expect will be arriving shortly,
that need to be dealt with.
-I understand.
-Hey, Bount.
Not quite dead yet.
-I see that.
-According to what the
two of you just said,
it sounds like
Rukia and the others
could use a little
bit of help right now.
So if you don't mind,
I think I'll just
finish up here and head on
over to give them a hand.
-How much help will you
be in your condition?
ICHIGO: You haven't done as much
damage as you think you have.
-Hm.
Impressive.
You obviously have incredible
spiritual pressure.
Is that protected your body?
-Pretty much.
I've learned to envelope my
body in spiritual pressure.
It reduces the damage
I take from my enemies.
It's not like I spent all
that time in the Soul Society
fighting for nothing.
-Ha.
I wish I could say I'm impressed
with these tactics of yours.
But it's only a matter of
time, because you cannot escape
Fried's Snake Net.
I plan on crushing you
with a power so strong,
your spiritual pressure
will be helpless against it.
-I don't think so.
But you can go ahead
and try, because I'm not
going to run away.
And I'm not going
to be by some snake.
-Get him, Fried.
-Yes.
Here I go.
I'll tear you into pieces!
-Getsuga Tensho!
-What was that?
That spiritual pressure?
-Ichigo.
-[gasp] Master Kariya!
-Come back here!
Hado 33!
-[gasp] That
spiritual pressure--
it was Getsuga Tensho.
Damn it to hell.
SADO (VOICEOVER): Ichigo.
ORIHIME (VOICEOVER): Ichigo.
-What now?
-Keep running.
-You know, I just
remembered something.
This hide out of yours
is nice and secluded.
I don't have to worry
about bothering anyone.
So there's no need to hold back
with using my Getsuga Tensho.
[gasp]
-You were able to overwhelm
Utagawa's technique using
nothing but raw power.
What an amusing young man.
ICHIGO: You bastard.
UTAGAWA (VOICEOVER):
He's completely reckless.
Still, it's perfect.
-Fried.
KARIYA: This was my
favorite mansion.
But now look what you've done.
You've completely ruined it.
ICHIGO: Gee, sorry about that.
Do you want me to tear it down
so you can start all over?
-I think I'll pass on that.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Damn.
He sure doesn't lack confidence.
-[gasp]
What the hell?
KARIYA: Hm.
What is this, Utagawa?
What are you up to?
-What does it look like?
I've decided to relieve you
of the burden of [? mansho ?]
Kariya.
-Utagawa.
UTAGAWA: Tell me, Koga, are you
honestly satisfied with the way
things are going under
Kariya's leadership.
Kariya's method is
far too convoluted.
There is no end in sight.
-So, Utagawa, you honestly think
you can do better than him?
-Without a doubt.
BOUNT: I don't trust you.
-The only reason Kariya has
been in charge up to this point
is because he had the power.
But as you can all see, his
[? mansho ?] is in my hands
now!
I've been biding my time,
waiting for the opportunity
to take it from him.
But never in my dreams did I
imagine it would be so easy.
ICHIGO: What are you doing?
You're fighting each other now?
-I doubt it'll come to that.
Remember what I
said earlier, when
I mentioned that we Bounts
are fiercely independent?
For us to collaborate on
anything is very rare.
We are a few in number.
But when we have
to work together
to achieve a single goal,
the one who acts as a leader
must be truly exceptional.
Someone with qualities
like mine, not Kariya's
KARIYA: Like arrogance
and stupidity?
-Quit acting like
you're in charge!
In case you forgot, I'm
holding your crest in my hand!
KARIYA: And your point is?
-Have you completely
lost your mind, Kariya?
You stand there as if you're
still in control, knowing
full well that I now possess
the source of all your power!
You have nothing at all.
You're powerless, defenseless.
At this point, you
couldn't defend yourself
against me, much less this
substitute Soul Reaper.
-So tell me then.
Why is it you seem
so panicked, Utagawa?
-I'm in complete control
of the situation.
You're the one who's panicked.
You're just acting calm.
Now, kneel down before
me as your leader!
I have your Mansho
here, and I'll-- [grunt]
-Why do you keep
telling me that?
Am I supposed to be impressed?
-Kariya!
[gasp] What was that?
The only that can block a
doll's attack is a doll!
It's impossible!
-Did I ever say that
I removed my crest?
-You bastard.
Ichinose.
-Hes' a Soul Reaper.
What's that?
FRIED: Don't interfere!
UTAGAWA: [gasp] What's this?
[shouts]
-It's all over.
-No, it can't be.
-Hey, you.
What's with the Zanpakuto?
MAKI: Nijigasumi.
That's the name of my Zanpakuto.
-Nijigasumi.
MAKI: Master Kariya.
I'm glad your safe.
KARIYA: Everything is fine.
ICHIGO: Hey, what is this?
What's a Soul Reaper doing here?
-So tell me, is it true that
you defeated Kenpachi Zaraki?
-What the--?
-Ex-Squad 11, Maki Ichinose.
-Tell me something.
Why would a Soul Reaper
want to help a Bount?
-Since you won't
live long enough
to understand the
answer, there's
no point in telling you.
Come on!
-Fine.
All right.
So you don't want to talk now?
That's just too bad,
because you're not
going to get another chance.
[theme music]
ICHIGO: Ririn, how does a
Bount's spiritual pressure
differ from a regular
Soul Reaper or a Hollow.
RIRIN: It tastes different.
A Soul Reaper's spiritual
pressure is refreshing.
A Hollow's spiritual
pressure is smooth and rich.
A Bount's spiritual
pressure is a bit thick.
Get what I'm saying?
ICHIGO: Not at all.
[theme music]
-Illustrated Guide
to Soul Reapers.
GROUP: Golden!
-The lieutenants meeting
is now called to order.
Lieutenant Kusajishi shall
address the first item
on the agenda.
-Well now, let's see.
Should a banana be
considered a proper snack
to bring on Hollow
extermination expeditions?
-[clears throat] Any ideas?
-Bananas are an excellent
source of potassium and fiber.
We should probably consider
them more as a main course.
-I think Byakuya hit the
nail right on the head.
-Why did Captain
Kuchiki say that?