[theme music]
-Move it, move it!
-Put your back into it!
[shouting]
SQUAD MEMBER: Here's my report.
We've confirmed the
rumors of strange events
in Kusajishi, Captain.
-Just what sort of events?
-Someone has gathered all
the able-bodied men together,
and has put them to work cutting
down trees in Kusajishi Forest.
-Captain.
-And are the Bounts behind this?
-On the surface,
the leader seems
to be the bookie who runs one
of Kusahishi's gambling dens.
-Who's behind all of this?
-Well, there are some clues,
but nothing definite yet.
-What should we do now?
-This is the clue
I've been waiting for.
We're going to have to
investigate it ourselves.
-Are you going to
search the forest?
-No, not the forest.
We're going to see Renji Abarai.
-All right, but why are
we going to see him?
-Because Renji has had more
contact with the Bounts
than anyone else, and I need to
find out everything he knows.
And you're coming with me.
-I just got another report from
our scout on Kariya's gang.
-So let's hear it.
What kind of trouble's
he stirring up?
-Plenty.
He's gathered a pretty
big crowd of followers
in just a short time.
Word is he's lured in thugs
and low lifes from all
over Kusajishi already.
They're are pretty
tough bunch, too,
but of course, they
don't have any spirit
energy on their side.
So even in large
numbers, they can't
hope to win against
Soul Reapers in the end.
-Except Soul Reapers won't fight
for real against ordinary Rukon
District folk.
And fighting while continually
holding yourself back
is a huge burden.
-Good point.
You're right.
-The Bounts are well accustomed
to being outnumbered.
I think we can count on them
coming up with a bunch of ways
to go up against the Seireitei.
-What's your plan, then?
-We're going to stop them.
Mobs never have any discipline.
We'll take advantage of that
and make it easier for the Soul
Reapers to fight them by
breaking up the crowd.
Which is where you
come in, brother.
-Since when am I
your brother, Ganju?
-Look, we don't have
a lot of time here.
I need you to gather as
many men as you can, Bull.
-Ganju.
Why the hell's this
suddenly so important?
-A certain friend of mine
is working really hard
to take down the Bounts, and
he's asked me for my help.
That's all there is to it.
-So who is it?
-Ganju.
You must be talking
about Ichigo, right?
-Mm-hm.
-Ah, the amazing and
beautiful power of friendship.
When we have that, none of
us are ever completely alone,
are we?
Helping one another is the
most important thing of all.
That's what I--
-Oh, be quiet!
Anyway, the Bounts
gave this friend
of mine a real rough time.
And I want to make
sure he survives this.
-A bond between friends?
Coming from you, that's
a little bit surprising.
Well, all right.
I never liked that
bookie anyway,
so I'll join up with you.
I, Daiji Hirasago,
the Bull of Kusajishi,
hereby agree to help you, Ganju.
-I guess the Bull of Kusajishi
wasn't your real name
after all.
-What made you
decide to go by that
instead of using your real name?
-Because it's cool!
-He's just as bad as Ganju.
-Uh-huh.
-Hey, Konboi, Max, Lady.
-Yes, boss?
-Round up everyone you can
find, and get ready to move out.
-If nothing else,
it looks like we've
gotten better at
repairing things.
-With all of the Ryoka
invasions of late,
there's no shortage of
practice for both the swordsmen
and the brick layers.
-No matter how many
times we repair it,
the issue has not
yet been addressed.
We still don't know
who destroyed it,
or what their purpose was.
-It was obviously a diversion.
-Oh?
-No doubt the Bounts
did this immediately
upon their arrival to focus
our attention elsewhere.
-Well then, why did
they destroy something
that's so easily repairable?
-Ah, you are naive.
Don't you see?
The distraction
this provided was
intended to be
mental, not physical.
The entire Seireitei is
in complete chaos now.
-Hm.
-How lazy we must have
become, to let intruders
into the Seireitei so easily.
But wait.
I wonder--
-Is there anything wrong?
-What is it?
-It can't.
It's nothing.
Come, Nemu.
I just remembered there's
someplace I have to be.
[scream]
-An exploding egg?
-You have weird dreams, Ichigo.
-You slept too long.
-About time you finally woke up.
Now, let's eat.
-Mm.
-Ran'Tao.
-Hm?
-So, do you think we can
pick up where we left off?
-I'm so sorry about yesterday.
Now, what was it
you wanted to ask?
-Well, it's about your face.
-What?
-I met a Bount in the
world of the living,
and her face looked exactly
like yours, Ran'Tao.
Yoshino Soma.
That was her name.
So, what do you think it means?
-That's what I've
been wondering about.
How could that even be possible?
-From what you tell
me, I'd say this Bount
you met is probably
one of my copies.
-Copies?
-In the original experiments
that resulted in the Bounts,
we were trying to
create immortal souls.
Therefore we did not use
normal souls for that purpose.
-What kind of souls did you use?
-We created artificial souls
that were based on our own,
and then we modified
them according
to the parameters
of the experiments.
--Artificial souls?
-We did that to be
safe, because even
though the creation
of eternal life
was theoretically possible,
we knew that using human souls
was ethically on
questionable ground.
So we decided to use
our own souls as models
to create the artificial
versions based on them.
-Then what?
-There was an accident.
The artificial souls
suffered a mutation,
and were incorporated
into the cycle of rebirth.
-So the Bounts are a mutation?
-Yes.
And though we started
with artificial souls,
the fact remains they were
based on those of Soul Reapers.
As a result, the
Bounts can be expected
to possess incredible powers.
-Now I see.
So they can use their
dolls in the same way
that Soul Reapers
use their zanpakuto.
Is that right?
-Indeed.
Since then, the research
into artificial souls
has grown a great deal.
And eventually the gikongan
mod-soul technologies
were developed.
-Wait a minute.
Then that must mean that
the Bounts are really
my distant relatives, or
ancestors, or something.
-That's right.
And that explains why
you and the others
have the ability to
sense and track Bounts.
You're all based on the
same kind of technology.
-I always thought
that since they
dived through the
cycle of rebirth,
the features of the Soul
Reapers they were based on
would have changed.
But you say this Bount
called Yoshino resembled me
quite closely.
-Yes.
-So what happened to her?
-Jin Kariya betrayed
and murdered her.
-All I know is we
have to find a way
to stop the Bounts, and fast.
-Huh?
Kenny, are you
going to meet Maki?
-Yeah.
The word is Squad 10 has finally
managed to track and locate
him.
-I wanna go, too.
It's been a while, and I
haven't seen him in a long time.
-Move it, move it!
Come on!
-Pull!
-This way!
-Let's go, men!
-Men!
Take a rest from your
labors for just a moment,
and listen to me.
First I want to pay tribute
to the courage all of you
have exhibited.
This is your fight, after all.
Even though you are
from the Soul Society,
that same Soul Society has long
controlled and discriminated
against you.
But today you shall be released.
Today you will be free!
We shall soon commence our
attack on the Seireitei,
but we will need your help.
Are you prepared
to fight with us?
-Yeah!
-Go forth and crush
the Soul Reapers!
[cheering]
-It's just as I expected.
-What have you found
out, Master Mayuri?
-The one who snuck
into the Seireitei
and caused all that
destruction was Maki Ichinose.
And, that's not all.
Look.
-Yes.
I'd like to see this.
-Even though there have been no
Soul Reapers passing through,
nonetheless the Senkaimon
has been opening and closing
quite frequently.
This is the record of every
opening and closing, showing
all the times Ichinose
has entered and left.
The gate opens and
closes every time
he passes through the Senkaimon,
even if he's invisible.
And no matter how skillfully
he conceals himself,
he is not able to completely
hide his spiritual pressure
as he passes.
Of course, this was
something that only
I had the intelligence
to be aware of.
I knew that Ichinose had been
breaking into the database,
making alterations and
hiding information.
But I wasn't fooled by that.
Heh, heh, heh.
Naturally, I already knew
all about Maki Ichinose's
zanpakuto, and its ability
to make him visible
using light refraction.
And then there's the
special technique
the Bounts are able to use to
hdie their spiritual pressure.
If Ichinose had
such a capability,
there is no way that
he wouldn't use it.
So the obvious conclusion
is that Ichniose
was making himself invisible,
then entering the Seireitei
and creating these diversions.
There may be other
occasions where
he broke into the database
that I'm not aware of yet,
so I'm going to conduct a
search for any events that
fit that pattern.
I thought so.
it is amazing that he could
have broken in this many times
without anyone noticing.
What?
-What is the matter, master?
-It can't be!
It's not-- what's this?
Take a look at that!
-I see it, but--
-Isn't this one of
the missing files
that you restored for me
after they were somehow
secretly erased?
-Yes.
That's one of them.
-It was when I first
saw this that I came up
with the idea of drawing the
Bounts to the Soul Society
by using the Quincy
and his power.
Was it Ichniose who deliberately
entered this into the database,
knowing that I would see it?
If that's the case, then they've
been using me all this time.
It all makes sense.
They wanted the
Quincy to use his bow
so they could get here
to the Soul Society.
How dare they!
Filthy Bount invaders!
-I've found their location.
It appears they've been
building something deep
in Kusajishi Forest.
-Well, that fits
with the reports
we have that they've managed to
gather a large number of thugs
together.
-At least now, thanks to that,
the area around Kusajishi
is fairly calm and quiet.
-So, what shall we do, Captain?
-Since we've already
come this far,
let's go the rest of the way.
These thugs are still residents
of the Rukon District,
so in the event you encounter
any, try not to hurt them.
-Understand.
-Renji, are you able
to use your zanpakuto?
-Huh?
-You used your Higa Zekko attack
in the world of the living.
And your zanpakuto
hasn't recovered, has it?
-I'll be just fine.
I don't need my
shikai to take care
of a bunch of common thugs.
-But what if instead of thugs,
you should encounter Bounts?
-I'm not sure.
-Well, if that
happens, you can always
run back to the Seireitei and be
the messenger bearing bad news.
-Oh, thanks a lot.
-Let's go.
-Are you going?
-Yeah.
Orihime's Shun Shun
Rikka just told me
that the Bounts are
definitely up to something
in the Kusajishi forest.
So we've got to get going now.
-And what about you, Ran'Tao?
-I doubt that this is the only
thing the Bounts are up to.
And just in case
it isn't, I have
something I need to stay
here and get prepared.
-I understand.
I hope to see you again soon.
-Yes.
-Oh, wait.
-Hm?
-There's one more thing that I
still wanted to ask you about.
-Yes?
-I assume you know about Uryu,
and about his special Quincy
accessory.
How long do you believe
that'll keep on working?
-I'm afraid there's
no way of knowing.
It could become useless today,
or it could be tomorrow.
With all the destructive
energy it has,
it's conceivable that it
could obliterate everything
inside a 20 square mile radius
if it goes off accidentally.
-Well, there's no point
in getting scared of it
before I even use it.
I'll just have to do what I can.
-Hey.
Wait.
-Just be careful.
[shouting]
-Master, all of our
preparations for the surprise
attack on the Seireitei
are on schedule.
-Good work.
-Master Kariya?
-Yes, Ichinose?
-I've just learned that
there are several Soul
Reapers near here, and
approaching this location.
And apparently one
of them is a captain.
Unless you have
other plans for me,
I'd like you permission
to remain here and deal
with all of them myself.
-Finishing some of
the Soul Reapers
now can only make
our job easier later.
They're all yours.
-Sir.
You will not regret this.
Thank you.
[groan]
-Another two.
-There's no doubt
the Bounts are near.
So that's the reason why
these sentries are posted.
-But so few of them.
I heard that Kariya
recruited hundreds of men.
-So what now?
-We're going to split
up and keep moving in.
And be careful.
-Right.
-Guess I found one.
Who are you?
-Maki Ichinose.
-I see.
You're the Soul Reaper who's
been working for the Bounts,
aren't you?
-I am no longer a Soul Reaper.
My allegiance is to the
great master Kariya.
-So where are the Bounts, then?
-Enough of your
questions, captain.
-If you won't answer, then I'll
have to force it out of you.
Attack!
At least tell my why
you choose to fight
on the side of the Bounts
when you have this much skill.
-Because Master Kariya's
way is paved with justice.
-Meaning?
-There's no justice anymore
in the Soul Society.
But now Master Kariya
will cleanse this place
and purify it.
-You traitor.
[groan]
-Is that Ichigo?
-Well, it's Toshiro.
HITSUGAYA: That's
Captain Hitsugaya to you.
-What the hell are you
two doing here, anyway?
-Rangiku.
And Renji.
-It would appear that
most of the thugs
have already left
the forest, Captain.
-Wah!
Stop it!
I want off, I want
off, I want off!
Oh!
Oh.
Uryu and Ichigo.
-What are you doing here?
-Well, we're with Ganju.
[shouting]
-These low lifes
are no challenge.
-Round 'em up, men!
Don't let any of 'em get away!
-Chad and I came along
with Ganju and his friends
to try and stop all
of Kariya's thugs
from gathering in the forest.
-But for some
reason, there doesn't
seem to be as many of them as
we were told there would be.
-I'm aware of that.
ICHIGO: What is it, Chad?
-Among the Bounts,
there is one who
can control space the
same way Noba does.
-That old man.
ICHINOSE: You're all
too late, anyway.
-Huh?
-Hm?
-Master Kariya and
the main attack force
are already on their
way to the Seireitei.
-Are you Ryoka?
[laughter]
-Does it make any difference?
-Huh?
Just who are you, stranger?
-I'm Koga.
I am a Bount.
Stand aside, please,
and let me in.
-I will never let the
likes of you inside!
-Then I suppose I'll just
have to go through you.
Zeige Dich, Dalk.
Now.
MAN: The army of thugs which
has been forming in the Rukon
District 79 has now
appeared without warning
at the Kuto Gate
and Kukurio Gate.
Report to battle
stations at once.
-Prepare to pry open the gate!
MAN: I repeat, the
enemy has attacked--
-Soon now, Kurkuio Gate
will fall before us.
MAN: Report to battle
stations at once.
[shouting]
[theme music]
YACHIRU: Tah-dah!
Kenny finally has another
part in the next episode.
KENPACHI: Sorry to
keep you waiting.
Now, shall we do this, Ichigo?
Come at me for real
with your bankai!
ICHIGO: Ah!
No!
Find yourself another opponent.
KENPACHI: Relax.
It doesn't matter who I fight.
ICHIGO: It does to me!
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers.
RANGIKU: Golden!
Just look, everyone.
I've brought back
presents for all of you
from the world of the living.
A kitty, snacks, a penant,
a little bear, a shield,
and this.
-What are these cloth
scraps supposed to be?
-It's a bathing suit.
-Well, where is the
rest of the material?
-You should take that
up with Captain Kyoraku,
since he was the
one who insisted
I buy you something sexy.
I tried it on, but of
course it didn't fit me.
-Then give it to him!