[theme music]
NARRATOR: In order
to save Orihime,
who was kidnapped
by the Arrancars,
Icihgo, Chad, Uryu,
Rukia, and Renji
have all snuck into Hueco
Mundo, the realm of the hollows.
On the journey to Aizen's
fortress, Las Noches,
our heroes struggled
against endless attacks
from the Arrancar forces.
Upon breaking into the
fortress, the group
split up and took
five different paths
in their search for Orihime.
Standing guard over
Ichigo and Nel's path
was Privaron Espada number
103, known as Dordoni.
in the fight that
followed, Ichigo gravely
underestimated his
opponent's abilities.
-Well, Giralda!
-I hope it was worth the wait.
Let me introduce
you to my Bankai.
-It's about time.
I knew you'd have to
use it eventually.
And yet, you have a
stronger form, don't you?
I know all about
your hollowfication.
Now you need to use it!
Do it now, or I'll
force you to, nino.
-Is that so?
Don't you have any shame?
-Of course I do.
I'm ashamed at myself
for not getting
you to fight at full
strength before now!
-All right then.
Sorry, but I can only show
it to you for an instant.
-Oh?
What happened?
What's going on?
-I told you.
Only an instant.
-While hollowfied, Ichigo
was able to defeat Dordoni.
Nel then healed
Dordoni's wounds,
but within moments
after his treatment,
Dordoni surprised them
by attacking once again.
-How could you be foolish
enough to allow someone
to heal your enemy's wound?
You think I'm not going
to attack you again!
-That's insane!
You're barely in one
piece and now you
wanna come back for more?
-Wounds can injure one's
body, but not one's spirit.
As long as my will to
fight remains strong,
my physical wounds
are insignificant!
You're just as sweet
as the chocolate!
Nino!
-Ichigo.
-Huh?
What a surprise.
What brings the Exequias here?
-We have orders to locate
the injured intruder
and execute him.
-That order came from whom?
-I really can't say.
-You want to get
past me, I presume?
-Are you threatening
to block our way?
It would be hopeless for you
to resist us in your condition.
You're a Pivaron Espada.
Besides, your sword is broken
and you can't release it.
You don't stand a chance
against us in a fight.
-Heh.
Is that true, [spanish]?
I'm more powerful
than you think.
I am glad you were able to make
it out of here in time, nino.
If you had not countered
my final attack,
you would still
be here, and you'd
have been executed by
the squad of morons.
My powers have
weakened so badly,
you probably could have
defeated me without Hollowfying.
You must have sensed
how humiliating
that would have been for me.
You transformed, even though
it would drain your long term
strength to do so.
You preserved my
dignity as a warrior.
I am grateful for that.
This is the least I can do
to thank you, but beware
of the ones you encounter as you
move deeper into the fortress.
They will cut you down
without a moment's thought.
Do not hesitate to
attack your enemy,
do not waver when you
deliver the finishing blow.
Above all, do not
heal his wounds
once we have defeated him.
You'll have to leave your
chocolate sweetness behind.
You have to become like
the devil himself, nino.
Become as strong as a demon.
Become as fierce as a demon.
You must learn that the
only way to endure cruelty
is to become cruel yourself.
Otherwise, you will be consumed.
-I could be in trouble here.
Damn it.
-I have an update, Lord Aizen.
It's not good news.
We've just received word that
Parivaron Espada, number 103,
Dordoni Allessandro
Del Socaccio,
has been killed
by the intruders.
-I see.
Apparently it was a
bit harder for the boy
than I thought it would be.
I assumed defeating someone
of Dordoni's skill level
would've been less of a
challenge, and far easier
for him.
How interesting.
Regardless.
There's something you failed
to report to me, isn't there?
Tell me.
Who specifically
sent the Exequias out
to eliminate the boy?
-I-- It-- It--
-What's the problem?
Didn't I make the question
clear enough for you?
SZAYELAPORRO: It
was me, Lord Aizen.
-It was you, Szayelaporro.
-My humblest apologies, sir.
I wanted to make sure
we eliminated him
while he was injured.
I thought it was a
rare opportunity,
so I ordered them to go at
my own discretion, My Lord.
I realize, Lord Aizen, that,
even though I did it for you,
I was wrong not
to ask permission.
I'll accept any
form of punishment
you wish to administer.
-That won't be necessary.
Just as long as you
had a good reason,
there's no need to punish you.
-Thank you very much, my lord.
I should return to my duties.
-However, in the
future, Szayelaporro,
I want your reports to be
more detailed and accurate.
The data that you collected from
Dordoni regarding the intruder,
will it be of any help
with your research?
-Yes.
It will.
-That's splendid.
Keep up the good work.
-Interesting.
You seem to be having
quite a lot of fun,
even though one of your
subordinates was just killed.
-Do I look happy?
-You seem to be amused.
I think maybe energized
is the right word.
Excited that those kids are
winning fight after fight,
overcoming your
defenses, and making
their way to your inner sanctum.
AIZEN: Amused, you say?
Maybe so.
I suppose I do feel something
akin to that emotion.
Do you find that strange, Gin?
-Not at all, my lord.
Oddly enough, I feel
somewhat the same myself.
[laughter]
-You think you can save
yourself by hiding?
Hmph.
[mumbling]
[shouting]
-Huh?
Tell me, why was I
carrying you like that?
-What do you mean, why
are you carrying me?
That's my question, you egghead.
You said, I feel Nel's
spiritual pressure nearby,
forget about it.
Then you got hyped
up, grabbed at me,
and brought me
down this corridor.
Are you messing with me?
-No!
It's not that.
I just got excited when
I thought Nel was nearby.
Everything else is just a blur.
-You know what?
Your whole brain is a blur.
-I really couldn't help myself.
-Now you're telling me you
have no impulse control.
Great.
All right, stand up.
I guess there's
no way around it.
We'll have to go look for Nel.
-That hurts, you know?
I'd like it if you
didn't keep doing that.
RENJI: What you did to
me hurt a whole lot more.
-Hm?
Huh?
Pe--
-What?
Now what's wrong?
-Wait a minute.
Pesche's gone.
Where is he?
When did he disappear?
-What do you mean?
Are you talking about that
guy who looks like a skeleton?
He was never here to begin with!
-What?
Are you sure about that?
You mean Pesche, who's
with me all this time,
he's never been anything more
than an illusion in my mind,
right from the very beginning?
-How did you come up with that?
You are a mental case, an
hysterical personality.
-Pesche!
[shivering]
-How many times do I
have to tell you, moron?
You're not going to be
getting away from me.
Huh?
Where are your manners, idiot?
You shouldn't attack me when
I'm trying to talk to you.
Don't you have any matters?
Honestly.
I hope human men
aren't all like you.
It's hardly worth
the effort it's
going to take to wipe you out!
Come back here, fancy pants!
-That's a joke, coming from you!
-I told you that won't work!
-She may be an
Arrancar, but she's
a small, lightweight girl.
She's fast enough
to repel my attacks.
I'll just have to
keep coming at her
and hope I'm able to
score a direct hit.
-You're becoming a
pest, you weirdo.
-Veer, now!
Now strike!
Good.
I can do this.
-Nice try, four eyes.
-Her weapon moves in a straight
line when it's released.
Even after she throws it.
Or when she pulls it back.
So I should avoid
attacking her head on,
and focus on shooting at her
from positions she can't easily
respond to.
That way--
-Weirdo!
Having trouble
aiming that thing?
Hm?
-Now I just have to
control the arrows
with my spiritual pressure.
-Oh, no you don't!
Stop moving around!
Yah!
-I got her.
-It's time to quit
playing around.
-It's curving!
-You're not very bright.
Take a good look around you.
You just dug your own grave.
I tricked you, moron.
While you were on the offensive,
you broke all these pillars,
and now you're left wide open.
There were just too many of
them for me to destroy alone.
And decides, it
would've been a bother.
Thank you.
Now I can weave
my weapon around,
and you have nowhere
left to hide.
-Dammit!
-Now watch this!
Spin around!
Aw, what's wrong?
You're not giving
up already, are you?
-I'm in trouble here.
-You can't keep that up forever.
You're just wasting your time.
-Damn.
[laughter]
[panting]
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): Uryu and
Chad's spiritual pressures
have been fluctuating
for a while now.
Are they in battle
with the enemy?
No.
I don't need to
worry about them.
I need to focus on getting to
Orihime as quickly as possible.
What in the world?
Ah?
What's this?
How can there be
blue skies here?
All I did was follow that
corridor, and now I'm outside?
What's going on?
-Do you want me to
explain it to you?
-Huh?
-Come with me.
-Wait!
ARRANCAR: Ah.
Good.
I can finally relax now.
Sorry.
But I simply cannot stand
the sunlight out there.
It does not reach
inside the palace.
-Allow me to take off my
mask and greet you properly.
-My name is Aaroniero.
Aaroniero Arruruerie, also
known as Espada number nine.
-Kaien.
No!
[theme music]
SZAYELAPORRO: Lord
Aizen has finally
given me permission to
carry out my experiments
without restriction!
I just have to figure out which
subject will be the first one
to provide samples.
GIN: You're going
to let Szayelaporro
do whatever he wants?
AIZEN: Why not?
Let's leave him to
his own devices.