Ichigo Kurosaki.
I've been expecting you.
We'll meet again,
here in the Soul Society.
Returning to the Soul Society
is going to be far riskier than
when you went the first time.
Kisuke did warn me.
And I haven't forgotten.
There's no choice.
I have to get to the
Soul Society quickly!
Gokei.
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
There is one thing that
the both of us share.
To protect my pride...
I'll use any means necessary.
I knew we would face each other
in battle, sooner or later.
It was only a matter of time.
I can see that
you're wounded.
It won't be an issue.
Just as I expected.
You are predictable.
I would never run, no
matter what the situation.
Stand aside, I'm coming through.
I'm afraid I can't allow that.
[in unison]
There can only be one
Byakuya Kuchiki!
Kenny, I'm not so sure
you should be doing this.
Maybe you should have
rested a little bit longer.
You're walking like
a tired old man.
You're wrong.
And you're worried
for nothing.
The fact is, I'm
feeling awesome.
I'm ready for battle.
Hmmm...
[gasp]
Kenny, it's one of
those imposters!
You're right, Yachiru.
But it makes no
difference to me.
So how did you phrase it?
"When the leader of the
Punishment Force draws
her sword, an execution
battle is imminent."
Right?
So it's an ambush, is it?
Well, I sure hope you guys
are gonna make this fun.
Kill him!
I can feel it.
Many battles are
just beginning!
Oh!
Insolent youth!
We have to find Kageroza
and apprehend him quickly!
Ah!
Oh, Shiro?
Momo?!
So how does it look?
There's a lot of fighting
going on, and it seems the
Captains haven't made it to
Kageroza's location yet.
What about Ichigo?
He appears to be making
good time on his way to
the Soul Society.
That's a relief.
Except it's all
going too smoothly.
Kageroza couldn't possibly
have missed Ichigo's presence.
What's with the
provocative look,
you lech!
I know what you're up to,
and you can stop stripping
her with your eyes, buddy!
Hey, I'm not a perv,
like you!
What'd you say?!
You and I
need to talk.
Hey, let go of me!
I have a right to
speak my mind!
You can't treat me like
some kind of stuffed
animal or something!
Help! I'm being toy-napped!
So. What is it?
There's something I
want to ask about.
When you were with Nozomi...
Did you notice anything
different in the way
she behaved, anything
out of the ordinary?
I'm not sure what you mean.
I'm trying to figure out
why Kageroza's after her.
Once I return and I have
retrieved Nozomi...
Then I will be able to
completely show all of
you my true power.
When that occurs, not only
the Soul Society but also
the World of the Living,
will be forced to exist
under my control.
She is the key to all of this.
[Rukia]
My guess is, that girl is
carrying around some kind of
secret. It's something big.
[Mayuri]
It could be that what he
wants is something he's
hidden in her body.
After mulling it over,
that's what we concluded.
But of course, that doesn't
answer the key question.
What is it that's
hidden inside her?
What is the secret that
Kageroza needs that can
control both the Soul Society
and the World of the Living?
Do you have any idea
what it might be?
Hmm.
Something hidden inside
her body, you say?
All right, I admit it!
I did see her naked,
but it was an accident,
and it was just one time!
You have to believe me,
it was a coincidence that
I happened to walk in on
her at the wrong moment!
[sigh]
It wasn't like I was
worried about her or anything!
Anyway, the bottom line is,
if she knows about it and
doesn't want to tell us,
we can't force it out of her!
Well obviously you like
her and don't want to
see her get hurt!
Umm??
Wait a minute, what the hell
are you talking about?!
No! Are you out of your mind?
You've got to be kidding me!
No way would I be
attracted to her!
She's a violent smart-ass!
I don't have any feelings for
her, and I don't know anything!
That's my final word!
I really don't care if
she comes or goes!
That's how little
interest I have!
[sigh]
Augh!
Why did you
do that?
Just because.
[computer beeps rapidly]
Huh?
What does that mean?
It's good news.
Looks like Ichigo made
it to the Soul Society.
Hold on...
This is way off the mark.
Kisuke must have made a
mistake in his calculations.
Not really.
I summoned you here.
Kageroza!
Don't blame your friend.
I tweaked the Precipice
World a bit.
What the hell for?
Heh heh heh heh heh!
[Ichigo]
Yaah!
You said you'd eventually
control both the Soul Society
and the World of the Living!
How are you gonna
pull that off?!
Why is Nozomi so important?!
Heh heh heh heh!
This is funny to you huh?!
What did you hide inside her?!
You're just full of questions,
aren't you, young man?
I'd love to answer them all,
but I don't have the time.
I'm on a tight schedule.
The more pressing question you
should be asking yourself is,
why did I summon you here?
The answer is really quite
simple: To erase you.
Oh, Shiro?
Momo?
What in the world
are you doing here?
Well...
When I woke up, everyone from
Squad Twelve, who had been
looking after me, was gone.
I went looking for them...
and somehow, I ended up here.
Momo. You still don't look
well. You should be in bed.
You need to get your rest.
Hm. No, I'm all right.
It's dangerous.
Multiple battles are
going on right now.
I'm about to engage
the enemy, as well.
You really should find
somewhere safe to go.
Thank you, Shiro.
But, I'll be just fine.
[fainting gasp]
See what I mean? You're weak.
Don't strain yourself.
You need to rest right now.
I'm sorry Shiro.
I'm so sorry.
[gasp]
Not gonna happen.
The truth is,
you can't kill me.
Even so, can you kill me, Shiro?
Can you stab me... once more?
[gasp]
Haah!
Augh!
I am sorry, Shiro.
The truth is,
it's not my fault.
[pained gasps]
It's Kageroza's fault,
for coming up with this idea!
Yaa ha ha!
Take 'em all down!
Oh, I will, in time...
This is nothing,
compared to
fighting myself!
He was as strong as I was,
and yet I still won!
[giggle]
It was the fight of my life!
My body is still tingling!
Now I want more!
You never know when to give up,
Kenpachi Zaraki!
Whatever you're feeling,
you should barely be able
to stand up after
fighting your own Reigai!
Heh! What makes you
such an expert?
They're all planning to
attack us at the same time.
What are we going to do?
What can I do?
I'll just have to
take them down!
Yachiru. Get ready to dodge.
[agreeing]
Mm!
[chuckle]
[gasp]
Heh.
He took us all on, and we
weren't able to lay a
finger on him! His Spirit
Energy is ridiculous!
Augh!
[Kenpachi]
Are you okay, Yachiru?
[Yachiru]
Oh, absolutely!
How 'bout you, Kenny?
Not a scratch. These guys
were no challenge at all.
I barely raised a sweat.
I'm totally unsatisfied!
So what's the deal?
Are you gonna make
this fun for me?
Cat got your tongue,
Soi Fon?
She's behind you!
Hrrah!
[gasp]
[Soi Fon]
Sajin Komamura!
So you're alive, are you?
Sorry I'm a little late.
Allow me to assist you.
You want to assist?
I don't think so.
She's all mine.
I can take her
by myself.
Don't interfere.
Hm. Don't worry about me.
I'll admit it took time to get
through the Precipice World,
but my health is strong,
and I'm ready to go.
Are you hard of hearing?
Who says I'm worried about you?
Just stay out of my way!
Captain Soi Fon!
I'm going to be
your opponent!
What?! Have you
completely lost it?!
Yeah! Go for it, Bow-Wow!
Tch. You took the
fun right out of it.
I'm going on ahead,
after Kageroza.
[Yachiru]
Bye-bye!
Have a good battle!
[weak breaths]
[gasp]
Yahh!
Augh!
Sorry, Shiro.
It's not personal.
[gasp]
Now, snap...
Tobiume!
Augh!
Snap, Tobiume!
Shiro!
Rrrgh!
[gasp]
Are you me?
Rrrgh!
You attacked Shiro and hurt him,
didn't you?!
That's unforgivable!
It wasn't my fault!
I didn't do it because I
wanted to, believe me!
Huh?
Shiro!
Help me, please!
[gasp]
Bakudo Number Four! Hainawa!
Shiro, please,
you have to help me!
[stunned breaths]
Don't let her trick you!
She's an impostor!
I am not!
You're the
impostor!
Shut your mouth!
Impostor!
Yah!
Please believe me, Shiro!
Stop it now!
Uhn!
Urrgh!
I'm sorry.
So sorry.
[in unison]
Now snap... Tobiume.
UWAAAGH!
We're both sorry.
This is Kageroza's
strategy.
The truth is, we're
weaker than you, Shiro.
He said if you
dropped your guard...
...We'd be able
to defeat you.
He knew something we didn't;
That you could never attack us,
Shiro.
We're so sorry.
Please don't hate us
for what we've done.
So you're
both Reigai?
That's good.
[both gasp]
What did you say?
How can you say
something like that?
How can this be good?
We tricked you!
It is good. Because I didn't
have to get the real Momo
involved in this mess.
[gasp]
I made a vow...
To never hurt...
Momo ever again!
[sniffles]
I see.
In her honor,
We'll make
this quick.
[Yoruichi]
Shunko!
[gasp]
So close, but we failed.
And I'm glad.
I just wish I could
have been the original.
[clatter]
[small sigh]
I have to tell you, Toshiro.
You're too naive.
You've been here in the
Soul Society from the start?
The whole time.
I was taking care of some
business. And you?
I had some unfinished
business, as well.
Hey. Be careful, don't
push yourself. I'll join
you as soon as I can.
[amused sigh]
Erase my existence?
Why am I your target?
Heh heh heh heh heh!
Answer me!
Uh??
You are a great threat to my
plan, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Agh!
You are not human.
Nor are you a pure Soul
Reaper or a Hollow.
You're an anomaly.
I'm not even able to create
a Reigai of you from Reishi.
It's upsetting.
Really.
You're the unaccountable
variable, and frankly,
a thorn in my side.
Uwaagh!
I bid you farewell...
Ichigo Kurosaki.
What? Is this the...
Precipice World?
Ah!
[gasp]
What is it?
What's wrong?!
Ichigo's
Spiritual
Pressure!
It just completely disappeared!
What??
[small frightened breath]
[Kon]
Listen, four-eyes!
When you like someone,
your heart starts to pound,
and you probably feel some pain!
[Uryu] [concerned]
What? You've had that
experience before?
[Kon]
Of course! I've had my share of
romance, more than a few times!
[Uryu]
Do I need to take
you to the hospital?
Maybe you need a
heart transplant!
[Kon]
You're not very bright, are you?