[theme music]
-You better get
ready, Uryu Ishida,
because I'm gonna beat
the hell out of you.
Do you know that?
Oh no, you don't.
To you, this is just
a contest to see
which of us can kill
the most Hollows,
but I'm not interested
in playing your game.
Fight me.
If you're so sure that Quincys
are superior to Soul Reapers,
then why don't you
prove it right now.
Or are you too afraid?
What are you waiting for?
Come on.
-Ichigo, wait.
-What do you want?
-Look up there.
-Huh?
What the hell?
-The Hollows.
They're gathering.
-Where are you going?
There are too many of them.
-Now who's afraid, Ichigo?
If you don't have the guts,
just stay back here and watch.
I told you before,
I am the winner.
Down here, filthy Hollows.
I, Uryu Ishida, the last of
the Quincys, challenge you.
-Is he really the last one?
-It was thought they all
became extinct 200 years ago.
Well, not exactly.
They were systematically
killed by the Soul Reapers.
URAHARA (OFFSCREEN):
As you can imagine,
it was a very difficult
and painful decision
for the Soul Reapers.
But in the end, it became
necessary to destroy
the Quincys because
it was the only way
to prevent the
destruction of this world.
-Soul Reapers were also referred
to by other names back then.
They were called
Balancers or Regulators.
-What did they balance?
-The number of souls
in the Souls Society
and in the human world does not
change by much as time goes by.
They just trade places
between the two worlds.
It's the job of Soul
Reapers to regulate that,
to keep the balance.
It worked until the Quincys
disrupted the equation.
The Quincys didn't
cleanse the Hollows.
They destroyed them completely.
This meant that any
soul which left the Soul
Society for the human
world would never return.
If things had
continued that way,
the balance between the two
worlds would have collapsed.
It would have meant
the apocalypse.
-[gasps].
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN): So there were
many meetings between the Soul
Reapers and the Quincys,
but to no avail.
The Quincys refused
to listen to reason.
Finally, there was no choice.
The order was given for
the Quincys' annihilation.
Many have accused the
Soul Reapers of arrogance
for their actions.
-What the--?
They just keep on coming.
Sensei.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Uryu!
-Ichigo Kurosaki, you
are completely insane.
-All right, Uryu.
Now I understand why you think
Soul Reapers are your enemies.
I don't know who is
right and who was wrong,
the Soul Reapers or the Quincys.
But it was so long
ago that I don't
see how it matters anymore.
But I'll tell you one thing
I know for sure, Uryu,
your methods are completely--
URYU (OFFSCREEN): That's
all ancient history.
-Huh?
-I don't care about
some slaughter
that happened 200 years ago.
It's just one more fact
that was passed down
to me from my sensei.
In fact, when I
heard that story,
I think I sided more
with the Soul Reapers
than I did with the Quincys.
That is, until my
sensei was murdered.
SENSEI (OFFSCREEN):
After much thought,
I must conclude that in
the end, the Quincy had
only themselves to
blame for failing
to heed the warnings
of the Soul Reapers.
URYU (OFFSCREEN):
But why, Sensei?
How can you say that when
it was the Quincys that
were wiped out?
-It does seem cruel.
So many lives were
cut short so young.
But the memory of those
souls who are lost
is what is important now, and
to worry about who was right
and who was wrong
is meaningless.
We must do all we
can, Uryu, to prevent
such a tragedy from
ever happening again.
That is the lesson I want you to
learn so that such sadness will
never again occur in the lives
of humans or Soul Reapers.
-He was a kind, gentle man
with no hatred in his heart.
To the very end, he tried
to convince the Soul Reapers
that Quincys were necessary.
He kept encouraging
them to work together,
suggesting new ways
to fight the Hollows.
But the Soul Reapers
always had the same answer
to his efforts-- don't
interfere with our work.
Then one day five Hollows
appeared and surrounded sensei.
It was obvious that he
couldn't take them on his own,
and yet not one Soul
Reaper came to his aid.
They knew about the Hollows.
Sensei was under
constant surveillance,
and yet it was two hours
before they finally arrived.
If only they had
listened to his advice.
heeded his warning.
Then he wouldn't
have been alone.
Help would have
reached him in time,
and sensei wouldn't
have wound up dead.
Now do you understand,
Ichigo Kurosaki?
That's the reason that
this is so important,
why I have to prove to you
and to all Soul Reapers
the superior strength
of the Quincy.
I realized that our
methods are different,
that our ways of thinking
are at opposite poles,
so if you really
believe my way is wrong,
then stay back and watch.
Watch and witness
the true power of--
-Shut up already.
-What is your problem?
-You messed up your own story.
Your sensei wouldn't
want you to prove
the strength of the Quincys.
You said it yourself.
His greatest hope was for
Quincys and Soul Reapers
to work together.
Isn't that right?
Come on, think about it.
When will you ever
have a better chance
to do that then right here
surrounded by enemies?
You say we're at
opposite poles, but I
say when two warriors
are heavily outnumbered,
the trick is to
fight back to back.
-Very well.
-Now that was nice.
-I didn't do it for you.
I only did It because they
were about to attack me.
-So what?
That's all right.
It's kill or be killed.
What's more important
here is, together
we can kill a lot more.
Isn't that a good enough
reason for us to join forces?
After all, we both share the
same single-minded purpose.
We both have reasons to want
to destroy as many Hollows
as we can.
-You know my reason,
but what's yours?
-My mother was
killed by a Hollow.
-[gasps].
-I'm sure you'll agree
that's enough of a reason
all by itself, but there's
still more to it than that.
After all the
agony I suffered, I
want to make sure others
don't suffer the way I did.
My father and my sisters
went through so much pain
after mom was killed.
It was so hard for me to watch.
That's something I don't
ever want to see again,
that sadness in their faces.
-So that such sadness
will never again
occur in the lives of
humans or Soul Reapers.
-I'm not a superhero.
I know that I can't protect
everybody in the world,
but that doesn't mean
I'm gonna be content
protecting only the people I
can hold in my arms either.
I am going to protect as many
people as I possibly can.
Your method of using bait to
deliberately draw Hollows here
just to prove a point is only
endangering innocent lives.
I don't agree with
that, but right now
is not the time for arguments.
We've got to work
together, you and me.
So what do you say?
URYU (OFFSCREEN): What do I say?
I think you talk too much, but
I understand what you're saying.
I have to help you
survive this battle
or you won't be around
for me to kick your butt.
-Sounds like a plan.
-What the--?
Ichigo?
-Huh?
-Look at the sky.
-What's that?
URYU (OFFSCREEN):
I-- I don't know.
-Oh, no, is that
what I think it is?
It can't be.
-What is that huge thing?
Tell me.
-That's not your everyday,
garden variety Hollow
-That little bit of bait I used
can't possibly have drawn this.
-Maybe not, but it's here.
Here they come.
-I'm sorry we're so late.
-We just love the triple.
-I thought you might need a
little assistance, Ichigo.
-Mr. Hat-and-Clogs.
-And if you don't mind me making
a suggestion, why don't my crew
and I take care of these
small fries for you, Ichigo,
while you go concentrate
on that big guy?
Oh, uh, you should probably get
started before it's too late.
-Menos Grande.
-Menos what?
-It's a huge Hollow, born
from hundreds and hundreds
of Hollows mixed and folded
and crushed together.
Until now, I've never seen
it except for illustrations
in textbooks.
Menos Grande.
I don't know what we can do.
Only one group can handle this
thing, the Royal Special Task
Force.
Menos Grande is way too much
for any single Soul Reaper.
-That thing is too big
for any of our weapons.
-Ha, just because it's overfed
doesn't change anything.
We're just gonna have
to chop a little more.
-Chop?
-Yep, and the bigger they
are, the harder they fall.
Come on.
Together, we'll take
that ugly sucker down.
Let's go, Uryu.
-Ichigo, don't be crazy.
-Ichigo?
Ichigo, stop.
You two aren't enough to
go up against Menos Grande.
Huh?
-Urahara, are you trying to
get Ichigo killed out there?
-Of course not.
Just watch.
There is a method to my madness.
This is a battle
that must be fought.
-(SUFFERING) This
is a binding spell.
-It is for Ichigo, and
for you too, Rukia.
-I told you that would happen.
Dammit.
Hey, Ichigo.
So can you get up?
-Sure, I'm good as new.
-That was the dumbest charge
I think I've ever seen.
What were you thinking?
Did you actually
think that would work?
-Huh?
-Well, I figured if I
just kept chopping away
at him like a giant tree,
I'd eventually bring him
down to the point where I
could whack him on the head.
-I can't believe
you're acting like this
is some kind of
little kid's game.
Now, get up and let's
try a different strategy.
[groaning]
-What is this?
There's power flowing
into me from his sword.
This must be Ichigo's power.
What'll I try next?
URYU (OFFSCREEN): Ichigo, look.
-Huh?
What did you do, Uryu?
How did you bow get so big?
-Just be quiet and listen.
I think there actually may be
a way we can defeat this thing.
Are you ready to do it?
CHAD (OFFSCREEN):
Orihime, do you
see Ichigo and Uryu next to him?
-Yes.
Mr. Urahara said to
watch from here, so-- uh.
Does he mean we should
so when the time comes,
we'll be able to choose
the path we'll walk?
The truth is, I' haven't
forgotten a single thing that
happened that horrible night.
But having seen my brother
as a monster, and Ichigo
trying to kill each
other, it would
be easier if I could forget.
Chad?
-Huh?
-Well, what are we
supposed to do now.
-Hmm.
-Now, we are ready
to fight that thing.
-You're not serious?
This won't work.
-Quiet.
Just do what I say.
You've got to release
all of your spirit energy
at once while we're connected.
That way, I should be
able to harness the power
and shoot an enormous arrow.
It's the best way to
use all of your energy.
Right now, you're
just wasting it.
-Well, you don't have to
be so insulting about it.
-Argh, quick taking things so
personally and just release
that energy already.
-How do I do that?
-You mean to tell
me you don't know?
What's been your method for
battling with the Hollows
all this time?
-Just instinct.
-Just instinct?
But that's impossible.
-I never did really
understand that stuff.
I figured my spirit
energy was pretty much
always at its maximum level.
[cracking noises]
-Oh, no.
the Cero.
Does he intend to release
a Doom Blast right here?
You've got to run, both of you.
If you're hit by that, there'll
be nothing left of you.
-This will work.
I'm sure of it.
-Ichigo, grab that
sword and let's do it.
I meant let's do it together.
What's he doing?
I'm feeling extraordinary
spiritual pressure.
Ichigo's power, it's
actually increasing.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): I figured
my spirit energy was pretty much
always at its maximum level.
-But there's no way that can be.
If someone's spirit energy
was always at maximum,
it would all drain
away in no time,
no matter how much he had.
Ichigo says he can't control
the spirit energy at all.
He must have an
incredible amount
to let it spill out the way
he does and still have more.
It's like a faucet
that's been left turned
on with the water gushing out.
Most people will
quickly turn it off,
but if Ichigo were to do that,
if his spirit energy were
to stay bottled up, then
soon the spirit pressure
would begin to skyrocket,
just like it is now.
And then, if through
some incident,
that pressure were to
be suddenly released--
-[grunts].
-I think it's time.
-He cut it open.
-Menos is retreating.
-I win!
-What in the world is he?
-Well done.
Now I can understand
why the boss
has been keeping
an eye on this one.
[thunder]
-Well, what's the matter, Uryu.
You don't have anything to say?
I just saved your butt and
cleaned up your mess too.
It seems like you could
at least say thank you,
or congratulations or something.
That's weird.
(STRUGGLING) I can't move.
What's happening?
-The zanpakuto,
it's breaking down.
-Ichigo released all his
spirit energy at one time.
It looks like it's put way
too much strain on his body.
-I've got to do something
before it's too late.
[grunts]
I must endure the pain.
I think I can save
him if I can really
Ichigo's out of control spirit
energy bit by bit by firing
arrows until his energy
level stabilizes.
-What do you think
you're doing this?
-Shut up.
-But Uryu, your arm
is getting torn apart.
-I said, shut up.
How many times do
I have to tell you?
I have to make sure
you survive so I
have someone to
pummel in the future.
Stay alive, Soul Reaper, so I
can beat the hell out of you,
and so you can try to do
the same to me, Ichigo.
[grunts]
Dammit.
My need to prove myself
against Soul Reapers
is responsible for all of this.
Forgive me, sensei.
I've always blamed Soul
Reapers for your death,
just so I could
avoid blaming myself
because I wasn't willing to
risk my life to save you.
But I know you never
hated Soul Reapers.
Your sincerest wish was for
Quincys and Soul Reapers
to join together.
So today, I'm going to
save a Soul Reaper's life.
I'm a weak disciple,
sensei, a weak apprentice
unable to give his life for you.
Can you ever forgive
me, grandfather?
-How am I supposed
to beat up that guy?
He's just so pathetic.
[music playing]
-Hey, how are you?
I'm Kon, the superstar
of the world of Bleach.
And I've got good
news, because right
after this comes my
own brand-new special.
Even the Soul
Society is shocked.
Mr. Kon's Soul
Reapers Dictionary
is about to start,
so stay tuned.
Ow.
-I've never heard of that.
-No, it's not for
real this time.