The Zanpakuto. Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined by
its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper and
dies with its Soul
Reaper.
That is the existence of
a Zanpakuto.
You better watch your
mouth Ichigo! Talk like
that will get you in
trouble around here!
Try taking a deep breath
Lieutenant Abarai.
I beg your pardon sir, but I
find it completely inconceivable
that Captain Kuchiki would ever
betray us!
There must be a
plausible reason for
his actions!
I don't know what his
reasoning is...
But I do know that
Byakuya is working with
his Zanpakuto.
This is great. We still
haven't been able to
locate Old Man Yama,
and now Captain Kuchiki
has turned against us?
So what other surprises
are out there waiting for
us?
Captain.
The only good news is
that after quite an ordeal,
Captain Hitsugaya was able
to recover his Zanpakuto.
But the battle he fought
cost him. He will not be
able to fight for
sometime.
Now we know how to
reclaim our Zanpakuto.
But we cannot afford to risk
such injury in every fight.
I'm afraid I must share
more distressing news
from Squad Twelve
regarding this subject.
After testing the samples
we provided, they learned
that there would be
serious consequences if a
Zanpakuto were destroyed
by anyone other than its
master.
It appears that if
Zanpakuto are destroyed
that way, they could be
lost for good.
Really?
Then what are we going to
do when we're fighting
against someone else's
Zanpakuto?!
I guess we'll have to
go easy on them.
How do we do
that? We're barely
beating them now!
You're right-this is a
tough one to figure. It
sure seems the enemy's
plan is to have us
destroy our own
Zanpakuto.
Sir.
I suggest we keep Captain
Kuchiki's defection a
secret from all personnel
except our captains.
Nope. If we start
keeping secrets now, the
rumors will start and
create problems that
might affect troop
morale.
It's not easy to keep
people from talking.
And so how do you propose
that we explain this to
Rukia?
I'll take care of that.
Captain Ukitake.
She'll be fine. Rukia
will have to accept the
truth as we have.
Byakuya did what?!
It's true. Byakuya
Kuchiki has joined the
rebellious Zanpakuto.
We shouldn't jump to
conclusions, it could just
be he's trying to handle
the matter on his own.
Yes. That could be it.
Byakuya.
Byakuya Kuchiki!
What's this guy doing
here?
What's going on?
Muramasa, what is the
meaning of this?
Why did you help me?
Senbonzakura.
Explain why a man of your
rank turn against the
Soul Reapers?
He turned against his own
people?
You mean he's on our
side now?
The reason I have come to
this decision, is strictly
based on my own pride.
Ha! Your own pride, my
ass! I don't believe this
guy for a second!
But his actions prove
it-he helped us to
escape.
What is this?!
What do you think
he's here for?!
Wait, why are
you doing this?
All of us are here
because we've grown
weary of our Soul
Reapers.
Expecting us to accept
you into our group would
go against everything we
have fought for...
That's for sure. Besides,
he could just be a spy.
Byakuya Kuchiki, if you
are indeed serious about
defecting from the Soul
Reapers, then you need to
do something to prove it
to us.
So what is it you want me
to do?
Slay your sister's
Zanpakuto, Sodenoshirayuki,
right here and now.
Hey, hold on! What
are you talking about?!
You want him to slay one
of us?!
A Zanpakuto killed by
someone other than its
wielder, never returns to
its original form.
This test will certainly
show us where his true
loyalties lie.
Ha! This oughta be good!
He really does love this
Rukia Kuchiki, more than
anyone.
So then you're saying
there's no way he would
slay her Zanpakuto.
Hey wait!
So from the start, you
never intended to let him
join us.
No, of course
we didn't!
This farce will end here.
Time to settle this,
Byakuya.
You want her slain now,
you say?
Hey! Looks like he means
it.
Tsuginomai!
Hakuren!
Hado number four.
Byakurai!
He's going to
finish her!
Even if you really want to
kill me, you don't have the
strength to defeat me in your
present condition.
Somenomai!...Tsukishiro!
Tsukishiro!
Stealth Hoho. Shiho
Number Three.
Utsusemi.
Rikujokoro.
This can't be!
If it is for the sake of
my pride, there is nothing
I won't destroy.
I don't believe it!
Have you lost your mind!?
No-not at all. You
could never even begin to
comprehend my mind.
What was that?! Are you
mocking me!
That's enough.
Muramasa.
We all know, a Soul
Reaper who's lost her
Zanpakuto is as good as
dead.
And even knowing that, he
callously snapped his
sister's sword without
hesitation.
You are free to join us.
I accept your resolve.
What the hell is going
on??
Relax, Kazeshini.
If Muramasa says that
he's all right, we need
to accept that.
Keep this in mind
Byakuya, if you waiver for
even a second, I will slay
you without hesitating!
Know that I'll always
be right here, watching
your every move!
Now then, Byakuya
Kuchiki. If you are
truly going to be
joining us...
There is a certain,
matter I want you to take
care of for me.
Thanks, Renji.
Don't mention it. I
was thinking about doing
the same thing.
The Captain may have left
behind some clues in his
office.
Rukia, I'm sure Byakuya
will be back soon.
He's too good a man to
ever be a traitor to us.
Yeah. I believe that as
much as you do.
Lieutenant Abarai, sir!
We're ready to change
shifts sir.
Good! Be right there!
Rukia. Try not to
work too hard.
Okay thanks.
See ya.
Byakuya. You always sat
alone,
What were you thinking?
I must've dozed off.
feel worn out.
It's his spiritual
pressure!
Byakuya.
Rukia.
Did you--?
It's been a long time.
What are you doing here,
Byakuya?
Where have you been?
Why is it that you
won't answer me?!
This is his answer!
Who are you?
Sodenoshirayuki!
I don't sense her
Spiritual Pressure! Did
he actually---?!
With your Zanpakuto,
Sodenoshirayuki gone, you
have no means to fight
us.
Impossible.
You will stay out of our
way.
Byakuya. What have you
done?
I'll be glad to show
you.
Renji!
Damn it!
Captain! I need to know
what has happened to you!
Are you really on their
side? What reason could
you have to betray us?!
Captain Kuchiki, I have no
choice but to detain you as
a material witness in the
Zanpakuto Rebellion incident.
Stand aside. Or you
will suffer the results
of obstructing my path.
I will not!
Damn it!
Roar!
I heard you used
Higazekko in a previous
fight, so I know what
shape you're in.
Which means that, you can't
even use Shikai with that sword.
Who can't use their
Shikai?
Oh. It's you two!
In the larger scheme of
things now that both of
us have manifested,
whether Renji can use
Shikai or not, really has
no importance here.
Yeah-that's right.
I'll take care of this.
You return to Muramasa.
Oh, so you think you're
ready to take us on?
Sounds good, maybe we can
finally settle that unfinished
business of ours.
I would not be so confident
if I were you. With your skills,
you will be lucky just to
survive.
Heh! Sounds like
you're underrating our
abilities!
Come on, let's
do it, Snake.
I'm with you, Monkey!
Roar!
Wait up!
Byakuya-Don't go!
You and I are not
finished yet!
I do not have the time
to explain all of this to
you.
It's clear that talking
to you does no good.
Shakkaho!
So this is how you fight
when you can't use Shikai.
Well, it will not be good
enough to defeat me.
Yeah, you're probably right.
But it might just work well
enough for me to capture you!
Take this!
Shakkaho!
Hado number four.
Byaku---
Bakudo Number Four!
Hainawa!
You're going to tell me
everything!
I want to know what
could've caused you to
turn your back on all of
us!
My turn!
Jerk!
There's nowhere to run!
You mean for you?
What?!
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
You need to explain why
you've done this!
I'm gonna force you to
explain it! To all of the
Captains and to Ichigo!
You're gonna explain it
to all of Squad Six's
members!
And to your sister Rukia!
Hikotsu Taiho!
What?!
Bankai.
Scatter.
Renji!
Are you all right?
Byakuya.
This is your final
warning. Stay out of
our way.
Brother, why?!
Hey, come on now, aren't
you going to finish them
off?
It sure looks to me like
you were having fun, right?
What are you all doing
here?
Is that any way to greet
us? Muramasa said to lend
you two a hand, so we all
came to help with things.
Beat those Soul Reapers
to death! Do it now!
What's wrong? You
not gonna do it?
Well then, if you
won't do it...
We're happy to
do it for you!
Get going, Rukia! I'll
stay here and hold them
off!
As weak as you are?
Don't be ridiculous!
Go!
Enough chitchat! Your
lives will soon be over!
And there'll be two
less Soul Reapers to--
What the hell is this?!
Don't move!
No one move!
Hey! Up here!
You're gonna beat who
to death?
Damn bastards!
Rukia! You all right?
Byakuya.
Byakuya Kuchiki. As
proof that you are one of
us, you'll wear a mask
identical to mine.
Why?
Because Muramasa approved
it.
Why?
It's a fine mask. It
will help you feel the
spirit of the samurai.
Why?