Ahhhhhh!
All right, attack!
Gran Caida.
How's this?!
It's too flashy for
an assassin.
I will show you the
meaning of fear.
Rot...Arrogante.
[gasping]
What is that?
Look at that, everything
he's touching is completely
rotting away!
As I told you earlier,
I govern Senescence
Everything around me
ages and dies.
Suffer the Dying
Breath.
Respira.
[gasping]
Ahh!
[screaming]
Marechiyo!
Cut off my arm right now!
But Captain--
Hurry up! Are you going
to let your Captain die?
Marechiyo!
Damn it!
Hmph.
How amusing.
It seems that even Soul
Reapers are afraid of
death.
Are you all
right, Captain?
Back up, Marechiyo.
Huh?
He's a...
real monster.
I've faced my share of
tough opponents, but
nobody compares to
him. This guy's way
more terrifying and
dangerous than Aizen ever
was...
We can't get near him,
let alone touch him...
So how the hell are we
supposed to defeat a guy
when we can't even attack?!
But that's not the
biggest problem we've
got.
He was able to take
Captain Soi Fon's arm.
That means... nobody in
the 13 Court Guard Squads
can evade his attacks.
Marechiyo.
Huh? Yes, ma'am?
Listen. Earlier you
were saying that it's
your duty to assist me.
Huh?
[grunting]
And even though you told
me to run, it's my duty
to assist you, Captain!
I, uh... guess
you're right.
But I said that because I
think both of us will need
to combine our efforts to
defeat this guy!
You're right.
So then...
... you attack
him alone.
Yes, ma'am, alone.
Huh? Wait... what'd
you just say?
Act as a decoy.
Draw him in.
So, you mean
one on one?
I have an idea.
Wait, wait, wait,
wait, no! It's
impossible!
Me against him? That's
crazy talk! I said it
would take both of us to
bring this guy down!
Ha-ha-ha! You're
kidding-right?!
A minute ago you told me
to run away!!
Well...?
If you will not
attack, I will.
You see? You see
Captain?! Did you hear
what he just said?
What should I do?!
Just protect your right
arm...
You'll need to use it to
amputate anything that
begins to decay.
I'm counting on you.
Wait! Uh, Captain!??
Wait a sec, Captain!!
Come back...
[groaning]
[chuckling]
Cero.
Whoa!
I made my move, it's
your turn! Just know...
... that you won't fair
so well if you keep on
running away from me.
Got it?
You've seen my
Cero twice.
It's only fair you
return the favor and
show me a Bankai.
I don't know.
Do you see over there?
Your skull faced friend
has presented something
called a Resurreccion.
How about it? Why don't
you show me that and in
exchange, I'll give you
an appropriate response.
You're gonna hold
out... aren't you?
But I'm not the
only one!
[grunting]
Ahhhh!
All right, attack!
[grunting]
Ahhhh!
Keep it coming!
[grunting]
[groaning]
[whining]
I'm gonna kill you!
Well said! That's the
spirit!
Gimme back my sword, ya
creep!
I can't do that!
Ahhhhh!
Die, ya gray-haired
geezer! Dry up and blow
away!
Come on!-Put more Oomph
into it!
[crying]
What's wrong? You
worried about that
kid down there?
No, it's not that.
Don't worry. Jushiro
won't do anything to
hurt that kid.
You should be
concentrating on
our battle instead.
I said, that's not it!
I'm just not
getting this...
That kid down there is
your subordinate. She's
a Fraccion, right?
Can't say I grasp what
their relationship is
with an Espada.
But I don't think
there's a difference
between you and I, when
it comes to the feelings
we have when your
subordinates are in
trouble.
What do you mean?
It's just something
I realized...
Once you felt that kid
was in danger, I saw that
you couldn't keep your mind
focused.
Damn you! Give me back
my sword now!
So are you planning to
kill her first?
No I'm not. I just
told you... Jushiro Would
never hurt her.
Uh!
Ohh!
Not bad.
Cero!
Hmph! Are you capable of
mounting an attack alone?
I know one thing, I better
keep my distance from
this guy, or he'll turn
me to dust!
Ahhh! The way I see
it, this is crazy!
One-on-one against a guy
this powerful? What is the
Captain thinking leaving
me to handle this alone?!
[chuckling]
Try to make this a
challenge for me.
Shut up! Stupid skull
head. I'll show you a
thing or two.
Except I've got nothing
to show him!
Ahhh! Screw it!
Well, here I go!
Smash 'em, Gegetsuburi!
From your actions it
appears you wish for your
Zanpakuto to rot away as
well.
Ahhhh!
Wait! Time out-time
out! Big mistake! My
Gegetsuburi will be gone
if he touches it!
Better change my attack!
[struggling]
Weren't you aiming for
me? Instead, your attack
ended up being self
destructive.
Moron! I'm not self
destructive, I'm
warming up!
My attack was stronger
than I thought, that's
all! So I was hit by
some rubble!
Wait, that's it!
Let's see you keep
up with me if you can!
How boring. All you're
doing is running away.
[panting]
What I have to do is lure
him to someplace where
it'll be harder for him
to fight.
Fighting him up in the
sky, where he has a clear
view is pointless.
Over here!
How's this!
[grunting]
Good thinking. You
realized you can't
attack with your
Zanpakuto, so you tried
using other objects. But
pathetic efforts like
yours are useless.
I've only begun to
fight!
Ahhhh!
Oh yeah!
Well, well...
Rainin' shards of
glass!
How will you understand?
You cannot wound me with
shards of glass.
You're right, I don't
expect some small glass
shards to hurt you. But what
about an entire building?!
[laughing]
[coughing and panting]
That probably wasn't enough
to kill him, but I know that
it's bought me some more time.
Now I need to hide out
somewhere and come up
with a plan that works.
Huh?
[chuckling]
Did you just say, bought
you more time? You say
some interesting things.
What now?
Have you forgotten that
I signify the aspect of
death known as
senescence?
Time means nothing before
my power! For it can rule
time itself!
Speaking of time, it's
time for you to suffer
the Dying Breath.
Respira!
Ahhh!
I am not done!!
[groaning]
By now, you must know.
You cannot take this
sword back from me.
I'm afraid that's
reality, and you need
to accept that fact.
Hmph! So what
if I can't?!
You Fracciones are
persistent.
And you're quite
fiercely loyal to the
Espadas, aren't you?
Nevertheless,
you should stop.
Your duty shouldn't
require you to die here
needlessly.
Stubbornness isn't
loyalty.
You are so full of it!
And wrong!
You reek from lecturing,
old fart.
Old far?! I
don't approve of you
and your foul mouth.
Address me properly.
Call me Mister!
I don't know anything
about loyalty and stuff
like that... But Coyote
and I...
We're different than
the other Espadas and
Fracciones. We just
are--
Now that was a close
call. I thought that
Cero of yours had nailed
me.
And I would hate for
anything to happen to
this kimono.
But my suspicions were
correct. You became a
little desperate after
thinking I was going to
go after that kid,
didn't you?
How unbecoming of you,
Captain. Using cheap taunts
like that won't get you
anywhere in this fight.
Maybe they won't.
But as far as I can tell,
the relationship between
you two seems to be more
personal than as usual
with other Espadas
and Fracciones.
And so what if it
is? Do you think
that lecturing me is
going to help you?
Possibly. I'm not sure
that was my intention,
but I'm thinking that's
definitely the key to
the two of you.
You'll know soon enough.
That is, of course, if
you're worthy enough
to find out.
Respira!
I can't let that Dying
Breath thing hit me.
Ahhhh!
That was close! That
breath of his almost
got-- Ahhh!
[grunting]
Haven't you realized?
You can't evade my
Respira. I released it
slowly on purpose... I
know your captain is
hiding out there
somewhere and I will find
a way to flush her out!
Yeah, well I wish she'd
hurry up and get involved!
The only move I have
left is running away!
I must say, you're very
good at running away for
a fat chunk of meat!
Shuh- Shut up!
You're just jealous
because you're nothing
but a bag of bones!
I can't do anything
directly using my
Gegetsuburi! It'll
turn to dust!
That's just my luck! Why
isn't my Zanpakuto a
Kido-type, that shoots
flames or ice or does
something really great?!
That's it!-Kido!
A Kido can get him! I
just figured out your
weakness!
Bakudo 21, Sekienton!
Damn it! I almost blinded
myself with that. You
know when I really think of
it, I can barely use Kido!
Damn! That was close. I
got carried away and
almost made him mad.
This isn't going to
work! It's obviously
not going to work!
I'm screwed! I'm
gonna get killed!
Captain!!
Save me!
Screaming out loud like
a coward... idiot.
Can't leave him in
charge for even a
second...
When this fight is over,
I'm gonna beat that loser
within an inch of his life.
All right, that should be
enough.
Looks like that's about
all he can do. Run away
from me.
Time to end this.
What the
hell is that?
Gran Caida... A
guillotine too good
for a coward.
Rot... and die!
[trembling]
Bankai!
What?!
Huh?
Unh?!
Jakuho Raikoben!
So that's what your
Bankai looks like.
Uh-- Captain!
So that's Captain Soi
Fon's Bankai! This is my
first time seeing it!
What's with that shape?
How's she gonna fight
with that?!
Huh? That's a ginjotan!
A steel band used as an
under layer for armor!
Why did she wrap herself
in something so heavy?!
With that steel sash
wrapped around her,
even the Captain won't
be able to move freely!
If possible, I had hoped
to end this without using
this Bankai.
This Bankai, it violates
my standards as a member
of the Stealth Force.
This Bankai's too big
for me to conceal it.
And it's too heavy to
move freely.
And its attack...
... it's too flashy
for an assassin!
Ahhhh!
I won't lose to you,
you old fart!
Let's play with these
spinning tops.
I told you, kids' games
won't work on me!
How about candy then?
I've got strawberry,
green tea or milk
flavored.
Which would you like?
Uhh... umm... then
I'll have the--
Quit falling for it,
Lilynette.
[giggling]