[music playing]
[theme music]
NARRATOR: Ichigo
and his friends,
still undergoing intense
training in preparation
for the showdown this winter,
were forced into action
when Aizen's elite group
of Arrancars appeared.
But the Arrancars
suddenly retreated
in the midst of battle.
The Espada's attack
was merely a diversion
to draw attention
away from Orihime.
Aizen's plan was
proven successful
when she was captured
by Ulquiorra,
and taken to Hueco Mundo.
The Soul Society alerts
Ichigo and the others
of Orihime's disappearance.
And Ichigo vows to save her.
But he is forbidden
from taking action
by Head Captain Yamomoto.
-You must not.
We are going to need your
help in this battle, Ichigo
Kurosaki.
I won't allow you to plot
your own course of action,
and die for nothing.
NARRATOR: Meanwhile,
Tatsuke, realizing
that Orihime is one, pressures
Ichigo for information.
-You know.
You know where she
went, don't you?
Admit it!
I've had it with all the lies.
Tell me the truth.
What are you trying to hide?
-Mind your own
business, will you?
NARRATOR: Ichigo decides that
he will go to Hueco Mundo,
and that he must go by himself.
He visits Urahara's shop
in order to get help.
-Hey, welcome back.
I've been waiting
for you to show up.
NARRATOR: Already waiting there
for Ichigo were Uryu and Chad.
-Now do you think that I'm
still not strong enough?
Believe in us.
-Chad.
-Don't take this on by yourself.
This is what friends are for.
-All right.
Are we all set?
It looks like everybody's ready.
Finally.
[dog barking]
-Ichigo.
It was him, right?
-Definitely.
-I don't get it.
What can he be doing
here, at Urahara's shop?
-That's the only reason
we came here, isn't it?
To find out exactly
what's going on.
-Oh, yeah.
That's why we're here.
I almost forgot.
-Can you believe this?
Ichigo sure is hopeless.
-You can tell he's
hiding something.
I read Ichigo like a book.
He is going to do something.
It's like he's telling
us right out loud.
-What a big idiot.
-You're one to talk, Tatsuke.
Both of you share a certain
kind of straightforwardness.
You're a lot alike in that way.
-And do yourself a favor,
and just stay away from me.
-That stupid jerk.
Just what the hell
am I to him, anyway?
-This isn't like you.
Look, you want to know where
Ichigo's going, don't you?
-I guess.
-Then I have an idea.
-Hm?
-What now?
-Well?
-Well, listen to you.
What are you saying?
You're the one who brought
this up in the first place.
We followed Ichigo
all the way here.
-So what do you think, then?
What should we do?
-Tell us, Tatsuke!
What exactly is our plan
at a time like this?
Tell me, please!
-You talk too much!
-No, please don't get all
mad at me, for real, Tatsuke.
-We're definitely
going in there.
-Now you're finally
acting a little more
like yourself, Tatsuke.
-What a pest.
-All right.
Let's go.
-Ichigo.
-All right, boys.
The time has come.
I shall now open the
path to Hueco Mundo.
The rest of you better
stand back a little bit.
It's pretty dangerous here.
-Ah, this doesn't happen
often, so I wanna see it!
-Ririn's right.
This is a special
event, and it's
rare to get such good seats.
-Not a problem.
-Afraid I can't
let you to do that.
-What?
-Put me down.
-What do you think you're doing?
I demand you put
me down right now.
-Hm.
I can walk on my own.
-Leaving us out is not fair!
-All is well!
Ready here, sir!
-Good work!
All right.
It's time.
Here in my right hand, the
stone that connects the worlds.
In my left hand, the blade
that binds existence.
The shepherd with black
hair, the chair of the noose.
I strike the Ibis when
the clouds gather.
This hole that the Arrancars
come and go through
is known as the Garganta.
There is no solid ground
beyond this point.
Only a chaos of resihi.
Each of you must create his
own path out of that reishi.
Go towards the darkness, and
you will arrive in Hueco Mundo.
-All right, fine.
-Kisuke?
-Hm?
-Can you let my family
know that I'm all right?
I want you to tell
them not to worry,
that I can take care of myself.
-Yes, of course I will.
And what about your friends?
-When I come back home,
I'll apologize to them.
-All right, then.
Good.
-Well, I guess the best we
can do is wish you luck.
-Please be careful.
-Yeah.
Let's go!
-There they go.
Why don't you
three come out now?
[laughter]
-How's it going?
So how long did you
know we were here?
-Since before you had arrived.
I was well aware that you
were following Ichigo.
So I left the store unlocked.
Ichigo.
I cannot believe how
naive that boy can be.
He thinks that
friendship is a thing
that you can end, just by
being cold to everyone.
Well then, time
waits for no man.
Got to get to work.
[music playing]
-Ah, welcome.
This is Las Noches, our palace.
Orihime Inoue.
Is that correct?
-Yes.
-Sorry to rush you, Orihime.
But, will you show
me your power.
-Yes.
What was that, just now?
It felt as if my strength was
being sucked out of my body.
-It seems there are certain
people who would much
prefer if I had not brought
you here, to Hueco Mundo.
Isn't that right, Luppi?
-Yes, of course I don't like it.
Our entire battle
has meant nothing.
All of it was little
more than a diversion,
so we could bring
this girl here.
Frankly, it only makes
me disgusted with her.
-It was shocking.
I was surprised to see
you beaten so severely.
Oh, I know what we should do.
Orihime, demonstrate the
strength of your power for us.
I want you to heal
Grimmjow's left arm.
-Impossible!
That's crazy, Lord Aizen.
It can't be done.
Grimmjow?
Director General Tosen
turned his arm into ashes.
How is she going to heal
something that doesn't exist?
She's not a God.
-Soten Kisshun.
Now why, I reject.
-Hey!
Are you listening, girl?
If you're putting on an
act in a pathetic attempt
to save yourself, you
might as well stop it.
Should I see proof,
you haven't any power.
And there's no reason to
keep someone like you alive.
Huh?
How?
This is beyond the
point of healing.
What sorcery is this?
What did you do, girl?
-Don't you understand?
Ulquiorra thinks it's temporal
or spatial regression.
Both are interesting theories.
-Yes.
-It can't be.
No human could have
such advanced power.
It's completely impossible.
-It is neither one.
Temporal or spatial.
It rejects all
forms of phenomenon.
Her power limits,
rejects, and negates
what has happened to an object.
She has the power
to return things
to the state they existed in,
before events changed them.
It exceeds temporal
or spatial regression.
Effortlessly, it
overcomes the limits
of all established phenomenon.
It knows no borders or barriers.
In fact, it oversteps the
limitations set by gods.
-Hey, girl.
Come heal one more thing.
-Just what do you think
you're doing, Grimmjow?
Grimmjow.
You bastard.
-Your days are done.
Good bye, Mr. Ex-Number 6.
It's back!
My power is back.
The sixth Espada
is Grimmjow again!
[laughter]
-Hueco Mundo's beyond here.
Dammit.
He talked about making
a path with reishi,
as if it were so easy.
But I'm really
terrible when it comes
to doing little
things like this.
[heavy breathing]
[crash]
-Chad, are you all right?
-I'm doing fine.
-Sorry about that.
-My, my.
That's pathetic.
I mean, really.
Can't you make footing
that's any better than that?
-Just shut the hell up.
I told you I'm not good at
things like this, didn't I?
And I want to know what
that thing is you have.
It looks to me like
you're cheating.
-This is a variation
of the Hirenkyaku.
It's nothing, really.
-I want you to make me one.
-Look, your inability
to control spirit energy
means that you wouldn't
be able to use this.
-Huh?
The way that you're
talking, you'd
think I didn't even
have any powers at all!
-Was I wrong?
You can't make your
own footing properly.
-Yeah, well I'm gonna kill you.
-I'll go ahead of you.
-Uryu.
I was told you made a
deal with your father.
Kisuke said, that in exchange
for all of your father's
training, you promised
you wouldn't get involved
with the Soul Reapers
or associates.
That's what he
said you agreed to.
-Huh?
-So, Uryu, why are you here?
-Is that true?
Because I didn't
hear anything about.
Talk, Uryu.
-In exchange for the training.
Yeah, that was the agreement.
[music playing]
[gasping]
-Hello, there.
Sorry to disturb
you at this hour.
Well, actually,
it's still evening.
-Kisuke.
-Oh, your father isn't here.
I'm in luck.
-Tell me what it is
you want, Kisuke.
-Oh yes, right.
-What?
Get to the point, already.
Orihime's been abducted
by the Arrancars?
-To be more accurate,
the Arrancars
did it on Sosuke
Aizen's command.
Ichigo is probably going to
go and save her by himself.
I strongly suspect that
he'll come looking for me,
seeking a way to get
into Hueco Mundo tonight.
-Please leave.
-Huh?
-I see what it is you're
trying to tell me.
To go with Ichigo to
Hueco Mundo, right?
That can't happen.
Because right now I
can't involve myself
with Soul Reapers.
Please, go now.
If Orihime needs saving,
I can do it by myself.
By himself?
Wait a minute.
Did you just say a moment ago,
that Ichigo is by himself?
-Yes.
The Soul Society
is having nothing
to do with this incident.
Ichigo made the decision to
head into enemy territory
by himself.
-Is that so?
Then that changes everything.
-Really?
Why's that?
I mean, I don't get it.
I'm still a Soul Reaper,
even without the Soul Society
helping me out.
-That's incorrect.
You're a substitute Soul Reaper.
And furthermore, you've been
abandoned by the Soul Society.
In other words, right
now you're neither
a Soul Reaper nor one
of their associates.
So even if I associate
myself with you,
it doesn't go
against my contract.
-That's an illogical argument.
-I prefer to think
of it as a loophole.
-Whatever.
What the hell is the
difference between the two?
-Shut up.
Whose side are you on, anyway?
-Your enemy's.
-How typical of Uryu.
-Hm.
Hey.
It looks like Uryu
ran away, doesn't it?
-How did you get
in here, Isshin?
-Huh?
What's this?
In all the years
that I've known you,
you've never called me that.
What's with the change
in your attitude?
-Just answer my
question, Isshin.
I'm asking you how
you got in here.
That attire.
You've got all your powers back?
-Pretty much.
How do I look?
-It makes me sick.
-Well, thank you very much.
Aren't you going
to read the letter?
Foolish.
-Why bother?
I already know what it says,
without having to read it.
-So you wanted him to go, huh?
-That is none of your concern.
I brought back his Quincy
powers, it's up to him.
Whether he makes use of
them or suppresses them,
it doesn't really matter
if he lives or dies.
-What a horrible father.
-I'm a great
improvement over you.
-Yeah, I know.
[music playing]
-I was told to stay quiet here.
But there's nothing
for me to do.
I'm so hungry.
I can't help but
wonder if it was really
a good idea for me to come here.
I wonder if the
battle got worse,
because I healed those people.
[music playing]
-No.
But right now, I
have to make them
think that I'm of use
to them, no matter what.
At least, at least
until everyone
is prepared for battle.
[rumbling]
-They're here.
[theme music]
-I wanted to go to
Hueco Mundo, too!
-It can't be helped.
Our gigai's were destroyed
in our last battle.
-What a waste.
-Then let's get
some new ones made.
This time I want a sexy one.
-And I want a handsome one.
-Get real.