The Zanpakuto... Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined
by its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born with
its Soul Reaper, and dies
with its Soul Reaper...
That is the existence
of a Zanpakuto.
What's this about? What
the hell happened to
Muramasa?
[screaming]
My body! It's
burning up!
I must withstand
this pain!
Koga...
Koga... Koga...
Koga!!!
Getsugatensho!
Those Hollows were
trapped inside of him!
How's that possible?!
The only thing I can
imagine is that he's
been absorbing them.
And now he's unable
to suppress all of
their Spirit Energy!
He's put his very
existence at risk for
the sake of his master.
He's even exceeded his
own limitations.
Right now, he's only
retaining this state
through sheer willpower.
Ko... ga....
What's happening?!
Amazing...
Ichigo. It looks like
Muramasa's attracting all
the Hollows in this area!
Damn. We can't allow that
to happen. I'll have to put
a stop to it.
Getsugatensho!
Uryu?!
Nothing personal, Ichigo,
but it seems to me, in a
situation like this, my
bow and arrows are going
to be more effective than
your single sword.
It's about as handy as
a can of bug spray.
Take that back!
Ichigo! Rukia!
We've come to help!
Chad! Orihime!
Santenkesshun!
Good job, Orihime!
Damn! This doesn't look
good for Muramasa.
How?
It can't be...
I won't...
...let them beat me!
Come to me... Muramasa!
What's happening?
Answer me, Muramasa!
Why won't you respond?
Your master's calling
you!
Mura... masa!
This is over.
I agree. If not for his
extraordinary power,
I doubt he would have
deluded himself into
attacking the Soul Society.
It was the fate of a
weak-hearted man,
consumed by his ambition.
Instead of a blessing,
his power became a
destructive curse.
Hmpf! He was the exact
opposite of you, who
willingly allowed himself
to be branded a traitor,
in order to head off a
threat that could have
destroyed the Soul
Society.
Now you can finally
reclaim a place of honor
among your peers.
You can hold your
head up high again.
Senbonzakura,
you talk too much.
What's going on up
there?!
The Hollows are being
drawn into him!
Wait a minute! Is
that... Muramasa?!
He seems to have become
some kind of Arrancar!
A Zanpakuto is of one
mind and one body with
its Soul Reaper master.
It attaches itself to the
soul of its master and
co-exists with him.
Are you saying Muramasa
needed a source of energy
to replace his Soul
Reaper master, if he
wanted to maintain his
physical form?
Yes, he had to take in
all those Hollows, if he
was to have any chance of
holding on to his body.
You mean that was what
deflected my barrier before?
It shows you how deep and
obsessive his devotion to
Koga was. Exactly what you
would expect of a Zanpakuto
for his master. It must
have been horrifying for it
to end with such anger and
betrayal.
But, why?
You've become nothing
more than a hindrance to
me. I don't need to use a
pathetic, unstable sword
like you. My power
alone's enough.
A Zanpakuto is merely a
tool...
Damn!
If we don't do something,
Karakura town is going to
be enveloped by his Spirit
Energy!
We have to stop him!
Get ready!
He's too fast!
He's in such pain.
I can feel his
loneliness.
He so desperately reached
out to his master, only
to be abandoned.
It broke his heart.
Byakuya!
I'm so glad
you're okay!
Byakuya!
Did you defeat Koga?
Of course. Were you
worried I was going to
lose?
Hm... Well, that was
always a possibility, I
mean, you do look pretty
beat up.
He's right. We need to
treat your injuries.
Never mind that.
Muramasa should be
our main concern.
I never expected him to
release a Cero. He has
completely transformed
into a Hollow.
I won't give in! Not to
the power of the Hollows!
I won't give in!
What's happening?
I'm not completely sure,
but it looks like he might
be fighting the Hollows
he absorbed.
This is wrong...
Orihime!
Listen to me! Stop this
right now! Don't fight
anymore!
I'm sorry, but the master
you're looking for no
longer exists!
It's no use, Orihime.
He can't listen to reason
in this state.
Not true.
I can feel it. He's
fighting. He hasn't been
completely possessed by
the Hollows yet.
He's in a state of
despair, but he's fighting
desperately to maintain his
Zanpakuto identity.
Are you sure?
I won't give in. No
matter what, I can't
give in!
Ko... ga!
I can't believe he's
still searching for Koga,
after transforming into a
Hollow.
This guy is
determined.
Muramasa, you have to
stop this, it's useless.
You're only gonna cause
yourself more suffering.
Let go! Please end this
before it's too late!
I won't give in. I
won't! I won't give in!
Move, Orihime, get
out of there!
You bastard!
That was very brave,
are you all right?
I'm fine, thank you.
Can't we save him from
his pain? He's just so sad.
Getsugatensho!
Muramasa!!!!
Damn! The Hollows are
all swarming again!
Chad, let's split
up... We need to attack
them from two fronts!
El Directo!!!
Hado Number
Thirty-Three! Sokatsui!
Scatter...
Senbonzakura.
Muramasa!
Getsugatensho!
I won't... give in!
What the hell?
Unbelievable!
Ichigo!
That awful thing just
swallowed Ichigo right up.
Impossible!
What's happened?!
The spike in Spirit Energy
from all those Hollows has
caused the sky to break.
Orihime?
I have to save them. I
have to go in and save
Ichigo and Muramasa.
Don't be ridiculous,
it's dangerous!
Let me go!
This really isn't good!
A Garganta is opening.
And we're trapped!
We're gonna have to
do something fast!
Scatter...
Senbonzakura.
Tsuginomai Hakuren!
Sodeno... shirayuki.
I'm sorry it took so
long to find you.
Sodenoshirayuki...
How are you here?!
More importantly, you
should know I didn't come
alone.
Hey!
You didn't think we'd
let you have all the
fun, did you?
Wow! Zanpakuto are
incredible! There are so
many different types! There's
a cat and a snake...
And a dog , too!
You're right! It's so
cute!
If it was were a little
smaller, I'd want it as a
pet!
Come here, boy!
I hate to tell you guys,
but that's actually
Captain Komamura.