Good morning! How
are you, Captain Omaeda?
[yelling]
Hi there, Captain Omaeda!
[screaming]
It's a miracle, that's
what it is!
[snoring]
Damn you...
...Stupid Soi Fon.
That was strange. Must
have been a dream.
It sure felt good,
though. It's like
it was real.
Wonder if sleeping will
get it back. Guess I'll
give it a try.
Huh?
[screaming]
Oh great, now I've done
it! I was only gonna take
a short nap! But I ended
up sleeping for three
hours! Captain Soi Fon's
probably been looking for
me, and she's gonna be
steamed!
She's gonna make
me pay for this one!
I gotta get back there
quickly!
[breathing heavily]
[screaming]
[roaring]
[growling]
End of the road, kid!
Give back what you took
from me and I'll make
your death painless!
[growling]
Arrrh!
Ahhhhh!
[grunting]
A Soul Reaper?! What's he
doing here?
[groaning]
In my current state, I'm
at a disadvantage! I'd
better get out of here!
Oh, that really hurt!
I thought there was a
Hollow here, but he's
disappeared.
Oh well, whatever...
Gotta move.
Wait, please!
Huh?
You just saved my
life. Thank you
very much!
What? I did that?
Yes!
Won't you please tell me
your name, sir, so I know
who to thank properly!
Uh...
Yeah...
Well, you see... I'm with
Squad Two of the Thirteen
Court Guards.
Ohhhh.
In fact, I happen
to be the Captain!
[gasping]
You're a...
Captain?! Really?!
I kinda blurted that out
without thinking it through.
Oh, well, he's just a kid.
What harm could it do?
[chatting]
Captain... Everyone
in the village wants
to thank you for saving
Ryuzaburo's life.
Please have another cup
of sake, Captain.
Thank you, Captain!
Captain, you're great!
How 'bout some food?!
Huh?!
Well... Uh...
...Sure! Why not?!
[laughing]
Hey, Captain, have
some more!
I might as well. I am a
Captain, after all!
Everyone, please bring
more food for our guest!
He's worked up quite
an appetite!
So? Were you able to
steal it from the
Hollow's cave, just
like you promised?
I sure was!
And because I was brave,
I win the game of
courage!
Whoa.
But you didn't do it by
yourself. You had help
from a Captain. That's
not fair.
Mm.
Wait a minute! There's no
rule that says someone
can't help me!
This has been a blast!
I really enjoyed it!
Let's have some more
sake, what do you say?
Sounds good!
Captain!
I just wanted to thank
you again for saving me,
sir!
You're the bravest
warrior any of us
has ever met!
You know what, I want to
be just like you when I
grow up! Would you come
and visit us again?
Of course! I'll come
over any time you want!
You're our hero!
That's just part
of the job!
[laughing]
[snoring]
No, really, I can't eat
another thing...
Oh, crap!
The Captain's gonna
give me hell when I
get back to base!
No really, Captain! I'm
telling you the truth!
That's the reason I'm so
late reporting in!
I saved a kid named
Ryuzaburo from a Hollow!
Please, you have to
believe me! I rescued the
boy and took him back to
his village! There's no
other reason why I'd be
running behind! I would
never neglect my squad
duties!
Oh,calm down, Marechiyo! The
fact of the matter is,
your absence wasn't
missed in the least!
[groaning]
It's kinda sad when
you put it that way.
However... You did break
the rules.
So I'm assigning you to
clean up the Seireitei
grounds...
...By yourself.
You can't be serious! I
have to clean the whole
place...?
By myself? I
mean, I am a Lieutenant,
after all! That wouldn't
be right!
If you prefer... I can
come up with some other
punishment. Perhaps you
would prefer latrine duty?
Uhh...! No.
I really don't understand.
If you were free and had
the time to handle this,
why did I have
to come along?
Don't be so negative.
Why can't we go in there?
Huh?
Sorry boys, but I have my
orders. No outsiders
allowed.
If it were up to me, I'd
let you in, but I'm not
allowed to let anyone
enter the area without
the permission of a Soul
Reaper.
We're telling you, if you
contact the Captain,
he'll be happy to let
us in!
That's right, we're
good friends of the
Captain!
Hmm...
But how do I
know that's true?
Hey! Jidanbo!
Hm?
Long time, no see!
I can't believe my eyes!
If it isn't Ichigo!
What's going on here?
These three boys showed
up and insist they're
friends of one of the
Captains.
We're begging you!
Would you please
let us in?
We just came down here to
see the Captain.
Hm? Which
Captain is that?
The good one! The one who
came and saved me from
a Hollow!
We wanted to show our
appreciation! But
before we could, he
disappeared.
[sighing]
Isn't there something we
can do, Yoruichi?
Jidanbo...
Hm?
I'll take responsibility.
Go ahead and let these
boys in.
[gasping]
So. Who's this Captain
you came to see?
Well, the thing is, we
don't actually know his
name.
Seriously?
Was there anything
physical about this
person that stood
out in your minds?
I do remember he was kind
of husky!
He was a big guy! Pretty
tall!
Yeah!
Oh, and one other thing
about him! He was pointy!
Hmm?
So he was husky...
...And pretty tall...
And on top of that, he
was pointy!
Wonder if it's
Kenpachi...
But wouldn't you say
Komamura is pointy as
well... especially
around the ears?
No, he'd stand out too
much. I mean, wouldn't
they just describe him
as looking like a dog?
Uh!
The guy said he was the
Captain of Squad Two!
[gasping]
Oh brother! Why do I have
to do this grunt work?
It's a ridiculous waste
of my time and energy!
Huh?
Ah, perfect. Just the man
we want to see. Let's ask
him where Soi Fon is.
[laughing]
Captain, there you are!
Uh, huh??
What in the world are you
kids doing here?!
Captain!
Why did you leave the
village so suddenly?
Uh... Well...
I... See...
Uh...!
[grunting]
Uh-oh! What am I going to
do? I lied about being a
Captain, and I ate and
drank all the stuff the
villagers put out for me!
This is bad! If anybody
here finds out the
truth...
What's going on, Omaeda?
We're very pleased to
know your name is Omaeda,
Captain!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Why are you addressing
the Captain without a
term of respect?!
That's very rude!
You say 'Captain'...
But the Captain of Squad
Two is---
Ahhhhhhh!
Lady Yoruichi,
can we talk?!
Huh?
So I said this, and that,
and one thing led to
another...
So that's what happened.
Please don't bust me!
But we'd be contributing
to a lie...
Alright, fine.
What?! Yoruichi?!
Thank you! I
really owe you!
Heh! Hey...!
This is gonna be fun!
[chuckling]
This can't be good.
Awesome!
What a great place! This
is where the Captain
lives?
Of course he does! He's
the Captain!
Okay, you boys have had a
pretty good tour! It's
time for you to head
home, now.
Already?
Come on, we just got
here! We want to see more
of how you do your job!
Please, Captain! Can't
we hang out?
Well of course you can!
In fact, by Captain
Omaeda's authority, you
boys can do almost
anything you want while
you're visiting.
All right!
I... never
said that!
[cheering and giggling]
I knew it. She's
enjoying this!
[grunting]
Ikkaku.. and Yumichika!
Damn! What lousy timing,
to run into these two
guys!
Yo.
Hey.
Oh, hi there.
Just a minute, you two!
Uh?!
Hm?
You can't just walk
by like that! It's
disrespectful!
You owe Captain
Omaeda a more
proper greeting!
Huh? What are you
talking about?!
Ah!!
Like this! Stand at
attention!
And say 'Good morning,
sir!' Now you try it!
I think these boys are
serious. How strange.
Yeah, I don't intend to
ignore their behavior,
just because they're
little kids.
Uhh... Well... you
see.. It's... uhh...
I mean...
Huh? Hey, Ichigo.
What are you doing?
What the hell? Let
go of me!
And that's the
situation...
I'm sure he'll make it up
to you properly, once the
kids are gone.
I guess we can play
along. Right, Ikkaku?
[grumbling]
Good morning! How are
you, Captain Omaeda?
Why am I
doing this?
Oh, play along. It's not
that difficult.
Damn! This is gonna
cost a lot!
Come to think of it, you
must be thirsty, Captain.
What are you waiting for,
you two? Bring the
Captain some tea!
Tea, you say?
Uh!
Oh, of course,
sir----Right away!
Oh, you're gonna pay
for this big time.
Come on.
I'm getting out of here
while I can still run.
What's the matter? Are
you all right?
They're gonna bring you
some tea.
Yeah, about that--- I'm
not in the mood...
Sorry for the delay,
Captain!
I brought you that cup of
tea!
What are you doing here
Rangiku?
Well, we came here to
serve you! Mm?
Right, everyone?
Hi there, Captain Omaeda!
You people should take
the Captain somewhere
nearby, where he can
relax!
He's been under a lot of
stress!
You got it!
Hey, wait a second! Hang
on there! What?!
[growling]
They took it all. My
wallet...
...my watch... my ring,
everything.
I feel like I've been
mugged or something!
[groaning]
What are you doing here?
Forget it. I don't
have anything left
to give you.
Ah!
[trembling]
Captain.. Soi Fon!
I seem to recall
assigning you to cleaning
duty, yet here you are.
Well... I was...
Oh boy. This is bad.
Really bad!
I'll ask again. Why are
you not carrying out your
assignment?
Insolence!
Hm?
You can't speak to this
man like that!
No! Not to her! Anybody
but her! Please!!
Really now, who do you
think this person is
you've been talking to?
You happen to be
addressing Sir Omaeda,
Captain of Squad Two!
Impressive. Their
timing was perfect!
Where did you boys
get that information?
Marechiyo, you're in
serious trouble! You can
say goodbye to your days
at the Seireitei, and
hello to an unknown
future!
[crying]
I'm done for!
[clearing throat]
I apologize, Captain
Omaeda. I should have
been more respectful.
Huh?!
What?! It's a miracle,
that's what it is! I've
been saved by the Gods!
How long can we keep this
up?
This is the attitude you
should have had from the
start!
Go ahead, Sir Omaeda...
It's time to give this
misguided woman some
orders.
What?! No... Really...
Didn't you mention
earlier that you needed
someone to do some
cleaning?
Oh boy. She's really
enjoying this!
Sir... what's next?
[gasping]
I don't... know.
Bring another bowl!
Yes! Right away!
And I want another one,
as well!
Of course!
Hey, the Captain is out
of sake!
Yes!
Sir... What's next?
Uh...! Next?
Well... I do have sore
muscles...
Oh yeah! That's the spot!
If you could push harder
right there, that would
be great!
[groaning]
Uh...
This is the best!
[chuckling]
I'm so glad
we came to visit!
Yeah! We're lucky to have
met such a great man!
It's been like a dream!
Damnit!
Huh?
That bastard Marechiyo
was so insulting to me!
One thing's for sure.
That coward could never
be a Captain!
Really. He just hasn't
got what it takes.
I'll get him back--
What's happening here?
The Captain must have
been lying about
everything!
We've been played for
fools! The guy's not a
Captain at all!
Ryuzaburo! You're the one
who told us he was a
Captain!
It's all your
fault!
I'll see you guys again,
sometime. If you come
back for another visit,
I'll take you on a tour
of the Captain's
quarters!
[laughing]
He sure plays
the part, huh?
What a liar!
What's the matter,
Ryuzaburo? Next time
you come to visit,
how 'bout I give you some
training in swordsmanship?
Soon, you'll become a
good fighter, like me!
Hm?
What happened?
It was nothing
but a big lie!
Liar!
[gasping]
I've been waiting for
you! Give back what you
stole from me!
[gasping]
[grunting]
Finally, I've got you
back! With this piece, my
power will return!
[gasping]
Excellent! Now all that's
left is to devour you!
[gasping]
[roaring]
[screaming]
Man...
[gasping]
I don't know about you.
You just keep getting
into one mess after
another!
[gasping]
Now stay here and don't
move!
[yelling]
[growling]
Really? You think you
can defeat me with your
predictable moves, as
slow as you are?
You're not getting away!
[gasping]
Uh?
[grunting]
Surprised?
My movements may not be
that fast in a one-on-one
confrontation. But if I
use the power of my tail,
I can completely
neutralize the speed of
whoever I'm fighting.
Damnit!
That bastard! He
completely suppressed my
speed! This is bad! This
is really bad!
I need to get some help
immediately!
Oh no! What are they
doing here?!
I can't just run off with
them watching me! To
them... I'm a... I'm a...
Captain! And a Captain
doesn't avoid facing an
enemy in battle! Ever!
[grunting]
He's getting himself beat
up!
[grunting]
He's not good... at
anything.
Why would you say that?
Huh?
It's true that the guy
fighting in front of you
isn't a Captain...
[yelling]
But it doesn't change the
fact that he saved your
life.
Was it the idea that the
man might be a Captain,
that impressed you? Or
were you impressed by the
man himself, when he
stepped in and saved you?
Uh.
I suggest you keep
watching him. You might
decide he's your hero
after all.
Damn! I could have run
away by now if those kids
weren't watching me! Not
that it would do any
good, since that Hollow
can neutralize my speed.
Wait a minute! If they
weren't watching me...
That's it!
You haven't got anything
left, have you? Then I
guess it's time I
devoured you!
[grunting]
[gasping]
Well now.. Tell me, how
does Gegetsuburi taste?
Bakudo Number 21!
Sekienton!
[groaning]
How's that? You can't
see me very well, can
you?
And I can't see you!
But so what?!
[grunting]
Smash 'em!
[groaning and yelling]
I guess you shouldn't
have... underestimated
me.
Thank you... Mr. Omaeda.
I see you went and
demoted me from 'Captain'
to 'Mister'.
What did you expect?
You did lie to me!
I have to admit that's
true, but...
Don't worry, it's cool!
Huh?
My friends were so
impressed by your
bravery,
that they want to
become strong Soul
Reapers, like you!
And what about you,
Ryuzaburo?
Mm!
Someday, I hope to become
an even stronger
Lieutenant than you, sir!
Huh. I'll keep
that in mind.
You should hurry on home.
[chuckling]
Bye!
Apparently, all's well
that ends well, right,
Marechiyo?
Absolutely! Hm...
What do you say we go
back and have some tea...
Ahhhh! Captain!
Who's gonna serve you
that tea?
Ahhhhh!
Please--
I suppose you'd have to
say, he brought this on
himself.
Didn't we contribute,
just a little?
[grunting]
I'm sooorryyy!
I'm exhausted. I'm gonna
head back now. Yoruichi,
open the Senkaimon, will
you?
You can't go!
What? Why not?!
Because there are more
stories like this one
coming up!
You get caught
in the middle of another
mess in the next episode!
You're kidding me,
right?