[theme music]
NARRATOR: Ichigo
and his friends were
on the brink of being defeated
by the formidable Espadas when
the captains of the
13 Court Guard Squads
arrived in Hueco Mundo.
Under the orders of
Head Captain Yamamoto,
the captains quickly
challenged the Espadas.
Captain of Squad
11 Kenpachi Zaraki
came to the aid of Ichigo
and initiated a fierce battle
with Espada #5, Nnoitra Gilga.
After his eye patch
was cut off, Kenpachi
unleashed a massive
amount of spirit energy
that forced Nnoitra to
reveal his Resurreccion form
and fight back with
his six lethal arms.
But no matter how seriously
Kenpachi was wounded,
he howled with laughter and
relished fighting his opponent.
Nnoitra was enraged by
Kenpachi's behavior,
and attacked him
even more brutally.
Bleeding profusely
from his deep wounds,
Kenpachi found he was unable to
counter his opponent's attacks.
His situation was
becoming desperate.
Kenpachi realized
he would die soon
unless he could find a
weakness in Nnoitra's defense.
Suddenly his solution was clear.
With Nnoitra about to defeat
him, Kenpachi made his move.
-This has gone on too
long, hurry up and die!
-Kenpachi!
-Huh.
If we keep this
up, I think there
is a chance that I'll die.
-Oh, Kenny, no.
-Oh well, then.
Guess I have no choice.
It's been a while
since I've tried this.
Time for some kendo.
An important
lesson-- that a sword
becomes much more
powerful when it's
swung with both hands
instead of just one.
-Of course it does.
That should be
perfectly obvious!
-But you don't know
the half of it.
-(VOICEOVER) Is he giving up?
He's just standing there!
I am the strongest!
[gasp]
-(AFRAID) All right,
I surrender, you win!
Just don't kill me.
Guaagh!
-You have something
you want to say?
You think it's wrong for
me to kill my opponents,
especially since he's
a fellow Arrancar?
Oh, please.
I think the answer
should be obvious.
It's because we're both
Arrancars that I killed him.
Listen carefully.
If you intend to travel with
me, then remember something.
Taking pity on an enemy
won't save a comrade.
It's foolish.
-Now listen to me, Nnoitra.
I said I don't
want to fight you.
I just don't see
the reason for it.
It makes no sense to me.
-You may not see it,
but it's clear to me.
The fact is, fighting
itself is my purpose.
-That doesn't explain much.
Why are you so desperate
to engage in these fights?
-Because I want to die.
I want to die
gloriously in battle.
That's why I work so
hard to become strong.
If I'm strong, people will
come to me looking for a fight.
And when I'm fighting, that's
when I feel truly alive.
-You must be
addicted, obviously.
-You're right.
The strongest liquor is
nothing compared to a fight.
In our world, there's
no such as salvation.
And that's true whether
or not Aizen is here
to absolve us of our sins.
If I am grateful to him
for anything at all,
it's for making
me more powerful.
Because of him, I experience
more intense battles.
I am determined
to become strong.
Stronger than anyone else.
If I'm going to fight
the strongest foe,
there can't be anyone
else stronger than me.
I'm going to crush everyone with
whatever means at my disposal.
I want life to have fled my
body before it hits the ground.
That's how I want to die.
-Good fight, Nnoitra.
That was fun.
-Kenpachi.
Kenpachi--
[crash]
[gasps]
-What's the matter with
you, are you crazy?
Aaahh!
Hey, I'm on your side!
-Your sword.
Pick it up.
Now that you've got it,
take the women and go home.
Your work here is done.
It's time for us to take over.
-What are you saying?
I've come this far, I'm
going to see it through!
-What are you?
You're a substitute Soul Reaper.
Your job is to
protect Karakura Town.
Isn't that right?
You rescued this woman.
You should be satisfied.
So accept what I'm
saying and go home.
You've had your share
of fighting, kid.
It's time to let the
professionals take over.
Woman!
-Yes, sir?
-Come and heal my wounds.
-Uh, right!
[gasp]
-Sorry for this.
I don't enjoy these
kinds of assignments,
but I have my orders.
Need to borrow her for a bit.
-They're gone.
AIZEN: Welcome back, Orihime.
What's the matter?
I thought you'd be happy to see
us now that you're back again,
but you look so troubled.
You should try to smile.
Everyone gets so depressed
when the sun doesn't shine.
Smile and wait here a while.
That's all you need to do,
just until-- just until my men
and I finished
destroying Karakura town.
-You're going to
destroy Karakura Town?
-That's right.
I need to destroy Karakura
Town to create the Oken.
Kaname.
-Yes?
-The Tenteikura.
-Right.
Bakudo #77, Tenteikura.
AIZEN: Can you hear me,
my daring intruders?
-That awful voice--
-Aizen.
-They're using the Tenteikura.
AIZEN: I commend you
for coming this far
and defeating my Espadas.
As a reward, I will
tell you this much.
We are proceeding with
our plans to invade
the world of the living.
-What's that?!
-They're what?!
I thought they determined
that such an invasion was
impossible to carry out, unless
Orihime awakened the Hogyoku.
-Wait a minute,
where is Orihime?
AIZEN: Orihime Inoue is being
held in the fifth tower.
If you want to
effect her rescue,
feel free to come and get her.
She is no longer
of any use to me.
-What's that?
-She is no use?
AIZEN: Her powers
are indeed amazing.
Her ability to reject
all forms of phenomena
is beyond anything the human
race has ever demonstrated.
The leaders of the Soul
Society are not fools.
They have understood the
importance of that power
from the beginning.
That's why her capture
was a threat to them.
It helps to explain
their response to her.
They were afraid.
They immediately
took steps to protect
not the world of the living,
but the Soul Society itself.
-With this new
information, we now
know that the Arrancars
are ready for battle.
All members of Captain
Hitsugaya's advanced troops
are to return immediately
and defend the Soul Society.
AIZEN: Her very presence
caused them to mobilize.
She became the bait to
lure in the Soul Society's
potential new military
strength, the Ryoka, which
included the substitute
Soul Reaper and his friends.
-Damn it.
AIZEN: If you were wondering
about the fate of the four
captains who came to assist
the intruders, don't worry.
I was able to imprison
them here in Hueco Mundo.
--[gasp] The four Garganta that
we passed through in order
to get here have
all been sealed.
-Wait a minute, Mayuri.
Can't we open them
up from this side?
-I'm afraid it's impossible.
The trouble is there's
only one person who
knows how the Garganta works.
And that, unfortunately,
is Kisuke Urahara.
If we can't contact him I'm
afraid opening them again is
going to present
something of a problem,
' as much as I hate to admit it.
-The strength of the
13 Court Guard Squads
is really quite simple
when you break it down.
The 13 captains all
possess enough power
to be able to stand as a
military force of their own.
But now, however, three
of them have defected.
And four of them are imprisoned.
If you do the
math, you could say
that the military power
of the Soul Society
has been cut in half.
It makes our job easy.
We will destroy Karakura
Town, create the Oken,
and overthrow the Soul Society.
AIZEN: When all of this is
done, I shall take each of you
on at my leisure.
-Karakura town, destroyed?!
-Hold on, Ichigo.
Where are you going?
What the hell do you think
you'll be able to accomplish?
-You have any
better suggestions?
Karakura Town is in real danger!
Do I just wait for
them to destroy it?
-Didn't I mentioned this?
The old man gave Kisuke
Urahara a set of orders.
He waited until he knew
the final battle was
coming in winter.
Then he acted.
The first order was
to the captains.
They were all assigned
to duty in Hueco Mundo.
Do you know what the
second order was?
It went to the rest
of the officers.
It was short and to the point.
Every officer of
captain level was
to prepare for battle
in Karakura Town.
-Do you know what
the second order was?
It went to the rest
of the officers.
It was short and to the point.
Every officer of
captain level was
to prepare for battle
in Karakura Town.
-Wait a minute.
That means the 13 Court
Guard Squads are--
-Yes.
If my calculations
are correct, they
should have arrived by now.
-That's crazy.
They can't have a battle there.
The power of all those
captains is too much.
What do you think will
happen to Karakura Town?
I'm telling you right
now, it'll be destroyed.
-Remember what I said.
Everyone should be
ready for battle.
That was his order.
Think about it.
Just increasing the number
of captain level fighters
doesn't necessarily equate
to being ready for battle.
-He meant Tenkai Kecchu.
It means to reconstruct
Karakura Town in order
to make it possible
to fight there.
In order to do that, Kisuke
Urahara did something creative.
He constructed a device
called Tenkai Kecchu, which
connected four pillars to
form a giant Senkaimon.
He then placed the Tenkai
Kecchu around the four corners
of Karakura Town.
At the same time, he
asked my Department
of Research and Development
to do something incredible.
He asked us to construct
an elaborate replica
of the entire town, down
to the last dwelling.
He asked us to place it
near the Rukon District.
An incredible challenge,
but I have to humbly admit,
we pulled it off.
Here's the twist.
Whatever Tenkai
Kecchu encircles can
be switched with something
inside the Soul Society.
By utilizing this
technique, we were
able to transfer
the real Karakura
Town from its present location
into the area surrounding
the Rukon District.
-Wait a minute, Captain.
What about the residents?
-We put them to sleep, and then
transported them and the town
to the Soul Society.
MAYURI: What you
see out there now
is merely a replica of Karakura
town, completely devoid
of people.
Presuming the captains
do battle there,
even if the town is destroyed
it won't matter a bit.
YAMAMOTO: Excellent.
It seems we made
it here in time.
-Made it in time.
Now, why would you think
to say something like that?
I'm well aware that
what lies beneath you
is not Karakura Town.
This may come as a surprise,
but that means nothing to me.
Starrk, Barragan,
Halibel, come here.
If Karakura Town is now
inside the Soul Society,
we'll just kill you right
here and create the Oken
within the Soul Society.
It is that simple.
Until then, I shall
leave Las Noches
under your care, Ulquiorra.
[glass breaking]
-Sir.
-[gasp]
-Kenpachi.
You said earlier that I had
only one job, didn't you?
And that job was to
protect Karakura Town.
You were wrong.
I know what my job is.
It's to protect my friends.
-(VOICEOVER) Come
on, Ichigo Kurosaki.
[theme music]
ORIHIME: Ichigo, I
got an invitation
to Rurichiyo's
Kemari tournament!
ICHIGO: Weren't we going to
talk about the Soul Reapers'
past in the next episode?
URYU: That can wait until
after the tournament.
We get so little
screen time as it
is, let's take advantage of it.
ICHIGO: Uryu, don't make
us sound so pitiful.