ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Ever since
the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me, my
whole world has changed.
Now I'm Ichigo Kurosaki,
substitute Soul Reaper,
and I'm combining my
powerful spirit energy
with this blade in order
to protect my friends!
[theme music]
[alarm ringing]
-Right.
I came back home.
ISSHIN: Good morning, Ichigo!
Well, you've certainly
improved, Ichigo.
I'm impressed you
were able to ward off
my wonderful welcome home kick.
-Shut up.
-But, don't think you
can avoid my crazy-- it
ICHIGO: Too much noise
this early in the morning!
ISSHIN: That's the sound of--
YUZU: Ichigo.
Dad.
Breakfast is ready.
ICHIGO: Oh no.
KARIN: What are they doing now?
-Dad?
What happened to your face?
-Nevermind.
-I see.
-Oh, by the way, Ichigo.
Have you been
working out lately?
I noticed yesterday
you got a few muscles.
-Wow, what do you now?
So, how about you guys?
I know they piled the
homework on this summer.
Have you finished it yet?
-Mhmm.
We got it done in
hardly any time at all.
We didn't have anything else to
do while you were on your trip,
so--
-Oh yeah, I forgot to tell you.
That Kanonji guy came
by a couple of times.
He said he'd made you a
disciple or something.
YUZU: That's right.
-I don't know what
he's talking about.
ISSHIN: Think fast!
You're gonna have to move a
whole lot faster than that.
What do you think you're doing?
-Hey, knock it off!
Not at the table, you two.
-Ichigo!
-Hey, Keigo.
What's up?
-Good morning, Ichigo.
What's happening?
-What's going on, Mizuiro?
-Long time no see.
How's it going?
You have a good summer?
-Hm.
-Morning, Ichigo.
How are you today?
-Good.
Hey, Tatsuki.
How you been doin'?
-Hi.
I guess you had a pretty
busy summer, didn't?
You're never home
when I stop by.
-Hey, everyone.
Good morning.
Check it out.
Chad and Ichigo got tans
-Awesome.
-I did?
-Hey Don't tell me you guys
went off together somewhere?
-Ah--
-Hm?
-Ah!
You two are checking
each other out!
Well, now, are we talking about
a little summer camp romance
here?
Ah!
-Try to keep your
imagination in check.
-Wah!
-How about you, Orihime?
Did you have a good visit
with your relatives?
-Huh?
Oh, yeah.
Sure.
It was wonderful
to see them all.
Gosh, we did so
many things together
-Yeah?
Like what kind of things?
-Huh?
Well, for one, we all went
somewhere really strange
-What do you mean by that?
-Well, it kind of looked
like an Edo period town,
and all the people
there were in costume,
and carrying swords and stuff.
There was a cat there
who could actually talk.
But you see, he was a
boy cat, and then he
turned into a human girl
-Right, right.
Of course he did.
Now, why don't we concentrate
on second semester?
-Good morning, everyone.
Take your seats.
-I wonder what his problem is?
-All right.
It looks like everyone's here.
That's excellent.
Great.
But I don't see
Oshima and Sorimachi.
Those two are a
couple of delinquents,
so that's no big loss.
Now then, I want you all to get
out your summer assignments.
I hope you remembered
to bring them in.
-Thank you, Rukia.
-Yeah.
Thank you.
MAN: Where are you hiding?
Come on out here!
-Huh?
-I know that voice.
-Ichigo Kurosaki!
You're up there!
Don't pretend you're not!
-What?
-Ichigo, you know that guy?
He's all hippied out.
-Hey!
Ichigo!
-Oh, that's very retro.
RENJI: Don't keep me waiting!
-Kurosaki, is he any--
-A relative!
RENJI: Not gonna be pretty!
-How groovy.
[chatter]
-How strange.
-Hurry up!
Come on!
ICHIGO: What are you doing?
-Yo.
-Are you totally
out of your mind?
-What are you so excited about?
-Excited?
You think you might explain what
the hell you're doing there?
-Yeah?
Well, what do you care
what I'm doing Here?
No reason for you
to get all upset--
-Oh, yes there is,
you yelling like that
in front of everybody.
-Oh, man this Gigai's
not comfortable at all.
I can't imagine why Rukia stayed
in hers as long as she did.
-What are you doing here?
-Uh, well, it's like this.
It seems I've been put in
charge of this Karakura Town.
Mr. Urahara told me where
you were, I came to see you,
and that's the story.
Now I'm in charge.
-You are, are ya?
-Yeah.
-You're just a Lieutenant.
You got demoted.
-I did not!
I had to come over
here because of idiots
like you leaking spirit energy.
-What are you talking about?
[beeping]
-That's what I was telling you.
Huh?
-Huh?
[roar]
-That's a Hollow.
-All right, pass all of
your assignments forward
and I'll collect them
-(VOICEOVER) What should I do?
-(VOICEOVER) This is bad.
It's getting closer.
-(VOICEOVER) Ichigo,
what are you doing?
TEACHER: Does anyone
know what page that was?
-Damn this Gigai!
-What's the matter?
-I can't get out!
You're going to have the do it.
-What?
Are you serious?
Dammit
TEACHER: Compare these
with last semester's work,
you'll see some differences.
-Huh?
[roar]
TEACHER: And so we
get the same result--
[shout]
TEACHER: --using entirely
different approaches.
-Yes!
Way to go!
TEACHER: What are
you doing, Orihime?
-Huh?
Ah--
[laughter]
-Good job.
-Cut the crap.
Don't just leave your body
lying around like that.
Hurry up and put it on.
-I don't want to go back in.
I just got out of it.
-Now, listen up.
I don't want you comin'
around my school.
You got that?
-Yeah, but--
-You got that?
TEACHER: And I'm
sure you'll all be
pleased to know
that's the solution.
-It's still hot like summer.
-Brainfreeze!
Ow!
But then it's so refreshing!
And then it's so painful!
-Maybe you should
eat it more slowly.
-Yeah, Tatsuki.
You're absolutely right.
How's your hand doing, anyway?
-100% no problems at all.
And the championships
are next month.
I'm doing great.
-You know, Tatsuki,
you're really amazing.
Compared to you, I'm just--
-Orihime?
-Aw.
Not again!
-At your relatives' house, was
there some kind of problem?
-It felt like-- I didn't feel
like I was of much use there.
To tell you the
truth, I really wanted
to contribute, and be helpful.
But I think that it's possible
I might have just gotten
in the way.
-Oh, Orihime--
-But then I-- I
could hear your voice
telling me to hang in there.
And that's why--
well-- I decided
to keep on doing all I could.
-I think that's good enough.
You went because you wanted to.
You can't decide whether
to help people or not
the only thing you
can do is be yourself.
The most important thing is
that you came back safely
Welcome home, Orihime.
-I, Orihime, will always try!
TATSUKI: Are you all right?
ORIHIME: Oh, yeah.
Never better.
Ow!
ICHIGO: Hey.
I'm home.
-Hi.
You're just in time for dinner.
-You're late!
-Finally.
Payback for this morning.
-In this house,
dinner's at 7:00.
Have you forgotten?
ICHIGO: Shut up!
-Not again.
Would you two cut it out?
-Leave them alone.
Just try to think of it
as a bonding experience.
ISSHIN: --super kick of
reality you don't like.
Ah!
-So, are you ready
for seconds yet?
-Hm?
-I wouldn't want you to think
that just because you're
a moocher, you can't
ask for seconds.
How about it?
Can I dish you up
another serving
of our meager meal, Mr. Mooch?
-Yeah.
Sure.
-You're the first
one to get seconds.
But don't worry.
You go right ahead, Mr. Mooch.
TESSAI: Come on.
Don't be shy.
-Well, I guess so, then.
-Why stand on manners?
Even a sponger like you
needs seconds Go on.
Eat up.
-Speaking of manners,
it's not very
polite to call our
guest here a moocher.
How can he feel comfortable
asking for seconds?
Am I right, Mr. Moocher?
-(VOICEOVER) I can't
ask for seconds?
JINTA: Oh, by the way, you need
to clean the front of the shop
tomorrow morning, all right?
-Hey, what the--
-After all, it's the least
you can do as a moocher,
don't you think?
You're the one
who wants seconds.
Ha.
-Well?
What do you say, moocher?
You going to pass
that bowl over?
-It's OK.
-Thanks, but I couldn't
eat another bite.
-Ah, ha ha ha!
-Jinta, I can't believe
how mean you are.
-I never imagined he'd be
as sensitive as all that.
TESSAI: I got to admit--
-That guy's pitiful.
I've been meaning
to ask you, Kisuke.
-Yeah?
What is it?
-I know it's been awhile since
I've been back in this town,
but I sense something unnatural.
Do you have any idea
what's going on?
[sigh]
-There's been a
little disturbance
of spirit particles.
But I don't really
think it's anything
to get too excited about.
-Hm.
Orihime, I know this
might sound crazy,
but after spending
some time there,
I think I might finally
be able to understand
the reason behind my strength.
-It's so confusing.
I don't know what to think.
I only went to be
there for Ichigo.
I just wanted to
help him in some way.
But I couldn't.
And now I just don't know
what I should do anymore.
-We can only keep fighting.
-Huh?
-It's only through Ichigo
that our powers were awakened.
So, if we have any intention
of staying with him,
then we must do
everything we possibly
can to enhance our powers.
[shout]
-What are you doing?
Chad, don't you remember
what happened the last time
you did this?
-Hm?
-Come on, Chad!
Hurry!
I'm sorry.
Gotta hurry!
-(VOICEOVER) Those who have
traveled to the Soul Society
and learned the real truth
can no longer keep their eyes
closed.
They can no longer keep
their ears covered.
But I-- such an ominous moon.
-Why are you trying
to act like Mr. Cool?
-You think I don't
know what's going on?
-Well, no, I mean--
I'm not quite
sure what you expect me to say.
-Oh, so now you're going to
start acting all obsequious.
Well, forget it.
Your sister's tried that
on me, and it didn't work!
-Fine, I'll take you
to Uryu tomorrow.
-You know what you are?
-You're lazy,
that's what you are.
Mr. Big Shot thinks
he's all high and mighty
because he's got a substitute
Soul Reaper combat pass,
and can turn into a Soul Reaper!
-I don't think I'm all
high and mighty, all right?
What's gotten into you lately?
All you ever do
is piss and moan.
-Yeah?
Well, maybe I wouldn't
complain if you
had done what you
were supposed to do.
Why didn't you bring Rukia back?
-Hey, what--
-Shut up, already.
I went so I could stop
Rukia's execution.
I never said I was
going to bring her back.
You don't have any idea
what happened there, so
why don't you give that
mouth of yours a rest?
-Oh, no.
I'm just some dumb
stuffed animal.
How could I know?
But you're sadly
mistaken if you think
you can do everything
by yourself.
-What are you talking about?
-I do the best I can.
And yet, and yet--
Rukia, I want to see her!
I want to see her, I want to
see her, I want to see her.
I want to see her.
I want to--
-Shut up and go to sleep.
-Fine.
-Just look at you,
my little bunny.
Huh?
Oh, you're finally home.
-I wish you wouldn't wait
outside for me, Orihime.
I couldn't wait to see you.
I made this bunny as
a welcome home gift.
See?
-It's looks just like one.
Now, we'd better go inside,
or you'll catch a cold.
-Aw, please, not yet.
This is the Sora Bunny.
I still have to make
an Orihime Bunny.
-All right, then.
Why don't we make it together?
-OK.
-My brother.
-Byakuya!
Brother--
-I don't-- why am I crying?
[doorbell]
-Coming!
[gasp]
-I'm home again.
-I can't believe it.
[snoring]
[beeping]
-Huh?
A Hollow?
What the-- how can that be?
-Hm.
Looks like he's going out on a
job in the middle of the night.
-How strange.
-It's good to see you again.
You're looking well.
-Thanks.
I was never sure-- on
that day, did you--
-Yeah.
I was able to make it
to the Soul Society.
It's all right now,
because I'll never
have to become a Hollow again.
-And you weren't hurt?
You were able to
get there safely?
-Yes.
You were there, too.
Weren't you, Orihime?
The Soul Society?
-Yeah.
How did you know about that?
-Hey, older brothers
know everything.
-What is it?
What's so funny?
-I was just thinking, you
haven't changed at all
since you were a little girl.
You would worry about
me all the time.
You were so cute.
I remember you
waiting outside for me
in the freezing cold,
your hands frozen
from making snow bunnies.
-Yeah.
RENJI: Hey.
Ichigo.
Wake up.
Hey!
-Huh?
-It's about time you woke up.
You shouldn't let
your guard down.
-Shut up.
What the hell are you doing
here at this hour, anyway?
-I've got a job that
needs to be done.
And you're going
to come with me.
-Huh?
I don't see why I have to go.
That is, unless
you're like Rukia,
and you can't handle
things yourself.
-Why, you-- I oughtta--
-Put a sock in it, you two.
It's the middle of the night!
-Ah!
Wha-- wha-- what is that?
-Hm?
-After arguing with
you about Rukia,
I was so upset I had to
count three herds of sheep
to get to sleep.
And now I'm awake,
and the sheep are out
of the pen because of you!
Idiots!
-You've gotta be kidding.
Is this one of those--
-I don't have any cavities!
-Well, what do you know?
It's a Soul Candy.
So it'll move even when you
put it in something like this?
-Why are you so
interested in it?
-I don't know.
I guess it's just
one of those things I
forgot about when I got here.
-Maybe that's why you couldn't
get out of your Gigai.
So, what's this job
you woke me up for?
-Right.
I almost forgot.
It has to do with the strange
message I got on my Soul Pager.
I mean, the spiritual pressure
isn't all that strong,
but you can feel it, can't you?
-Orihime!
-Yeah.
Whatever the source is,
it must be close to her.
-You should have
said that before!
[squeak]
-Come on, what are
you waiting for?
-Oh.
Yeah.
Right.
-Hey, what about me?
-No.
It isn't that I was worried
about you as much as-- well,
I just always felt so lonely
inside that big, empty house.
I can still remember
how relieved
I felt whenever you came home.
-I felt just the same.
Once I was with you, I knew
that everything would be OK.
-Is that true?
-Orihime--
-What is it?
-Is there something
that's troubling you?
Something that makes
you dream about me?
-Hm?
What is it?
I sense something odd.
-Orihime.
ORIHIME: I don't understand.
How did you know about my dream?
[laughter]
-I know.
Isn't that enough?
I've got a good idea.
Why don't we get some fresh air?
-There it is!
-Look!
RENJI: What the hell is that?
-Now, then, come with me.
-What are you doing?
-There's nothing to worry about.
Join me.
[laughter]
-Don't let those be the
gates of the underworld.
I'm not ready.
URYU: Ichigo!
-Uryu!
Chad!
[scream]
-Orihime!
-It disappeared.
ICHIGO: Orihime!
[laughter]
[theme music]
URYU: I wonder where
Orihime disappeared to?
Hey.
Why don't we follow her scent?
You could do that,
couldn't you, Yoruichi?
YORUICHI: Sure.
No problem.
ICHIGO: What?
You mean cats can do that?
YORUICHI: Are you kidding?
It's a piece of cake
for someone like me.
ICHIGO: I had no
idea you could that!
YORUICHI: Not really.
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers!
KIDS: Golden!
-Perfect.
-What?
You've got a lot of
nerve, dressing me up
to look like some pansy!
Just who do you think
you are, anyway?
URYU: I thought you
might like a change.
KON: This is your
idea of change?
Look at me.
With all this lace, I look more
like a princess than a lion.
Maybe you'd like me to
go dance in the daisies?
-Well this make you happy?
-Yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
Thanks, Uryu.
-The back of his head
is in Quincy style,
but I won't tell him that.