The Zanpakuto... Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined
by its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper and
dies with its Soul Reaper.
That is the existence
of a Zanpakuto.
[chatting]
Hey look! It's the
Captain! He's here!
How come you're not going
over to say hi to him?
I'm fine right here.
I've dealt with him
plenty---It's time for
everybody else to have
a chance.
Maybe so, but the fact
is, they look all tense
and uneasy around him.
It's understandable.
He's not usually this
open.
I never thought he'd let us
use his house for a Garden
Party.
Well... The battles with
the Zanpakuto left
everyone completely
exhausted.
It's my brother's way of
trying to help the squads
to relax. You should be
grateful he cares!
Calm down, there... Hm?
Come to think of it,
wasn't this place blown
to bits during all the
fighting?
By your Zanpakuto, if I
recall! I mean, Squad Six
hasn't even begun making
repairs to their barracks!
The Kuchiki Clan has
money and connections--
Lieutenant, will you join
us? It's getting awkward
over here!
Come on, you guys! He's
just a person, like
anybody else.
Well that was annoying.
Renji wasn't even listening
to me. Unbelievable.
[screaming]
Hey, that's enough!
Who are you and what do
you want?! Explain
yourselves!
I'm unarmed.
Great.
Dance...!
Tsuginomai... Hakuren!
You're not getting away.
Be careful...
Sodenoshirayuki!
I told you before, you're
not getting away! Somenomai!
Are you all right,
Sodenoshirayuki?
Completely unharmed, Sir
Senbonzakura. And you,
are you all right, Lady
Rukia?
I don't understand. I
thought you both returned
to being swords!
What are you talking
about?
Huh?!
As far as I can recall,
neither of us ever made
such a promise to you.
I suppose that's true,
but...
You shouldn't blame us
for your own false
assumptions.
Wait a minute!
What is this
commotion about?
Explain.
I must say... this
is most unusual.
I wasn't expecting a
visit from any of you.
Um, well. As you can see,
our Zanpakuto are still
manifested...
... And we were hoping that
you could tell us why!
Well of course they are!
After all the trouble, I
was able to reverse their
brainwashing,
but I never said I was
returning them to their
normal state.
Here. Take a look for
yourself.
See? That's your
explanation.
Now please stop bothering
me with all your simple
questions---I barely have
time to get things done
as it is. Nemu.. It's
time to get back to work.
Yes. As you
wish, master.
Wait a minute, Captain
Kurotsuchi---
What is it now? I told
you I was busy, didn't I?
Yes, I'm sure you are,
but can you help us with
one more thing?
One more and that's it.
This Zanpakuto has me
concerned.
Ah... fascinating.
This is an instance of a
Zanpakuto going out of
control, after Muramasa
manifested it.
So then you were
aware of this?
Absolutely. It isn't
hard to understand. You know
that Muramasa's abilities
affected not only captains,
but also regular squad
members, right? And in
those cases, once their
Zanpakuto were released,
some of them found that they
had suddenly lost control
over these weapons.
And as a result,
they died.
This Zanpakuto is one of
the many that lost control
after the unfortunate loss
of its master.
I was unaware of this.
Usually, when a
Zanpakuto's owner dies,
the Zanpakuto disappears
as well.
We can only assume
something abnormal
happened here.
At that point, truthfully,
the weapons are no longer
Zanpakutos, Soul Reapers
or even Hollows.
The most accurate
description is that
they're mutants. That
gives me an idea!
I should have thought of
this before. I shall call
them 'Sword Beasts'.
More importantly, why did
that sword suddenly lose
its manifested appearance?
We don't know yet.
But we do know it no
longer possesses
Spiritual Pressure.
Now from what I've been
told, one of them
escaped, right? If
you're somehow able to
recapture it, I can run
experiments and possibly
find an answer to your
question.
Oh. There's one more
thing you should know...
The power of a Sword
Beast is equal to that of a
Zanpakuto's true power. In
other words, its Bankai.
Even if they belonged to
lower-ranking Soul Reapers,
their power is probably far
greater than you think.
Knowing that might help
you stay alive, if you're
going to confront one
directly.
Zanpakuto that have lost
their owners and are now
out of control...
This sounds particularly
dangerous, doesn't it,
Byakuya?
Those fiends caused a
great deal of damage
to the Kuchiki Manor!
Their actions are
unforgivable!
I absolutely agree!
Oh, give me a break, you
two were the ones who
destroyed most of the
mansion!
The bottom line is this:
How do we now capture the
Zanpakuto who escaped?
Oh, there you are!
I've been looking for
you!
Captain! You We need to
assign the next Seireitei
guard duties.
Yes, of course.
Rukia... For now, I'm
going to leave you in
charge of handling this
case.
Right!
I'm going to leave
Senbonzakura with you.
He is at your disposal.
Are you sure about that?
Absolutely.
I know exactly how we can
proceed. We will lure the
fiend out of hiding by
destroying one of the
barracks and getting the
attention of the entire
Seireitei.
We're trying to rebuild
around here! Causing
more destruction won't
help!
All right, then. I have a
better idea. How about we
freeze the entire town with
the fiend inside it?
The buildings will
easily thaw out.
Completely out of the
question!
These drastic solutions
are the best you can come
up with?!
Think of the trouble
you'll cause if we do
what you suggest!
You're saying it's a
problem?
All I'm hearing is, 'We
can't do this, we can't
do that'. It's not very
helpful.
What in the world
can we do?
Suggest something less
destructive!
I know just the thing,
but you have to promise
to keep an open mind.
Everyone.. Thank you
all for your hard work!
Raise your glass!
All right!
Ahhh...
Impressive--You really
know how to make the
booze disappear.
We've had a bit of
practice!
But wow, I never thought
they day would come when
we'd actually be ordered
to throw a party!
Gosh, I'm so happy!
Me too! This is amazing,
it's awesome, really!
Hm?! Wait just a minute,
I never summoned you, why
are you here anyway?
Just what made you think
I was gonna miss this
party?
Come on, girl. It
really doesn't matter
what form she's in, does
it?
Now, who is ready for the
next round?
What is the meaning
of this... Rukia?
Um, this thing? Well,
you see...
It's... it's
a party, sir.
Thanks, I figured that
out. I received an
order yesterday to let
you use this area...
But... Nobody mentioned
that you were going to throw
a big party. Is this necessary?
The party is meant to
lure the out-of-control
Zanpakuto that escaped,
sir.
We... believe
it likes parties.
What?
The last time anyone saw
the fiend, it crashed a
garden party held by
the Kuchiki Clan.
So we're throwing
another.
That is your
justification?
Well, it seemed appropriate
at the time... sir.
I hope you're prepared
to clean up this mess.
Well, I don't see the
fiend showing up.
That's very odd.
'Very odd?'---Really?
You think this is odd?!
Under the circumstances,
I wonder if we didn't
party hard enough.
We partied more than
enough, believe me! I
hope this whole fiasco
wasn't just an excuse for
you to have some fun.
Now that you mention fun,
have either of you seen
Senbonzakura anywhere?
I believe you'll find him
on his back, out in the
courtyard.
[mumbling]
You'd better be careful,
your mask is coming off.
What?! You mean he's
been drinking, as well?!
Rukia. Are you ready to
wrap this party up?
Captain Hitsugaya.. I'm
terribly sorry for any
trouble we caused.
Don't worry about it.
Ever since the Muramasa
incident, my squad's been
under a lot of
pressure. They did need
some time to unwind.
This will certainly give
them a breather.
Oh, there you are,
Captain! How 'bout a
little drinky-poo..!
No chance! And you've had
enough for one night!
Whhhaaaatt? What's a little
winky drinky between friends?
Rukia. You'll need to
take care of this mess.
Yes, understood, sir.
Wait for me, Captain! I'm
reporting for duty!
I'm very sorry about
this..
It sounded like a good
plan, but it didn't work
out quite the way I
thought it would.
Don't blame yourself. The
only thing that matters is
you did the best you could
under the circumstances.
We were just unlucky this
time around.
Thank you, m'lady.
You know, I must say, it's
nice to be able to talk to
you like this every once
in a while.
Uh, something wrong?
Truth is, we Zanpakuto
are truly nothing but
weapons meant for
fighting...
Maybe beneath it all, we
actually do lack heart.
Sodenoshirayuki...?
Don't you see? I always
prided myself on the
extent of my power.
The fact is, that's why
I was so anxious to act
on my own just one time!
That's how Muramasa was
able to worm his way into
my heart.
I was blinded by my ego.
I started thinking I
could do anything and
everything myself.
But the results of this
incident have made me sit
up and realize how
mistaken I was.
I really am only a weapon
with nothing to offer
except my power. Without
your heart to guide me,
I'm just a
simple tool of
destruction.
You're wrong about all of
that! Absolutely wrong!
You and I have always
been partners, right from
the beginning!
You watched over me
through difficult and
painful periods of my
life, through triumph and
tragedy. I couldn't
begin to count the number
of times your presence
has saved me.
In the end...
...I was able to stay
strong because of you.
Don't ever believe you're
just a tool.
Lady Rukia...
Do you sense that?!
Let's go!
Right!
[screaming and yelling]
Run, run!
We have to capture him!
Yes!
You! Stop
right there!
Lady Rukia!
Stay away from here.
If I don't distance
myself, he's going to
destroy me!
Hado Number Thirty-Three!
Sokatsui!
Lady Rukia!
Do it now, I'll
cover you!
Right!
Sokatsui!
Somenomai!
Tsukishiro!
Well, done, M'lady.
M'lady, you're injured!
Looks like we have
him cornered.
As you wish,
M'lady.
Let's go.
Right.
Tsuginomai... Hakuren.
I see... And what did
you do with the Zanpakuto
you captured?
I sent it to the
Department of Research
and Development.
[laughing]
Well, that was probably
the right thing to do.
Captain Ukitake.. I
wanted to ask about that
Sword Beast...
Yes. That probably
won't be the last time
we'll see one.
I've received several
reports of such incidents.
They're spreading.
I thought so.
And the Zanpakuto have
begun to manifest again.
I guess that means
we still haven't found an
effective solution to the
problem.
It couldn't happen at a
worse time. We're forced to
rebuild the Seireitei as fast
as possible, and frankly...
...We may not pull it
off.
[giggling and yelling]
But it out, kids. We can't
hear ourselves over your
racket!
Okay!
It will be all
right.
No matter what challenges
are facing us, we'll all do
what we can to help.
Yes, you're right. And
I'll be counting on you.
...Just as I have been,
all these years.
Right.
Why are the cherry
blossoms in full bloom at
this time of the year?
Perhaps they're not
exactly what they seem.
It sounds like you know
something about this.
Yes,
we had help from Sir
Senbonzakura...
Does that answer
your question?
No wonder there are so
many injured people
around here!