Heeeyaah!
Hurggh!
I think it would be a
good idea if you'd let me
run in front of you now.
e-eh...
Sure. If you insist.
Rrrgh!
Huah!
You sneaky piece of crap,
that hurt!
How dare you interfere
and cut my leg off!
I'll gonna kill you,
you damn insect!
Hunh!
Oh good.
That first one was bad...
It felt like a fly buzzing
around me.
But If you're going to hit me,
why don't you do it with all
your strength, maggot?
You're the pest here...
and it's time to swat you!
I won't describe what's
inside the Garganta.
To find the World of the
Living, go the opposite way.
Right.
Just make sure you're aware
of each step you're taking.
One mis-step inside and
you'll wind up in an unknown
space between the World of
the Living and Hueco Mundo,
and there will be
no way to get back.
But, that might be very
entertaining for me to watch.
What's the matter?
Well, come to think of it,
when Kisuke saw us off,
I remember he was talking
down to us, just like
you're doing right now.
So?
Since you're the second person
to become Chief of Research and
Development, you must have been
his apprentice or something.
The two of you are very similar.
How dare you!
Bye now!
Lieutenant Isane...
We'll be back soon.
Take care of them.
I will, Captain Unohana.
Ichigo...
Quite fearless.
He has my interest.
Oh, I've got plans for you,
Little Ichigo.
Master Mayuri...
At first, I thought it might be
interesting to trap him in the
Garganta... But forget it.
When this battle is finally
over, I'm going to take my time
putting some real fear into him.
As awful as this battle is going
to be for him, it's going to
seem like a walk in the park,
...after I'm done.
Let me think about it,
Master Mayuri.
I'll come up with a plan.
What a surprise,
You're pretty tough
for a filthy maggot.
Big talk for a scrawny bug!
Take this!
Heh heh heh, Can't
fight back anymore?
Give it up, It's over.
I'll crush you!
Like the bug you are!
Huh??
Rgh!
Auuugh!
Damnit! You cut off two of my
fingers!
That was a really cheap shot!
Huh??
Argghh!
Not done yet!
[fighting]
Hee-yaa!
Dyaahh!
You damn bug!
[fighting]
Huwah!
Gyah!
Why did you stay behind,
Mayuri Kurotsuchi?
Odd. My whereabouts don't
seem like something you
would even take the time
to concern yourself with.
I keep thinking, there
should be many more things
of interest to you in the
World of the Living.
So why stay here?
Unless of course you're
plotting something?
Ah, We're very
suspicious, aren't we?
Don't worry so much.
When all is said and done,
you'll see that I'm not
planning anything that
will scare you.
Actually, at the moment,
in case you're wondering,
I've discovered that the
corpses over here are
more interesting.
That is really all
there is to it.
Once the battle in the World
of the Living is over,
someone will open up a
Garganta from the other side.
By then I should be finished
with my work here and be able
to use that Garganta to go to
the World of the Livin
g,
where I'll take time
examining each of the corpses.
Well, what is it?
What is it??
How many times must
I ask you to speak?
If you have something to say,
say it and be done!
HM?
Well...
I never would have expected
you to say such a thing...
or make such
an assumption.
Like what?
You know very well.
You believe sending Ichigo
Kurosaki to the World of the
Living will end that battle.
On top of that, it
sounds like you believe
the boy will ultimately
be victorious.
Huh?
That's nonsense.
Total nonsense.
I never expected that
you would make such
absurd assumptions,
Captain Kuchiki.
Almost there! Hang on, guys!
Ichigo...
I have been meaning
to ask you something.
I heard that you had
encountered Sosuke Aizen
once before, at Sokyoku
Hill, Is that correct?
You heard right.
What about it?
What did you think?
There was only one
thing to think.
The guy had
monstrous strength.
I was completely helpless.
He didn't even use his Shikai.
It was a one-sided encounter.
Wait a minute, are you
absolutely sure he didn't
use his Shikai when he
was fighting you?
Yeah.
That's really good.
Huh?!
The fact that you seemed so
weak, he didn't need to use
his Shikai, is now actually
your greatest advantage.
Huh?!
There are some things I need to
fill you in on, Ichigo.
At the moment, you are
probably the only person in
the World of the Living,
the Soul Society, and
Hueco Mundo, who can
fight Sosuke Aizen...
and actually defeat him.
What do you mean?
I'm going to tell you about
the power of his Zanpakuto,
which is called Kyokasuigetsu,
...and the requirements
to activate it.
This is my
Zanpakuto,
Kyokasuigetsu.
Its ability is
perfect hypnosis.
Impossible! It couldn't change!
Kyokasuigetsu has always been a
running-water-type Zanpakuto...
It uses the diffused reflection
of mist to confuse enemies into
attacking each other!
You yourself explained to
us exactly how it worked,
Captain Aizen!
And we saw it with our own eyes!
You specifically gathered all
the lieutenants together because
you wanted to demonstrate it!
I see now.
Your demonstration
was actually the
hypnosis ritual.
You're catching on quickly.
Complete hypnosis controls all
five senses and is able to cause
every dimension of a target,
including its form, shape, mass,
feel, and smell, even its vocal
patterns and the way it tastes,
to perfectly replicate
that of an enemy.
In other words, it
is possible for me
to make a fly appear
to be a dragon,
...Or a marsh,
a flowerbed.
And all I need to do
to activate it...
is simply show my
enemies my Zanpakuto's
Kanzensaimin release.
The power of my
Zanpakuto is limited
only by my mind,
because whoever
lays their eyes
on it, even once,
will be hypnotized into
doing my bidding whenever I
release my Kyokasuigetsu.
Anyone who sees it?
Just once?
That's right.
All of us who
make up the
Thirteen Court
Guard Squads,
Kisuke Urahara's people,
with whom you are acquainted
in the World of the Living,
And even Sosuke Aizen's
subordinates, the
Arrancars and the Espadas,
Everyone who is even remotely
involved in the battles in
the World of the Living, has
seen Aizen's Shikai.
Everyone, that is,
except for you, Ichigo.
You possess Spiritual Pressure
equal to a Captain,
And you have not seen the
Kyokasuigetsu's Shikai.
So as long as I don't see
Aizen's Shikai, I won't fall
under his perfect hypnosis?
That's right.
Keep in mind, your advantage is
very important in this battle.
But you have to maintain
that advantage.
If you do anything to
lose it, you will become
vulnerable, and the
battle cannot be won.
Listen to me. No matter what
happens in this confrontation
from here on out,
you must not look at
Sosuke Aizen's Shikai.
Do you understand?
Got it.
Thank you,
Captain Unohana.
I'm glad you explained all
of that to me before I have
to meet up with him again.
If I'm the only one who can do
this, then my path is clear.
This time...I'll defeat Aizen!
Rrgh.
You're pretty slow!
Hey, maggot, that gets me itchy.
Is that the best you've got?
Heeeo~
YARRGHHH!!
Wow! I see his
personality isn't
the only thing
that's brutish.
He's also got some brute
strength, to be able to
flip that giant body over.
That hurt. Damnit!
You're starting to piss me off!
You're like a
pesky mosquito!
You damn bug!
Guess I'll have to squash you!
Heh!
[fight yells from both]
Heeyah! Augh! Raugh! Yaah!
If he's going to defeat him,
I wish he'd get it over with
quickly, for heaven's sake.
I'm on pins and needles!
I'm dying to dissect
that big Espada.
Huh?
Haugh!
Oh, great! It appears I'll be
dissecting the Squad Eleven
Captain, instead of that big
bruiser I was so excited about.
But That should be enjoyable
too, just less to cut up.
How bad does it
look, Isane?
Real bad. But I'll handle it.
Please
save them.
I will.
Ichigo...
Ah...
Listen, Ichigo...
Huh?
How about you let me run in
front of you for a little while?
Ah No, I'm all right. If
you're worried about me using
up my Spiritual Pressure...
don't be,
I'm doing just fine.
Ichigo I think it would a
good idea if you'd let me
run in front of you now.
e-eh...
Sure. If you insist.
Sorry about that.
No worries.
Wow! The path looks so
nice when it's laid out by
a Captain's Spirit Energy.
Mine'd be nice too If I
were in good condition.
What are you talking about?
Don't you know that you and I
have similar Spirit Energy?
Huh?!
From what I can see, your wounds
have already healed up.
But you'd be making a mess even
in your best condition. Your
sloppy Spirit Energy is not
suited to this sort of task.
That's not true!
I'm- I'm just not
recovered yet!
That's the problem.
I know I could do
better if I were.
You must be day-dreaming!
Although I have to say,
you look to be wide awake.
Hold on! Don't you think you're
being too hard on me? I'm not a
day dreamer This is very real!
Let me point out to you,
In case you missed it,
I only have one sleeve!
When I release my Bankai,
my robe transforms.
It seems this different robe
is a part of my Bankai.
Uh..?
However, when Isane
was healing my wounds,
Only part of my robe
got fixed.
When Orihime healed me
before, my robe was
completely restored.
So I asked Isane
what happened.
She said she discovered she
can heal wounds quickly, but
it takes her a while to revive
a person's Spirit Energy.
I was in a big hurry.
Rukia and the others
were in trouble, and I
couldn't stay to finish.
I left before having all of
my Spirit Energy restored.
So this is it. This is all the
Spirit Energy I have right now.
See? If I were at my best,
I could do better.
Impossible! His robe is less
than half of what it usually is.
This is not what I
expected to hear.
If he only has half of his
Spirit Energy, that's bad.
I was under the impression
that his level was equal to a
Captain's, and it needs to be.
Ichigo.
Hm?
I think you should run
in front of me now.
I'm going to try to restore your
Spirit Energy as best I can
while we're moving along.
On the run? While
we're in motion?
You're able to do that?
Yes, I am. When healing with
Kido, we start by restoring
one's inner Spirit Energy...
Then the restored internal
Spirit Energy is combined
with the healer's external
Spirit Energy,
which causes the whole
body to be repaired.
Ah.
As it turns out, restoring
missing Spirit Energy in a body
that has been healed is quite
easy. I've done it many times.
Now. Ichigo... To the front.
Okay.
If what I am sensing
is really only half of
his Spirit Energy...
Then if I restore him, There's
a very good chance he could be
the advantage we need!
The one with enough
power to end this battle!
I've got you!
I don't think so, maggot!
Urrghhh!
Yahh!
Go on, get away from me!
Bastard! That hurts!
Try this!
Raaauggh!
That was my leg,
you creep!
Ahh!
Last one!
Thank goodness!
I was getting so tired of
all this waiting around
that I almost fell asleep!
But it looks like
now I can begin
dissecting.
Prepare to
dissect, Nemu.
Yes, Master Mayuri.
Hmpf! He finally went down.
He was pretty tough.
Hey big guy, are you really done
now?
[kick]
Tch.
Hey! Byakuya Kuchiki!
Looks like this
guy's had it!
I'm going to let you
handle the rest.
I don't understand
what you mean by that.
What are you stupid?
I figure you must be bored
from standing around
watching all this.
So I'm letting you take
care of finishing him off.
You'll be the clean-up crew.
I see. You're telling me to
tidy up after you by taking
care of your unfinished
business, is that it?
Just who do you think you are?
S'cuse me?!
I don't like finishing off
those who are weaker than I am.
Stop complaining and just do it!
I refuse. Clean
up your own mess.
I think this type of
dirty work is more suited
to a brute like you.
Huh.
Is that so.
Ah!
Huh?
Hm?
Damn! Damn!
DAAAAAAMN!
[Ichigo]
Capt. Unohana, your healing
powers are amazing!
[Unohana]
Why, thank you so much.
[Ichigo]
Those skills must
come with age, right?
[Ichigo]
Captain?
[Unohana]
It's outrageous to
mention anything about
a woman's age, ever!
[Unohana]
I would appreciate it
if you would kindly
keep that in mind.
[Ichigo]
Yes, ma'am!