[theme music]
NARRATOR: Sosuke Aizen has
stolen the Hogyoku, an object
that can remove the barrier
between Soul Reapers
and Hollows.
He defected from
the Soul Society
and began raising a
powerful army of Arrancars
in Hueco Mundo.
Ichigo and his friends
managed to fight off
the first wave of Arrancars,
they suffered major damages.
Aizen's ultimate goal
is to kill the Reio, who
is the king of the Soul Society.
He will destroy Karakura Town to
harvest the spirit energy that
gravitates to the area.
The Arrancars plan
to mount their attack
on the world of the
living in the winter.
In anticipation of
the upcoming episode,
the Soul Reapers and their
friends undergo harsh training.
Ichigo, Chad, Uryu,
Rukia, and Orihime
are all preparing for
the final showdown
while Captain Histugaya's
advanced troops
in the world of
the living continue
to clash with
powerful Hollows, who
begin to appear more
frequently as the days go by.
[footsteps]
-Huh.
Ah.
Just as I expected.
It's here.
-What are you doing?
-Well, everyone.
Take care of the place
while we're gone.
-Be sure that you get
plenty of nutrition
by eating three meals a day.
And don't forget to brush
your teeth after each meal.
Do you promise?
-I promise, but why
are you taking Chad?
I thought you were
just going to stock up.
-To help Chas
unwind, that's all.
If he focuses
solely on training,
then the poor boy
is gonna burn out.
He needs to get some fresh
air once in awhile, right?
Tell them, Chad.
-I'd rather keep training, but
I appreciate your consideration.
-Fine.
Then hurry up and
bring him back, Kisuke.
There's still a lot of important
things I need to teach him.
-Renji.
You're just as short
tempered as usual.
I won'y miss that.
-Well, we should get going.
-See you soon.
-I'll be back.
-Bye.
-Leave the shop to us!
-Have a nice trip, everybody!
-Kisuke's really good
at this, isn't he?
-Good at what, Ririn?
-He says that his goal
is to help Chad unwind,
but he really plans on
making him carry things.
-Oh, really?
-Definitely.
-I see.
Well, the good news is
that, if Chad is with them,
he'll be able to carry back a
lot more than they usually do.
-Poor Chad.
-How much are they
planning on buying, anyway?
Nobody even comes in this store.
-Jinta.
-Did I hear you say
something disparaging
about our lack of
customers, Jinta?
-A lesson learned.
-Be careful of what you say.
-This is not a place
you should be entering
without Lord Aizen's
permission, Patros.
-I'll tell you something.
I've grown tired of
your suck up attitude.
-Regarding?
-Lord Aizen.
Always with Aizen,
and the Espada
are all following suit as well.
I don't get it.
It makes no sense.
It's an unpleasant feeling.
He's nothing but a Soul Reaper.
Why should powerful
Hollows have to take orders
from a Soul Reaper?
It makes absolutely
no sense whatsoever.
Hollows eat souls and
crush Soul Reapers.
why?
Tell me!
Tell me why our
freedom was taken away
for someone like him.
You know Aizen used
Hollows in his experiments?
-I know.
So what's your point?
-Ever since he appeared,
this place has changed.
I have no intention of
following a Soul Reaper.
-I see.
-Ulquiorra, why don't
we use Hogyoku ourselves
and control the world?
Doesn't that make more sense?
-Don't bother.
How can you control the
world when you can't even
become an Espada?
-So I don't have your support.
-Mm.
-Fine.
Then I've no choice.
Fortunately, I already
have two supporters.
-Patros.
You'll never get away with this.
-It's really too bad.
Without doubt, Be
Espada have fallen.
I never really
hated you, though.
-Heh.
Easy.
-Yeah.
Pretty pathetic
furnace for an Espada.
We're going to make Aizen
regret the day that he decided
to strengthen us with Hogyuko.
And then I will become king.
-Um.
-Hm?
-Could you please move?
-Oh, sorry.
I just don't know what
to do when I'm suddenly
given so much free time.
-Um, could you move again?
-OK.
-Jerk.
You gotta train for the
final battle, right?
Then go do it!
-I know what I'm
supposed to be doing
without you having to tell me.
-Um.
-Hm?
-Could you move?
-Uh, OK.
-You're completely useless
when you're not fighting.
You know that, don't you?
-What did you say?
-You wanna fight?
[growling]
-Ah.
The weather sure
is nice, isn't it?
-Yeah.
-But it's starting to get
boring without Ichigo.
It's so much fun teasing him.
-But last time you saw
him, all you did was yell.
-Is that what you call teasing?
-Of course it is.
He always reacts to it so
seriously, which makes it fun.
-I see.
-Well, I always thought
that the two of you
were having a lovers' quarrel.
-Of course not.
-But, honestly, it
would be nice of him
to show up here
every once in a while
-Oh my, you're really worried
about him, aren't you?
-Yes, I agree with Kurodo.
-It's not like that at all!
What's happening?
-Something's going on.
-What incredible
spiritual pressure.
RIN: We have a
confirmed Arrancar
presence in Karakura Town.
I repeat, we have a
confirmed Arrancar presence
in Karakura Town.
We have confirmed the Arrancars'
presence at coordinates 3, 8,
0, 0.
-We know.
I'm requesting a Gentei Keijo.
RIN: Don't worry.
We've already simplified
the procedures
to receive permission.
You should be granted
permission immediately.
-Understood.
Sure has gotten convenient.
Rangiku, Renji, Ikkaku,
Yumichika, acknowledge.
-Yes.
I have a confirmation, sir.
-Looks like things
will be fun again.
-I hope this one's
stronger than the last one.
-This is Renji.
I'm the furthest one away.
You guys just go on ahead of me.
-The Soul Reapers have
quickly sniffed us out,
and it looks like
they're on their way.
-What a letdown.
They all seem weak.
What should we do, Patros?
-I want you to handle
the Soul Reapers.
They don't seem very powerful.
But they mustn't interfere
with our investigation.
-Tell me, is it true there's a
Soul Reaper in this town that
actually knows how
to use the Hogyoku?
-That's what we've
come here to find out.
At this point, we've only
obtained the Hogyoku.
If we don't know how to use it,
then it's just a paperweight.
Someone from Los Noches will
come for us soon enough.
That's the real battle.
Act swiftly.
We'll rendezvous as soon
as the job is finished.
-What now, Captain?
-Keep a look out.
They're very close.
-Captain Hitsugaya, sir!
-Yes.
They're coming.
-Heh.
How cocky of them.
Well, they're going down.
Now stab, Erizo!
-The difference in
our power is obvious!
There's no need to
take you seriously.
Unfortunately, we
don't have time.
We need you to die here.
Freeze, Jaboli!
[humming]
-Yay!
Gee, ever since
Rukia and Orihime
went to the Soul
Society, things have
been so boring around
this dreary place.
I wonder if there's a paradise
level goddess anywhere?
Perhaps over there!
Wait.
There's something!
Who are you?
-No.
-Kon!
-I see.
So that's your releases
Zanpakuto, is it?
-That's right.
This is my true form!
I'll end this with one shot!
-Rain over the frosted
heavens, Hyorinmaru!
[laughter]
-It's useless!
-Ha ha ha ha ha!
This is my Zanpakuto release!
-Yumichika, this fight belongs
to me, so don't interfere.
-Yeah, I've heard that before.
When are you ever going
to let me fight again?
-Not today.
Extend, Hozukimaru!
-You're going to take
me on by yourself?
-You Arrancars.
As usual, you've got
some pretty thick skin!
Yah!
-Is that-- Hey, Kon.
What happened to you?
-Oh.
Renji.
-Tell me what happened.
-Some guy with incredible
spiritual pressure.
-It's an Arrancar.
Did you see which way he went?
-That way.
-Could it be that--
-Stop there!
This is no place for someone
of your kind, Arrancar!
-Yeah.
-We're gonna mess you up if
you don't stop right there!
You heard me.
Stop now!
-What do we do?
-He's dangerous.
It's going to be impossible
to take him on like this.
-I agree.
-Retreat!
-Hey, wait up!
-I understand
someone in this place
knows how to use the Hogyoku.
I'd like to meet him.
RENJI: He's not here.
-So, there are others here.
Who are you?
Squad Six Lieutenant
Renji Abarai
of the 13th Court Guard Squad.
-And where is the person who
knows how to use the Hogyoku?
-I told you that he's not here.
-Well, in that case I'll
just wait until he returns.
-I'm afraid I can't
let you do that.
No customers allowed in the
shop while the owner's away.
-Oh, but I'm not a customer.
En garde, Soul Reaper.
-Roar, Zabimaru!
-What are you doing, moocher?
-It's on!
-Ururu!
Get inside!
-They won't be any
safer hiding in there.
You see, if we fight here,
that shack will certainly
be crushed to pieces.
-You think so?
Because the store owner's
a pretty good carpenter.
I don't think it'll be
that easy to knock down.
Besides, there won't be
anything to worry about about
if I end all this
before that happens.
-Perhaps we should
test that theory.
-What should we do, Jinta?
-What should we do?
We've gotta fight,
that's what we should do.
Ururu, you stay down here.
-But--
-Huh?
-Hello.
[laughter]
-Hey.
-We're going out first.
We've got to assist Renji.
-Well, as moochers,
we believe that it
is our duty not
to hide like this.
-Good luck.
[shout]
-Roar, Zabimaru!
-Too slow!
-Ho, ho!
So you have a little
skill after all.
-More than just a little.
-Very well.
I wasn't going to unsheathe
my sword for the likes of you,
but you leave me no choice.
I
-Hope I don't disappoint you.
Come on.
-Ha.
-Ah!
[cough]
-How weak.
My sword skill is
comprised of 20 levels.
That was the very lowest
I have, level one.
It was a gesture of respect.
But you're outmatched
if you can't even
keep up with that level.
-Bastard.
Don't get excited.
I just let my guard down.
-Nonsense.
If that's the case,
then try handling this.
Ha.
Pathetic.
Huh?
-Things won't go
that easily for you.
-Oh, really?
Who are you?
-We're also keeping
an eye on the store
while the owner is away.
-You'll pay if you
don't leave right away.
And that's not just a threat.
-No, don't.
Stop taunting him.
-Be quiet.
-It is the job of
a moocher to defend
the household during
times like this.
-It's all right.
We won't do anything rash.
-OK.
But I warned you.
-Here we go!
-Ah!
What is this?
-What are you lookin' at?
-What?
-We forced him into the barrier!
Now, Kurodo!
-All right!
The Renji twins attack team!
-This is creepy.
-It's like looking in a mirror!
Roar, Zabimaru!
-You should give it up!
-I've got you!
Huh?
-You may look like
your counterpart,
but your spiritual
pressure's weak.
-Ah!
-Kurodo!
-Think you're pretty smart, huh?
Trying to trick me.
Take this!
How impertinent!
How long will you last?
It's over.
-I don't think so.
-Apparently you didn't
understand what I said.
So let's up the ante.
Level two.
Not bad.
But it's still
just the beginning.
[theme music]
KURODO: We've had quite
a lot of scenes today.
Could it be that when the
spotlight returns to us,
they're going to kill us off?
NOBA: Kurudo, don't
say such things.
RIRIN: What an
ominous thing to say.
We are forever immortal!
NOBA: That's doubtful.