[music playing]
[music - kelun, "chu-bura"]
NARRATOR: As the only surviving
heir of the noble Kasumioji
clan, Princess Rurichiyo had
become a target for trouble
in her homeland.
For her own protection,
her guardians
took the unsuspecting princess
to the world of the living,
where Ichigo reluctantly
agreed to become her bodyguard.
Rurichiyo quickly turned
Ichigo's world upside down
with her spoiled behavior.
Kenryu and Enryu continued
to keep the truth away
from Rurichiyo for
her own peace of mind.
But one day, after an argument,
she ran away from them
and was attacked by an
assassin on the streets.
Orihime happened to be nearby
and tried to fight him off
but found herself in peril
because of the assassin's
bizarre Zanpakuto.
Fortunately, Ichigo arrived
and defeated the assassin
before he could harm anyone.
KENRYU: (SHOUTING)
Ichigo Kurasaki!
--[sleepy sigh] What do
you want this early?
[glass crackling]
-Huh?
[glass shatters]
-You broke my window!
-That's not important!
Because Lady Rurichiyo
has disappeared again!
-What the?
-What is it?
-Huh.
No one here.
-Must be a malfunction.
[giggles]
[gasp]
-Good morning, Princess.
-Kumoi, you scared me.
VASSAL: Look, over there!
There she is.
It's Her Highness!
VASSAL: It's her!
Finally.
Oh my.
Oh, Princess.
VASSAL: Oh, are you all right?
-I'm relieved to see
you safe, Your Highness.
-Are you hurt?
Are you hurt, Your Highness?
GYOKAKU KUKOI: Princess.
-Ah?
-You ran off without telling
me where you were going.
Where have you
been all this time?
-I did not need your permission.
I was properly accompanied
by Kenryu and Enryu.
GYOKAKU KUKOI:
Nevertheless, Princess,
if something were
to happen to you,
you would not be
the only one shamed.
It would also shame
your late parents.
Your behavior has consequences.
Think about the disgrace
you could easily
bring down on the
Kasumioji clan.
-[indignant gasp] I'm aware.
I need no reminding.
-If you truly understand
that, then you
must behave as a princess of the
Kasumioji family would behave.
It's expected of you.
[pbbbt]
-Huh?
Go.
Prepare my sedan chair.
There is someone I must visit.
-I see.
Just where might you be going?
-To a party!
-You're ready to work, Hanza?
-Yes, Lord Kumoi.
-For some unknown
reason, she has
returned from the
world of the living.
Kenryu and Enryu
aren't with her.
This is a perfect opportunity.
-Understood.
-Not again.
-Be ready this time.
-What the hell?
Nice welcome.
-Stop this at once!
Stand down!
GUARDS: Yes, sir.
-Must I instruct
you on protocol?
Only the princess
and her guardians
are permitted to
use this entrance.
-Yes, we know, Sir Kenryu.
But the gate flew open
earlier this afternoon,
and yet no one came through it.
-Apparently she made
it back after all.
-Sorry, everyone.
We can't go to the Soul
Society through that gate.
I was told that
it was forbidden.
-On top of which,
there's always a chance
that Miss Kasumioji will
return before you do.
We'll maintain a tight watch on
this side in case that happens.
-Thank you.
We'll be counting on
you to stay alert.
-Time to get moving.
Better hurry.
These gatekeepers don't
seem to be all that bright.
I'm sure she slipped right by
them and entered the palace.
-Right.
You guys hide her in
the world of living
and then the very
first chance she gets,
the princess undermines
all your hard work
by going right back home.
I guess that's what
happens when you become
glorified nannies to
some spoiled brat.
Yaah!
What?
Why'd you do that?
Say something!
-He's saying that someone of a
lower class, such as yourself,
should not be
criticizing the princess.
Am I right?
-That doesn't change the fact
that she's a spoiled brat.
I just hope this guy
Kumoi who's trying
to harm her doesn't
find her before we do.
Hm!
I'm staying away from you.
[whap]
-Oof!
What's wrong with you two?
Are you nuts?
-You deserved that for
saying the enemy's name
in the open where
anyone could hear it.
-Come on, her life's
in danger, and yet she
runs home like it's
perfectly safe.
-Yes, but Lady
Rurichiyo's still young.
She may not understand
the situation.
That'll make our job harder.
[annoyed sigh]
RUKIA KUCHIKI: We'd better
split up and search.
KENRYU: We'll start by
checking in this area.
-Damn it.
This palace is big.
She could be hiding
anywhere in this place.
That brat's a lot of trouble.
MALE SPEAKER: Hey.
What's the big hurry?
-Long time no see. [giggles]
RUKIA KUCHIKI: Captain Zaraki
and Lieutenant Kusajishi.
-Quite a surprise.
What are you doing here?
-Yeah, that's right.
Why aren't you in the
world of the living?
-Uh, well, um--
-Is Ichigo here as well?
-Uh-- um--
[inhales deeply]
-Hm.
[tinkling]
-He is here.
-Yep.
I sense him too.
-And he's pretty worked
up about something.
-You're right.
He must be on a mission.
-No, actually.
That is-- well, uh--
-He comes all the way out here
and doesn't even say hi to me?
Now that's just rude.
-Uh--
-I'm gonna go find
him and see what's up.
-Uh, uh-- but wait, Captain
Zaraki-- (VOICEOVER)
Oh, this isn't good.
This whole situation
with Lady Rurichiyo
was supposed to be kept secret.
Things could get out of hand
if Captain Zaraki finds Ichigo.
-It doesn't look like
the princess is anywhere
in the palace.
What?
Did you see something, Enryu?
Huh?
Wait a minute!
This veil belongs
to the princess!
[hinges squeaking]
[thud]
KENRYU: Did that door
just close by itself?
Enryu, where are you?
It's so dark here.
I can't see a thing.
Ow!
-Now that I have the
both of you locked away,
I can dispose of the princess.
-Princess, we've arrived
at the residence.
-Hm.
-Princess Rurichiyo is
here and awaits her host.
-I am honored and
truly grateful to have
been invited to
your party today.
-I thank you with all
my heart for gracing us
with your presence.
-You may keep the sedan
chair here for me.
-Yes, my lady.
-There she is.
Why, that little--
-You are dismissed.
We will call when we are ready.
ATTENDANTS: Yes, ma'am.
[giggles]
-Hm?
-[laughs] Rurichiyo!
-How are you, Sacchi?
BOTH: I missed you.
[giggles]
-It's been so long.
-Everyone's here.
They've all been
waiting for you.
It seems like we haven't
seen you for ages.
-That's true.
[laughter]
-Look, everyone.
Rurichi's finally here.
GIRL: Oh, it's been so long!
Oh, Rurichi, so good to see you!
-Oh, it is.
It's fabulous.
-How've you been?
-I'm well.
What about you?
Is everyone doing OK?
-Hey, Rurichi?
[giggles]
-Right!
[both laugh]
-You remembered!
That makes me so happy.
-How could I forget
something so important?
It's a sign of our lifelong
friendship, Sayori.
[laughter]
KENRYU: Almost there.
Can you get me up
any higher, Enryu?
I can just about
reach the latch.
A couple more inches
ought to do it.
We can't let Kumoi
get away with this.
I did it!
We've got a way out!
Oh-- ohhh!
[thud]
-Hold on, Princess.
We'll save you.
-I wonder what she's
doing in there.
GUARD: Don't come any closer.
-Wait a minute, guys.
I saw Rurichiyo go inside.
I need to speak to her.
I'm a Substitute Soul
Reaper, Ichigo Kurosaki.
-Substitute Soul Reaper?
-How dare you speak
the Princess's name
in such an informal manner?
-You're a suspicious character.
-Wait!
Cool it!
I'm not a threat to anyone.
Kenryu asked me to come here
as his personal representative.
-You dare speak Sir
Kenryu's name as well?
-I've never even heard of a
Substitute Soul Reaper before.
[shoom]
-He vanished!
-Where did he go?
[shoom]
-Nobody respects a
Substitute Soul Reaper.
GUARD: There he
is, up on the roof!
-Oh, great.
[shoom]
[girls chatting and giggling]
SAYORI: Rurichi?
-Huh?
-These are the first tea
leaves of the season.
-Oh, thank you.
Mmm.
[spits]
-That was gross.
What'd you do that for?
-You surprised-- Ichigo,
what are you doing here?
-I should be asking
you the same thing.
You're putting yourself
and all of us in danger.
Come on, we're going back, now.
Everyone's waiting for you.
-I will not go.
You should not have
followed me here.
I am attending an important
tea party right now.
-Rurichiyo, you're
behaving like a brat.
-There he is!
I knew he couldn't get very far.
-Don't let him away.
-Oh, boy, here we go again.
-Just what is going on?
-I beg your pardon, milady.
We have received a report
from your guardians
that a thief had
managed to get by them.
-Ah?
-What?
Wait, this is wrong.
I'm not a thief.
I'm a friend of the princess.
Rurichiyo?
--[scoffs] I do
not know this man.
Never seen him before.
SAYORI: Rurichi, wait!
-What?
Rurichiyo?
Whoa, whoa!
[shoom]
-Oh no, he's gone.
-Where did he go?
-Well, look around.
He's got to be here somewhere.
-He can't have disappeared.
-[sighs] How very rude.
No one asked him to
show up like that.
I come back here to
enjoy myself and now he
has taken all the
fun out of the party.
[girl sobbing]
-Huh?
[girl weeping]
-What's wrong, little girl?
Are you the child of
one of the servants?
Did you get into trouble
with your mother?
Now there, don't cry.
Huh?
What's over there?
What do you want to show me?
Hm.
Huh?
Where are we?
Is this where you play?
[mean laugh]
-Hm!
[gasp]
[scream]
[laughs quietly]
-Oh!
Ahhh!
[panting]
[cries out]
[laughs quietly]
[frightened gasp]
GIRL: Goodbye, Princess.
[whimpering] Mm-- huh?
Ichigo!
-Rurichiyo, are you all right?
-Mm-hm.
ICHIGO KUROSAKI: Who
the hell is this kid?
[grunting with effort]
-Huh?
GUARD: There, look!
The princess is in danger.
GUARD: He's got a sword!
GUARD: Stand fast.
Quick!
-This creep really is a monster.
He's threatening a little girl
at the point of his sword!
-There's no point in running--
-Hey!
I wasn't-- it's-- it's not--
GUARD: Stay where you are.
You don't move.
-Hold on!
It's a mistake!
[guards shouting]
-Stop, guys!
-Lady Rurichiyo, are you hurt?
-[whimpers]
Ichigo!
-Yaaahh!
-Aaaahhh!
-Unnh!
Hyaah!
GUARD: She's a fighting machine!
ALL: Huh?
-Ahhhhah!
[boom]
ICHIGO KUROSAKI: Kenpachi!
-I've been looking for you.
I figured you were
here somewhere.
-I told Kenny we'd find you!
-It's Captain
Zaraki of Squad 11!
-[grunting with effort]
[wet slurping]
-Huh?
-Nnnnnnnh!
-Captain, we need to-- huh?
Ichigo, what are you doing?
[grunts]
Now, Lady Rurichiyo,
please-- get in.
-I ask of you, please don't
be angry with Rurichi.
-Mmph.
-You see, she came to my
party because very soon, I'm
going to be married.
-Congratulations.
That's great.
-It is awful!
This is an arranged marriage.
She is being forced
to marry someone
she's never met and doesn't
even know if she likes!
It's horrible!
The whole thing was
set up and agreed
to by the heads of both
noble families right
after Sacchi was born.
-Don't be upset about it.
It's the way life is sometimes.
I accept it as my fate.
This was going to be
my very last tea party.
Rurichi knew that when
I sent the invitation,
so she did everything she
possibly could to attend.
Because the way
things work out, we
may never be able to
see each other again.
-You're marrying into an
extremely strict family,
aren't you?
-Mm-hm.
Oh, how strange.
Why am I crying?
I've accepted it.
It's not like I'm sad. [crying]
-Sacchi!
-It's tough being a noble.
They don't have much freedom.
-Without a doubt.
Their lives are quite
different than yours
in the world of the living.
Captains Zaraki,
I didn't tell you,
but we're working on
a top secret mission.
Because of that, I'm
asking that you please not
mention today's
events to anyone else.
-I don't know why
all that happened.
And in the second
place, I don't have time
to think about stuff I didn't
understand in the first place.
--[giggles] And in the third
place, he's not smart enough,
right?
-Uh.
Thank you for your discussion.
-Today was
interesting, at least.
Bring Ichigo back sometime so
I can smack him around a bit.
-[giggles] That's funny!
-Yeah, sounds like fun.
-Next time, kid.
-Ah, what a charmer.
-We'd better be heading back.
-Yeah.
[gasp]
RUKIA KUCHIKI: What
are you looking at?
-Nothing.
HANZA: [quiet laugh]
He didn't even
tremble when he felt
my spiritual pressure.
Impressive.
This is going to be interesting.
[music - lil' b, "orange"]
ICHIGO KUROSAKI (VOICEOVER):
I'm kinda worried.
Do you really think Kenpachi
will keep everything a secret?
YACHIRU KUSAJISHI
(VOICEOVER): Sure he will.
Kenny always says reports
are too much of a bother,
so he never does them.
ICHIGO KUROSAKI
(VOICEOVER): What?
Then who's been preparing
all Squad 11's reports?
YACHIRU KUSAJISHI
(VOICEOVER): I don't know.
ICHIGO KUROSAKI (VOICEOVER):
That can't be good!