I say
It's neither just nor virtuous
to live in peace and let the
dead go unavenged!
It is evil!!
Stop now! Kaname!
Is this how far you've fallen,
bastard?!
Shuhei, no!!
Nngh!
What...is this power?!
Bankai!
Kokujo Tengen Myoh!
[Sajin]
Kaname!
I swear, I will do
whatever it takes,
to open your eyes
to the truth!
How foolish of you.
You've seen my power, and yet
you still think you can defeat
me with the likes of a Bankai?
"The likes of a Bankai."
Now, that sounds like
something an Espada would say.
Don't compare me
to the Espadas.
I have surpassed
all of them.
And you Soul
Reapers as well.
Have you forgotten your
days as a Soul Reaper?
Soul Reaper?
Becoming a Soul Reaper...
that was never really
what I was after.
Mmm.
[Sajin]
Kaname... When was it that you
chose this path to follow?
[Kaname]
I- I beg your pardon...
I didn't think anyone was here.
Over here...
Eh?!
That's odd...
My apologies.
I wasn't able to
sense you over there.
Eh?
I'm Kaname Tosen.
Pleased to meet you.
I have to say,
you're extremely
good at masking
your presence.
Especially since
you're so big.
You can see, I'm blind,
but there was never a
time I couldn't sense
the presence of another.
Sorry. Force of habit.
Sajin Komamura?
It's been quite a
while, hasn't it?
I see. You've joined the
Thirteen Court Guard Squads...
Have you ever considered
becoming a member of my
squad, Sajin?
I have a wonderful superior,
I'm sure you'd like him.
You're Sajin Komamura?
Kaname's spoken of you.
Hmmm?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Sosuke Aizen,
lieutenant of squad five.
[Kaname]
I'm curious, Why did you
choose to become a soul reaper?
[Sajin]
To repay a debt
of gratitude...
to the one who
saved my life.
Repaying a debt.
That sounds like you.
And what about
you, Kaname?
Me? Well...
[sigh]
All right, let us begin!
You finally drew
your sword.
You like to take your time,
don't you?
Scared?
It's no use trying
to ignore me.
No matter how strong you are,
I know you have your doubts.
You said so yourself,
a hundred years ago.
I never opened up to you.
I never let you get close enough
to learn anything about me.
That's why, even
after all this time,
you don't know what my
Zanpakuto's power is.
You think
that matters?
Do you really think I
need to understand its
power before I can act?
Who knows?
But I understand yours.
I know that your Zanpakuto
tries to gain control of
your opponents by working
on their nerves.
You think that puts me
at a disadvantage?
Not necessarily.
But I'll tell you this.
If you think your Kyokasuigetsu
is the only Zanpakuto with the
capability of controling an
opponent's nerves,
you're sadly
mistaken, Sosuke.
Now Collapse.
[Shinji]
Sakanade.
Yahhh!
Have you forgotten?
I know your
abilities too well.
I can anticipate
your every attack.
Rrraagh!
Well, I never said
your destructive power
wasn't impressive.
He's taken hardly any damage...
He stopped it with his
Zanpakuto.
Well, then. You said I
couldn't defeat you with the
likes of a Bankai, right?
Yes. That's right.
What about Tengen Myo-oh?
Compared to its power,
yours is like an infant's
next to an adult's.
Give this up while
you still can.
My power,
like an infant's,
you say?
You have grown so arrogant,
it's almost pitiful.
Very well, Sajin.
It's time that arrogance of
yours was cut down to size.
Where did he
get that speed?
I'm over here.
Agh!
Myo-oh!!
You and that thing
are linked together.
Every move you make,
the giant makes.
And any wound I inflict on it,
is inflicted on you as well.
A very inconvenient
Bankai, Sajin.
I'm familiar with it
from seeing it in
action several times,
so it's easy for me to
target its weaknesses.
You've always relied
on its overwhelmingly
destructive power,
never imagining that
any opponent could
survive the first blow,
let alone counterattack.
I don't even need to
target your vital spots.
If I just inflict enough damage
on your limbs, eventually
you'll become immobile.
The same thing is true
for you as well.
You think so? Hah.
Hah ha ha ha ha!
Don't try to put me on
the same level as you.
Instant Regeneration!
[Sajin]
So that's it, then.
You've really given up being a
Soul Reaper, Haven't you?
Given our current situation,
you sound like a sore loser.
As I recall, you said
that I was depraved.
That deceiving my friends
and subordinates was a
sign of my depravity.
But I ask you this...
If someone joined
an organization
solely for revenge,
and then abandoned his purpose
in order to live peacefully
within that organization,
wouldn't that be
depraved as well?
To my unseeing eyes, you
appear to be dealing with a
much greater moral issue.
You mean that? You became
a Soul Reaper for no
other purpose than...?
Yes. Revenge.
[Woman]
I love watching the
night sky, Kaname.
I see the world in it. There's
so much darkness, and yet, in
that darkness, so many, many
shining points of light.
Clouds come along and try to
smother the lights. Do you
understand what I mean, Kaname?
I wish I could gather all the
clouds so they would never
again obscure the light that
shines from the stars.
[Woman]
I'm getting married, Kaname!
What's more, I received
my acceptance from the
Academy yesterday.
I'm going to become a
Soul Reaper, Kaname!
and I will let
justice shine.
I wanted you to hear
it from me, Kaname.
Congratulations. Of course
you know that if there's
anything I can do to help,
you have only to ask.
Thank you. But all I want
you to do is to stay
just as you are.
I want you to be here
to listen to my stories
when I come back.
[Kaname]
She said it was a promise.
And I could tell she was
smiling when she said it.
[Kaname]
Those were the last
words I heard her say.
She never came back.
It was her own husband
who murdered her.
He had killed a
colleague over some
petty disagreement.
When she reproached him for it,
he killed her too.
There was no one who desired
peace more than she did,
no one with a stronger
sense of justice.
It's why she had
chosen to fight...
But she wasn't even
given the chance to do that.
What was she lacking?
Is believing in
justice and peace not
enough to attain them?
In that case,
I want power.
I want the power
to impose peace.
If wanting justice is
not enough, I will
become justice itself.
And then, I will sweep
away the evil of the
world like clouds.
I will put my sense of
justice to the test.
For revenge? Really?
That's right.
You seem surprised, Sajin.
You've taken your sight
for granted and become
blind to the truth.
Those eyes of yours will never
see the truth that I can see.
Too slow!
Ngh!
Augh!
Ngyauughh!
What's wrong, Sajin?
Have you lost the
will to fight back?
Yaahhh!!
Here's a question for you.
It's something I've been meaning
to ask. Didn't you ever wonder?
Didn't you think it strange
that someone would join the
very same organization that
had killed his dearest friend?
... You never
wondered about that?
I thought you were in
pursuit of justice.
I assumed you were following in
the path of your fallen friend,
trying to find the
justice that eluded her.
You're right.
It was for justice!
Well, then?!
But what is justice?!
Is it to forgive the man who
killed my beloved friend?!
That would certainly
be virtuous.
Admirable.
Sickeningly so,
in fact.
But even if a thing is
virtuous, does that
make it just? No!
I say...
...it's neither just nor
virtuous to live in peace and
let the dead go unavenged!
It is evil!!
Now I understand.
It would seem that I
completely misjudged your
feelings all this time.
If that's what you truly
believe, Kaname, then you and
I will never see eye to eye.
And because of that
you would kill me?
Is that justice?
How absurd.
Yes, it is justice.
Our beliefs are
incompatible and it's
fruitless trying to
reason with you.
Therefore I must destroy
you, for the sake of the
Soul Society.
I don't want to kill you,
But I'm glad I've learned
your true feelings.
It makes it easier
to forgive myself.
I've already forgiven you.
You've forgiven me?
Really.
You talk as if you
were a god, Sajin.
When did I ever ask
for your forgiveness?!
If you want to kill me,
then do it!
But I'm warning you...
...you won't think it's such an
easy task once you have
witnessed my Resurreccíon!!
Eh?
Suzumushi Hyakushiki.
Grillado Grillo!
At last, I can see...
I can see..!!
Heh.
Yeea-ha ha ha ha ha!
I can see, Sajin!
I can see, I can see!
So that is the sky!
So this is blood!
So this is what the
world looks like!
And so that is what
you look like, Sajin.
You're not how I imagined.
You're much, much uglier.
[Kaname]
All people are evil, every
living one of them.
Most don't
want to admit it.
So in order to make themselves
believe they're good,
they need to convince
themselves that someone
else is more evil.