[theme music]
NARRATOR: Rurichiyo Kasumioji
arrived from the Soul Society
and transferred
into Ichigo's class.
Soon afterwards,
she was targeted
by a mysterious assailant.
Ichigo attempted to
identify the enemy,
but the assassin took his own
life before he could do so.
It turned out
Rurichiyo was actually
princess of the Kasumioji Clan.
When her life was
perceived to be in danger,
her guardians took her to
the world of the living,
and now Ichigo has
been forced to accept
the task of serving
as her bodyguard.
-Oh, wasn't that
another fun-filled day?
-Indeed, Lady Rurichiyo.
-It's too bad I can't
say the same thing.
Ichigo Kurosaki, when
addressing the princess,
I find you have a rather
poor choice of words.
You should watch your mouth.
-Yeah, right.
Way I see it,
she's the one who--
hey, what's the deal, guy?
Come on, out of my way!
Quit it!
Why is he in my face?
-Because we didn't
care for your response.
-Fine, all right.
I get it, already.
I swear, yesterday you
guys were basically
on your hands and knees, and
now this is the thanks I get?
-What you're talking about?
Did Kenryu and Enryu ask you
to assist them with something?
-Uh--
-There's just one other thing.
Lady Rurichiyo has no
idea she's being targeted,
and we'd like to
keep it that way.
Ir would traumatize
her, and she's
been through enough already.
-No, they, uh, just wanted some
tips on relating to humans.
Right?
-Huh?
-Uh, right.
Last night, Ichigo Kurosaki was
teaching us some social customs
from the world of the living.
Yes.
Uh, my Lady?
-Oh!
Ichigo, what is
this strange thing?
-Hmm.
My Lady, this device is
called a vending machine.
-What purpose does it serve?
-Huh?
Uh, well, uh--
-Here.
-Huh?
-Go on, try it.
-But my Lady--
-I will be fine.
Such a flavor!
Tastes just like an orange!
-A vending machine's a machine
that sells different snacks.
-Amazing!
Wow, Ichigo.
This world is brimming
with fascinating items
about this I know nothing.
You will not hesitate to teach
me more about this place.
-You kidding me?
That's how you ask
someone for a favor?
[snap]
-I mean, OK!
I'll teach, uh, Rurichiyo
a little bit at a time.
-Address her as Lady Rurichiyo.
-A little close--
-It's fine, Kenryu.
I have a huge heart,
therefore I shall
forgive Ichigo's indiscretion.
-How magnanimous,
Lady Rurichiyo.
I, lowly Kenryu, am
in awe of your grace.
-No need to overreact, Kenryu.
-Lady Rurichiyo.
-Huh?
-How would you like to check
out a few more fascinating items
from this world?
-Where are they kept?
-I think you're
going to enjoy this.
[music playing]
-Here you go.
-Oooh!
You were so skilled at that.
-Lady Rurichiyo, what do you say
we go check try that one next?
-Oooh!
-Our princess,
she's so delighted.
Thank goodness we brought
her to this world.
-He's crying?
Let me guess.
I bet you haven't figured out
what you're going to do yet.
-Hmm!
There's no need for you to
rudely point out the obvious.
ICHIGO: Well, you might want
to come up with a plan soon.
We don't know when those weirdos
are going to come around again.
-Miss Kuchiki, I've never
visited such a wonderful place
in my life.
-I'm glad to hear that.
-OK, then, it's about
time to take you home.
-It's all right, I can
get home by myself.
-Yeah, but--
-If you ask me, those two
worry about me far too much.
Hurrying ahead to
inspect the house
before allowing me inside?
Those two are stifling.
-That's kind of their thing.
-Oh, Ichigo.
-What's up, Yuzo?
Yep, I'm home.
-It's kind of on the late
side, but welcome back.
Oh, is this the girl
who moved in next door?
-I am Rurichiyo Kasumioji.
-Hello, I'm Yuzo Kurosaki.
So you're really
high school student?
You look like--
-Sorry, what is a high school?
-Uhhh-- let's get
going, Rurichiyo.
-Wait, Ichigo.
Since we're
neighbors, wouldn't it
be polite to invite
her over for dinner?
-Uh--
-This is delicious!
-You think?
-Yes, it's truly scrumptious.
The World of the Living
has some wonderful cuisine.
-World of the--
-Ahem!
That's Yuzu for you.
Her cooking is always to notch.
-Aristocratic dinners can
be so formal and stuffy.
Isn't that right, Miss Kuchiki?
-Aristocratic?
-You know what?
Don't worry about it, Yuzu.
-But--
-She's just a little different.
Rurichiyo, what's wrong?
-I do not eat these.
-Oh, you don't like carrots?
I'm sorry.
-Now you listen up.
Farmers are out there working
very hard in the fields
to grow all these vesicles
vegetables, so eat everything
on your plate.
-Farmers grow all
of these things?
-You bet.
Just growing one of these
veggies takes a lot of labor.
-And if you eat them in some
curry, they taste amazing.
-Mmm.
-It's not a big deal, really.
-Yuzu, don't encourage her.
KENRYU: Halt!
-Hey, who the heck
are you people?
-Pardon our late intrusion.
-Not cool, you guys.
-Ichigo Kurosaki,
how dare you compel
Lady Rurichiyo to
consume lowly carrots.
-What?
-I can't even recall
how many servants
have been severely
punished for serving
her carrots in the past.
I suppose in this case
you weren't aware,
and for a number of
the Kurosaki family,
we will make an
exception just this once.
-Huh?
Who, me?
-Now, listen.
It's you two sheltering
her like this all the time
that makes her totally
ignorant of reality.
-I warn you, this is
none of your concern.
Now keep quiet.
-Ichigo!
-You beg me to babysit for you,
and that's how you talk to me?
-Babysit?
What's this about, Kenryu?
Answer me!
-Uh, I-- well, um-- uh,
with a Lady as noble
as yourself, we just thought
maybe we were short staffed?
-Hold on.
Have you been hiding
something from me?
-Ahh!
Umm-- no, it's just--
-Kenryu, Enryu, why won't you
ever tell me the whole truth
about anything?
-Uh, my Lady, I--
-If mother and father
were still here,
I know they would have told me
about farmers and food and all
the rest.
All this time, I
never gave any thought
to how our meals were
grown and prepared.
But I am not a full, either.
What Ichigo said before,
he speaks the truth.
-But my Lady, I--
-That's enough.
I am tired of you two always
trying to keep me in the dark.
I cannot trust you!
I hate the both of you!
-Rurichiyo.
-Yuzu!
-She hates us.
The princess
genuinely despises us.
-Man, what a couple of idiots.
-Oh, so you think this is none
of your business, huh, Ichigo?
You're at least half
responsible for this.
-Yeah, all right.
Pull yourself together.
This is my fault, too.
We can all apologize together.
YUZU: Ichigo!
-Yuzu, Karin!
-Rurichiyo disappeared.
She just stormed off!
-Hey!
[music playing]
-Come on, she's right here.
-That's just her Gigai.
-Lady Rurichiyo!
Where are you?
Answer me!
-Looks like she changed
back into a soul form.
This is not good.
If she got attacked
by another assassin--
-Whatever the case, we should
split up and search for her.
-Right.
[music playing]
-That fool, Kenryu!
And Enryu, too.
[sobbing]
ORIHIME: Rurichiyo?
-Huh?
-Is is you, Rurichiyo.
What are you doing
all the way out here?
-Wait a moment.
Aren't you-- oh, yes!
Orihime.
-Yep, that's me.
I'm Orihime.
Orihime Inoue.
-How could I forget?
Your name, Hime,
implies you too are
a princess from a noble family.
--[laughing] Hime is
just part of my name.
-So you are a Hime but
you're not a princess?
The World of the
Living is strange.
-[laughing]
Hey, Rurichiyo.
-Huh?
-Why are you all alone?
Where's Mr. Kenryu
and Mr. Enryu?
-I'm not sure whom
you're speaking of.
-Did something happen?
-It is true that I never
ate carrots before,
but-- well, I could
eat them if I wished.
It seems as though
the two of them
have always kept the
world away from me.
-Mr. Kenru and Mr. Enryu
care deeply for you,
don't they, Rurichiyo?
-Huh?
-You're important to them.
That's why they didn't want
you to worry about anything.
-That is not it.
-Huh?
Kenryu and Enryu,
they treat me like
they think I'm still a child.
-Listen, Rurichiyo.
When people constantly
shower you with affection,
eventually you start
taking it for granted.
But if you don't realize
it until they're gone,
you'll end up with
a lot of regret.
-Orihime--
-See?
Try to look at it from
their perspective.
-I suppose I did say some
pretty horrible things to them.
I cannot trust you!
I hate the both of you!
Do you think
they'll ever find it
in their hearts to forgive me?
-I'm sure they will.
Now, we should get you home.
-Right.
Ahh!
My veil!
-Look out!
-What do you think
you are doing?
Are you aware that
you are threatening
Rurichiyo Kasumioji?
Orihime!
-I'm all right.
[music playing]
[screams]
-What-- what just happened?
-Come on!
[music playing]
-He's trapped us!
-This is bad!
RURICHIYO: Why--
why is he after me?
Why is he doing this to us?
-Santen Kesshun!
Ahh!
-Is this because I snuck off
to the World of the Living?
Or am I just being punished
for causing my closest
caretakers all this heartache?
-No, Rurichiyo, you haven't
done anything wrong.
-Then why is he-- ahh!
-I-- I can't hold him back!
-I don't like this!
I don't like this at all!
Kenryu!
Enryu!
-At your service.
-Kenryu and Enryu!
-My Lady, speak to me.
Are you all right?
-Kenryu!
You came when I called.
And Enryu, too!
Please forgive me.
I was wrong before.
-Rurichiyo!
-Ichigo!
Rukia!
-You're late, Ichigo.
-What happened?
-Up there!
RUKIA: Is he--
ICHIGO: Yeah, looks
like another assassin.
-Be on your guard.
-Right!
[music playing]
-Be carefully, Ichigo.
He might use another one of
those strange techniques.
-Got it!
-What?
Hey, Rukia!
What's going on?
-It's some technique that
converts a blade attack
into walls.
It's stuck!
-Damn!
Heads up!
Rurichiyo!
-Oh, no!
Ichigo isn't here!
Huh?
-Leave this enemy
to me, my Lady.
-Kenryu!
-Bloom in glory.
Benishidare!
-Oh, that's pretty!
-What is that!
Some kind of joke?
-No joke.
Observe.
KENRYU: My Benishidare's pollen
will sprout flower blossoms
on any weapon it
touches, rendering
them completely useless.
-You couldn't come up with
anything a little more badass?
-So cool!
-Are we looking
at the same thing?
-You have an opening.
Do it, Ichigo!
-Good point.
Getsuga Tensho!
-Sokatsui!
-Wait, don't--
-All right, you masked
pain in the ass.
Let's find out who
ordered you to do this.
Wait!
How the hell did he
capture you people?
What about your flower power?
-Yeah, well, you just blew
away all of the pollen!
My Benishidare only
works when there's
a large cloud of pollen
surrounding the enemy.
-That's unfortunate.
-However, there is a plan B.
-Wow!
-All right, I blinded him.
-Let's go!
You take it from here!
-Did, uh, that
really just happen?
ICHIGO: You're
doing it all wrong.
Here, let me show you what
a real attack looks like!
Getsugaaaa!
Tenshooo!
-End of the line.
OK, start talking.
On whose orders were you sent
here to kill Lady Rurichiyo?
-Huh.
-What?
-Rukia!
[music playing]
-Damn, we lost another one.
-Guess this is just
how they operate.
-It looks to be over my Lady.
-Now that's our
substitute Soul Reaper.
But still, who was
that horrible attacker?
-Probably just a common thief.
Lady Rurichiyo, you have
nothing to worry about.
-What did I say?
Stop treating me like
a baby and-- huh?
[music playing]
-Oh--
-Rurichiyo!
-Sir Kenryu, are you all right?
-Yes, I'll be fine.
Ichigo Kurosaki, you
did surprisingly well.
I give you my thanks.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Boy, this
guy sure doesn't look grateful.
-Are you OK, Rurichiyo?
-Yes, I am fine, because I had
Kenryu and Enryu to protect me.
-My Lady!
-Ahem.
Now let us return home
and continue our meal.
-Yes, but we'll--
-Dot not worry.
I'll be sure to eat
all of my carrots.
-Huh?
-If I didn't, it
would be an insult
to the farmers who
grew them, wouldn't it?
-Oh, my Lady!
You mustn't wander
off like that again.
Lady Rurichiyo, we were--
we were so-- so worried!
-I know, I know.
-Hey, hurry it up or we're
going to leave you three behind.
-Oh, hey, wait!
Ichigo!
Enryu, will you
cut it out already?
-[sobbing] Yes, ma'am.
[sobbing]
[music playing]
KENRYU: Ichigo Kurosaki!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
-What do you want this early?
Huh?
Oh, my window!
-That's not important,
because Lady Rurichiyo
has disappeared again!
[theme music]
ORIHIME: So, Ichigo, your family
puts carrots into their curry?
ICHIGO: Huh?
ORIHIME: My curry only
has normal ingredients.
Boiled taro, arrowroot
paste, red beans.
ICHIGO: That's normal?
RUKIA: It was
delicious, Orihime.
ICHIGO: You ate that?