The Zanpakuto. Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined
by its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper and
dies with its Soul
Reaper.
That is the existence of
a Zanpakuto.
That's not good enough.
So you're the one.
Come back here!
You're always turning
your back on reality!
Admit to what happened!
What are you getting at?
You have been betrayed!
By the person you trusted
the most!
I couldn't say anything
at the time. But I was
right there, watching as
it happened.
It's frustrating!
I see.
I can't stand seeing this.
If you keep this up, you'll
end up destroying yourself.
Even with me trying
to help you.
You're quite harsh.
Tell me. Tell me
what to do.
You need me to help you.
I wanna put you to sleep
forever, you poor little
thing.
Put me to sleep?!
Oh, sorry, I forgot. You've
already been asleep for some
time now.
Does it hurt?
Well, what you're feeling
now, that is the pain of
reality.
It's nothing like the
naive world you live in.
Reality is harsh and painful.
I'll help to change your
mind.
Who knew an old lady like
you could still move. I'm
impressed.
What did you call me?
Momo!
What are you doing?!
Trying to get through to
you. I bet you still
think that you're good
looking, right?
What?!
Women are just like milk.
They all have an
expiration date.
So face it. You're way
past your expiration date.
You brat.
I've had enough of you!
Like you could make me
stop!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Would you
just stop?!
I thought I would help
you look sexier. But
since your shelf time's
already passed, you're
pretty much done in terms
of appealing to anyone.
Hmph! Maybe you
shouldn't be pushing
yourself.
Old-lay-dee. Hmm?!
You are so dead!
There's one more thing I
want to tell you.
All of those so called
friends of yours that
you trust...
That's all just
a big joke.
To be honest, none of them
are really your friends
at all.
They're just pretending
to be your friends because
it's a part of their jobs.
For instance, there's
Rangiku Matsumoto...
It's obvious that she
only cares about herself.
She couldn't care less
about what you're
struggling with. Really.
Is she paying any
attention to you now?
Why are you getting so
crazy? If you weren't
such an old lady, you
wouldn't care!
It's really sad and
pathetic to see you
acting like this!
Now die!
You are done!
You old witch!
The one who reigns!
Mask of flesh and
blood Universe
soar. The one crowned
with man's name!
Disintegrate, black dog
of Rondanini!
What do you think
you're doing?
Read through, burn away,
claw out your throat!
Bakudo Number Nine!
Horin!
Your aim is awful.
Have you heard
anything I've said?
Shakkaho!
What are you aiming
at? Old la---
Bakudo Number Nine!
Horin!
Let go!
Hey! Stop pushing
against me, will you?!
You really think I'm the
one in control here?! It's
not me doing---
That hurt!
We sure showed them!
I hope they paid
attention!
What are you saying, old
lady?
You mean you planned this
from the beginning?
And it worked, too! Do you
really think I'd ever take
anything a spoiled brat like
you said seriously?
We knew in order to go up
against our own Zanpakuto
powers, we needed to find a way
to catch you both off guard!
We knew if we split you
two up and got you paying
attention to us individually,
defeating you
would be easy!
You two deserve each
other!
You've gotta
be kidding me!
You might want to try to
get along better.
Get along with her?!
You know, after seeing the
way the two of you treat each
other, I'd have to say I feel
sorry for you girls.
And why is that?
You're selfish and self
centered. You never think
of anyone but yourselves.
That is not true!
Oh no?
Don't pay attention to
her. She's just bitter
'cause she's an old lady.
You will quit calling me
an old lady right now!
It's not a bad thing.
Huh?
Honestly, I'm looking
forward to growing older.
Huh?!
What?!
Being young isn't really
all that great.
When you are young, your
heart is still unrefined.
Your emotions are at risk
every time someone in your
life gains your respect or when
they turn their back on you.
It can feel as though
you're flying at times,
or even drowning.
Your emotions are always
getting the best of you
and it's easy to lose
sight of who you are.
But as you grow older
your heart and mind are
able to mature.
You gain perspective and
develop the ability to
set aside your emotions
to better understand who
you really are.
That's why I think growing
older is a good thing.
Using "expiration date"
when referring to someone's
age, makes you sound simple.
Well said.
Hmph. You believe that?
Oh, well! Girls as
immature as you don't
want to understand.
Sure, whatever you say.
Such a touching and admirable
speech.
Yeah, what a joke, right?
Hey, what's going on with
you?! Who's side are you on?!
Uh, that's my own business,
got it?! Huh!
Yeah, like anything goes
on in that head of yours!
What?! When it come to
brains you really shouldn't
talk!
Brains don't make you
cute, dummy!
Just shut up!
Your name is Hyorinmaru!
And I am Toshiro
Hitsugaya, I am your
master!
Hm. Don't
make me laugh.
A mere boy could never be
the master of such great
power.
Are you serious?...Have
you completely forgotten
who I am?
You have already wasted
enough of my time. How
could you expect me to
believe such nonsense?
What has Muramasa done to
you?
Muramasa has no say in my
actions. Everything that's
happened has been a blur.
When I was released from
my master, I lost all my
memories.
All of your memories?
I've chosen to continue
working for Muramasa at
this time,
but my real goal is to
find my true master.
Your true master?
That's right. Because of my
enormous power, the one who
uses me must be the most
powerful Soul Reaper of all.
That is why logically, it
could not be a child like you.
It's true that my power
hasn't reached its potential.
But that doesn't change
the fact that I am your
owner!
Easy to say.
But if you truly are my
master, then you will show
me proof. Words will not
convince me.
Bakudo Number
Sixty-Three!
Sajosabaku!
A wasted effort.
What?!
Toshiro!
Damn it!
Stop, Hyorinmaru!
I am the one that
you are fighting!
Hado Number Thirty-One!
Shakkaho!
Your attempts are
useless. Do you hear me?
Zanpakuto.
I've heard the
Zanpakuto were released
from the Soul Reapers to
fulfill their desires.
If that's the case,
Hyorinmaru, what is it
you desire?
What do I desire?
That's right, what
is it you want?
Only you know what your
soul desires most in
this world.
Have you forgotten even
that?!
It would be a place to
call my own. It would be
home.
A home?
I feel I'm searching
for a home.
Searching...
... for a home.
Why are they afraid of
me?
I haven't done anything to any
of them, but it seems to me
that everyone's afraid of me.
Is it my silver hair? Maybe
it's the color of my eyes
that frightens them.
Could it be because I'm
distant towards people I
don't know?
I'm going to go buy some
snacks. I'll get you some.
Grandma's gotten very thin.
Maybe it's a coincidence, but
she seemed to get thin after I
started having those dreams.
Here's your change.
Thanks.
If that's all you want,
then get going.
Hey you!
That's how you treat a
paying customer!? Just
because he's a kid, you
think it's alright to
disrespect him?! I am
surprised as a shop owner
you lack common courtesy!
I didn't mean to be
rude.
If you ever wanna become
a man...then stop crying
and stand up for yourself!
Hey, what happened
wasn't my fault! And
I'm not crying! Now
let go of me!
I said let go!
Hey you! Hold on!
That dream...
I hear a voice...
it's echoing.
It feels like it's
crushing me.
It's surrounding me.
It feels like lightning
is striking my hand...
What's going on?!
Who are you?!
Boy! You are my--
I can't hear you!
What are you saying?!
My name is--
I can't hear you.
Hey!
You're that girl!
You should conceal your
Spirit Energy when you
sleep. You've got your
grandma shivering.
I did that?
You did. You need to
become a Soul Reaper,
boy.
When a kid is strong like
you are, they need to
learn how to control
their power.
I'll tell you this...
If you continue doing
what you're doing now,
the power you've got
will eventually kill your
grandma.
What do you mean?!
You can hear a voice,
can't you?
Reign Over the Frosted
Heavens.
Hyorinmaru!
Somehow you are using my
power! But how?! You're
just a boy!
So you still can't
remember?
Then I will show you.
Though I don't know
what'll happen if I use
this attack in Shikai...
Ryusenka!
Getsugatensho!
Toshiro!
Remember!
Remember who it was that
heard your voice.
Remember where you're
from! Remember your
home!
Child. Do you think you
are capable of mastering
me?!
My name is...
You are--
Hyorinmaru!!
Master!
You remembered.
But my name... it
is not boy.
My name is Toshiro
Hitsugaya.
There is no time.
It looks as though you
will have to do for now.
Captain! Please let me
borrow Hyorinmaru just
this once! It has always
been my fantasy to put a
handsome man on a leash
and walk him like a dog!
No.
In return, I'll let you
borrow Haineko!
What? You are really
annoying!
Absolutely not!