[theme music]
NARRATOR: In order
to save Orihime,
who was kidnapped
by the Arrancars,
Ichigo, Chad, Uryu,
Rukia, and Renji
have all snuck into Hueco
Mundo, the realm of the Hollows.
On the journey to Aizen's
fortress, Las Noches,
our heroes struggled
against endless attacks
from the Arrancar forces.
Upon breaking into the
fortress, the group
split up and took
five different paths
in their search for Orihime.
Rukia was confronted by Espada
number 9, Aaroniero Arruruerie,
who appeared before her outside,
on the roof of the fortress.
-Come with me.
NARRATOR: Shockingly, when
Aaroniero removed his mask,
he revealed the face of a man
who was supposedly deceased.
It was Kaien Shiba, former
lieutenant of Squad 13
and Rukia's mentor.
-It can't be.
Lieutenant Shiba?
-Ha.
Yeah.
It's been a while.
You're looking well, Rukia.
I'm just glad that it
was you ended up in here.
I've got a plan,
and I think you're
the only person who can help
me pull it off successfully.
I want you to bring me the
heads of your four friends.
You're familiar with all of
their abilities and weaknesses,
so you don't have to
worry about getting hurt.
It shouldn't be too difficult
to catch them off guard.
If you do this, we'll wipe
the slate clean between us
and I'll completely
forgive you for killing me.
You see?
Pretty simple, huh?
I would say it's an
awfully small price
to pay for taking my life,
don't you think, Rukia?
Well?
What's wrong, Rukia?
-You're not gonna say it's
a joke this time, are you?
-Rukia.
-You want me to kill
my friends for you?
Something like that
could never be a joke.
You'd never joke about
something like that.
The Kaien I knew would
never force someone
to choose between their friends
and themselves, no matter what.
Now dance!
Tsude no Shirayuki!
-Rukia's spiritual pressure.
She must be fighting again.
Is she winning?
Damn it.
It's too far away.
I can't get a clear read.
[groan]
[screaming]
-Don't get in my face like that!
I'm telling you right now, if
you keep sneaking up on me,
you're gonna give
me a heart attack.
Hey, come to think of it,
what were you screaming about?
-You started screaming out of
nowhere and it surprised me,
you know what I mean?
And just when I was
getting over that,
so suddenly stopped
screaming and started
talking to yourself.
Have you gone
completely bonkers?
-Get over it.
I wasn't acting crazy enough
for you to be worrying about me.
Come on.
Time to get moving.
-Wait, don't leave me behind.
I'm coming.
RENJI (VOICEOVER): Rukia.
Don't you dare die on me.
Dance.
Sode no Shirayuki.
-Some no mai.
Tsukishiro!
-What's wrong, Rukia?
Is that it?
Is that the extent
of your power.
The first dance is Tsukishiro,
and the second dance
is Hakuren.
I know them both very well.
Who was it who helped you
practice those movies?
Me, if you recall.
I watched you work them both
out, right from the very start.
Come on.
Do you really think they'll
work against me, Rukia?
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
I have to remember.
This man isn't
who he says he is.
He's not Kaien Shiba.
He's an imposter.
Two of my friends
are in trouble.
It's Uryu and Chad.
-Are you worried
about something?
Your friends are fighting
very highly skilled opponents.
They're Privaron Espada.
That's the fallen Espada.
-They aren't even full Espada.
-Why are you so relieved?
Even though they're
ex-Espada, they
have the skills of trained
assassins and, as such,
shouldn't be taken lightly.
One of your friends defeated
an ex-Espada earlier,
but not without consequence.
He paid a heavy price
for his victory.
You can sense his
distress, can't you?
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): I
knew there was something
wrong with Ichigo's
spiritual pressure.
KAIEN: It looks like I didn't
need to ask for your help
in bringing me your
friends' heads.
They'll all be dead soon.
One way or another, you'll see.
You think you're gonna
be a hero, Rukia?
There's nothing you can do.
-Tsugi no mai.
Hakuren!
-What a clever idea, using
Hakuren to distract me
and then attacking me.
Good, but, not good enough.
You still don't get it, do you?
You don't have the experience
or power to defeat me.
I'm tired of this.
Rage through the
seas and the heavens.
Nejibana.
Does this bring back memories?
-But how?
-You're finished, Rukia.
Here I come.
Take your position.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): His
unique upper body stance
is so familiar.
The spear techniques, like
a beautifully choreographed
dance.
Using one wrist as the
center of rotation.
The way he splits
the enemy in two
by crushing them with a
blast of spirit energy,
and slashing them
with his spear.
Without a doubt, these are
Kaien Shiba's techniques
No matter how much my heart
denies it, my eyes and my brain
try to tell me that this
man is the real Kaien.
But the core of my
being can't accept it.
I must trust in the
mentor who lives
on in my heart, not the
impostor who stands before me.
I must trust in the man
who taught me how to fight,
and gave me a place
where I knew I belonged.
I must believe in the warm,
kind-hearted Kaien I once knew.
NEL: Hey, whoa there!
What's the matter, Ichigo?
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): That
surge of spiritual pressure
I felt just now.
Did it come from Rukia?
Wait.
It isn't just her.
It's Uryu and Chad, as well.
Are they going to be all right?
I can't have doubt.
I have to trust in their skills.
NEL: I can't breathe!
Sorry.
I didn't mean to
squeeze so hard.
I was lost in thought.
-Goodbye.
-Wait a minute, Nel!
You can't be dead!
I'm really sorry.
-Tell me, Ichigo, are you
really, truly, honestly sorry?
-I really, truly am!
Will you forgive me?
-I suppose I'll forgive you if
you give me a piggyback ride.
-Wha-- why you little--
this is serious business.
We don't have time
to be fooling around.
-You almost squished
me to death,
and now you're yelling at me!
I don't think you're very nice!
-All right, whatever you say.
Just stop crying, will ya?
Come on.
-Ichigo, are you sure
you're really sorry?
-Yeah, I'm really, really sorry.
-Then we'd better get a move on!
Giddyup, horsey!
Now we're really
gettin' somewhere!
Faster, faster!
-I swear, I'm never having kids.
-You lose, Rukia.
-Huh?
-Hado number 33, Sokatsui!
-Kido without the incantation.
You've improved.
I must admit, I'm impressed.
But it won't be
enough to defeat me.
-What?
Why did he run away?
He dodged my spell with ease.
I was completely open.
He could have killed me in
one stroke if he wanted to.
-Do you want me to
explain it to you?
-Come with me.
-Nothing he said has
made any sense, right
from the beginning.
Starting with his
explanation as why
we had to come inside for
our face to face encounter.
-Everywhere the light
touches in Las Noches
is being monitored my Aizen.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
This much I know.
Everything he said so
far has been a lie.
Keeping that in mind,
the real question
is why did he invite
me inside this tower
before removing his mask?
-Sorry.
I simply cannot stand
the sunlight out there.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): I don't
believe he's telling the truth.
But it's worth
testing him to see
if I can find out
what's really going on.
Bakudo number four, Hainawa!
-What do you think
you're doing, Rukia?
Stalling for time?
Weak moves like that
won't get you anywhere.
RUKIA: Mask of flesh and blood.
Universe, soar.
The one crowned with man's name.
Carriage of thunder, and
gap of the spinning wheel.
Divide into--
-A double incantation.
She's desperate.
RUKIA: --between lotuses
into the wall of blue flame.
Wake for the edge of the
great spire in the heavens.
Bakudo number 61, Rikujokoro!
-Dammit!
-Hado number 73, Soren Sokatsui!
[screaming]
-Huh?
Wait a minute.
What in the world are you?
-Hm.
I guess our cover's been blown.
-What's done is done.
At this point, we may as
well reintroduce ourselves.
We are known as Espada number
nine, Aaroniero Arruruerie.
-But you haven't
explained what you are.
-Don't make us repeat ourselves.
We are known as Espada number
nine, Aaroniero Arruruerie.
-And don't ask us
about our faces.
We are tired of hearing
peoples' opinions.
-Let's talk about your
technique instead.
Rikujokoro, among the
current Soul Reaper captains,
Byakuya Kuchiki
is the most adept
with this particular Kido.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): He
even knows about that.
-A double incantation using
Rikujokoro and Soren Sokatsui.
We don't have a
memory of your being
able to use those
particular techniques.
But you blew your chance.
If you had the skills to hit
us directly with that Kido,
you might have easily
inflicted a serious injury.
-I didn't aim for you.
-Hm?
-I realized that the
sunlight would rob you
of your shape-shifting powers,
and in the process force
you to reveal your true form.
-To what purpose?
-It was critically important
to me, and it proved my point.
I had to reassure myself that
you weren't actually Kaien.
Now that I kow the truth,
I have no reservations
about this battle.
I can fight you without
holding back, and destroy you.
-Did we hear you
correctly, Rukia?
Did you say you could
win now that you
don't have to hold
yourself back?
-You have good hearing
for someone without ears.
-You've made a mistake, Rukia.
-Don't take us lightly.
We can't use our power in
the sunlight, that is true.
But as long as we stay in the
shadows, we're indestructible.
We can use it endlessly.
-To be perfectly
honest, I don't know
what Lord Aizen was thinking.
Whether he put the light
there for security or not,
it's been a real
pain in the ass.
Hueco Mundo operates
just fine in the dark.
I can't believe Lord Aizen
tried to copy the sunlight
from the world of the living,
especially when there are so
many others who need the dark
to operate at their best.
You seem to be
under the impression
that I have the
ability to shape-shift.
-Why?
Are you telling
me that I'm wrong?
-Not exactly.
I'm just saying there's
much more you haven't seen.
-What are you talking about?
-Hm.
You don't know, but
I'm the only Gillian
who's also a member
of the Espada.
-Oh, yeah?
So what?
-Under normal
circumstances, I wouldn't
have nearly enough power to
become a member of the Espada.
Yet here I am, a
full fledged member.
And I am number nine.
So why would they
make an exception?
They were impressed.
Out of all the Arrancars
in Hueco Mundo,
I'm the only one who has the
ability to evolve infinitely!
The power to merge
with another entity
originally belonged to a
creature called Metastacia,
who took over Kaien Shiba's
body when they fought.
When Metastacia died, his
body returned to Hueco Mundo.
That's when I made my move.
I ate him and made
his power mine!
-You are that monster's body?
-You bet I did.
[gasp]
-My true ability is
called Glotoneria.
It's quite simple.
I devour dead Hollows and
absorb both their spirit energy
and abilities.
Understand?
When Metastacia came back
in Kaien Shiba's body,
I devoured him and was able to
absorb both their abilities.
-That explains all
your knowledge.
-Of course.
You weren't wrong
to believe you were
talking to the
actual Kaien Shiba.
Because this body really
did belong to Kaien Shiba.
The muscles retain
all his experience,
and the mind retains
all of his memories.
They're accessible for my use!
It's an elegantly effective
system when you think about it.
I simply accessed all of his
memories and acted accordingly.
It's the endgame.
Allow me to demonstrate for you.
I'll show you what an Espada
sword release actually
looks like.
Devour her, Glotoneria!
[theme music]
NEL: Riding on Ichigo's
shoulders is great!
It makes me taller and faster.
I don't ever wanna
get down from here!
DONDOCHAKKA: You're so lucky.
I want a piggyback ride, too!
Man, what gives?
RENJI: What are you
looking at me for?
DONDOCHAKKA: Please, Renji?
RENJI: Whoa, hey!
Get off of me!
NEL: You boys sure
know how to have fun!
RENJI: Gah!