The Zanpakuto. Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined
by its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper
and dies with its Soul
Reaper.
That is the existence
of a Zanpakuto.
There's faint Spiritual
Pressure here...
I want all of you to
split up and find where
it's coming from.
Right!
Relax! Leave it to me!
Hold on! Think you can
handle this job?
Stop treating me
like a kid.
All right,
found one.
You're a Sword
Beast, aren't you?
Don't move!
[flustered]
Uhhh!
Why am I feeling so
weird?! I mean, he must
be a Zanpakuto! I'm a
Zanpakuto, too,
but just by looking at him,
I can tell that he's clearly
a lot younger than me.
Come on, Haineko, you like
older guys, you don't like
kids! You're never interested
in skinny-looking wimps.
You're into more mature guys.
Guys who have more meat on
their bones than his beanpole.
Yet...
I can't help myself!
I'm lovestruck!
Damn---
[struggling]
You all right?!
I don't get this. I
like manly men. Guys
filled with testosterone.
Not passive guys like
this weakling who's
breaking a sweat just
trying to stand up.
But a Sword Beast is a
Sword Beast. I'm gonna
have to take you down.
[gasping]
I can't believe he's using
puppy dog eyes on me and it's
working! All I wanna do is
take care of him!
[sighing]
Well, I guess you
need some help.
Is everyone okay?
All clear on
this side.
They've all been
taken care of!
So, were you
able to find one?
Sure. Yeah.
So then you
dealt with it?
Yup.
Hmmm?
Say, Rangiku... uh--
Haineko? Is something
wrong?
No, no. Nothing worth
talking about!
Hey. Wake up Rangiku!
Hm? Oh Captain! What
are you doing here?
Never mind why I'm
here! Why are you
laying around?!
I'm depressed because
someone took these special
sweets I'd been hiding.
They're gone.
You ate them, didn't you?
Why would I do that? And
besides, it's rude not to
share! You shouldn't hide
them!
Hyorinmaru, can you
get me some tea, please?
Yes, ma'am.
I never gave you permission
to treat my Zanpakuto as
if he's your servant.
Anyway, we're still not
finished hunting down all
those Sword Beasts...
We can't relax yet!
I know.
Lieutenant, where exactly
is Haineko?
Who knows?
Probably somewhere
sleeping.
Is this really okay?
I mean, I don't owe anyone
anything. It's not like I'm
a Soul Reaper.
But still...
[exhaling]
Hey! I've
come back.
Ta-dah!
There we go!
Thank you so much
for helping me.
But... why are
you doing this?
You need help.
But isn't destroying
all of us your sworn duty?
Why would you be treating
the injuries of your enemy?
Attacking an opponent
who's really too wounded
to fight back, isn't my
idea of fair.
Besides, you're not like
other Sword Beasts I've
met!
You're not aggressive at
all! You're quite nice!
What am I talking about?!
Oh, well. He does seem
harmless.
You are a Sword Beast,
aren't you?
That is the name the
Soul Society has given me.
But I'm not a beast, I'm
just an ordinary Zanpakuto
who's lost his master.
My master was a cowardly
Soul Reaper. And now I've
found out, I'm just like him.
So to survive, I needed
to protect myself.
I was scared and knew I
was weak. I thought if I
aligned myself with the
other sword Sword Beasts
I'd be protected.
But because I was close
to them, I was hunted
down, as they were.
At the first sign of
danger, I ran and hid.
[heavy breathing]
And I'm still hiding
to this day.
You really need to get
some rest. You're obviously
in a lot of pain!
Thank you.
[gasping]
What?! Is there...
something on my face?
You're not like any other
Zanpakuto or Soul reaper
I've ever met!
I'm not?
So! I'm gonna help you
with your situation!
Huh?
I can tell there's
nothing dangerous
about you.
So I'll ask the others to
treat you like a regular
Zanpakuto instead of a
Sword Beast!
Oh, and I brought
you some sweets.
Could you really do that?!
Just leave it to me!
Please tell me.
What's your name?
I'm Narunosuke.
Mm-hmm. Well,
I'm Haineko.
[gulping]
Nice to meet you,
Miss Haineko.
Don't call me that.
Makes me sound old.
Lady Haineko?
That sounds even worse!
[giggling]
That's not possible.
Why?
Once Zanpakuto lose their
masters, there's no way of
knowing when they'll
become violent and
turn dangerous.
So we have to deal with
all these Sword Beasts
the same way.
But there may be some
Sword Beasts that aren't
really dangerous to us at all!
I wish that that were
true, but...
While each Sword Beast
is different, we know
from Squad 12's research
there's an extremely
high possibility that they
will eventually lose their
minds and go out of control.
Our job is to stop them
before they can hurt someone.
Why are you asking?
Have you found another
Sword Beast?
No! It's nothing! I'm
just kinda curious about
them! See ya!
I can't let any of them know
about him! These Soul Reapers
would wipe out even a harmless
guy like him!
She mentioned that Sword
Beasts have a very good
chance of losing their minds!
So then, are there Sword
Beasts out there who haven't
done that?!
That's it! He's not like
the others! He's just a
scared Zanpakuto who lost
his master.
I'll explain that.
That'll change Rangiku's
mind!
Whoa! You like younger
guys, really?! Ew!
[laughing]
Maybe telling her that
might not work.
Hey! Haineko!
How are you?
All I know is, I've gotta
do something about this
myself!
Wha-- Huh?
Is it good?
Yes! Very good!
He's just a young guy. I
can't see him becoming
violent.
He's definitely not a
Sword Beast. He's a
Zanpakuto. Just like me!
I'm glad you
like it!
Oh, I meant to ask. Am
I still going to be dealt
with as a Sword Beast?
Did you talk to the
others like you promised?
[gasping and coughing]
Oh that! Why sure! I did
ask my Soul Reaper about
that!
She said she'd talk to
her superiors about it,
but it seems they're kind
of busy right now, so it
might take some time for
them to get back to you!
Oh, I see.
Speaking of my Soul
Reaper, those sweets I
brought for you for lunch
yesterday, were
candies that she hides
from everyone because she
swears they keep her from
catching colds! Have you
ever heard of
anything so nuts?!
Achoo!
[laughing]
Now that's pretty funny!
Isn't it?!
[struggling]
You okay?
Uh, yeah. Fine.
You're still not
completely healed. Maybe you
should rest a little more.
I can't thank you
enough, Miss Haineko.
No one's ever cared about
me before. You're special.
Um! Wow! Really?
[laughing]
Oh!
Huh?
[laughing]
I wonder what
happened to her.
Who knows?
What's up?!
I'm back!
What is it?!
What's going on?
It is just so darn
amazing to be alive!
Don't you agree,
my dear Rangiku?
Uh... D-d-dear Rangiku?!
Not again.
It's happening more
often!
[humming]
Heyyyy!
I brought you lunch
again! I brought a
little sake too!
You can have a sip,
right? You must be
feeling better,
so I thought we'd
have a drink together.
Mmmm. Miss Haineko...
Huh?
I'm sorry. But right
now, the last thing on
my mind is having fun.
What?
Don't you see? I need to
know what will really
happen to me!
You told me you were
going to handle it! Were
you just telling me lies?!
No, but you see...
I'll tell you
the truth.
Now I see.
I'm so sorry.
It's okay. None of this is
your fault. A Sword Beast
is a Sword Beast.
I must accept my
situation and not
expect any help.
Wait! What
will you do?
If I stay here, the Soul
Reapers will eventually find
and destroy me! I must leave
before that happens.
Aaargh!
You're not well! You're
in no condition to go!
Thanks to your help, my
wounds have healed enough.
I'm very grateful to you.
Please, don't leave
yet! Besides, I--
[screaming]
What's wrong?!
Narunosuke!
Ahhh!
This is bad.
While each sword Sword
beast Beast is different,
we know from Squad 12's
research there's an
extremely high possibility
that they will eventually
lose their minds and go
out of control.
[gasping for breath]
Sorry I hit you.
Sometimes I get these
excruciating headaches.
And my hands start doing
things on their own...
It's been happening more
and more frequently.
What's with
that look?
Nothing! Nothing
at all.
You're just gonna need to
stay here until you're not
having those headaches anymore.
Heh. You're so
very kind.
Someone's taking our
supplies?!
That's what it looks like.
We've had a lot of things
missing lately.
It's true. Some medicine is
missing and someone's taken
some food rations from the
barracks.
Mmmm.
Do you have any idea
who it might be?
No clue.
But there may be some
Sword Beasts that aren't
dangerous to us at all!
Oh...
Come in, Haineko.
You knew I'd
been gone?
Of course I did. Where
were you, anyway?
Nowhere.
So, Haineko...
What is it?
Um, I, uh--
By the way, have you heard
the news that we've discovered
someone has been stealing
medicine and food
from our barracks?
What?! Wow,
that's bad news.
Yeah. Awful. Who
would do that?
[sighing]
No idea. Goodnight!
[screaming]
Another headache?!
What can I do?!
I just need to know what's
going to happen to me!
Well, I don't know.
You'll be okay, you
just need some time to--
Stop lying! You know
what's happening to me!
[screaming]
Narunosuke! I know it
hurts, try to hang in
there!
Just tell me the truth!!
You're becoming
a Sword Beast.
Rangiku!
I knew that something strange
must have been going on. Now,
it makes perfect sense.
So you followed me?
Why didn't you tell me
about this earlier? Why
did you try to hide this?
I need you to try to
understand my position.
I'm a lieutenant. And
you are my Zanpakuto.
I'm ordering you! Back
away from that Sword
Beast!
Hold it! He's not a
Sword Beast. He's
just suffering!
That's just the start! Soon,
he'll lose his mind and go
out of control!
That's what happens
to Sword Beasts!
I'm turning... into
a Sword Beast?!
Wait, there has to be some
way to save his life!
[trembling]
There isn't.
What?
Miss Haineko,
please save me!
[screaming]
[gasping]
Out of the way, Haineko!
I'm getting rid of him
for his own good!
No way! I will find a
way to save him!
Why do you refuse
to hear me?!
If you must kill him,
think of me as a Sword
Beast, too and get rid
of me.
It's disappointing that
I can't get you to listen.
Growl! Haineko!
[yelling]
Ha!
She leaves me no other
choice! I'll restrain
her with bakudo!
Narunosuke! Don't!
[growling]
[gasping]
Rangiku!
[growling]
Haineko!
I'm sorry..
Please Haineko get away!!
[screaming]
I'm here for you. You
wouldn't hurt me. I was
sure of that.
Haineko...
Narunosuke.
Thank you, Miss
Haineko.
Narunosuke!
I was in love with him.
I couldn't help myself.
And I couldn't admit
it. I couldn't tell him.
I know you were. You
all right?
What's that?
Nothing.
I was blinded and made
a big mistake. Is that
what you think?
No, not really. But I do
think that you're foolish.
I might be. I think I'll
give younger guys a rest
for a while.
Why is that?
I'm sure they'll be lots
more fun when I'm your age.
Whatever works.
Captain, should we give
Haineko something to help
to mend her broken heart?
Oh, yeah. Perhaps
she'd like--
I've got it! Booze and
shopping always helps a
broken heart!
But I'm worried about Haineko
going off on her own, so I'll
go with her!
This bottle's
for Haineko!
Rangiku!