[menacing growls]
Damn it!
I Gotta do this again?!
[big roar]
Huaaahh!
I don't get it!
Why didn't that work?
I released it just like
Getsuga Tenshou, but it's
power isn't even close!
Unh!
That's it!
This thing doesn't have a
blade I was initiating
my attacks way too soon.
If I charge it with more
Spirit Energy than
I did with Getsuga...
All right, let's do this!
Kyaaa!
Raaagh!
[hurt]
Aaagh!
He learned how to produce that
much destructive power in such
a short time. Impressive.
Your training this time will
take place in this fish tank!
Now, I permit you.
[Jackie]
Welcome.
[Ichigo]
Oh, so it's you.
Not giving me a
plushie this time, huh?
That's 'cuz we figure
that you've moved
past fighting them.
I haven't introduced myself to
you Have I?
I'm Jackie Tristan.
You ready?
Ichigo Kurosaki.
I sure as hell am!
Nice. I like your determination.
"Dirty Boots"!
Not bad.
I didn't think
you'd be able to
dodge that attack.
I didn't think
I would either.
Is that a joke?
You tell me, what's
with that outfit?
I didn't know there was a
Fullbring you could wear.
Well there is.
My Fullbring is
why I'm dressed
like this.
Gotcha.
So, this "Dirty
Boots" of yours.
What's its ability?
You really think I'd tell you?
Hey, just thought I'd ask.
Coulda helped to know.
Oh well. Guess I'll
hafta find out myself.
Here we go!
Hnh.
Hey, where you going?
We need you to stay here
and watch, so you can
undo your "Dollhouse"
when they're done.
No!
Huh?!
I wanna say something
that's been on my
mind lately.
Save it, Yukio.
Oh yeah? Well Riruka's
attitude stinks.
Y'know, you really
didn't have to say that.
What do you think?
[Giriko]
Me?
Well.
I don't mind her, really.
Hmmh.
I just hate having to look at
Jackie's Fullbring outfit!
Hunh!
How 'bout this!?
[gasp]
Hmm.
[sloshing]
Do you think he'll
be able to complete
his training?
Hard to say.
Haaaaaa!
Eyagh!
One.
Raaagh!
That's two.
And three.
[panting]
So what now?
Aren't you going to
try to attack me?
Then it's my turn.
Haaaaaa!
Yah!
For this entire session,
you've been repeating
the same pattern.
You dodge, then my
kicks get to you.
Your fighting
instincts are good,
but you're being
way too cautious.
Here's what I think
you're trying to do.
You're still attempting
to get the hang of
Fullbring as you fight.
[grunt]
Well that's fine and all,
but you better do it fast.
Because the dirt here is
starting to turn into mud.
You see this?
My "Dirty Boots" are
about to get dirtier.
Hyah!
She's getting serious now.
Yeah.
Do you think
Mister Kurosaki
will survive?
All we can do is
hope for the best.
[spits]
Ptoo!
Her kick got a
lot stronger.
So do you get it now?
As the name "Dirty
Boots" suggests,
The dirtier my boots get,
be it with sand, dirt,
mud, blood, rust,
No matter what the
substance, the
stronger I become.
I'm not sure if you've
noticed this, but I've
been slowly building up
strength until just now.
But from here on,
they'll get stronger at
an even faster rate!
[gasp]
Haaaa!
Haaa!
[Riruka]
[relieved sigh]
Hmpf.
The dirtier they get,
the stronger she becomes?
What's with that?!
That's stupid!
Ugh, getting dirty is
totally disgusting!
Hm?
I never want to
end up dirty.
I'll always be the
clean and cute one.
Even when I die.
Will you buy it
for me next time?!
Sure, anything for you
princess. [Chuckle]
Yay Daddy!
Damn you, Ichigo.
Have you forgotten
why you're here?
C'mon, fight me!!
Don't you understand
this yet?!
You're fighting
with a mortal body!
Right now, you are
not a Soul Reaper!
What is it? Have you lost your
sense of reality from fighting
too long as a Spiritual Entity?!
You are flesh and blood.
And you can die here!!
Do you have a clue what'll
happen if you continue to
take more of my attacks
with your current body?
Your life will be
over much sooner
than you'd like!
Is that all you know how to do?!
That technique of yours
has nothing but flaws!
It's useless
in real combat!
Haven't you
realized that yet?!
Since you don't get it,
I'll have to show you!!
Your technique's too
inconsistent to be effective!
Depending on the level of your
concentration, the number of
blades on your weapon varies
from three to six!
Right now you only have
four blades and that
number's decreasing!
My kick can destroy
four blades or less!
Plus! After three consecutive
shots, that's when...
"That's when I become most
vulnerable." Is that it?
[gasp] He did that on purpose?!
Where'd he go!?
A Bringer Light...?!
Heh!
[Jackie]
Yeegh!
Amazing!
The flickering of the Bringer
Light indicates for certain,
that Ichigo executed
a high-speed jump
using fullbring!
It's a sign that he's
beginning to master it.
Now I'm impressed.
You realized the flaw of
your newly acquired ability,
then you quickly used
that flaw completely
to your advantage.
So, who taught
you how to fight?
All I was taught
were the basics.
But the rest,
Well,Ilearned
thatasIfought.
I was a Soul Reaper
for a short time.
But as for experience,
let's just say, I've
got plenty.
Experience, eh?
His mind's been unconsciously
sharpened by all those
battle she's fought.
And now, since he's
been forced to fight
without his powers,
his uncanny battle instincts
have been reawakened.
Not bad, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Ready?
Yeah!
Haaaa!
Huaaah!
[microwave alarm]
Hm? Oh hey.
[grunt]
Thank you so much,
Mister Sado.
Sure.
Where's Ichigo?
He's in
there.
I see.
That's perfect.
Huh?
I wanted to ask
you something.
That guy you warned
me about earlier.
Shukuro Tsukishima.
I want to know what
his ability is.
Hmm.
[Kugo]
I see.
So Orihime Inoue
said that, huh?
I'm sure I got cut.
But then when I came to,
there wasn't any blood
or any kind of wound.
And both of the guys who were
there with me had disappeared.
And when I saw, that both you,
and Ichigo had showed up to
see if I was okay,
I don't know why,
but for a second there,
I thought of that
person as a "friend".
I don't understand
what I'm trying to
say either.
But I was overcome with
this feeling that this
stranger was my friend.
It's not like I mistook him for
someone else, I mean after all,
he attacked me.
But how should I put it?
It felt like when I
thought about the past.
It suddenly seemed like
I knew who he was,
it was weird.
Based on her story, I've
got my own thoughts about
Tsukishima's ability.
And what are they?
It's mental, I think.
like mind games.
Do you happen to recall if
his Fullbring had the power
to alter people's memories?
Hmmf.
Please tell me what you know.
There's no point in
keeping secrets.
Yahh!
Haaaaa!
Huh.
[pleased]
Hm. That's
much better.
At this pace--
Ah!
Ichigo!
Huh?
My Combat Pass!!
[pain]
Eyaagh!
GAHHHH!
You don't want
to answer?
No, it's not that.
Hm?
I'm a bit puzzled.
You're "Puzzled"?
If Tsukishima had the
ability you just described,
I would've definitely told
you about it at the start.
The Fullbring ability
that Tsukishima uses is
called "Book of the End".
It is an extremely
deadly weapon.
A sword, that can cut
through anything.
But that is all.
That sword possesses no
other unique abilities.
Huh??
Waaauugh!
[gasp]
[panting]
Don't just stand there with
that look! Let's continue this!
We're stopping!
Unh?! What're you talking
about?!We're not done!
Your Fullbring is
out of control!
I've never seen
anything like that!
We've pushed the pace of
your training too hard!
We have to
stop now.
It's all right,
Let's keep going!
Riruka! Undo "Dollhouse"
right now!
Agh!
[yanking]
Yaagh!
I said, let's keep going!
Don't worry, my Fullbring
isn't out of control!
[gasp]
This is exactly how
I've always done it!
My Combat Pass is talking to me.
I gotta hurry and regain
my Soul Reaper powers.
You need to listen to me!
I'm telling you it's dangerous!
Do you need to be completely
destroyed to understand?!
Could it be that his
ability has changed?
That couldn't be it.
Fullbring powers don't
change with time.
Then what about
my ability?
It's gone through
several changes!
In this case,
you are mistaken.
As for your particular
situation, in the early
stages you were unaware.
It took you some time
just to discover your
Fullbring's innate ability.
Keep in mind that we've lived
with our Fullbring powers many
more years than you have.
We're well beyond the
stage you've just passed.
Then what was it that
happened to Orihime?
That's why I said
that I'm puzzled.
As far as I know, what
happened wasn't done by
Tsukishima's ability.
Hmmh.
What about
Uryu Ishida?
He was attacked by
Tsukishima as well, right?
Does Ishida's memory
seem to be affected?
[straining]
Fine.
Great, look how
dirty they are now!
Now I'll crush you
like you want me to!
Heh.
Haaaaaa!
Raaaaaa!
We need to be sure.
If Uryu Ishida's memory is
affected too, that's something
else we have to worry about.
But if his memories
haven't been affected,
What, Kugo?
What are you thinking?
That means it
wasn't Tsukishima,
who stabbed Orihime Inoue.
Mh!
[Tsukushima]
You sure about that?
[gasps]
[gasp]
Well now. It's been
a long time, Ginjo, hasn't it?
Tsukishima!
So this is him.
So, how have you all been?
Kutsuzawa, hope you haven't
been drinking too much.
Yukio. Looks like you're still
hooked on playing video games.
That's not good. You should try
reading more books instead.
And Riruka's not here?
Tsukishima!
Why did you
come here!?
Hm.
I don't see Jackie
around here, either.
Don't ignore me!
They in there?
[gasp]
No, don't do it!!
What is this?!
[gasp]
Ichigo.
Hmm.
[phone rings]
[Kugo]
Huh? That you, Riruka?!
Listen, Tsukishima just--
[Riruka] [over phone]
Hey! I bought too much
stuff to carry back.
Can you come pick
me up in your car?
[Kugo]
I don't have a car!
Forget that, Tsukishima, just--
[Riruka]
What?! God, you're
so useless! [click]
[Kugo]
You're the one who's useless!