[theme music]
ORIHIME: "On laundry
day, all the dirty towels
go in the top right drawer.
After they're washed,
fold the clean towels
and stack them in
the bottom drawer,
so you can find them
when you need them.
Make sure to take
out the garbage
before 8:00 AM on
Tuesday and Thursday.
If you don't get it out on
time, the trash collectors
won't pick it up.
If you don't finish
your dinner, you
should wrap the
leftovers in plastic
and put them in the freezer.
They last longer that way."
Period.
Well, that's pretty clear.
I think that covers everything.
I wish I didn't have to do
this, but Rangiku and Toshiro
would be helpless on their own.
Hm.
MAN (VOICEOVER): Take
this and do not remove it.
While wearing it, a special
type of spiritual barrier
will surround you.
And you will be invisible
to the outside world.
Only we, Arrancars, will
be aware of your presence.
You'll find you have
one more ability.
While you have it on,
you'll be able to pass
through any physical object
that exists in your world Don't
take it off for any reason.
-Yes.
ULQUIORRA (VOICEOVER):
You have 12 hours.
I give you permission to
say goodbye to one person
during that time.
-Huh.
ULQUIORRA (VOICEOVER): However,
if that person realizes
what you are doing, then you
will have disobeyed my orders.
You will come to me at midnight.
Finish whatever business
you have by then,
and meet me at the
designated area.
Don't forget, you can say
goodbye to one person and one
person only.
[door opens and shuts]
MAN: Eeh, grragh!
Ow!
That hurts.
Are you listening to me?
That's enough!
Back off!
-Forget it!
Ugh!
I can't do that!
-Don't give me that crap.
The bandages are
already too tight!
Agh!
Urrgh!
-Good work, Ururu.
Don't let him go.
Make him pass out.
And then we can finish him up.
MAN: Stop it!
-Hm?
-Let go of Ikkaku!
Leave him alone, you bully!
-You need to calm down
and stay still, Yumichika.
If you keep struggling, you'll
make your injuries worse.
-[groans]
[group grunting]
-You're getting very worked up.
This is for your own good.
-Yahh!
Wahh!
-Uh-oh, that's going
to leave a mark.
The man is injured.
Ririn, if you want
to restrain him,
you have to find a way
to do it more gently.
You can't just yank
on him like that.
RIRIN: Don't get on my case.
It's his fault for
not listening to me
and doing what he was told.
KURODO: [chuckles] You're
OK, right, Yumichika?
NOBA: Of course, he is.
-Don't worry.
Once he comes to, I'm
sure he'll forgive us.
-Urrh, rrahh!
[shrieks]
RIRIN: Run for it!
KURODO: We're sorry!
Just doing--
NOBA: Does this mean
you're not forgiving us?
-If I catch you, I'm going
to turn you inside out.
By the time I'm
through with you,
there won't be enough
piece of what to identify.
Come back here and
face me, you maggots!
-That was predictable.
They always get so
manic wherever they go.
[whooshing wind]
TOSHIRO (VOICEOVER):
I wonder what's
going on up there
with Kisuke Urahara.
He's been very quiet
since the fight ended.
He's such a mystery.
I know he's had
something on his mind
since the Arrancars retreated.
Maybe he's planning
our next offensive.
I know one thing, though.
For having fought so
many of the Espada,
we're lucky that this is
all the damage we suffered.
We were careless, and
we underestimated them.
They had prepared
for the battle.
And we hadn't.
We're going to
have to work harder
to be ready for the
next encounter, whenever
that may be.
I just wonder if we'll have
time to do what's necessary
before they come at us again.
How long will it take before
we can get up the strength?
-Rangiku.
-[gasps]
Yes?
-Have you been able to
contact the Soul Society yet?
-No, I'm not having any luck.
[beeps]
[static noise]
-Hm.
[gasps]
Uh, I'm so sorry.
-Huh?
-Hey, what's up?
What are you looking at?
-It felt like I
bumped into something,
but I can't see what it was.
-What are you talking about?
There's nothing near you.
Are you going nuts on me?
-I don't know.
Maybe.
I thought I hit something.
It was a weird feeling,
that's for sure.
It felt kind of
soft and squishy.
[gasps]
ULQUIORRA (VOICEOVER):
You will be
invisible to the outside world.
Only we, Arrancars, will
be aware of your presence.
You'll find you have
one more ability.
While you have it on,
you'll be able to pass
through any physical object
that exists in your world.
-Hm.
BOY 1: [singing] I'm sure
I left it in my desk.
BOY 2: Good thing your
head's screwed on,
or you can misplace that, too.
BOY 1: [singing] I forgot it.
I forgot it!
BOY 2: Would you
please not sing that.
It's irritating.
-Uhh.
--[singing] He, he
forgot something.
He, he forgot something!
-Mr. Asano, will
you stop singing?
ORIHIME (VOICEOVER):
Uh, why am I hiding?
They can't see me.
-I thought I told you.
Stop being so formal,
calling me by my last name.
I mean, we're
friends, aren't we?
-Of course, we are.
You certainly are touchy today.
-You don't know the
pressure I'm under.
-Huh?
-What is it?
-That's weird.
I wonder why Ichigo's
chair fell over.
You think he came
to school today?
-No way.
Someone must have just
bumped into it or something.
-Hm.
I guess.
But don't you think it's
strange that he, Chad, Orihime,
Rukia, and Uryu were all absent
from school on the same day?
-Hrrh!
Wait, that's it!
They're all doing something
fun together. [bawls]
And we've been left out.
The cool kids are
deliberately snubbing us.
-Don't put me in the
same group as you.
-What's that?
MIZUIRO: And besides--
-Huh?
-If you take a minute
to think about it,
we're not the only ones
who have been left out.
-Oh, really?
-Well, what do you mean?
Like who?
-Off the top of my head, the
first one who comes to mind
is Tatsuki.
-Uh.
MIZUIRO (VOICEOVER): If you
take a minute to think about it,
we're not the only ones
who have been left out.
Off the top of my head, the
first one who comes to mind
is Tatsuki.
-[panting]
-Keep up your pace.
Don't slack off now.
GROUP: Yes, sir!
-Uh.
Tatsuki.
[gasps]
Uh.
BOY: Where were you
aiming at, you idiot?
Go get the ball.
TEACHER: Arisawa,
what's the holdup?
-Nothing, sir.
ULQUIORRA (VOICEOVER):
Don't forget.
You can say goodbye to one
person and one person only.
[static noise]
[beep]
-That's strange.
I can't reach Orihime
in the Soul Society.
Maybe there's some
spiritual wave interference.
[sighs]
HACHIGEN (VOICEOVER): I'm sorry.
This is the best I can do.
My ability doesn't
actually involve
healing someone's
illness or injuries.
It's more a type
of time reversal.
In order to use my
techniques most effectively,
I must have precise knowledge
of what conditions to reverse.
This is critical to
success or failure.
Right now, Ichigo's
spirit energy
has intermingled with the
spirit energy absorbed
from the Arrancars' attacks.
In his current condition,
this is the best I can do.
In order to get him through
this as quickly as possible,
he needs to be isolated.
It's important that
he be separated
from beings like ourselves since
we all have spirit energy that
is similar to the
kind found in Hollows.
Being around us will only slow
down or reverse his recovery.
So my advice to you is
to take him home and let
him rest for as
long as necessary.
That would be the best
treatment for him right now.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
Yes, I understand.
Ichigo.
I wonder who those people were.
And even more importantly,
what kind of power
were you trying to
obtain from them?
Why did the Arrancars retreat
in the middle of the fight?
It doesn't make sense.
There are so many things
I don't understand.
All right, Ichigo
will be safe here.
I better go check on Orihime.
KARIN: We shouldn't
be bothering him--
-Huh?
KARIN: --Yuzu.
We were supposed
to let him rest.
YUZU: But, Karin,
what if he wakes up?
We should be there.
He should see somebody
he knows, right?
KARIN: Maybe.
[both gasp]
-Um, Rukia, would it be OK
if we eat dinner in here?
-Hm, of course.
I don't see why not.
I'm sure Ichigo would like that.
-Rukia--
RUKIA: Hm, what's wrong?
-Aren't you hungry as well?
It's dinner time.
I made a special
dish just for you.
RUKIA: Wow, what's this?
-A surprise.
Smells good, huh?
-Yeah, but I was on my way out.
I have to go somewhere.
-Oh, really?
-I'm not very hungry just now.
[stomach growls]
[chuckles]
-Wasn't that your tummy talking?
-Your tummy knows
more than you do.
You are hungry.
-[chuckles]
I guess I will have
some, Yuzu, since you
went to the trouble
of making it.
YUZU: Yay!
Thanks, Rukia.
Come on, Karin, let's
bring the trays in.
KARIN: Huh?
Oh, sure, Yuzu.
[water flowing]
-[sighs]
D-ah!
Mr. Kurosaki, I didn't
know you were still up.
-Good evening there, Rukia.
How's my idiot son doing?
-He's fine.
Of course, he's still sleeping.
-Ahh, don't worry about him.
It's his own stupid fault he
got beat up by some bullies.
I mean, how pathetic.
They're not even
from his school.
-I'm sorry, Mr. Kurosaki.
I mean, this only
happened because I
got him involved with
those delinquents.
-What are you
talking about, Rukia?
The kid's old enough
to know better.
I'm just glad that you're safe.
[fizzing]
I got it!
-Well, thanks a lot.
ISSHIN: [coughs] Got it.
Hey, Rukia.
It's pretty cold
out there tonight.
So if you're planning to
go somewhere, be careful.
And be sure to bundle up.
-All right.
All right!
-(WHISPERS) OK.
There we go.
[giggles]
That's hard to get
used to, but here I am.
Uh.
Hm.
I decided to say
goodbye to you, Ichigo.
There are actually a
lot of other people
I wanted to say goodbye to as
well, like Tatsuki, Chad, Uryu,
Rukia, and a bunch of others.
But I'd get in trouble if I did.
So I had to choose.
[breathing heavily]
YUZU: Hrm.
-[gasps]
Uh.
Oh, uh, hm.
Oh, I get it now.
I guess Yuzu and Karin wanted
to be close to you tonight.
You haven't been
around much, so they
must have really
missed you a lot.
That's so cute.
They brought their
plates in so they
could have dinner
next to your bed.
Huh?
Wait, I just realized--
your bedroom!
Come to think of it,
this is the first time
I've ever been in your bathroom
by myself since I've known you.
It has your scent.
[soft music]
[sobbing]
Just look at me.
The truth is, I can't
bring myself to do it.
[sobs]
I'm so ashamed of myself.
It's my last moment
with you, and I'm
trying to-- when I
think about it, Ichigo,
there were so many
things I wanted to do.
I wanted to become
a school teacher.
I wanted to become an astronaut.
I wanted to be a baker.
I wanted to go to a
bunch of donut shops
and ask for one of everything.
I even wanted to stop the
ice cream man and truck,
and tell him to give me one
of everything he had as well.
Haah, I wish I could have had
five different lives instead
of one.
Then instead of
one town, I could
have been born to a family
in five different ones.
And each one would have fed me
a lifetime of different foods.
And I would have grown up to
have five different careers.
And in every one
of those lives, I
would have fallen in
love with the same person
five different times.
Thank you, Ichigo.
Goodbye.
[theme music]
WOMAN: Hm.
I'm not getting through.
MAN: Maybe you should get a new
cellphone, like mine, he-he.
It's awesome.
Look, it's got all the
latest bells and whistles.
WOMAN: But it's ugly as hell.
MAN: You're crazy.
And you can download
music on this one.
WOMAN: Oh, really?
How's the reception?
MAN: I have no reception!
WOMAN: Don't talk to me anymore.