[Yuzu]
It's morning!
Rise and shine,
Ichigo!!
Time to get up!!
[yawn]
I'm tired...
Hee hee hee!
Ta-da!
Oh. Today's your first
day of school, right.
Karin, pass
the soy sauce.
Here! Your soy sauce!!
Hey, what're you
so angry about?
I am not angry!
I'm just disappointed that my
stupid big brother doesn't
even notice that I'm wearing
my new school uniform!
Especially when it's my
first day at my new school!
Just for that, I'm not
leaving you the crispy tasty
scorched part of the rice!
Your skirt's unzipped.
Yaah!
Ya see? I noticed.
Dummy! You were born
with a dirty mind!
Ooo!!
Huh?
Yaaaagh!
You wrecked
my glasses!
Hm?! What's up, Karin?
Nothing.
[Isshin]
Yuzu!
Help me out. How's this suit
look on your dear old daddy?!
Which matches better,
this bowtie or this necktie?
Whaddya think?
Hm?
They both look okay.
Doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter?!
Yuzu! Don't be like that
to your dad, C'mon!
Take a look and
help me decide!
Hey, why don'tcha just
wear both? Whatever.
Just "whatever"?!
Augghh!
Later guys.
[Ichigo]
It's been a little over a year,
just seventeen months, since
the battle with Aizen.
Now, I'm in my last
year of high school.
From what I know, Chad and
Orihime told everyone about
my Soul Reaper powers.
And they said everyone believed
them pretty much right away.
Of course, seeing stuff
like that happen right
before your eyes doesn't
leave much room for doubt.
I'm glad that they accepted it
without asking any questions.
Mornin', Ichigo!
So now,
I no longer possess any
of my Soul Reaper powers.
Around the time I lost my
powers, Karin's Spirit Energy
started growing stronger.
Bye, Ichigo!
Have a good day!
Thanks! The same to you.
Nowadays, the high-level
spirit medium abilities of
our family belong to Karin.
I know she's not too thrilled
about it, but she doesn't
come to me for advice.
It seems like she's working
her way through it.
[Ichigo]
Let's go, Mizuiro.
[Mizuiro]
Alright.
I-chi-go!
Yo.
[choke]
Bye! See you guys later.
Oh yeah. I guess we'll
see you at lunch later!
Ichigo! Ichigo dude!
I'm tapping!
I'm tapping ow-out!
Hm!?
Good morning!
Hey.
Ichigo, You bring
that game I lent you?
The new version's coming
out soon, so I need it
back to trade it in.
Yeah. I've got it right here.
Hm?!
What?!
You forgot it?
Shut up!
I said I had it!
Here you go.
[Ichigo]
Ever since I lost my Soul
Reaper powers, my Combat
Pass has also stopped.
The visual barrier is gone,
and the Hollow alarm
doesn't go off anymore.
It's just become nothing
but a piece of wood.
I even forgot that I'd
left it in my school bag.
Still, this carved piece of
wood is the only evidence I have
left of my Soul Reaper past.
[teacher] [distant]
Ishida! Where do you
think you're going?!
[Ishida]
To the nurse's
office, sir!
[Ichigo]
Now it's Uryu who's taken over
exterminating the Hollows
that I used to handle.
We were hoping he could
just let Imoyama do it,
but it's turned out that
Imoyama's a lot less
capable than we expected.
I hope Uryu doesn't
overdo things and upset
the Soul Society.
Speaking of the Soul Society,
Ever since our last goodbye,
Rukia hasn't come to visit
Karakura Town even once.
[Keigo]
So, have you thought about
your plans for the future?
Hnh?
You mean like,
after high school?
Duh!
Sure that's what I mean!
What else is there?
Hm. We still
have some time.
Well y'know after this
semester, we'll start
getting career counseling...
So pretty soon you'll
hafta start thinking
about that stuff.
You had good grades to
start with, but then
you bottomed out.
Stop reminding me.
I had a lot of stuff
going on last year,
it couldn't be helped.
And besides, I'm
still above average.
What about Rukia?
Hnh?
Wonder how she's
doing these days.
Wait, what's Rukia got
to do with anything?
I was just thinkin'.
She could at least
drop by once in awhile,
to say hi to us.
Since she left, she hasn't
dropped by even once to say
"Hello!" That's pretty cold.
She's not being cold.
She got relieved of her
Karakura Town duties.
Her not coming back
here is normal.
Don't you miss her?
Of course I don't miss her.
After sixteen years,
I finally get to live my
life as a normal human.
I hope it stays this
peaceful until I die.
Hm. You've got a
good point there.
I don't wanna go through
really scary stuff like
that ever again, either.
It's true.
Being able to see ghosts
never once made me feel
superior to others.
I never thought of making
a living from it, or using
my unique gift to help
people I didn't know.
All I ever really wanted
was a normal life
without seeing ghosts.
Well, I finally got the
life I wanted, didn't I?
[Kugo]
Hey! Come back here!!
Huh?
Hey!
Drop it, jerk!!
Give me back my bag!!
Hold this.
Sure.
[Ichigo]
Come to think of it,
I'll be back.
Stop!!
Besides my Combat Pass,
there's one more thing that
I still possess, that proves
I was once a Soul Reaper.
The physical training I had
and the reflexes I developed
in order to survive, do come
in handy sometimes.
Whoa!! Man, that was pretty
incredible there, kid!
Thanks pal!
So hey, are
you hungry?
C'mon, I'll buy you some ramen!
That sound good?
No thanks.
I'd rather not get in
any trouble for this.
So do me a favor,
Don't tell anyone
what I did.
Oh? Sure. You got it.
Well, thanks again.
Let's go. We don't
wanna be late.
Hm. How 'bout that.
You're more cautious
than I thought,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
[Rejni]
How long you planning
to sleep Ichigo?!
Do I have to slug you?!
[Byakuya]
Come on, Ichigo Kurosaki.
wake up.
[Rukia]
Ichigo, you fool!
Get up!!
[Isshin]
Goood morniiing, Ichigooo!
Huwaaagh!
Ah-You idiot!!
You really are
an idiot!
I could've fallen all the
way and hit the street!!
You could've killed me!
Whatever.
If you die, you'll go to
the Soul Society, right?
Uh!?
Ohh. Now you're
big-timing me, huh?
Look, you're not going
to die falling from the
second floor, okay?
Uh!?
You woke me up from a
really interesting dream.
So to make it up to me
you should go ahead and fall!
Whoa!! Stop that!
You'll make me fall for
real!! C'mon quit it!
Huh?!
You had a weird dream?
What was it about?
Mh!
[Ichigo]
I can't remember.
Trying to tell you
made me forget.
So? How much then?
Uh, how 'bout five thousand yen?
Five thousand yen per week?!
Get real! Next!
Huagh!
Sir!
I am Satoda, co-captain of
the school's soccer team!
We'd like to offer you--
Just tell me how
much and how long.
Well, we members of the
soccer team have prepared
a budget of two times...
Ichigo!
Huh?
He's talking some business.
So he'll probably be awhile.
Okay, gotcha.
So he's all done
renting himself out to
the basketball team?
This really sucks!
Ichigo's not gonna have
time to hang out with us.
Funny. You make it sound
like he actually ever wanted
to hang out with you.
Whaaat?! Hey, what's
your problem, man?!
I have better stuff to
do than to make a total
nuisance of myself!
By hanging around
bugging Ichigo while
he's working at his part
time jobs all the time!
It's true, so true,
I swear it is!
Whatever...
So what position?
We'd like you to play
as our goalkeeper!
Chad would make a
better goalkeeper.
We talked to Mister Sado,
but he turned us down.
He said he'd found a
better paying job.
[Ichigo]
So then, I'm your
second choice?
So how come I don't
recall Ichigo being this
obsessed about money?
He might be saving up
for after graduation.
Y'know, so he can
go live on his own.
What?!! You mean...
he's moving out?!
Heh... well, I'm not
sure about that.
But if you ask me,
Ichigo's dad doesn't seem like
the type who'd loan Ichigo
money for anything at all.
I'd say it's probably a
good idea for him to save
as much as he can now.
Ah, you just might be
right about that.
[Satoda]
Thank you so much!!
[soccer team member]
We did it!
Yeah!
Great! Let's go tell
the other guys!
[blubbering]
Goal!!
So! The soccer team won out!
How much didja get?
That's personal.
When do you start?
Right about now.
Ichigo?
Hm?
Aren't you doing
basketball?
My contract
ended last week.
What about you, Tatsuku?
You headed home?
I'm off to work.
I thought I told you.
Last month I became
assistant instructor
at my dojo.
Eh? You're the
assistant instructor!?
I'm sure glad I
quit your dojo.
There is no way I could
ever call you Sensei.
How would you like it
if I forced you to call
me that right now?
[humming]
[male student A]
Ohhh, There
goes Orihime.
She's gorgeous.
Like some teen
goddess.
The first time I saw her,
I thought, "Man, am I glad
she's at my high school!"
I got a great shot of her
with my phone the other day.
Really? Send it to me!!
Huh?!
[Orihime]
[giggles]
Tatsuki!
Ichigooo!
Hey! Orihime!
Hnh?!!
You idiot, that's dangerous!
You'll fall!!
We can see
your panties!
Oww!!
You deserved that!
The next time you do
something that dangerous,
I'll hit you even harder!!
Harder than you just did?!?
You'll crack my head open!!
Hey you don't have to
get so angry about it.
I mean, its not like
she hurt herself or
anything--
Just shut up!
You've got no business
lecturing me about the
best way to teach
Orihime a lesson!!
I wasn't lecturing you!
I was saying that I
felt sorry for Orihime!
In my book, I call
that lecturing!!
Uh, the thing is...
Y'see I've really wanted
to ask the two of you for
your advice on something.
"Advice"!?
Yes. It's about...
My life's theme song,
"The Ha-ha-ha-ha Song,"
Where I cheer on comedians
who have the right amount
of popularity,
By matching their names
to the tune of ♪ Do-Re-Mi ,
which I love so much...
"Right amount of
popularity"??
See the problem is,
all I can do lately
is hum it!
[sigh]
Uh, isn't that
a good thing?
Why do you think
that's so?!
It's 'cuz you've
grown up!
That's wrong!
Whoa!! How the hell
did you do that?!
Your eyes look just
like the number 3!
That's funny. She's more
expressive than ever.
The correct answer...
Is right here!
But I don't know whether I
should start at "Do" with
Dokurodan or Doburock!
Which one would
be better?
[both]
It doesn't matter!
Oh! I forgot!
I don't have
time for this!
Oh, where do
you have to go?
To my job!
Aren't you working too?
Better get going.
Boy you sure are busy.
Hang in there.
Just shut up!
Don't act like you're
above it all!
Did you let your boss know
you took another job?
Oh yeah! Your boss is gonna
chew your ass just like the
last time you did this to her.
If you don't give her a
week's notice, don't say I
didn't warn you about what
she's gonna do to you!
Mr. Kurosaki!!
Please join us!
It's time for practice!
Mr. Kurosaki, we should--
Uhh?!
[Ikumi]
You dumb ass!
Mmh.
Do you even realize what
you're asking of me?! Do you?
You took off all last week,
then came into work only
one day after that,
and now you're saying
you want to take off
another week again?!
Yeah. That's why I'm calling
you to apologize for this--
You think an apology makes
it all okay?! Maybe it does
for you but not for me!
You don't give a crap, do you?!
Well get your butt over here
now, or you're fired!!
Hm! So I'm fired?
Well guess I had it coming.
What?!
Hey, no no no no, wait wait,
hold on, dearest Ichigo.
What're you saying to me?
I'm saying I don't blame you
for firing a guy like me who
doesn't take his job seriously.
Sorry for causing you
so much trouble.
And thank you for giving
me the opportunity to
work at your place.
Hey, it hasn't been that long!
It's only been six months!
The real fun of working
here at Odd Jobs Services
is still ahead for you!
Our adventures will go
on for a long time to--
[click]
And so the adventure
comes to an end.
[female student]
Aaahh!
We're here looking for the
guy named Ichigo Kurosaki!
Where is he!!
What's with that guy?
Just what era is he from?
I don't recognize
this guy at all.
Look what he did! He busted
up seven teeth of one of my
homeboys here! Seven!
He must be some
kind of moron!
Normally it's two
teeth at the most!
Ah. Now I get it.
Heh heh!
I know you can
hear me Kurosaki!
You gotta be trembling in
fear out there, wondering
how I was able to find
out your name and all!
You got careless! My boy here
got a good look at your face!
After that, finding you
was a piece of cake!
So here's the deal Kurosaki!
Until you decide to come out
here, me and my boys from
Miyasho High are sealing off
your school gate!
[Uryu]
'Scuse me.
Huh?
Enough with the
outdated scare tactics.
Can't you see you're
making everyone nervous
for no good reason?
Actually, for Kurosaki's
friends, you guys seem
pretty clever.
You understand what I'm
saying, don't'cha boys?
Now hurry along
and go home.
Huh?! What's that?!
Are you Kurosaki?!
What'd you say?!
Augh!
Hey! What the
hell was that?!
You asking for
trouble, ya punk?!
That's exactly what I
was going to ask you.
So you did get a good
look at the guy, right?
What part of me
says "Kurosaki"?!
Did you
find him?
Yeah.
The next Substitute
Soul Reaper.
Seems like an
interesting fellow.
[Orihime]
Tatsuki!
[Tatsuki]
Orihime! People will see your
panties if you run too fast!
[Orihime]
Say, does this look
okay for my lunch?
[Tatsuki]
No! You can't just eat
sweets for lunch!
[Orihime]
There's this two-hour
comedy TV special today
that I want to see.
[Tatsuki]
No! It's bad for your eyes,
so you can only watch TV
for one hour a day!
[Ichigo]
What are you, her mom?