[theme music]
NARRATOR: In his mad quest to
become the most powerful Soul
Reaper, Third Seat Makoto Kubine
took possession of a Bakkoto
from the Kasumioji clan.
Lieutenant Izuru Kira challenged
Makoto in a desperate attempt
to keep him from achieving
his goal of gaining more power
and attacking his
fellow Soul Reapers.
After an intense battle,
Izuru was finally
able to defeat Makoto.
Meanwhile, Ichigo
and his friends,
in an attempt to rescue
Princess Rurichiyo,
entered the Kasumioji palace.
There, they encountered
Toshiro Hitsugaya and squad 10,
who had been waiting for them.
-Go.
Out.
Just leave this place to me.
-Right.
Thanks.
Let's go, Shu.
-Ray over the frosted
heavens, Hyorinmaru!
-Sever, Raika!
NARRATOR: As this
fight continued,
Head Captain Yamamoto was
shown the Bakkoto retrieved
from Makoto Kibune.
Armed with proof of
the Kasumioji treason,
he took immediate action.
-It has been brought
to my attention
possibly acts of trason have
been committed by the Kasumioji
clan.
All 13 court guards
squads are hereby
commanded to occupy
the Kasumioji
grounds to search for
and seize any evidence.
-Won't get by me.
Ha!
-Sorry, guys.
Shu, any idea
where Rurichiyo is?
-Uh-- but I think they might
have taken her to the back
tower.
That was one part of the palace
we were never allowed to visit.
-So, which way?
-That way.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
Where are you, Rurichiyo?
YAMAMOTO: For generations,
to Kasumioji clan
forged heirloom swords
for the royal family
to be used for
ceremonial purposes.
The techniques to make these
swords were kept secret,
and for that reason,
the Kasumioji
have maintained the
right of immunity.
However, certain
factions within the clan
have taken advantage of
this cloak of secrecy
and have broken the taboo
against the production
of forbidden blades, such as
the one you see before us.
Now that we know what
they've been up to,
we must move against the
Kasumioji immediately.
-Head Captain.
Did you expect this
to be uncovered
when the substitute
Soul Reaper went--
-Hm.
I'm assigning Captain
Kuchiki of Squad Six
to lead the raiding party.
-Yes, sir.
[cheering]
-Reporting, sir.
-Hm?
-Head Captain Yamamoto has
given new orders to his troops.
He has directed all
13 court guard squads
to move in and take
control of our clan.
-What?
That bastard.
I knew he was too arrogant.
the one thing I was
worried about the most.
He assured me this
would never happen.
-They won't figure it out
until we're ready to move.
I can absolutely guarantee your
safety in a position of power
once we've taken over.
Now I have no choice but to
use these to protect myself.
RANGIKU: What?
What do you mean a
change of orders?
-Yes ma'am.
We are now being told to
seize the Kasumjioji clan.
-What are you talking about?
That's the opposite of
what we were told before.
-That's the word
from headquarters.
-If that's the case, I guess
we don't have to fight anymore.
-Finally, some good news.
Huh?
-Look out!
He's coming in!
-Who are they?
-They're trained assassins
from Kasumioji clan.
I should've known.
Be careful, Lieutenant.
These men are using a forbidden
blade called the Bakkoto.
-Bakkoto?
RUKIA: It's the
secret the Kasumioji
clan has been protecting.
RANGIKU: Intersting.
Then we can use our
entire arsenal, right?
Growl, Heineko!
I don't understand.
Don't they feel any pain
when they're attacked?
Shuhei!
-The head captain
has given the order
to raid the clan's palace.
From what I heard, the Kasumioji
are accused of treason.
His orders are to assist
the substitute Soul Reaper.
-Step right up.
I'm ready for you.
-Their swords are very unusual.
But not much to look at.
Even with those weapons, you
boys are hardly a match for us.
-Don't let all the
other squads show us up.
Let's prove that Squad
7 has the best fighters.
-Looks like they were
able to make it in time.
-Captain Hitsugaya.
It appears evidence of trason
in the form of forbidden arts
has been found in
the Kasumioji clan.
We've been given orders
to take over immediately.
-Treason?
-I'm glad we're back at the
same side, Captain Hitsugaya.
This could have been unpleasant
-Wait.
Come back.
-Rurichiyo!
Damn.
Just how big is this place?
-It's enormous,
even for a palace.
-We'll have to keep
going until we find her.
-Ichigo!
-Get back, Shu!
What the-- You've
gotta be kidding me.
You mean all their
swords are Bakkotos?
Unbelievable.
Their souls have been
taken over by their swords.
RUKIA: Ichigo.
Hado number 33.
Sokatsui!
-Rukia.
-Renji was able to get the
proof back to headquarters.
The order was given to
raid the Kasumioji clan.
-They're on our side?
-Which means that
bastard Kumoi decided
to arm his men with
his secret weapons.
RUKIA: That's right.
I can't believe they were
able to produce so many
of the Bakkoto.
-Rukia.
You and Shu go on ahead.
The fact that they've chosen
to beef up their defenses
here tells me that something
important must be up ahead.
-You're right.
You keep them busy,
and we'll slip through.
-Come on, Rukia!
We have some
unfinished business.
Now, which one's first?
-Enryu, I can hear the sounds
of fighting in the mansion.
Ichigo and the others must
be taking on Kumoi's army.
Good.
We need to take advantage
of this commotion
to rescue Lady Rurichiyo.
You can feel it,
can't you, Enryu?
The princess is
somewhere nearby.
-Man.
Nobody surrenders.
What's up with these guys?
-No matter what we do to
them, they keep charging us.
We're gonna have to
step up our efforts.
-I can't believe how
they're reacting.
They keep getting back up.
They don't even seem to
care about their own lives.
It's like they're possessed.
-It must be the power of
their swords, the Bakkoto,
or whatever they call them.
-Maybe so, but if they think
that power's going to stop us,
they're sadly mistaken.
-Captain.
What's happening?
-Just what it looks like.
As confusing as
this seems, this was
all part of the
head captain's plan.
-What are you talking about?
-It's the Kaumioji clan.
They're protected by
their aristocracy.
Under ordinary
circumstances, nobody
could interfere with them.
-The head captain had received
information some time ago
that the clan was up
to no good, but he
had no way to go after them.
By chance, Ichigo came along and
got involved in their affairs,
so he used him.
-Without telling him?
-He couldn't take the chance.
It shows how much he trusts
in Ichigo's abilities.
He's a wily old fox.
-Master Kumoi?
Why are you dressed like that?
-Silence.
Man your posts and keep alert.
-Reporting, sir.
The central gate
has been breached,
and the main building is now
occupied by the Soul Reapers.
Fighting is still
going on in the garden,
but we're not going to be able
to hold them back much longer.
-I'm aware of that.
All I need at the moment is for
my forces to buy me some time.
Just a few minutes until I get
inside the Bakkoto workshop.
Then we'll be fine.
-Sir.
The Soul Reapers have broken
into the Bakkoto workshop.
-They what?
That's impossible.
The barrier to that
building was bestowed on us
by the royal family.
It cannot be breached
by a mere Soul Reaper.
[confused mumbling]
MAN: Charge!
[screaming]
-I'm Jushiro
Ukitake of Squad 13.
Everyone remain where you are.
We're going to conduct an
inspection of these premises.
Resistance will be
dealt with severely.
[whimpering]
-Forget it, boys.
All the exits are covered.
The jig's up, fellas.
There's no way out, so you
might as well start talking.
-Sui-Feng.
Fine work back there.
You did a good job breaking
through that barrier.
-Thanks.
But really, it was very strong.
We couldn't have begun to break
through without your insight.
How did you find
the vulnerabilities
in the barrier's
composition that
allowed us to breach
its weaknesses?
-I got a blueprint from a man
who was angry at the Kasumioji
clan for interfering
with his business.
-We're surrounded.
Curse those Soul Reapers.
-Master Kumoi, we have
nowhere else to run.
-I'm aware of that.
The princess!
Go quickly and bring her to me.
We have no options left.
We'll have to use
her as a shield.
[grunting]
-Incredible.
Wait.
Listen, you guys.
You'll die if you keep fighting!
-Huh?
We've reached a dead end.
-I don't get it.
What were all
those guards trying
to protect if
there's nobody here?
-Huh?
What's that?
[mumbling]
SHU: Those girls are
Rurichiyo's attendants!
-They kidnapped her.
Some horrible men took
Lady Rurichiyo away.
-So I was right.
Rurichiyo was here, wasn't she?
-Yes.
She returned a while ago,
and was locked in this wing.
No one was allowed
to speak to her.
-We were told to stay
here and look after her,
but we weren't allowed
to leave, either.
-How were they able
to get out of here?
-They used a secret passageway.
The man standing guard
opened that wall over there.
-A hidden escape route.
It's heading up.
There must be a
hatchway near the roof.
-You're right.
We better move.
Quickly.
[panting]
MAN: Master Kumoi?
-We've been waiting for you.
Where have you
been all this time?
-Everywhere.
There were many things
that required my attention.
-Under the circumstances,
only one thing
should have required
your attention.
Squads from the 13 Court
Guards have stormed the palace.
As of now, they've taken
control of most of the property.
-Is that right?
-You have to diffuse
the situation.
Go to the front lines and
talk to their commanders.
-That would present
quite a problem.
-What?
What kind of problem?
We're not idiots.
We hear stories from the
servants and the soldiers.
Don't you think we
know what you've
been doing behind our backs?
[groan]
[struggling]
MAN: Princess!
MAN: Is she all right?
MAN: The princess!
-What is the meaning
of this outrage, Kumoi?
What have you done
to Lady Rurichiyo?
-Ah!
[gasping]
MAN: Master Kumoi,
what have you done?
-Eliminate them.
MAN: What?
ASSASSIN: Yes, sir.
MAN: No!
No!
[screams]
-Why did you kill those vassals?
-Shut your mouth.
-I am the princess
of this clan, Kumoi.
Do you think I'm going
to stand by and let
you go unpunished for
killing my vassals?
-Silence I'm taking
over this clan.
It's mine.
You, princess, are nothing
more than a mere hostage.
You have no more power.
-And what are you
holding me hostage for?
I can see that you're trembling.
What is it you are so afraid of?
Speak up, you coward!
-Go away, princess!
-How dare you.
I want to know why I'm being
treated in this manner.
Explain yourself.
-Don't you ever stop talking?
Come on.
RUKIA: Ichigo!
-Huh?
Rukia, Shou.
There you are.
-Lady Rurichiyo is
in this building.
-What?
So she was here, after all.
-Yes.
-She was brought up
in this direction
through a secret passage.
-Then she has to be-- there!
Rurichiyo!
-Enough!
Stop mistreating
me this instant!
-Will you shut up?
You seem to forget
that you're my hostage.
You should be thankful
I'm allowing you to live.
-Well, excuse me.
I'm just a mindless hostage.
I have no idea what I
should be thankful for.
-If that's the
case, then perhaps I
should give you a little lesson.
ICHIGO: Get away from her!
-Who said that?
RURICHIYO: Ichigo!
-Sorry I couldn't get
here sooner, Rurichiyo.
-I'm sorry, too.
You're very late.
What took you so long?
I was getting tired of waiting.
As my bodyguard, you
should be more prompt.
-Well, then, don't worry.
I'm here to rescue you now.
-Kill this fool.
-I think not!
-Damn him.
-I'm taking Rurichiyo
back, you traitor.
-Oh, really?
-Lady Rurichiyo!
-Rurichiyo!
-Miss Kuchiki!
And Shu, as well.
KUMOI: Don't you move.
-You bastard.
-Rurichiyo.
-I'll cut her throat if
you attempt to approach.
-Oh, no.
-Damn.
-Tell me something, Kumoi.
Why are you doing all of this?
Why did you even develop
a weapon like the Bakkoto?
-I don't have to explain.
I have my reasons.
-He was planning to use the
Bakkoto to disrupt the Soul
Society, and in the midst
of the chaos that followed,
he was going to grab power as
the leader of the nobility.
-Shut up.
-You are sick.
That's the reason you did
all this to Rurichiyo?
-Eliminate the opposition.
That's one of the primary
rules of achieving victory.
-Unforgivable.
-Fortunately for me, I
don't need your forgiveness,
you half-wit.
-Kumoi, you're delusional.
It's absurd that you aspire
to lead the nobility.
-I will be the most
powerful ruler in history,
and I assure you
nothing will stop me.
I may already be old, but
will still savor my triumph.
-Rurichiyo!
[laughter]
-Stop it!
-Huh?
-It's Captain Amagai.
-I'm surprised you
could find this place.
-Yes.
RUKIA: From what we
can tell, it appears
that Kumoi has
been the mastermind
behind this entire plot.
-So it would seem.
-Captain, are you all right?
-Ichigo!
[scream]
IHCHIGO: Shusuke,
why did you do that?
-Why do you think?
RUKIA: I don't understand.
Now that you've
killed the mastermind,
how are we ever
going to find out
the truth of what
he was planning?
-What truth do you mean?
ICHIGO: What's going on here?
What did you just do?
-You've been most helpful,
Substitute Soul Reaper.
-What do you mean,
I've been helpful?
-Ichigo!
-Rurichiyo!
-See you around.
-I don't get it.
What the hell just
happened here?
-Tell me why-- I
followed orders.
I did everything
you asked of me.
I don't understand.
Why did you betray me?
-Wait a minute.
-Kumoi and Captain Amagai
were working-- it couldn't be.
-Dammit.
What the hell was that?
What's going on?
[theme music]
AMAGAI: Out past the
fields lay darkness.
A life that faded away,
feelings that we're left behind.
Many years have passed
since that moment,
and now I have come
back to this place.