[theme music]
NARRATOR: The final
showdown with the Arrancars
is this winter.
Ichigo, Chad, Uryu,
Rukia, and Orihime
have all been undergoing
intense training,
pushing their
bodies to the limit
to get as strong as possible
with the little time they have.
Meanwhile, Captain Hitsugaya
and his advanced troops
have remained in Karakura Town.
As they prepare for the
inevitable showdown,
they're forced to
battle powerful Hollows.
Then, the situation
takes a dramatic turn.
Several of the Espada
appeared in Karakura Town.
Hitsugaya and this team
confronted the Espada,
but Luppi, the new number
six, released his Zanpakuto
Trepadora, and easily
defeated Hitsugaya.
-But just think.
That attack.
the one you were able
to block just now,
would you be able to stop it if
it were eight times stronger?
-What the-- What is that?
-Rangiku!
-Yumichika!
Damn it.
Let go of me.
NARRATOR: Rangiku and the
others were in great danger.
Then, suddenly, Kisuke
Urahara appeared.
-Well, looks like I
made it just in time.
That was certainly
close, wasn't it?
NARRATOR: Meanwhile, Ichigo
abandoned his Visored training
in order to fight Grimmjow.
And while the battle continued
to unfold across Karakura Town,
Orihime headed to the world of
a living from the Soul Society
to do her part in the fight.
But she was ambushed by someone
unexpected in the Dongai.
-Come with me, little girl.
-Ah.
-Well, you surprised me.
What was that attack just now?
That was a first for me.
-Ah.
Ah.
[wicked laughter]
-I'll tell you what was.
It's called a Bala.
A Bala is a projectile
of spiritual energy.
It's not as strong as a Cero.
Doesn't need the power.
It's 20 times faster.
Hey, what's wrong?
Can you dodge this?
You can't, can you?
Die, die, die, you dumb bastard.
-My, my.
When someone gets
in my way, they die.
I wanted to kill the
guy wearing the hat.
But Yammy is-- Whatever the
case, he's not alive now.
-Well, such is life.
It's time we return
to the task at hand.
Don't you agree, dear?
You really are pathetic.
Even after that
clog-wearing bastard
came along and saved you,
what did you do but get caught
again?
Oh well.
I suppose you can't escape
if it's eight against three.
-Just give it a rest.
-Hm?
-I've heard enough of your crap.
I think you've got a big mouth.
-And what would your point be?
-There's nothing more disgusting
than a man who won't shut up.
Do you ever even
listen to yourself?
-Look, lady.
Have you forgotten that
I have captured you?
You should be aware that if I
get upset, you'll be skewered!
Wha-- what is this?
HITSUGAYA: Huge mistake
to let your guard down.
Against any of your opponents.
Be ready minded, you see.
Always alert.
-You're dead.
You have to be dead.
-Hyorinmaru's power
is without limit.
Hyorinmaru will always reform as
long as there is water around.
It can be reborn a
countless number of times.
You have no chance
of winning now.
I've had too much
time to prepare.
You made a critical
mistake in your strategy.
The fact of the matter
is your resources
are limited and finite.
Your weapon is eight arms.
My weapon is all the
water in the atmosphere.
Sennen Hyoro.
[scream]
-Those eight arms of
yours just weren't
enough to defeat me, Arrancar.
-Captain!
-What the hell just happened?
Did those bastards defeat Luppi?
Moron.
When you underestimate
your enemy, you lose.
Hurry up, or--
-Lord Aizen will
be terribly mad!
-Huh?
-Alive?
But how?
-You're asking if
I'm still alive?
Is that what you want to know?
Well, I'm wondering
about that myself.
-So you're making
fun of me, huh?
I'll show you where
that gets you.
You are powerless against me!
Bala!
Ha ha ha!
Idiot.
Dead and gone.
Huh?
-I know that attack.
I can't get hit by it anymore.
You find all of this
puzzling, don't you?
In your flurry of Bala attacks,
you felt all of them connect.
But I know you're wondering
why it is that I'm still alive.
It's only natural
that you'd be curious.
The answer is right here.
-Huh?
What?
-A portable gigai!
-What are you talking about?
I've never heard of anything
like a portable gigai.
-That's because
I've never shown it
to anyone since I invented it.
-Huh?
-Well, this is a prototype.
Actually, it turns out it's
very difficult to operate.
I don't think that anyone
else aside from me can use it.
It needs to be done right.
And getting the
timing right is hard,
whatever I want it to
take my place for a while.
So, what do you think?
Did I do a good job?
When I switched places just
now, did you suspect I had?
-You'll die!
-You just don't get it.
I can't be hit.
Earlier, I analyzed the reishi
structure of your technique.
I've even analyzed how your
muscles move when you fire it.
So as long as I have
determined these two things,
I can dodge it, and I can even
match your timing in order
to cancel your move
out completely.
Well, it's pretty
difficult to accomplish.
Now then, is it
time to end this?
[crying out]
-Damn.
-Ha ha ha!
Well, it seems you
have a problem.
Once that mask is broken,
you just can't bring it back.
Wait.
You're not gonna try again?
That's crazy.
It seems I was wrong.
But you've either
taken too much damage,
or you've spent all of
your spiritual energy.
Maybe you have a limit as to
how many times you can use it.
It doesn't matter
what the reason is.
That mask isn't here now, is it?
It's a moot point,
whatever the reason.
Don't worry.
because a Cero at close
range will wipe away
that mask wearing head of yours.
-Tsugi no mai.
Hakuren.
Ichigo!
-That's a pretty
incredible move.
When did you--
-Don't speak.
This is tricky.
It's hard enough to
get you free as is.
It's really stuck.
The power that you're
using certainly
seems ridiculous, too.
You're in bad shape.
-Just shut your mouth.
-Ichigo.
Huh?
-Don't underestimate
me, Soul Reaper.
Did you think that
you could kill me
by freezing me under
a thin sheet of ice?
You're an idiot!
-Rukia!
[laughter]
-What was that?
SHINJI: My, oh, my.
I just detest
having to interfere
with another Soul
Reaper's fight.
And yet, I have no choice.
I can't ignore you-- if
you're making so much noise.
-It's Shinji.
-Who the hell are you?
Are you a friend of theirs?
-Do I look like I am?
-Who are you, then?
-Does it really matter?
-No.
You're right.
Whoever you are-- you're dead!
Because I am gonna
rip you to shreds!
[groan]
-If every time I
dodge an attack,
you destroy a building,
I won't be able to dodge,
because I'll just
feel so guilty.
Try to hold back a little
when you're fighting.
-Can't move any
better than that?
Huh?
-He's obviously a
hot-headed one, this guy.
-That mask you have on--
you are one of his friends.
Go on, admit it!
-Don't make me repeat myself.
Does it really matter?
-Huh?
-Sorry, Arrancar.
-It can't be.
SHINJI: You're pretty strong.
So I'm not going to hold back.
-A Cero?
[coughing]
-Damn.
Damn.
Damn!
-So, you countered with
your own Cero right
before it hit to
reduce the damage.
That's pretty good.
-Now grind!
-Huh?
-Ulquiorra?
-Our mission is complete.
We're leaving.
-Our mission's over?
-Huh.
-Negacion.
-How unfortunate, Captain.
You weren't able to
kill me, you see?
Be sure not to forget my face.
When we meet again,
I'll have my revenge.
I will twist off
your little head!
You and I shall meet
again, Soul Reaper.
-Ah.
Ah.
-You said you're going to
finish this, didn't you?
I won't forget that.
I'll be back soon enough.
And the next time we
meet, I will crush you!
-I should've known.
-Captain!
Thank you very much.
-We still haven't defeated them.
It's only going
to become harder.
-Dammit.
-What an inelegant ending.
ULQUIORRA: There are some
traces of spiritual pressure.
It seems that he has
gained a new power.
Still, is that the
best he can do?
It's over.
You have no means
to fight anymore.
The sun has set.
The day is ours.
[theme music]
ORIHIME: There were so
many things I wanted to do.
[sigh] I wish I could have had
five different lives, instead
of one.
Ichigo-- I--