[theme music]
-Now it's Mabashi's spiritual
pressure that's disappeared.
It looks like the enemy is
putting up a good fight.
Why don't you come out?
Quit playing these
hide and seek games.
I much prefer
talking face to face.
-Hmm.
So you knew I was
there, did you?
I tried to copy you and
hide my spiritual presence.
-Haha.
Even if you hid your
spiritual pressure,
there's no way to conceal
your lust for blood.
I can smell it in the air.
-My apologies.
But it has nothing
to do with you.
I was looking for Ichinose.
You don't know
where he is, do you?
-It's hard to say.
Perhaps he's dead.
His spiritual pressure
disappeared quite a while ago,
so I assumed one of your
cohorts had done the deed.
-Ah, I was hoping to
have that honor myself.
But since I can't
have him, I suppose
I'll just make do with you.
You understand.
It's the price you have
to pay for humiliating me.
-If I must, I must.
But don't make the mistake
of underestimating me.
You might just be
in for a surprise,
because I have been given
a very specific job.
To send all the
captains to their grave.
-Baura.
-Hmm.
Oh?
-Boss, is this
our next opponent?
-That's right.
But he's not like the small fry
you've been fighting lately.
This one is a captain of
the 13 Court Guard Squads.
-That's good.
Then perhaps I'll
have fun today.
-So I take it this fish thing
is the doll you control.
-Yes.
This is my doll, Baura.
-Haha.
-What is so funny?
-I beg your pardon.
I was just thinking that
you Bounts are certainly
interesting.
I wonder how much you know.
Are you even aware of the
source of your powers?
They're derived from an
ancient technology that
was developed right here
in the Soul Society.
-And what does this have
to do with anything?
-It was a technology deemed
so dangerous at the time
that it was sealed away
after a single accident.
Such a wasted opportunity.
Even my department of
research and development
doesn't have any
compete data on it.
But here's a thought.
Now that I've met
you, it occurs to me.
How about volunteering
yourself to become
a subject for my research?
-Are you joking?
-To be honest, I never
thought about it before,
because I never found the
Bounts very interesting.
But lately, because of
the Bounts activities,
I've been looking at
a lot of the old data
and it's led me to
think about conducting
my own research on the subject.
Rest assured, I'll do my best to
make it as painless as possible
for you.
And I'll even overlook the fact
that you Bounts humiliated me
by using me to return that
young Quincy's power to him.
-Unfortunately,
I have to refuse.
-Huh?
-The ultimate goal of the
Bounts is the utter destruction
of the Seireitei.
As such, I intend to remove
any who stand in our way.
Baura.
-Yes, Boss.
-Oh well.
It was worth a try.
But in that case, I intent to
make you regret that decision.
-Strong spiritual pressure.
But in the end, it
still won't help you.
-I have read several
reports on you.
And they said that
as a mole-type,
you can only reappear
from large surfaces,
such as the ground or walls.
Such tactics might
have worked against me
in the world of the
living, but here it
makes you quite predictable.
Now, claw out.
Ashisogi Jizo!
Well, bring it on then.
I'm right here.
[deep yell]
-How can this be?
Damn it!
I never heard
about this ability.
[deep yell]
-But you're still
no match for me!
Huh?
-I've got you now!
[yelling]
-You barely escaped that.
-Shut up you.
-Your reports were incomplete.
You should have known that
since we Bounts came to the Soul
Society, we have been
absorbing large quantities
of high quality Reishi, making
us all immeasurably stronger.
Baura is no longer limited to
only appearing in the ground
and in the walls.
Now the sky itself which
is filled with Reishi
is open to Baura's powers.
-So there is nowhere
for you to hide.
-Haha.
You call yourself a captain and
this is all you have to offer?
What a wretch you are.
-I can feel the Soul
Reaper captain's
elevated spiritual pressure.
Is someone fighting
a Bount somewhere?
When the Soul Reapers
turned on each other before,
that was the work
of the Bounts too.
Damn those cursed Bounts.
I only hope my powers hold up.
-Well, well.
You have the nerve to damage me.
-Hmm?
-You have certainly
proven to be an annoyance.
-Well, what an amusing body
you have there, captain.
-Shut your mouth.
I don't need any opinion
from my guinea pigs.
You're nothing but an
experiment gone wrong.
When I get through
dissecting you,
you won't be able
to talk at all!
-Baura!
-Yes, Boss.
[yelling]
-Don't think I'm going to
fall for that trick again.
[yelling]
-I would have brought
Nemu along if I'd
known it was going
to be this way.
She would have made an
excellent decoy for his attacks
and thus saved me
a lot of trouble.
Huh?
How interesting.
He always hides himself
in an alternate space
when he's transporting,
and then reappears right
before he attacks, engulfing
everything around him.
In that case, this
is the perfect spot.
Come on out now and die, Bount.
[explosion]
-I can see you, Bount.
[groan]
-I watched you long enough
to notice the pattern.
Every time you appeared
from an alternated space,
you have to swallow everything
that was in your way.
So I set off explosions
to release this matter
into the air.
Now with so much
floating debris,
I can see all of your movements.
-Release me.
-Haha.
Tear him apart.
Ashisogi Jizo!
It's over now.
[yelling]
-What?
-That was unexpected.
It appears I didn't
stab you deep enough.
-You are mad.
-No matter.
From what I've
seen, it shouldn't
be that difficult to
finish you off later.
Oh, wait.
I can't finish you
off if I intend
to keep you for experiments.
I can come close,
but I have to keep
you at least partially alive.
-Haha.
How confident you are.
-Why shouldn't I be?
-So soon you've forgotten.
Everything in this world is made
of Reishi, and because of that,
we Bounts are invincible here.
-This power again.
That Quincy had the same
ability to control Reishi.
-By absorbing high quality
Reishi in this way,
we Bounts are able to
quickly heal our wounds.
So as a result, it doesn't
matter how many times
you are able to
strike at me which
your attacks, because
sooner or later,
you will run out
of spirit energy
and end up lying on the ground.
Huh?
What is this?
I can't move my arm.
[yelling]
-Who's the one that's going
to end up lying on the ground?
[yelling]
-Ashisogi Jizo has a
nasty habit of paralyzing
the limbs of anyone it cuts.
Although I'm sure
you've noticed by now,
it leaves the pain
receptors and their signals
to the brain fully intact.
Movement is the only
element it takes away.
[yelling]
-Unlike in case of
normal paralysis,
the pain never does go away.
-Boss.
-You hold still.
This is good.
Thanks to you, I now know
Ashisogi Jizo's power
is highly effective
against Bounts,
which means it doesn't
matter how well you
recover by absorbing Reishi.
I will still have
superior power.
[yelling]
-Isn't it rewarding to
have made a new discovery.
However, we'll have to
continue this study back
at my research facility
-Baura.
-Boss.
-It is useless to keep trying.
-Do it.
-Yes, Boss.
[yelling]
-Huh?
What the?
-Hmm?
He has vanished.
But Ashisogi Jizo's
paralyzing effect
won't wear off no
matter how much distance
he puts between us.
You should know better than to
think you can ever get away.
-Boss.
Are you all right?
-Don't worry about me.
I just absorbed a
large amount of Reishi.
So these wounds will soon heal.
But the paralyzing
effect of his Zanpakutou
has not lessened at all.
Damn that Soul Reaper.
I'm I can't afford
to end it here.
Baura, counter attack.
-Yes, Boss.
-I will kill you, Soul Reaper.
All right then.
We'll wait here.
It shouldn't take long
for him to come after me
once he senses my
spiritual pressure.
-In fact, I'm here already.
-Huh?
-What took you so long?
-How did you-- how'd
you get here so fast?
-Most disconcerting, isn't it?
I was going to finish
this all at once as soon
as you appeared, but as it
turns out, I'm glad I held back.
It's given me a chance to watch
and study you a little bit
longer.
-But how did know
where I would appear?
-My, my.
Aren't we full of
questions today?
But I suppose there's
no harm in telling you
since you'll be
dead soon anyway.
I received a detailed
report concerning
your battle with the
lieutenant of Squad 10.
She mentioned that she
had been able to track you
during the fight by using
the Kakushitsuijaku.
Therefore, because I had
your spiritual pressure data,
I knew I too would
be able to find you,
even if you hid in
an alternate space.
And then, I learned that
the human, Ichigo Kurosaki,
had been chasing you
using a Mod-Soul, which
could sense Bounts
spiritual pressure.
And so, I used
the same principle
and created this
tracking device.
-Incredible.
-Haha.
Isn't it though?
Of course, a device like
this is only as good
as the data one has
to input into it.
As a result, I can't
use it to discern
the locations of any
of the other Bounts.
Only your data
has been inputted.
It was difficult
to get information
from the group that returned
from the world of the living.
It was only in our
last battle that I
was able to make the
final adjustments
to your spiritual
pressure record.
-Then you have been targeting
me from the very beginning.
-Did you think it was
just a coincidence
that you met me here
in the Seiretei as wide
as this place is?
By the way your body has aged
after absorbing so many souls,
I'd say you're the
perfect research subject.
-You're quite mad.
-Anyway, that's enough
talk for one day.
If you'll be so kind as to
accompany me to my research
lab now.
No doubt there is
a great deal more
I can learn about
the Bounts once I
begin dissecting your body.
Running away is pointless.
Now that I have your
complete spiritual pressure
data recorded, you're
as good as mine.
[laughing]
-Is that what you
think, Soul Reaper?
You're the one who is mine.
-Huh?
-Baura!
-Yes Boss.
-What the?
-This is the combined
spirit energy
I've absorbed from all the Soul
Reapers who have attacked me up
to now.
[blasts]
-Huh?
[yelling]
[explosion]
-What the hell?
Ah!
I didn't think it
could move this fast.
-Baura!
-I got him!
-Ah!
[yelling]
-Do you feel that?
-Yes.
It's a Bount!
Someone is battling with a
Bount and it's somewhere close!
-Tell me.
-There!
Up there on that big tower!
-Senzaikyuu, huh?
Right.
Let's go.
[groaning]
-All we're doing now is
trading blows back and forth.
-You disgusting Bount.
-I'm ready for your
tricks this time.
I'm going to finish you off
before you can inject yourself
with that drug again.
Go get him Baura.
-Yes Boss.
-How annoying.
As a research subject,
you may be more trouble
than you're worth.
So I'll make you pay!
Bankai!
-Now what?
-Konjiki Ashisogi Jizo!
Konjiki Ashisogi Jizo
creates a poison.
It uses my actual
blood and turns it
into a deadly mist,
which it then scatters.
There is no place to run.
-A mist of poison.
[sprays poison]
-Baura!
Suck in that poison!
-Yes, Boss.
-Baura, I'm going to temporarily
give you all my spirit energy.
-All right.
I'm ready to suck
everything in, Boss.
-Still trying to win?
I have been graciously
offering to keep
you alive as an experimental
subject, but I give up!
I shall take pleasure
in watching you die!
-No, this cannot be the end.
I refuse to go out this way.
I broke the laws of my tribe.
I devoured tens of
thousands of human souls.
I watched as my body aged
prematurely as a result.
Despite all of that,
I never stopped
trying to consume souls.
I did it to increase my power.
I did all these
things for the goal
of becoming the Bounts' leader.
Me, not Kariya!
[groaning]
-I am the one most
worthy of leading them.
It should always
have been my role!
[yelling]
-We shall see.
Attack, Konjiki Ashisogi Jizo!
[yelling]
-Haha!
Die!
[explosion]
-That's Konjiki Ashisogi Jizo.
-So much for them, but someone's
having a serious fight.
[groaning]
-Didn't I tell you there was no
where you could hide from me?
-Baura!
Baura!
[groaning]
[gagging]
-It seems that although you may
have had the necessary ambition
to become the
Bounts' leader, you
was sadly lacking when
it came to the ability.
-Spare me and I will
tell you everything.
-Oh my.
How pathetic.
-Help me!
-Unfortunately, I find I'm
no longer interested in you.
So.
-Help me!
Oh no!
-My my.
The poison had already spread
throughout his entire body.
Oh well.
It appears the whole thing
was a waste of my time.
And since I've used up all
the Hojiku-Zai I had with me.
I suppose I had better return
to the research development now.
-So this is all there is?
Haven't you got anyone
worth fighting around here?
-Get her!
-Neider!
-Leave them to me!
-Ah!
-Huh?
Huh.
So the Quincy boy has returned.
[theme music]
-Uryu, sorry to interrupt
you while you're fighting,
but could you do
something about uniform?
-What are you talking about?
There's nothing wrong with this.
This is the ancient
Quincy uniform.
Wearing this makes me a
part of a glorious history.
Don't you understand
how fabulous it is?
-I'm trying, but it's hard.
[theme music]
-Shinigami Soul Reapers.
-Golden!
-Captain Hitsugaya!
-Izuru?
-Reports say that the
Bounts have already
invaded the Seiretei.
I need to know where
the captain wants
squad three to be positioned.
-Oh, well I guess I must have
forgotten to contact you.
-Damn, Matsumoto.
This is not good.
Anyway, as for you, take
the third squad and guard
the Hakuto Gate, Izuru.
Understood?
-Understood.
There aren't any other squads
you're forgetting, are there?
-Oh, of course not, Captain!