[theme song]
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN): Red
patrol, to the east sector!
Blue patrol, you search
the northwest sector!
Green patrol, head south!
Now go!
Report any sightings
of the Ryoka intruders!
Capture them at all costs!
GUARD 1 (OFFSCREEN): How
could those damn Ryoka
have disappeared so fast?
GUARD 2 (OFFSCREEN):
Never mind how.
Let's get moving!
We've gotta find them
before the other patrols do!
GUARD 1: Follow me!
This way!
GUARD 2 (OFFSCREEN,
DOUBTFULLY): Are you sure?
Idiot!
It's a dead end!
GUARD 1 (OFFSCREEN): Hey,
who you calling an idiot?
GUARD 2 (OFFSCREEN):
What do you expect,
a medal for leading
us down a blind alley?
GUARD 1 (OFFSCREEN): Oh, like
you have any better ideas!
If you're so smart
then why did you
follow me in the first place?
GUARD 3 (OFFSCREEN): Oh, just
shut up and keep looking,
both of you!
GUARD 4 (OFFSCREEN): Get moving!
Come on!
GUARD 2 (OFFSCREEN): Come on!
Everybody!
Forward!
Let's go!
GUARD 3 (OFFSCREEN): Up!
Up!
MALE SPEAKER 2 (OFFSCREEN):
Attention, please.
The search for--
-Hey, you!
You're in the way!
Move it!
-Oh!
Forgive me!
Uh-- Oooh!
-Stupid [inaudible] peon!
Take your menial
chores someplace else!
-I'm just trying not to spill!
Hoo hoo hoo!
MALE SPEAKER 2
(OFFSCREEN): Effective
immediately, Squad Six's new
perimeter is West Sector.
-Whew!
Hello there, Rukia!
I've brought you your lunch!
Are you awake?
I don't see you!
Are you in there?
FEMALE VOICE (OFFSCREEN):
Who goes there?
Squad Four?
-Yes.
I'm Hanataro, the caretaker
for Rukia Kuchiki.
I've brought her lunch.
Where is she?
-Rukia Kuchiki has
already been transferred
to the repentant cell
to await her execution.
-[gasping] But--
But I was just--
-Hm?
What's the matter?
You got a problem?
-No, I just wasn't expecting it.
-In any case, you shouldn't be
here during the intruder alert,
understand?
Return to your
squad, immediately.
-Oh, Rukia.
-I wonder what that
strange light in the sky
could have been.
Behind these walls, I can't
feel any spirit energy at all.
Ichigo, could it be
that you're really here?
-You talk as if this
battle is already over,
but you haven't even caught
a glimpse of my skills.
yet.
Get ready, Ikkaku,
because this time
it'll be you who finds he
can't hold onto his sword.
-If only your talents
were as well-developed
as your boasting, newbie.
Your arrogance is
just a cheap disguise.
Too slow!
What was that you were
saying before, you amateur?
Did you really think you could
make me lose grip of my sword?
-If I'm so slow, then
how did that happen?
-Just a fluke.
And it won't happen again.
-Your predictions are even
shakier than your fighting
ability.
-You're still not
fast enough to beat--
-You're lucky!
-Hey, what's wrong?
What happened to all
that big talk of yours?
Hozukimaru can
transform at will.
I guess you really aren't
in my league after all.
-I'll admit, it took me a little
while, but I've got it now.
I finally have your attack
completely figured out.
-(THINKING) Impossible!
He took Hozukimaru
with his bare hand!
-Heh.
-Hey, this way, Kenny!
They're right up ahead!
-They'd better be.
We've been running for a while
now without seeing a thing.
-Oh, don't worry!
My super-sharp intuition
never lets me down!
Turn right!
Right here!
-Oh, super-sharp, eh?
It's a dead end!
-Oh, whoopsie, wait a minute!
I meant to say it's that way!
-(DEADPAN SARCASM) That's
some intuition you've got.
I'm beginning to wonder
how reliable it really is.
-Wow.
Get back, Orihime.
-No sign of the
Ryoka in this sector.
-Damn!
Where did they disappear to?
-It looks like our arrival
has caused quite a commotion.
It's going to be almost
impossible for us to meet up
with Ichigo and the
others with so many guards
out looking for us.
Maybe instead of risking
capture you and I
should just start looking
for Rukia on our own.
Or we could start a fight
and hope Ichigo shows up.
I don't know.
What do you think, Orihime?
Orihime!
Where are you?
Great.
Where did she disappear to?
ORIHIME (FAR
OFFSCREEN): Uryu, help!
They're after me!
Help!
[crying]
GUARDS (OFFSCREEN):
There she is!
Get her!
She's getting away!
This way!
Run!
-What did you do, Orihime?
-I'm sorry!
I just went down that alley
to take a look around,
and a bunch of them spotted me!
-At least you settled on a plan.
Now I'm going to
have to fight them.
-I'll stand and fight with you!
-No, just go and hide
and leave this to me.
-Attack!
-We got 'em now!
-Let's go!
C'mon, c'mon!
-Boy, there sure are a
lot of them, aren't there?
-Yeah.
GUARD (OFFSCREEN):
There they are!
C'mon!
GUARD (OFFSCREEN):
We've got you now!
-Now there are even more!
What do you think?
Do you have a strategy?
-I do-- run!
-What is that?
(THINKING) I know.
It must be Ichigo.
-What's wrong with you, Ikkaku?
You look like you've just
seen a ghost or something.
I hope you haven't lost the
will to fight all of a sudden.
But if you won't attack, I will.
I'll tell you one
more time, Ikkaku--
the one who's not going to
be able to hold their weapon
is you!
-(THINKING) This can't be!
I guess you think it's over, but
you're dead wrong, my friend.
It won't be over as long
as I can hold my sword.
You really want to end this?
[laughing maniacally]
-'Cause the only way I'll put
down my sword is if you cut off
my arm!
-Don't make me do this.
-You don't have
the stomach for it?
-Why don't you just face the
fact that this fight is over?
You can't win, and you
know it, so give it up!
-No chance, greenhorn.
This battle isn't over yet.
And it's not going to be
until one of us is dead.
-You're too slow!
-Maybe you are strong.
I'll give you that.
Not so lucky after all.
-This wasn't a lucky day
for either one of us,
if you ask me.
-Where'd that guy go?
-When are you going to
stop running from me?
-Just as soon as
you surrender to me.
-This is getting so tiresome.
I think I'll just end it.
It won't require much, just
one stroke of my Fuji Kujaku.
-End it, huh?
If that's what you want.
I could show you
a trick of my own!
-What is this, some
kind of poison gas?
Augh, my eyes!
It's burning my beautiful eyes!
-You like that?
Isn't it wonderful?
The one and only original
Kukaku brand Chili Pepper Smoke
Bomb with bloody tears effect!
Hey, wait a minute,
what's going on here?
My eyes are starting
to hurt, too!
-Now it's burning my throat!
-Some powerful stuff, huh?
-Powerful, and stupid!
I can't believe you
actually blasted yourself
with your own toxic smoke bomb!
-That's OK.
I can take it.
-I'd kill you if
I could see you.
-You know, somehow, that's
not very scary right now.
-Whoa!
-Hey, let go of
me, you big leech!
-Oh, right, so I could
fall to my death?
I don't think so.
-How come-- how come
I'm still alive?
-ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): I
see you're finally awake.
Hey.
-Ichigo!
What are you doing?
Why are you still here?
-Well, I learned something.
I learned that a Zanpakuto
goes right back to normal
just as soon as its
owner passes out.
-My Hozukimaru!
Give it back to me!
-Come on, relax.
I'm not going to
take it from you.
I only used its ointment
to stop the bleeding.
Unfortunately, between
both our injuries
I had to use it all up.
I have to admit, though, that's
some pretty amazing ointment
you have!
-You bastard!
You had no right to do that!
-Are you kidding?
Sure it's all gone now,
but it saved your life.
-That's exactly the point!
-Huh?
-Don't you see?
Now you've denied me
the glory of death
after being so
thoroughly defeated.
How can I possibly live on
now, in such humiliation?
Dammit, Ichigo, if
I could get up now,
I would beat you
to a bloody pulp!
-What an idiot.
Obviously, I shouldn't
even have bothered
saving your life
in the first place.
But, whether you
appreciate it or not
doesn't really matter to me.
I just need some
answers from you.
-Oh, I should have known there
was something more to this.
I am unlucky.
So what is it you want from me?
You want to know my birthday?
-I want Rukia Kuchiki.
Where is she?
-Let go of me!
I can't hold us both up!
Let go!
Then at least one
of us will live!
-No!
Believe me, there's no fate
worse than falling in there.
We've both got to hang on!
YUMICHIKA (MEMORY
VOICEOVER): These days,
those who fall into this
pit can never get out.
-I can't-- hold on-- anymore!
I don't want to die!
Urgh!
Holy crap!
This place smells like a dump!
Wait, it is a dump!
Hey, I thought you
said falling in here
was the worst fate that
could happen to someone!
-Goes to show you, you can't
believe everything you hear.
Regardless of that,
how dare you plunge me
into a disgusting pit like this!
You'll pay!
-Dumbass!
You fell in here
all on your own!
-Shut up!
-Don't tell me we're
back to running again!
-Rukia?
Right.
Yes, I know about
that capital offender.
What do you want with
someone like that?
-We're here to save her.
-What the--?
Do you mean a rescue?
How many of you are there here?
-I'll check over here.
IKKAKU (VOICEOVER):
I mean, for something
like that there must be at
least nine or 10 of you, right?
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): No,
five humans and one animal.
-Five humans and an animal?
And you seriously intend
to rescue her with so few?
-That's right!
You'll never pull off a suicide
mission like that, you idiot!
What, are your real goals
stupid or something?
Agh!
I laughed so hard I
opened my wound again!
Dammit that hurts!
-And he's telling me
I'm the stupid one?
-Yeeaugh.
All right, listen.
If you go directly
south from here,
you'll come to the stations
for the 13 court guards squads.
-So, you are willing to
give me the information?
-Just shut up and listen
before I change my mind.
Off by itself at the far west
end of all the squad stations,
you'll see a tall white tower.
That's where the
prisoner is being held.
-What?
Are you sure?
-Now you're doubting me?
I have no interest in
the success or failure
of your rescue.
Save the girl if you want.
I don't care about
it either way.
But, if you stay
here any longer I
guarantee you other soul
reapers will find you.
So go if you're going.
-Right.
Thank you.
I owe you for this, Ikkaku.
-Don't go getting
sentimental on me.
It's annoying.
Just a minute.
Can I ask you a question?
-Hm?
-Who's the strongest
member of your group?
-Well, that would be me.
-If so, then I suggest
you keep an eye out
for my captain, Ichigo.
The captain has no
interest in fighting
against weak opponents.
If it's true that you are
the strongest, then it's you
he will come after.
-He's that good?
-You'll find out when you meet.
That is, if you can somehow
manage to stay alive
long enough after he finds
you to take his measure.
-Tell me what his name is.
Captain of Squad
Eleven, Kenpachi Zaraki.
-Crap.
It's another dead end, Yachiru!
-Hey, I'm only the
passenger here!
I can't help it if your
sense of direction stinks!
-Don't get smart.
We only came this way
because I believed
in your so-called intuition.
Let's keep moving.
-Aye-aye, sir!
[theme song]
URYU (VOICEOVER): Absolutely
no sense of fashion.
It really bothers me.
Do you mean these soul
reapers are actually
happy with their look?
I can't understand it!
That's why I've always
despised soul reapers!
-Uryu, Are the soul reaper
are still your enemies--
-Because of their clothes?