[theme music]
-This is Ulquiorra.
Permission to enter.
-Welcome, Ulquiorra and Yammy.
It won't be long now.
-What's the status
of the Hogyoku?
-50%.
It is going to awaken exactly
when the Soul Society expects
it to.
But there's a secret.
A secret that only
those who have actually
possessed the
hogyoku are aware of.
I have my doubt that even Kisuke
Urahara, the man who originally
developed it, has the slightest
clue about this unusual secret.
When the Hogyoku, in a dormant
state with its seal removed,
is joined with someone who
possesses twice the spirit
energy of a captain,
for a very short time,
its full power is
suddenly released,
as if the Hogyoku were
completely awakened once again.
Can you tell me your
name, new comrade?
-Wonderweiss.
Wonderweiss Margela.
-Do you remember the
order that I gave you
approximately one
month ago, Ulquiorra?
-Yes.
-It is time to carry it out.
I will even give you a choice.
And take whomever
you like with you.
-Thank you, sir.
-Oh, by the way, would you
like to go as well?
Grimmjow?
-Ki-ya!
LOVE: You're already dead.
Whoa.
That's such a deep
line, isn't it?
Here he's telling these
guys they're dead,
but they don't even have
enough sense to realize it yet.
Don't you realize it yet?
You are alive.
Alive, yet you are already dead.
You get me?
-That's the fifth time
you've quoted that.
I'm so sick of you, love.
And will you please stop
reading all of my comic books
before I get the chance?
You keep spoiling
everything for me.
-Why don't you put up a
fight, you stupid idiot?
Do you have any
idea how many times
I could've killed you already?
I get it.
You thought Soul Reapers had
extra lives or something,
that they have the ability
to keep coming back
to live over and over again.
Well, they don't, dumb ass!
-Shut up.
-Chow time!
Get your butts over
here on the double.
The last one in line
has to do the dishes.
You hear me?
-Huh?
SHINJI: So, how's Ichigo's
training going, Hiyori?
-Weren't you watching?
It's not going anywhere.
The idiot's still only up
to a little over 10 seconds.
That dumb ass is a joke.
Real dog meat.
-Maybe he doesn't
have what it takes.
Maybe he should just give up.
-Shut the hell up,
you little pervert.
You're not even
involved in my training,
so I would appreciate it if
you kept your mouth shut.
-I'm already involved, moron.
I lent you my dirty
magazine to get your mind
off training the other day.
-You didn't lend me anything.
Why the hell would I wanna
borrow that crap anyway?
-It's totally cool.
I borrow it myself.
Every couple of days or so.
-I'm not like you, am I?
-Personally, I like to
look at them twice a day
to clear my mind.
-Yeah, I know.
Good for you, but I'm
not like either of you.
Those pictures are distracting.
-But I am not a pervert!
I'm just very
curious, that's all.
-Isn't that the definition
of a pervert, huh?
-That doesn't stop
you from constantly
looking at my magazines.
MAN: I do not.
-I saw you reading
it this morning.
SHINJI (VOICEOVER): A
little over 10 seconds?
After one month.
I guess it's just going
to take more time.
The Hogyoku wakes at
the end of December.
We've got two more months.
So little time.
We have to hurry.
-There you are.
What are you doing here?
-Oh, hi, how are you, Shuhei?
I was just taking a break
to watch the ladies train.
Take a look.
They're in the middle of
preparing for the winter
showdown.
-Hold it, that's Rukia and
one of the humans, isn't it?
-Do you know that girl?
-It looks like Orihime Inoue.
-All right, then.
Hado 33, Sokatsui!
-Interesting.
Looks like they might be
enjoying their training
a little too much.
-Oh, you picked up
on that too, huh?
-Huh?
-Sorry to bother
you, Captain Ukitake,
but I have a personal
request to ask of you.
-A personal request?
What is it you want, exactly?
I want you to authorize the
opening of the training ground
behind the barracks for my use.
-Open the training ground?
What do you need it for?
-Sir, a friend and
I would like to use
it to train in preparation
for the showdown
this upcoming winter.
-Who is that?
-Oh, Captain Ukitake.
I'm glad you're here.
I've brought you Orihime Inoue.
-What are you talking about,
you armpit-smelling monkey?
I'm the one who brought her
over here and you know it.
-Don't lie, you
little booger eater!
Anyhow, Captain Ukitake,
would you like more tea?
-Hey!
No fair.
We made a deal that
we would figure out
who gets to pour him tea by
playing Rock, Paper, Scissors.
-Whoever makes the
first move wins.
-I'm sorry.
Sorry for the sudden request.
I know that I came
here uninvited.
-Orihime.
This is not the
time to be timid.
It's imperative that we're
ready for the final showdown
against Captain Aizen.
As long as we have
somebody with powers,
it doesn't matter if they're
a Soul Reaper or a human.
I mean it.
At a time like this, I would
even accept help from Chappi.
(HIGH PITCHED)
I'll do what I can.
-Rukia.
You really don't have to
bring things down to my level.
-Listen to me.
We need to start training!
-Yes.
Yes, sorry.
You're right.
RUKIA: It's fine, as
long as you understand.
Let's do our best, Orihime.
ORIHIME: OK.
-I was surprised
when she showed up
one day with that desperate
look and asked me to open up
the training grounds
behind the barracks.
But I'm happy for her.
She found a friend.
-I don't know.
Even if that friend's a human?
-You shouldn't talk like that.
-Please, forgive me.
-No.
It's OK.
Even if they live in
completely different worlds,
friendship's always
a fine thing to have.
And you know, Orihime and
her friends are unusual.
Maybe they'll even
become soul Reapers
after they've passed
on to the Soul Society.
-Hado 33.
Sokatsui!
-Santen Kesshun!
-I'm not finished yet!
-Koten Zanshun!
-Don't hesitate.
If you're indecisive,
you can't hope to win.
-OK.
-Hado 4.
Byakurai!
-Santen Kesshun!
-So, tell me.
What did you come
here for anyway?
Was there, um, something
that you wanted?
-Oh, yeah.
That's right.
It's this month's
Seireitei bulletin.
The mail order catalog's inside.
-What the-- What are
you doing with this?
-It's chaos around here.
Squad 10 is still on assignment
in the world of the living,
Squad 11's captain
won't wake up,
and I don't know where
the Lieutenant is.
And all of the members of
Squad 12 are still in the lab.
They won't come out.
I guess it never
really occurred to me
for just how difficult a
captain's duties truly are.
When Captain Tosen
was in charge,
I don't remember him asking
his subordinates for any help.
Well, I guess I'd better
get back to my duties.
-No, no.
Don't be in such a hurry.
You should stay
awhile and relax.
-Sorry, I can't.
I still have a
lot of work to do.
Although I wouldn't mind
watching those two girls
train for a while longer.
Maybe later, when I have
a little more free time.
UKITAKE (VOICEOVER):
Four months, huh?
Not much time to mend
the heart, is it?
Much less to build strength.
If only this fleeting peace
could last a little longer.
[shouting]
-Damn it, damn it,
damn it, damn it.
Break, break,
break, break, break.
Take this!
And this!
I hate you, I hate you, I
hate you, I hate you, damn it.
Damn it, break.
Ah!
Break, break, break, break--
-Shut up!
What is wrong with
you, anyway, Yumichika?
-My Fuji Kujaku is
totally ticking me off.
He's such an obnoxious
snob, and he's bossy,
and he thinks that he's the best
looking guy in the whole world.
I hate him, I hate
him, I hate him!
I can never fight
next to him again.
In fact, if he were the
last sword in this world,
you couldn't pay me to
fight alongside this jerk.
Not ever.
Even if he begged me.
-What are you talking about?
He's exactly like you.
-Argh.
-Now, my Heineko is a stupid,
needy, selfish, temperamental,
lazy, and moody slob,
which, when you boil it
down to basics, makes
her the total opposite
of my personality.
-Yeah, well I think
that's you to a T.
I bet you're the
kind of person who,
whenever she looks at a
picture of herself, says,
oh, look at me, I am so fat.
-What did you say, Yumichika?
I dare you to say
that once more!
-Argh!
Will you two just shut the
hell up and concentrate?
Or I'll send you back
to the Soul Society.
Honestly.
Can't they at least talk to
their swords more quietly?
-The clouds are moving.
-Hm?
I'm sorry.
Did you say something, Ikkaku?
-Never mind.
Forget it.
It's nothing.
-Arrancars?
Already?
They're a little
early, aren't they?
-Yes.
They're definitely early.
But there's no time for us to
sit around and figure out why.
-Oh.
It looks like we picked
a good spot to show up.
There are some guys with
pretty high spiritual pressures
down there.
Wanna start with them?
-Take a good, long look.
Those are Soul Reapers, Yammy.
I wonder what
they're doing here.
Maybe they're reinforcements
from the Soul Society
that Mr. Six told us about.
Right?
Oh.
Sorry.
Of course I mean the former six.
-The guy that I'm
looking to kill.
He's not even down
there with them.
-Hey.
Wait, Grimmjow.
Damn.
That idiot.
-Don't bother about him.
He's not even an Espada anymore.
He's worthless.
-Ugh.
The guy I wanna to kill's
not down there either.
-Who do you mean?
The guy who chopped
your arm off,
or the guy who kicked your butt?
Or the one who
deflected your Cero.
With you, there are always so
many enemies to choose from.
-I want all of them.
Hey.
Let's get going, rookie.
Don't just stand there
drooling like that.
-Ah.
Ah.
-Ugh.
Just what we need.
Another freak to join the team.
-I think I've got it!
I've got some kind
of reaction here.
-What about the Gentei Kaijo?
-It's been authorized.
-The reaction.
What color is it?
-It's crimson.
They're Espadas!
-I'm Squad 10 captain,
Toshiro Hitsugaya.
-That's quite a coincidence.
I'm also a 10.
Arrancar 10, better
known as Yammy.
-You're number 10?
Then that means that
you are an Espada.
-Yeah.
You seem to know about us.
It seems that you've
been fighting somebody
who obviously has a big mouth.
-I take it you're an Espada too.
-That's right.
My name is Luppi.
I'm ranked number six.
-Huh?
-Can I-- can I cut that one?
[groaning]
ICHIGO: Let go of me.
-No.
You're not ready yet.
-This is exactly why your
friends from the Soul Society
are stationed here in
the world of the living.
So why don't you just
let them handle it?
-Well, this just happens
to be exactly what I've
been training for, dammit!
Look, this is now
or never for me.
-Just let him go.
-Hey!
Are you nuts, or something?
Shinji!
-Rukia!
-Yes, sir.
I just received the report on
the Espadas' recent activity.
-The Kido Corps are working
on opening up the gate.
-Go to the Senkaimon in
front of the barracks.
-Yes, sir!
-Wait, Rukia!
I'll go with you.
RUKIA: No, Orihime.
You don't have a hell butterfly.
If you try to pass through
the Senkaimon with me,
you'll end up in the Dongai,
the border between the world
of the living and
the Soul Society.
-I just ordered the outer
wall to be stabilized,
so you'll be able to pass
through the Dongai safely.
It will take a little
time, but now you
can return to the
world of the living.
I know you're in a hurry,
but you have to stay calm.
Understand?
-Yes, sir.
-Don't make that face, Orihime.
I'll be waiting for
you on the other side.
This isn't right.
It's too soon for the
Espadas to show up.
The Hokyoku wasn't supposed
to awaken until the winter.
What's happening?
-Hey.
I've been looking
for you, Soul Reaper.
-And I've been waiting for you.
It's taken me some
time, but now I'm
ready to show you
what I've learned
since the last time we met!
Bankai!
-Bankai, huh?
So, what?
Maybe you've forgotten.
Your Bankai couldn't
stop me, or do anything
to slow me down the
first time we met.
-Well, maybe you're the
one who's forgotten.
It was my Bankai attack that
originally gave you that scar.
I've got a question
for you, Grimmjow.
What happened to
that arm of yours?
-Oh, I got rid of it.
Because I'm only going to
need one arm to kill you.
-Is that right?
Then in that case, I guess
I don't need to hold back.
-If you do, then
you'll just die faster!
-I know I can Hollowfied
for exactly 11 seconds.
I'll finish him by then!
-No way.
Forget it.
You can't come with me.
You've used up too much
energy, so I'll go,
and you stay here and rest.
Understand?
-I can't.
-Yes, that's right.
It's just as Renji
explained to you.
But it seems to me you're
nearly exhausted as well, Renji.
Both of you, stay here and rest.
Instead...
I'll go.
[theme music]
RENJI: Are you really
sure I don't have to go?
URAHARA: You don't have to.
Instead, organize the
merchandise that I purchased.
RENJI: You don't mean all those
things you bought, do you?
URAHARA: Kurodo, Noba, help him.
KURODO: Leave it to me!
NOBA: No problem.
URAHARA: Well, I'm off.
RENJI: Nice getaway.