THEME SONG: [sung in japanese]
-[gasping] What the
hell is going on?
Ganju, I'm talking to you.
-Sis, I'm so sorry.
-Huh?
-It's just that I
only showed him once.
I never thought it would
turn out like this.
His spirit energy is strong,
but he's out of control.
-[gasping] Urgh!
Urgh!
Ah!
-Hee.
-I did it.
-Eh.
Great.
You did it, Ichigo.
-Yeah.
-You ignorant dumb ass!
Ya gotta stay focused.
-Ah!
-What are you, freagin
death or freagin stupid?
-Eh.
-Remember I told you if
you don't concentrate,
you're going to blow up.
-Yes.
Yes, you did.
-Next time, just be
sure not to do this.
-Ah!
-You're as guilty
as he is, schmuck.
-Ah-oh.
-Ah.
Why do you always have to
treat me the same as him?
After all, I'm your brother.
-You quit your whining.
-Yoruichi, you're back.
-So our Ichigo has
finally succeeded
in forming a cannonball, has he?
-[snoring]
-What's wrong?
-Nothing's wrong with him.
He's just sleeping it off.
I need the rest of you
to go and sit over there.
-Um.
-Ah.
-We haven't got much time
before we begin our mission.
I'm going to tell you now
what you can expect once we're
inside the Seireitei, and
you must remember that-- yah!
-The fate of three sparrows.
The fate of four dragons.
The fate of the four
dragons enclosed
on five sides unable
to return six leagues.
1,000 sprinkles of ashes.
[sighing] A thousand
pieces of wisdom.
The knowledge of the ages.
-Yow, man.
Holy crap.
[gasping] What was I
dreaming about just now?
-How the hell would I
know that, you moron?
-I hate when I forget my dreams.
Have I been here long?
What am I doing sleeping
here on the floor?
-Like I just said,
stupid, I don't know.
-What's with all that
chanting I heard you doing?
-None of your business,
dandelion head.
Now, why don't you
just shut the hell up?
-Watch it!
Huh?
-Oh.
I see you're awake.
Come on.
It's time for us
to get out of here.
-Hm?
We're leaving now?
-Very well.
Are we all here now?
-(TOGETHER) Yes, sir.
-Hm?
But what happened to
your tail, Yoruichi?
It looks like one of those
flexible toothbrushes.
-M-m.
-Ah.
-What do you mean?
Is there something
wrong with it?
-Yeah-- Eh, no.
Nothing.
It's a perfectly
wonderful, beautiful tail.
-Don't you remember?
You're the one that
actually did that?
-Huh?
I did?
-After you created that
cannonball, you fell asleep
and grabbed Mr. Yoruichi's tail.
It took the three of
us to get you to let go
and by then it was too late.
-M- m- my tail.
My pride and joy, ruined!
-(TOGETHER) Oh.
-I highly recommend avoiding
that subject from now on.
-Yeah.
Got it.
-Hey, wait.
Why isn't Ganju here
with the rest of you?
-Hm?
Last time I saw him
he was downstairs
muttering some
nonsense to himself.
-Never fear.
Ganju is here.
[gasping] You should know.
There hero Is always the last
one to make his entrance.
-OK.
But what's with that outfit?
-Heh, heh.
You like it, huh?
This is my custom battle custom.
It's pretty sweet, right?
Save your breath because
I'm not lending it to you.
Don't even ask.
-Oh, I'm crushed to hear that.
Hey, wait.
What battle?
You're not coming.
-Hm.
-M-m.
-My big brother was
killed by a Soul Reaper.
-(TOGETHER) [gasping]
-Ganju, don't you dare.
-Why don't you
just listen and let
me talk for a change, sister?
-Huh?
-My brother, he was
a brilliant man.
He passed the Soul
Reaper Academy entrance
exam on his first try.
At that time, his spiritual
power was at sixth class.
That's the same level as a
lieutenant of the 13 Court
Guard Squads.
Then he finished his sixth
year curriculum in one year,
and he became a
member of a squad.
In just five years, he
became a lieutenant.
But he was betrayed
by his comrades.
His own Soul Reaper allies
led him to his grave.
I was still just
a kid back then,
so I don't remember all the
details of what happened.
But there are two things
I'll never forget.
Faces.
Those two faces.
The cruel face of
that Soul Reaper as he
dragged my brother's
mangled body back home,
and the face of my
dear, dying brother
happily giving thanks to
that same Soul Reaper.
Why did he do that?
Why would my brother
be so forgiving?
To this day, I just don't know.
But there's one thing
I do know for certain,
somehow my brother never
blamed the Soul Reapers,
and he never hated them.
-All this time he's kept
this pain bottled up inside.
-But how?
Why didn't he hate the fiends
who completely destroyed him?
Why did he continue believing
in them to the bitter end?
Somehow you seem different
from the other Soul Reapers.
-I owe her.
-Ah.
You see, she saved my life,
and I haven't repaid her yet.
I don't want to turn into
some kind of deplorable guy
who had just turned
his back on her.
Understand?
-That's what I think.
I think that's what
makes you different,
and I think if I go
with you, I might
discover something important.
That's why I've decided
I'm going to help you.
I'm willing to go along with
you into the heart of enemy
territory and try to learn
what being a Soul Reaper
really means.
-Oh, Ganju.
-That's so noble.
What a guy.
-Oh, Ganju.
-Such a fine man you've become.
-Huh, huh.
Well it sounds like you've got
your mind made up about this.
-You and me then.
-You and me.
-All right, then.
Are you all ready
for the cannonball?
-(TOGETHER) Yes.
-Hey, I just thought
of something.
-Hm?
-Do you know how to
make a cannonball?
-Actually, that's
a good question.
I guess I ought
to give it a try.
-(TOGETHER) Hm?
-Don't tell me this
is your first attempt?
-Put that down on
the floor, Ichigo.
-(TOGETHER) Ah!
-Hm.
Just as I suspected.
The task was as natural
as breathing in and out.
-Wow, Yoruichi.
In one try, you did something
that took us forever to learn.
[laughter]
-I can see it bothers
you, but I don't
know why you find
it so surprising.
You'll learn that
there are many things
I can do that are far
beyond your reach.
-Hey, Ganju.
Were you able to
master it as well?
-I think so.
-Then we'll use flower crane
cannon launch method number 2.
All right?
-Very well.
-You better not chicken
out and run away
in the middle of the
launch, you little brat.
-I would never do that.
-Huh.
Not afraid to lay
your life on the line?
-No.
No way.
-If you're all ready to go, then
the final countdown begins now.
Get inside, everyone.
The sun will be rising soon.
That will be the signal to
begin the launch ceremony.
-Now, listen.
Once we're inside
the Seireitei, it's
important we stick together.
If you should encounter any
captains, don't fight them.
Don't even think about it.
Just run.
Our goal is to save Rukia.
Do you understand?
You must avoid taking
any unnecessary risks.
-Ah!
Far away.
Copper colored green desires
the domination of 36 degrees.
-Now, it has begun.
Pour your spirit
energies into the center.
-72 pairs of legends.
13 pairs of horns.
The right paw of the
monkey captures a star.
Embraced by the 25 wheels of
the sun, the cradle of sand
will flow with blood.
Flower crane cannon number
2, Kakisaki Blossom!
-The launch is a success.
You've done it
again, Master Kukaku!
-May the fates
smile on you, Ganju.
-Oh, wow.
Somehow I thought blast off
would be more explosive.
-That was only the
start, you simpleton.
-(TOGETHER) Whoa!
-Huh.
-What is that thing?
-These are the directions for
the next stage of the launch.
The first stage of flower
crane cannon number 2
was just the blast
off itself and
the initial directional setting.
Now, we go to the
secondary spell,
which controls the acceleration
and axis adjustment.
This will help with
the precision guidance.
-Ah.
-Right.
So stay out of my way if
you want to land safely.
-All right.
I will.
-Now, there's just
one more thing
I have to explain to you all.
In order to enter the
Seireitei successfully,
we have to stabilize
this cannonball.
That requires keeping
the spirit energy output
from each one of us
at a constant level,
and to do that, keep your hands
on the crystal in the center
so that you'll be able to see
how much energy the others are
releasing and then
simply adjust your energy
release accordingly.
-(TOGETHER) Hm.
-One mistake and that's it.
We'll all die.
-M-hm.
-I understand.
-I got it.
-Now, flower crane
cannon number 2 begins.
The fate of three sparrows.
The fate of four dragons.
Five sides unable to
return six leagues.
Winds of heaven.
Orangutan.
Spoon.
Elm.
Cane.
-Ichigo, I think you're
releasing too much energy.
-You really think I am?
All right, then.
I'll back off.
Whew.
-Ichigo, you've got to
lower it a little bit more.
-What?
Are you kidding me?
But I've already lowered
my output by almost half.
-Ichigo.
-All right.
All right.
I'm working on it.
-A thousand sprinkles of ashes.
-You've got to
lower your energy.
-A thousand pieces of wisdom.
-I know.
I know.
-The knowledge of the ages.
A thousand sprinkles of--
-There.
I've turned it down
almost all the way.
-Ah.
Would you shut up!
You and your big mouth made
me repeat the same line twice.
-Don't blame me just
because you can't
remember your
stupid little chant.
-That stupid little chant
might save your precious life
if you could just
shut your big yap!
-Err.
-Cut it out, you two.
This is no time to
be arguing about who
did what when we're
all in danger.
-She's right.
Stop this.
They're going to upset the
balance of the spirit energy.
-I'll show you who
needs to shut up!
-Hey, look.
What's that?
-ICHIGO (OFFSCREN) Er.
-It's the Seireitei.
-What's happening?
VOICE OVER INTERCOM
(OFFSCREEN): Red.
Alert.
Red alert.
The Seireitei has been breached.
All squads report to battle
stations immediately.
Repeat.
This is a red alert.
All squads report--
-Intruders in the Seireitei?
-Do you think it could be
those same Ryoka from before?
VOICE OVER INTERCOM
(OFFSCREEN): Red alert.
Red alert.
The Seireitei security
has been breached.
-Huh?
Wait, Kenpachi.
-Where are you going?
-[chuckling] Keni, wait up.
-Yachiru.
-Eh.
So you're off to
kill the intruders?
-You've certainly
got that right.
I'm off to battle
some strange Ryoka who
went up against Ichimaru
and somehow survived.
Let's get the carving
started. [slurping]
-This is most unfortunate,
but such a major disruption
leaves me with no
choice in the matter.
This squad captain meeting
is hereby dismissed.
I shall inform you
later as to how
Ichimaru will be dealt with.
All squads are to heed the
alert and report immediately
to their battle stations.
-Saved by the security alert.
Convenient timing, eh, Ichimaru?
Why don't you just
come out and say it?
You're not making much sense.
You don't really think you'll
get away with this, do you?
Just remember, don't
underestimate me, Ichimaru.
-Uh.
-What the hell is that up there?
-Whatever it is, the Soul
Shield Membrane should stop it.
-Just in case, we probably
ought to clear the area.
-I think it's
headed right for us.
-Run!
-We're going to crash.
-The only way to
survive this is for you
to pour in all the
spirit energy you've got.
-(TOGETHER) [grunting]
-It hit the membrane.
-Yes.
And it looks like it's
being held there somehow.
-How could it have
crashed into the membrane
and yet not have been destroyed?
It would take a body of
unimaginable spirit power
to survive.
-Push through!
-(TOGETHER) Ugh.
Ah.
-Ah.
-[gasping]
-What's going on?
We blasted through the
shield, but we're not
falling to the ground.
We're just floating here.
-Don't get separated.
The cannonball was
destroyed by the shield,
but its residual
energy will still
hold us up until it dissolves.
-And what happens then?
-It will coalesce
into a whirlpool
then explode and vanish.
-Uh.
-We must stick together, because
anyone who gets separated
will be blown away
by the explosion.
-(TOGETHER) Uh!
Uh!
-We're in the whirlpool.
-Ooh!
No.
Not a chance.
I'm not about to get blown away.
Uh.
-Ah!
-What are you doing?
-Stay away from me.
-Get out of my way, you.
-You big luger.
Don't you to drag
me down with you.
-Will you too cut
it out already?
This is ridiculous.
-Grab the person closest
to you and hold on tight.
Then don't let go,
no matter what.
-Great.
-What do you mean
by that, dandelion?
-Ah.
-Eh.
I'll sit here on your shoulder.
-Sure.
No problem.
-Ah.
-Uryu.
-Oh.
Oh.
-What are you doing?
-Ah!
Why did you do that?
-Oh, Chad, no.
-You'll be blown away.
-No need to worry.
I can almost promise you
the Chad will survive.
But if you want to be able
to reunite with him down
on the surface, I
suggest you worry
about ensuring your
own survival first.
-C-- c-- come on!
-Grab on to me.
-Brahimi!
-Damn.
The intruders have
split into four.
Which one is he?
Which one is the strongest?
That's the one I have to find.
THEME SONG: [sung in japanese]
-What's going on?
I'll go and take a look,
but my Zabimaru is gone.
Do you know where
it is, Hinamori?
-I think I saw someone
using it to slice up
some pickled radish.
-Roar, my Zabimaru.
Chop up that radish.
-Your character seems to
have changed a lot lately.