[theme music]
NARRATOR: Patros, the
Arrancar, reveals his disdain
for Sosuke Aizen for making
himself ruler of the Hollows,
so he stole the Hogyoku and left
Hueco Mundo with two Arrancars
that he persuaded to join him.
In the world of the
living, they searched
for someone who knew
how to use the Hogyoku.
They sought out Kisuke
and attacked his shop,
hoping to find him.
Then, a fierce battle
broke out with Renji,
who was left in charge
of Urahara's shop.
-Apparently you didn't
understand what I said.
So let's up the ante.
Level two!
Not bad, but it's still
just the beginning.
[footsteps]
-Shatter, Kyoka Suigetsu.
GIN: What an elaborate scheme
you cooked up, Captain Aizen.
AIZEN: Gin.
-Even if they did collaborate
and were obviously up
to no good, making them believe
that they had killed Ulquiorra,
and letting them
take the Hogyoku.
There was no need to do this
in such a roundabout way.
You should have
just had Ulquiorra
kill them immediately.
What were you thinking?
-Don't worry about Ulquiorra.
I have something else
I need him to do.
-If you prefer, I would be
happy to kill them for you
if you just give the word.
-Thanks for the offer,
but that would be boring.
-Oh.
-What are you doing, Ururu?
-Jinta Home Run!
-Jinta!
-I'm getting very
tired of waiting.
When will a person who knows
about the Hodyoku return?
This whole thing is
beginning to bore me.
-The owner of the
shop will come back
when you're dead,
you filthy Arrancar.
-Renji.
-Moocher, good.
Are you all right?
-Ha.
Relatively speaking.
-You again.
Oh, well, I guess this time I'll
just have to finish the job.
-You two, go and get Kisuke now.
-No, we can't!
-I said go!
-If you say so.
-All right.
We better go, Jinta.
-Damn.
Don't die, moocher, all right?
-Thank you for sending
them off to find
the person with the
information I need.
Now only one question remains.
Will you be alive to greet them?
Time for level three.
-Ah, shut up.
You keep going up one
little level at a time.
What's the matter, tough guy?
You act like you have all
the time in the world.
You're sadly mistaken.
Gentei Kaijo!
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru.
-Oh ho.
I haven't seen a
Bankai in a while.
-Roar!
Zabimaru!
Hi-yah!
-Not possible.
-OK, get up.
Unless you're already dead.
-This is a very interesting
shop you have here.
-I'm glad you like it.
We don't have to
hold back out here.
let's go.
-Captain.
-You're already out of breath?
-Shut up.
-Honestly.
You guys defeated
five Arrancars?
Boy.
How pathetic!
-Rangiku!
-Come on, come on, come on.
What's wrong?
Can't take it?
-Rain over the frosted
heavens, Hyorinmaru!
I can't waste anymore
time on an Arrancar
that's not even an Espada.
-Don't get too cocky
with your weak attack.
-No matter how many
times you keep trying,
you still can't defeat me!
-I wouldn't brag if I were you.
Your only attack is hurling
yourself at your enemy.
How truly pathetic.
-Get ready.
I'm blowing you away next.
IKKAKU: Don't turn
your back on me!
Huh?
IKKAKU: I'm your opponent!
-You can't get through.
-And for the record,
I just got through.
-Let's try level 10.
[scream]
-What is this?
-Heh.
I haven't even gotten
serious with you yet.
If this is all you've
got on level 10,
you're not really as
strong as you say, are you?
-Lowly little soul reaper.
Don't get carried
away with yourself.
You might be under
the impression
that you're a worthy
opponent, but we've
been wiping out Soul
Reapers like you
since long before you were born.
Despite that, we allowed
someone like him.
-Yeah?
Despite what?
Go on.
-Nothing.
It's of no concern to your kind.
-But apart from that,
you said something
earlier that I find it
difficult to ignore.
-What would that be?
-You called me a
lowly Soul Reaper.
Don't underestimate us.
We Soul Reapers
are very powerful.
-Fine, then.
Out of respect for
your fearlessness
in the face of death,
I'll reward you
by showing you my
most powerful form.
Defile, Gerifalte!
This is my maximum level.
-I fell asleep!
-Ririn, rather than
falling asleep,
I think the correct term
is losing consciousness.
-Shut up!
Renji.
Has he already been defeated?
-Now, now.
Such negative thinking
won't get us anywhere.
-I sense spiritual pressure
coming from the basement.
Let's go.
-What?
We're going there?
-Of course we are.
-My apologies.
I simply can't control my own
strength when I'm in this form.
-What are you talking about?
-Meaning my next blow
will be my most powerful.
Sorry to end the fun so soon.
-Bring it on, then.
-Here I come, Soul Reaper.
URURU: Please hurry.
CHAD: How's Renji?
-He'll be all right.
He won't be defeated
that easily.
-I'm more worried about
the store than the moocher.
-Ah!
-You sacrificed your own
weapon to protect yourself.
-That's right.
It's not over yet.
-So it seems.
So it seems.
-Whoa.
-Renji.
-He can't go on much longer.
-I want to ask you one thing.
-What is it?
-What do you plan to
do with the Hogyoku?
-Control the whole world.
RENJI: You mean the Arrancars
are rebelling against Aizen?
-Ha!
We don't accept
him as our leader.
-Oh, really?
You're saying you're not
totally united under him?
-Are you kidding?
A lowly Soul Reaper
must never be
allowed to become the
ruler of Hueco Mundo.
What happened to you?
-Shut your mouth.
Forget me.
-Our pursuers will
be here any minute.
Did you find out how
to use the Hogyoku?
-Pursuers?
-You don't know yet?
-Know what?
-You've been wasting your
time on someone like this?
Impossible.
No.
It can't--
[scream]
-This is terrible.
Patros, I wish I never took you
up on your-- on your-- offer.
-You monster.
You knew you were
sacrificing them, didn't you?
-Yes.
Sadly, it couldn't be helped.
Besides, anyone who could
be beaten by a Soul Reaper
wouldn't have been any help
in furthering my goals.
-You're sick.
-I did it all for the Hogyoku.
And to defeat Aizen.
Consequently, I cannot and
will not lose to you here.
-The same goes for me, so we'll
just have to fight it out now.
-Let's finish this.
-OK.
Let's go.
Now roar, Zabimaru!
RIRIN (VOICEOVER): Oh, no!
[scream]
RENJI: Damn!
-I should commend you.
Because of your efforts, I
have slightly more respect
for Soul Reapers.
But I think we've now
reached the end of the line.
-It won't be that easy.
-I believe there are times
when one must accept defeat.
Any last words?
None, huh?
So be it.
Huh?
-Roar, Zabimaru!
-Another illusion?
-This isn't only an illusion!
-Damn you!
[laughter]
-You dare to mock me?
-Renji!
Are you OK?
-You followed me again?
You guys shouldn't
be messing with him.
-Well, we can't leave
you alone, either.
-Would you go away?
-Here!
-You weaklings are in my way!
-Ah!
-Heh.
-You idiots.
I thought I told you
to get out of here.
-Don't you worry.
We're fine.
And guess what?
I think I found his weakness.
Wait and see.
-What is it?
-Kurodo.
Noba.
You know what to do.
-Right.
-Got it.
-Oh, my hip!
-Renji, the three
of us are gonna
go out there and distract him.
And then you can hit him
with a really big attack.
-No.
Don't!
Even the three of you
are no match for him.
-Quiet.
You have to understand,
we're modified
souls that were originally
created for battle.
We can't quit just because
we're up against an opponent
that we can't defeat.
And besides, Renji, you can't
just let it all end like this,
can you?
-Fine.
Do what you have to.
And try not to die.
-Right.
-What's wrong?
How long are you
going to stay hidden?
RIRIN: We're not really hiding.
-Huh?
-We see right
through your attacks.
-Heh.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
I was wondering who
was interfering,
but it was just some
small fry using illusions.
-Hey!
Who you callin' a small fry?
At least I don't just use
the same stupid attack
over and over again
the way you do.
-What?
-I told you!
We can see right through
that attack of yours.
You better use something else,
if you really want to win.
-Ha!
If you're going to stand
there and challenge me,
I guess I have no choice
but to eliminate you.
-He fell for it.
Here I go!
Ha!
-So stupid.
Burst, Gerifalte!
-No!
-Fools.
What?
Impossible.
RIRIN: What do you think?
You're the only
one who can fight?
You're the foolish one!
Whenever you draw your
sword, you immediately
put it back into its sheath.
We knew that you storing
energy in your sheath
and using your sword as a
trigger to release that energy.
As as long as you're unable
to put away your sword,
then there's no way
you can attack us.
And not only that,
we also noticed
the larger your movements
were, the stronger your attacks
became.
Struggle all you want, but as
long as we keep your sword away
from your sheath, we
can avoid your attacks.
Renji!
Do it now!
-OK!
-Huh?
-Hikotsu Taiho!
-Dammit.
It can't end like this!
-Ririn!
-Yes, you did it!
Renji-- Kisuke?
-Well, hello there.
I'm sorry I'm late.
-Kisuke, what the--
-Hey, I just made it back here.
How's it goin'?
-Ah!
-Kurodo.
Noba.
-Nice.
I'm very proud of
the job you guys did.
-I was nothing.
We just got beat up
a little, that's all.
-Noba.
We got beat up a lot.
-Renji, are you all right?
-Captain Hitsugaya.
Yes.
We're fine.
-Oh, my.
It looks like you had
some trouble too, huh?
-Where's the enemy.
-It seems they're dead.
Aizen was toying with them.
-Aizen?
What do you mean?
-Is that the Hogyoku
they brought with them
from Hueco Mundo?
-What happened?
-Aizen probably let
them have a fake.
But I was the one who
originally made the device,
so you could believe
me when I tell you
it wouldn't break that easily.
I'm guessing that Aizen
probably tricked them.
Most likely with
his Kyoka Suigetsu.
There's no way
that could happen.
Aizen would never allow them
to steal the Hogyoku from him
so easily.
-But he did allow them
to take a fake one.
Why would you do that?
-I'm not sure that
we'll ever find out.
Why have you come here?
To fight us?
-I have no intention
of fighting any of you.
KISUKE: Maybe Aizen was
after something else,
and he needed these Arrancars
to create a distraction
so that he and his cohorts
wouldn't get caught themselves.
Otherwise there wouldn't
be a need for someone
to follow them back here
to the world of the living.
He knew that he would
have taken care of them
one way or another.
Purging his ranks of dissidents
in a little act like this
would prove more entertaining.
That's just the type of
man he is, I suppose.
-Well?
-There are traces of
that past incident.
At the time, most of it
was just simple guesswork.
But upon further
investigation, I've
deciphered the basis behind
her actual abilities.
-So what do you think?
-I think she possesses a
power that you can definitely
benefit from.
-I see.
So, where is she right now?
-I'm not sure, but
she's probably not
in the world of the living.
-Good work, Ulquiorra.
-My please.
[theme music]
MAN: Hiyori, how long can
Ichigo maintain Hollowfication?
HIYORI: He just
reached double digits.
MAN: Ah.
He finally surpassed 10 minutes.
HIYORI: No, dumbass.
He's still at 10 seconds.
MAN: Is that all?
Why didn't you just say so?
ICHIGO: Hey, I'm at 11 seconds!
MAN: It doesn't matter.
ICHIGO: It does!