[theme music]
NARRATOR: Lieutenant Izuru Kira
obtained a forbidden Bakkoto
that provided proof of the
Kasumioji Clan's treason.
The 13 Court Guard Squads then
stormed the Kasumioji palace
and overcame their assassins.
Gyokaku Kumoi took Princess
Rurichiyo hostage and attempted
to escape, but he was cut
down by Shusuke Amagai
in a surprising blow.
Shusuke later
revealed that he was
the mastermind of
the Kasumioji treason
and had been directing Kumoi
from within the Seireitei.
He had been plotting the
assassination of Head Captain
Yamamoto for years to avenge
the death of his father.
His plan was to create such
a diversion that all Soul
Reapers would be
distracted during the raid
of the Kasumioji
Clan, and Yamamoto
would be left unprotected.
Shusuke first used to
the power of the Bakkoto
to neutralize the Head
Captain's Ryujin Jakka
and then released his Zanpakuto
to carry out his revenge,
but his attack was
blocked by Ichigo
who raced to the scene
thanks to a message
left by Kenryu, Rukia,
and Princess Rurichiyo.
-My time is now!
I will avenge my father!
Stay out of my way, Ichigo!
Enough!
-Knock it off!
I've been here the
whole time, and I
heard all of your completely
self-centered nonsense.
Get your revenge, but
leave her out of it.
Don't involve other
people in your business!
-You just don't get it.
You cannot save her.
Don't act like an idiot!
Move it!
-I don't think you
understand what's going on.
You say you want me to move?
Well, you're going to
have to make me do it!
[wind blowing]
-Ichigo.
-Rukia, take care of Rurichiyo.
-Right, I'm on it.
-Ichigo!
Your curiosity will
be your undoing.
I presume this means
you refuse to back down.
-Hmm!
Bankai!
-How useless!
-Haaaa!
I thought I told you
my Bakkoto seals away
the spirit energy
of Soul Reapers
and the power of
their Zanpakuto,
therefore your attacks
are no match against me.
Leave the princess
behind and be gone.
-Just forget it.
I'm not handing over Rurichiyo.
-You don't seem to understand.
It doesn't matter.
Whatever you do, the
princess's fate is sealed.
-How dare you!
-There's no way she
can escape death.
It's the curse of being born
into the Kasumioji Clan.
-Not happening!
-There's no way you'll
be able to win this, not
with your weak swordplay.
Haaaaa!
-Getsuga, ha!
Tensho!
Damn it!
AMAGAI (VOICEOVER):
What's going on?
My Bakkoto should have sealed
away his spirit energy.
But his technique
is still strong,
even though he's
lost some power.
Raika!
Sorry, but this fight has
dragged on long enough.
Haaaa!
I'm not done yet.
-I think you're over confident.
-Think again.
Haaaa!
-Ahhhh!
-Ichigo!
-Sorry to make you wait.
Now it's your
turn, Head Captain.
ICHIGO: Is that all
you've got for me?
-Huh?
-I'm just getting started.
-You're a fool.
-Yeah?
I thought you said you
sealed my Zanpakuto.
Well, here's a surprise.
I still have plenty of
energy left for you.
-You're all talk.
If you'd had the sense
to stay down quietly,
your life would
have been spared.
-Shut up!
-If that's how you
want it, you leave
me no choice,
Substitute Soul Reaper.
Haaaaa!
You expect to defeat me by
skipping and jumping around
like this?
AMAGAI (VOICEOVER): Incredible.
How can he be exposed
to the power my Bakkoto
and still have this much speed?
[grunting]
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
Ichigo should be affected
by the power of that Bakkoto,
but instead his power
is increasing.
What's happening?
AMAGAI (VOICEOVER): He
uses his spirit energy
to reduce the damage
from my attacks.
-[laughing] What's the matter?
-Ichigo, what's the
point of you fighting me?
What do you gain from it?
-I don't know what
you're talking about.
-Why would someone from
the World of the Living
put so much effort into risking
their own life for this?
Why involve yourself
in a fight that
only affects the Soul Society?
-None of that makes
any difference.
I'm here to protect Rurichiyo.
That's a commitment I made.
-That's ridiculous.
You're telling me you're
prepared to throw away
your life for a
complete stranger.
-Captain Amagai's spiritual
pressure is rising.
He's about to attack.
-If that's all
your life is worth,
Substitute Soul
Reaper-- then die!
-Kenryu!
Enryu!
Where is Ichigo?
-So much for that.
ICHIGO: So much for what?
-Huh?
-The fight's just begun.
-What's the meaning
that mask, and how
did his spiritual
pressure become so strong?
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
Hollowfication.
I knew it!
AMAGAI (VOICEOVER): He's fast!
AMAGAI (VOICEOVER):
His power is different.
It's stronger and more brutal!
--[laughing] You're
quite surprising.
[wind blowing]
-Ahhh!
Don't underestimate me!
Ahhhh!
I see now.
That's the Hollowfication I've
heard so many stories about.
My Bakkoto is powerful.
It suppresses a Soul
Reaper's spirit energy,
and in the process renders
their Zanpakuto powerless.
But you have the power of a
Hollow, and that's different.
AMAGAI (VOICEOVER): It
was because of this power
that you were able to
defeat all other Bakkotos up
to this point.
That power is more
savage and elemental.
-Of course.
That's why Ichigo
wasn't hindered
by Captain Amagai's Bakkoto.
And now, by completely
Hollowfying,
he's been able to reduce
the effects of that Bakkoto
even further.
He's leveled the playing field.
Right now Ichigo is more
than a match for him.
-I'll just have to
find your weakness,
and then eliminate you.
-What is your problem?
Why are you so obsessed
with your revenge?
-I sincerely doubt
you'd understand.
AMAGAI (VOICEOVER): The
emptiness of being left behind.
The hatred you feel
toward those who remain.
The power of these
emotions become
so strong you find them more
and more difficult to resist,
until your life is
controlled by them.
You always have just
one thing on your mind.
Revenge.
You ask yourself what
am I doing with my life?
But no matter how much you
struggle toward the light,
the voice in your head plunges
you back into darkness.
It says the only way to
find peace in your heart
is to destroy the lives
that destroyed yours.
And so finally,
you're committed.
It becomes your life's goal.
No force in the universe can
remove you from your path.
ICHIGO: Are you that weak?
Huh?
You possess the ability to
rise to the rank of Soul Reaper
Captain, so why can't
you find strength
to move past this
obsession with vengeance?
-If I could find a way
to have my revenge,
I don't mind dying
in the effort.
That has always
been my strength!
Ahhhhh!
Haaaa!
Tell me, why are you so
protective of that mask?
-Ichigo!
-I'm not going to be
defeated that easily!
[gasping]
-You bastard!
-You're never going to win.
I'll take you down with me.
They won't find a trace
of you when I'm done.
I'm going to completely
incinerate you!
Haaaaa!
Ha!
Goen Ryuga!
[rumbling]
-What's happening?
-Ichigo!
-Ahhh!
-[gasping]
-Ichigo!
-Lady Rurichiyo!
-Ichigio, you have
to stop fighting.
You have done enough.
I do not want anyone else
to get hurt because of me.
I can't live with it.
-(WEAKLY) Don't
worry, Rurichiyo.
Uh!
In a few more minutes, I'll
make it so you can rest easy.
You'll never had to worry
about that problem ever again.
-You're still coming at me?
-You're damn right.
-Hmm.
-Yaaa!
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): What
are you doing, Ichigo?
From the intensity
of your attack,
I presume you're
trying to prevent him
from firing his weapon, but
he still has plenty of energy.
How long can you keep it up?
AMAGAI (VOICEOVER): Why
is he so persistent?
-I see what he's trying to do.
Captain Amagai's weak
spot i on his right side.
If he can find a way to
get past that huge weapon,
he can attack Shusuke directly
and target his Bakkoto.
-I already figured out
what your strategy was.
You were trying to
destroy my Bakkoto.
-Getsuga Tensho!
-Ahh!
Ahhhhhh!
-Lady Rurichiyo!
Where's the princess?
-Oh, no!
Are the two of you all right?
-Don't worry about us, my Lady.
We'll be fine--
ICHIGO: Rukia!
We're not out of the woods yet.
[rumbling]
-He survived that?
It can't be.
-I knew it was too
early to celebrate.
-This will not be over until
I've achieved my revenge.
Shigekuni Genryusai Yamamoto,
Rurichiyo Kasumioji,
and you, Ichigo Kurosaki, I
swear I will not be stopped.
I'm sending all of you to hell!
-Forget it, Shusuke.
You're in no condition to
carry out your threats.
-Don't be so sure.
You see, I've dedicated myself
to complete this vendetta.
Beyond that is death!
Yaaaaaa!
-What is that?
-[laughing]
[theme music]
RURICHIYO (VOICEOVER):
That mask!
So Ichigo was no
ordinary soul Reaper.
KENRYU (VOICEOVER): That's
right, Lady Rurichiyo.
The truth is Ichigo Kurosaki
is a Mod Soul Reaper created
by the 13 Court Guard Squads.
RURICHIYO (VOICEOVER):
Wow, that's amazing.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Stop it!
Stop it!