[theme music]
NARRATOR: In order
to save Orihime,
who has been kidnapped
by the Arrancars,
Ichigo, Uryu, and
Chad have snuck
into the Hollow
world, Hueco Mundo.
Before they could
reach Las Noches,
Runuganga, the Guardian
of the White Sand,
appeared before them,
and they were pulled down
into the depths of Hueco Mundo's
underground realm, the Menos
Forest.
Rukia was separated from
Ichigo and the others
when they entered the forest.
She then met a mysterious
Soul Reaper named Ashido.
Long ago, Ashido ended
up in the Menos Forest
after his pursuit of a
Hollow led him there.
Since then he has remained,
to try to kill as many Hollows
as he can.
-Ashido, why did
you bring me here?
-Whenever I talked, you'd
respond, ask questions,
and interact with me.
I wanted to let my friends hear
another voice besides mine.
NARRATOR: Rukia
and Ashido started
searching for Ichigo
and the others together,
but the Adjuchas, caretakers
of the forest who lived deep
within its depths, had set a
trap, and were laying in wait.
-If we defeat the leader,
the rest will scatter.
-OK.
-Fire!
-Ah!
-Aim for the girl, Gillians!
-Rukia!
-Ashido!
I'm sorry.
-It's all right.
Don't worry.
[laughter]
-I see you brought along
a friend today, Ashido.
Are you sure she
won't slow you down?
You should worry
more about yourself.
[laughter]
-Ashido, it's all my
fault that you even
got hurt in the first place.
So I'm going to defeat
that Adjuchas myself.
-What are you two
chatting about?
I'll give you
something to discuss.
Yah!
Yah, ha ha ha ha!
Dance, Sode no Shirayuki.
Some no mai, Tsukishiro!
Do you still think I'm
going to slow him down?
This slow enough for you?
-Ashido, I'm sorry.
I know how much
this meant to you.
Ashido.
It may not be my
place to say this,
especially at a time
like this, but maybe it's
time for you to once again
return to the Soul Society.
I understand your feelings
towards your friends,
but the situation has changed.
Things aren't like
they were before.
More importantly, you're alive.
The friends that
you lost down here
won't blame you if you return
to the life that you had.
-Thanks for the advice, but
I'll choose my own path.
Come on.
We better get going.
-Yeah.
-Nel's spiritual pressure.
You're sure that
they're here, right?
[mumbling]
-What should we do know?
-Isn't it obvious?
All we have to do is
barge in and swipe them
like the Hollows did.
What else are we supposed to do?
We can't just stand
around and waste time.
We have to find Rukia
as soon as possible.
-Hold on.
It's too dangerous to
just barge in there
without knowing the
situation inside.
Huh?
Hey, wait a minute!
-Can you see 'em?
-Uh, no.
-They're not here.
-Come on, seriously, you guys.
I just felt a trace
of spiritual pressure.
But it must be too late.
It looks like
they've already left.
[mumbling]
-Yeah?
Do you think you
know where they are?
[mumble]
-Let's go.
Over here?
-Where are they?
[mumbling]
-Look!
[whimpering]
-It's Nel!
It looks like she's all right.
-What are they doing up there?
-Ichigo!
Run away!
-Whoa!
[roaring]
[laughter]
-Hang on, Nel!
-I was going to get you
with one shot, but I missed.
Oh, well.
Don't move, Soul Reaper.
Don't move a single hair.
If you do, the Hollows
are going to eat them.
-They're really gonna eat us.
-Hurry up and save us!
-Damn it!
-It seems like were
planning to draw us out
by using them as bait
from the beginning.
-And that's not all.
The guy who Lord Aizen placed
in charge of this forest
says that he wants to
fight Ashido one on one.
So we drew you out.
-Ashido?
-That's why we made you come
to this amusing little place.
-You call this place amusing?
-That's right.
-This spiritual pressure--
-Let's hurry.
-Where to?
-The exit.
Up ahead of us.
-Slow down.
Where do you think
you're going, Ashido?
-Ichigo!
Ichigo!
-Did they get 'em?
What?
Where did they go?
-Whoa!
-Ichigo!
-Those bastards!
-Nicely done, Uryu.
-Thanks, Chad.
[laughter]
-We did it.
-You didn't do anything.
-Aw.
-Now we can finally
get out of this forest.
Let's go.
-Some Soul Reapers are
fighting over there.
It's easy to get a sense of
their spiritual pressures
from here, isn't it?
I know you want to save them,
but I won't allow you to pass.
You're going to sense
the pain of your friends,
and you're going to die, unable
to do anything to help them.
-You're sick.
-Let's finish this once
and for all, Ashido.
-Just stand back.
I've already fought him
countless times before.
Las Noches gave him the position
of guardian of the forest,
so unlike the others, this
one can't be underestimated.
-But I-- I will
settle this myself.
It shall be my
final job down here.
-But Ashido, you mean that--
-Afterwards, I want to
know the truth, Rukia.
I want to know what's going
on in the outside world.
-Ashido!
-What?
Urgh.
-You're in our way!
-Damn!
-Roar, Zabimaru!
Hmph.
That was too easy.
-Hmph.
-Damn you!
Damn you!
-Getsuga Tensho!
[roaring]
-What's this?
-Ichigo!
I'm scared!
-They suddenly began
to move more slowly.
-Yah!
So, did you notice?
Your friend's
spiritual pressure has
been completely extinguished.
-Damn.
-It's all over now.
-Ha ha ha.
-Hurry!
Run away, Rukia!
-Tsugi no mai.
Hakuren!
-What?
Ah--
-Yah!
[scream]
-Hey, are you all right?
-Yeah.
Let's hurry.
-Hold on.
-Thank you, Rukia.
-Don't mention it.
-Let's go!
Bankai!
[roar]
-Hihio Zabimaru.
-Getsuga Tensho!
-Looks like we got 'em.
-Think so.
Hey, is everyone all
right over there?
-Yeah.
-Huh?
[sigh]
-We're saved.
-It's a miracle.
If I remember
incorrectly, the Hollows
told us the exit is right
over here, so let's hit it.
-Really?
-Yes.
It's true.
-Hold on.
We can't leave without Rukia.
-That's right.
And now that we've figured
out where the exit is,
we should go look for her.
-Don't bother.
I'm right here.
-Rukia.
-Ichigo.
Hey, Renji.
-Rukia.
You--
-Rukia, it's good to see you.
I'm so glad that you're safe.
-Thanks.
Sorry for worrying you.
-Who's that?
-His name is Ashido.
He's actually a Soul
Reaper, like us.
-A Soul Reaper?
-Yes.
He saved me, and he helped
me get up here to the exit.
-So they weren't
kidding when they
said the exit was around here.
-You thought we lied?
What'sa matter with you?
-Man, are they persistent?
[shouting]
-Quit freaking out.
We should be able to handle
anything that comes our way--
-Just hold on.
They're still far away.
-Ichigo, our goal
is to save Orihime,
and we can't lose focus of that.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Ashido knows where the exit is.
Let's hurry.
-All right, then.
[mumbling]
-It's up ahead.
ICHIGO: That's it, huh?
Is this the same
place we came in from?
-No.
You entered from somewhere else.
Once you pass through here,
follow the flow of the sand.
Then you'll reach the surface.
-All right.
Come on, let's go.
-Damn, they're back again.
-You won't get
away, Soul Reaper.
-So, it looks like we didn't
finish you off after all.
[shouting]
-Get back!
Go on.
Now!
-What?
-Ashido!
-It's coming!
Dammit!
It's collapsing!
-Hurry!
Let's get out of here!
-Ashido!
Come with us!
-I'll catch up to you later!
Go on ahead without me.
-Stop interfering!
-Ashido!
-Rukia!
Look out!
-Damn you!
Argh!
Lord Aizen!
-Ashido!
-Go.
Save your friend.
[shout]
RUKIA: Ashido!
-Ah, Nel can hardly believe we
got back to the surface alive!
-I never thought that I'd
live to see the gleaming
moonlight ever again!
-Yeah.
And we're almost to Las
Noches, so let's celebrate.
-Yeah!
-Nel's so happy!
Yay!
-Wah-ha!
-Ashido had said
that the Adjuchas'
powers have changed recently.
I couldn't tell him that some
Soul Reapers have joined forces
with the Hollows, and
are trying to change
the world with the Hogyoku.
Ashido had been
fighting Hollows alone
for centuries in that forest,
because he was a Soul Reaper.
I couldn't tell him.
-Rukia.
After we save Orihime, we
need to steal the Hogyoku back
from that bastard, Aizen.
NEL: Hey!
-Hm?
-You want a lift to Las Noches?
-Let's hit it.
-Rukia.
-Yeah.
Let's go.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): Ashido.
I promise I'll
come back for you.
Until then.
ULQUIORRA: That outfit
unexpectedly suits you.
-You scared me.
When did you come in?
-Just this second.
Don't fuss over everything.
It's quite annoying.
I have some news.
Your friends have
entered Hueco Mundo.
-Why would they come here?
-This wall.
I wonder what it is?
It doesn't seem to be
made out of Sekkisekki.
-Well hell, if it's
not Sekkisekki,
then we should be able
to break through easily.
All right.
Let's go, Renji.
-Hey, you're not the boss here.
Smart ass.
-Why, you ask?
They have come to save you.
Why else would they
choose to come here?
They have no other reasons.
[shout]
[theme music]
ORIHIME: Uh--
ULQUIORRA: What is it?
ORIHIME: These clothes
fit me perfectly.
I was wondering how
you knew my size?
ULQUIORRA: Everything is as Lord
Aizen has intended it to be.
ORIHIME: What?
He knew just by looking at me?
That's amazing!
ICHIGO: Orihime!
You're not supposed to
be excited about that!