[theme music]
THEME SONG: Woke up with yawn.
It's dawning.
I'm still alive.
Turned on my radio
to start up new day.
As god damned DJs
chattered how to survive,
amazing news got
over on the air wave.
Tonight love is rationed,
tonight across the nation.
Tonight love infects
worldwide-- almost another day.
She's a shooting star.
Good night.
Good bye.
Tonight love is rationed,
tonight across the nation.
Tonight love infects
worldwide-- almost another day.
See you some other day.
-To exact our revenge, we're
returning to the Soul Society,
where all Bounts
were first created.
[gasp]
[rumbling]
-What was that sound?
-It seemed to come from
somewhere behind these walls.
Do you think it could be
Ichigo and the others?
It would have to be an
incredibly fierce battle for us
to be able to hear
the sound of it
right through this cave's
solid rock and stone.
-I can't stay here.
I've got to go and help.
-Rukia, you haven't fully
recovered enough to battle.
-I have to.
-Is something wrong?
What is it, Chad?
-No way.
[grunting]
-What did you say?
-Long ago, the Soul
Society conducted
a series of strange experiments.
It's never been quite clear
exactly what their purpose was,
but one thing we know for sure.
At that time, they
obviously thought of humans
as nothing more than
laboratory subjects.
The name of the one
who is responsible
for this great crime
is in the records.
And all of this began
because of his madness.
There was a sudden,
giant explosion,
and something, created by
an unexpected phenomenon,
caused a mutation in certain
souls in the cycle of rebirth.
During that limited
period of time,
individuals with
strange new abilities
began to appear all over
the world of the living.
These were the Bounts.
At first, we tried to
cover up our differences,
not wanting those
around us to notice.
But it was not
something we could hide.
Even though we were still
human, we were ostracized.
We were labeled demons and
monsters and abused terribly.
We were forced to live
in a world of darkness.
Then when the Soul Society
learned of our existence,
they kindly gave us a hand,
and we were glad to accept.
But that was all just
a part of their plan.
We didn't know any of this,
of course, and so many of us
tried for a very long time
to live alongside the Soul
Reapers.
This underground labyrinth
was a virtual city
where many of our
comrades lived in secrecy
to escape persecution.
Did you notice how big it is?
That's how many of us
there were at one time.
But now, sadly, there are
only a handful of us left.
Do you understand what the
Soul Society did to us?
They attempted to annihilate
us, to erase is from history.
We will never trust them again.
Our only wish now is
for the annihilation
of the Soul Society.
May they now be
exterminated just as cruelly
as they tried to
exterminate the Bounts.
Now at least you know the truth.
-It still doesn't
make any sense.
No matter what
happened, whatever
terrible things the Soul
Society may have done to you,
it doesn't give you
any right to take
the lives of your fellow humans.
I can't forgive you.
No, not for that.
[japanese]
-I'm surprised you still
have that kind of power left.
But that will end now.
-What the--
-You bastard.
-Give this up.
You don't have anything
close to the power
you need to defeat me.
[yelling]
-Absorbing so many
other living souls
has increased my
power immeasurably.
There is no limit to how much
stronger we Bounts can become.
The Soul Society
and its Soul Reapers
are insignificant next to us.
Soon now, they will know
the taste of defeat,
and they will all
kneel before us.
-Dammit.
Is this the end?
No.
I did not come all
this way by myself
just to have it end here.
I won't-- I can't let it
end in a place like this.
[struggling]
-Zangetsu.
-Zangetsu-- it that the name
of your Zanpakuto, then?
ICHIGO KUROSAKI
(OFFSCREEN): Shut up.
What do you think you're doing?
-A Soul Reaper's Zanpakuto is
another incarnation of himself,
yes?
Perhaps, then, you consider
this sword as your partner.
Just imagine if you were
killed by that partner.
How ironic.
-Damn you.
-I think I'll kill you with
your own blade, Soul Reaper.
[chuckling]
-Oh, really?
Zangetsu, tell me.
What do you think you're doing?
-You sound like you've lost it.
-Come on.
Show yourself to me.
-What the-- what is this?
-Zangetsu!
Zangetsu.
-Are you prepared to do this?
-It may be that I've been
relying on you too much.
I've always had my Bankai
if things got too bad.
Kisuke Urahara
even told me that.
So I know I must have
thought that somewhere
deep inside my heart.
-Bankai is the state
of extreme readiness
that involves both
blade and pain.
You must not be afraid.
The slightest hesitation
will dim your blade.
Once before, you were
able to gain power
by demonstrating an
unwavering heart.
I will ask you once more.
What are you preparing
yourself to do?
Why are you fighting this fight?
For whom do you seek this power?
ICHIGO KUROSAKI
(OFFSCREEN): Now I remember.
I remember that I wanted to
become a Soul Reaper in order
to protect those who
were important to me.
That's when I was able
to achieve Bankai--
by swearing on my
soul that I was
prepared to sacrifice my life.
Zangetsu, lend me your power
one more time-- the power
to protect everyone.
-I am that same power, Ichigo.
Trust in yourself, and
the power is yours.
-All right.
-You-- what the
hell have you done?
-I'll show you.
I'm protecting everyone.
Bankai!
Zangetsu.
-So this is your Bankai.
-Master, watch out!
-Don't distract him, Ichinose.
You just concentrate on
controlling the Senkaimon.
Master Kariya will be fine.
-Get up.
I can see you.
[yelling]
-We're almost there.
-Right.
OK.
Let's hurry.
I hope we're not too late.
-You dodged that one well.
-I guess I should also give
you credit for a good strike.
-I think it's time we put
an end to this little dance.
-My thoughts exactly.
-Uryu?
-Ichigo!
-Are you all right?
-Orihime!
Chad!
Rukia!
And Uryu, too.
But I'm not so sure
about your new look.
-I've had enough of being
a burden to everyone.
And now, finally, I can
look out for myself again.
-So you have all your
Quincy powers back again?
-Well, most of them,
but not completely.
-It's very old.
It was designed for battle.
It's a Quincy artifact, passed
down through generations
to a select few for
hundreds of years.
The Department of
Research and Development
discovered it and
saved it for study.
Go on.
Take it.
Perhaps it will help.
-Ah.
You'd better not miss with
your next shot, Quincy.
-Despite what you
may be thinking,
I didn't miss with
the last shot.
-He's back.
-[non-english speech].
Evidently, your powers have
been almost fully restored.
-Ichinose, is everything
prepared for us now?
ICHINOSE (OFFSCREEN):
Yes, master.
It's ready.
-[non-english speech]
-What's this?
What's going on?
-Stay where you are, Ichigo.
-Uryu, we've got
to do something.
They've opened up the portal!
-No, it hasn't opened
completely yet.
-So what do you hope
to accomplish, Quincy?
-Be careful, Orihime.
-Thank you.
Sorry about that.
-Uryu doesn't seem to be
aiming his bow at the Bounts.
-You're right.
It looks like he's aiming
at that portal instead.
-What is this strange
feeling that's come over me?
ICHIGO KUROSAKI (OFFSCREEN):
Uryu, what are you doing?
-No time to explain.
Just let me do this now, Ichigo.
-Exactly what we needed, Quincy.
My thanks.
Now, we have no further
need of your services.
-Wh-- what do you mean by that?
-He means that by
firing through it,
I've just opened the portal
into the Soul Society.
-So you knew what you were
doing when you fired that arrow?
-Yes.
The Soul Reaper who helped
me to regain my Quincy powers
told me what the result
of this would be,
which also explains why
you were so determined
to capture me for so long.
-Now you know.
-A Bount who has managed
to gain the immense power
of concentrated
souls can open spaces
into different dimensions,
but he must still somehow
convert his body
into rashi in order
to pass through the portal
and into that new dimension.
-And as you know, we
Bounts unfortunately
do not have that power.
But we learned some
time ago that there
are a select few
among the Quincy
who can freely control rashi.
If we use an arrow
from a Quincy who
has that power as a conductor,
then rashi conversion
is possible.
-Then the arrow you fired--
-Yes.
The arrow I released just now
passed through the Senkaimon
and changed it into
a rashi conversion
gate that will allow the
Bounts to convert into souls.
-Uryu, why the hell are
you helping these monsters?
-That's not hard to understand.
I always believed you'd
come around, Quincy.
After all, isn't the
Soul Society just as much
of an enemy to the Quincies
as it is to the Bounts?
It was devastating
news when I learned
that you had lost
your Quincy powers
and were no longer
any use to us.
Fortunately, Yoshino
managed to protect you.
For that, I am grateful to her.
She not only helped to
give birth to the Betoes.
Even in death, she was able
to influence you and bring you
back to me.
Now, against all odds,
you have succeeded
in regaining your Quincy powers.
Come, and walk forward with
me as befits the last Quincy.
-I think you've got
me wrong, Kariya.
The only reason I'm helping
you go to the Soul Society
is so I can settle all
of this with you there.
-So you have in mind to
try and avenge Yoshino?
Then you are a fool.
I thought you were seeing
the bigger picture here.
-I am going to defeat
you, Kariya, on the honor
and by the pride of the Quincy.
-All right.
If that's what you want.
-Master Kariya.
-Now, I'm afraid you'll
have to excuse me.
So Quincy, and you,
Soul Reaper-- we'll
be waiting on the other side.
Follow if you want to.
-Uryu, why'd you do that?
Why'd you help them, dammit?
-Ichigo!
Uryu!
-Yoruichi.
-Oh, no.
We've come too late.
-Ichigo!
-Uryu!
-What just happened here?
-Uryu, you've created
a serious problem.
-Uryu, why?
Why were you helping them?
-I'll tell you why.
I know you have your Bankai
back, but even with that,
do you really believe that
if we had continued to fight
we would have been able to
defeat someone so powerful?
-Well, I think that
if-- well, now,
we'll never know since
we didn't even try.
-It would have been
very difficult.
-But you don't know.
URYU (OFFSCREEN): Listen.
This Quincy power is all
I have to defeat him with.
And yet, as great as a
Quincy's full power may be,
it is still not strong enough
to defeat Kariya, certainly
not at the level
he's reached now.
-That tool I gave you gathers
the rashi in the air around you
and channels through your
weapon with great force.
But with so little rachi
in the world of the living,
this may be all you can do.
Things would be very
different in the Soul Society,
where virtually everything
is made of rashi.
-So I knew what would happen
if I tried to settle this here.
It would have been pointless.
It will be different
in the Soul Society.
-But you have no
idea how shortsighted
your thinking is, Uryu.
Soul Reapers and Quincies
aren't the only ones
who become more powerful
in the Soul Society.
The Bounts also
become stronger there.
-But how can that be, Yoruichi?
-When they go to
the Soul Society,
where all matter
is made of rachi,
they can absorb all they
want from everything
that's around them.
-No way!
-This is not good.
-Uryu, do you do
you even know what
that tool is that Namu gave you?
Do you know how it works?
-Well, I know that it's
capable of bringing out
a Quincy's full power
very forcefully.
And I know that it
isn't very stable,
although I get the
feeling that it
could stop working at any time.
But I have got to hang on
to this power for as long
as it is still working.
-I don't think you understand.
What you've started may
result in the destruction
of the entire world.
-Hey, what was that for?
-So why are we standing
around listening to you talk?
If we're going to the Soul
Society, then let's go.
-Ichigo.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): Right.
After all, you have serious
business to take care of, Uryu.
And we'll all go along
with you and back you up.
-You're all hopeless, but if
this is what you really want,
then fine.
-Thank you all.
-Incredible.
[sighs]
-Well, why not?
As long as we've come this far.
In order to finish
this, though, we're
going to have to mobilize
every Soul Reaper in the Soul
Society.
-When you really
think about it, that
might be the best
solution we have.
-It was in the Soul
Society that the Bounts
were created to begin with.
It's true.
So if there are going to be
casualties and blood spilled,
then the Soul Society ought
to take some responsibility.
RENJI (OFFSCREEN):
Hey, everyone.
YORUICHI (OFFSCREEN): Renji!
ICHIGO KUROSAKI (OFFSCREEN):
You're all right.
-Of course I am.
You can't kill me that easy.
Where are the
-Bounts?
-They all got away.
-Then we've failed--
not a beautiful ending
to our mission.
-Dammit.
That hurts.
-We can still get
them, but it'll
have to be in the Soul Society.
Let's do it.
-But how can we get there?
Chad and I don't
have that power.
-That isn't the only way in.
Don't forget, we still
have the Senkaimon
here that the Bounts left us.
I think with some
adjustments, we
can probably use it ourselves.
-That's a relief.
-I'll report in.
Hello, Captain, it's me.
Yes.
Everything's OK.
-Hey, what are you going?
-We're going along
with you too, you know.
You can't just
leave us behind now.
And besides, you're gonna need
Bount sensors more than ever.
-It's true.
You could actually be useful.
-As for me, I guess
I'll just go back home.
-Fine with me.
But don't forget, you'll be
there in the house all alone.
-Home alone, huh?
Oh, no way!
I changed my mind.
I'm going with you.
-All right.
I've just kicked in
with the Captain,
and everyone's cleared
to make the trip.
-Well, it looks like
we're headed back
to the Soul Society.
-So this is what
rashi-filled air is like--
better than I imagined.
Now, to begin
exacting our revenge.
[music playing]
-Here we go-- about to
charge into the Soul Society.
I wonder if I can make friends
with some cute Soul Reaper
girl.
Oh, I know.
I'll go and pay my
respects to Rukia's family.
ICHIGO KUROSAKI
(OFFSCREEN): Kon, I
don't think you should do that.
KON (OFFSCREEN): Why not?
ICHIGO KUROSAKI
(OFFSCREEN): Her big brother
doesn't have much
of a sense of humor.
KON (OFFSCREEN): Oh, brother.
[music playing]
-Illustrated Guide to
Soul Reapers-- golden.
[phone ringing]
-Yeah.
Hello?
RANGIKU (OFFSCREEN):
Hello, Captain.
It's me.
How are you doing today?
-Fine, Rangiku.
What is it now?
-Well, everything was going well
and we had the Bounts cornered.
But then, unfortunately, they
escaped to the Soul Society.
-They what?
RANGIKU (OFFSCREEN): I want to
bring Ichigo and all the others
back with me.
So can you get us permission?
-Yeah.
All right.
RANGIKU (OFFSCREEN):
Oh, and one more thing.
Don't use your new teacup.
I think I might have cracked it.
-Rangiku!