[theme music]
-What is that thing?
-It's huge.
-You can quit worrying about
getting through the wall.
With this launcher, I'll get
you all into the Seireitei
through the air.
-The air?
-Or my name's not Kukaku
Shiba, fireworks expert
of the Rukon district.
-Fireworks?
-That's right.
Koganehiko, Shiroganehiko,
raise it up now.
[shouting]
-Heave.
-Ho.
-Hey, what's going on?
-I don't understand this.
-It's the floor.
It's-- it's going up.
SHIROGANEHIKO (OFFSCREEN): Ho.
KOGANEHIKO (OFFSCREEN): Heave.
Heave.
SHIROGANEHIKO (OFFSCREEN): Ho.
Ho.
-Look.
The ceiling, it's opening up.
-Is this for real?
[grunting]
-So did that scare you kids?
This is my one and only
enhanced fireworks launch pad.
-And that's the
flower crate cannon.
-Ugh.
That was my line.
-Sorry.
[sigh]
-Huh.
Left you all
speechless, didn't I?
-I know that you're supposed
to be a pyrotechnical wizard,
but I'm still not
fully convinced of it.
The idea of shooting us up into
the air is completely-- ugh.
-What's this?
-It's a reishukaku
or spirit core.
Place your palms on it and
concentrate your spirit energy.
-Hm.
Like this?
Can someone show me how to
concentrate my spirit energy?
-Huh.
Any soul reaper should
easily be able to do that.
So you should know how to use
your spirit energy to do this.
-Well, actually, he's the
substitute soul reaper
I was telling you about earlier.
And he can't use
spirit energy at all.
-Yeah.
I can see that.
-Uh, you mean like this?
-This kid is
completely hopeless.
-Ganju, show this
amateur how it's done.
-Hey, give it here.
Why you!
So, kid, you want
to fight for it?
-Yeah.
Come on and take it
if you think you can.
But I, for one, would
rather die right here
than to learn it from you.
-Stop this right
now, both of you.
-(BOTH) I'm sorry.
[moaning]
-What's that?
-This here is the cannonball.
-Cannonball?
-Now pay close
attention, every one.
You may think that the only
thing guarding the Seireitei
is that barrier, but
you are dead wrong.
It isn't nearly that simple.
That barrier is made from
a stone known as Sekkiseki.
It's rare, even in
the soul society.
This is a fragment of it.
As you can see, it completely
repels spirit energy.
Therefore, it's
impossible to smash
through the barrier with
spirit energy alone.
Even cut into a small
piece such as this,
it emits a wave that
breaks down spirit energy
from all sides, which means
that the Seireitei has
a spherical barrier which
surrounds them, protecting them
not only from the sky above
but even below the ground.
So you see, that's
why we use this.
-Enough show and tell.
I'm tired.
KUKAKU (OFFSCREEN): Suck it up.
This cannonball is a special
hard spiritual partition
penetration device I invented.
In other words,
if all four of you
combined put your spirit
energy into this Reishukaku,
you can create a
temporary cannonball
that can break
through the barrier.
Then I'll use the
flower crane cannon
to shoot that
cannonball into the sky,
and it'll punch a hole
straight through the barrier.
Any questions?
-Eh, well, I was--
-All right then.
Now take them to the
underground training room
so they can practice
concentrating their spirit
energy.
-(BOTH) Yes.
Yes.
-Get them out of here.
-Yes.
Yes.
-What do you think you're doing?
Put me down this instant.
-Get your hands off
of me right now.
-Listen, you guys.
If any one of you
loses concentration,
then you'll blow up on the spot.
-What?
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN):
Where are we going?
-Practice hard.
-Hey, you never mentioned that.
-Oh yeah, thank you.
-(EXHAUSTED) You're welcome.
-Now, get your ass down
there and help them practice.
-All right.
But sis, are you seriously
going to help them?
-What are you talking about?
-I'm against it.
Helping a soul reaper is
something we shouldn't do.
I mean think after what
happened to our brother.
Listen, sis, I--
-Ganju, what did I tell you?
Didn't I say you were never
to speak of this again?
-But sis.
-You have your orders.
Now go.
Listen, you must never show such
a weak face in front of them.
Understand?
[birds chirping]
-This is the first time I've had
to wear my lieutenants badge.
-Yeah.
I hear what you're saying.
I think this is probably
the first time I've ever
been asked to wear
it like this myself.
All lieutenants are
to put on their badges
and wait in conference room two.
This certainly is
becoming interesting.
-Tetsuzaemon and Renji.
-So Momo, are you
the only one here?
-Uh, yes, I think so.
RANGIKU (OFFSCREEN):
The lieutenants
are scattered, working hard
all over the soul society.
It might take about half a
day for everyone together.
And to make matters
even worse, my captain
can't be reached at all.
This is starting to turn
into somewhat of a problem.
What to do?
-So then, just who exactly
is Rangiku's squad captain?
-You know, young Hitsugaya.
-Oh, not that little genius.
And I thought I had it rough.
-Renji?
-Yeah?
-You haven't seen Captain
Aizen around, have you?
-Uh, no.
I-- I haven't.
-I'm worried.
He's been acting strange lately.
I ran into him just this
morning and asked him
if anything was wrong,
because I was concerned.
But he didn't answer.
I don't know what to do.
[sigh]
-It'll be all right.
It's nothing to worry about.
My guess is that
even this summons
will be canceled
before much longer.
-In your personal
opinion, should Rukia die?
-What's happening,
Captain Aizen?
Just what the hell
is going on here?
SHIROGANEHIKO AND
KOGANEHIKO (OFFSCREEN): No.
That's wrong, Ichigo.
It's not right.
-No.
No.
-How many times do
I have to tell you?
[groaning]
-Do it.
Do it.
-[inaudible].
-Come on, Ichigo.
Try harder.
-It's supposed to be
[inaudible], right?
-[inaudible].
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
Help me out here.
Is it working?
I can't tell.
-Sorry, brother.
I've decided to help
that soul reaper who
came to me, a soul reaper not
unlike the one who killed you.
If you were still alive and
saw me not helping them,
you'd be the first to scold me,
you who loved soul reapers all
your life and also
died as a soul reaper.
SHIROGANEHIKO (OFFSCREEN): Now,
you, if you please, Orihime.
Good.
You're doing just fine.
KOGANEHIKO (OFFSCREEN):
Now you, Uryu.
SHIROGANEHIKO
(OFFSCREEN): It's narrow,
but the overall shape is there.
KOGANEHIKO (OFFSCREEN): Hm.
I'll bet that the
shape most likely
stems from the boy's
own personality.
SHIROGANEHIKO (OFFSCREEN):
Chad, you are up next.
Ah, this one is a bit
unstable, but very powerful.
KOGANEHIKO (OFFSCREEN): And
now, it is time for Ichigo.
-Ah!
-That's terrible.
-Just worthless.
-What is that supposed to be?
-It is obvious that you have
absolutely no talent for this.
You have no talent at all.
-Shiroganehiko!
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): How many
times do I have to tell you,
I don't understand?
You, teach me some
useless pointers.
Damn it.
[heavy breathing]
-Excuse me, boss man.
I'm sorry to
interrupt what you're
doing but dinner's ready.
-Huh.
Hey, guys, listen up.
Why don't we take a break?
Dinner's ready.
I bet you guys are starving.
-I suppose we could eat.
-You didn't get to eat in
the Rukon district, did you?
Well, those guys
over there don't
know how to use their spirit
energy, so they're not hungry.
So why don't you three go eat?
-OK, but what about--
-Never mind about me.
Go on ahead and eat.
I'll join you guys
when I'm done.
-All right.
If you're sure.
Then I guess we will.
[grunt]
-Come on.
Let's go and eat, Orihime.
-Oh, Uryu.
I'm not hungry at all yet.
So I'll just hang
out here for a while.
[stomach growling]
-Hey.
OK.
Busted.
I'm fibbing.
Maybe I am hungry.
Oh, this is embarrassing.
-Orihime, go on.
It's OK.
I'll be fine.
-I know that.
It's just that I want to
stay and practice some more.
Besides, I'm not
really that hungry.
Really.
-Orihime.
Please.
Do it for me.
-OK.
I'll do it, just because
you're asking me so nicely.
[giggle] I'm going to go then.
URYU (OFFSCREEN): Orihime,
are you going to join us?
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): OK.
Let's go eat.
I'm starved.
[groaning]
-Damn it.
-So she that important to you?
-Huh?
-That girl, the
other soul reaper.
You know, the one
you came to save.
-Not really.
-Huh.
-Give it here.
-I know why you're doing this.
It's got to be because
you promised to save her.
Right?
-No.
That's not it.
-Then it's money.
That's got to be it.
She promised to pay you
if you saved her, huh.
-No way.
How the hell am I
supposed to use money
from here in my world?
-Then why the hell are
you so damned determined?
-I owe her.
You see, she saved my life,
and I haven't repaid her yet.
She gave her power in order
to save me and my family,
even though she just met me.
Because of that,
she was captured.
And now she's about
to be executed.
I don't want to turn into
some kind of deplorable guy
who would just turn
his back on her.
Understand?
What now?
-Give it here.
-What are you doing?
Give it back to me.
-I've got practice myself.
So cover your ears.
I don't want you to
hear my technique.
I'm going to do some
work on an old trick
that I developed for
myself a while back.
Visualize this.
Draw a circle inside
your mind as dark
as possible and as
heavy as possible.
Then imagine yourself
jumping right
into the center of the circle.
This is a basic
imaging technique
that allows you to get in
touch with your spirit energy.
I could cry it's so easy.
And I didn't even
have to practice it.
Well, sorry about that.
Besides, since you
totally suck, I
doubt you'd be able to
do it like I can anyway.
Good luck.
-Hm.
Talk about a ham.
That guy is one bad actor.
What an idiot.
Draw a circle inside my mind.
-Thank you for the meal.
-Yeah.
URYU (OFFSCREEN): Uh.
Orihime, are you done?
-Oh yeah, really.
I'm full.
[stomach growling]
-See.
Really.
My stomach is full after all.
-You really don't
have to go that far.
Just forget that I ever asked.
-Actually, I was going to
take the leftovers to Ichigo.
-That's right.
He still hasn't had
anything to eat.
[explosion]
KOGANEHIKO (OFFSCREEN): No.
It's breaking apart.
-Oh no.
The great Kukaku arm
is going to fall.
-Oh no.
Please don't.
-It's Ichigo.
URYU (OFFSCREEN): Let's go.
-What the hell's going on?
Ganju, I'm talking to you.
KOGANEHIKO (OFFSCREEN):
Sis, I'm so sorry.
It's just that I
only showed him once.
I never thought it would
turn out like this.
His spirit energy is strong,
but he's out of control.
-You stupid idiot.
Concentrate your spirit energy.
-I did it.
-Great.
You did it, Ichigo.
-Yeah.
-You ignorant dumbass.
You've got to stay focused.
-What are you?
Freaking deaf or
freaking stupid.
Remember, I told you if
you don't concentrate,
you're going to blow up.
-Yes.
Yes, you did.
-Next time just be
sure not to do this.
-You're as guilty
as he is, schmuck.
Both of you, no food tonight.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): But why?
GANJU (OFFSCREEN): Come on,
you can't lump me together
with him.
KUKAKU (OFFSCREEN): Shut up.
Any more complaints?
GANJU AND ICHIGO
(OFFSCREEN): OK.
We understand.
YAMAMOTO (OFFSCREEN):
So you're here.
Captain of Squad
Three, Gin Ichimaru.
-An unexpected summons.
Tell me.
Should I be appalled
or impressed?
And look at this
distinguished crowd.
The captains who control
the soul society,
all here just for me.
Or am I mistaken?
I see the captain of Squad
13 is conspicuously absent.
What's wrong?
Did something happen to him?
-He's not feeling very well.
-Oh, not again.
I hope he gets well soon.
-Quit joking around.
You know that's not the
reason you were summoned here.
It is my understanding that you
went and played with that Ryoka
by yourself, didn't you?
And I also hear that you failed.
Explain yourself.
You should have no trouble
dealing with four or five
Ryokas without backup.
-I see.
So then you're saying
that they survived.
ZARAKI (OFFSCREEN): They what?
-Well, I was under the
impression that they were dead,
but I guess my instincts
are starting to fail me.
-Stop all this monkey
business right now.
There's absolutely no way
that captains such as us
could fail to instantly
tell whether an opponent's
spirit has ceased to exist.
-Oh no.
Not again.
Old fools caught up
in stupid bickering.
-Can you not see?
Your petty accusations
seem to imply
that I let him go on purpose.
-That's exactly what I'm saying.
ZARAKI (OFFSCREEN):
Shut up, Kurotsuchi.
Can't you see I was the one
who was talking to him first?
Or perhaps you'd rather
be done in by me.
KUROTSUCHI (OFFSCREEN):
What did you say?
-So stupid.
-Well, what do you know.
Tempers are running high today.
-Stop!
Enough of this foolishness.
I think the true
reason for which
you have been summoned here
to stand before your peers has
been made abundantly clear.
It is the fact that
you acted alone,
that coupled with the
fact that you also
permitted the target to escape.
So then, how do you defend
your actions, Ichimaru?
-I cannot.
Well, you see.
There's nothing to say.
I made a simple mistake.
I'm not going to stand
here and make excuses.
I'll accept whatever
punishment--
-Just a minute, Ichimaru.
I have something I
want to ask you first.
MALE SPEAKER
(OFFSCREEN): Red alert.
Red alert.
Intruders in the Seireitei.
All squads get into position.
Repeat.
Red alert.
Intruders in the Seireitei.
All squads get into position.
ZARAKI (OFFSCREEN): Those Ryoka.
It can't be.
-Ichigo.
[theme music]
-Four students and one cat
are going to Seireitei.
-Got it.
I'm off, sis.
-Attention, everyone.
The cannonball will
be shot very soon.
Take your seats now or else.
-OK.
Now, I'm really worried.