-I don't know.
Is this one too loud?
But since I never get a
chance to go to the beach,
maybe I should just be daring.
No, I couldn't take
the embarrassment
of showing my belly button.
-I don't know what
you're so worried about.
You haven't got anything up
here to fill the suit out.
So what difference does it make?
-Would you leave me alone?
-Mmm, this is exactly what
I've been looking for.
-Lady Yoruichi is so wonderful.
Even picking out swimwear,
she has such elegance.
I forgot.
I have to find a
bathing suit for myself.
-Soifon, I think this swimsuit
would look adorable on you.
What do you think?
-No, it's hideous.
What's she thinking?
I wouldn't make a
five-year-old wear that thing.
No.
Wait a minute.
There's no way Lady Yoruichi's
choice would be wrong.
Still, am I supposed to just
accept whatever she says?
Even if she is Lady
Yoruichi, there
are times when I have
to stand my ground.
Thanks.
If you don't mind,
I already have
my heart set on this yellow one.
-We'll take this one.
-Excellent choice, ma'am.
-Lady Yoruichi.
-I'm so jealous.
Captain Sui-feng has such
a petite little body,
she looks good in any swimsuit.
I hate it that they
never make any cute
swimsuits for
girls as big as me.
-Hey, sis.
You're never going
to believe what
I found for you, the
perfect swimsuit.
-What were you thinking?
There's no way.
I can't wear
something like that.
-It's lovely.
It'll look great on you.
I've decided on this one.
What do you think?
This is a good opportunity
for you to loosen up a little.
Choose that one.
-But-- but Captain.
-Choose that one, Isane.
[bell toll]
-Oh, yes, of course, Captain.
[theme song]
-That's all there is to it.
The Women's Soul
Reapers Association
decided to come here
for a little R&R.
-You don't really expect
me to believe that story.
-I'm sorry.
Allow me to explain.
The fact of the matter is
that the Women's Soul Reapers
Association had been secretly
building a pool for some time.
And unfortunately, it was
discovered and destroyed.
-Scatter.
[inaudible]
-Oh, damn.
Why'd he have to
go and destroy it?
-[inaudible] is such a meanie.
All
-The reason we
were discovered is
because you built it in
the middle of the yard
where the entire
world could see it.
-I accept full responsibility.
Next time, I will make
sure to equip the pool
with a device that will
intercept Captain Kuchiki
before he can get to it.
-That is not what I meant.
-But shouldn't we be discussing
what we're going to do now?
-Why don't we just build another
pool in a different location?
-Yeah, but the
question is where?
-Hm.
-I think I may have a
solution to your problem.
-Captain.
-During meetings,
you will address me
as Executive Chairwoman.
-Yes, ma'am.
-So, you say you
have a solution?
-Why, yes.
I was thinking that we
all deserve a little R&R
at one of those lovely beaches
in the world of the living.
-What?
-All right, yippee.
-Do you understand now?
-I think you all ought to
get your heads examined.
-I don't know what
you're so upset about.
You get to spend all
this time at the beach
with beautiful women
wearing next to nothing.
You should be grateful.
-She's right.
It's a good opportunity.
You can finally show your
gratitude to all the people
who've helped you over
the years, even Byakuya.
He's here too.
-Are you kidding me?
How did they ever convince
you to come to the beach?
-They wanted to
apologize for building
a swimming pool on my property.
So they offered to bring me
here for some fun in the sun.
-Now that you're
here, I hope you'll
enjoy everything the world
of the living has to offer.
-And how exactly
is this an apology?
-Don't waste too much energy
trying to figure it out
or you won't have enough
left to enjoy the day.
-Jushiro, you're here too?
-I took the liberty to invite
Captain Ukitake as well.
I thought he might like a
little fresh air and some time
away from the Soul Society.
-That's right.
And then Rangiku
invited us to come along
cause she knew that we would
liven things up around here.
-And we had nothing
else going on.
-Well, I figured, why not?
And I've been feeling
much better lately
and I thought this might
be a nice change of pace.
I have to admit,
soaking up the rays
feels pretty good,
the sun on my head.
-Jushiro.
-Captain.
-I'm sorry, I feel
a little dizzy.
-Coming here may not have been
such a good idea after all.
-If he's had too
much sun, maybe we
should get some ice
to cool them down.
-That's a good idea.
-There's a snack bar up
the beach a little ways.
Would you mind?
I'm sure they'll have some.
-Yeah, I know
where the place is.
I'll go get it.
-I'll go along with you.
-Excuse me, could you
guys spare a little ice.
-Sure.
-Orihime.
-Hey there, Ichigo.
How's it going?
-I don't mean to be rude,
but what are you doing here?
-Working part time.
-You mind keeping it down?
I'm trying to concentrate.
-Uryu?
-Chad's working here too.
-I don't get it.
Why are you all--
-Nobody told you anything, huh?
Captain Unohana hired
them to help out
while we're on vacation.
-I know that soul
reapers are my enemy,
but when Unohana asked
me for this favor,
I couldn't refuse her.
-She's very persuasive.
-She just thought
it would be easier
if we rented out the
entire beach today.
We don't feel like we can
spread our wings with humans
running around all
over the place.
-You just rented out
the entire beach?
-I almost forgot,
Ichigo, did you want ice?
-Oh, yeah.
-Jushiro got too much sun and
fainted back on the beach.
So we need some ice
to cool him off.
-Of course, I'll get
some for you right away.
Wake up, Toshiro.
We need some ice, please.
-Give me a break.
I told him this would
happen if he overdid it.
-Toshiro, what the hell
are you doing here?
And how come you're
not out there
on the beach with everyone else?
-I'm not real big on all
that sunshine and heat.
-When he saw us working at
the snack bar on the beach,
Toshiro said he'd help us out by
making ice with his Hyorinmaru.
-Wait a minute.
Are you allowed to
use your zanpakuto
for something like that?
-Hey, did you come here to
ask questions or to get ice?
-Oh, right.
Could you make us some ice?
-Rain over the frosted
heavens, Hyorinmaru.
It's all yours.
-It's kind of big.
-Well, if you're not
going to use it all,
then can I take half?
I thought up a recipe for
a curry mitsumame frappe
and I can't wait to try it out.
I'll make sure there's
enough for everyone.
-What a recipe, sounds lethal.
-It's good to see
you on your feet.
Are you feeling better,
Captain Ukitake?
-Sorry to have worried you.
Thanks to all of you, I'm
feeling much better now.
See?
-Maybe you should take it easy.
-Of course.
-Jushiro, you said you had
an announcement to make.
-Right, I had forgotten.
-The first annual
beach art competition?
-We'll see who can build the
most creative sculpture using
sand and other objects
from around the beach.
-And I will be judging
the competition.
-That's pretty much it.
So break up into groups
of two or three people
and start creating.
-So we came all the way to the
ocean just to play in the sand.
-What about a test of courage or
smashing watermelons, anything?
-The winner of the
competition will
receive an envelope filled with
cash from the head captain.
-Let's get started.
--[laughing] It's
all about the money.
-What do you think?
Shall we give it a try?
-Unlike the others, the prize
money holds no interest for me.
However, I do find this
challenge of artistic ability
intriguing.
Rukia, let's go.
-Right.
-You're not going to win this
competition standing around
with us.
-I think I'd prefer to
watch, if you don't mind.
I'm not good at this
sort of thing either.
-I wonder where Soifon and
Yoruichi have gotten of to.
-I saw them heading for the
water right after we arrived.
They said they wanted
to go diving for fish.
And I haven't seen them since.
You think there's
any need to worry?
-I think the only ones we need
to worry about are the fish.
-Hey, have you seen
a bucket anywhere?
We'll need water
to wet the sand.
-Bucket?
You and I don't need a
bucket to carry water.
-Hm?
-What do you think
these are for?
All we have to do is
make some cleavage
by pushing our boobs
together, and we
can carry all the water we need.
-You're so smart.
-Here, let me show
you how it's done.
Just grab your boobs like this.
-It's broad daylight.
What do you think you're doing?
-Hm?
-Booby buckets.
-Disallowed.
-Huh?
But why?
-This behavior is
hardly appropriate.
-Oh, who cares about that?
I get it.
You're just jealous because
you don't have enough upstairs
to make your own booby buckets.
-That has nothing to do with it.
-Huh?
Were your boobs always that big?
-Why do you ask?
-Don't be so shy.
-[inaudible], what's the matter?
-Look what we got.
She's wearing pads.
-Just leave me along.
-OK, looks done to me.
-Oh no.
This baby's not done
until the first guy
digs a secret passageway inside.
-I got this.
-Knock yourselves out.
I stopped playing those kind of
kiddie games a long time ago.
-Kiddie games?
That sounds like
an excuse to me.
I think someone's
afraid of losing.
-All right then,
you're going down.
-Yeah, I don't think so.
-You two turkeys
don't stand a chance.
-No, no, no, get it off,
get it off. [shouting]
-Ikkaku, what happened?
-No, Ikkaku's been buried alive.
-We've got to dig
him out of there.
Don't worry, Ikkaku.
-Just the way I planned.
-They're acting like
rowdy idiots over there.
Why can't they work
quietly like everyone else?
-Rukia, they're of
no concern to you.
Ignore the distractions
and focus on your own work.
-Yes, I apologize, Byakuya.
I'll try to focus.
Not bad, if I do say so myself.
-Huh, perhaps adding
some muscle definition
would make a bolder statement.
-Oh, my big brother
has such talent.
His aesthetic sense
is so polished.
I knew I'd never be able
to hold a candle to him.
At the very least, I must try
to complement his artistry
and not distract from it.
-Brother and sister?
Maybe not, but they're
still two peas in a pod.
-Oh dear.
It's so hot.
If I don't take
it easy, I'm going
to collapse again and
spoil everyone's day.
I think I'm going to lie
down a while, [inaudible].
Wake me when it's
time for the judging.
-Yes, sir.
-You'd think they could at least
put flush toilets at that snack
bar.
-Kiyone, try not to
make so much noise.
-Hey, what are you doing anyway?
-What are you, blind?
I'm building a wall of sand so
the sea breeze doesn't disturb
the Captain while he's sleeping.
-What?
You're such an idiot.
You need to keep the sun
off him, not the wind.
Did you think he was
going to blow away?
I'll go pick some flowers.
The petals will block
the rays of the sun
without overheating him.
-Yeah, well then I'm going
to light some incense
so the Captain'll
sleep more comfortably
and have sweet dreams.
-I don't get it.
What is this?
-I'm not sure why, but it
somehow touches my heart
in a way I can't explain.
-If you ask me, it looks like
someone's pulling a bad joke.
-Lunch is here.
I hope everyone's
got a good appetite.
-There's fried noodles and
rice balls, specially prepared
at the seaside snack
bar by yours truly.
-And we've got drinks too.
-Did they have to
set it up there?
-Looks like a funerary
offering, doesn't it?
-I must say, when you
consider all these elements,
Captain Ukitake's team
is the obviously winner.
-Was Captain Ukitake
even in the competition?
-Oh, I just assumed he was.
-I'm not sure.
-Hey, Ikkaku, are you all right?
-That damn crab.
-I'll bury you bastards.
-It's ruined.
[screaming]
-What the hell?
-Something's got
the lieutenants.
What the hell is that thing?
[screaming]
-Watch where you're
putting that tentacle.
-Get that spine
out of my swimsuit.
-Oh damn, why didn't I
bring my camera today?
I could have sold that shot
for a nice chunk of change.
-I can't believe you would
say something like that.
-I never believed it
would actually appear.
-Hey, what's going on?
You know what that thing is?
-There were rumors
that a strange Hollow
with immense spiritual pressure
had appeared at this beach.
But I just figured it
wouldn't be much of a problem.
-Looks like you figured wrong.
But why would you rent
out this entire beach
if there was a chance something
like that might show up?
-Ichigo, forget about that.
We've got to rescue
the lieutenants.
-You're right.
That thing's dangerous.
Be careful.
[shouting]
-What the hell?
-Spirit energy attacks
have no effect on it.
-How is that possible?
-The vines of that
Hollow have the power
to absorb radiated
spirit energy.
The only possible way to inflict
damage is with a direct attack.
-You mean we can cut that
thing with a zanpakuto?
Dammit, I don't have my
substitute soul reaper combat
pass or any right now.
Rangiku, Rukia--
-We came here for
a day at the beach.
If we brought our
zanpakuto, they
would have just got in the way.
-I'm sorry, Ichigo.
I also left [inaudible]
inside the snack bar.
-Renji.
-Heh, I figured something
like this might happen.
So I brought Zabimaru
along just in case.
Roar, Zabimaru!
[screaming]
-Renji.
-Ichigo, look out.
-Where's Byakuya?
-I haven't seen him since we
were working on our sculptures
together.
-How could he disappear
at a time like this?
And where's Jushiro?
-Our captain is taking a nap.
-Remember, no
matter what happens,
it's our duty to protect
the captain at all cost.
-I know that, you idiot.
-Looks like we're going to have
to take care of this monster
ourselves.
[screaming]
-Orihime.
-Ichigo.
[screaming]
-Chad and I'll keep
it busy until you
can get your substitute
soul reaper pass.
-Yeah.
-That's a good idea, thanks.
What the?
Dammit.
-Sting all enemies to
death, [speaking japanese].
-You should have been
trying to help instead
of standing around
doing nothing.
-Well, yeah, but I was--
-We were going after
sharks in the ocean, when
all of a sudden Renji
dropped in out of nowhere.
We figured something
must be wrong.
So we raced back here.
What is going on around here?
And where did that
monster come from?
-[yawn] Nice nap.
-Captain.
-He slept through all of
that screaming and fighting,
but now that it's
quiet, he wakes up?
-I don't know.
Sometimes I wonder
about that guy.
-Oh, I see you've started the
watermelon smashing already.
-Watermelon?
-He's right.
You It does taste
like watermelon.
-It's about time
you figured it out.
-Byakuya, I still don't
know what's going on.
-Sorry for the confusion.
Allow me to explain.
The other captains and I thought
you all deserved some fun.
So we put our heads
together and came up
with this watermelon
smashing event.
-We thought you'd enjoy it.
-Huh?
What about that story earlier?
-I just made that
up because I thought
it would add to the excitement.
-The truth is it's a very
special watermelon recently
developed by the Department
of Research and Development
for use against Hollows.
-She has to be joking
with us, right?
-How can a watermelon
stop a Hollow?
-It's not a day at the beach
without watermelon smashing.
So I put a request in to the
acting assistant chairwoman,
and guess what?
-Fortunately, I was able
to fill that request.
-Excellent.
-So you any other captains
went to all this trouble just
to throw a surprise for us?
-That's right.
I hope you all enjoyed
it as much as we did.
-We were supposed to enjoy this?
-Captain.
-Hey, Ichi, want to
eat some watermelon?
-What, you mean you
can really eat that?
-That's not all.
There are still more
surprises to come.
-Huh?
[screaming]
[giggling]
-We've prepared one
watermelon for each of you.
-This way, no one's left out.
Now you can all enjoy
smashing watermelons
to your heart's content.
-Wait, hold on a minute.
-Ha, what are we waiting for?
Let's smash.
Ichigo: I don't even
like watermelon.
-Huh?
So here you are.
-Give me a break.
If you think I'm going to go
out and sweat in that heat,
you're crazy.
[theme music]
-You guys are such
a bunch of losers.
You'd think at least
one of you would
have the manners to complement
us on our swimsuits.
-You're giving them
way too much credit.
-Maybe they'll notice
if we take them off.
--[inaudible], what
are you doing?
-Let go of me.
If that's what they
want, I'll take it off.
Let go.
-You're drunk, aren't you?