[theme music]
[whispering]
CHILD: He's scary.
What is he doing in our village?
[whispering]
-Did you do it again, Ikkaku?
You'll soon run out of
people who will fight you.
-Then I'll have to leave
and go to another area.
-Hm.
Why don't you wipe your face?
You don't look very good.
IKKAKU: Impatience.
Irritability.
A short temper.
At the time, that defined
me, and all I was.
I didn't belong in
the Soul Society.
I didn't belong anywhere.
Yah!
-We didn't mean it, I swear!
IKKAKU: Fighting
and pain, those were
the only things that
felt real to me.
Who wants to fight?
I need a good challenge!
There must at least one or
two of you who want to die?
[frightened whispers]
[laughter]
-Hm?
Who's that?
What the--
-If you were smart, you'd leave.
Kenny's in a good mood today.
Unless you enjoy a lot
of pain, you should go.
-Yeah, right.
Your friend is in a good mood.
And that's reason to worry?
-You sure are stupid.
He loses all control when
he's feeling really good.
That's when he
ends up having fun.
-What's that?
-Hey.
Don't even think about it.
Are you gonna run?
-No.
I'd prefer to stay.
My spirits are high, too.
So let's have a little fun!
[whispering]
-Ikkaku.
-I don't want you to help.
-I know that.
-You're strong.
Or so it would seem.
-Yeah.
-I am strong, as well.
-That's it.
No more talking.
Now fight.
-Who is this guy?
He's not only strong,
he's incredibly fast.
Now this is fun.
In fact, this is the most fun
I've had since I came here!
-Ah.
Good for you.
-Who is this guy?
The strikes are so
fast, I can't see it.
YACHIRU: Look.
Kenny's smiling.
[giggle]
-It's a shame, really.
It's almost over.
-I really enjoyed that.
It's been awhile since
I've had so much fun.
-Yah!
Where are you going?
Finish me off!
-What do you know?
You're still alive.
What are you thinking?
You're obligated to kill me.
You won.
Do it!
-Sorry.
But I'm not here to put you down
like you were a sick animal.
I've got no obligation to
end all of your suffering.
-Hm?
-I'm a warrior.
I have my pride.
Kill me!
-Shut up.
If you like fighting
so much, then
stop moaning and whining
for me to kill you.
Don't accept a loss
and wish for death.
Never admit defeat
until you're dead.
If you lose and
manage to live, then
consider it your lucky day.
When that happens, only
think about surviving.
After all, there's a
goal in your future.
-What's that?
-Live, and dedicate
yourself to killing
the one who left you alive.
You know, I didn't hold back
while I was fighting with you.
You had plenty of luck, and
that's why you're alive.
Live.
And try and kill me another day.
See ya around.
-Wait!
Tell me your name!
Don't go.
Not until you tell
me what your name is!
-Kenpachi.
Kenpachi from Zaraki.
-Kenpachi from Zaraki?
When my wounds finally healed,
I searched for him everywhere.
I had only one thing on my mind.
To fight him once more.
YUMICHIKA: Hello.
It's been a while.
How are you doing?
-Yumichika.
Yeah.
Fine.
Well, you brought
some news, or what?
-I've heard something
that's very interesting.
IKKAKU: The 13
Court Guard Squads?
-Hear and obey.
As a member of the 13
Court Guard Squads,
be aware of your duties.
YUMICHIKA: I heard Kenpachi
defeated the former captain
in a single blow and immediately
became the new captain.
Being a captain is probably
the best way for him
to fight as much as he wants.
-Hm.
So he plants to protect
this disgusting world?
Kenpachi.
It can't be.
That's not his style.
-You want to go take a look?
-Nothing can stop me.
I'll track him down.
I'd go to the gates
of Hell to find him.
-I knew you'd say that.
-Oh.
They're all we have to
work with this time.
-Huh?
Oh.
What is a child doing here?
Now go on.
Get away.
Huh?
I'm Lieutenant
Yachiru Kusajishi.
-Huh?
-Kenny!
-Hm.
-I'm the captain of Squad
11, Kenpachi Zaraki.
Listen carefully.
I don't care where you're
from, how old you are,
or about your personal life.
I'm not going to condemn
any of your viewpoints,
nor will I sanction them.
-Huh?
MAN: Wait.
-There's something I want!
What I want is very simple.
Your strength.
Strength and will.
If you're strong and
know how to fight,
then you and I will
get along very well.
IKKAKU: Sounds good to me.
Here I am, as you suggested.
-Huh?
[crowd murmuring]
[roar]
-Look!
It's a team of caterpillars!
-Lieutenant!
It's already slaughtered
15 Soul Reapers.
You mustn't underestimate it.
-But--
[roar]
-All right, then.
I'll go.
KENPACHI: Hold on.
-Captain.
-Get the men who fought
first to pull out.
They're only in the way.
-Yay!
Kenny!
Come on!
Give them a beating!
-5.
6.
7?
-He won!
Victory!
Kenny!
-Hm.
[roar]
-This is bad.
-This is gonna be great.
There's more of them to kill.
IKKAKU: Hold on.
-Hm?
-That's very unfair, Captain.
-You're having all
the fun, while we
have to watch from
the sidelines.
-What do you think you're doing?
I told you to stay back.
-Contest time!
Hey, Kenny, we're
gonna have a contest!
It's a contest to see who can
slice off the most caterpillar
tails!
Contest!
Yay!
A contest!
-Let's do this.
I'll join ya.
Careful.
Get in the way, and
you'll be sliced.
Everyone got that straight?
-All right!
-Oh.
Good morning, Third
Seat Madarame.
-Yeah, yeah.
Huh?
And you are?
-Renji Abari, sir!
-Oh, yeah.
From Captain Aizen's
squad, right?
I heard about you.
As soon as you joined,
you got into a huge fight
and were thrown in
the punishment cell.
So what do you want?
-A request, sir.
Please, will you
teach me how to fight?
-Huh?
-Would you please, sir?
-Hi-yah!
-Seven.
Eight.
That was 10.
You would have been
dead every time.
-Once more.
Can we?
-So tell me, why do you want
to become strong so badly?
Answer me.
-I need to surpass someone.
-Hm?
This lesson is over.
-Huh?
-You've learned enough.
That's it.
-But I'm sure there's more.
-Figure out the rest yourself.
Unless you want
people to say you're
a copy of me for the
rest of your life.
-I've been waiting
to see your Bankai.
-Bankai?
RENJI: You can do it, right?
Why don't you use it?
Tell me.
Are you hiding it?
-I have my reasons.
-What?
What do you mean, reasons?
-I'm also chasing someone.
Desperately.
Now it's time for me to
tell you what my name is.
Ikkaku Madarame.
Remember that.
The next time we fight,
it'll be to the death.
Make no mistake, it will
be your final battle.
When you tell your name to
the one you plan to defeat,
that's when you show them
the greatest respect.
Someone who assumes he's
going to die in battle
should always know
before he dies
the name of who defeated him.
-Thank you very much!
MAN: Captain Aizen
joined the Hollows?
Is that true?
-You saw those Menos
Grande too, right?
-Yeah.
But there hasn't been any
formal explanation yet.
IKKAKU: The answer's no.
-Ah?
-I'm sorry.
Ask someone else.
-What?
-Hey, hold on a second, Ikkaku.
It has to be you!
Aside from you, there's no other
lieutenant who can do a Bankai.
None of them.
I know it's
presumptuous, but there
is no other lieutenant
who's fit to be a captain.
Think for a minute.
Who else is there?
The first choice, last choice.
You're the only choice.
Aizen is gone now,
and there's a void.
Fill it!
Aid us and our captain.
Ikkaku!
-Fool.
I told you when I was
training you, aside
from you and Yumichika,
I have no intention
of telling anyone
about my Bankai.
When word gets out
that I can do Bankai,
I'll be hounded
by fools like you.
I'll have no rest.
-Now is the time.
We need to find a new
captain as soon as possible.
-Well, that isn't
something that concerns me.
I didn't intend on
becoming a captain.
There's a problem
with being a captain.
It would mean I can't
fight under Captain Zaraki.
You want to surpass
Byakuya Kuchiki.
I have a dream, as well.
To fight and die as
Zaraki's subordinate.
End of discussion.
Don't ever ask me again.
Damn.
-Ikkaku Madarame.
I'm glad I asked
you for your name.
YUMICHIKA: I knew it.
I knew that you
were alive, Ikkaku.
-Of course I am.
I was lucky today.
Luckier than you can imagine.
[theme music]
MAN: Oh, no!
I can't cancel the funeral
service for Ikkaku.
IKKAKU: What?
MAN: The lieutenant really
got into preparing it,
and she doesn't want to cancel.
YACHIRU: Baldy,
which picture do you
want to use for your funeral?
I'm gonna make it a fun one!
IKKAKU: Ah, give me
a break, Lieutenant.
[theme music]
MAN: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers.
Golden.
-Yeah!
Today I'm finally gonna
put my plan into action,
you faithful listeners!
-Kon?
What is it you're planning?
-First I take his gigai, then
I use this soul candy self
extraction pad.
Extraction princess!
Yeah!
A body at last!
It's a weird look, but the
ladies like it, so I'm happy.
My manly erotic conquest
of the Soul Society
will begin in the next episode.