Yaah!
Hrg!
Ngh!
Heh!
You have absolutely no chance
for victory, and maybe now,
you'll understand why!
D'augh!
What the...?
Heh heh! What's the
matter, Mr. Know-It-All?
How dare you attack me!
Oh my, surely you of all people
would have noticed by now?
I changed places with
my double a while ago.
How very disappointing.
As a fellow scientist,
I thought you'd be smarter.
But as it turns out you're
a fool who cannot even tell
the difference between his
enemy or his own creation.
Then you are the original?!
When did you make the switch?
Why do you need to know?
It's an irrelevant question,
really, but if you insist.
I made the substitution
when the lieutenants in
your invading army left for
the World of the Living.
Unfortunately for you,
my power is far beyond the
comprehension of someone with
such a limited intellect.
Hrgh!
Of course, not everything
went as I had hoped it would.
While I managed to swap
places with my Reigai,
the other captains who
were supposed to come and
liberate the Soul Society,
were taking forever
to get here.
As a result, everything
was delayed,
and that's the reason
it took so long for
me to reveal myself.
Heh ha ha ha.
Wonderful. I admit,
you completely had me,
Captain Kurotsuchi.
However...
It's best not to forget,
no matter how clever you
think you are,
you're playing
on my field.
Such youthful arrogance!
D'augh!
I'll teach you a lesson,
my friend.
You've made one
small error.
Perhaps a fatal one.
You've pissed me off!!!
[gasp]
I said, who are you?!
Huh?
Ichigo!
Guys?
Does this mean...
I'm in the World
of the Living?
Yes, that's right.
Well hello there.
I see you've finally
come around, Ichigo.
Kisuke... Nozomi.
You said you were going
to defeat Kageroza.
Huh?
You promised you'd end this
quickly and come back to us!
Uh...
I'm sorry.
We all thought we lost you!
That you were--!
I guess I blew it, huh?
At least I was able to make
it back here in one piece.
Ah!
That reminds me, Renji.
When I was stuck in there,
were you the one who rescued
me from the Cleaner?
Huh? That wasn't me.
All I did was bring you back
here after I found you passed
out in the Precipice World.
[Ichigo]
Then, who was that Soul Reaper?
[Kisuke]
So, Ichigo. You were swallowed
by the Cleaner, after all.
Uh?
Do you know something
about this, Kisuke?
Yeah, I do.
But before we get into that,
would you like some tea first?
Rrgh!
Agh!
Not a bad move, Inaba.
I had no idea, after all
this time, that you
excelled in close combat.
I wish I could say
the same for you.
Did you really think you
could capture me with
this silly little toy?
Oh come on!
Don't get so
full of yourself!
That act was just designed
to buy me a little more time.
Let me guess...
For Ashisogijizo?
But if you recall, as I
mentioned to you earlier,
everything you see around
you is under my control.
Really? Because once my
Ashisogijizo strikes anyone,
it renders their limbs useless.
Ordinarily, by this point,
I would expect you'd be
unable to move.
But maybe not in this case,
since you're telling me you
were already prepared.
[chuckle]
I don't suppose you'd
mind if we gave it a
little test, then?
Huh?
Tell you what, I'll even make
it a sporting proposition.
I'll keep my eyes closed.
And if you find you're
able to move, you go
ahead and attack me.
Huhh??
Well? Come on!
I'm waiting!
Heh heh.
I'm not falling for any
of your mind games,
Captain Kurotsuchi.
Your action
clearly suggests
this is a trap to lure... me...?
[gasp]
I'm opening my eyes!
Auggh!
[wet cough]
This can't be!
My body's moving!
So why...?!
This is the reason.
What?!
When I first attacked you,
I took the liberty of injecting
this drug into your body.
He he he he!
Can you tell?
It's very powerful.
It stops all thought processes.
Stops... thought?!
Heh heh!
If I had suddenly slashed at
you, your defensive instincts
would have probably allowed
you to avoid the attack.
Instead, I allowed you
time to think about
how I would attack,
and therefore, how you
would deal with it.
So you're saying you
used your drug to
muddle those thoughts?
Inaba. Do you know what a
scientist fears most in this
world, above all else?
It's oblivion, my friend.
We scientists measure our
lives in the ways we develop
and expand our knowledge
through myriad variations.
Nothing can take its place.
It's our very soul.
I have done the worst thing one
scientist can do to another.
I have altered the very nature
of your thought processes.
When my drug takes full
effect, you will find that
your mind has completely
lost the ability to think.
Try as you might, you will
be unable to use the
knowledge you've accumulated
up to this moment.
Your mind and its
memories will be
consigned to oblivion.
Rrrgghh!!
[Kisuke]
Those who stray from
within the confines of the
fixed Precipice World
are condemned to wander
within it for all eternity,
until they are swallowed
by the Restrictive
Current, or Cleaner.
[sips]
...And then perish.
This is something that you
are all well aware of.
Of course, there are several
ways to escape from it before
that happens, as demonstrated
by Captain Kurotsuchi.
But to be swallowed by a
Cleaner and survive as
Ichigo has, is unheard of.
Then what happened?
I don't know.
Huh?
How would I?
After all, as I mentioned,
it's never happened before.
I do plan to look into it.
[sip]
But I don't expect to
find a quick answer.
Well that's just great.
You're a big help.
However, I did find out
the reason why Kageroza
is so obsessed with the
Precipice World.
[Renji]
You did?
[Kisuke]
Yes.
Here's what I
discovered.
For years, Kageroza was
studying control and use
of the Precipice World.
But that alone was not
his most important
consideration.
What do you
mean by that?
I'm saying that his
intentions lay elsewhere.
The research was simply
an instrument needed to
achieve his true purpose.
He was trying to obtain specific
information that was hidden deep
within the Precipice World.
[Kagerosa]
[gasps, moans]
Well, now.
What's the matter?
[choked growling]
What are you
waiting for?!
Hurry up and
finish him off!
HUAAAGHHH!
Hmm?
[Kagerosa]
[growling hysterically]
You'll be all right,
I'll heal you!
Not only did he
out-maneuver me from
the very beginning,
he was able to
literally stop my
thoughts as well!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
This one time only, I'll
admit to being a fool because
of my overconfidence.
[standing pains]
Nggh!
Careful, you'll
overexert yourself!
Huh?
And how did you reach
that conclusion?
It's just that you
look... weak!
Ha ha ha!
[gasp]
What the hell...?!
Rrrgh! No one
tells me I'm weak!
Agh!
[clatter]
Huh! So the drug can stop
one's thought process,
but not emotions as strong
as hatred and anger.
Didn't expect that.
What a surprise!
Rrrgh.
Hm?
What does he have there?
Is it a
Soul Candy?!
[Kurotsuchi]
No, it's definitely
not a Soul Candy.
[Renji]
A Mod Soul?
[Kisuke]
Yeah.
I was able to determine
that Kageroza's objective in
studying the Precipice World,
was to obtain
information hidden there
regarding Mod Souls.
Huh?
What are Mod Souls,
specifically?
I know! I know!
Here! Here!
I'll explain.
There's a history
involved.
Years ago, an experiment
took place.
The Soul Society came up with
a project called 'Spearhead'.
The plan was to place artificial
souls, specialized for battle,
inside the bodies
of deceased humans.
These bodies would then
be used as advance troops
whenever Soul Reapers were
forced to confront Hollows.
Heh heh.
It's been a while
since you 'graced'
us with your art.
What was that?
Never mind!
It's not important!
Keep going!
Your drawings
suck.
Huh??
I- I- I...
Blegh...
The project was
abandoned as being
reprehensible.
But the result of the
experiment was the
development of Mod Souls.
She's right.
Kon here is one
of the surviving
Mod Souls.
Guh... Gah!
Nnnngh... Sshh...
Oh my. Apparently you've
lost the power of speech,
which is extremely
unfortunate for me,
since I wanted to ask why you
possess Mod Soul technology.
[forced out]
Oh I can still speak,
Mayuri Kurotsuchi.
Clearly there's something
you haven't understood.
From the very
beginning...
...I've been operating
at a different level.
Agh!
Yaah!
Huaaghh!
YAAHHHHH!
Unh...
And what do we have here, hmm?
Hmpf!
In the simplest of terms...
What you're seeing is an
alternative use of Mod Souls.
So did that spark
your interest?
Oh yes. You made the Mod
Soul you just swallowed...
...take the fall.
It's suffering the effects
of the drug I injected you
with, earlier.
Yes. It's not a
perfect technique.
but it does get
the job done.
Huh?
Stop!
Hmpf!
[Uryu]
But how did you find out that
the Mod Soul data was hidden
in the Precipice World?
[Kisuke]
Pure chance.
I got suspicious.
It was when we went into
the Precipice World to
retrieve Ichigo.
I sensed there was something
odd about the Reishi that
was lingering around his
unconscious body.
When I did an analysis
there on the scene,
I was surprised to find
fragments of previous Mod
Soul development data mixed
in with the Reishi itself.
I realized that Kageroza had
used that data to create the Mod
Souls of the Squad Captains.
[Nozomi]
You're absolutely right.
Huh?
[Ichigo]
Nozomi?
Tell us, Kageroza.
How did you know that
the information on the
Mod Souls was hidden in
the Precipice World?
You might as well
spill it, pal.
You might think you can still
keep some things secret, but
with a little more time,
we're going to find
out everything anyway.
So why don't you tell
us who you really are?
[Orihime]
Nozomi?
[Kisuke]
I see now.
You knew, didn't you?
All right, then..
Let me tell you.
He's the one.
I'm the one.
...who originally
developed the Mod Souls.
You developed the Mod Souls?
Well that's just absurd.
I'm telling you
all the truth!
Explain yourself.
When Project Spearhead
was scrapped,
it was decided that
every Mod Soul, and the
supporting research done
up until that point,
would all be
destroyed.
The science behind the
research was sound.
The Mod Souls I was
striving to create, were to
be incubated from a portion
of a Soul Reaper's Reishi.
From that, they would
inherit the Soul Reaper's
mental structure,
but their physical
capabilities would be
far more advanced.
Do you understand
what I'm saying?
This was sublime research,
years ahead of its time,
that approached the
realm of the gods!
However, your research
was too dangerous.
Project Spearhead was
dispensed with because
the Central Forty Six
recognized the immorality
of using the dead as
implements of battle.
That was the reason
they presented.
But that wasn't
the real reason.
The unrestricted power to
control the capabilities
of Mod Souls was judged to
be an unacceptable threat.
You're correct.
The fools feared
my research.
I found that unacceptable...
...and I determined I
had to take action.
Before everything
could be destroyed,
I converted the immense
amount of information I
had developed,
into special Reishi.
I then hid that Reishi
in the Precipice World.
[Nozomi]
After that, Kageroza spent
the next several years
studying the Precipice World.
He then retrieved
the information from
inside the Cleaner.
So that's how
this came about!
[Kon] [nervous laughs]
Heh! Heh!
That explains
quite a bit,
actually.
It finally comes out that
this bastard is the one who
originally created Mod Souls!
Kon...
It all makes sense now.
It's no wonder you
couldn't trust me, Nozomi.
You're wrong!
That's not
the reason!
Then what is it?!
You've kept me at arm's
distance all this time,
pushed me away!
Come on, stop it!
It's
obvious!
You thought of me as
nothing more than one of
Kageroza's creations!
Please just listen to me!
He didn't create you!
And how in the world could
you possibly know that?!
Well... Because...
[gasp]
[Kagerosa]
How did you put it,
Captain Kurotsuchi?
The thing that a
scientist fears most
is oblivion, was it?
I have to agree.
I couldn't stand the idea
of losing everything...
of having my creations ripped
away from me, forgotten, and
buried in time.
Is that why you came up with
the idea of resurrecting
Project Spearhead?
That's right!
I will rule the
Soul Society!
You will bow before
my invading army!
Raaahh!
Their power has
skyrocketed!
[Kageroza]
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Until this moment,
my forces were
holding back their power!
Now you will see the true
capabilities of Reigai!
Observe.
He brought them
all back to life?!
Well...
They are Mod Souls,
after all.
As long as he retrieves
their core, he can make any
number of spares he wants.
I'm afraid it's much
more than just numbers.
I doubt even you could create
Reigai that would be able to
channel and withstand this
much Spirit Energy!
Shunsui!
Oh, boy. Here we go again.
Interesting.
This guy has got
my attention.
Lady Yoruichi!
Right.
Ya-haa!
Soi Fon!
Agh!
In your current condition,
none of you can expect to win.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ha HA HA HA HA HA HA!
The truth is...
...out of all the Mod Souls
that have been created...
...I was the first.
[Kon]
Hey Nozomi, if you're a Mod
Soul, that means part of your
body is enhanced, right?
It's definitely not your boobs,
so I'm guessing it's your--
[squeaky punch]
[Kon] [weakly]
muscular arms?
[Nozomi]
Pervert!
[Kon]
[gets kicked]
S-Strong legs?
[gets headbutted]
Head! You got a
hard head!