[theme music]
-Rukia Kuchiki.
Yes, we finally found you.
-Then give me that
blade, Soul Reaper.
-My name is Rukia,
Rukia Kuchicki.
-Hey, can I ask you something?
Do you have a crush on Ichigo?
--Huh?
-I'll be sitting
next to you from now.
My name is Rukia.
-[gasps].
It's-- it's you.
-Tell me, how do I
drink from this thing?
-Uh, you gotta
poke a hole in it.
You just use the sharp
end of your straw.
-[laughs].
-[groans].
-My goodness.
I better get you to
the nurse's office.
-That's all believable to
me, along with flying pigs
and the Tooth Fairy.
-Anyway, Rukia, tomorrow
I'll be sure to bring some
of my other yummy desserts so
you can try them out yourself.
Then we can enjoy them together.
-OK, I'll think about it.
-Aww, that's the same thing
you said to me last time.
You keep saying that,
Rukia, I'll think about it.
-Oh, really?
I guess I do.
-I did not.
Take that back right now.
-Do you want more?
RUKIA NARRATING: If I'm
going to leave here one day,
all these memories will only
be a burden, compassion,
friendship and affection.
-Ichigo and I are just friends.
That's all there is to it.
RUKIA NARRATING:
They're a nuisance.
All these feelings aren't
necessary for a Soul Reaper.
They're unbecoming of me.
I've remained in world
for far too long.
It's time to move on.
RENJI (OFFSCREEN):
finally get it, don't you?
-Huh?
-But you know, I really
gotta hand it to you.
I'm very impressed.
By skulking around so
long here in this world,
you actually managed to prolong
what little life you have left,
Rukia.
-Renji.
What in the world
are you doing here?
-So you're telling me you
had two hunters from the Soul
Society lurking
right behind you,
but you were so lost in thought
that you didn't even notice,
huh?
I'll grant you that you
spent the last few months
in that Gigai, but
still, don't you
think you've grown
just a little too lax?
Spit it out, Rukia.
So where is the human who
took all of your powers
away from you?
-What are you talking about?
Just because I'm inside
a Gigai right now,
it doesn't mean I've
lost any of my power.
And anyway, why
would you even think
it was a human who
took that power?
-It was a human.
It's obvious.
Just look at you.
Otherwise, you wouldn't have
that stupid human expression
on your face.
-[gasps].
-You're a runt from the
Rukon district like me.
And yet, you were taken in by
the noble house of Kuchiki.
They put a lot of time
and money into making
you the perfect Soul
Reaper, one of the elite.
Huh?
Am I wrong?
You're the great Rukia
Kuchiki, aren't you,
gaping like some
worthless human.
What the hell is
the matter with you?
Right, Captain Kuchiki?
-Huh?
Byakuya.
It's you, brother.
-Rukia.
-Passing your Soul Reaper powers
to a human is a grave sin.
Be glad the higher-ups
were compassionate
and let us handle this,
instead of the execution squad.
Now, tell us where
this human is, Rukia.
It's over.
We're taking you
in, and then, we're
going to find the human who
stole your powers and kill him.
Don't even try to protect him.
You know what just happened.
The only reason you
dodged my attacks
is because I let you dodge them.
The next move I make with
this blade will be fatal.
-[groans].
-This is it.
Huh?
[grunts]
-Two armed men attacking
a defenseless young girl?
I have to tell you,
it's not a pretty sight.
I don't know.
Just isn't my style.
Know what I mean?
-All right, kid.
You can see us.
So tell me, who
the hell are you?
-Hmm, just a classmate.
-Classmate, huh?
-One who hates Soul Reapers.
-Uryu Ishida, what
are you doing here?
-Just passing by, nothing
for you to worry about.
But if you must know,
I had a sudden urge
to go to Sunflower Seams,
this all-night thread shop
I frequent.
So I happened to be out
for a stroll this evening
and came across
your little party.
I mean come on, it's
not like I sense
the presence of Soul
Reapers in the city
and then ran off into the
night carrying a bag of needles
and thread with me
to use as an excuse
when I finally
caught up with you.
RUKIA (TO HERSELF): That's
the worst lie I ever heard.
He's not that stupid.
-Although I understand
if you're skeptical.
RENJI (OFFSCREEN): Hey, I
just asked you a question.
I said, who the
hell are you, kid?
Hey, that's fine.
You don't have to answer
if you don't want to.
We could just skip ahead to
the part where I kill you.
-Wait a minute, Renji, he's
got nothing to do with it.
-Just what are
you talking about?
I already gave you an answer.
As I already told you, I'm a
classmate of Rukia's, and I
hate Soul Reapers.
-Well, I don't care
much for your answers,
so why don't you try again?
-Uryu Ishiga, it's a pleasure.
-Huh?
What with you all of a sudden?
-Well, I just thought
you had a right to know.
You may be a Soul
Reaper, but you
should know the name of the
one who's about to kill you.
-That settles it.
I'm going to cut you in half.
-When in the hell is Rukia
planning on coming home
tonight?
I mean it's already
2:00 in the morning.
Ah, well, it's not so bad.
At least I can get a break
from the Soul Reaper business
tonight.
[muffled cries]
-What the hell?
OK, what's that noise?
[muffled cries]
-Back here.
You?
[muffled cries]
-Kon?
Just what exactly are
you doing back here?
[muffled cries]
-I thought you were
taking a little trip.
-Man, thanks for the solid.
You totally saved my ass.
-Don't mention it.
-I couldn't even see who was
coming in tied up like that.
I was trying to figure
out if it was you or not,
and all I had to go on was
sound, you know? [chuckles].
[screams]
What the hell did
you do that for?
Is that how you treat a
best friend right after he's
been through the worst
suffering of his life?
-Shut up.
We're not best
friends, and you stink.
-Look, it's not my fault.
Rukia was the one.
Oh my gosh.
That's right, Ichigo.
Rukia's in trouble.
-Get out of my face.
-Look at this right here.
Are you telling me you've
been home all this time,
and you didn't see this, pal?
-Yeah, so what is it?
-What's the matter with you?
It's obviously a farewell note.
-Farewell note?
-So then what were you doing
goofing around in the bathroom?
Shouldn't you have
already hit the road?
-What?
Are you even awake?
I didn't write the damn letter.
Rukia did, you fathead.
After that whole
incident with the dress,
I wanted to come back here
and say goodbye to her
before hitting the road.
And it wasn't with my
tail between my legs, OK?
I just thought it was the
honorable thing to do.
So I decided I'd pop in.
Rukia?
You see, Rukia,
she's-- she's left us.
She's left us for good.
-What do you mean?
She left without even
telling me she was going?
-Shut up.
Shut up.
How should I know?
I was right here with her
when she decided to go.
She just up and left
here without offering
even the slightest explanation.
Who the hell cares about you?
Oh, Rukia. [sobs].
-Oh, man.
Just what is this?
Damn, Rukia, what the
heck are you thinking?
"Enjoy decoding.
Before besir beten bereasons,
I befear I must bego."
Ah, what the hell?
"Here's a hint."
What the frig is this?
Son of a-- Why are there
so many Bs in this,
and what's with the damn bunny?
Oh, I get it.
Lose the bunnies.
"For certain reasons, I must go.
Do not look for me
and do not worry.
After you read this, make
sure that you burn it.
And also, if you can, keep
yourself hidden for a while."
I don't get it.
I mean, she doesn't even
give a reason for leaving.
-Don't you understand?
Something must have happened.
She said to burn the letter
and keep ourselves hidden.
What could be so
terrible that got
Rukia this worried about us?
Isn't it obvious?
Something's happened between
her and the Soul Society.
Use your head a little.
Rukia's is the
middle of something,
and she doesn't
want us involved.
So she-- she struck
out on her own.
-Ah.
-Poor Rukia.
What if she's, uh, dead.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
That's enough.
-Huh?
-We can't just go jumping
to conclusions, OK.
Let's just think for a minute.
All of this
yammering isn't going
to help us solve anything.
-Ichigo?
-Let's go come, Kon.
I'm changing into a
Reaper and finding Rukia.
-All right, I'm with you, buddy.
Uh, do you mean again?
-I don't have another choice.
I've got to get that
gikongen out of your belly.
-No, no wait!
[screams]
-Hold it.
-Forget it.
-Knock it off.
I don't have time for this.
Rukia's in danger right
now, and I can't do anything
to help her unless
I'm a Soul Reaper.
-(MUFFLED) Well,
that's not the point.
Who in the right mind would
want a hand shoved down
their throat?
-This suck just as bad for me
as it does for you, you idiot.
MR. HAT-AND-CLOGS
(OFFSCREEN): Hi, there.
Boy, it looks to me like
you're in a bit of a bind
this evening.
Is there anything I can do to
help speed things along here?
-[groans].
-Well, well.
Looks like you were
nothing but talk.
RUKIA (TO HERSELF):
Renji's strong.
He's even stronger than before.
I can barely move,
let alone stop him.
-Now then, let's finish
this off, shall we?
Remember this as you
depart this world,
Renji Abarai is the name
of the man who killed you.
-Hold on.
-Pleasure knowing you.
So who in hell's name are you?
-The name is Ichigo.
I'm the one who's
gonna beat your ass.
How's it going?
-Wearing a shihakusho.
I don't know you.
What squad are you from?
Check out that
overgrown zanpakuto.
-Oh, yeah?
So you're saying I
got a big one, huh?
It's funny.
To tell you the truth,
I've been thinking
this thing looked kind of
big next to Rukia's blade.
But you know, I've got
to say, up until now, I
haven't had anything
else to compare it to.
-The size of it reflects a
Soul Reaper's spirit energy.
How did a snot-nosed little
brat get a sword that size?
Is he for real?
-Ichigo, you fool.
Why did you come?
-Oh, I get it.
You're the lowly human
who took Rukia's powers,
aren't you, Carrot Top.
-Huh?
-Come on.
Come on.
What's wrong?
You got a big sword
just for show?
Huh?
-Ichigo!
-Don't go.
-Uryu.
-It's over.
Very soon, you'll be dead, and
Rukia will get her powers back.
And then, Rukia will go back
to the Soul Society to die.
Man, you are as
dumb as they come.
Rukia came out here
on her own, just
so you wouldn't have
to get involved.
You should have
stayed put at home,
but you had to
come play the hero.
Just what did you think
you could accomplish here?
You're not a Reaper.
You're a fake.
There's no way you could
hurt a real Soul Reaper.
You couldn't even lay
a scratch on one of us.
-Sorry about that.
I know you were in the
middle of saying something,
but you left yourself
so wide open there,
I just couldn't help myself.
I apologize.
Why don't you continue?
Were you saying something
about a scratch.
-You punk.
[growls]
CAPT. KUCHIKI (OFFSCREEN): You
let your guard down, Renji.
-Captain Kuchiki.
-This young man here,
Ichigo Kurosaki,
I believe I've seen him before.
There was a report from
the Secret Remote Squad.
He dealt the Menos Grande
quite a serious blow
and forced it back to
Hueco Mundo as well.
-Huh?
-You've got to be kidding me.
Man, the Secret Remote
Squad must really
be slipping these days.
This kid wounded a Menos Grande?
Who in their right mind would
believe that load of crap?
I mean look at him, Captain.
And that zanpakuto.
It's nothing but an
overgrown piece of junk.
He obviously can't
control his spirit energy.
So tell me, what's the
name of that monstrosity?
-Huh?
What's its name?
-You didn't even ask, did you?
-What?
You mean Rukia?
Wait, are you guys telling
me you all name your swords?
-I knew it.
You're not even able to ask
your zanpakuto its name.
And you really think you
could fight me as an equal?
Come back in 2,000 years.
[roar]
-Roar, Zabimaru.
Now open your eyes.
See what lies before you
and fall upon your prey.
[chuckles]
It's all over, you little runt.
You've lost to Renji Abarai
and will die where you stand.
[music playing]
KON NARRATING: It's time once
again for Kon's Bleach Triva.
Soul Reapers in the Soul
Society belong to 13 Court Guard
Squads
Byakua Kuchiki is the
captain of Squad 6.
Renji Abarai is his
second-in-command.
ICHIGO NARRATING: Just shut
up and do the preview already.