THEME SONG: (SINGING JAPANESE)
-You seem to think just because
you fought me once before, back
there in the world
of the living,
that now you know my true power.
Well, let me tell you
something, you amateur.
Whenever captain or
lieutenant rank Soul Reapers
are sent outside, severe
limits are placed on our powers
so that we won't adversely
affect the world of the living.
My strength right
now is five times
what it was that
first day we met.
So no matter how confident you
are or how strong you become,
there's still no way
you can defeat me.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): I see.
I suppose that means
that last attack of yours
was you best shot.
Because that didn't have
any effect on me at all.
So thank you.
If all I have to worry about
is 11 more like that one,
then I think I'm going
to be just fine, Renji.
-I'm going to enjoy this.
-Ichigo, you're hurt.
-Are you all right?
-Yeah.
It's nothing for
you to worry about.
-That's amazing.
I-I can't believe it.
How does he still remain
standing in the condition
that he's in?
-(INTERNAL MONOLOGUE) Damn.
My vision's getting blurry.
And my legs won't stop shaking.
Quit shaking, damn it.
-Heh.
You talk big, but it seems
that standing is about all
you can manage to do right now.
Heh.
It's over.
If you didn't exist and
she'd never met you,
Rukia wouldn't have to
go through all of this.
[grunts]
[gasp]
-Move, Ichigo!
-You won't get away.
-Ichigo.
[gasp]
-No way.
This is impossible.
It's madness, trying to
take on a lieutenant.
-Izuru, this is--
-It's Renji's lieutenant badge.
-I know this looks
suspicious, but he
did disappear in the
middle of the meeting.
I was worried about him, so I
went to the Squad 6 barracks.
And this badge is
all that I found.
It was in front of his office.
-Now tell me, are the
captains aware of this?
-Uh, I haven't told them.
-I see.
-At first, I thought
about telling
Captain Aizen about
what I'd found,
but I didn't want Renji to be
punished because of something I
had said.
-Until we know exactly
what's going on,
that was a very wise decision.
-Izuru, what could
this mean, for him
to remove this before he left?
-It must mean
something important.
Recently, Renji has been mulling
over the Rukia Kuchiki case.
All right.
I'll see if I can find out
what's happened to him.
-You stubborn fool.
You really want to
save her that much?
-You idiot.
No, not "want," I will.
-Don't mess with me!
Don't you understand Rukia
was condemned to die?
And that's because
you stole her powers.
Don't you get it, Ichigo?
It's all your fault.
It's your fault that
Rukia is going to die.
-You think I don't know that?
That's the reason
why I will save her.
(INTERNAL MONOLOGUE) I think
I finally figured him out.
His limit is three attacks.
-OK, listen up.
Now, when it comes down
to the heat of the battle,
remember this one thing.
The stronger the attack,
the more limitations
will be put upon the
number of the attacks.
-How so?
-Well, let's look
at it this way.
A revolver can be fired six
times, a missile only once.
In the same way, the number
of consecutive attacks
is always predetermined.
-(INTERNAL MONOLOGUE)
Which means,
when he first extends
his Zabimaru, that's one.
After that, he can
use it two more times.
And then, after
the third attack,
his Zabimaru returns
to its original state.
So let's test it.
-Look, it doesn't have to be
the same number each time.
The crucial element is the
maximum number of attacks,
especially in a
prolonged battle.
That is when your
enemy will be forced
to use the maximum
number of attacks.
-You bastard!
-(INTERNAL MONOLOGUE) One.
-If you can determine the
maximum number of attacks,
you'll know when
he's vulnerable.
-(INTERNAL MONOLOGUE)
That's two.
-Remember, the key thing
for you to keep track
is the last of his
consecutive attacks.
Wait for the moment between the
start of a consecutive attack
cycle.
-(INTERNAL MONOLOGUE)
And that's three.
-Damn it.
-At that point, your enemy
will be completely vulnerable.
-It's over, Renji.
-I told you.
There's no way that you'd
be able to defeat me.
[gasps]
-(INTERNAL MONOLOGUE)
He dodged it.
But--
-You look totally
shocked that I was
able to counter your attack.
Looking for an opening between
thrusts is a good strategy,
and your timing was perfect.
So, why weren't you
able to beat me?
The answer is simple.
Because you must be
slower than I am.
You see?
You cannot overcome it.
You can;t overcome the
difference in our powers.
Now do you understand?
You cannot save Rukia.
-Aah!
-Ichigo!
-That large release of
spiritual pressure just now,
I hope Ichigo's all right.
-Renji's spiritual pressure.
-Huh?
-The spiritual pressure.
-All right, follow me.
-Ahh, Ichigo.
-Ahh.
-Look, Ichigo's alive.
He's alive.
-You're damned right.
Guess he must have
dodged the blow.
-You are truly stubborn.
-Why, you, you really
tried to kill me just now.
-You bet.
You got that right.
And now, get ready because
I'm about to drive you
right into a corner.
I'll just keep pushing you
and pushing you to teach you
that you can use this technique
anytime, anywhere to attack.
-Come on, get real.
What just happened
was a total fluke.
There's no way I can keep on
using it whenever I want to.
URAHARA (OFFSCREEN):
You'll learn
to use it whenever you want.
Now listen here.
You are just on the
verge of learning
how to fight by being able to
summon your true Zanpakuto.
You have potential,
but your strength
is still only third or
fourth seat level at best.
In order to stay evenly matched
with a lieutenant or someone
of higher rank,
you will have to be
able to use this
technique at will.
That's all there is to it.
-Easier said than done.
It just about took
everything out of me then,
and I don't even remember much
about what I actually did.
-I already know all that.
That's why we're
going to do it again.
Understand?
See?
I am going to keep pushing
you and pushing you
so you can always
remember that attack.
Am I making myself clear?
-Wow.
The subject just hit the rock.
-Oh, time to dispatch
the first aid unit.
-Damn it.
He's pitiful.
So what's the
problem, Mr. Uruhara?
-Not yet.
-Damn it.
If he keeps this
up, I'll really--
-I'm so disappointed,
Ichigo, so very disappointed.
Sadly, your sword
exhibits only fear.
When you counter, it's
because you fear being killed.
When you attack,
you fear killing.
And when you try
to protect someone,
you fear you could let them die.
At this point, the only thing
that your sword speaks of
is senseless fright.
And that's not good.
What you do not need
in battle is fear.
Nothing will come of it.
When you counter, you
don't let them cut you.
If you protect someone,
you don't let them die.
When you attack, you kill.
Understand?
Can't you see?
My sheer resolve to kill you
is reflected in my sword.
Yeah.
That's better.
-His Zanpakuto.
-It's howling.
-It's as if they're
crying out, as
if they can't wait to do battle.
-Huh?
[chuckling]
-Oh, yeah.
Now you've got it, resolve.
-Don't do it, Ichigo.
-Do you think he intends
to keep on fighting?
-I do.
But you see?
He's acting differently
than he was before.
-Sorry to keep you waiting.
I found my resolve.
This time, I will get you.
-(INTERNAL MONOLOGUE) What's
with him all of a sudden?
Was he like this the last time?
No, it's different.
That time, he was just radiating
spirit energy at random.
This time, it's
calm and controlled.
And without a doubt,
it's much stronger.
-(INTERNAL MONOLOGUE) When you
counter, don't let him cut you.
-Why you!
-(INTERNAL MONOLOGUE)
When you protect someone,
don't let them die.
And when you attack him, kill.
-(INTERNAL MONOLOGUE) He got me.
What was that just now?
What was it, Zabimaru?
Damn it.
-Resolve.
-(INTERNAL MONOLOGUE) Resolve.
It hurts.
My body feels heavy.
I can't move my legs.
I can't left my arms.
Damn it.
Have I lost?
Damn.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
Rukia, [inaudible].
CLOSING THEME:
(SINGING JAPANESE)
MALE ANNOUNCER
(OFFSCREEN): Next time,
Renji's shocking past
will be revealed.
FEMALE ANNOUNCER (OFFSCREEN):
A youth's bittersweet memories
and a sentimental secret story.
BOTH ANNOUNCERS
(OFFSCREEN): Don't miss it.
-Izuru, Momo, you're going to
give everybody the wrong idea.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): The
wrong idea about what?
RENJI (OFFSCREEN): I wasn't
talking to you, amateur!