[theme music]
-Sosuke Aizen has invaded
the world of the living
with a force of Hollows
to destroy Karakura Town.
In order to stop
him, the Soul Reapers
have taken up
defensive positions
and are prepared for
a fight to the finish.
Under orders from
Genryusai Yamamoto
to enable members of
captain class to do battle,
Kisuke Urahara
constructed four pillars,
one at each corner of the town,
to form a giant Senkaimon.
He also had Karakura Town
relocated to the Soul Society,
and placed an identical
replica of the town
back in the world of the living.
Genryusai then stationed
one Soul Reaper
at the base of each
pillar and assigned
them to defend the
perimeter at all costs.
The warriors are Ikkaku
Madarame, Izuru Kira,
Shuhei Hisagi, and
Yumichika Ayasegawa.
All four easily
defeated the Hollows
who attempted to
destroy the pillars,
but each defender
now finds he is
faced with an even greater
threat, Espada Baraggan's
Fracciones.
-Hm.
Now what's the matter, Gin?
-Well, I've been
getting the feeling
that-- that Izuru
is really angry.
-You're worried about the
subordinate you abandoned?
Can you blame him?
Actually, I think
it may have helped.
-Excuse me?
-Yeah.
It's toughened him up, and I
think he's doing better now.
-Very good.
That's the face I
was hoping to see.
The face of a man in battle.
You're becoming an asset!
Now scrape the summit.
[shouts]
MEN: Crumble.
Crumble.
-Crumble to pieces,
along with your spirit.
Crumble to pieces, starting
with your big nose.
What so you mean, crumble to
pieces along with your spirit?
That's out of line,
you big, ugly jerk
-Yeah, well, you said
crumble to pieces
starting with your big nose.
You have no business
insulting my nose, you ugly
little bastard.
-What do you mean, ugly?
You empty headed freak!
Come on!
-I've been listening to you
call me ugly over and over again
for days now.
And that makes you the
real ugly one you know.
-Ha.
I don't think you've been
paying very close attention.
As a matter of fact,
you've used the word ugly
three more times than I have.
So, if calling someone
ugly makes you ugly,
then doesn't that make you
three times more ugly then me?
-That's enough.
Hm.
It appears that trading insults
isn't giving either of us
an advantage.
So let's simplify things.
I have a proposal for you.
-A proposal?
-Whoever dies is
automatically the ugly one.
-Makes sense to me.
When I win, it'll prove
I'm superior to you
in both fighting
skills and beauty.
-You never stop talking, do you?
It's going to make my
victory all the sweeter.
-Glad I amuse you.
-Enough fun.
I guess you won't mind if I make
things a little more serious.
Time for my special kill!
Watch out, kids.
You're in for it now.
Here comes beautiful
Charlotte Chuhlhourne's
ultra funky, fantastic,
dramatic, romantic, sadistic,
erotic, exotic, miraculously
apparatic guillotine attack!
My, my.
Is he gone already?
Maybe I overdid it.
Should have given him
more of a fighting chance.
Nice try.
YUMICHIKA (VOICEOVER):
I didn't expect
him to be so powerful
when he attacked.
He really is a monster.
-Well now, running
out of energy already?
You'll never defeat
my beauty if you're
exhausted before we even begin.
-Oh, I'm fine, really.
I was a little
sick to my stomach
because of the stupid name
you gave your attack technique
a minute ago.
-Huh?
You must be jealous.
That's the only
possible explanation.
You're jealous of my unique
and exceptional word skills.
Why don't you admit it?
-Stop spewing nonsense while
you're swinging your seaweed
hair all over the place.
-Wha-- What did you just
call my beautiful hair?
Seaweed?
How dare you talk
about my lovely,
jet black hair with
it's shimmering purple
highlights and compare it to
something as common and gross
and seaweed.
-If you have the nerve
to be that nasty,
then I don't feel guilty calling
you a big, black toadstool!
-You think I'm a toadstool?
-Let's face it.
You're feeling inferior
because you found out
my amazing killer
technique was unstoppable.
Believe me.
I understand your feelings.
Your mouth is the only
thing operating effectively.
-OK, why don't you
give it another try?
We'll see if your
confidence is justified.
Maybe you got lucky
the first time.
-You think so, huh?
All right then.
Since you insist, I'll be
happy to play your little game.
Let's try this one more time.
-Ready.
-Special kill!
No complaints.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Beautiful Charlotte
Chuhlhourne's
stylish, dangerous,
psychedelic, variable
economic, continental,
incredible, unbelievable,
shining attack!
-Take this!
-Seems you can fight.
-Have you changed your mind
about my lack of energy?
-Apparently you were
holding out on me.
That's very good.
It's what I would expect
from a rival warrior.
-Rival warrior, hm?
You're showing me some
respect at long last.
Not that I'm impressed.
How can I take it seriously
when it comes from someone
with a weird hairdo like yours?
-Argh.
You filthy, rotten bastard!
How dare you attack my
hair and spoil my beauty?
A mane so perfect, people
gasp in admiration.
So perfect that
people are amazed.
So perfect that people
literally cannot find the words
to describe it.
You have crossed the line.
Unforgivable.
Unforgivable!
Now you are going
to pay for this!
-Is he going to do it?
-Ready to die?
Glitter.
Reina de Rosas!
-What the hell?
[gasp]
-Ha ha ha ha.
What the hell is that?
[laughter]
-Well, that's an
unexpected reaction.
Ignoramus.
I can see what a
Philistine you are.
My beauty must truly be
unimaginable to someone as ugly
as yourself.
Allow me to educate you.
The design that goes from
my shoulders to my waist
is stunning.
It's an artfully
arranged tableau
that conjures a
silhouette of flowers.
You may have noticed
the sleek accoutrement
that adorn my ankles and wrists.
These delightful
accents complete a look
that possesses both
novelty and elegance
while maintaining a balance
to the overall look--
pay attention!
-I'm so sorry!
Wait a minute.
What in the world am
I apologizing for?
This guy's making my head spin.
I mean, look at him!
He's ridiculous!
[laughter]
-That's weird.
I could swear I heard Yumichika
laughing his ass off somewhere.
But that would be impossible.
He wouldn't do that
during a fight.
Hm?
Ha!
Too slow, big boy.
I told you, you can't win this
fight with just muscles alone.
[panting]
-I've finally calmed down.
-I'm glad you got
control of yourself.
I have an idea of
what happened here.
From what I can tell, you
were so dazzled by my beauty,
it threw you completely
into hysterics.
Isn't that right?
Ah!
-He's faster than he was before!
-Ready for a surprise attack?
-Huh?
Damn.
-Ha!
-Dammit.
That single assault broke my
arm in three different places.
-Yoo-hoo!
So, are you beginning to
appreciate my beauty yet?
How about a closer look?
-Not a chance.
CHARLOTTE: I guess you
need more instruction.
But don't worry, I can help.
Be thankful.
I'm going to be giving you
a customized beauty lesson.
-I think I'll pass.
I'm not interested in
experiencing your wacko
aesthetics.
-Oh!
Wacko?
-Now bloom, Fuji Kujaku.
[gasping]
-Heh, heh, heh.
-Sorry.
Fooled ya.
-What?
-Your weapon is Fuji Kujaku.
How appropriate its
name would be so plain.
But it's completely ineffectual,
even though it has four blades.
[shouting]
[scream]
-Custom Kill!
Beautiful Charlotte
Chulhourne's lovely, fanatic,
frenetic, artistic, aquatic,
gigantic, climactic, dynamic,
didactic, historic--
oh, I bit my tongue.
Here comes my Thunder Punch!
Pity.
Biting my tongue caused my
attack to lose half its power.
But did you notice how
both my speed and power
have increased
since I transformed?
You have to understand, it's
all because of my beauty.
Can you feel it?
You have to admit, it's
truly overwhelming.
Power is beauty.
Beauty is power.
Isn't it about time
you opened your mind
and accepted that idea?
-I can't accept it.
-I see.
So you're unable to
understand what I'm saying?
OK, all right.
I can forgive you.
The fact is, when
you think about it,
it isn't a crime to like
an appreciation of beauty.
I'm sure lots of people are
deficient in that regard.
Truthfully, it's
something to be pitied.
-Oh, really?
CHARLOTTE: Living with
such a vulgar aesthetic
must be absolute
torture for you.
Believe me, I have the utmost
sympathy for your condition.
In fact, since I am the object
of your tortured ignorance,
relieving your pain is my duty.
-You like to flap your gums
in the wind, don't you?
-Please accept this.
Special kill, beautiful
Charlotte Chulhourne's
delicious, apparitious,
superstitious, surreptious,
expeditious, ceremonious,
felonious, glorious,
uproarious, sexy,
sexy, glamorous Cero!
-It's just an ordinary Cero!
Damn.
That's a dirty little technique.
The attack is so broad, there's
nowhere to get away from it.
It's over!
-Oh, really?
For whom?
-You still think those
blades give you an advantage?
Forget it!
-Wait a minute.
-Now do you get it?
If I say it's over,
believe it, my friend.
A princess always gets her way.
It may not be fair, but
that's the way things are.
-This blackness.
What is it?
-Rosa Blanca.
The Sentence of the White Rose.
My most beautiful, and my
most cruel battle technique.
You're enveloped in this
brier covered with black.
This is your fate.
You will die here,
unseen by anyone,
smothered in white petals.
-Completely unseen by anyone?
-That's right.
The ebony black brier shuts
out all views from the outside.
It's so efficient
that no one will even
be able to detect the presence
of your spiritual pressure.
Your life force will continue to
weaken until it's extinguished.
The moment of your death
will go entirely unnoticed.
It's an ugly way to die,
alone and unmourned.
But it's a fitting end for an
ugly little warrior like you,
who has no sense of grace
or beauty in his life.
-No one can see in here at all?
In that case, thank you.
-Huh?
Tear in frenzy, Ruri'iro Kujaku.
[gasp]
-What is all this?
-The final act.
Look around.
-Are those buds?
Why are they growing?
-Your spirit energy is slowly
collecting within these blooms.
-What are you saying?
-The flowers are feasting
on your life force.
All the spirit
energy you radiate
is being stolen absorbed
into these buds.
Do you understand?
-Why did you wait to
use such a technique?
-If you had fought
an ordinary battle,
I wouldn't have had
to use it at all.
However, you isolated us.
You created a space where
no one could see in,
and nothing that happened
inside would ever be revealed.
It was the perfect place
to use my secret weapon.
This way, when you're gone
it will remain a secret.
You've created your
own death trap.
Think of it as an honor.
You're the only one who will
ever see my Ruri'iro Kujaku.
-Ruri'iru Kujaku?
-Your time is almost over.
The moment those
flowers bloom will
be the moment your life
ends, Charlotte Chulhourne.
-No!
[theme music]
YUMICHIKA: Those blooms really
made the end of the episode.
I wonder, though, do you think
your screen was big enough?
CHARLOTTE: Well, now
that I think about it,
you make a good point.
I'll tell you what?
Why don't I just do it over?
YUMICHIKA: Mm, sorry.
We don't have time for that.
CHARLOTTE: No!