[theme music]
-[groan] Damn it.
This hangover is killing me.
-Dumbass, I drank more
than you, and I feel fine.
It's your smoking that makes you
feel like crap every morning.
-[groan] Shut up!
I didn't hear you give me
crap like that yesterday
after I kicked your ass.
Want some more?
-Yeah?
Come on.
Bring it!
Draw your sword, you
arrogant little punk,
and I'll polish you off and then
sweep you up with the trash.
-Polish me off?
Who the hell talks
like that anymore?
You better get ready
to die, old man.
-Huh? [groan]
[wind blowing]
-Hm?
-Huh?
-What the hell kind
of a sound is that?
[shouting]
-[together] Good
morning, Captain Zaraki!
What a surprise!
Thanks for giving us the
honor of sweeping the streets
for you! [shouts] Huh?
If
-You two are gonna goof off,
try to be so obvious about it.
-And you'd better get this
street clean enough to eat off,
or I'll kill you both.
-You heard the man.
Keep up the good work if
you want to live. [laughs]
-Why the hell would
the captain have
that fool Aramaki
tagging along with him?
-Forget that.
Weren't there two women
riding on Zaraki's back
instead of just one?
-Well, just which way am I
supposed to go now, woman.
-I think it's probably that--
-No!
It's this way!
-That hurt.
What was that for, Yachiru?
That wasn't very nice.
-[laughs] Kenny knows
it's this way, too.
Don't you Kenny?
-Perhaps we would
be better off just
listening to Orihime, Captain.
After all, the lieutenant
is not exactly known
for accurate sense of direction.
-Perhaps you should shut
up, cueball head. [spits]
-Oh, I'm gonna
kill her for that!
-Hey, come on.
Keep your cool, now.
You have to admit,
Ikkaku, you were
kind of asking for that one.
-Enough of all your bickering.
I'm just going to go
with my instincts.
-All right!
-That's an excellent plan, sir.
-You go, Kenny, and we'll
follow you anywhere.
You're the best!
URYU: Huh?
A little butterfly just
flew into the room.
Such a fragile thing.
Heh.
Does this mean that it's
spring in the Soul Society.
-Oh, great.
Now he's seeing butterflies
and talking to himself.
Why don't you see
if you can catch
the pretty butterflies, Uryu.
-What?
Why would I do that?
And where do you get off
calling me by my first name.
You are nowhere near a close
enough friend for that.
And if you're going to
make insulting comments
about chasing butterflies,
then you never will be.
-Hey, who said I
wanted to be friends
with an oddball like
you in the first place?
URYU: You must have thought
you could be my friend,
or you never would
have called me that.
GANJU: It's part of
the Shiba clan legacy
to always reach out
in friendship, even
to those who don't deserve it.
URYU: What kind of
ridiculous legacy is that?
-Sh.
[crowd talking]
-What?
What's wrong?
-Listen.
Don't you hear that?
-[together] Hm?
[crowd talking]
-Yeah, now that you mention it.
MAN: [shout] What are you doing?
MAN 2: Get out of here!
MAN: Get out of his way.
[shouting]
-Well, whatever it
is, it does seem
like it's headed this way, huh?
-I'm sure it's just some kind
local parade or celebration
or something.
-Huh?
-You think so?
[shouting]
GANJU: What the hell?
We're done for!
We're all gonna die!
It's-- it's you.
But how can this be?
[shout] I never wanted
to see you again,
Captain Kenpachi Zaraki.
Huh?
Not you, too.
I remember your stupid
haircut and your massive ego.
-I wish I could say the same.
I have a good
memory for the faces
I've seen, with the
exception of the ugly ones.
-Hm.
You don't know what you're
talking about, pretty boy.
The fact is, everyone
tells me that I
look cooler than ever with
all these bandages on.
Besides, how could
you recognize me
from before with
my face covered?
URYU (VOICEOVER):
Interesting that he
didn't argue about being ugly.
[groaning]
-Hm?
-Huh?
Orihime?
-Oh, hey, Uryu, Chad, and Ganju.
I'm so glad to see the
three of you are all OK.
[groaning] Ow, Yachiru!
[laughing]
-Stop!
Stop!
MAN: Byakuya, sir.
It is almost time, master.
You should leave
for the Sokyoku.
-Very well, then.
I'm off now, Hisana.
TETSUZAEMON: Ah!
This is terrible!
How could I do such
a thing? [shout] Yeah
A thousand pardons, my captain.
Somehow, I fell asleep
sitting on the toilet.
And I'm late arriving
to assist you.
Please allow me to kill
myself as punishment.
KOMAMURA: Never mind that.
Calm yourself, Tetsuzaemon.
Everything is fine.
All the preparations
have been made.
-Uh, huh?
-You needn't take the blame
for everything, Tetsuzaemon.
-Huh?
Well, thank you
for saying so, sir.
-Don't try to hide it.
You're worried, aren't you?
You think I may yet doubt the
legitimacy of this execution.
And so you've been making
excuses and arriving late
to give me more time
so I can think it
through until I'm convinced.
-Uh, exactly so, sir.
-Do not worry.
I have no doubts.
-[gasp]
-My loyalty and dedication to
Captain Yamamoto are absolute.
When I was despised and
made an outcast because
of my appearance, he was the
only one who believed in me.
Why would I not spend
the whole of my spirit
to repay that debt to him?
I have no doubts.
If he should ask, I
would give my life.
How about you, Kaname?
-For me, the path
ahead is crystal clear.
The road the
sightless eyes choose
will always be the one
not dyed red with blood.
And I believe that you and
I walk the same path, Sajin.
[chewing]
-What an annoyance.
What a pain in the ass.
As if it wasn't bad
enough with these Ryokas
sneaking around and then
some kind of murder.
Now we got captains
and lieutenants
all arguing about whether the
execution is legit or not.
What's there to talk about
when the superiors have
made their final decision?
Pretty stupid, don't
you think, Captain?
SUI-FENG: Idiotic.
-Huh?
-I have no interest in
who's right or wrong.
I am interested
only in the mission
and in executing my orders
as the captain of Squad Two.
I kill enemies.
That's all there is.
-Yeah, huh?
I guess so.
SUI-FENG: You, too, Marechiyo.
You had best remember
where your loyalty lies.
If you cross me, or
trying to get in my way,
then you, too, are my enemy.
-Yeah.
Well, I'll be sure
to remember that.
[humming]
[grunting]
-Here you are, Captain.
I've been looking for
you for an hour now.
What are you doing
just lying there?
Get up.
You've got to get ready
to go to the Sokyoku.
-Well, I can't get up just now.
I seem to be having a little
problem here at the moment.
Tell me what you
think I should do.
-Why?
What is it?
KYORAKU: OK.
You see, I put this blade
of grass in my mouth,
thinking it would relax me.
But I guess it must be toxic
or something, because now,
the more I chew
it, the more I can
feel it burning the
inside of my mouth.
-Try spitting it out!
-Let me ask you, Nanao.
What do you think I should do?
-It doesn't matter what I think.
And we both know that.
Regardless of any
advice I might give you,
you'll just go
right ahead and do
what you were
going to do anyway.
But don't worry about it.
I'll be sure to walk
several steps behind you
when we get there.
That way, I won't get
dragged into whatever trouble
you cause.
-That's too bad.
That means I'll be on my own.
And old man Yamamoto
will blame it all on me.
[gasping]
KENPACHI: Another dead end.
-Well, let me explain.
You see, it's not that easy.
Guiding a big group
through a city
is really more luck
than it is science.
ORIHIME: Sure, you could run
into dead ends 10 or 12 times
before finding your way.
-I told you we shouldn't
let the lieutenant lead.
What would you
expect to happen when
you follow someone around who
has no sense of direction?
[shout] Someone get
this creature off me.
-Captain?
-Yes?
You should be ashamed
of yourselves, boys,
sneaking around like that.
Show yourselves.
Hiding your spiritual pressure
in order to stalk others
is no way for a captain to act.
[bang]
KOMAMURA: Your arrogance
knows no bounds, Kenpachi,
to talk that way, given what
you appear to be involved in.
[gasping]
-What are you doing
with these Ryoka?
Did you lose your self-respect
when you were defeated?
[gasp] Captain Komamura,
Captain Tosen, Lieutenant Iba
and Lieutenant Hisagi?
Oh, damn.
-Don't get your
panties in a twist.
We still outnumber
them almost two to one.
-Yeah, but it's not
numbers I'm worried about.
KENPACHI: Quit whining.
Who ever said any
of you are going
to be in this fight
in the first place?
After all, even taking these
guys on four against one
won't give my blade much
more than a little practice.
KOMAMURA: Four to one, you say.
So, you think you are good
enough to fight all of us
by yourself, Kenpachi?
Though your strength
is well known,
Captain, it is no match for
your excessive self-confidence,
as you will soon learn.
KENPACHI: You talk
too much, Sajin.
Just hurry up and fight already.
And the four of you had better
attack at the same time.
If you come at be from all
four sides, then one of you
might actually be
able to wound me.
-Uh, Captain, sir?
What about us?
What will we do, sir?
-Go!
You'll just get in the way.
-OK, OK.
But he didn't have to
be so mean about it.
-Come on.
Get over it, Whiskers.
Kenny's happy right now.
Believe me, you don't
want to mess with that.
MAKIZO (VOICEOVER):
Don't tell me
you've changed my
nickname to Whiskers!
-We're gonna go now!
We'll go find Ichigo,
and you catch up later.
OK Kenny?
KENPACHI: I'll be right there.
-Muscles, Jiggles, Monkey,
Pencil, let's get going!
-Uh, what did you say?
-Huh?
Did I just get nicknamed Pencil?
-Oh, you'll figure
it out eventually.
You too, Whiskers.
Run everybody, run!
-Wait for me!
-We're coming!
-I'm not staying here!
-I'll be right there, huh.
It seems you're deliberately
trying to provoke us now.
Or do you really believe you
can defeat all four of us
that easily?
Either way, it looks like
you've lost your grasp
on sanity, Kenpachi.
KENPACHI: Ha, sanity.
What would I do with
something as useless as that?
Lucky for me, I never
had any such thing.
ORIHIME: Yachiru, wait a minute!
-Hm?
-Are you sure it's a good
idea to leave your captain?
He's pretty heavily
outnumbered back there.
-Oh, no problem.
Those guys could never beat
Kenny, even if was 20 to one!
-Yachiru.
MAKIZO (VOICEOVER):
This Ryoka girl
sure has some nerve,
calling the lieutenant
by her first name like that.
Either that or she's crazy!
-Right, you two?
Can you believe
nerve of this girl?
What do you think, sir?
Huh?
Hey, where did they go?
-Captain, allow me.
-And me.
Let the two of us
go first, Captain.
-You idiots.
I told you I want all four
of you to attack me at once.
YUMICHIKIA: You
think so little of us
you would send in
only your lieutenants?
What an insult to our captain.
-If that's the case, sir, then
the two of us should go first.
-What the-- why didn't
you two clear out
along with the others,
like I told you?
-Listen, all four of you.
You've got a lot
of nerve to think
your two lousy lieutenants
are good enough
to take on Squad 11's
Captain Zaraki by themselves.
In fact, you should
be happy just
have to me as your opponent.
Right, Captain?
-[laugh] So in other words,
you two clowns want to get
in on the fight?
All right, then.
Go.
I'll give them over to you.
But take it somewhere else,
so you don't get in my way.
Or I'll have to kill
you both myself.
-[together] Thank you, sir.
-I can hardly believe
what I'm hearing--
you guys arguing over
who's going to fight us.
You certainly have
gotten pretty cocky
since the last time
I saw you Ikkaku.
-A coward who had to
transfer to another squad
just because he
couldn't make the grade
and become a lieutenant
in ours has no business
lecturing me, Tetsuzaemon.
-You're going to pay
for that, Ikkaku.
-Well, if I do,
it won't be here.
Let's get moving.
I have no desire to be
killed by our captain.
-Yes, let's do it.
Are you two ready to take
this fight somewhere else?
-It won't matter.
You'll die just the same.
KENPACHI: All right, then.
We can finally get
down to business.
Of course, your number
has been cut by half.
This will probably be no more
of a workout than my morning
exercises.
-And still, you brag.
I think the time has come to
put an end to your arrogance!
Here I come!
-[gasp]
-Now stand back, Sajin.
I will break all his limbs.
Suzumushi Nishki.
Benihiko!
-It's over.
Not even Kenpachi Zaraki could
have survived such an attack.
KENPACHI: Ha.
[laughs]
That's it?
That's all you got?
[gasping]
-Impossible.
Tenken, Benihiko-- How
can he still be standing?
KENPACHI: Oh, dear.
Forget what I said before.
My morning exercise
is tougher than this.
-Well then, I guess
I'll be doing.
ICHIGO: All right.
-Tell me the truth, Yoruichi.
What do you think?
Do you still think he's
going to be able to do this?
Because we're out of time.
Can he really
reach Bankia today?
-Let's go, Ichigo.
One more time now.
And let me be clear-- just
because the hour is drawing
near, I don't intend
to go easy on you.
-No, of course, you won't.
And that's because I'm
not going to give you
the chance to go easy on me.
-Renji.
-Hm?
-Do you remember
the first time when
you were a child that you stood
up and walked on your own?
-What?
Of course not.
No one remembers
anything that early.
-If you don't remember doing
it, and yet you did it,
it means that you weren't
conscious of it at the time.
So how did you
know how to do it?
The answer is all
humans are born already
knowing how to stand up, just
as birds are born knowing how
to fly, and fish are born
already knowing how to swim.
It's because of what
we call instinct.
All living creatures
use instinct
to obtain their
natural power when
the time comes that
they need them.
That's what Ichigo's
face reminds me of.
I think he knows instinctively,
somewhere deep down
inside, that he has that power.
And that is why I
still believe that he
will be the one to reach Bankai.
-[shout]
[music - "happy people"]
-Yo, how's everybody doing?
I'm your idol, Kon, and
this is the last installment
of the Soul Reaper guidebook.
Last but not least is
that legendary man.
By the way, the new Soul
Reaper golden dictionary
will begin right after
the next episode,
so be sure to keep your
eyes peeled for it.
RUKIA: You mean there's more?