[music playing in japanese]
-I hate to spoil
your fun, Mr. Hollow.
But Ichigo's little
busy right now.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I always forget to do that.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I am Ishin Kurosaki.
[laughter]
[roars]
-Remember this.
You should never
judge your opponent
by the size of his Zanpakuto.
Don't talk to me
about Soul Reaper
lore until you know that much.
-(GRUNTING) Impossible.
Ahhh!
-(GASPING) He used
just one strike.
-Wait a minute.
I'm really confused.
What happened?
-Ichigo's father just
saved all our lives.
-Nobody here got hurt.
-What the hell?
I don't believe this!
Am I losing my mind?
This is crazy.
[laughs]
-Is that really
Ichigo's goofy old dad?
-Let's hear it for Daddy!
-Have you avenged her?
-Has justice been meted out?
-Look who's shown.
[footsteps]
-Urahara.
-It's been a long time since
I've seen you, my friend.
Huh.
I see you haven't
lost your touch.
That's good to know.
-Why are you being so civil?
It's not like you.
-Oh, come now.
I don't want you to blame me
because your spirit energy has
withered away.
That would be upsetting.
-Ah, well, you
can stop worrying.
I wouldn't have blamed
you if it did wither up
and disappear after
all this time.
Some may have seen it that
way, but that's not my style.
Tell me.
How's it feel, being a Soul
Reaper once again after 20
years?
-All right, I suppose.
-I see.
And do you feel better now?
-(BREATHING OUT)
In some ways, yes.
Truth is, I never held a grudge
against that stupid Hollow
the first place.
If I'm being perfectly
honest with myself,
there's only one
thing I've really
regretted over
these past 20 years,
and that was my lack of power.
The fact that, in
spite of everything,
I couldn't save
Masaki that night.
-Yeah, some things never change.
It seems your son is much
like you in that regard.
-What?
You're wrong about that.
-Oh, I don't think so.
-I said, you're
wrong about that!
-Then I guess we'll just
have to agree to disagree.
While we're on the
subject of your son,
did you happen to notice--
-Yes.
It appears they've
made contact with him,
just as you
suspected they would.
The masked army, the Visoreds.
-The Visoreds?
-What are they?
-I don't know, but he
called them the Masked Army.
They're a lawless gang
of former Soul Reapers
who attempted to
obtain Hollow powers
through the use of
forbidden techniques.
Their names and
whereabouts are unknown.
They've kept their
presence completely hidden.
They're obviously dangerous.
At the moment, the
only thing I do know
is that the Arrancars
and the Visoreds
don't appear to be
working together.
-That's helpful.
We don't need our enemies
forming alliances.
In one way, we're lucky.
The Visoreds don't
trust any Soul Reapers,
former or otherwise.
-So I've heard.
-In spite of their
hatred for Soul Reapers,
they made contact with your son.
That must mean they--
-Yeah.
If they're willing to
go to those lengths,
they must be preparing
for some kind of battle,
just like we are.
The only explanation
can be that they
must have noticed this sudden
change in the Arrancar as well.
-So that last Hollow, the one
who was found with the broken
mask--
-He called it Arrancar.
-Oh?
-Is that right?
-So, we should be
calling this an Arrancar?
-Mmm.
As you already know, we've
been aware of Arrancars
popping up from time to
time, but this one, this one
surprised me.
This Arrancar's
level of development
was beyond anything
I'd ever seen before.
The Arrancars have been stuck
at the same level for decades.
But this one had power.
Serious power.
Something's happened.
I didn't take much
to figure it out.
I guess you know what it means.
Sosuke Aizen must
have made a deal
with the would-be Arrancars.
He's going to help them
achieve their goal.
It's the same goal
he's been chasing.
He's trying to create
a true Arrancar using
the power of the Hogyoku.
-Ehh.
Well, according to
my calculations,
I figured it would take
another year for the Hogyoku
to reach full power.
-I think it's safe to say
that power isn't yet complete.
The Arrancar we encountered
was still flawed.
His power has surged, but
his spiritual pressure
is still imperfect.
He was probably a
prototype, sent here
to collect data on how well
he could fight at this level.
That's this level now,
but who knows how long.
The Hogyoku's power
is immeasurable.
There's no question Aizen
will perfect his prototype.
His research must be
very near completion.
Once he has
something that can be
used in the front
lines of battle,
he'll lead the true Arrancar
an army of Menos Grande
and they will conquer the world.
How do we fight back?
-We'll figure something out.
We just have to rise
to the occasion.
With the situation
the way it is,
everyone will be mobilizing
for war, friend and foe alike.
You, me, the Visoreds, and not
to mention the Soul Society.
Hey, someone's coming
in this direction.
-Eh?
I know this spiritual pressure.
-Yeah, it's your son, Ishin.
If he meets you like
this, I'm afraid it
will make things
difficult for you.
Listen up, everyone.
It's time for us to go home.
ALL: All right, we're leaving.
-I see.
Message received.
I'll leave immediately.
[footsteps]
-This is such a pain in the ass.
-Thank you all for gathering
here on such short notice.
With that formality
out of the way,
we shall now begin
the Captains' Meeting.
[buzz of conversation]
-So who the hell did that other
spiritual pressure belong to?
Whoever it was is
gone without a trace.
This is all because of
that bastard, Hirako.
-You see, I'm a Visored.
You are one of us, Ichigo.
You do not belong
with them, Ichigo.
Just stop fighting it.
You've got to know what you
do not belong with them.
-Tsst.
-I do have one condition.
You must swear to
me you'll never
associate with a
Soul Reaper again.
-Mmph.
[buzz of conversation]
-(BREATHING HARD) Hi, Ichigo!
Good morning!
-Hello there, Ichigo!
-I can't believe it.
Hirako showed up like
nothing happened.
-Good morning!
Uh, let's see.
Shinji, right?
-Whoa!
You remembered my name!
I can't believe it.
[squeals]
-You're great, Orihime!
-What?
What is this?
Just what do you
think you're doing?
-What's going on?
Who's making all that noise?
-Who in the hell are you?
-What do you mean, who am I?
You've got a lot of
nerve, asking me that.
You act like you're best
friends with the people
in this classroom.
I've known them a lot
longer than you have,
Mr. Johnny Come Lately!
-Already been shot down
this morning, have we?
-Get your hands off
of her, you pervert!
She obviously doesn't like it!
-Are you crazy?
If she didn't like it, she
would have screamed or hit me
over the head with her book bag.
But she didn't do
that, which is proof
that she's not uncomfortable.
Am I right, Orihime?
-You're implying that I'm
the one who's out of line?
You're behaving badly
and everyone knows it!
Isn't that right?
Come on, guys!
Tell this creep off.
Give me some support!
-It's all right.
Don't worry.
I've got your back.
-Leave this to me.
He won't bother us anymore.
-But wait, Chizuru.
What are you gonna--
-He has to pay!
Right?
Orihime is too sweet a
girl to say something,
even if she's being
treated badly.
A creep like you takes
advantage of her good nature,
and indiscriminately goes
around attempting to hug
her should not be
allowed to live.
-Um, I know this isn't
something you want to hear,
Chizuru, but
following your logic,
you should be the first
one who gets wiped out.
Ahh!
-I am the hands of justice!
Special attack,
Chizuru Genocide!
-Maybe you could just let
him off with a warning?
-Mmm.
-Ahh!
[footsteps]
-Come out here for
a second, Hidako.
-Ahh!
-Oh, that's odd.
What do you think is going
on with Ichigo, guys?
In all the years we've
gone to school together,
I've never known him
to be so protective.
-I-- Ichigo?
[whimpers]
-Aaugh!
Maybe you're not aware of
it, but that really hurts!
And what are you getting
so mad about, anyway?
It's not like Orihime
is your girlfriend!
I mean, let's face, Ichigo.
You're socially inept.
You and I both
know that a hottie
like that is never gonna give
you the time of day, right?
-Shut the hell up!
And I expect you to apologize to
her when you go back in there.
You should know better!
-Yeah, well, that's just
a matter of opinion.
But either way, you
don't have the right
to be telling me what to do.
Blehhhh!
-Hirako, all I want to
know is what the hell
you're doing here.
-Well now, that's
a stupid question.
What do you think I'm doing?
I'm a student and I
have to go to school.
-You had one reason for
coming to this school.
It was to somehow recruit
me into your ranks!
And if so, you have no
reason to be here anymore.
-I'll be the judge of that.
Surely you don't
think I've given up.
I mean, just because of
what happened between you
and me yesterday.
You'll find I don't
give up so easily.
I'm going to follow you
around until you say yes.
Besides, it's too late.
Once the symptoms
appear, Visoreds
can never become normal again.
And no matter what you may
think, the die is cast.
You're already on
our side, Ichigo.
[gasps]
-(SIGHING) Orihime,
the big guy, Four Eyes.
You think that they're
all friends of yours?
Well, you're wrong.
Fact is, they're only your
friends for the time being.
If you continue to
be a Soul Reaper,
sooner or later you'll be
swallowed up by the Hollow
inside because you
will lose your sanity.
When that happens,
it's all over.
Your power will destroy
everything around you.
Your friends and your future.
Even your identity will
be blown to smithereens.
Oh, come now, Ichigo.
Don't tell me you
haven't already noticed.
Your inner Hollow is slowly
starting to take over.
It's already so powerful
you can barely control it.
You should come with me, Ichigo.
I'll show you how
to save your sanity.
[clock chiming]
-Ichigo!
How about we swing by the old
arcade on the way home today.
What do you say?
-Mmph.
Sorry.
I need some time alone.
-Ichigo!
Huh?
What's the deal, Mizuiro?
Ichigo sure is acting weird.
-Really.
Because you know, he's
always kind of weird.
-This isn't ordinary weird!
It's something else.
What I'm talking
about is that stuff
that happened after
the summer break.
You remember how
he was back then?
-You're imagining
things, Mr. Asano.
-Huh?
What's with calling me "Mister?"
-What do you mean, Mr. Asano?
You're becoming paranoid.
-Whaaa!
You just did it again!
Don't tell me I'm paranoid!
Why are you and everyone
else being so distant all
of a sudden?
I know you're all against me.
I hate it when you do that!
-Man.
I'm bone tired.
And what's with that test
right after we get back
from summer break?
I guess I'm just not used this
kind of activity these days.
And why do I have to go to
that stupid school and recruit
Ichigo?
That's not making the
best use of my talents.
[bam]
-Aaugh!
What the hell?
Wait a minute, who did that?
You're-- Hi-- Hiyori.
[fwap!]
-Why's it taking you
so long to accomplish
one lousy mission, dumbass?
-Sorry about that!
-Have you done anything?
Where's Ichigo Kurasaki?
-There are complications.
-Complications?
You know I don't
like complications.
Bring him here right now.
Get off your butt and find
some way to talk him into it.
-That's the problem!
I tried to talk to him into it
and he wouldn't listen to me!
-If he won't cooperate, then
use force to make him join.
-What?
That's not what you
told me the other day!
You told me to persuade him!
-Ugh.
-There you are.
Mmph.
-Orihime!
-Shinji.
-Huh?
[smack]
-Why was someone following
you, you dipstick?
-I knew.
Even if I asked him
directly, Ichigo
wouldn't tell me
what was going on.
He'd tell me it was nothing
to be concerned about,
but that's not true.
So I thought I'd
ask you, Shinji.
Who are you, and what
you want with Ichigo?
-Huh.
You've got some nerve!
You think you could
just ask and we'll
tell you everything
you want to know.
[whimper]
-I'm Hiyori Sarugaki.
CHAD AND ORIHIME: Huh?
-Don't make me repeat it.
All right, you two.
I told you my name.
Now it's your turn.
Tell me yours.
-I'm Orihime Inoue.
-And I'm Yasutora Sado.
-Huh.
A princess and a tiger, huh?
Those are pretty
impressive names.
Well, our names only
mean monkey and common.
I have to say,
we're very jealous.
Really.
-I don't know what
you're talking about.
The only one that's
common around here is you.
Even' I've got more going
on up there than you do.
[crunch]
[yelp]
-I mean, just look at you.
You've got such smooth hair
and a really beautiful bod.
I totally despise you,
now that I think of it.
-Instead of holding
a grudge, maybe you
should work on making yourself
a little more desirable.
[crunch]
[yelp]
-Pardon my friend's words.
Anyway, I'm afraid that I can't
answer any of your questions.
In fact, I think we'll be
better off if I just kill you.
-(GASPING) Sorry, guys!
Gotta go!
-Wait, Shinji!
-Orihime, don't stop them.
-What's the matter, Chad?
-It's no use.
At their speed, we'd
never catch up with them.
We just don't have the power.
And the truth is, even
if we could catch them,
we'd only end up getting
ourselves killed.
-Put me down!
They're getting away!
All I wanted to do was
kill them a little bit.
-Well, you can't!
Don't you get it?
We're trying to recruit Ichigo!
There's no need to cause trouble
with the others just yet.
-Shut up and put me down!
-Aaahhh!
Stop that!
You'll give me diarrhea!
You're worse than drinking
water in a foreign country!
-Whoa!
Knock that off!
You little creep!
How dare you goose a young lady!
-Shut up or you're
going to get punished.
You know what happens
to little brats who
don't do a they're told!
They get a spanking!
-Try that without
hands, monkey brain!
-Aaugh!
-(LAUGHING) Yeah!
-Knock it off or you're
really gonna get it!
-Humans make me crazy.
I really despise them.
-Yeah, I know what you mean.
-You know what else I hate?
Soul Reapers.
-That's not surprising.
-I know you're
angry, but you have
to be patient and control
yourself, all right?
[piano music]
[door closing]
-You've come.
So let's have it, Uryu.
Tell me what you've decided.
-I've thought about
it, and I want
you to restore my
Quincy powers to me.
I don't want borrowed powers.
I want my own powers back
so I can control them.
-And if I do?
-I give you my word.
I won't have anything to do with
Soul Reapers or their allies.
I swear this on my life.
[music playing in japanese]
-10, 11, 12.
-What are you doing, Ririn?
-The lieutenant asked me to
prepare substitute Soul Candy.
-Someone's exiting
the Soul Society?
-Yes.
The people on this list.
-It'll get pretty noisy there.
-Who is it?
Is it someone that I know?
-Mmmm, well.
-Oh, who is it?
[music playing in japanese]
-Illustrated Guide
to Soul Reapers!
-Mornings sure have
been rough lately.
-Good morning to you,
Lieutenant Hisagi.
-And to you, my friend.
-That man was a member
of Squad Seven, right?
-Yeah, you have a good memory.
We became friends during
the Bount incident.
-I meant to tell
you, Tetsuzaemon
has you on his mind, and
not in a positive way.
He said something like,
certain Squad members
don't respect me as
much as they used to.
-Believe me, he doesn't need
to be worried about that.
-It's hard to believe people
used to respect him at all,
considering.
-That's a pretty cool statement.
Aren't you worried
it'll get back to him?