[theme music]
[doorbell]
-Hello?
[squeak]
-Huh?
Huh?
-Wow.
Nice view.
Ah!
[growl]
[scream]
-I told you I had no chance
to get out of the way.
-Yeah, nice try.
But it looked to me like you
had the whole thing planned out.
-Honestly, Rangiku, it
was just a coincidence.
That's all.
Give me a break, I
barely saw anything.
My eyes were mostly closed.
Ah!
-Listen.
I'm the one who got perved
on, you little squirt.
I'll give you a
break, all right?
How about if I start
with your neck?
-You're kind of choking me!
[car horn]
[gasp]
-What are you doing?
Are you crazy?
-Hey!
Be careful!
-Ah!
-Oh, no!
-Help!
Ah!
-We've gotta save her!
-The water's really cold!
-I know!
-OK, we jump into
the river on three.
Ready?
-Huh?
RANGIKU: Get moving!
She's drifting away!
[scream]
-I'm coming!
-Speed it up!
Swim faster!
-I'm trying, but all the
water this body's absorbing
is slowing me down.
Hang on, I'm coming!
I thought I was gonna drown!
What was the big idea, Rangiku?
-It was going to be a lot
quicker than leaving my gigai.
Thank goodness.
You better just stay
still for a moment.
Are you OK?
-Yeah.
But where's Shintaro?
-Shintaro?
-What happened?
Is she all right?
-She fell in the river.
-That's terrible.
-My friend, Shintaro.
He's the one who saved me.
-Shintaro?
If anyone here is
named Shintaro,
you're a hero, my friend.
-Huh?
Wait a minute.
I'm Shintaro?
I think.
Rangiku, what do I do now?
-Have a good time, teddy bear.
[groan]
-Are you sure you're going
to be OK here by yourself?
-Yes, sir Thank you
for bringing me home.
Man.
Pretending to be a stuffed
animal is exhausting.
Look at this joint.
The family must
be really loaded.
That TV's huge!
The furniture looks
expensive, too.
Everything's first class.
I wonder what kind of
work her parents do?
Uh-oh!
-Now, let's get you dry.
-Ow!
Wah!
Hot!
-Um-- Shintaro?
-Huh?
Actually, I'm not-- that is--
-Hey!
Shintaro!
Wow!
This is the best gift ever!
You can really move
and talk to me.
-I can't breathe!
-Oh.
Sorry, Shintaro.
-Forgot how much
I like to breathe.
Hey.
Wait.
Aren't you surprised to see
that I can move and talk?
-Mm-hm.
But it just means that
I finally got my wish.
Every night when
I went to bed, I
wished that you would
be alive when I woke up.
-Somehow that just
makes me feel worse.
-So I didn't dream it, right?
You really were the
one who saved me
when I fell in the water.
-Yeah.
It's true.
-Well, then thanks very much.
I owe you my life.
-No big deal.
I was just being
a good samaritan.
Yep.
So, what was your name again?
-It's Miyuki, silly.
How come you don't know
my name after we've
been living together
for so many years?
-Uh-- well, it's just that,
you see, I-- of course,
I do know your name-- but--
-But what?
-Apparently when I
fell in the river,
I must have gotten amnesia.
It's the weirdest thing.
-Yeah.
That is weird.
-Anyway, are we the only
ones home right now?
-That's right.
-Where's your mommy?
-She's at work.
-And your daddy?
-He's not here.
-How come?
-Mommy dumped him because
he was a good for nothing.
-A good for nothing?
Does she even know
what that means?
-Mommy's very busy all the time.
She has a real important
job, and she always
comes home late at night.
I told here I was big enough
to stay alone in the house
by myself.
-Yeah?
You're pretty mature
for someone so young.
-Uh-huh.
Hey, Shintaro?
-Hm?
-Wanna play a game with me?
-What?
Huh?
What the-- why am I
dressed like this again?
I wonder if she's in cahoots
with Ichigo's sister.
-Here you go.
I spent all day cooking, so
dinner would be ready for you.
Be sure and clean your plate.
Isn't it yummy?
-I can't eat this!
It's garbage!
Sorry.
I mean-- of course I'll eat it.
It looks delicious.
And you worked so hard on it.
-Very good.
Isn't it delicious?
-It really sticks to
your ribs, you know?
I'll never make it
out of here alive
if this is how it's going to be.
-Now that you've had
dinner, Shintaro,
what should we play next?
Should we play work, or
should we play school?
-Uh, no!
Let's see.
Wait.
I know.
It's such a nice day,
let's go play outside.
I always find it's fun to
run around and play outdoors
with your friends on a
day as beautiful as this.
-I don't want to go outside.
-Huh?
Really?
What's wrong?
-Nothing.
It's just I don't have
any friends, that's all.
-Why is that?
-'Cause!
Stop asking!
I don't need any friends!
-All right.
I won't ask anymore.
Please stop crying.
Oh, she's so touchy.
[sneezing]
-You know, you're
a real cry baby.
-Stop teasing me.
You're being mean.
-Why were you outside earlier
today, if leaving this place
is so upsetting?
What was so important out there?
It's just a question.
Don't cry.
-I wanted to see my house.
-Huh?
-The house where we
all used to live.
You, and me, and
Mommy and Daddy.
-Your old house?
-Mm-hm.
Back when Mommy and Daddy
were both still together,
we lived in a different place.
It was a really big house on
the other side of the city,
and it was really fun.
I remember I used to
laugh all the time.
my family lived there together.
Mommy, and Daddy, and me,
and my big dog Shintaro.
-Wait a minute, Miyuki.
I thought I was Shintaro?
-Well, yeah, but he
was the real Shintaro.
But then they wouldn't let him
live with us in this apartment,
so Mommy bought me a stuffed
animal Shintaro to take
his place.
-Uh-huh.
I get it.
So what happened to
the real Shintaro?
Is he with your daddy?
-No.
He died when he
got hit by a car.
-Whoa.
She's really had it tough.
-I understand.
-You're sad, because
you really didn't
want to move here
when you were having
so much fun at your old house.
-We had to move here.
Mommy and Daddy
fought all the time.
-Don't you think she's going
to be even more upset when
she finds out you left
here and fell in the river?
-Yeah.
Except I asked the
policeman who brought me
home not to tell her.
She goes out and works so
hard at her job every day.
I just don't want her to
have to worry about me.
And anyway, now that you're
here, I can have lots of fun
inside.
I don't need to go out at all.
(THINKING) This kid
puts on a tough face,
but I'm not buying it.
She's lonely.
If she was OK with
her life, she wouldn't
have been out there trying
to find the place where
she was truly happy.
Hey!
I have an idea.
Let's visit your old home.
-Huh?
-You want to go, right?
-Yeah, but--
-Don't worry, I'll be
right there with you.
[gasp]
-Oh!
Thank you, Shintaro!
-Oh, boy.
Wow.
What a huge house.
So you really lived
in this place?
-Uh-uh.
-It doesn't look like anybody's
living here right now.
-I don't know.
-Wait a minute.
Is this the first time
you've visited here
since you moved away?
-Mm.
-What's that vase doing here?
-We put it there after
Shintaro died, as a memorial.
-Sorry.
[gasp]
-Hey.
-What's wrong?
-There's danger.
We need to leave right now.
Huh?
(THINKING) There's
something evil here.
-I'm scared.
[scream]
-Miyuki!
Let's go!
[scream]
-Damn.
We're cut off.
The only way to survive
is to get inside.
-Shintaro!
-Damn.
That thing was trying
to corner us in here.
Huh?
Come on, let's get going.
-Shintaro, what's going on?
-It's a Hollow.
-A what?
-Trust me, it's an evil spirit.
This isn't good.
There have been a lot of Hollows
showing up in town recently.
I wonder if there's something
going on I don't know about?
[scream]
-Don't look back!
-Oh, yeah?
Take that!
This is bad.
Let's hurry up and
get out of here.
So it's finally showing itself.
Oh no, there's two of them.
Oh, it's just two-headed.
What am I thinking?
It's still bad news.
[growl]
-It doesn't plan on
letting us get past.
-Shintaro.
-Huh?
-What is that thing?
-Miyuki, you can
see that hollow?
-I don't know for sure.
It's kind of all blurry.
-She isn't able
to see it clearly,
but she can actually tell
that something's there.
[grunting]
-Run!
-Shintaro!
-It's gonna be all right.
(THINKING) What are we gonna do?
That gate's lock, and the
Hollow has us trapped.
I'm afraid the only
way we're getting out
if I defeat it in battle.
Huh?
Looks like it
stopped following us.
Ah!
-Shintaro, what's happening?
This is getting really scary.
-Don't worry, Miyuki.
I will protect you.
(THINKING) Who's
going to protect me?
I don't even know if I
can fight in this body.
Miyuki, the second you
have a chance, run for it!
-Shintaro!
-All right, Hollow, here I come!
Over here!
Nyah, nyah!
[roar]
-Ah!
-Miyuki!
You freak!
Let's go!
Huh?
[growl]
-That's what I was afraid of.
[scream]
-Shintaro?
[roar]
-Run, Miyuki!
Just keep running!
Yah!
-Shintaro!
-Yah!
Hey, you gotta admit,
I'm pretty tough.
[grunting]
[scream]
-Shintaro!
-Miyuki!
Get away from here!
[scream]
-Wait!
-Shintaro!
[roar]
-Gotta save Miyuki.
-What's going on?
Help me, Shintaro.
Do something.
It's after me.
Please, Shintaro, save me!
[growl]
[roar]
RANGIKU: Kon!
-Huh?
[scream]
-Oh, Rangiku.
What took you so long?
Huh?
I see.
That was him.
-Shintaro!
Are you all right?
-I'm sorry, Miyuki.
I got you caught up
in a scary situation.
-Shintaro.
You're all messed
up from that fight.
-Miyuki?
Something really
amazing happened.
-Huh?
-The one who came to save you
when the monster was going
to attack-- he was
the original Shintaro.
-You mean my dog?
-Yeah.
He was really concerned
that you might get hurt.
I think this is it.
It's all over for me.
-Huh?
No!
I don't want you to go!
-It can't be helped.
-It's not fair!
You can't go.
I need you.
You just started talking to me.
-No!
This is all wrong!
You've got to be strong and
stand on your own two feet.
It'll be fine.
Even if I can't talk,
I'll be watching over you
to make sure you're all right.
You need to get
out there and start
making yourself
some new friends.
-I don't need any new friends.
I just need you, Shintaro.
-Stop saying that!
I understand.
-Huh?
-I know that deep inside,
you're very lonely.
You had to move because
of your parents.
Your mommy is busy working,
so you try your best
not to cause her any trouble.
But that doesn't mean you
have to hide in a corner
the rest of your life.
I myself was a victim of
unfortunate circumstances.
They made me a modified soul.
And then, at someone
else's convenience,
they decided to destroy me.
But I guess you wouldn't
know about that.
Anyway, things got
so bad I felt like I
didn't have any
control over my life.
But my friends saved me.
-You have friends?
-Of course.
I made some friends and
had some adventures.
Don't tell them, but
they're all so stupid,
they'd be helpless without me.
But that's what makes
them so amusing.
I discovered to have a friend,
you've got to be a friend.
I'm sure your Mommy would
agree with me, Miyuki.
It's almost time now.
-Huh?
-And believe me when I tell
you this, because it's true.
The original Shintaro and I
will always look after you.
Make us proud, Miyuki.
Do you hear what I'm saying?
-Yeah.
-All right, then.
Always remember me,
and have a good life.
[sirens]
[crying]
-Mommy.
-Are you all right?
-Yeah.
I admit, she was a handful.
-Tell me something.
Do you really think
she heard you,
and that she'll take
your words to heart?
-Of course she will.
I'm the fantastic Kon,
hero to little children.
They all listen to me.
-You don't say.
-Tell me something.
Why have so many more Hollows
been appearing around town?
Is there something going on?
-Yeah.
Something.
It looks like a big battle's
coming in the near future.
-Why wasn't I told about this?
-I'll fill you in
at headquarters.
Let's go.
-Do your best.
You'll be all right.
RANGIKU: What's the hold up?
I have work to do.
KON: Cool your jets.
I'm coming.
[theme music]
RENJI: I finally get some
screentime in the next episode.
KURODO: I heard that
we'll be house-sitting
while Kisuke's out.
RIRIN: He's got a lot of
enemies, and strange customers.
It's gonna be a big pain.
AIZEN: Pain is the price
you pay for maturity.
RENJI: Yeah, great.
Now can we concentrate on me?