[Kugo]
We want to become
ordinary humans again,
so we will help you regain
your Soul Reaper powers.
That's not what I came
here to discuss with you.
What's that?
Listen. I only came here
for one reason, to find
out why stuff's
happening to my friends.
As for me getting back
my Soul Reaper powers,
That's beside the point.
[Yasutora]
So, you're okay
with letting him
leave like that?
Sure. Out of nowhere
we ask him to become
a Soul Reaper again.
I mean seriously, I never
really expected him to
agree to our suggestion as
soon as we brought it up.
You of all people
should understand that.
He's most likely already come
to grips with never being a
Soul Reaper again.
He came to us because
he thought we might
know something
about all these incidents
that are suddenly
happening around him.
But he did approach us, so
we've made great progress here.
Now the pressure is on us
to not let this golden
opportunity slip by.
He must be convinced
to see things our way.
Failure in this matter
simply can't happen.
[Jackie]
You really think so?
Hnh?
I'm not feeling as sold as
you are that this Ichigo
guy is really worth all
that much trouble.
Besides...
You having personal
reasons for wanting
him to have his
powers restored,
and whether he
can actually be
of help to us,
are two distinctly
different things.
Mmm.
But, I'd say some of us are
already interested in him.
Hmm?!
So, maybe I'm the
only one who
thinks otherwise.
Wait! Were you just
referring to me?!
She didn't
say that.
Well I don't think that
he's worth taking a lot
of risks for either!
But from what I see, it
sure seems we do need his
powers, wouldn't you say?
So says the one who got
all hot and bothered
after seeing him.
Ahh!
Shut it!
That is so not true!
Now, now.
Fine then!
So what do you
guys think?!
Well, Yukio?!
Don't care.
Ya don't care
either way?
And you Giriko?!
It's appears
quite clearly,
that we really do need
this Ichigo character.
[struggled breathing]
[frantic grunts]
Ah! Ahhhn! Egh ahhh!!
You'll pay for thiiiiiaagh!
Huh?!
Oh, good. The Soul Reapers
haven't found you yet.
Who the hell
are you?!
It must be so agonizing,
to be weighed down by
such a huge grudge.
I will free you.
But in exchange...
Agh!
I'd like you to do something for
me.
That's it.
AugghhhAAAAAAAAHH!
See you tomorrow!
Alright I came like
you asked me to,
so what's up?
Shush! Don't talk
so loud, or he
might hear you!
You and I are going to
confirm with our own eyes
whether this Ichigo guy
is really someone we need.
You're crushing on
this guy, aren't you?
Hell no!
I am not!
He'll hear you.
[gasp]
He's turned
the corner!
Let's go!
I don't think so.
Count me out.
Wait!
Rrr!
[Uryu]
Come in.
Hi, there!
Huh?
Hi, Orihime.
He he he! I came to
see how you're doing!
Uwah!
What's this?
I figure you've got a lot
of free time on your hands!
So I brought you a bunch of
DVDs of some up and coming,
unknown entertainers,
who might break out
and become famous
in a few years.
Uh... Oh, ah!
Thanks so much!
Heh!
So how're you feeling?
Me? I'm doing well.
It still hurts
sometimes, though.
Nhf!
If the pain's really that bad,
would you like me to heal you?
That's okay.
Thanks for offering.
But I'd rather just
be here for now.
Oh...
So then, You didn't
come here just to see
how I was, did you?
Well, I heard that the
paramedics found you somewhere
close to Ichigo's house on the
day that you were attacked.
I was wondering why you
were there... uh...
Could it have
been because,
You sensed that something's
going on around Ichigo,
like I do, and
you were worried?
No, it was just
a coincidence.
But it's true that I did
sense some kind of Spiritual
Pressure surrounding him.
But that had nothing
to do with the guy
who attacked me.
Really?
Yeah. But more
important--
[spiritual explosion]
Was that a...?!
It's a Hollow.
And it's close!
Ngh!
Don't move, Uryu!
I'll go and see
what's happening!
But Orihime!
I'll be fine! I won't
put myself in danger!
I'll be right back!
Okay...
She's right, a Hollow
like this shouldn't
be a problem.
But, what
worries me is...
Mh?
Ahh!
[phew] That was so close!
Why'd he look back this way?
Hm?
There's some kinda
presence here!
Ichigo!
Uh?
Orihime?
What's wrong?
You look flustered.
What's up?
Stay behind me!
Huh?
Is it a Hollow?!
No, wait...
I must've imagined it!
Now you're putting
yourself in danger?
Of course not!
I usually let Uryu
and Chad take care
of it. Really!
Hey, wait up!
[Orihime]
So anyway, what were
you doing over here?
[Ichigo]
Oh, not much.
But hey, what
about you?
Damn it.
Who is she?!
Thanks for
walking me back.
Take care.
Yeah, see you
tomorrow.
[Ichigo]
Hanging on to the
past isn't my style.
So you're saying you don't
want your Soul Reaper powers?
Ah!
Listen, I'm not asking
for you give me an
immediate answer.
I can wait
until tomorrow.
You just go home and
think it over tonight.
Sure.
It's true. The way I am now,
I can't protect anyone.
But I did all this
knowing the consequences.
Yuzu, Ichigo says he's
not eating dinner.
Oh, that's alright.
No it's not. I mean I
know you went all out
and cooked him some of
his favorite stuff.
Whatever. I'm through with him!
Yeah. Think I'll go
take a bath now.
[sigh]
Nh!
Ah?
[groaning]
Hmmmaugh!
It certainly appears
that he's not coming.
Looks like you figured
this guy wrong.
It seems the more you
ask him to help us, the
less he really wants to.
INTERNAL MEDICINE
PEDIATRICSKUROSAKI CLINIC
[Yuzu] [mean]
Here Ichigo. You get to finish
the leftovers from last night.
Thanks, it
looks tasty.
By the way, last night,
were you expecting a
visit from someone
around dinnertime?
What are you talking about?
Wait, did someone come by?
No, I just felt like
there was someone out in
front of our house, but,
When I went out front to
check, no one was there.
Probably just the wind.
I can certainly wait
until tomorrow.
How about you go home and
think it over tonight.
Chad!
What are you
doing here?
Hey, did you happen
to drop by my house
last night?
Your place?
No, not last night.
Huh. In that case I
guess it was him.
Ichigo.
Hm?
Ya got a minute?
[Ichigo]
So what's going on with you?
I mean you haven't
been at school in
like forever.
Do you remember,
the promise we made
in junior high?
Back then it was you,
who protected something
very important to me.
[Ichigo]
If there's ever anything
so important you'd protect
it with your life,
I'll protect it
with mine as well.
Whattya say?
[Chad]
From that day on, you and I have
fought as a team, and in my own
way, I've tried to follow you.
Yeah.
Ichigo, I know that you've
been trying to hide it,
but to tell you the truth,
It's been awful to watch you
since you lost your power.
I know you want to fight!
And it's tearing you up that
you're unable to protect
everyone with your own
power, like you did before!
[gasp]
There's nothing to
feel ashamed of.
That's a quality that
defines you, Ichigo.
Hold on.
Good talk, Chad.
So, what's the plan now?
My thought is there really
isn't anything we can do.
I did have a talk
with him, but he
didn't say
anything about it.
Ginjo.
Why didn't you actually talk
with Ichigo last night?
What'd'ya mean, Chad?
You went over to his
house last night, right?
What the hell are
you talking about?
I didn't go to his house.
Well if you didn't,
then who was it who did?
What exactly
are you saying?
Last night, one of Ichigo's
younger sisters apparently
sensed the presence of
someone at their home.
There's a simple
answer to that.
And what's that?
One logical explanation is
there's someone besides
us who's trying to make
contact with Ichigo as well.
Now that you say that!
I've also sensed a strange
presence very close to him.
It's him...!
Hey!!
By the way, last night,
were you expecting a
visit from someone
around dinnertime?
That could've been him!
Hey!!
[panting]
Damn!
[Yuzu]
Ichigo! Is that you?
Huh?
I knew it!
Yuzu!
What're you doing
here, Ichigo?
You're all right!
"Alright"?
Uh, forget it.
It's nothing.
So Ichigo, I'm
on my way to buy
groceries for dinner tonight.
Would you come with me to
carry the bags?
Sure. Be glad to.
Hm? Was that a
breeze just now?
Uh, is something wrong?
Uh!
Yaahhh!
Yuzu!
Help!
Help me!
Yahh!
Help! Help!
Ichigo! Something's
got a hold of me!
There's no doubt! It's a Hollow!
Make it stop!!
Dammit!
Drop her!!
Augh!
Agh!
Ichigo!
Help me!
Damn! Why the hell
can't I see it?!
Ichigo... Run... away...
Yaahhh!
Uht!
Dah!
[panting]
[roar]
Hraaagh!
Yuzu!!
Agh!
[gasp]
That hurt, you
Hollow bastard!
Ginjo!
You hung in there
well, Ichigo.
What do you say we
get some ramen.
Right after I take
care of this problem.
[roar]
Bastard! Why'd you go
after this girl anyway?!
Hrrrr...
Raagh!
Haaaaaa!
[roar]
Haahhh!
Ah! Yuzu! Hey!
You alright?!
[coughs]
[Ichigo]
Thank you.
Huh?
Ginjo, I owe you for this.
Forget about it.
I didn't show up to make
you feel like you owe me.
But truth is, we can't
afford to have you die.
Besides.
It would suck for us to have
the door slammed shut on us
'cause we didn't protect
someone we were able to.
[Riruka]
You did what?!
Are you a moron?! You saved him
and then just left him there!?
If we really need his
powers like you've said,
why didn't you say,
"I'll save you if you
cooperate with us" and
make a deal with him?!
From the sound of it you
really want to invite that
guy back to our place.
Yeah.
No, I don't!!
I still don't get why you
two keep exaggerating
about my interest
in that goofy dude with
that tacky orange hair!
[Ichigo]
Hey, I'm not THAT goofy.
Huh?!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Is your
sister okay?
Yeah.
Why'd you come?
Look don't get
the wrong idea.
Huh?
[Ichigo]
I didn't come 'cause
I feel like I owe you.
I want my power back
to protect people.
That's all.
So let's do it.
Straight to the
point, huh?
How did...?
It's my...
That's the symbol of
your power, right?
Be sure to keep it safe.
Right.
[Riruka]
You could've told me
he'd be joining us!
[Kugo]
Come on. Stop picking on me
just because you're happy.
[Riruka]
No one said
I'm happy!
Or that he's my type...
Or he's got a sexy voice...
Or he has a cute smile!
I'm not thinking
any of that, okay?!
[Kugo]
I think you just
gave yourself away.