What happened here?
That's right...
We lost.
[gasping]
I see you're finally
awake, Ichigo.
Kisuke, how long was I
out?
Easy now. You weren't
unconscious all that long.
Not much more than half a
day after you collapsed.
I see. What about the
others?
Well, they were badly injured,
no question about that, but
it looks like they'll
make it. Right now
Orihime is doing all she
can to bring them back to
full health.
That's good.
By the way, we didn't
want to worry your family
so we brought you here to
my place instead. I hope
that's okay with you.
Yeah. I appreciate it.
You still look pretty
tired. Why don't you
rest for a bit longer?
We can plan what we're
going to do after that.
Here, let me go make you
some tea.
Hey, Kisuke...
Did I... lose all my
Spirit Energy?
Yes.
That means... I can't
help Nozomi anymore,
doesn't it?
I guess it's all
over
I allowed Kageroza to
win.
Well... I wouldn't be
so sure just yet.
Huh?
[grunting]
[gasping]
Head Captain Yamamoto has
gotten past the worst of
it.
However.. I'm sorry to say
that after assessing his
injuries, he won't be
returning to battle
any time soon.
That's not good news.
What's the prognosis on
everyone else?
As far as I can tell,
they're still
touch-and-go.
The wounds of Third Seat
Madarame and Fifth Seat
Ayasegawa are still
particularly severe, and
showing no signs of
improvement.
I see...
We just have to be
patient, and give it
time. We're doing
everything we can for
them at the moment.
That's fine. But what can
we do?
I mean.. Kageroza has
also suffered injuries.
We need to
finish him--
And is your plan to go
and face that man alone,
Lieutenant Abarai?
[sighing]
Knowing how he operates,
he's probably already
re-grouped his invading
army, somewhere in the
Soul Society.
Even so...!
I sympathize with you.
And I share your desire
to save that Mod Soul
girl. But right now, all
I can tell you, from my
position, is to stand by
and wait.
[grunting]
Yes, ma'am.
Mmm.
What's all this? Leaving
so soon?
But I brought you some
tea.
Thanks, but staying here
isn't going to help
anything.
Ichigo...
Huh?
Come with me. Let's take
a little walk.
I remember this place...
Hmm...
What? Okay, then how
'bout karaoke?
You mean just the two of
us?
Nah, I'll call over
some friends.
Who's gonna be there?
Atsuko and the others.
It'll be a party!
Can I also invite Yoshie?
The more, the merrier!
What a mess. I'm
powerless...
I...can't even protect
myself.
Tell me something,
Kisuke.
Yes?
My Spirit Energy... Is
there any way to get it
back?
Ichigo...!
Oh, hey you guys.
Ichigo...
Why the long faces?
Uh--
Is it because I lost my
Spirit Energy? If that's
the case, don't worry
about it.
Right now.. We have to
find a way to rescue
Nozomi. I do realize I
can't fight anymore...
...But in spite of that,
I want you to know, I'm
here to help any way I
can.
Ichigo...
Huh?
Hey there, Ichigo!
Huh? Wait a minute...!
How come.. I see you?
Why wouldn't you be able
to see us? I mean, we're
in our Gigai forms, aren't we?
Oh.. Of course.
Hey.. We came because we
were worried about how
you were doing. But you
seem to be just fine.
Well sorry to disappoint
you.
Uh--
What's wrong?
Listen. As you know, I
lost my Spirit Energy...
But trust me on this.. I
haven't lost my soul...
I might have to leave
the actual fighting
to you guys--
But I'm still here for
those who need help.
Are you a moron or
something?
Uh?
You're not the only one
who's dealing with Kageroza.
We're all in this together.
Well yeah, of course...
You're damn right! But
even so, you presumed we
thought you'd given up.
Don't be silly. If you
gave up, we wouldn't have
anybody to lead our little
group of misfits around.
So get over it.
Thanks, Rukia.
Uh!
[grunting]
Don't waste your breath
thanking us.
What did you do that
for?! I'm a normal
human right now!
We're supposed to go easy
on you?
Well you don't have to
break my leg to prove
your point! And what are
you nodding about?
I think you got exactly
what you deserved!
Oh, so now you're ganging
up on me, is that it?!
[heavy breathing]
Are you all right, Master
Kageroza? You need
treatment, sir---
Get your hands off me!
I will now initiate the
fusion of Nozomi and
myself. Begin the
preparations!
Yes sir, right away. But
I must warn you, in your
current condition, there
might be excessive
post-fusion stress on the
Reigai---
Silence! Silence!
Silence!
He's waiting, patiently.
Nozomi and I must hurry.
We must become what we
were meant to be, as
quickly as possible!
Here's how I see it...
We have to break into the
Soul Society as quickly
as possible. Kageroza now
has Nozomi in his
possession. The only good
thing about that is, it
means his attention has
shifted completely away
from us.
Realistically, the people
here comprise our entire
fighting force. We have
no backup.
That's the absolute
truth. Against their
invading army, we're at a
disadvantage, with or
without you, Ichigo. So
you might as well relax.
You're not helping us
here, Renji.
Hold on. I think we have
to consider the impact of
Ichigo's presence on all
this.
Huh?
We now know why Kageroza
was so tenacious in his
pursuit of Nozomi. But
there was something else
that's been bothering
me...
Why was he so concerned
about Ichigo, as well?
I thought it was because
he was constantly around
Nozomi, protecting her.
That was part of it, I'm
sure. But I think a much
bigger reason was
Ichigo's Hollow powers.
Why would that be so
important?
Here's why. Kageroza was
able to create a Soul
Reaper's Reigai...
employing just the
tiniest amount of Reishi.
But he never created a
Reigai of Ichigo. He
personally confronted him
numerous times, and
though he studied him
carefully, he always kept
his distance. Apparently,
he somehow lacked the
ability to reproduce his
essence.
I get it. In spite of
everything, Kageroza is
unable to manipulate Hollow
powers.
And that's why he was
cautious around Ichigo.
Is that what's going on?
Yes.
Then that explains the
Cleaner. He used it to
attack Ichigo in the
Precipice World.
You have a point. In
fact, I got attacked
twice.
Really...?
That's right. The first
time it happened was when
I went in with you,
Rukia. We came under
attack, and I dropped my
Combat Pass.
I remember that.
The second time was when
I tried to re-enter the
Soul Society.
I got swallowed up by the
Cleaner.
It's weird. How did I
survive that experience?
Interesting question...
I believe I can see now,
what happened to you.
Huh?
Ichigo... I think there
might be a way to restore
your Spirit Energy.
Uh! Are you
serious?
You might be able to
restore Ichigo's Spirit
Energy?!
What in the world are you
talking about?
This is really just a
theory right now, but...
The Cleaner reacts to
Reishi and swallows its
victims. The time axis
inside the Precipice
World is isolated from
all other planes of
existence. So the
consumed Reishi remains
suspended there, without
ever dissipating. The
bottom line is, if I'm
right about my analysis,
it might very well exist
there for all of eternity.
Don't forget, folks..
Kageroza obtained
decades-old information
about Mod Souls from
inside there.
If Ichigo's Reishi is
still in there, we'll
need to collect it, then
use Kageroza's
Reigai-creation
technology in reverse, to
artificially re-create
Ichigo's Spirit Energy.
But that means we'd have
to---
That's right. We'll have
to break into the
Department of Research
and Development.
[gasping]
Oh please! Is that even
possible?
Not to mention this is
all based on theory.
Regardless.. We still
have the problem of how
we're going to collect
Ichigo's Reishi.
Once the Cleaner swallows
someone, that person is
dead, right?
That's what seemed
strange to me all this
time. Why don't we sense
any Spiritual Pressure
from Nozomi and Kageroza?
The answer will clear up
a lot of questions.
There's only one way
Kageroza could have
obtained the Mod Soul
information from inside
the Cleaner, and still
live to talk about it...
He must have created a
special Reigai of himself
that shuts off his Spirit
Energy. The Cleaner then
wouldn't recognize him as
a living being.
[gasping]
If so... then Ichigo, who
lost his Spirit Energy,
might also be able to get
in and out of the Cleaner.
Does that sound like the
kind of action you might
be willing to risk...
Ichigo?
To be honest.. I don't
really understand it.
But I've been thinking.
and I can't come up
with any other way to
rescue Nozomi.
So I'll have to try it.
Mm.
Huh?
[gasping and grunting]
Are you ready?
Yeah.
I'm attaching a
communication device.
In the event of an
emergency, I want you to
follow my directions.
You also need
to carry this.
I've calibrated it
very carefully, to respond
to the location of your Reishi.
When you find it, push
the button at the bottom.
All right. Sounds easy
enough.
Hey!
Uh--
[grunting]
Kon!
Where do you think you're
going, in your
condition?!
Into the Cleaner, to
retrieve my Reishi.
Huh?! Are you crazy?!
What are you thinking?!
It's the only way...
Huh?
...to go and rescue
Nozomi.
[grunting]
See you.
You've gotta be crazy.
This whole thing is my
fault and you know it.
And if it is my fault,
then why is it that you
have to go?
Kon...
I'm a powerless being...!
I can't do anything! I
can't even protect
anyone!
I have to rely on you to
fight my battles for me!
I have to rely on everyone
else to protect me!
This.. whole.. situation
is my fault!
[sobbing]
Kon...
None of this is your
fault, trust me.
Uh?
Now stop crying and just
wait here. I'll be back,
I promise.
[grunting]
Take this.
What is it?
I don't see any point in
me keeping it.
A good-luck charm, eh?
Thanks.
Ichigo... Are you ready?
Yeah.
For the moment, you'll be
able to move fairly
freely inside the
Precipice World.
That being said, we don't
know exactly when the
Cleaner will make an
appearance, so please be
patient until it does.
I hear you.
Thank you for waiting,
Ichigo. It's coming.
Distance, five hundred
meters.
Four hundred... Three
hundred... Two hundred...
One hundred...!
[roaring]
It scooped him up! The
plan's working.
So far, so good.
Kisuke was right. Without
my Spirit Energy, the
Cleaner doesn't register
me at all. But the
pressure in here is
overwhelming...!
How are you doing,
Ichigo? Check your
device. If your Reishi is
nearby, the collection
software should respond.
Looks like it's working.
I'm heading toward it!
[grunting]
[screaming]
Ichigo!
The Cleaner's movements
suddenly changed, without
warning.
What does that mean?!
As a response to
swallowing Ichigo, it
might be trying to expel
any foreign objects.
Ichigo! Abandon the plan!
Get yourself out of
there!
Ichigo...!
[grunting]
Get out of here? How am I
supposed to do that? No
way! I'm finishing this!
[gasping]
[grunting]
Damnit!
Ichigo. Ichigo! Hey,
Ichigo!!
Come on, answer me!
Ichigo!
Quit fooling around, you
idiot! You promised me
you'd come back! If you
lied to me, I'll never
forgive you, ever!
Ichigo!
Will you keep it down!
I can hear everything
you're saying!
I've got it! It's
working!
Okay!
Now to find a way out!
Could that be it?
Only one way to find out.
What the hell?
Why is there... another
me in here?
I don't know what's goin'
on!
[yelling]
[panting]
Ichigo!
Huh?
Yeah! I gotta admit, for
a minute there, you had
me worried!
Had you worried? How do
you think I felt?
Ichigo, what happened to
you, while you were in
there?
Well, to tell you the
truth, I don't really
know for sure. It all
happened pretty quickly.
I can't figure out how,
but there was another me
inside the Cleaner. I
thought I rescued him, but--
You're saying you rescued
another you?
Did you get bumped on the
head?
What are you trying to
say?!
Ah, yes. I think
I understand what
happened.
Well, tell me.
I believe what you saw
was the you who was
previously swallowed
by the cleaner.
Huh?
Basically, the time axis
inside the Cleaner itself
is isolated from all
other worlds. That means
anything swallowed by the
Cleaner cannot exist
within any other time
axis.
So you're saying he met
himself from the past,
inside the Cleaner?
Yes. Apparently, the
Ichigo from the present
was able to get in there
and save the Ichigo from
the past.
All of this seems very
complicated, to me.
That also explains the
Combat Pass.
The Reigai was able to
obtain Ichigo's Combat
Pass before we even
arrived in the Soul
Society. I was wondering
how they pulled that off,
but this seems to be the
answer.
You're right. Everything
was done using the same
trick.
Please, stop! Enough
already. You lost me.
Anyway, I presume we can
now move on to the next
step, right?
Let's go visit Kageroza.
Alright.
I came back, just like I
said I would.
Yeah. But in the end, I
couldn't do anything at
all to help you.
And what makes you think
that's true?
Huh? My charm?
Without this, I wouldn't
have been able to make it
back here safely. And I
wouldn't have had the
chance to save the other
me.
I owe that to you.
Ohh.
Hey! Stop
messing with me!
[chuckling]
How can you
say that?
Cut that out! Keep away
from me, you! I'm a
dangerous being!
Now you're gonna get it!
Hey, that's my cotton!
Stop flattening me out!
Both time and space are
rightly aligned. So let
us begin...
[chuckling]
Captain Unohana, is there
anything you'll need
while you're here in the
World of the Living?
Not really. The Shinto
priest in the town
provides me with goods
whenever I whisper to him
during his sleep at
night.
He probably thinks you're
a deity, ma'am!
Well, I'm a Soul Reaper,
so he's not too far off.