[Shunsui]
Hey there Captain
Hitsugaya! What's up?
Hi Shunsui, Jushiro.
It's been awhile.
Something happen today?
No, just reporting in here.
I was being grilled on
the cleansing progress
in the Tenkai zone.
Oh, that should be
all finished by the
end of today.
What?!
That's what Nanao said in
the report she sent me.
That Rangiku! She knows
she should be including that
in her report as well!
Sorry, but can you please
pass on that update?
Umm...
He's pretty
worked up.
I think it's nice.
Seeing our own getting
angry or laughing about
little things...
It's a sign that
things are getting
back to normal.
That's true.
[relaxing exhale]
Ahh.
I'm all done over
here, Nanao.
Well now, that means we've
completed our share of the
cleansing. Very nicely done.
Ah! I am worn out.
Who'd have thought we'd
be putting up barriers
over such a big area.
This work certainly
had to be done...
And after such a huge project,
I really expected this,
I mean swapping the Soul
Society with Karakura Town!?
Heh, but what I didn't expect
is that you and I would be
doing this kind of painstaking
work for an entire month.
A month already?
Rangiku...?
Ah!
Are you feeling
all right?
Of course! So Nanao, since we've
finished with all our work here,
what do you say the two of us
reward ourselves just a little?
[chuckle]
What?
Oh nothing. It's just nice
to see you acting like your
old lively self again.
Really? I've been--
Really depressed!
I know, I've seen you!
[laughs]
[phone rings]
Oh!
Hi! Rangiku, here.
Rangiku, you idiot!
Do you know how many times
I tried to call you?!
Explain to me why I
haven't been receiving
any reports from you!
I'm sorry, sir!
I was too busy
working all this time.
We finally finished our
assignment, so Nanao and I
were about to take a break
and go out for some--
Get back here right now!
Aww come on, sir!
All work and no fun
affects our morale!
Right now, we can't have
you two taking time off!
It's always like this!
Well, let's go back.
Why do you do this to
me every single time?
Everyone's waiting for us.
[sighs]
Aww...!
Geez! What's up with this
passageway? It's creepy!
True. But it is the designated
path for us to use.
[sigh]
Huh?
[Rangiku]
Nanao...
Yes? What's wrong?
Tell me, do you sense
anything strange here?
What's strange?!
You don't mean some...?
D'ah!
Huh!?
Ah!
What's going on here?!
Well, we're back!
My Rukia how
I've missed--!
Umph!
Kon, I told you not to
leave the room, didn't I?
Bug off! You are not stopping
me from giving Rukia her
daily hug, ya rat!
Hug?!
Damn right! The feeling
of her kick shifting
my cotton stuffing...
It's such a magical
moment of ecstasy!
You could never
understa--
Ack!
You're right, I don't!
[klaxon]
Hollow! Hollow! Hollow!
Man! They keep popping up
every minute don't they?
That's how it is.
[Kon]
Hey wait! I'm
not done yet!
Mmhglf!!
Agh!
Whoa!
Oof!
We'll be gone for awhile.
Try to behave yourself, Kon.
Okay?
You too Chappy.
Aye-aye, Sir!
Wait a minute Ichigo!
So what am I to you anyway?
Huh? Why bring that up now?
You're always using me
when it's convenient!
I'm not just your
substitute, you know!
What're you getting at?!
Ichigo, we have to go!
Right! Anyway, keep an eye
on things while we're gone!
Hey! Sheesh!
Y'ever feel like
tellin' them ta--?
La-la laaa!
La! la la la!
[exasperated sigh]
ughhh!
Whatta buncha--
Hnh?!
Ichigo! A Senkaimon
just opened nearby.
Really? Does it have
something to do with Hollows?
Not sure.
Well, we'll handle
that later!
[Orihime]
Ichigo! Rukia!
Need any help?
We've got it!
Isn't that something?
Ichigo sure has been
doing a lot better lately.
Yeah. I think it's 'cuz Rukia
stayed here to assist him.
So Ichigo hasn't had to use
much of his Spirit Energy.
That's good.
Hm.
[Akon]
You are concerned about
Lieutenants Matsumoto
and Ise...?
Yes. I haven't been able
to reach either of them
since yesterday when they
said they were returning.
I'd like to check to see
if there's any record of
them passing through the
Precipice World.
Understood, no problem.
Give me a minute,
all right?
Hey, Inaba! Bring me the
Precipice World traffic log.
Yes sir.
I agree that it is rather odd
that you haven't heard from
either of them in so long.
Here you are, sir.
Well then?
Ahem! We're looking for
Lieutenants Matsumoto
and Ise, that correct?
Well, at this time, we have no
record that they returned from
the World of the Living.
Perhaps they haven't
passed through the
Precipice World yet.
But they had to!
This is all starting to get
pretty strange, if you ask me.
[Kon as Ichigo]
It was right around here,
that I sensed something odd.
But there's nothing here.
Well, instead of wasting
my free time doing this,
I think I'll go find me
some beautiful babe.
Whaauauauaua!
Ooff!
Oww-ee-ah! What the
heck tripped me?
Whaat?!! Huh?
Nng!
Whoa! What's a girl doing
lying here all n-n-naked?
Wait, never mind that.
Is she alive?
[gulp]
Hey you!
Hnh?
Just what do you
think you're doing?!
It's not how it looks,
I was just--!
[nervous laughter]
Hey! Help!
This guy's
a pervert!
Yaaahhh!
Wait you're making
a mistake!
Come on, lady!
I--Uggh...
The situation is
becoming clear to me.
What do you think,
Captain Kurotsuchi?
Well, if their entrance wasn't
recorded in the traffic log,
then they both must still be
in the World of the Living.
But that doesn't make
any sense to me, sir.
If they stayed there,
we would've heard
from them by now.
Could they of had some
sort of accident in
the Precipice World?
Our Research and Development
Department monitors the
Precipice World 24 hours a day.
Are you really suggesting
that we missed them?
Yes.
Ha! What?!
So you're going to blame
your subordinates' lack
of training on me!?
Hey, Hold on.
We've gotta work together.
We'd like to confirm that
the both of them are safe.
Excuse me Head Captain,
but I have timely news
to share.
Lieutenants Matsumoto and
Ise have just arrived and
wish to report in.
They're here?!
Rangiku! What the hell
were you doing for the
last twenty four hours?!
Huh? What's the problem?
[Mayuri]
This is turning
into a farce.
Nanao, where'd
you go off to on
your way back?
Nowhere. We did as ordered
and came straight back here
after completing our mission.
Exactly! You were
screaming in my ear just
a few hours ago, Captain!
Whaa?
Wha?
Huuh?
A few hours?!?
Yes, almost exactly
three hours.
Well that means,
the time axis is
out of sync.
So it does seem,
something has gone wrong
in the Precipice World.
[grumble]
Hng! Ghhh...
Then I am calling a Captains'
Meeting immediately.
Captain Kurosuchi, report.
Well, after a detailed
study of the data from
within the Precipice World,
I have discovered that a
"stretching of time" gap has
formed between the World of the
Living and the Soul Society.
And this gap is continuing
to grow even larger.
So at this rate, within the
next day or so, we will no
longer be able to intervene
in the World of the Living.
Captain Kurotsuchi,
is there any way to
stop that gap from expanding?
Of course there is!
An adjustment can be
made immediately.
But I'm more worried
about the cause.
I would like to do a
detailed survey of the
Precipice World first.
[Yamamoto]
Very well.
Regarding to this latest
incident, I appoint Squad
Twelve Captain Mayuri Kurosuchi
to be in charge of organizing
and conducting the survey.
[Yamamoto]
I also order Squad
Eleven Captain Zaraki
to provide security
within the Precipice
World for those involved.
What?
Tch! But why should I
get saddled with such a
bothersome assignment?
I should be the
one complaining!
Can a barbarian like you
even provide security?
You might just trigger
a catastrophe instead.
Good idea.
would you like me
to start with you?!
Tch.
Enough! That is an order!
Hmf!
Hrrm.
[Yamamoto]
I also order Squad Six
Captain Byakuya Kuchiki
and Lieutenant Abarai,
as well as Squad Ten
Captain Hitsugaya
to assist Captain Kurotsuchi
in his field survey.
And you will all work together
cooperatively. Dismissed!
Ehhh...
Ooh!
Hee.
So...
[Ichigo]
Who is this girl?
[Kon]
Uh, I don't know.
But she's a big problem.
If she's a problem,
then why the hell did
you bring her here?!
How should I put this?
I guess it just
happened this way?
Things never
"just happen"!
Wait! No don't!
Kon, what have
you done here?!
Nothing, Zip!
I haven't done
anything at all here!
I found her unconscious,
she was just like that!
Ichigo...
Hm? What is it?
I don't sense anything
from this girl.
Huh?
Even if someone
lacks Spirit Energy,
I would still sense
something if she was human.
But this girl's
really different.
I don't even sense
her existence.
Kon! Where exactly
did you find this
girl anyway?
Lying there in that
parking lot down on Third.
I knew it.
Hnh?
That's where the
Senkaimon opened earlier.
Then is she
a... Gigai?
I dunno.
Anyway, I'm sending a report
about this to the Soul Society.
[Hiyosu]
Hmm?!
Hey Akon. We just got an
inquiry from Rukia Kuchiki
of Squad Thirteen here.
Ignore it!
Not right now.
Aww come on.
Come take a look at it.
Huh?
Alright,
so what is this?
Excuse me, sir.
Ah, Inaba!
A group of officers needs
to enter the Precipice
World to do a survey.
Would you
mind showing
them the way?
Of course, understood sir.
[Hiyosu]
Hey, we've established
communication with
Captain Kurotsuchi.
What took you so long?!
[Akon]
Sorry about that, we had
trouble making adjustments.
How do things look?
Figured out
what's going on?
Hnh! As I suspected,
the cause of the
problem was man-made.
Ha ha! Oh, Kenny!
Being here's a lot of fun!
Hunh?
More importantly,
are all the
others ready yet?
Ooo! It's so gooey!
Yes, sir. They're
about to enter now.
Gzhhh!
STOP IT!
Even with things as they are,
the Restrictive Current still
reacts to Spirit Bodies!
I couldn't care less if you
fools turn into space-time dust!
But I won't allow you to
interfere with my survey.
Hnh! "Won't allow us", eh?
Try me!
Oh my. It appears
you're too stupid
to understand me.
[spirit explosion]
Sir! There's something coming!
You've returned!
What's wrong?
We suddenly lost all
communications with the
Precipice World sir,
and since then, a state of
emergency has been declared!
[Toshiro]
What about Captains
Kurotsuchi and Zaraki?
We... haven't
heard from them...
Where're you going, sir?
To Squad 1.
We found something important
in the Precipice World that
we need to report.
[Jushiro]
So, you're saying when
you arrived there,
you didn't meet up with
Captain Kurotsuchi and
the others?
That's right.
[Yamamoto]
What are you here
to report, then?
We found this near the area
where we were supposed to
rendezvous with Captain
Kurotsuchi's group.
I'm not sure, but perhaps it's
connected to this incident.
This is...!
I believe this warrants
further investigation.
Hmm.
[Kisuke]
Take Ichigo with you?
Yes. I received orders
from the Department of
Research and Development,
to appear before them
with the Substitute
Soul Reaper.
I've never received an
order like that before,
so I tried contacting them
again to try to confirm it.
And your communication
failed. That does seem
strange, doesn't it?
By the way, has the girl
Kon found unconscious
woken up yet?
[Ichigo]
She's still asleep. I was
hoping to ask her some
questions, But I don't know.
So hey, I think I'm
gonna head to the Soul
Society with this.
Right now, I wouldn't
recommend doing that.
Hnh?
The reason I say that,
is 'cause Yoruichi went
there a few days ago.
She was supposed to return
here right away, but we
haven't heard from her since.
In your current state,
I'd say it's not too wise
to go there right now.
[chuckle] You worry too much.
I have to go.
Mmm.
Hm! Well then, fine.
Just one last thing.
At this moment in time,
your Spirit Energy is
pretty stable.
But soon it's going
to start to decrease.
Right.
And, the more you overexert
yourself, the sooner the day
will come when you lose your
Spirit Energy completely.
Don't forget to keep
that fact firmly in mind.
Yeah. I got it.
Both of you please,
be careful out there.
What is it?
Something's not right.
How so?
[Rukia]
Haven't you noticed?
There's not a trace
of Spiritual Pressure
around here.
Not a trace?
[Rukia]
Think about how many Soul
Reapers come and go through here
every day. And yet...
Let's see now.
That's 'cause that Cleaner
thingie comes through and
cleans up all of it !
That can't be why.
Remember? Aizen destroyed the
Cleaner over a month ago.
Ohh. That's right.
Hnh?
Anyway, let's get out
of here quickly, okay?
Right.
Huh?
Hey, Rukia!
What now?
It's coming...
Just what are you
talking about?! Ah!
[panicked]
Yaah! The Cleaner!
I thought you said
it was gone?!
I never thought it would
regenerate so fast!
So how long does it
normally take?!
Honestly... I don't know.
Are you kidding me?!
Damn! My Combat Pass...!
Never mind that!
Just keep running Ichigo!
Bankai!
Hyaaaaah!
Ichigo! You all right?
Oh yeah. I'm fine.
Hnh.
[faints]
Hey! What's wrong?! Ichigo!!
The more you overexert yourself,
the sooner the day will come
when you lose your
Spirit Energy completely.
Egh.
Damn it.
Ngh. Crap, that sucked.
[Toshiro]
Hold it!
Hm?
Toshiro!
Hey, have you seen Rukia?
She should be arou--
Don't move!
Huh?
Throw down your sword, now!
What's going on?
What the hell's
up's with you?!
My duty is to take you in
as a material witness!
Stop resisting!
I'm a material witness?!
What the hell d'ya mean?!
[gasp]
Byakuya!
This isn't personal.
We're not doing this
because we want to, Ichigo.
Ichigo Kurosaki.
We hereby place
you under arrest.
Thank you for
waiting so
patiently.
Now then, shall we go?
Heh.
[Ichigo]
Hold on! We start a new story
arc, and the first thing we do
is arrest the lead character?!!
[Byakuya]
Calm down, Ichigo Kurosaki.
[Ichigo]
Byakuya!
[Byakuya]
Don't concern yourself, we'll
fill in your spot while you're
away in confinement. We promise.
[Ichigo]
This is all wrong!
[Chad]
Just leave it to us.
[Ichigo]
Wait! You too Chad?!