The Zanpakuto... Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined
by its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born with
its Soul Reaper and dies
with its Soul Reaper...
That is the existence
of a Zanpakuto.
[crying]
Why...?
Why have I been
abandoned?!
Orihimeeee!
I was worried! I'm so
glad you're all right!
Huh?
I've been freaked out
since I heard that
someone attacked a high
school girl last night!
I was beside myself!
I was afraid it might
have been my precious
Orihime!
It's really scary, isn't
it?
Are people getting
assaulted at random?
There was nothing random
about this!
All right, take your
seats, everyone. I want
to introduce a new
transfer student.
[snoring]
[singing]
This is Kyoko Haida.
She's your classmate now,
and I want you all to
make her feel welcome.
I am very
pleased to meet you.
I've never
seen her before.
... I know...
What?
So someone targeted a
high-school girl?
That's how it appears.
And about the victim...
She carried a phone
with a pink bear charm.
That's a weird detail.
How did you find out
about it?
That's a secret.
Let's just put it this
way, it'd take all day
to explain.
Really? So what do you
think?
The Sword Beasts are
extremely unstable, so it's
very difficult to track their
Spiritual Pressure.
We're not certain yet,
but a Sword Beast may be
involved in this
incident.
A Zanpakuto attacking
humans? I'll tell you this
much. That's not good...
Hello.
Oh, hello!
Excuse me, but could you
tell me your name?
Sure, I'm Orihime
Inoue! Nice to meet you!
Hm?
Orihime!
Huh?
Come on, slow-poke,
we're gonna miss our
entire lunch break!
I'm sorry about that!
I'll be there in a minute!
Do you wanna
sit with us?
Oh, uh...
Where did she go?
I know something you
girls don't!
I just heard from Ms.
Ochi that the new student,
Kyoko, is incredibly smart.
And not only that,
apparently she's great
at sports as well...
Wow! That's really
amazing!
Now that I think about
it, she got up and solved
that problem in math class
really easily this afternoon.
So... Does Ms. Ochi know
why she transferred?
Mmmm...
I don't know... I didn't
ask her about that.
Victim is a female, 16
sixteen years of age. She's
in a state of shock, but
otherwise seems unharmed.
Are you picking up
a Sword Beast?
No. It seems different
from a Sword Beast in
many ways.
What do you suppose is
happening?
I'm not sure, but we need
to go down there and
check it out.
Okay.
Huh?
Isn't that the kind of
charm Kisuke mentioned?
[whistle blowing]
Get around to the
side! Oh, nice!
There you go! Oh!
Wow! She plays like
a professional!
I guess she really
is a serious athlete!
You gotta pass!
Cover her!
[gasping]
I'm so sorry,
are you all right?
Huh? Hey, time out!
I didn't mean to trip
her. Our feet just got
tangled up!
Do you think
you can walk?
We need some help here,
can someone take her to
the nurse?!
It's just a little
further. You're doing
great.
Our nurse is one of the
best ones in the this
school district!
She'll make you feel
better right away!
She's so gentle, you
hardly know she's
working on you!
OMG and we all had
such a great time!
[gasping]
[screaming]
Oh, dear. Are you
all right, Kyoko?
I knew it.
Huh?
From the moment we met, I
knew you were special.
What do you mean,
"special"?
Your power, of course.
You're a special human
who possesses special
powers.
I've decided you're
worthy of me.
What are you
talking about?
I have certain special
powers, as well. And
since we both have
special powers...
...I'm saying that we
should be friends.
Uh-uh. You have it all
wrong. I'm not a special
person.
Huh?
Like you said, I do have
a few strange powers I've
accumulated over the
years, but it definitely
doesn't make me special.
Where I come from, that's
the definition of special!
Hmm... it's secret.
Now why in the world
would you want to keep
something like that a secret?
Maybe I should tell
all your friends about it.
That way, they can stare
at you suspiciously,
every time you come into
a room.
They'll be terrified of
you! Won't that be fun?
Why?
[gasping]
Why on earth would
you would you want to
do something so mean?
Kyoko!
Back at my last school,
there was a girl named Mai
that I used to hang out with.
We were always together.
She was the only person I
could call a friend.
Kyoko!
After awhile, we came to
completely trust and respect
each other.
No matter what was going
on in my life, she was the
one person I could go to and
talk openly about it.
...Things about school,
things about home, things
about the people we
liked...
I thought she would
accept me, even if I
were different from
other people.
That probably won't
be on the test.
Huh? What are you
talking about? The
teacher said it would!
Right. He just
made a mistake.
He's going to
use the next one.
How would you know that?
I got this for you. You
said that you wanted it,
right?
Wow, you did that for me?
Thanks a lot!
You're welcome! I'll see
you later.
Mai...
Kyoko?
Are you going out
with that boy?
I've gotta tell you,
he's bad news.
No-one else knows about
this, but he has lots of
other girlfriends,
and when he needs it,
he steals money from
his parents.
I'm sorry, Mai. I
didn't wanna have
to tell you.
But I don't want you to
get hurt, and I can't
stand to see him playing
you for a fool.
If I were you, I'd stay
away from him. He's not
worth your time.
Mai...?
You creep.
You scare me, Kyoko.
You're not normal.
But... Mai...
Just stay away!
Mai, don't--
No!
Don't come near me,
anymore! There's something
wrong with you!
Kyoko? Kyoko?
Hey, about what you said,
can't you and I still be
friends regardless.
of whether or not we
have any kind of special
powers?
Huh?
I'd like to be your
friend, if you'd let me.
[groaning]
What's wrong,
Kyoko?!
What is that?!
Kyoko!
Was she holding...
a Zanpakuto?
Did you just
pick that up?
Yeah, it was only there for
a moment, but it was the same
Spiritual Pressure we sensed
last night.
Come on, Ichigo.
It's near Karakura High
School.
Hm? You sure about that?!
[heavy breathing]
I hope...
...after all you've
experienced, you weren't
taking that girl seriously.
If I hadn't shown up at
that moment, you would have
made the same mistake you
made with that other girl.
Those who are always
surrounded by friends
have it so easy...
They will never understand
what we have gone through.
Loss, hate, abandoned
by everyone!
Yes, but...
What is it?
She only said she
wanted to... be my
friend.
Believe me, she didn't
really mean it.
You think so?
Of course. You have a
short memory.
The lesson to be learned
from our abandonment is not
to trust what people say.
They're likely to
lie to you.
That's why you and I
were drawn to each other.
I understand your anger.
Go ahead and unleash
your feelings!
Let it all out. If you
hold it in, the emotions will
turn back on you and your
heart will be crushed.
Quit denying your
true feelings. You want
to kill that girl, Mai
Suzuki, don't you?
Stop it,
you're wrong!
Let me be the instrument
of your revenge!
Stop it. Don't do
this! Leave me alone!
Can you take over my
cleanup duty today?
What?
You wouldn't believe what
she did then...
What was that?
It can't be good.
[heavy breathing]
[screaming]
[shaking]
What do you want?
Please, don't hurt me!
[chuckling]
[gasping]
Stop it!
Stop it? I was simply
trying to grant your
wish, Kyoko.
Why would I ever stop?!
Isn't this what you wanted?
It's not! You're
mistaken!!
[sobbing]
Please forgive me! I
didn't mean to make
you so angry!
It's all right, Mai. I'm
not going to hurt you.
I don't believe you!
You're gonna kill me!
You're wrong! Listen to
what I have to say!
No!
I'm not the one who
chased you up here!
[screaming and sobbing]
Mai!
[growling]
[screaming]
It's hopeless. No one will
ever accept me. How could
they?
So long, Mai.
[screaming]
This is perfect! Your
heart is completely
synchronized with
mine, now!
I've been waiting
patiently for this
moment!
Your body and soul belong
to me, now!
[laughing]
[struggling]
Kyoko! I'm here!
What's happened to you?!
You are too
late, girl.
What have you done to
Kyoko?! Bring her back
right now!
Silence!!
Ichigo!
Rukia!
I thought this Spiritual
Pressure felt odd. It was
because it was fused to a
human!
Who are you
supposed to be?
Ichigo Kurosaki! And I'm
the Substitute Soul Reaper!
Substitute Soul Reaper.
Yes, I've heard things
about you.
What should we do?
We need to be very
careful. However...
...If she's been
completely absorbed
by the Sword Beast...
... We'll be left with no
choice but to kill her.
No, wait a minute!
Hm?
Make it quick.
Kyoko is still fighting
inside of her body!
You're sure of that?
She's suffering.
Enough of this
nonsense!
Yeah, it's faint,
but I can feel it.
So what do you think we
should do?
I'm begging you, don't
draw this out any further,
just let go of her!
That's out of the
question. But let me pose
another possibility. Are
you willing to trade
places with her? I might
let her go, if you don't
mind becoming my host and
giving me complete control.
It's impossible, and you
should already know that.
What?
No one can belong to you
in the end. Neither myself,
nor Kyoko nor anyone else!
It's an illusion you've
created in your own mind!
And it's a completely false
presumption!
What do you
know? You're an
ignorant child!
My master despised me
and discarded me, and
perished without me by
his side! I lost my honor
as a Zanpakuto! And I was
left to die without hope
of anyone finding me!
I won't listen to your
ideals! I can operate on
my own, without a master! I
will absorb everything I can!
I will gain power on my
own! And when I'm done, I
will show everyone what I
can do!
This is crazy,
you're out of
control!
Kyoko!
Kyoko, can you
hear me?!
[struggling]
She's suffering horribly!
Orihime!
Huh?
Use your Sotenkishun!
I think you can separate
the Sword Beast from its
host!
Sotenkishun!
I reject you!
She's vulnerable now!
Getsugatensho!
[giggling]
I wiped Mai Suzuki's
memory.
Kyoko?
Orihime!
[giggling]
Let's walk home together.
Is something wrong?
Mmm-mmm.
[giggling]
You want to stop by a
sweet shop, don't you,
Orihime?
That's right, but how did
you know that?
By the look on your face.
[giggling]
Where's Uryu
and Chad??
Chad found a stray cat
and took it over to the
animal hospital. And Uryu
has the stomach flu.
But, I was with him all
day yesterday! I need to
gargle and wash my hands!
I think it's too late for
that.
Why am I so hot? Am I
getting a fever? My
stomach hurts!