(Gasps)
Hello, good to see you.
You seem to be doing
well.
[Tsukishima]
Yes...
(Gasp)
In fact he appears to be
brimming with energy.
That actually makes me
quite happy.
(Grunt)
Now then...
(Explosion)
[Ginjo]
I destroyed the stairway.
Yukio's the only one who
has the power to get up here.
[cont'd]
That levels the playing
field.
[cont'd]
So now, there's really
nothing to hold you back.
Fight them with everything
you've got!
[Ginjo]
Let'em have it,
Ichigo!
(Growls)
(Gasp)
(Growl)
Ah!
(Grunts)
(Fighting Grunts)
Huh?!
(Attacking Grunts)
Ahh!
So that's your Fullbring
in it's completed form?
If so, you've come a long
way in a short time.
Is that supposed to
be a compliment?
You might as well speak
while you still have
the opportunity.
My mission is simple.
I came here to kill you.
(Stunned Breath)
(Gasp)
Chad! Orihime!
Sotenkishun!
[Orihime]
I reject!
Don't do it!
Stop it, Orihime!
Don't help him out by
healing his wounds!
That guy is...
Hm!
Well as always, that was
amazing. Thank you,
Orihime.
Sure, any time!
Tell me, Chad....
[Ichigo Cont'd]
Have you and Orihime
lost it like the others?
What are you talking
about, Ichigo? I don't
know what you mean?
If you ask me, you're
the one who's losing it.
Ichigo, how could you do
something so terrible to Mr.
Tsukishima? Have you forgotten
he's always helped us!
Ichigo, how could you do
something so terrible to Mr.
Tsukishima? Have you forgotten
he's always helped us!
[Chad]
That's right. Like the
time when we saved Rukia.
[cont'd]
Or the time we went to Hueco
Mundo to rescue Orihime
from the Arrancar.
And finally, defeating
Aizen.
[Chad]
We were only able to
accomplish all that thanks
to Mr. Tsukishima!
You see what's happening?
Ichigo...
(Grunt)
Ichigo!
[Moeh]
Going somewhere?
We're the ones your
fighting, remember?
You can't afford to be
thinking or worrying about
anything but that!
Who is this guy?
[cont'd]
What did he just do?
Did he make that thing
fall?
[cont'd]
Doesn't look like he's
got anything in his hands.
[cont'd]
How strange. The chain on
the chandelier that fell
isn't cut.
[cont'd]
All of its screws came
undone.
So then, what is this
guy's Fullbring?
You're staying here.
There is a time and a
place for everything, but
this is inappropriate.
(Grunt)
[Tsukishima]
You know those science fiction
novels where people go back
in time to alter events?
Ever notice how the
slightest tampering can
completely change the future.
That's because everyone
accepts the idea that time
flows from the past to
what lies ahead.
[cont'd]
But my Fullbring, "Book
of the End," insinuates
itself into peoples pasts.
(Gasp)
[Tsukishima]
You see, my power doesn't
manipulate time or
radically alter someone's
[cont'd]
memories. Instead, I have
the unique ability to
physically insert my complete
[cont'd]
presence into the past
of others.
So Ginjo's guess about
your power was right.
Oh? So Ginjo was actually
able to figure me out.
What a surprise. I really
didn't think he was that sharp.
Perhaps I've underestimated
him all these years.
[Tsukishima]
Well I know it's
regrettable, but I
want you to understand.
[cont'd]
The past your friends
experienced and the past
you experienced are two
[cont'd]
very separate
realities.
Hah!
That's a pretty distorted
description of what
you've done. What you
should say is that you
used your powers to
twist reality into
what benefits you.
But that's where
you're wrong.
[Tsukishima cont'd]
I didn't twist reality
at all. I am part of the
lives of all your
[cont'd]
close friends and
family.
[cont'd]
You're the only one
that's leading a life
with a false past.
[cont'd]
You must feel empty knowing
it's only different for
you, but don't worry.
Soon that isolated feeling
inside you will have never
existed in the first place,
(Gasp)
Ahh!
Orihime...
(Punch Grunt)
Chad, why?!
[Chad]
That's what I want
to know.
This is not the reason
that I've worked so
hard to become strong.
It's not so I could
fight you! Why are you
doing this?!
You've got it all
wrong! Please, stop!
Brazo Izquierdo
Del Diablo!
Damn it! Damn it!
Why is this happening?
Why won't they believe
me?!
All I've wanted to do
was protect you guys!
So why this?! I-I tried!
It's not fair! I
didn't regain my powers
for things to end up
like this?!
Tsukishima!
(Explosion)
Ichigo!
Dirty Boots!
Ahh!
(Fighting Grunts)
Time tells no lies.
Stop it, Kutsuzawa!
(Grunt)
Damn it! Not you
guys too!
I have to do something!
[Riruka]
Doll House!
(Gasp)
You're not leaving!
Ahh!
Damn it!
(Grunt)
Ah!
What the hell?
That punch felt like
nothing to me.
(Gasp)
My sword...
It's broken!
Hah! You're damn lucky
that I hit your sword
instead of you!
That last spin I made
was so good, there's no
telling how you would've
ended up!
[Ginjo]
What do you mean?!
My Fullbring is
called...
[Moeh]
Jackpot Knuckle!
I can control the odds
and make a jackpot hit for
me, right from the start!
[cont'd]
That last punch I threw
hit the jackpot and look
what happened?
[cont'd]
The guard of your
sword went and snapped
from wear and tear!
[cont'd]
The coin I flicked
earlier hit the jackpot too
and you saw the result.
[cont'd]
Those screws of the
chandelier came undone and
it all came falling down.
Come and get me,
Kugo Ginjo.
Do it and I'll show
you how a one shot kill
can really happen!
Damn, I can't just stand
here and let Ichigo
get cut down!
Sorry, but my time's too
precious to waste goofing
around with you!
Let's go!
(Fighting Grunts)
Tsukishima!
What is it?
Is this getting to you?
I see your so angry, you
can barely even speak to me.
Ah!
(Grunt)
Getsuga!
Tensho!
He's fast!
(Grunt)
He's in Fullbring mode,
yet he was able to unleash
Getsugatensho.
He's advanced rather
dramatically.
His powers have
definitely reawakened.
Not only that but the
speed of his attacks
are several times faster
than I had expected.
[Tsukishima]
He really has succeeded
in combining his Soul Reaper
powers with Fullbring.
Damn you!
[Tsukishima]
And as I thought it would,
despair helped fuel the
completion of his power.
Well, okay.
It's time to put the
finishing touches on
this.
Ichigo!
I'd keep your eyes
over here!
(Grunt)
No you don't!
(Kick Grunt)
The time has come.
(Annoyed Grunt)
Time for what?
What do you mean?
Ahh!
There's no way I've got
a chance against all
four of them.
Now where's Ichigo?
Ahh!
(Gasp)
Why are you two
protecting him?!
Please, stop! Orihime!
Chad!
I say the same
to you!
Come back to your
senses! Ichigo!
Don't you get it?
I only came here to
fight Tsukishima, not
you!
Come out! Stop hiding
behind my friends,
you bastard!
Get out here and
fight your own battle!
Where'd he go?
(Gasp)
(Struggling Breaths)
Damn it!
Ginjo!
(Grunt)
Damn it!
(Painful Sigh)
Ginjo!
What'll happen next?!
With my Fullbring, "Book
of the End," I can insert
my presence into another
person's past.
Will Ginjo end up like
all the others?
Will he suddenly side
with Tsukishima?
Ginjo! Hey Ginjo,
are you all right?!
Ginjo!
(Painful Breathing)
Pipe down, will ya?
Right now, you really need
to stop focusing on me,
Kurosaki.
[Ichigo]
Ginjo...
Think only about
what I said earlier.
[Ginjo Cont'd]
If Tsukishima blindsides
you, you're done!
(Fighting Grunt)
[Ichigo]
So are you sure you're
all right?
[Ginjo]
I don't know...
But...
[cont'd]
At the moment, I still
consider Tsukishima to
be my enemy!
[cont'd]
And I still see you
as a friend.
Yeah, that's good
to know.
I could feel that he
cut me pretty good.
But for some reason his
power didn't work.
[Ginjo Cont'd]
Could it be that the
time his power needs
to take effect varies?
[cont'd]
Or maybe he hasn't used
his full power yet, but
I'm not sure how we'll
[cont'd]
be able to tell.
Whatever's going on here,
we have to defeat him
now while we can, because
if his power do take effect
there won't be a
thing we can do to
stop him!
Ichigo, what happened
to you?
What's gotten into you,
Ichigo?
Ichigo..
It's all your fault!
Hey, Ichigo!
(Gasp)
Right.
Hm?!
Ichigo...
Uryu!
Whose side is he on?!
[Ichigo]
After all, Uryu was also
cut down by Tsukishima.
[cont'd]
And who healed his wounds?
Was it Orihime?
[cont'd]
But she was cut down
by Tsukishima as well.
[cont'd]
So did she go heal Uryu,
before or after she thought
of Tsukishima as her friend?
If it was after, does
that mean she healed
Uryu so he could join
Tsukishima's army?
And fight me along
with everyone else?!
[Ichigo]
So Uryu, which is it?!
(Gasp)
So then, you're one of
them too, huh?
Uryu!
Uryu...
Ichigo, come over
here.
I saw what's going on
down here. Relax.
I'm on your side.
Oh really?
Come on! You need to
move now!
(Gasp)
Uryu!
Ichigo!
[Uryu]
Don't you get it?!
(Gasp)
The guy who attacked
me, is standing right
behind you!
The guy who attacked
me, is standing right
behind you!
No!
(Grunt)
(Painful Exhale)
(Laughing)
Ginjo, why?
Huh?
[Ichigo]
Is it because of
Tsukishima's power?
It sure was.
[Ginjo Cont'd]
It was definitely because
of Tsukishima's power.
But you need to
understand something.
I didn't become your
enemy just now when you
saw Tsukishima cut me.
I didn't become your
enemy just now when you
saw Tsukishima cut me.
I let Tsukishima cut me
twice so I could return
to my original self.
[Ginjo Cont'd]
Now your Fullbring is
mine!
(Painful Grunt)
[Moeh]
You're all very strong!
Just what I'd expect from
Mr. Tsukishima's friends.
[Riruka]
I've been meaning to
ask. Uh, who are you?
[Moeh]
I'm Mr. Tsukishima's
apprentice!
[Jackie]
He had an apprentice?
[Moeh]
You haven't hear about
me from him? Like how
useful or handsome I am?
[Riruka & Jackie]
Not a word!