[theme music]
NARRATOR: Soul Reapers,
the spiritual guardians
to the world of the living.
Their job is to maintain the
balance between the myriad
of good and evil souls
that fill this world.
Ichigo sought out the
Visoreds with hopes
of increasing his power.
Shinji guided Ichigo
to his inner world,
where he was forced to
face his Hollow self.
-I am Zangetsu!
NARRATOR: Byakuya and Jin
Kariya appeared before Ichigo
as illusions.
They questioned his
resolve, as well as
his determination
to truly fight.
Finally, Ichigo confronted
his Hollow self,
who viciously ran him through.
-Which means I'll be king.
ICHIGO: What the--
where am I now?
[shout]
-So, it looks like you're
finally awake, eh, kid?
Thought you might be dead.
-Kenpachi.
So, you're next, huh?
-Kenpachi?
Who the hell is that?
Makes no difference, because
I'm here to kill you!
[growl]
-Well, it looks like he's
completely Hollowfied now.
Who would've thought?
LISA (VOICEOVER): By the
time Love began his turn,
60 minutes had already passed.
Shouldn't be long now
before it's my turn.
Kensei.
-Hm?
-What's the longest amount
of time any one of us
has taken to control our Hollow?
-It was Hiyori, at 69
minutes, 2 seconds.
-How many minutes
has it been now?
-68 minutes.
And 44 seconds.
LISA: I see.
-Why are you doing this?
Cut it out!
We settled things
a long time ago.
There's no reason
for us to fight!
-Settle things?
One thing was never settled.
This is a battle with
swords, not some fist fight.
As long as one of us
is still breathing,
then this fight's not over.
-You're making this
a fight to the death?
Why?
There's no reason.
-You mean you need
a reason to fight?
Why don't you just
accept it, Ichigo?
You enjoy fighting
as much as I do.
you cave power.
Isn't that right, Ichigo?
And anyone who truly
loves power loves
to measure that power in battle.
It's a simple fact.
The question is, do we fight
in order to gain more power,
or do we gain more
power in order to fight?
I haven't figured it out yet.
But who cares?
Because one thing
is for certain.
There is no reason we should
ever deny it, or try to change.
Because we were born this way!
You have always wanted to fight,
and you always will, Ichigo.
It's part of you.
You do it instinctively.
You have no choice but to fight.
Because it's the only
way to gain power.
Fight, Ichigo!
If you want to control
that power, take your sword
and cut down your enemies.
There is no other path.
No way to move forward.
Or back.
Fight, Ichigo!
-It's a Cero!
Look out!
-Don't worry.
-Do you think he's going
to have to Hollowfy?
-Of course.
He's not an idiot.
Even Love must
Hollowfy to block that.
The spiritual pressure
is too intense.
[roar]
-What's going on?
-Hachi!
Get love out of the barrier now!
[scream]
-Damn.
What do you know?
I guess I must have
been wrong about you.
Looks like you still have a
little of that killer instinct,
after all.
Fine.
You've defeated me.
You have won the fight for now.
I guess I've no choice.
I'll have to accept
you as the king.
Still, I wouldn't
want you to forget.
While you're strutting around
like a king on his horse,
I can take that crown
away at any time.
I'll keep an eye on you, and
the moment I sense the slightest
weakness, I'll toss you to the
ground, stomp on your skull,
and crush it like an egg!
Just one last piece
of advice before I go.
If you're serious about
controlling my power,
then all you have to
remember is one thing.
Don't get yourself killed
before we meet again!
-Now, Hachi.
-As you command.
-He's looking pretty
banged up, Hachi.
You think he'll be all right?
-Shh.
-So how do you feel now?
-Fine.
Not bad at all.
-Very good.
-Don't forget, I'll
keep an eye on you,
and the moment I sense
the slightest weakness,
I'll toss you to the
ground, stomp on your skull,
and crush you like an egg!
-Sorry to break it to ya, but
that's not going to happen.
-Ichigo wasn't in
school again today,
and it's not like him to
be missing for two days.
When I concentrate, I can
sense his spiritual pressure.
And it's still strong, so I
guess he must be all right.
If I know Ichigo, he
probably just went off
to do some kind of
training in secret
because he doesn't want
anyone to bother him.
And if that's all he's
doing, then I probably
shouldn't go looking for him.
Rukia must be worried, too.
I wonderif he disappeared
without saying anything to her?
Wh-- what am I doing?
Would you listen to me?
This is so depressing.
I need to figure out what
I want to do this weekend!
Ha ha!
Oh!
I know.
I'll give Tatsuki a call.
She said she wanted
to go out and find
something interesting to eat.
Rice cream.
Skewered donuts.
And yokon steaks!
[chatter]
-Oh, yeah.
I just remembered,
Tatsuki really
hasn't been herself lately.
-Oh.
It's good to see you
back home, Orihime.
-Thanks.
It's good to be
home, Mrs. Shimura.
-I've been meaning
to ask you something.
It's about your
two young friends,
the ones who've been visiting.
Now, I don't mean to pry, but
are you sure they're all right?
-Uh, sure.
Why do you ask?
-Well, I wasn't spying, but I
couldn't help but notice them
carrying something
odd into your place.
-Whoa.
That's really cool.
No!
I mean not cool!
What's going on?
-Damn.
She couldn't have
picked a worse time
to walk through that
door if she'd tried.
-I'm sorry.
Thank you for waiting.
You've reached the call
center for the Department
of Research and Development.
-Tell him Toshiro Hitsugaya,
captain of Squad 10,
is calling.
-Yes, sir.
He's expecting your call.
-It's the Head Captain.
-I must commend you for taking
care of this so quickly,
Captain Hitsugaya.
The recent development made it
imperative that we establish
this emergency channel
as soon as possible.
We have discovered Sosuke
Aizen's true objective.
-That's what this is about?
So you've found out
what Aizen's after?
-Mm.
We have, indeed.
-You know what?
It sounds like you guys are
discussing important Soul
Reaper stuff, so I'll
just go outside, OK?
-Wait a moment.
Unfortunately, the matter
I'm about to discuss
concerns you humans as well.
You should hear
what I have to say.
-Yes, sir.
-As you may know, Sosuke
Aizen disappeared months ago,
and since then we have launched
an extensive investigation.
We've had teams scouring the
Squad 5 captain's room where
Aizen lived, the underground
assembly hall of Central 46,
the Seijoto Kyorin,
where he hid himself
after his feigned death.
And even the Daireisho
Archive, where
after countless hours of
sifting through all the data,
Captain Ukitake
discovered something.
-Hey.
You're working hard.
-Shunsui and Nano.
What are you doing here?
-We had some free
time, so we thought
we'd come down here
and help you out.
-Hopefully we can
help you find whatever
it is you've been looking for.
-Thank you.
MAN: Captain!
We just found some
traces of Captain Aizen's
spiritual pressure!
-I'm sending the data over
to your monitor right now!
-The Hogyoku.
Look at that.
See?
He accessed all the research
and data related to it.
-Yeah.
Since that's what
Aizen was after,
it only makes sense that he'd
be poking around in there.
-But look at this one.
It's different from
all of the others.
This information
here is completely
unrelated to the Hogyoku.
-This is--
-The information
Captain Aizen had
ben looking at-- what was it?
-The Oken.
-Um, what exactly is an Oken?
-The literal translation
is the royal key.
You may not have known,
but the Soul Society
has a royal family.
We do have a king, but he had
placed Central 46 in charge
of governing the Soul
Society, and the royal family
chose never to get involved.
Neither the captain
nor myself, none of us
have actually seen the
royal family in person.
-Indeed.
Our king is called the
Reio, or Soul King.
Not only is he
revered, he is also
an important symbolic figure
within the Soul Society.
The royal palace is located in
a completely separate dimension,
and is guarded by its own
private force, an elite group
known as the Royal
Security Guards.
And the Oken is the
key that opens the gate
to the dimension where
the royal palace is.
-If that's true, and
Aizen's after the key,
that means he wants to--
-Murder the king.
I'm afraid we must assume
that is his motive.
However, I believe there
is a more immediate threat.
-Could there have
been any information
in the book Aizen was looking
at that would lead him
to the location of the Oken?
-Not exactly.
The location of the
Oken is a secret
that has been passed down from
one head captain of the 13
Court Guard Squads to
the next for generations.
There has never
been, nor ever shall
be a written record
of its whereabouts.
The document Aizen was looking
at dealt not with the location,
but the creation of the Oken.
He now possesses the
knowledge with which
to create the royal key.
-The Oken Codex.
The materials required
to create an Oken
are 100,000 souls and a jureichi
one spirit mile in diameter.
A jureichi is an
enriched spirit zone
found in the world
of the living.
Its location changes over time.
Because it is so
spiritually charged,
it's an area spirits
are drawn to.
-Nanao, is there any
way to figure out
the current location
of the jureichi?
-Of course.
It'll only take a minute.
-I don't believe it.
HEAD CAPTAIN: Perhaps
you understand now.
The jureichi that Aizen
is after is Karakura Town.
I realize 100,000 souls and the
jureichi with a radius of one
spirit mile may seem
like abstract concepts
and be difficult for
you to visualize,
so I'll put it in
more concrete terms.
If Aizen is able to follow
the instructions which he now
possesses, and he succeeds
in completing the Oken,
Karakura Town, the land
on which it stands,
and every person
living there, will
be carved out of this world
and erased from existence.
-No.
That's not possible.
But-- isn't there
anything you can do?
Isn't there some
way to stop him?
HEAD CAPTAIN: We
will find a way.
The 13 Court Guard Squads were
created for this very purpose.
Thankfully, we still have
a little time to work with.
According to Captain
Kurotsuchi's report,
the Hogyoku remains a dormant
state for a period of time
after being released
from its seal.
There is nothing Aizen
can do to change that.
We believe it will take
four months to fully awaken.
Aizen will be unable
to assemble his forces
until the Hogyoku
has fully awakened.
Then he will make his move.
This winter we shall flight.
Until then we must
hone our skills,
and not rest until we
are prepared for battle.
-Yes, sir.
-Now as for you, Orihime
Inoue, since Aizen's objective
is the world of the
living, the area
may be too large for us
to handle by ourselves.
We will need the
world of the living
to gather its strength as well.
Go.
I want you to inform Ichigo
Kurosaki of this matter.
-Yes, sir.
-I'll find Ikkaku and make sure
that everyone else is notified.
-Good.
I'll give you a hand.
-Wait.
I was wondering if I might have
a moment of your time, Captain
Hitsugaya?
I realize there are
urgent matters at hand,
but there is
someone here who has
been waiting to speak with you.
-It can't be.
-Is that it?
Have you had enough,
Yasutora Sado?
Considering the fact
that the sun's still out,
it's a little early to
be calling it a day.
-I'm not done yet.
-Now you're talkin'.
-Where are they?
Ichigo.
[theme music]
RANGIKU: Orihime, since we've
got such a huge wide screen,
what do you say we go
out and rent something?
ORIHIME: There's a new comedy
I've been dying to see.
RANGIKU: Sounds good.
HITSUGAYA: Listen, you two.
That's not what this was
meant to be used for.
RANGIKU: Don't worry.
I'll rent one of
those kids' anime DVDs
that you like so much.
HITSUGAYA: Rangiku.