MIZUIRO KOJIMA
(VOICEOVER): Spring, a time
when everyone sets off for
new places with their hearts
full of hope-- that's spring.
But the hope in my
heart had died long ago,
and not even the magic of
the season could revive it.
MIZUIRO'S MOTHER
(ON PHONE): Mizuiro,
why are you calling me again?
Didn't you hear a
word I had last night?
I specifically remember telling
you that I have a very busy day
today, and I don't
have time to talk.
This is so like you, always
thinking of yourself.
You need to try putting
yourself in my shoes sometime.
-Calling your mother again?
You're such a good son.
-I don't really have a mother.
I made her up.
-You know, you really
shouldn't talk like that.
You're going to make
your mother cry.
Here, your jacket.
It's your first day of
high school, isn't it?
Would you like me
to drop you off?
-Sure.
Thanks.
Hello, hello.
This is Mizuiro,
calling the world.
Come in, world!
Are all of our cords
properly connected?
My world appears to
be spinning correctly.
All systems are green.
Communications--
(DISAPPOINTED)
failure.
[music - scandal, "shojo s"]
YUZU KUROSAKI:
Ichigo, up and at 'em!
Get out of bed already!
It's breakfast time!
You'll be late for school!
[ichigo yawning]
-There we go.
That looks absolutely delicious.
-Catch you guys later.
-Wait a minute!
Ichigo, what about
your breakfast?
-Sorry, Yuzu.
I'll be back before noon.
Leave it there.
I'll eat it later.
YUZU KUROSAKI: But
I fried you an egg.
It'll be all cold by then.
MOMO HINAMORI:
Captain Aizen, may
I have a moment of your time?
-Of course, Momo.
Please come in.
What can I do for you?
I'm impressed.
It shows a free-flowing style,
with a nice sense of artistry.
MOMO HINAMORI:
Thank you very much.
Oh, I almost forgot.
Here's my report from
the lieutenants' meeting.
SOSUKE AIZEN: Thank you.
I'll go over it later.
TOSHIRO HITSUGAYA:
Rangiku, are you in here?
Answer me.
Where the hell is she?
Wait.
If she's not here, why does
this room reek of liquor?
-Mmm, hi there, Captain.
-Ugh.
-Join me for a drink?
-Forget it.
In case you've forgotten,
there's a lieutenants' meeting.
You were supposed to attend
and bring me the report.
Hey, wake up!
Are you even listening to me?
-[moans] Stop.
No, don't stop.
Mmm.
-[sighs] What an idiot.
I'm pretty sure I don't want to
know what she's dreaming about.
-I'm sorry I'm late.
Looks like you haven't
even started yet.
How lucky.
-Just take your
seat while we wait.
-Oh, of course.
-So we have to sit here
and wait for Rangiku?
-She probably has
a hangover again.
-[groans]
-She's always doing that.
Ah!
-Hey, I'm the one who brought
those snacks, Yachiru.
You might want to leave
some for the rest of us.
-For such a rich
guy, you sure talk
like a tight-fisted,
money-grubbing cheapskate!
-What?
Did you just--
-Keep it down.
Ugh, your voices
are like cannons
in the back of my skull.
Do you have to shout?
-Well, well.
I take it Rangiku's not the
only one with a hangover.
--[sneezes] [groans]
It's spring again.
[sniffles, swallows] Yep,
definitely the best cure
for a hangover.
MIZUIRO KOJIMA (VOICEOVER):
A new uniform-- [chuckles]--
and a new school.
Well, guess I should start
feeling-- [chuckles]--
the same way any other
new student would feel.
-Are you listening to me?
We're not talking about a simple
violation of the school's dress
code or anything like that.
Your entire head
is bright yellow.
-Hey, Chad.
-Mmm?
-Sado Yashutora.
What, you think you're
too good to say hi to me?
Well?
-Who are you?
-I'm Reiichi Oshima from
Tokata Junior High, damn it!
Are you playing me?
-Uh, what's the problem here?
-Huh?
Listen, this is
between me and him.
So why don't you
just don't bug off?
-(HOWLING) Mizuiro!
(BABBLING) Trouble!
We've got trouble, Mizuiro!
-Hey, Keigo.
How's it going?
-You're not going to
believe what I just heard!
We've got big, big, big trouble!
-You seem kind of
hyper this morning.
-Chad and Ichigo from
Mashiba Junior High School?
-Now do you get it?
For some reason, they
both entered this school.
This is no joke!
-So what if they did?
Why are you freaking out?
-You moron!
Chad and Ichigo are
the most disgusting
super juvenile
delinquents of all time!
You wouldn't believe
some of the stories
I heard about these guys!
People say that they're
in with the Yakuza!
They've got arrest records
that are like a mile long!
They smuggle drugs
and go into bookstores
and look at porn for
like five hours straight!
-But you've never met them,
and those are just rumors,
so you don't know what
kind of people they are.
-We're talking about
Chad and Ichigo here!
We know exactly what
kind of people they are!
[continues yelling]
MIZUIRO KOJIMA
(VOICEOVER): Let's see.
First, each class assembles
for a short homeroom,
followed by the
welcome assembly.
-Hey, look at that.
They've already posted
the class assignments,
and it looks like we're
both in class 1-3.
-You can see that from here?
Man, I've got to
get my eyes checked.
Huh?
Aaah!
There's no way!
The unimaginable has just
become a horrible reality!
-What's the matter?
-[groans] Our youth just ended.
-Hey, that's Mizuiro.
-Am I crazy, or is
Mizuiro kind of hot?
-He sure is.
-He's like, not pushy
or overly aggressive,
you know what I mean?
-Nothing bothers him.
I think that's so sweet.
-I know.
It's like he has
this healing quality.
[girls giggling]
MIZUIRO KOJIMA (VOICEOVER):
I don't feel driven,
because I don't have any
expectations, or any anger.
My smile is nothing
more than a pose.
I can give it to anyone,
anytime, anywhere.
ORIHIME INOUE: [humming]
Oh, this must be the room.
Let's see.
Where is Tatsuki?
TATSUKI ARISAWA: Think fast.
-Huh?
ENTIRE CLASS: Whoa.
STUDENT: Man, did you see that?
-Very good, Orihime.
-You'll never catch me
off guard again, Tatsuki.
-Good.
You passed the test.
I'm impressed with how much
your reflexes have improved.
-Thanks to you.
If you weren't such
a good teacher,
I never would have
learned anything.
But please stop with the
surprise attack test.
I'm worried you'll
scare everyone.
-[laughs]
-Oh, Zu.
[both screaming]
-[screams]
[crashing sound]
-Oh my gosh, are you all right?
I'm so sorry.
I don't even know your name.
-(STAMMERING) It's a
pleasure to meet you.
I'm Chizuru Honsho, one of the
new students in this class.
-What'd you do that for, anyway?
Are you some kind of psychopath?
-Look who's talking!
What were you planning
on doing, sneaking up
on Orihime like that?
-Orihime-- that is the
loveliest name I've ever heard,
and so appropriate for
my lovely new Venus.
--[grunts] You need to back
off, you wacko airhead.
[screaming, crashing]
CHIZURU HONSHO:
That was nothing!
This violence will not
make my love waver!
TATSUKI ARISAWA: Oh yeah?
Then I'll show you some real
violence, you little pervert!
What do you think about that?
Are you wavering yet?
How about this?
There's more where
that came from!
[weeping]
-Hey, come on.
Tell me what's the matter.
Did you see I brought
you some flowers again.
I picked them myself.
-Hey mommy, look.
That man over there is
talking to the flowers.
-Don't point.
I told you, it's not polite.
-What is it that's
making you so sad?
-It's just that
something's not right.
-Huh?
-I'm afraid of the sky.
-The sky?
Why?
YUZU KUROSAKI: Hey Karin, what
are you just standing there
for?
We're going to be
late for school.
-[groans]
-What's wrong?
Is it going to start
raining or something?
-Uh, I don't know.
There's something
strange about the sky.
I know that sounds weird,
but it seems heavy somehow.
--[gasps] You think it has
something to do with that
spooky old ghost again?
-What, you mean that ghost
who's standing right behind you?
-What?
You're kidding, right?
Where?
NANAO ISE: Next, we need
to discuss the replacement
of the soul monitoring officer
stationed at the 3,600th access
on the world of the living.
The position is
currently being occupied
by a member of Squad Four.
But due to chronic back
pain, he has been out
on extended sick leave.
-Ah, a good swift kick
in the ass and that guy
will be back on his
feet in no time.
-Back pain is serious business.
We need to give him time
to rest and recover.
-Lieutenant Sasakibe?
-Yes?
-I would like to recommend
Rukia Kuchiki from our squad.
-Hmm.
Your reasons?
-Sir, Captain Ukitake
and I discussed it.
He feels Rukia would
benefit greatly
from being stationed as
an officer on the world
of the living, and gain much
needed experience as a Soul
Reaper.
-Interesting.
So it's Captain
Ukitake's recommendation?
-Yes, sir.
-Hmm.
I'm going to approve this.
Rukia Kuchiki of Squad 13
will be the replacement.
Proceed to the next matter.
-Yes, sir.
As you know, we've been
looking for someone
to fill the vacant lieutenant's
position is Squad Six.
The captains held a meeting
to address this matter,
and they've chosen Renji
Abarai, 6th Seat of Squad 11,
to fill the position.
LIEUTENANTS: Huh?
-Huh?
That punk?
What a loser.
I can't believe
they think someone
like that is
lieutenant material.
All that jerk'll do is scar
the name of the 13 Court Guard
Squads.
--[laughs] Then you'll fit right
in, because your bald head has
a scar on it too.
Whoa!
-Cut that out!
That's not a scar!
And quit calling me bald!
-You mean I'm being transferred?
To where?
-No, that's not it.
We're not talking
about transferring
you or anything as
extreme as that.
We're just sending you to
the world of the living,
just like that mission you
and I went on together.
You know, that was back when
you had first joined the squad.
You remember that, right?
-Uh, actually, I--
-You see?
She doesn't even remember going.
The experience was
so bad, she probably
erased it from her memory.
Right, Rukia?
-Well, uh--
-Argh!
Keep quiet!
Nobody asked you, so
why don't you just go
stick your head in
the sand somewhere!
-Oh yeah?
What do you think I am, some
kind of ostrich or something?
-Please stop.
[arguing continues]
-Your new post is in a
four-kilometer radius
around Karakura Town, and
it's just for one month.
With your skills,
it should be easy.
I'm sure you can
handle it, Rukia.
-[gasps] Captain Ukitake!
-Oh-- Captain!
-You shouldn't be out, sir.
You need your rest.
-Well, that's kind of you,
but I'm feeling good today.
Even though this is just a
month-long assignment, Rukia,
I thought you might be a little
anxious about being sent out
on your own for the first time.
So I came to see you off.
-Thank you, Captain.
-Please, Rukia.
It's nothing, really.
Have you told Byakuya yet?
-Uh, of course.
I mean-- not yet.
Captain Kuchiki hates
it when I bother him
with every little detail.
[sighs] So I was going to
leave without saying anything
to him about it.
-I see.
It's all right.
If that's what you
really want to do,
then I support your decision.
I'll tell Byakuya for you.
So go with a clear conscience.
-[gasps] Thank you, Captain.
I hereby promote Squad
11 6th Seat Renji Abarai
to the position of
Lieutenant of Squad Six.
Congratulations,
Lieutenant Abarai.
-Yes, thanks.
Uh, I mean, it is an honor.
I humbly accept, Lieutenant.
-You don't have to do so
formal with me, Renji.
-Well, are you happy, Renji?
With a promotion
like this, you've
gotten yourself one step
closer to Captain Kuchiki
and his sister.
-What do you mean?
-Isn't it about time
you talked to her?
-When are you going to get over
your insecurity with Rukia?
I mean, come on, Renji.
Even though she's
some kind of royalty,
you can approach her, now
that you're a lieutenant.
You haven't spoken for 40 years.
Don't you think it's about time
you patched things up with her?
-If you want to do that, then
I suggest that you hurry.
Rukia's just been assigned
a month-long station
in the world of the living, and
she's scheduled to leave soon.
-Oh no!
You've got to hurry up, Renji!
-No.
I won't be officially promoted
until the ceremony a month
from now anyway.
So I'll wait until after that.
I'll surprise her
when she comes back,
and tell her that I've
been made lieutenant.
-(WEEPING) Oh, goodbye,
goodbye, cruel world.
Why, why did this
have to happen?
[rumbling]
-Huh?
[explosion]
[students screaming]
KIEGO ASANO: Gah!
No, it's Chad and Ichigo!
Aaah!
[boys laughing]
-No!
No, no, no, no!
This can't be happening!
This is like some kind
of horrible nightmare
that just keeps getting
worse and worse!
It's a nightmare!
Tell me it's a nightmare!
-Please shut up.
--[laughs] Chad and
Ichigo running away,
like two scared rabbits.
-Reiichi Oshima from
Tokata Junior High!
-Hey, Kiego?
How is it you're so
well-informed about all
these juvenile delinquents?
And I don't know
if you've noticed,
but all their names seem
to be on our class roster.
-What's your problem?
You a friend of
Ichigo's or something?
-No, no, no, not me.
I've never seen or met the
guy before today, honestly.
-Mizuiro Kojima from
Hiragi Second Junior High.
I'm in class 1-3.
Nice to meet you.
-[croaks weakly]
-Mizuiro Kojima has joined
the other side. [hums]
-Aaah!
He hasn't He doesn't
even have a side!
He's-- you know!
Tell him you don't have a side!
Tell him you're not
that kind of kid!
Tell him anything!
You've got to help me out!
Mizuiro, I'm going to die!
Mizuiro!
-Class 1-3?
We're all in the
same class, then.
I'm Ichigo Kurosaki, and
this here is Chad Yasutora.
It's good to meet you.
Who's your friend over there?
-Mizuiro!
-That's Kiego Asano.
He doesn't do too
well in school,
but he's a pretty smart
guy-- honest, likable, loyal.
What can I say?
He's 100 times better than me.
-Whoa, you're incredible.
-Huh?
-I mean, for someone to have
so many nice things to say
about his friend.
That's pretty rare nowadays.
-Mizuiro, how are you
at making up excuses?
-I'm so good it's sick.
-All right, then.
You've got five minutes to come
up with something creative,
because we're going to need
a story that's good enough
to keep us all from
getting suspended.
We're rescuing
your friend Kiego.
MIZUIRO KOJIMA (VOICEOVER): And
who should I tell of this joy?
MIZUIRO KOJIMA: They were
different than what we thought.
KIEGO ASANO: Hmm, yeah.
I guess maybe they were.
But how different were they?
-Way different.
MIZUIRO KOJIMA
(VOICEOVER): Sometimes
I think we're all
connected to this world
with countless cords.
We're kind of like a
patient in intensive care.
Even though we don't
want them, we're
terrified to remove
even one cord.
But the truth is, no
matter what we do,
sometimes it's just too hard
to maintain a connection.
-Hey Mizuiro, aren't you going
to give Nanako a call today?
MIZUIRO KOJIMA (VOICEOVER):
It's almost impossible
to reattach the cord to
its original location.
I still can't do it.
--[chuckles] I don't
feel like it today.
-Glad to hear you say that.
-Hello, hello,
calling the new world.
It's a pleasure to
make your acquaintance.
Are all our cords in place
and ready to be connected?
Is my world spinning
properly on its axis?
System, all red.
Communications, good.
-I sense powerful
spiritual pressure.
[MUSIC - SAMBOMASTER, "KIMI WO
MAMOTTE, KIMI WO AISHITE"]
TOSHIRO HITSUGAYA: Renji, I
hear you're going to the beach.
I've got too much work, so
would you mind taking my camera
and getting some pictures
for the Seireitei bulletin?
RENJI ABARAI: Of Rangiku
in a swimsuit, right?
TOSHIRO HITSUGAYA:
Uh, I didn't say that.
RENJI ABARAI: You mean
you don't want them?
TOSHIRO HITSUGAYA:
Please get them.
RENJI ABARAI: Should've
just said so from the start.