[music -- yui, "rolling star"]
[melodic chanting]
[male grunting]
[crackling]
-Ichigo Kurosaki.
-Hey, good morning Ichigo.
-Hey.
How's it going?
-Ichigo!
[thud]
-I see that you
have found yourself
a nice spot on the floor.
-[weakly] I need first aid.
-What a nut.
I don't know why he
keeps trying that trick.
It'll never work.
-Hi, Ichigo.
Good morning.
-There's something
called a comb.
You you, you should try one.
-Oh really?
Shut up.
--[whining] Oh, you're standing
around together like you've got
a secret club and I'm
not allowed to join it.
Why is Chad with
Orihime and Uryo?
It's like the beauty, the beast,
and the nerd all together,
without me!
Ever since the beginning
of summer break,
you've been stuck
together like glue.
I demand to know why that is!
Those three never
used to hang out,
what could have
happened over the summer
to create such an
unnatural alliance?
And what are you
doing with them?
Oh, the humanity!
It's the tragic end to
a beautiful friendship!
-Chill out.
Nothing happened.
-I've got it.
I'm nothing but an aging puppy
that no one wants to pet.
I'm finished.
-Sounds about right, puppy.
So why don't you go
stand somewhere else?
[keigo gasps]
-Get a grip on yourself, Keigo.
Don't you know
you're being teased?
-Oh, stupid blue skies, I
knew you were teasing me!
-Good morning!
It's nice to see you!
-Back off!
-As usual, an
impressive reaction.
It's nice to know nothing's
changed around here.
-I just want to keep you
abreast of the situation.
Nothing ever changes with
you does it, Chizuru?
Here it is autumn, and
you're still in heat.
-Good morning.
How you doing, Tatsuki?
-Oh, hi.
So, how's your
assignment coming along?
-An assignment's due?
-You forgot about
the assignment we
were given over summer break?
I told you all about it, Ichigo.
-Oh yeah.
I guess I forgot.
-Oh man, I can't believe you.
Don't blame me if you
don't finish it in time.
-Don't worry.
I won't.
-Well, you better not.
Man, you're going
to get in trouble
if you keep missing
so much school.
I mean it.
Hey, what's that thing?
-Huh?
Oh, this?
It's a lucky charm.
-Dad, I'm sorry.
I forgot to return this to you.
Actually, I'm not even
sure why I still have it.
-Hmm.
I don't want it.
-Huh?
-I don't need this
lucky charm anymore.
So I'm giving it to you out
of the goodness of my heart.
-Hey, hold on a second!
Why are you sewing that
thing onto my uniform?
Dad!
-My dad did it.
He sewed it on my uniform.
-I could figure that out
without even asking you.
-How the hell did you
already know that?
-It's a simple case of logic.
Who else but your dad would
give you something as goofy
as that thing?
[ichigo chuckles nervously]
-Anyway, that doesn't matter.
What I really wanted to ask
you about was that skull there.
-Oh, you mean this.
Interesting you should ask that.
I bought it from this guy I met.
I mean, I found it.
Wait a sec.
Tatsuki, you can see this?
-Huh?
What's the big deal?
It's right there?
-Hi, everybody.
-Ah, Miss Ochi.
MISATO OCHI: All right, get
to your seats every one.
-OK.
-Right.
Let's see if all my students
are in attendance today.
Oshima and Sorimachi
are never hear,
because they're
juvenile delinquents.
So we won't worry about
them, will we, class?
I have an exciting announcement.
A transfer student's
going to join our class.
[class ooh's and ahh's]
-This badge is more
powerful than it looks.
It is dangerous for anyone other
than a Soul Reaper to use this.
That is why it has a visual
barrier built into it,
to keep ordinary
humans from seeing it.
-That's what he said.
I wonder if it's broken.
[ichigo shrieks]
-A hollow.
-Something wrong, Ichigo?
-It's nothing, really.
A little gas?
-Hey.
Please be quiet.
You can come in now.
Odd, where'd he go?
Hey Ichigo, where are you going?
-To the restroom!
-Restroom?
Right.
Hey!
Chad, Orihime!
Where are you two going?
--[chad and orihime together]
To the restroom.
MISATO OCHI: Orihime,
shame on you.
You should know that
a young lady never
runs off to the
restroom like that.
Honestly.
ORIHIME: But I'm about to
pee my pants, or worse!
-Go on then and come right back.
-Ha, ha!
Bathroom, bathroom,
bathroom, bathroom, bathroom!
-You're not going anywhere.
[keigo gasps]
-Favoritism, favoritism,
favoritism, freedom to pee!
How come Orihime, Chad,
and Ichigo get to go?
I demand a [inaudible].
[tatsuki sighs]
-Beef, pork!
[hollow cackles]
-The Hollows are still around.
I can't believe it.
-Yes, it's true, Orihime.
I fear that hollows will
inhabit this planet for as long
as there are human beings.
-Beef!
-Look, just make up your mind.
Beef, or pork.
-Dinner.
Pork.
-Enjoy your meal.
-Look who's here.
Didn't trust me to take
out a Hollow all by myself,
so you tagged along, huh?
But you two didn't
have to skip class.
-Well, honestly, I've
always had this fantasy
about lying just so that
I could get out of class.
-It's a great quality
to be honest about that.
But try not to overdo it.
-I'm really surprised
that Uryu isn't here.
-There's nothing he could.
Remember, he doesn't have
spiritual pressure anymore.
-It's been two now and he
still hasn't joined us.
-I wouldn't worry about it.
He'll figure something out.
It'll be fine.
He fought like a champ when he
didn't have his powers before.
CHAD: We should believe in Uryu.
ORIHIME: Yeah.
You're right.
-Ichigo Kurosaki.
-My oh my.
We finished our
unpacking finally.
-Well, good for you.
Though I'm surprised
to find out that
you actually had
things to unpack.
-I certainly did.
I received a number
of parting gifts
from Miss Orihime, which
was very kind of her.
-Are you sure she
wasn't just dumping
all the useless garbage she had?
-What a thing to say.
How rude.
Well, you seem to
have made yourself
just as cozy as can be inside
of that stuffed animal suit.
-Hey, why don't you two start
ditching your gegai as well?
It's not so bad once
you get used to it.
-I agree with you.
We're going to be staying
at Urahara's shop,
and it's not going
to cost us a dime.
The least we should
do is try not
to take up space and
cause a lot of trouble.
-What was it that made
you all decide to come
and live here with us?
-We' are Bount sensors.
And now that the
Bounts are gone,
are roles have come to an end.
-Plus, Ichigo and the others
spend their entire day
at school.
Living in secret
every single day
would be too much of a bother.
It's easier if we just
live here instead.
-We can see them
whenever we like.
-Oh, now I understand.
Ah, that hurts!
You're hurting me!
Please stop!
-Why'd you have to ask the
most obvious questions?
Can't you figure it out?
They're modules that
the boss created.
Is it starting to
make sense yet?
They should help out
around here from now on.
-Don't fight.
Let's all try to
get along together.
-Quiet.
I'm trying to read.
MISATO OCHI: Pay
attention, everyone.
The transfer student I told
you about earlier is here.
Why don't you
introduce yourself?
-There's he, as in
the flat footed.
The ko from Imoko Onono,
that old politician.
Tshin and ko as in Kaguro
makes Shinji Hirako.
Very nice to meet you.
-Hey, Shinji.
It's the other way around.
-It's a really good
trick, isn't it?
Backward writing is a very
unusual skill of mine.
MISATO OCHI: So that's
what you were up to.
Now, where will we have you sit?
SHINJI: Oh, Miss Ochi?
MISATO OCHI: What?
SHINJI: I'd like to sit
next to a cute girl.
MISATO OCHI: A cute girl?
-Uryu.
I thought that you would
have recovered by now.
But I guess your
powers won't come back
as easily as I imagined.
MISATO OCHI: I think
better have you sit there.
-OK.
Looks like you and I
going to be neighbors.
Yeah.
I hope we can be
friends, Ichigo.
-Oh, yeah.
Yeah, sure thing.
[shinji chuckles]
-No, I don't want to
live like this anymore.
I want to go out and meet
girls with bodacious bodies.
A cute little guy like me
would be a chick magnet.
But I'm stuck inside.
-You'd look even better
with a sock in your mouth.
Be quiet, or everyone in the
whole house will hear you.
-You're just jealous
because you're not cuddly.
One way or the other, this party
animal is getting out of here.
This town better lock
up all the ladies,
and this lion ain't lying.
To be perfectly frank, if I
may, you're a pain in the butt.
I miss being in your body.
All that peeping in
windows and under skirts
didn't ruin my reputation.
It only ruined yours.
-Dammit, Kon.
That had better be a joke.
Don't tell me that you were
doing something illegal
out there.
-Being locked up was bearable
when Rukia was around.
Oh, Rukia, please come back.
Please come back!
Come back!
-Quiet, Kon!
I'm tired of hearing
you complain!
[medallion buzzes]
-Oh, that's just great.
He goes.
I always worry
what kind of shape
my body will be in
when I get back.
Try not to get my body arrested.
And behave.
-Goodbye.
Take your time.
Ah, it's been awhile since
I've been inside this body.
It's time to go out, get
down, get funky, and par-tay.
[hollow howls]
-Looks like Halloween
must have come early.
Those damn things.
They just keep getting
uglier all the time.
-Hey, wait!
Why are you dressed
up like a Soul Reaper?
I see you.
What are you up to?
-Who the hell are you?
-What?
Who am I?
I'm Zennosuke Kurumadani.
Miss Rukia Kuchiki had a
little trouble with the law,
so an elite Soul Reaper was
left in charge of the area.
So tell me, are you shaking yet?
-I'm Ichigo Kurosaki,
substitute Soul Reaper.
Look, this is my pass.
-Combat pass?
No way.
Ha ha ha ha, that's funny.
A combat pass?
Give me a break, kid.
Who do you think you're
fooling with that thing?
-What's with this?
This damn thing is
completely useless.
-Come on, say something.
If you want to apologize,
now's your chance.
[shinji chuckles]
[zennosuke gasps]
-Dammit.
Hirako.
Is that a zanpakuto?
Who the hell are you?
-Shh.
You mustn't make too much
noise, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Those who have spiritual
pressure like you possess
need to learn how to stay calm.
Or your presence will be felt.
-Felt by who?
Who will feel it?
-It seems I need everything
to be out in open
for you to understand it.
Children are so
foolish and blind.
-That was weird.
What a strange sound.
I thought that Ichigo found
me for a second there.
It's a perfect night
to get into trouble.
Better lock up the ladies,
because here I come.
I'm a party animal!
I won't get Ichigo's
body arrested,
but I do plan to wear it out.
-Ichigo Kurosaki.
-It's a hollow.
It's huge.
I wonder if that could
be a Menos Grande.
It tore open the sky
and came through.
-What the hell?
What was that about?
Something almost blasted me
right out of Ichigo's body.
What?
-I hope you haven't forgotten
me, Ichigo Kurosaki.
-No, no it couldn't be.
It's Grand Fisher!
-This spiritual pressure,
it's so powerful.
What is it?
Those guys are
monsters, both of them.
-It's here.
-Who the hell are you?
Hirako, answer me!
-I explained it.
You're the one to blame.
It's all because
you were releasing
your spiritual pressure.
-I demand that you
tell me who you are.
-You're a pain, you know that?
With all that's going on,
you only care who I am?
Then take a good look.
What do you see?
Tell me.
Try and guess, if you can.
-A Hollow mask.
-Yes.
A zanpakuto and a Hollow mask.
You get it now?
I'm a soul reaper
who crossed over
into the realm of the Hollows.
You remember what
I told you, right?
I hope we can be friend, Ichigo.
-Oh, yeah.
-You see, I'm a Visored.
You're one of us, Ichigo.
You do not belong with them.
You have got to know that you
do not along with them at all.
-What incredible
spiritual pressure he has.
Is he really a Menos Grande?
Well, it doesn't
matter in the end.
I can still fight, even with
my diminished spiritual energy.
I am not helpless.
Take this! [inaudible] I filled
those ginto with spirit energy
when I was in the Soul Society.
They may not be
enough to kill him.
But maybe I'll be able
to discourage him.
Instant regeneration.
His upper body disappeared.
It split in two.
No, there were two of them.
[uryu gasps in pain]
[hollow roars]
-My, my.
How clumsy.
Uryu.
-So it's you.
Ryuken.
-Is that any way to
address your father?
You haven't changed
at all, have you, son?
[MUSIC -- MAI HOSHIMURA, "CHERRY
BLOSSOM WEATHER"]
-I didn't know that Uryu's
father was a Quincy.
-Does that mean his father
wears those goofy clothes, too?
-Of course.
Those clothes are the
traditional Quincy attire.
-You and your father
are both Quincys?
That's awful.
-Don't be such a hypocrite.
What?
-It's a secret.
[MUSIC -- MAI HOSHIMURA, "CHERRY
BLOSSOM WEATHER"]
-Glad you saw me first!
-Hello?
What in the world is
going on in this town?
Some of the weirdest people
I've ever known live here.
And there are people
who can see me.
Even a substitute
soul reaper showed up!
-I'm sorry.
Due to the disruption
in the Zerrete,
we were delayed
in informing you.
-What do you mean, delayed?
-Uh, continue to focus
on the lesser Hollows.
-What Hollows?
-And stay out the way of
the substitute Soul Reaper.
-I used to be a
somebody in this town.