We found out
we weren't strong...
Nor were we weak...
There was no
hatred....
No anger...
Only...
[sob]
"Bankai," huh?
I'm certainly hoping that
isn't your way of serving
notice that your Spirit Energy
has fully returned to you...
Maybe, Wanna
find out?
Why don't you
guys wait right
here.
[gasp]
But, Ichigo...
[grunt]
I'll finish this
right now!
I wouldn't go
pushing your
luck with a
makeshift Bankai.
That could
prove fatal.
[fighting grunts]
[screaming]
[attack grunts]
[fighting grunts]
Ichigo!
Ahhh, damnit!
No, Kon!
Don't!
Huh!? What do you
mean, "don't!"
We can't just
stand by and watch!
Kon...
At a time like this we
can't stand still! We
should fight together!
How much rest do
all of your guys
need!? Get your
asses up!
[chuckle]
You don't know
when to shut up,
do you?
Well?! Let's
go!
Wait!
Oh what!?
If we're going to
fight together...
Let's give it
everything we've
got!
[grunt]
[attack shout]
What are
you doin!?
Somenomai,
Tsukishiro!
You refuse
to learn!
Stop interfering!
You're the one
who keeps butting
in here!!-- Whoa!
[grunt]
[shouts]
El Directo!
[grunt]
Hado Number Seventy-
Three! Soren Sokatsui!
[gasp]
[struggling grunts]
[attack roar]
[gasp]
Getsuga....
....tensho!!!
[struggling shouts]
He can't absorb
Ichigo's Getsuga...
I knew it!
Kageroza isn't
able to control
Hollow powers!
[panting]
He's stronger?!
You must be wondering
why my Getsugatensho
is more powerful now
than it was before...
I was really afraid
somewhere in the back
of my mind, of losing
all my Spirit Energy.
But something
came to me once
I lost my powers.
And what
was that?
I can't stand
the thought of
not giving this
my best shot!
I'll use everything
I've got to defeat you!
I have to admit that
compared to the last
time we fought, you
are different.
However...
[gasp in pain]
You still
can' beat
me...
He's controlling
space again.
At this rate,
we'll never be
able to save
Nozomi.
We have to find a
way to neutralize
him somehow...
But he doesn't
seem to have any
weaknesses so far.
Go for his
vital point.
If we can
shatter his Soul
Chain, we have
a chance!
Makes sense.
If we stop the flow of
Spirit Energy in his body,
there's a chance he'll split
back into 2 entitled again.
Hold on...
The Soul
Chain, huh!?
Kon?
You're not...
I will let
Ichigo know!
[gasp]
[weak gasps]
Is this the best
you can do with the
help of your so-
called friends!?
Or has your
Spirit Energy
completely
run out!?
As long as I
save Nozomi, and
protect all of
my friends...
Nothing that happens
after that matters!
In that case,
I'll end this
quickly for you!
The charm!!
[gasp]
[grunt]
[attack grunt]
Ahh!
Finally...
I've waited
for this...
What?!
[gasp]
[big attack yell]
Let go of me!
[gasp] Damn
you!!!
Take this!
[frightened yell]
Go!!!!
Getsuga...Tensho!!!
[frightened shouts]
[bracing grunts]
[screaming]
[panting]
[grunt]...Did
he get him?
[panting breaths]
Damn you...
You bastard...
We aren't
through yet...
[gasp]
Don't move!
What the hell!?
What's happening
to my body?
[agonizing shouts]
My head!!
[panting in pain]
[labored breaths]
Ichigo...
Nozomi!?
[exhausted breaths]
Finish us! Now!
[gasp]
Please! This is
our only chance
to do it!
[gasp]
Ichigo! The
Soul Chain!
(Kon)
Shatter his
Soul Chain!
[determined grunt]
[attack shout]
Do it!! Ichig--
What!?
I... haven't
given up... yet!
Sop fighting this
pointless battle!
You've lost,
Kageroza!
So you think...
that I've lost
Huh!?
So this is pointless?
I'll show you you're
dead wrong!
[gasp]
If I'm going to
lose this body...
then I will
destroy everything!
Renzan... Hajokuri!
[gasp] What's
this!?
[big attack yell]
[grunt]
Hey! What the
hell is that!?
I don't know!
What the hell?
What is that?
Spirit Energy?
Unbelievable...
He still had
this much power
left!?
No, wait. That
Spirit Energy is
the reishi of the
Soul Society itself!
(Uryu)
And it looks like
he's absorbing it..
I've never seen
this before!
We can't handle
that! It's too
much Spirit Energy!
This was never
part of the plan!
[gasps]
[laughter] Finally!
Things are getting
interesting!
Damn!
From what I see, it
certainly appears that
you Reigai weren't
expecting this either.
That Spirit
Energy is
really insane!
So much force with
just a single blast...
This can't be good.
You're right, and
it keeps growing
bigger and bigger.
(Shunsui)
I think we're
in trouble...
Damn! We have
got to act
fast here!
Ohhh boy.
Danku!
(Shunsui)
Old Man Yama..!
Every scheme of Kageroza
Inaba's, or should I
call him Ouko Yuskima
instead...
...has been spurred
by a vengeance against
the Soul Society
His intention is
clear. He means to
destroy the Soul
Society.
[charging shout]
Damn!
How unexpected! Never
in my wildest dreams
did I think the end
would be like this!
Well, then so
be it!
Now join me, Ichigo
Kurosaki, in the
place between chaos
and nothingness!
(Kageroza)
[evil laughter]
It just keeps
on growing!
Now it's up to
us to stop it!
(Sajin Reigai)
Wait!
[gasps]
Those Reigai...!
Why are you
here?
Are you gathering
to go for an
all-out attack?
No. That's
not it.
Do you remember
what I said to
you, Master
Genryusai?
Certainly to you originals,
what we're doing might seem
like a selfish rebellion by
mere pretenders...
But still, we Reigai
have our own way of
pursuing our beliefs!
(Captain Yamamoto)
And what is that!?
We cannot tell
you that just
yet...
Now we will
demonstrate to
you what I meant.
Explain.
You have told us that
what you protect is very
clear to you, and it is
the same as well for us.
We will protect the
Soul Society in our
own way.
We accept our duty
as Mod Souls to stop
a fellow Mod Soul
who's lost control.
Let's go!
What!?
Impudent children...
[charging yells]
Ha ha ha ha!
[attack yell]
Damnit them! You're
not stopping me!
[attack yell]
[gasp in pain]
Not again!
[painful screams]
You've done
enough!
What are you
doing!? Nozomi!?
Stop it!!
We must end
all this!
Nozomi! What
are you doing?!
[screaming]
[gasp] They
did it!
They were Reigai,
but they had the
pride of true Soul
Reapers.
Ow ow ow ow ow!
Is everyone okay!?
Yeah... just
barely...
(Thinking)
Ichigo...
[panting breaths]
I guess your big
invading army plan
didn't work out the way
you thought it would.
Now it's time
to save Nozomi!
I don't understand!
Why is it I can't
defeat you!?
Why do you refuse
to give up!? Why
can you keep on
fighting?!
What makes you
so driven!?
[gasp]
[scoff]
You damn bastard!
You have something
to protect!
You have friends to
be there for..! To
shield! To support!
People you
care for!
(Thinking)
Only the truly weak
seek out the aid and
comfort of others.
So why then!?
Why are you
so strong!?
[attack shout]
[attack yell]
(Nozomi)
We found out
we weren't strong.
(Nozomi)
Nor were we
weak...
(Nozomi)
There was no
hatred...
No anger...
(Nozomi)
Only that all this
time, we were just
...alone.
Nozomi...
Were we mistaken..?
Misguided by our
beliefs..?
I don't know.
I see.
Hm.
[gasp]
(Kon)
Nozomi!
Are you alright!?
Kon... Yes.
I'm alright.
Oh! Your...
Oh, you mean
this thing?
It's no big
deal really.
[gasp]
(Kon)
Well! So everything's
good now, right?
Yes. You're
right.
Come on! Let's
go back to the
World of the
Living, Nozomi!
[gasp] Hey!
You're...
Nozomi...
I'm sorry, Ichigo...
(Nozomi)
This was the
only way...
Ichigo! What's
going on here!?
Oh...
(Nozomi)
Kon...
This is as
it should be.
What is that
supposed to mean!?
It sounds like
you're leaving us!
Before he disappeared
I made a promise to
him...
...that this
time, I will
be his friend.
Friend..?
I learned from
you what it
really meant
to have friends.
So I'm going,
because it's
my turn to
teach him.
You're not going!!
You're talking like
you're going to
disappear forever!
Well I won't
let you go!
Thanks for
giving me
this, Kon.
[sigh] I guess
in the end I
couldn't
protect you.
That's not true!
You did protect
me! We were
alone...
...but now
we'll both
be at peace.
(Nozomi)
It's because all of you,
because Ichigo and you
were there for me, Kon.
Yeah! I'm here
for you! I'll
always be here
for you!
So then..?
All this time I
couldn't hear it,
but now I can
hear it...
The voice of my
soul from deep
inside me,
Can you hear
it, Kon?
No, I can't
hear what's
deep inside
of you. But I-
Well, if you let
me put my ear to
your breast I could
try to hear it.
You really are
a pervert, you
know that!?
[sniffling]
Well pardon me
for liking you!
[sob]
Please don't
forget us.
I won't forget.
After all, we'll
always be...
Real friends.
Always and
forever.
(Ichigo)
Hey, I wanna say something
before we head back to
the World of the Living.
(Kon)
Yeah? Go for it.
Let is all out
while you can.
(Ichigo)
Bankai!
Bankai! Bankai! Bankai!
(Kon)
What the hell
was that?
(Ichigo)
I'm stockpiling my call
outs since I won't be able
to do them for a while.