[theme music]
NARRATOR: To prevent Sosuke
Aizen from wiping out
Karakura Town, the Soul
Reapers used four pillars
to relocate the city and its
people to the Soul Society.
Chosen to protect the
pillars were Ikkaku Madarame,
Izuru Kira, Yumichika
Ayasegawa, and Shuhei Hisagi.
And the four soon found
themselves locked in combat
with Barragan's Fracciones.
The battle between Charlotte
Chuhlhourne and Yumichika
escalated into a
contest of beauty.
Yumichika struggled against
Chuhlhourne Resurreccion form,
Raina de Rosas, but
emerged victorious by using
Ruri'iro Kujaku, his
Zanpakuto's true form.
At the same time,
Izuru faced off
against Abirama Redder in
Resurrection form, Aguila,
and was forced on the defensive
by his enemy's Devorar Pluma
attack.
Biding his time
though, Izuru waited
for his foe to
come within range.
Using the power of his
Wabisuke to make Aguila's steel
wings many times
heavier, he finally
brought Abirama to the ground.
[crash]
-What's wrong?
Get your legs crushed?
Was I too fast for you?
Heh.
Pathetic!
I wasn't even going
at my full speed.
-I should thank you.
-What?
-Your long-range attacks
were pretty tough to handle.
In fact, this whole
time I've been
trying to figure out how to
draw you into close combat.
You see, my Zanpakuto
only works on objects
connected to my opponent.
[blast]
-What?
No!
Aaaugh!
[blast]
-Nngh.
Damn it!
What is this?
My wings can't move!
-My blade doubles the
weight of anything it hits.
A second strike doubles
the weight again,
and a third doubles
it once more.
Now you felt the power
of my Zanpakuto Wabisuke.
[grunting]
-I believe you
asked what exactly
this weird-looking sword of mine
could cut, isn't that right?
-Nnngh!
Wait.
Please, don't.
-A true warrior would never
beg someone for his life.
[slash]
[kring]
[clink]
-I don't get it.
-Don't get what?
-Earlier, I thought
you told me you
were going to battle with all
the power of a lieutenant,
but right now I'd
peg your strength
at the level of a
Fifth Seat, if that.
So, what's really going on?
-Hmph.
Exacta!
You got it.
-Hmm?
I got what?
-As you just said, my
current power level
is exactly that of one
of your Fifth Seats.
It pleases me that
you guessed correctly,
but I should have expected
as much from a lieutenant.
So, you pass.
-What?
-That was a test.
I wanted to see whether or
not you could accurately
gauge my power level.
Because otherwise, what would
be the point of engaging you
at a more potent
lieutenant level?
It's a waste if you can't
tell the difference.
I was at a Fifth
Seat's level, but now--
[kring]
-Nnngh.
[clang]
-Did his attack
just get stronger?
-Now I'm at a Fourth Seat.
[kring]
-Third Seat!
-Stop playing!
-We're almost at the same level.
Get ready.
[kring]
-'Cause now I'm at lieutenant!
[blast]
-Wel, can you feel it?
This is a lieutenant's
spiritual pressure.
[thudding]
-This is a lieutenant's power!
[slashing]
-And this, my friend,
is a lieutenant's blade.
[slash]
-Aaaugh!
-Heh.
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on!
[laughing maniacally]
What's the matter?
[laughing] Come on, come on!
Hyah!
[thump]
-Nnngh.
[thud]
-Hmph.
[whoosh]
[thud]
[roars]
[kring]
[whoosh]
[slashing]
[laughing]
Huh.
-It's useless.
[thunking]
-Wonder how long you'll last.
[thunk]
[yelps]
-[laughing] You like?
Those were Ceros and Balas.
They use lieutenant-level
spirit energy.
[labored breathing]
-So, tell me, Lieutenant.
How are you holding up there?
-Teh. [breathing heavily]
-You're looking a little tired,
If you don't mind my saying.
[thud]
-Don't you think it's about
time you got serious here,
Lieutenant?
[thud]
-Aaaugh!
-This is the speed
you should possess.
Look at you.
You're exhausted.
You sure you're going
to be OK, Lieutenant?
In a battle between
equals, you wouldn't
expect one man to
be so worn out.
[roars]
-Aaaugh!
[thudding]
[labored breathing]
-It's interesting.
What could this mean, I wonder?
You're fighting an
opponent whose abilities
are at the level of a
lieutenant's, and yet,
for some reason, you're
the only one who's lagging.
Would you care to warrant
a guess as to why?
-Man, you're a pain.
What are you trying to say?
That I don't have what
it takes for the job?
-Exacta!
You don't disappoint,
Lieutenant.
Provided I haven't misjudged
the strength of you
and your Court Guard
Squad, then you're correct.
That's precisely what
I was getting at.
-You can quit calling
me Lieutenant, already.
It's Shuhei Hisagi.
I told you that at the start.
-I beg your pardon.
Guess it slipped my mind.
Really, where are my manners?
I should have introduced myself.
Allow me to do so now.
You may call me Findorr Calius.
I am one of Lord
Barragan's Fracciones.
[spanish guitar music]
-Hmph.
Anyway, now that I've
complied with etiquette,
it's time I put an
end to this battle.
In the very manner you're
most accustomed to dealing in.
In other words,
this dance will end
with me slicing you into
ribbons, Shuhei Hisagi!
Cough Upon the Water.
[blast]
-Pinza Aguda.
-So that get-up's an
Arrancar Resurreccion, huh?
-Exacta!
Right again.
You're a sharp one.
-If you think you
guys are the only ones
who've done your homework,
then you're sorely mistaken.
-Oh, trust me.
We weren't fool enough
to believe that.
[laughing]
[thud]
-Exacta!
You evaded my Sonido perfectly.
-Save your critiques for
someone who gives a damn.
-It seems you have a decent
bit of fight left in you.
[crash]
[kring]
-To life is to face
one difficult dilemma
after another.
The ones who
survive are the ones
who come up with answers
in this sea of adversity.
It's only logical,
therefore, that we all
strive to possess as
many answers as possible.
Am I wrong?
-So, you've got all
the answers and you're
going to shove them
down my throat, huh?
Talk is cheap!
[clink]
-Aaugh!
-Bakudo Number 62, Hyapporankan!
[slashing]
[thud]
-You're through, loud mouth!
-Don't underestimate
me, Soul Reaper!
[laughing]
-Huh?
[blast]
-High-pressure water?
-Exacta.
But it's not a good idea to
take your eye off your enemy.
No es exacto, wrong move.
Too bad for you, Soul Reaper.
[laughing]
-Nnngh!
-Come now.
You don't think
you're getting away?
[slashing]
-It's all over!
[laughing diabolically]
-Reap.
Kazeshini!
[explosion]
-Huh?
-It's Shuhei.
Finally.
-Huh.
-I see.
So that is your Zanpakuto,
is it, Shuhei Hisaki?
-Yeah.
This is my Zanpakuto, Kazeshini.
Although, to be quite honest,
I'm not too fond of it.
-Hmm?
What are you talking about?
-You heard me.
I don't like it.
I mean, it works
at all, but I can't
stand the look of
the damned thing.
[clang]
-Look at the shape of it.
Like it was made
for reaping lives.
[slashing]
[grunting]
[crash]
-Heh. [laughing]
Aaugh!
[kring]
-You're not getting away!
[chains clanking]
-Aaugh!
[thud]
-Hard to predict, huh?
This thing's trajectory, I mean.
You afraid?
-Like hell!
-I see.
Well, I know I am.
-Afraid?
Afraid of what?
Your own colossal
mountain of power?
Hnngh.
Narcissistic drivel!
You're dreaming if you
believe that, Soul Reaper!
Allow me to wake you
from your slumber.
[laughing] It's over!
With over 90% of my
mask broken away now,
I am just as strong
as a captain.
You haven't a prayer
of winning, Lieutenant!
[clanking]
[gasps]
[thud]
[labored breathing]
-Thing is, any man who
doesn't fear his own strength
or the strength of his
enemy is no man at all.
Wielding a sword--
[thunk]
MALE SPEAKER: Wielding a
sword without fear of it
is to be unworthy of the blade.
-You see, that's
how I was taught.
[gasps]
-Finally afraid, huh?
You're equal with me at last.
-Aaugh!
Take this!
[roars]
Aaugh!
[explosion]
[thump]
-Strong as a captain,
you said, huh?
Sorry, pal.
You weren't even close.
[blast]
-The pillar!
It's coming down.
-It's been leveled?
But by who, though?
[gasps]
Ikkaku!
-Huh?
Ikkaku's down!
-Then he was defeated?
[thudding]
[music in japanese]
-Ikkaku was defeated?
He needs our help now!
-Leave it to me!
This whole arc was made for us
underprivileged lieutenants,
anyway.
We never get screen time.
-Fine by me.
Tetsuzaemon, you
shouldn't call yourself
underprivileged lieutenants.
And Shuhei, don't egg him on.