[theme music]
-Huh?
-Captain?
-The captain's back.
-What happened to you, Captain?
-Are you all right, sir?
-Yes, I'm fine.
I brought down the Bount.
The area's still frozen
over from my Zanpakuto,
but it will melt soon enough.
I want you to go there
and retrieve the Bount.
-Wait.
He's dead, isn't he?
-Of course.
Whatever remains
of the Bount's body
will need to be
handled properly.
We will need to give
it some sort of burial.
-Right.
-Has the lieutenant returned?
-Yes sir.
Lieutenant Matusmoto and
Squad 6 Lieutenant Abarai
are inside, supervising
the medical treatment
for all the injured.
And there's one thing.
HITSUGAYA: What's that?
-The substitute Soul
Reaper is inside too.
-What?
-Captain.
Welcome back.
Is the Bount--
-He's dead.
-Hey there Toshiro.
It's good to see you again.
-How many times do
I have to say it?
You are only to address
me as Captain Hitsugaya.
-What's the big deal?
Why does it matter?
-Why does it matter?
And what are you all
doing here anyway?
-Well, we were chasing
Kariya through the Seireitei
and then we just happened
to run into Rangiku.
-That's right.
And it was perfect timing
because Uryu was badly hurt,
so we needed a
place to train him.
-Yes.
As you may or may not know,
we don't have a home base
here in the Seireitei, so
it was quite the stroke
of good luck to all
of those concerned.
-Sorry to come
uninvited like this.
-So, that's the whole story.
I know it's kind of
a hassle, but you
could put us up
for a while, right?
-I suppose.
-Uryu?
-It's-- it's not that bad.
-Are you sure?
-I was the one who brought the
Bounts here in the first place.
Any injuries I sustain are
completely my responsibility.
-Hm.
Orihime knows how to
treat this kind of wound.
-That's a problem.
Orihime is still outside the
Seireitei, as far as we know.
-The battles with the Bounts
left injured men scattered
across the Seireitei, so Squad
4 is stretched pretty thin
at the moment.
But I put the word
out already, so relief
should be here before too long.
-You'll be all right.
Your injuries aren't
life threatening,
but you won't be
fighting for a while.
-That won't work.
I came to fight, and that's
what I'm going to do.
-Easy now.
We received confirmation
that Sui-Fend and Kurotsuchi
defeated the Bounts
they encountered.
If our intelligence
is correct, that
means the only Bount
left now is Kariya.
-I don't know how
you did it, Captain.
That metallic Doll gave
us so much trouble,
and you faced it down and
finished it off just like that.
-It wasn't that simple.
Also, there was something
very unusual about that Bount
and his style of fighting.
He didn't use full
strength in his attacks
against the other squad members.
Do you know what
happened with Kariya?
-Something strange.
He seems to have some kind
of new power all of a sudden.
-I think he called
it the Jokai Crest.
-He claimed that the crest
would give him the power
to destroy the entire Seireitei.
-Even the Bount that I
fought said something
about wanting to stop Kariya.
-If only we had stopped
him from getting this far.
-Well, there's no use
worrying about that now.
-Do we know anything about
what happened to Ichinose?
-The unofficial report is that
Captain Zaraki killed him.
[footsteps]
-Huh?
-Ichigo, Uryu, everyone,
are you all right?
-You can't just
barge in like that.
Orihime.
Izuri.
-I finished treating Jidanbo's
injuries and he seemed stable,
so I decided to come find you.
I saw Izuru there guarding
the gate along with Squad 3,
and I asked him if he
knew where to find you.
-Fortunately I knew
just where to find you.
-Thanks for bringing her.
-Will you see what you can
do about Uryu's injuries?
-Of course.
-Orihime.
Listen.
I don't need to heal completely.
Just enough to fight
again as soon as possible.
RANGIKU: Forget about it.
What do you mean?
-Haven't you been listening?
Look, I know you're
anxious, but think about it.
-Yeah, she's right.
-Rest.
And recovery are both essential
elements of battle, too.
Most of our forces have been
on the move since last night.
So if something
important were to happen,
we'd be sure to get
word of it immediately.
-OK, so just take it easy.
-Until you get some rest,
you won't be any good to us.
-So there's no need to panic.
-Izuru, who's
available for action?
IZURU: The only full
squad is Squad 11, sir.
Since they are temporarily
without their captain,
they didn't receive
any deployment orders.
-And since they weren't involved
in any of the day's battles,
they should still
be at full strength.
-That's right.
Because of Kenpachi, I
never did relay any orders
over to Squad 11.
-Damn.
I was really looking
forward to getting
in on some of the action.
But the odds aren't very good
now that there's only one
of them left.
-And I was hoping to get
some payback for what
they did to me back in
the world of the living.
-Seems like our captain
just abandoned us
so he could go fight on his own.
-Word is he fought with a former
Soul Reaper named Ichinose,
who was helping the Bounts.
By now he's probably sightseeing
there in the Rukon District.
-Ichinose.
I owe that guy a
little payback, too.
That bastard!
-Well, if it's revenge
against a Bount we want,
there's only one let.
The boss of the Bounts, too.
And I plan to be
the one to find him.
-Sirs, I have a report.
The North Rukon
District has been
declared completely secure.
No enemy activity.
-And with the other squads so
exhausted from the fighting,
we get to do whatever we
want to him if we fight him.
So go and find him!
-Head Captain, I have
an urgent message
from Captain Kyoraku of
Squad 8 and Captain Ukitake
of Squad 13.
-I tought Captain Ukitake was
too ill to even get out of bed.
He's in action?
-Yes.
I understand that he went
to the Central Library
in order to gather data
on the Bounts, sir.
-Hm.
Well, in any case, what
is this urgent message
you are referring to?
-Ran'Tao's old research
data has been recovered,
and in it the captains
have found a reference
to an explosive power that
was in fact sealed away
in the Jokai Crest.
-I see.
If the data is
accurate, then it means
that this Bount Kariya
was not lying, after all.
-According to the data, however,
the full power of the Jokai
Crest cannot be drawn
out immediately.
A short period of
time must elapse
after the Jokai
Crest is activated.
-And just how much
time do we have?
-About one day.
-Evidently, that
is what this Kariya
meant when he said
that everything
would be decided
in a single day.
-Yes.
-Hm.
Obviously there is no tactic too
low for this man to stoop to.
We dare not let down
our guard against him.
Kariya must be taken into
custody before this day ends.
I will send directives
to all the 13 Court Guard
Squads at once.
There will be no time
for a captain's meeting.
-Yes, sir.
-Tell Captains
Ukitake and Kyoraku
to continue
investigating the data.
-I understand, Head Captain.
[chatter]
-Captain Sui-Feng's
recovery has been
going much slower
than expected so she's
on reserve status
in her quarters.
-I see.
-Captain Kurotschi's
readiness to return to battle
is also listed as
questionable for now.
-Captains Kyoraku and Ukitake
have secluded themselves
in the Central Library to
gather further information.
-And Captain Komamura?
-Assigned to guard Head
Captain Yamamoto, sir.
-All right.
I understand the situation.
Excellent work, Isane.
-Thank you, sir.
My please.
-Isane!
-Rangiku!
RANGIKU: You have to come
and taste my cooking.
ISANE: But I'm still on duty.
RANGIKU: Are you saying
you don't like my cooking?
ISANE: No, but--
RANGIKU: Here.
Taste.
[wretching]
-Who's there?
-I know you.
Ran'Tao.
[cocking]
-A gun that fires Kido?
How did you find me?
A Bount sensor?
-Yes.
In fact, there isn't anyone
who knows more about the Bounts
than I do.
-Why haven't you
given that information
to the Soul Reapers?
-It's simple.
Because I intend to settle this
whole sorry affair by myself.
-Interesting weapon
you have there.
I'll admit that it does
pack quite a punch,
but I'm afraid it still won't
be enough to bring me down.
What's the matter?
-Those markings.
Impossible.
After the konpaku
experiment failed,
we were sent to the
world of the living.
Just before we
arrived, we had heard
reports of a large
number of humans
possessing strange powers.
They were the first Bounts.
The Bounts were confused
about their strength,
yet they were still trying to
live among the normal humans.
But due to their powers, human
tolerance towards the Bounts
waned.
And finally, they
were persecuted.
I tried getting
close to the Bounts,
hoping that I might
be able to save them.
I admit I felt
responsible somehow.
After all, they were
just innocent victims
of our experiments.
I am your friend.
I promise, you have
no reason to fear me.
I managed to round
up all the Bounts,
and I advised them to
hide and stay together.
I'm going to return
to the Soul Society.
There I'll make
arrangements to place you
all under their protection.
You will soon be safe.
-Can this be done?
-Yes.
Though as you can imagine,
it will not be an easy task.
Understand that it will
probably take a number of years
before the complete protection
of the Bounts is a reality.
-We understand.
Until you return,
we will wait here.
But something totally
unexpected awaited me
when I returned to
the Soul Society.
While I was gone,
central 46 had decided
that everything regarding
the konpaku experiments,
including their byproduct,
the Bounts themselves,
would be buried in secrecy.
Why are you doing this?
How can you turn your
backs on the Bounts?
-We freely acknowledged
that the konpaku experiments
were inhumane.
-If you believe that, why won't
you do anything to help them?
Don't you know they
possess incredible power?
But If we ignore them,
they may even one day
become a danger to
the Soul Society.
-We have nothing to fear from
Bounts who cannot control
reishi to pass through the
Dangai Precipice World.
-We have decided
that as a result,
they will never be a
threat to the Soul Society.
However--
-There in the world of the
living, such is not the case.
As you know, it is
our duty to regulate
the balance of konpaku.
We believe the Bounts may pose
a threat to that equilibrium.
-Are you saying that the Bounts
will be-- you can't mean it!
How can you make such a
fateful decision so lightly?
-We do not take it
lightly, I assure you.
We are aware that
we will have to live
with the burden of our
mistake, and strive never
to make such an error again.
-I cannot allow them to do this.
I cannot turn my
back on the Bounts.
-Seize them all, men.
Kill any who resist.
-Yah!
RAN'TAO: Without permission,
I hurried back to the world
of the living to try
and save the Bounts.
[scream]
-Thanks.
But there are others
further inside.
-I understand.
I'll see what I can do.
Now just go and save yourself.
-Thank you, Ran'Tao.
-This one's dead.
-There's one over here!
-Try not to move.
-Help me move this.
He's very bad.
MAN: Hey, give me a hand.
MAN: This one's still alive!
MAN: Another one over here.
MAN: I need two guys over here.
[whimpering]
-Hey.
Who's there?
-Hey, what's this?
-I recognize you.
You're Ran'Tao.
-That's right.
-Yeah, that's her.
From the Bount
Investigation Unit.
-But that unit was
sent home weeks ago.
Why are you still here?
Huh?
Hey!
She's trying to get away!
Come on!
Ran'Tao is a traitor!
Capture her, men!
-I'm going to stay here and try
to keep them busy for a while.
I want you to go on
ahead without me, OK?
-Huh?
-You can do it.
The other Bounts are
waiting for you outside.
I want you to escape
with your friends.
-But then they'll get you.
-Don't worry.
I'll be just fine.
Take this amulet.
The Bounts have a great
deal of power within them.
This will help draw
out that power.
I'm sorry, little one.
You be forced to
endure much suffering,
but I believe one day
you will rise again.
And to see that
day, you must live.
MAN: Over here!
MAN: I found one!
RAN'TAO: Now, run
up those stairs!
Get away from here!
MAN: Come on!
Get them!
-I was captioned and taken
back to the Soul Society.
The Seireitei held
me solely responsible
and buried the entire
case in secrecy.
Eventually, the
surviving Bounts took
advantage of the powers hidden
in the amulet I left the boy,
and perfected the method
of controlling Dolls.
With their newfound
power, the Bounts
plotted revenge and repeatedly
attacked the Soul Society.
However, they were defeated
each time by the Soul Reapers.
And over time, their numbers
dwindled to almost nothing.
Then even the record
of their existence
was erased from the Seireitei.
[screaming]
-But I never forgot
about the Bounts.
And then came the day when you
arrived in the Soul Society.
You are that same boy.
Don't you remember?
How you got that
mark on your body?
That mark could
only have appeared
as a result of the
activation of a certain item.
And you must
remember, the person
who gave you that item was me.
I have lived only to save you.
There is not a
single Soul Reaper
remaining who
remembers the past.
The Soul Society has changed.
Finally, I can save the Bounts.
-You bring that up now?
RAN'TAO: It's the truth!
But if you use the
power of the Jokai
Crest that was sealed away
here in the Seireitei--
-The power of the Jokai Crest?
I absorbed that energy
into my body long ago.
-Impossible!
-Now I shall use that power
to destroy the Soul Reapers.
-What?
[snoring]
-This spiritual pressure.
It's Ran'Tao.
Is she in a battle?
The only Bount left is Kariya.
That means whatever she
is, Kariya is there, too.
-No matter what
you are planning,
you are too late
to save the Bounts.
In case you hadn't noticed,
I'm the only Bount remaining.
-Even if you're the last
one, I can still save you.
-You idiot.
You're the one who created
the Bounts in the first place.
I had intended to deal
with you after you
had seen the Seireitei
destroyed, and felt
some of the pain you caused.
But I think it'll kill
you right here and now.
[gasp]
[theme music]
ORIHIME: Uryu just disappeared!
CHAD: Let's go find him.
KURODO: But you never know when
a Quincy's arrow might explode!
RIRIN: Yeah.
What if we find one and
it blows up in our faces?
KURODO: We'll just forget
it and run far away!
CHAD: Good idea.
URYU: Stupidity just flows right
out of your mouths, doesn't it?
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers.
ISANE: I'm hungry.
-It's Squad 10's famous
special dish, everyone.
Hot and fresh, right in the pot.
So come and get it.
-Yay!
-And not only that, but I
made lots of side dishes
with bean paste, just as
you requested, Orihime.
-You're the best, Rangiku.
-Ugh.
-Hey, don't just
add there, you guys.
Step up and serve yourselves.
-Is Shuhei the waiter?
-He wasn't doing anything
and he has no sense of smell,
so I asked him to help me.
-Hi-yah!
-I wish I had no sense
of smell right about now.