[music playing]
As the only surviving heir
of the noble Kasumioji clan,
Princess Rurichiyo had
become a target for trouble
in her homeland.
For her own protection,
her guardians
took the unsuspecting princess
to the world of the living,
where Ichigo reluctantly agreed
to become her body guard.
Rurichiyo quickly
turned Ichigo's
upside down with her
spoiled behavior.
Elsewhere in the Soul
Society, Shusuke Amagai
became the new
Captain of Squad Three
and has been sending his
men on unusual new missions.
-There!
He's over there!
-Get him!
-I don't see anyone
coming this--
-Over there!
-Let's go!
-Follow him!
-Come here!
-Maybe over here.
-Yeah.
-Ugh.
-Where'd he go?
-You see him?
-That way!
-I think I saw him over here.
-Hurry up now!
-No, over here!
-Don't lose him!
-Come back that way.
-This way?
-Where'd he go?
-Oh.
-I don't know.
-I don't see anyone.
-Like a ghost.
[footsteps]
[guitar-heavy music]
-That's right.
Hold still now.
-Nnngh!
[meows]
-It's all over.
[sighs]
-Third Seat Kibune!
Very well done!
-Sorry, Lieutenant Kira.
I guess you weren't fast enough.
-Lieutenant, care to confirm?
-Oh, OK.
[ding]
[meow]
-No doubt about it.
This is the cat.
-Well then, mission complete.
-Hey, uh, why are we chasing
after some nobleman's cat,
anyway?
-And yesterday, doing security
for some clothing store sale?
Lately all our work's
been like this.
-Well, I'm sure our
captain must have
reasons for giving
these assignments.
Lieutenant Kira,
what do you think?
-Huh?
Uh.
That's a-- good question.
-Well, I, for one, prefer going
on more important missions.
-I hear you.
That aside, what you
say we go for a drink?
-Now you're talking!
-Count me in, too.
-Care to join us,
Lieutenant Kira?
-Hmm?
I can't.
I, uh, should write
up the report.
[rapping on door]
-Excuse me.
-Well, welcome back, Izuru.
-Huh?
-You OK?
-I'm fine.
It's just-- I was a bit
startled to hear my first name.
-Yes, well, I thought it
would help the Squad feel more
comfortable with me if I started
using first names around here.
Do you approve?
-Huh?
Oh, I'm just not used to it.
-Ah.
Yeah, I see.
I thought it was a decent
idea, but I guess not.
Oh well, back to
the drawing board.
-Here's today's report.
And sir?
-Hmm?
-About the mission for tomorrow.
What's this about repairing the
walls at the Squad 12 barracks?
-Just what it sounds like.
You're fixing the walls.
-No, sir.
That's not what I'm getting at.
-What's the purpose
of these orders?
The Squad thinks that I--
-Lieutenant, look.
I know this might be difficult
for you to deal with,
but Squad Three's previous
Captain, Gin Ichimaru,
betrayed these men, understand?
-Mmhmm.
-And the fact is, when
you lose somebody's trust
it's tough to get it back.
I don't know how
things will play out,
but we'll have to work hard to
regain the respect of the Soul
Society.
Don't you worry, OK?
Seeing you like this makes
me realize something.
When he was Captain,
Gin Ichimaru
played too big a
role in this Squad.
-Huh?
-You are a lot
different than he was,
and no one expects you
to act the same way.
A charismatic Captain can
bring a team together.
But once that pillar falls,
the team can as well.
That's why I want to rebuild
this Squad with you and Makoto.
The three of us will be
the pillar of strength
his team needs.
-Hmm.
-Say, where is Makoto now?
-Well, he's drinking
with the others.
After the battle
of the other day,
the men really seemed
to open up to him.
-I say.
All right.
Well, then I think I'll
call it a day, too.
Go enjoy your evening.
You worry too much, you know?
-Huh?
But--
-See ya around.
[door shuts]
-Good evening to you, too, sir.
-Today we'll be learning
a new technique.
Recently we faced a marked
increase in powerful enemies
like the Menos.
Case in point, the Precipice
World incident the other day.
So from now on, you will
learn to work together
with fellow Squad members
in battle, or you'll die.
-Huh?
-What?
-I--
-Well, this training should make
certain that doesn't happen.
Makoto?
-Sir.
-Choose one of these
colored headbands.
When I call out a color,
those wearing that color
will act as the enemy.
The rest of you will then attack
the enemies in groups of three.
Keep in mind the enemy color
will change periodically.
The moment I call out another
color, the roles reverse.
This will refine your
decision-making as a group.
Makoto, go take your
place with the others
and lead the exercise.
-Sir.
-I'll join them, too.
-Hold up.
Stay here, please.
-Huh?
-I devised this
technique back when
we were with the
expedition unit.
Makoto is familiar
with all the tactics.
-Sir--
-Sorry for that.
Now let's go!
ALL: Yes, sir!
-First enemy, purple!
-Aida, stay close by my side.
-Right!
-Inose, rank around to the rear!
-Got it!
-Next group, yellow!
-OK, now red.
-Very good.
Keep up the pressure!
-Amazing!
How could the men become
so organized so quickly?
[water running]
-Captain Amagai's
fighting tactics--
they're unlike anything the
Squad has ever seen before.
-I hear ya.
I don't think Captain
Ichimaru ever used
group training techniques.
-It made me realize just
how much more powerful
our squad can be when we all
work together as a group.
-Yeah.
That Captain Amagai isn't bad.
I like his style.
-Third Seat Kibune, too.
-From what I've
seen so far, he's
much more experienced
than Lieutenant Kira.
-Something tells
me there's going
to be a change in
lieutenants soon.
-You should keep
your voice down.
-Oh. (CLEARING THROAT) Oops.
-Lieutenant Kira.
-Oh, Third-Seat Kibune.
-You OK?
-I know you heard the men.
-Yeah, um, I'm fine.
-Tell the truth.
-(CHUCKLING) I must admit,
you're good, Third Seat Kibune.
-Oh, no.
It's nothing compared to how
you kept Squad Three going
all this time, Lieutenant Kira.
-That's kind of you.
You're the kind
of leader the men
want to follow,
much more than me.
-But you--
-It's the truth and you know it!
Huh?
I'm-- I'm sorry.
Just a bit tired.
Please, excuse me.
[footsteps]
[laughter and conversation]
[playful music]
[gulping]
-Keep 'em coming!
-(LAUGHING) Looks like
you're thirsty tonight!
Here, you can have
a swig of my drink.
[gulping]
-You're really
putting them away.
Say, uh, did something happen?
-Nnngh.
(SLURRING) No, I'm fine.
Squad Three is just going to
be a little different now,
that's all.
It's not going to be this
same Squad Three anymore.
-OK, OK!
Easy.
-When the captain changes, the
whole squad changes with him.
-Huh?
-This must be hard on you.
I get it.
[sighs]
-But thanks to Captain Amagai,
Squad Three's reputation
is on an upswing.
He's done some remarkable things
in a relatively short period.
-I agree.
The Squad is better.
-Then you should hold
your head up high!
Because if you keep
acting like this,
all downtrodden
and miserable, then
that new guy in the
Squad-- what's his name?
That Third Seat fella--
-Third Kibune.
-Yeah, that guy!
Watch out or he'll steal
your title as lieutenant.
Huh?
-I'm OK with that.
May the best man win.
-Give it a rest.
-Oops.
-Uh oh.
Looks like we hit a nerve there.
-Malcolm, party of two?
Right this way.
-Do you have a private room?
-Yes we do, sir.
-Uh.
-Speak of the devil.
-What's he doing
with Captain Kyoraku?
-All right, then.
Bottoms up.
-I'm honored to
have been invited
for a drink with the new
Squad captain everyone's
talking about.
-Well, I'm still
relatively new to the job.
So getting to know the senior
members is quite helpful.
-I see.
So, what is it you
wanted to talk about?
-I'll be straight with you, sir.
-Fine by me.
I'm not a big fan of
beating around the bush.
Well, sir, it's regarding
the 13 Court Guard Squads.
I'd like to find a
way for this Squads
to coordinate more
closely with each other.
-Oh, I see.
That sounds like a
rather ambitious project.
-I don't expect to be able to
meet all my goals right away,
but things can't
remain as they are!
-Easy, no need to get worked up.
-Oh, my apologies.
But I kind of like that idea.
It's not bad.
-So you agree with me then?
-You know, Shisuke,
you're a pretty bright guy
for a youngster.
-Me?
No.
-But listen, as long as you and
I are discussing Squad affairs,
maybe we should get
Jushiro in on this.
-You mean the
captain of Squad 13?
-Yeah.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I won't stand in
your way or anything,
but I'm just not
the type of guy who
likes to take the lead
on this stuff, you know?
So how about next time we
round up Jushiro and hash it
all up together?
-Sir, it would be my pleasure.
-Good.
Then let's kick off this
plan of ours with a toast.
Hold up, you're not drinking?
-No, I can't.
-Come on.
-Oh, uh.
Here goes nothing.
(GULPING)
-(CHUCKLING) Wait, what?
You can't drink?
For real?
Aw man.
[door opening]
-Lieutenant Kira, East
Area Seven is all clear.
-Good work, Third Seat Kibune.
-And all's quiet
in the Inner Court.
-Is that so?
Thank you for the update.
Sir, is something the matter?
-Oh no, nothing.
Everything's fine.
Uh, anyway.
Why don't we have some tea?
-Lieutenant Kira.
-Yes, what is it?
-I know this may
come across as rude,
but why is it that
you never seem
to trust in your own abilities?
-Huh?
I what?
Well, uh.
[jingling]
-An emergency message?
-A strange shadow seen
near the Execution Grounds?
Lieutenant Kira!
-Huh?
[footsteps]
-Lieutenant and Third Seat!
-Uh, and you are?
-I'm Shinta Seiko.
-Sorry I didn't
remember your name.
-That's OK, I'm still
new and I don't even
have seat ranking yet.
-Where was it?
-Over there, near the pit.
I spotted an unusual shadow
so I tried to follow after it.
-Then what?
-Well, sir, it appeared to
vanish down into the hole.
-Into the Execution Grounds?
Nothing could survive
that fall, could it?
[rumbling and cracking]
[screaming]
-We'll hit the bottom!
[thud]
-Lieutenant!
-Third Seat Kibune!
-Are you injured, sir?
-I'll be fine.
-That's good.
But why did the platform
suddenly give way?
-No use trying to climb out.
There has to be
an entrance where
the criminals are brought in.
Let's look for it.
[footsteps]
-Yes.
-Hmm.
Spiritual pressure.
[footsteps]
-Is that-- What's
that thing doing here?
[rumbling]
[roaring]
[slashing]
-There sure a lot of
them, but these Hollows
are all fairly weak.
Get away!
[slashing]
[wailing]
-Now, rampage!
Reppu!
[growling]
[slashing]
[slash]
-Third Seat Kibune!
[screaming]
-This is bad!
If the Hollows make it outside--
[growling]
-What's he doing?
-Raise your head
for a bee sting!
Third Seat Kibune!
What do you think you're doing?
-I'm simply putting
an end to the Hollows.
-And what about Shinta?
That fool.
He failed to carry out his
duties as a Soul Reaper.
He fell into enemy hands and
lies before us in disgrace.
-What?
-He's a Soul Reaper, isn't he?
He should be prepared
to die in battle.
But instead, he has
become a liability
and endangered us all.
He doesn't deserve to live.
-How can you say that?
-Why do you care so much
about a worthless failure?
You're too soft.
-I'm what?
-You have no strength,
no principles.
Your weakness is the very
reason you couldn't prevent
your previous
captain's betrayal.
Isn't that so?
-No, I-- I--
-And from the looks of it, you
have no discipline, either.
[blasting]
-You guys OK down there?
-Captain Amagai, it's you!
-We're all right,
but a Squad member
was attacked by the Hollows
and has been severely injured.
-Stay put.
I'll send the med
crew down there.
-Thank you, sir.
-Hmm.
[crack]
-(GASPING) Captain, what about
the Hollows that escaped?
-Oh yeah.
A few other Squad
members in the area
spotted them and informed us.
Don't worry, we took them out.
-That's good.
Thank you, sir.
-We transported Shinta to
the Squad Four med facility,
but his wounds are deep.
They're not sure
if he'll make it.
-I understand.
-And the platform
that collapsed--
there are signs of foul play.
It appears tampered with.
-Huh?
-Did you notice anything?
Anything unusual?
-Huh.
-If there's something
else, let's hear it.
-Huh?
Well, um.
-No, sir.
Nothing to report.
-You sure?
You two seem odd.
-Idiots!
What on earth were you thinking,
destroying all my Hollow
samples?
-You mean, those hollows
were from Squad 12?
-Yes.
We believe someone unlocked
the testing facility
and freed all of the Hollows.
-But who would do
something that reckless?
-Well, if we knew that, we
wouldn't be standing here!
Nemu, this is what happens
when you don't secure things
carefully, you bumbling moron!
-1,000 apologies, Master Mayuri.
-Ahh!
I'm furious with you!
You, too, Squad Three Captain!
Why didn't you
capture the alive?
My experiments are ruined!
-Now. now, let's just calm down.
[birds chirping]
[door opening]
-What the--
-What is it?
-Huh.
No one here.
-Must be a malfunction.
[door closing]
[giggling]
-Huh?
[music playing]
-Hey, Renji.
Why were you with
Tetsuzaemon today?
-He forced me to join him to
discuss the future of the Men's
Soul Reaper Association.
There's no chance against
the Women's Soul Reaper
Association.
-You're so right.
-It's that defeatist
attitude that's
going to cost us
the whole thing!