[music playing]
[MUSIC - ASIAN KUNG FU
GENERATION, "AFTER DARK"]
NARRATOR: In order
to save Orihime,
who was kidnapped by Sosuke
Aizen, Ichigo and his friends
snuck into Hueco
Mundo and infiltrated
Aizen's fortress,
known as Las Noches.
Upon entering the fortress,
they were engaged in battle
by some of Aizen's
most deadly Arrancars.
At every turn our
heroes found themselves
at a disadvantage, outmaneuvered
and beaten by their opponents.
Ichigo has now begun his
final desperate battle
against the lethal Espada
Grimmjow Jaegerjaquez.
-Grind.
Pantera!
Aaaaaaahhhhh!
[whimpers]
ORIHIME INOUE (VOICEOVER):
It's hard to believe.
Is that really Ichigo?
-Hey, you can do it, Ichigo!
Well, what are you just
standing there for?
You need to cheer him on, too!
-Huh?
-That's the best you can do?
He's out there risking
his life for you
and all you can say is "huh"?
[whimpers]
-Why are you so afraid of him?
You think he's some
kind of monster?
[whimpers]
ORIHIME INOUE
(VOICEOVER): That's right.
The whole reason I
came here was because I
wanted to protect everyone.
I thought I was ready to
make whatever sacrifice.
But then when I heard
that Ichigo and the others
had come to save me,
somewhere deep in my heart
I felt such happiness.
Then I saw Ichigo wearing
a mask and his eyes.
They looked like my
brother's eyes that night.
I was so scared.
I thought that maybe he didn't
come to save me after all.
-Hyah!
Aah!
Hah!
ORIHIME INOUE (VOICEOVER):
But I was wrong.
All of my fears,
they mean nothing.
None of that matters anymore.
[crash]
[panting]
-Please don't die.
-Nngh.
ORIHIME INOUE: (SHOUTING)
Don't die, Ichigo!
You don't have to win.
And you don't have
to fight for me.
Just don't get hurt.
I couldn't bear it.
-Kurosaki!
[boom]
-So Grimmjow, here's the deal.
-Nngh!
-You see, I've had
a change of heart,
and I can't allow myself to
get beaten by someone like you.
-[gasp]
[wind howling]
[whimpers]
[panting]
[breathing jaggedly]
ICHIGO KUROSAKI
(VOICEOVER): It's over.
GRIMMJOW JAEGERJAQUEZ: Nnghh!
You're a fool, Ichigo.
I'm still here.
You think that you've won?
You think you've beaten me?
I'll scatter your
bones in the sand!
-(SHOUTING) Ichigo, look out!
SHAWLONG KOUFANG
(VOICEOVER): There's
no such thing as an
individual Gillian.
Gillians are the
lowest class of Menos.
It's believed that
they are created
when hundreds of
Hollows come together,
but that's not
actually the case.
Hollows consume human souls.
And why is this
necessary, you ask?
They do it to satisfy
a hunger caused
by the emptiness inside them.
But each Hollow is unique.
There are certain Hollows who
are more ravenous than others,
and they begin to crave the
souls of their own kind.
[growling and snarling]
SHAWLONG KOUFANG
(VOICEOVER): Those Hollows
are drawn by a mutual
desire-- the desire
to consume each other.
[growling and snarling]
[snarling yell]
SHAWLONG KOUFANG (VOICEOVER):
Eventually they meld together,
losing all sense
of individuality.
They become Gillians,
massive mindless things
with enormous spirit energy.
[roar]
SHAWLONG KOUFANG
(VOICEOVER): But there
are times when the
personality of one Hollow
transcends the
others in a Gillian
and comes to dominate
the entire creature.
[roar]
[shriek]
[thud]
[roar]
SHAWLONG KOUFANG (VOICEOVER):
It consumes other Gillians
and grows stronger, and
eventually becomes an Adjucha.
[low snarl]
[roar]
[wolf howling in distance]
SHAWLONG KOUFANG (VOICEOVER):
But Adjuchas fall
prey to an even greater fear.
It's the fear of regression.
Unless it continues
to consume Hollows,
an Adjucha will regress
and become a Gillian again.
Those that regress inevitably
lose their individuality
and never again can
become Adjuchas.
DI ROY RINKER: What's this?
You're kind of little
for an Adjucha.
Sorry about this, but
I have to eat you.
[gasp]
[screams]
[roar]
[strangled cry]
No!
You bastard!
-What happened?
He took down Di Roy
like he was nothing!
-I've never seen a
Hollow move that fast.
[chewing noisily]
SHAWLONG KOUFANG: You're strong.
What's your name, Adjucha?
-Grimmjow.
-I'm Shawlong.
-Hm.
-Join us, Grimmjow.
You will not go unrewarded.
-What would be the point?
SHAWLONG KOUFANG: We
do not want to live
our lives as
Gillians or Adjuchas.
One day we will rise
to become Vasto Lordes.
But to do that, we need
power, an immense power that
can guide us.
You are that power.
Come with us.
Let us walk together.
You will become
our king, Grimmjow.
-Unnh!
[panting heavily]
[breathing jaggedly]
[panting]
GRIMMJOW JAEGERJAQUEZ: What?
Those eyes.
They keep mocking me!
No matter how badly I beat
you, somewhere deep inside,
you always think
you can beat me.
You always believe
you're superior to me!
I can't stand that!
Hyyaaaahhh!
Yaaahh!
--[laughs] Just what
is it you can't stand?
Are you upset that a
lowly human like me
would have the nerve to
treat you as an equal?
GRIMMJOW JAEGERJAQUEZ: Haaah!
[gags and retches]
-Huuuuayyyyah!
That has nothing to do with it.
It doesn't matter
to me if you're
a human, a Soul
Reaper, or an Arrancar.
They're all the same.
Anybody that looks down
on me will be crushed!
As for you, Ichigo--
-Nnngh!
-You're gonna be
the first one to go!
[shoom]
-Are you ready?
-What the hell is that?
-Heh.
[sound of shattering glass]
-Desgarron.
It's my ultimate technique.
What did you say?
-I said we're
giving up, Grimmjow.
Do you realize how
much time has passed
since we began
traveling together?
-What difference does it make?
-We now realize that we'll
never become Vasto Lordes.
-Since eating our
1,000th Hollow,
we can no longer feel
our powers increasing.
Today's meal marks number 3,000.
3,000 more won't
make any difference.
-Huh.
You're crazy.
If you want to give up, you're
all free to go die in a ditch
somewhere.
I'm moving on.
-Very well, Grimmjow.
But if that's your
decision, consume us first.
If even a portion of our
bodies is consumed by a Hollow,
our evolution stops.
Di Roy can never become
a Vasto Lorde now.
We know that.
Our evolution ends here.
-You're a bunch of cowards.
-As I said, we've
come to a realization.
There are those who can become
Vasto Lordes and those who
cannot.
Some are not destined to rise
beyond the Adjucha state.
Perhaps it goes even
deeper than that.
We are aware of that now.
From the moment
we became Hollows
we were destined to be Adjuchas.
But you were meant for
something far greater.
Eat us, Grimmjow.
GRIMMJOW JAEGERJAQUEZ:
Aaaaagggghh!
-Nnngh!
Aaaghh!
-[laughs] It's over!
You're finished, Ichigo!
GRIMMJOW JAEGERJAQUEZ
(VOICEOVER): They make me sick.
GRIMMJOW JAEGERJAQUEZ: I'm gonna
wipe that smirk off your face!
GRIMMJOW JAEGERJAQUEZ
(VOICEOVER):
They're all cowards!
Fine.
If that's what you
want, I'll eat you all.
Become my flesh and blood
and see what lies ahead!
I am-- I am the king!
[screams]
[shattering glass]
[glass tinkling]
[whimpers]
ICHIGO KUROSAKI: You
know, I got news for you.
You're not the only
one who wants to win.
-What's that?
-You want to kill me?
Because of how I look at you?
Well, I know how you feel!
As
-Yyyyah!
ICHIGO KUROSAKI: You
were right before when
you said that I came here
because I wanted to fight!
Gyeeeahhhh!
The real reason I came
here was to defeat you!
So I'm going to destroy you!
And Ulquiorra!
I'm going to defeat Aizen!
And then I'm gonna take Rukia!
And Chad!
And Uryu!
And Renji!
I'm going to take Orihime!
-[gasp]
-All of my friends-- and
bring them home safe with me!
I won't lose to you!
[glass tinkling]
--[jagged gasp]
[shudders] Damn you.
-[whimpers] Are-- are you--
ICHIGO KUROSAKI: Hurt?
I was gonna ask you that.
I'm fine.
ORIHIME INOUE (VOICEOVER):
Thank goodness.
He's-- he's my Ichigo again.
ORIHIME INOUE: I'm OK, too.
Thank you.
-(SCREAMING JOYFULLY) Ichigo!
-[gasp] Are you crazy?
I'm standing in mid-air!
You would have fallen
hundreds of feet to your death
if I hadn't caught you!
Did you even think about that?
-Nel's so happy!
(TEARFULLY) Ichigo,
you're alive!
Nel's so happy you didn't die!
[cries softly]
-Thanks, Nel.
I appreciate it.
-It's good to see you.
-We should go.
Everyone's waiting for us.
[giggles]
[music - rsp, "kansha"]
ICHIGO KUROSAKI (VOICEOVER):
All right, I've got Orihime.
Now I'm going to finish the
job and get the Hogyoku.
RUKIA KUCHIKI (VOICEOVER):
What are you doing, Ichigo?
Come on, you're gonna be
late if you don't hurry.
ICHIGO KUROSAKI
(VOICEOVER): Rukia?
Wait-- you're OK?
RUKIA KUCHIKI (VOICEOVER): Huh?
Are you nuts?
Come on, let's go.
We're gonna be late for school.
ICHIGO KUROSAKI
(VOICEOVER): But--