[MUSIC - BEAT CRUSADERS,
"TONIGHT, TONIGHT, TONIGHT"]
URURU: Jinta?
JINTA: What do you want?
There.
You
URURU: Didn't have
boil that much water.
It's not like we're gonna
deliver a baby or anything.
-Yeah?
Well, that shows
how much you know.
'Cause hot water can be
used for all kinds of stuff.
-The method I'm using to heal
them is very unconventional.
It doesn't require a
single drop of hot water.
-Really?
-Boy, I bet you feel
like a big dope.
Ha!
-What did you say, you
obnoxious little stuffed animal?
[shouting]
-Hey, what are you doing?
Just stop.
-Boy, you really stink.
And your fur is filthy!
-Wha?
What do you mean?
-Yeah, I think you could
use at nice hot bath.
-[shout]
-Huh?
-Ah, nothing like a nice hot
bath to release the stress.
-Stop enjoying it!
-My squeaker's getting soaked!
-Would you two keep it down?
We have inured people
trying to rest,
and they need some
peace and quiet!
[groaning]
-Sorry.
-What is it, Ichigo?
-You know, I don't
think it would
kill you to try to act
a little more cheerful.
-When did it get
so gloomy in here?
Ugh, it's bleak.
-So what have you heard?
Does the Soul Society have any
information that might help?
YORUICHI: The Department
of Research and Development
came up with something.
-Wait.
-As the captain in charge of
the Department of Research
and Development, I have
full authorization.
So there shouldn't be any data
that I'm denied access to.
It took me some time, but I
was able to unlock the file.
Allow me to demonstrate.
Nemu?
NEMU: Yes, I'll bring
it up on the monitor.
KUROTSUCHI: The ones
causing a disturbance
in the World of the
Living are called Bounts.
They're a tribe that
is basically human,
but can extend their lifespans
by feeding on human souls.
You dimwit.
Move on to the next file.
-Yes.
KUROTSUCHI: As I'm sure you are
all aware, these are Quincies.
At one point in their history,
the Bounts and the Quincies
were mortal enemies.
[shouting]
-The stealth force
took this footage,
which is surprisingly
well preserved.
[shouting]
-I think you'll find
this interesting.
[shouting]
KUROTSUCHI: It's
obvious the Bounts are
targeting one Quincy
in particular.
KYORAKU: What happens next?
KUROTSUCHI: The
file is very old.
That is all I've
been able to recover.
-Hm.
I hate it when a movie
leaves me hanging.
I'd be interested to know
how this one turned out.
-Unfortunately, it all
happened so long ago,
there's no way to find
out if the Bounts actually
got the Quincy.
However, according
to my records-- Nemu,
explain to these gentleman
what we actually did find.
-Yes.
The records after
the battle indicate
that the Bounts continued
feeding on living humans
and absorbing their souls
for a period of time.
-What?
NEMU: Originally, there
existed a kind of law.
It was understood
that the Bounts were
only to absorb the
souls of dead humans.
To absorb a living
soul was prohibited.
This incident seems
to be the turning
point at which the Bounts
began absorbing souls
from living bodies.
The data we've gathered
backs up this theory,
showing a decrease in the
quality of souls, and--
-You can skip the
unnecessary details.
-Do the records show
what happened after that?
-I'm afraid not.
But whenever there's an
upheaval in their tribe,
they abandon the law that
they themselves created
and attack living humans.
One has to wonder if
there is some connection
between this behavior
and their need
for that particular Quincy.
I don't know if these
old records have
any bearing on what is currently
happening in the living world.
But there are
definitely parallels.
And this much is obvious.
From this point
forward, the Bounts
will begin to freely and
recklessly attack the humans--
not dead humans,
but living ones.
[gasping]
-Yoruichi, are you
certain about this?
-Maybe if I had heard
from someone else,
but I got this from
Jushiro Ukitake himself,
and he was visibly upset.
There's no reason
to question it.
-Jin Kariya-- he's trying to
use Uryu's power as a Quincy
to somehow open a hole and
break through to Hueco Mundo.
-[gasp]
-I would imagine
the energy they've
been absorbing from
the souls of living
humans is necessary for
that objective as well.
But what is the
purpose of a Quincy?
Why is he so necessary
for their success?
-We don't have enough
information to answer that yet.
And we must be very careful
until we find the answer.
At any rate, we've got to
do everything we possibly
can to stop Kariya
and the other Bounts
from attacking
living humans until--
ICHIGO: Hey, Yoruichi?
-Yes, what is it?
-There's just one
thing in all this
that doesn't make any sense.
They're breaking their own laws
by sucking the souls of living
humans and going
to all this trouble
to get a Quincy just
to get to Hueco Mundo
But the thing is,
what does Kariya
plan to do once he's there?
-If we knew the answer to
that, maybe we could stop him.
-Kariya.
He's powerful enough as it is.
What could he possibly
do with more power?
After you've reached
a certain point,
what difference does it make?
-Ichigo, listen to me.
-He's incredibly strong.
But it's not like he has to
depend on some technique.
So then why does he--
-[gasp]
-[gasp] The truth, Ichigo.
Are you really
afraid of this man?
-No, I don't think that's it.
It's just that if I'm
really honest with myself,
at my current ability, I
don't see how I can win.
-Ichigo.
-Huh?
-What-- what the hell is that?
-[shouting]
-It's Ganju!
-[laughs] Do I know how to
make an entrance, or what?
[laughs]
-Thank you very much, sir.
Please come again.
-Hanataro, where's Ganju?
-Well, uh, I-- I
think he was just
restocking those
shelves a minute ago.
-Oh, I see.
He must be in the bathroom.
-I don't know.
I suppose he could
be someplace else.
-No, if I know him,
he's in the bathroom.
[laughs]
-You may be right.
But with Ganju, you
never can be sure.
-[sigh] Well, you've made
quite a mess here, didn't you?
You'll have time to
fix it all later.
-[laughs] It's just a couple
of walls and some furniture.
-First of all, what
are you doing here?
And secondly, why were
you riding that boar?
Where on earth did you find it?
-Sweet, huh?
They got some really
strange animals here.
I could get used to this.
-You stole it from
the zoo, didn't you?
GANJU: I got to
admit, he's not bad.
But he's nothing like my Bonnie.
[laughs] Oh, come to
think of it, you've
never met my sweet
little Bonnie, have you?
-Why are you here, Ganju?
GANJU: Oh, yeah.
Right.
Well it started all
of a sudden when
I got this feeling of a gloomy
spiritual pressure coming
from somewhere in town.
I'm the type who's very
sensitive to these kind
of things, so I just hopped
on my boar, followed my nose,
and look where I ended up.
And the gloomy bastard
I sensed was you!
-What'd you call me?
[groaning]
-I hadn't noticed
before, but you're right.
-How'd we miss that?
He reeks of it.
-Whoa, someone open the windows.
I can't breathe in here.
-Hey, you can't talk about me
like I'm garbage or something!
-You're right.
Rotten garbage is more like it.
I'm going to take you out
and freshen you up a little.
Hey, old man, do you know a good
place where I could do that.
-Old man?
You may not know
it to look at me,
but your older sister
and I are good friends.
[laughs] But that's
another story.
Right this way.
-Yeah, now you're talking.
Come on, Ichigo.
It's for your own good.
-All right.
Now get out of your Gigai
so we can get started.
-This isn't a Gigai!
[shout]
RUKIA: How's that?
-What the hell are
you doing, Rukia.
Ah!
-I'll come along and help you.
-The more the merrier.
Now move it, Ichigo.
-Hey, wait.
Can we talk about this?
Come on, guys.
What's the rush?
Hey!
-Ready or not, now here you go.
-[shout]
-Master, can we still use it?
-It's hard to tell.
Maybe if we somehow
fix it, then perhaps.
There should be some tools
around here somewhere.
-Allow me to find
them for you, sir.
-No need.
I'll do it.
-[groaning]
-All right.
Start spinning.
[laughs]
-You shouldn't be
doing that, Jinta.
-Come on, don't
be a spoil sport.
He'll dry out faster this way.
-You jerk!
I'm not some piece of laundry
you can hang out to dry.
Especially in the middle
of the night! [shouting]
-Would you keep
it down out here?
I've got injured people inside,
and they need their rest.
-Uh, sorry about that.
JINTA: See, I told you so.
JINTA: Shut up!
YOSHINO: [gasp]
-Does it hurt?
-Not much.
Whatever treatment he gave
me seems to have worked.
I'm sorry that
this has to happen.
I never should've gotten
you involved in all of this.
-I was already involved.
There's nothing
you could have time
to stop them from targeting me.
I'm still a Quincy after all,
even though I have no powers.
-It's funny but I
just remembered.
Jin Kariya once told
me the same thing.
He said, I'm sorry for
getting you involved in this.
-And I'm sure you
believed him, though I
doubt he really felt that way.
-I don't think he's
sorry for anything.
Still, it shocked
me when I finally
came to that realization.
No one knows what
he's really like.
He has deceived all of them.
-Is his plan to go to Hueco
Mundo just another deception?
-No, that's real.
Although I don't know exactly
what he plans to do once
he gets there.
He never told me that.
But whatever it is, I don't
see how it could possibly
justify breaking the laws
our tribe has always lived by
and sacrificing innocent humans.
-I agree with you.
-Still, I attacked
living humans, too.
I'm despicable.
-That's different.
Our fate was decided long ago.
When I was first born into this
world-- and many, many years
before that, since the first
Bounts came into existence--
out population has
been determined.
-[gasp]
-Every one of us were born
during a short period of time
when a genetic
mutation occurred.
Since then, the mutation
has never occurred again.
And as such, no new
Bounts have been born.
Besides that, we are not capable
of giving birth to new life--
ever.
We can live forever,
yet we are constantly
waiting to die, to die
slowly over endless years
and centuries.
GANJU: I'm telling
you you're scared!
You're a weak-kneed,
lily-livered coward!
And it makes me sick.
Now I'm going to break
that cowardice out of you.
-Yeah?
I'd like to see you try!
-[laugh] About time
you showed some spirit.
Why don't you take it from here?
-Huh?
You said you were going to--
-I thought you'd want to.
But I guess if you're afraid--
-What'd you say?
-That's the spirit.
Now get in there.
-I guess I might as well, then.
-Wait.
What about you?
Hey!
RENJI: Here I come, Ichigo!
[shout]
[fighting noises]
-Come on, you coward!
Put up a fight!
-I never should have
let Renji fight, because
in your pathetic condition, even
I could have whipped your ass.
[laughs]
-Oh, you think so?
Then why don't you come
down here and prove it!
-Don't let him distract you.
-Whoa!
Ugh.
-Now it's my turn.
-Seppa, become the power of Zen!
-Whoa!
[cough]
-Zenpebaga!
[shouting]
GANJU: Ow, ow, ow, ow.
My eyes!
The Tears of Blood got me, too.
-[taunting]
-Ganju, come back
down here and fight!
-Sorry, I don't take
orders from a coward.
But I will give
you some more sand.
[phone ringing]
-Huh?
Ganju here.
Oh, Hanataro, what's going on?
-The customers are all
lined up, and the owner
thinks you're in the bathroom.
So you've got to get
back here, because I
don't think I can
stall him much longer.
-Oh, right.
I'll come right away.
-[together] Huh?
-The store's busy, so Hanataro
says I've got to go back.
-[together] Huh?
-You'll have to finish up.
-Hey, what's the deal?
You ask me to come along to
help, and then you just leave?
-I don't want to
go, but Hanataro
said I've got to get back
to the shop right away.
I'll see you later!
Ha ha!
-Now the guys' running away.
Well, it doesn't really matter.
[shout]
-[gasp]
[grunting]
-He was right about one thing.
You're in such a
pathetic state right now
that you can barely
even defend yourself!
-Shut up, Renji.
-Why are you afraid of Kariya?
-I am not afraid!
-When did you turn into
such a sniveling coward?
-I'm no coward, Renji!
-Zabimaru, roar!
HANATARO: Sorry.
I-- I'll be right with you.
Oh, why is it so crowded?
Oh, right.
Would you like me to warm
that up for you, sir?
MAN: Please.
WOMAN: Hey, what's
taking so long?
Isn't there anyone
else working here?
-Uh, yeah.
Of course.
Sir, you think you could take
over the register for a second?
-Sure, I guess.
So Ganju's still in
the bathroom, huh?
He's been in there quite awhile.
Maybe I better go
back and check on him.
-Uh, um, why don't I go check,
and you can take the register?
-Hey.
-Hurry up.
-Right.
-Are you all right?
[crash]
-Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'll go help out
on the register.
-I knew it.
He was in the bathroom
the whole time.
-Can I ask you something?
It's kind of personal.
I know this may
sound odd, but do you
feel any pride as a Bount?
-Hm?
-I've always felt it.
I've always been proud of
the fact that I'm a Quincy.
The Quincies-- I believe we
were placed here and given
a tremendous power to
protect people from Hollows.
And even if I am the
last one remaining,
I will take pride in
fulfilling my duty as a Quincy
as long as I live.
YOSHINO (VOICEOVER):
I like that.
Pride-- it has a nice sound.
[fighting noises]
RENJI: Since when did you start
obsessing so much about winning
and losing, Ichigo?
You are pathetic.
That's the reason you're
so nervous, isn't it?
(MIMICKING) I don't
see how I can win.
Why are you wasting your time
thinking about winning now?
You never gave it
a thought when you
charged into the Soul Society!
[shouting]
-Looks like you've found some
of that old determination, huh?
Hey, you're not going to hold
that against me, are you?
Uh, wait!
That coward stuff?
I was just trying to give you
a friendly shove, you know?
-Thanks for the shove.
It worked.
-[laugh]
-You're right.
I think I might still have
a little bit left inside.
Goodbye, proud Quincy.
Thank you.
-She may die this time.
And i think she knows that.
-You're right.
But if she wants
to settle things,
there may be no other solution.
-Settle things?
-Yeah.
Put things in order and settle
the score with your life.
-I'm going back to
the Soul Society
to see if I can
find some answers.
All we seemed to have
come up with here
is a bunch of vague
information that's
getting us absolutely nowhere.
Maybe I can find out what's
really behind all this.
-Good.
-Huh?
[gasp]
[theme music]
JINTA: Really, barging
in with so many people?
I don't have enough ingredients
for tomorrow's breakfast.
URURU: It's OK, Jinta.
I'll go shopping.
JINTA: Nah, don't
worry about it.
The moocher can
just eat leftovers.
KON: Why me?
JINTA: Or you could
just have hot water.
KON: Give me a break.
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers!
GROUP: Golden!
-So, Ichigo, you fought him.
What kind of powers
did Kariya have?
-How am I supposed to know?
All I know is I couldn't move.
-Huh?
You fought the guy and you
weren't able to figure it out?
You moron!
-I wouldn't talk about
morons if I were you,
because you haven't
come up with one idea.
While we're on it,
where the hell were you?
We called for you,
but you never showed?
-[grunt] Oh, yeah?
Well, if you called, then
why don't I have a-- huh?
The battery is dead.
[shout]