[theme song]
NARRATOR: Ichigo and Rukia
entered the Soul Society,
disrupting Rurichiyo's
wedding to Shu Kannogi,
but were quickly surrounded
by Soi Fon and Squad 2.
Shu helped them escape by
posing as their hostage,
but this turned them
into fugitives on the run
from the Soul Reapers.
-What a surprise.
I must say we never thought
we'd run into you here.
NARRATOR: Shu intervened and
revealed to Captain Amagai
his reasons for helping Ichigo.
The captain then agreed to
help Ichigo to free Rurichiyo.
Meanwhile, the 13
Court Guard Squads
were perplexed by the news of
Ichigo becoming a fugitive.
In the meantime,
Lieutenant Izuru Kira
entered the Kasumioji
grounds and found himself
battling for his life
against savage assassins.
Izuru searched for Third
Seat Makoto Kibune,
but instead, came across
Rurichiyo just in time
to see her being carried off.
Even though Izuru fought
admirably and defeated
all the assassins, he soon
faced an even greater threat--
Makoto's true nature.
-[groan]
-What a shame.
Just like always,
you're too slow.
I'm afraid the princess
is long gone by now.
Sorry, Lieutenant Kira.
-So all of this madness--
it's your doing?
Third Seat Kibune.
[footsteps]
-Team 1 will cover from
here to Section Five East.
Team 2 to Section Eight South.
Team 3 go from Section
Four West to Fifth Street.
And Team 4 goes to
Section Three North.
-Sir, what about
Section Two North?
Central Street?
-No need.
That's Squad 8's jurisdiction.
-But that's near Team
4's assigned section.
Wouldn't it be best
to overlap them?
-Follow orders.
Moving outside your
jurisdiction will just
get you in trouble
with the other squads.
-Yes, sir.
-Get moving!
-Within the Seireitei,
the chaos has
been contained, thanks to the
work of the Punishment Force.
Each squad's deployment to their
assigned section is complete.
Our net is spreading quite
wide in this manhunt.
-I'll be.
I can't believe you're
still hanging around.
-Shunsui?
What are you doing here?
-I suppose you could
say our squad just
isn't fully ready to deploy yet.
What's with you?
You're looking pretty glum.
-I just had another talk
with Head Captain Yamamoto,
but it's no use what I say.
He refuses to take any action.
-Yeah, that old man Yama
can be a stubborn one.
-I just don't understand.
Is there a reason the
Kasumioji clan is off limits?
-Hm.
I did some research of my
own, but got zero results.
It seems they don't
want outsiders
looking into their business.
-What do you mean?
-They're high ranking
nobles, yet they rarely
present themselves in public.
And their clan certainly didn't
associate with Central 46
that much, either.
But that Ichigo
is something else.
Trouble likes to follow
him wherever he goes.
-That's no laughing matter.
Imagine if we're
attacked from the outside
while this is going on.
-Oh, we'd be fine.
Squad 12 is on it.
Seems like Captain
Kurotsuchi isn't exactly
eager to get involved
with the mess going on
within the Seireitei, so I'd
say we're covered pretty well.
It's probably best
we just concentrate
on taking care of
our own duties.
Don't you agree?
-Sure.
-Oh, a Hell Butterfly.
-Hm.
-Any news?
-It appears that while
Izuru was chasing Makoto,
he found Princess Rurichiyo.
-What?
Izuru found her?
-So where is she?
-He saw her at the
Squad 3 barracks.
-Then that means--
-That's right.
This fits with what
we've suspected.
Makoto is somehow
involved in all this.
-That's unfortunate, but you'll
have to deal with him later.
We've gotta save Rurichiyo.
-Yes, of course we do.
Especially because my squad
is responsible for this.
Hurry, come this way.
-Huh?
But Squad 3's barracks are
located straight ahead of us.
-True, but by going
this way, we'll
pass through the section
assigned to Squad 9.
-So now squads are
assigned to sections?
-It was done to better organize
the 13 Court Guard Squads.
But there's a little space in
between each of their assigned
sections.
This will help us
avoid confrontation.
-Right.
Sounds good.
-Then let's go.
-Hey, Kenny.
Now that he's a fugitive,
aren't you gonna go after Ichi?
-No way.
-Why not?
-I don't feel like it.
-Oh.
I heard that you were there
during Captain Amagai's
examination.
Is that true?
-Yeah.
-If he's on the run
with Ichi, don't you
think they'd say you're
responsible for that?
-I was tricked into
doing it by the old man.
I don't care either
way about that guy.
-Oh.
-Captain Amagai!
I take it you've
received Izuru's message?
-Yes, sir.
-Can you clear up
what's going on, sir?
-I'll explain later.
Now we need to get to
the fighting arena.
-Sir
-Hey, Captain!
-Those guys!
-They were carrying someone!
-Could it be Rurichiyo?
-We'll find out.
Rukia, look after Shu.
-Hold on.
I'll come too.
-Huh?
-Aida, Inose, Kano, I want
all of you to go find Izuru.
-Yes sir.
-Rukia, follow after
us with Sir Kannogi.
-Sir.
-Let's go, Ichigo.
-OK.
-It was you after all,
Third Seat Kibune.
-So you fended off their attack.
I guess that's to be
expected, Lieutenant.
Well, it almost worked.
I supplied each of them
with a scaled down version
of a bakoto.
But even that seems to have
been too much for these men.
-I see.
You're with the Kasumioji clan.
--[laughing] That's
quite an assumption.
I've heard enough.
It's time for you to die.
-Lieutenant!
-Third Seat Kibune?
-Why are you fighting?
-This just doesn't make sense.
-Where's Captain Amagai?
-He's with Ichigo Kurosaki.
They've both gone
after the princess.
-That's good.
The butterfly made it.
-But sir, what is going on here?
-Stay back!
Makoto Kibune is our enemy!
-Huh?
-You can't mean that.
-Third Seat Kibune, is
what Lieutenant Kira's
saying about you true?
-You better convince
us he's wrong,
or you'll be in
a lot of trouble.
--[laughing] You small
fries can be so confident.
-What?
-I guess I might as
well kill all of you.
Rampage, Reppu!
-You three, get out!
-Huh?
-Too late.
-Now raise your head, Wabisuke!
-You're through.
Your dull edged
sword is completely
useless against my Reppu.
-Huh?
Why, you-- what did you do?
-My Wabisuke doubles the weight
of any object it touches.
Weight will be added
with each strike.
Now your Reppu weighs
six times as much.
Since your weapon is
now too heavy to lift,
it is now worthless to you.
Makoto, it's time for the truth.
Just what are you up to?
What's your motive for working
with the Kasumioji clan?
I demand to know what has
been going on with this clan.
-Whatever the Kasumioji
clan is and whatever it does
is over your head.
But they do possess
tremendous power.
All I want is to use that
power to become even stronger,
until I am the strongest
Soul Reaper ever!
-[grunting]
-[screaming]
-[laughing]
[laughing]
-Such intense power.
Not even Wabisuke can
stop that massive force.
-What's wrong, Lieutenant?
Where are you?
Don't tell me you're dead.
Hm.
IZURU (VOICEOVER): Makoto's
Zanpakuto is too strong.
This isn't good.
-Look, I know
you're still alive,
and hiding just won't work.
Come out and face your fate.
Do it and I promise
you a swift death.
Die like a man
instead of a coward.
After all, your powers are
no match for what I possess.
IZURU (OFFSCREEN):
Third seat Kibune.
-Hm?
Come out, Izuru Kira.
IZURU (OFFSCREEN):
You said you wanted
more of Kasumioji's
power, didn't you?
From what I saw, you already
possess more than enough power.
-Show yourself.
Where are you, coward?
IZURU (OFFSCREEN): You've
been given so much power.
Why not use it for good?
-Did you say given?
Do you have any
idea how much I had
to sacrifice to attain my Reppu?
You have no idea the cost!
There you are!
-Hado Number 31, Shakkaho!
-[growling]
-Reppu!
-Too slow!
-[grunting]
-[laughing]
-What the hell?
-Ha!
-[groaning]
-He grew stronger.
But how?
-How dare you challenge me?
-Makoto.
-[pained groaning]
-What is that thing?
-What, you ask?
This is my very special bakoto.
-Bakoto?
-Yes.
The Kasumioji clan, using
their secret technique,
created this great sword.
It has vicious
spiritual pressure.
Like the ones those
assassins had.
-That's where you're wrong.
Their swords filled in for
their lack of fighting skills.
Those assassins
were so feeble, they
couldn't even use a Shikai.
But this bakoto utilizes
my spirit energy,
which means it can
grow endlessly.
Your cheap techniques
will not work against me.
-Why would you want to
possess such a weapon?
-Why, you ask?
It's simple.
To have power.
-Power?
-That's right.
Sheer power.
It's all about power.
I always did have power,
but for some strange reason,
no one chose to recognize it.
MAKOTO (VOICEOVER): Back when
I was attending the Soul Reaper
Academy, I was always at the
top of my class academically.
But during all my
years of study,
I never received a call to
join the 13 Court Guard Squads.
-Why haven't I been asked to
become a part of the 13 Court
Guard Squads?
When other classes
graduated, all their high
ranked students
got in, and I just
graduated the best in my class.
-You are indeed a high
achiever, young man.
But that's not the
only qualification
for being accepted.
Rather than focusing
on what you have,
reflect instead
on what you lack.
-[growl]
-I swear to see to it
that I lack nothing!
I will be strong!
MAKOTO (VOICEOVER):
Instead of allowing
myself to wallow in
days of idleness,
I continued to train
painstakingly for years.
Finally, I attained
a Shikai, and was
accepted into the squad.
No matter what the
situation, I proved myself.
I killed more
Hollows than anybody.
But--
My fighting style became
an issue with the others.
Instead of being praised, I fell
out of favor within my squad.
I faced the real chance of
being banished from the squad
altogether.
-Why would you sacrifice
your fellow squad members?
-Because they lack the
power to achieve greatness.
-It is the
responsibility of those
who have power to save
those of us who do not.
-[growl]
MAKOTO (VOICEOVER):
Though I did manage
to avoid being discharged I was
still sentenced to probation.
And so my chances to ever
become a seated officer
were effectively
over, and I was forced
to watch other less skilled
members move up the ranks.
I'd lost my station
within the squad,
and finally received orders to
join the Expeditionary Unit.
In my despair, I stayed
with the Expedition Unit
and continued killing Hollows
to prove my worth to those
who didn't recognize my talents.
And then finally, I
encountered this awesome power.
-[groaning]
[screaming]
MAKOTO (VOICEOVER): With
this power I now hold,
no one will ever be
able to ignore me again.
-But it's not enough!
I will have more!
I now hold here the
key to great power!
Possessing such absolute power
will force every Soul Reaper
to respect me and
bow down to me!
-His whole being.
That sword has
fully consumed him.
-Look at you, Izuru.
People like you who have
no real ability, yet
still get promoted
to Lieutenant.
It's your kind I
exterminate from this world.
Your weakness is a crime.
A sniveling toad
like you doesn't
deserve to have
what you possess.
When the last
captain went berserk,
you couldn't even stop him.
Powerless people like you don't
deserve to stand above me!
Your life's done!
Here's the killing blow!
[theme song]
SHUNSUI (VOICEOVER): Old
man Yama just won't quit.
He keeps sending request
for me to deploy my men.
UKITAKE (VOICEOVER):
So much for getting
to see how things play out.
SHUNSUI (VOICEOVER):
I'm out of excuses
to hold off their deployment.
UKITAKE (VOICEOVER):
How about we tell them
they just left a moment ago?
SHUNSUI (VOICEOVER):
[laughing] if he calls,
I'll just put him on hold.