[music playing]
[theme music]
-Kariya's plans for this world
are actually very simple.
He wants to create
a new, clean, world.
A world that will
be ruled by Bounts.
-What are you talking about?
-When a Bount gains power by
sucking the souls from living
humans, it also
increases the power
of all the other Bounts, because
of the multiplier effect.
Soon we will rule the world.
-That's what you think.
I'm not about to let you use
Keigo's life for that purpose.
-It's useless to defy us.
Admit that you cannot defeat
the Bounts, young man.
-No, never.
-The fire in your
eyes spells danger.
Such power without
principle is dangerous.
You must understand, or die.
-Go to hell.
No matter what you say,
I won't let Keigo die.
-Why am I destined,
again and again,
to witness the deaths
of young ones, who
forfeit their bright futures?
Farewell, young one.
-So, you want me to finish him?
-Do it now.
Hm?
Who's there?
-So then, you are
a Bount, are you?
From the Court Guard Squads,
I'm Squad Three Lieutenant,
Izuru Kira.
[gasping]
-Hold on a minute!
Ow, what is all this about?
It's not funny.
Ow, put me down, will you?
Come on!
-As you can see,
I brought Yamada.
-What's this all about?
I'm supposed to be
working the register.
Huh?
Whoa.
-I'm sorry.
I told Tessai it was urgent.
You can see for yourself.
-Oh, it's bad.
I can hardly feel
his pulse at all.
Can you put up a barrier
to gather spirit energy?
-Right away.
-Good.
Then I can handle
everything else.
-I knew that we'd
be in good hands.
It was very smart of them to
send a member of Squad Four.
-Here I come again!
-I'm not finished yet!
-If you treat this
like some child's game,
you are going to die!
-The one who reins.
Mask of flesh, all
creation, flapping
of wings, he who
carries the name human!
-Tsubaki!
Koten Zanshun!
I reject, I reject!
-I'm afraid that it is useless.
-Temperance.
Claw the wall of
seamless dreams.
Hado #33.
Sokatsui!
-Huh?
-Impossible.
How did she escape
that attack in time?
-What do we do now?
-So close.
But not close enough.
-Oh no!
Kurodo!
-Damn you.
Orihime!
-Hm.
No, wait!
The technique is
not perfected yet.
-You see?
I told you so.
You should have waited.
-What are you talking about?
-Fighting humans
requires patience.
Maybe you should take a break.
-Are you forgetting
who's in charge here?
-Oh no, of course not.
-She has a point.
-Hm?
-Just take a deep breath.
Meditate for a moment,
and gather all the power
inside you.
-Yes, that's it.
-Why don't you two just
shut up and do your jobs?
-Kurodo!
Are you all right?
-I'll be all right.
You see, we Mod Souls
are actually just pills.
No matter what happens
to our Gigai, we survive.
Well, I'm not saying
it doesn't hurt.
At any rate, we should
escape while we can.
-Happy now?
-Oh, yes.
-Absolutely.
It wouldn't do to
let the enemy escape.
-What?
-Hurry!
Run!
-Right!
-Where do you
think you're going?
-Oh, that's it!
Such timing!
-This is what I was waiting for.
Am I as beautiful as I feel?
-You're gorgeous!
-What?
I'll take over from here.
-Huh?
What are you doing?
-This isn't a job
for an old lady.
-Old lady?
What the hell's wrong
with you, Mabashi?
-Why, nothing.
In fact, I feel great.
Right now I feel as if I'm
a God who could do anything.
-All you are is a
cocky little punk
whose drunk with the power
of tasting their first living
soul.
-Such an ugly old woman.
-Huh?
-Zeige Dich.
Ritz.
[gasping]
-Is that little
thing a doll, too?
-It's definitely a doll, but I
can't tell what kind of power
it has.
-Stop it.
Before this gets out of hand.
-Go on, Ritz.
-With pleasure, sir.
-Huh?
-Going up!
Are you out of your mind?
I'm an ally!
-Going down!
[laughter]
-When things heat up a little,
you completely lose it,
don't you?
Must be old age.
Old and ugly.
Too bad.
-Is there anything
else I can do for you?
-Just give me a moment.
-Very well, sir.
-Now what?
-You're out of your mind.
You've completely lost it.
I don't need this.
Do whatever you want with them.
-Oh, are we leaving?
-It appears so.
-Mabashi!
I'm going to get you for this!
[laughter]
-That doll's power must
be very impressive,
to have frightened
her off like that.
-Stay here.
I'll handle it.
-Rukia.
-Hado #33.
Sokatsui.
-Is there anything else
I can do for you now?
-Well, why don't you play
with them for awhile, Ritz.
-Absolutely,sir.
Going forward.
Going diagonally right.
Going diagonally left.
-That thing's like some
sort of demented elevator.
-Now going down!
-Be careful.
You don't know where that
thing will spring up.
-Going up.
We have now arrived
at the rooftop.
-How is it, Ritz?
Having fun?
-Yes!
Is there anything else
you'd like me to do?
-I think we've had
enough play time, Ritz.
Now, let's begin.
-Absolutely, sir.
[music playing]
-What?
-It's speed is astonishing.
What are we going to do?
-Where is it?
-Damn.
Where'd it go?
Uh.
My kido is useless.
-She is cute, isn't she?
-Orihime!
Orihime!
-No!
What does it want?
Get it away from me.
Make it stop!
-Ow!
-You did it!
-That was amazing, the way
that you handled that stick.
It was just like a
Japanese samurai.
-Thanks, Rukia.
That was totally awesome.
-Orihime!
[gasping]
-Rukia!
Rukia!
Are you all right?
Say something!
-Come on!
-Rukia!
What in the world is so funny?
-You're about to find out.
Just watch.
-Rukia?
[music playing]
-Rukia, what is it?
-Very good, Ritz.
You're so unbelievably cute.
[moaning]
-Ichigo!
Ichigo!
What should I do?
I've got it.
Hang on, Ichigo!
-Izuru?
The hell are you doing here?
-Captain Hitsugaya of
Squad Ten gave the order.
He dispatched myself and
three other lieutenants.
Now stand back.
I'll deal with these two.
-So, they come in
all shapes and sizes.
I'm so happy I was born a woman.
That way you two
can fight over me.
-The Soul Society sent me.
They declared that the
Bounts must be stopped,
and that's what
we're here to do.
-My, how formal.
But it's actually kind
of cute, in a way.
Here's what I think
of the Soul Society.
-Raise your head.
Wabisuke!
-Hahaha.
Maybe if you had more
hands, you'd stand a chance.
That helpless expression on
your face, it makes me excited.
Huh?
What's this?
My body feels so heavy.
-Wabisuke's power
is to make whatever
it cuts twice as heavy.
Your steel body has
reached its limit,
and can no longer
bear its own weight.
-I can't move!
You tricked me!
-Hurry, now's your chance.
-I've got to get Keigo
to Uruhara's shop,
while there's still time.
Get out of my way.
-What'll you do if I don't?
-If you don't move,
then I'll cut you down.
Even if this guy is a
Bount, he's still human.
-What's wrong?
Why are you hesitating?
All right then.
I'll go first.
-What the hell?
This guy's strong.
You've caused enough
trouble as it is.
This one's for Keigo.
You're going down!
[music playing]
-Are you surprised?
You never thought an unarmed
human could be this powerful.
We Bounts have eternal life.
Incredible mental
strength is required
to withstand the
passing of eternity.
And that strength,
that is what allowed
me to push my body to
the absolute limit.
What you see before you, this
is a human's potential power.
-What an armor, too.
I'm done fooling around.
I'll be taking that
sword of yours.
-Now I just have to wait
until you stop breathing.
Or I could snap your neck,
with one little twist.
At least I'll be merciful, so
that you don't have to suffer.
Well.
I never would have guessed you
had that much strength left.
-Sorry to disappoint you,
but I'm taking you out.
-Cain.
-What's wrong with you?
-It's just that,
I've lived too long.
People are born, mature,
and then grow old.
I have seen life from all sides.
And yet, the lives that
should be lived, always
seem to slip
through these hands.
-No, Cain!
Get away from it, quickly!
[music playing]
Cain!
-Master.
Master!
What's happening?
I'm not ready to die yet.
-Cain!
No.
Don't tell me.
Cain.
[music playing]
-That's Dalk!
-Damn you, I can't move.
But I won't lose to
the likes of you.
-You all right?
-Don't worry about me.
-So young.
You haven't lived at all.
It's a pity.
-Hey!
Old man!
Where do you think you're going?
You think I'm Just going to
let you walk away like that?
-That's enough, Dalk.
-My body's so heavy.
I can't stand it.
-Yes, I know.
You've done well.
Don't feel like you
have to rush your life.
There's no shame in
cherishing the journey.
Farewell.
-Hey!
Old man!
[gasping]
-I can't go on!
It's no good.
I'll never make it.
They'll find me lying
dead in the street.
Ow!
Why don't you watch
where you're going?
-Hey Ririn.
Hey, wait a minute, what
are you doing out here
in the middle of nowhere?
Wow.
You look horrible.
You really ought to pay more
attention to your appearance.
And you call yourself a lady.
-Ha!
Get to Uruhara's
shop on the double!
-All right.
Just take it easy with
the stick, will ya?
I didn't mean it.
-Just shut up and run!
-Rukia!
-Can someone please explain
to me what happened?
-Say, why don't
we just start off
with you telling me your name.
-Rukia.
Kuchiki.
-Ah.
Well that's a very nice name.
Worthy of being my new servant.
-His servant?
-So Rukia.
Would you like to work for me?
-Yes.
[shouting]
-What are you doing, Rukia?
-Rukia!
-Stop.
I can't breathe.
You're choking me.
-You don't know
what you're doing.
-No, Rukia!
[theme music]
-Since we're in the
world of the living,
we should buy some gifts.
Candy for lieutenant, an
electric razor for Ikaku,
and I think Ichigo would
make a wonderful fighting
partner for the Captain.
-You may look nice, but you've
got a real nasty streak.
-Oh come on.
How can it be mean to
say what's on your mind?
[theme music]
-Regard the Soul Reapers.
-Golden!
-It's gone!
-Someone took all of the snacks.
-How could they do that?
I'm starving!
-What's all the noise about?
-Sorry if we disturbed you.
But do you know what happened to
the snacks that were left here?
-How am I supposed to know
what happened to your snacks.
[fart]
-Who did that?
-Wait a minute.
Wasn't the snack--
-Edamame?
[shouting]