Huh?
Where am I?
Wait... What the--?!
Why the hell am I
dressed like this?
[meow]
Huh? A cat?
Is that you,
Yoruichi?
[meow]
Okay, So what's
this big important
meeting about?
And what's with
these ridiculous
clothes we're
wearing?
I think our
clothes are fine.
They're the
same clothes we
always wear.
You fall and hit
your head or
something, Chigo?
Chigo? Who the
hell's that?
That's sad, even for you.
What, you've forgotten your
own name now?
What is this,
what're you
talking about?!
I know my name!
It's I-chi-go
Ku-ro-sa-ki!
Yeah, right.
Where'd you come up
with that nonsense?
It's time.
Right.
Let's go.
Hm? Wait, go where?
You wanna tell me what
the hell's going on? Hey!
I've had my eye on this
prize for a long time,
I don't want to blow it.
We'll have to move
very carefully.
Don't worry, it'll be
fine, Urio.
After all, you came
up with the plan.
Glad you're on board
with it, Ori Mei,
that's very reassuring.
Right?
Isn't it,
Chaido?
Mmm.
What's with these names?
Urio? Ori Mei? Chaido?
These guys have been acting
weird for awhile now...
On top of that...
When did this giant eel start
pretending to be a camel?!
If this is some kind of
joke, I'm afraid I
don't get it, Chigo.
Bawabawa's not
pretending to be a
camel, he is a camel.
Poor guy.
He's a mess.
Mmm.
Agh...
Okay, Chigo, here's the plan.
We're going to sneak into the
palace of Ura Vira, the
wealthiest merchant in town.
We are? Why?
Cuz that's where the legendary
Snow Crystal is, the only jewel
of its kind in the whole world!
And tonight's the night
we're going to sneak in
there and steal it!
You're kidding. So you're
saying we're thieves now?
No not thieves,
burglars.
Oh, well, that's a lot better,
thanks for clearing that up.
[All]
Ooh!
Whoa. This place
is straight out
of a dream.
Yeah. You're right,
it's just like a dream!
Well, that's because
this is a dream.
Huh??
[Uryu]
Okay, it's dangerous
to stay here too long.
So forget everything else,
just find the Snow Crystal.
[Chad]
Mmm.
Got it!
[Ichigo]
Might help if we knew what
we were searching for.
What's this thing look like?
The Snow Crystal...
shines with an inner
radiance of such beauty
it fills the beholder
with calm and wonder,
and when you touch it,
it's as cold as snow!
It's a treasure
beyond compare!
You know, this is
all sounding kinda
vague to me.
You sure you're not
just making this up
as you go along?
[Orihime]
Hey! I think I found it!
Can you open it?
Stand back and leave
it to me. Hmm-hmm!
[click]
[oohs, ahhs]
Huh??
One little lamp,
that's it?
Kind of a big treasure
chest just to hold that,
don'tcha think?
Huh?... Kon?
This looks like Kon--
[Uryu]
No, wait, now I get it!
Aladdin and the Lamp!
You know, the story from
Arabian Nights, the magic
lamp and the three wishes?
This whole dream
is obviously based
on that story.
Hold on, Uryu.
What did you just say?
Who's Uryu?
My name's Urio.
Never mind that!
Is this a dream
we're in right now?
Either you haven't been
paying attention or
you're really obtuse.
Of course it is.
If it wasn't a dream,
there's no way things would
be going so smoothly.
True!
Mmm-hmm.
Aah-ha ha ha haaa!
Call yourselves burglars?
You're too pathetic.
You look a lot more like rats
caught in a trap to me.
A dream. Yeah, okay. Now it's
all beginning to make sense.
That's Ura Vira,
the merchant,
whose collection of treasure
includes rarities gathered from
every corner of the globe!
The richest man in
this whole country!
Hello? Who the hell are
you talking to anyway?
Oh you poor fools,
use your heads.
Did you really think that with
all this priceless treasure
lying around I wouldn't be
prepared for break-ins?
[panicked shouts]
[Ichigo]
A giant boulder, really?
That is such a cliché!!
Laser beams? Oh, come on!
That's a cliché AND an
anachronism!
[Chad]
A dead end. What do we do now?
[Uryu]
Damn it! We'll have to
fight our way out.
[Ichigo]
Fight?? Fight with what?
We're unarmed!
[Orihime]
Who says we're
unarmed? Look!
That stupid lamp?
What're we s'posed to
do with tha--?!
Oh!
That's right! If this is one
of those magic lamps, you're
supposed to rub it, right?
To make the
genie come out?
(startled reax) ...(alarmed
reax)
It's working!
Here he comes!
Watch it! It looks
like the whole thing
is about to explode!
Who is it that summons
the genie of the lamp?
Rukia?! What are you doing in
there?
I'm not Rukia,
I'm Rukiruki!
Don't you start!
Hey, listen, you.
If you don't want
anything, leave me alone.
I happen
to be very busy.
Hey, where the hell're you
going? Come back here,
this is an emergency!
Emergency,
emergency!
[sigh] What is it?
You're getting to be a pest.
Well you're the genie
of the lamp, aren'tcha?
So that means you're able
to grant wishes, right?
Yes, that's right.
What's it to you?
[thud]
Huh?
That's right,
break it down.
I was going to remodel
this wing anyway.
Come on! Help us out,
we're in a real jam here!
Will you grant us a wish?
I refuse.
For one thing, genie law
prohibits me from granting
wishes to anyone who is not
totally pure of heart.
And then there's that
orange hair, that's
completely unacceptable.
What's the color of
my hair got to do
with anything?!
Dying your hair is a
sign of delinquency!
Are you a genie or
a vice principal?
Anyway, I don't
dye my hair!
I've given you
my answer.
It's no.
Okay, fine, fine.
Know what I think?
I think you're
full of it.
Rnn!
You can't grant any
wishes, can you?
You're just a big phony.
I am not!
Okay, then show me.
I can't, I'd be
breaking the law!
Yeah right, that's just an
excuse. You can't do it.
Can too!
Okay then, prove it!
I told you,
genie law
forbids it!
Admit it,
getyou're a big phony.
All right. You want
to see proof?
Well, go on then, make a wish.
Ooh, I've got one!
I wish for a piece of cake!
Maybe not the smartest
wish in this situation.
All right!
Coming up!
Whoa, amazing!
There, are you
satisfied? Is that
proof enough for you?
Big freakin' deal, my kid
sister can make a cake.
I was thinking of something a
little more challenging.
Gah! You get a total of
three wishes, that's it.
You have two left.
And again!...
Almost there.
This door won't
hold much longer!
Rukia! Our second wish is
for you to get us the hell
out of here, and fast!
Language. If you want a
favor, you should learn
how to ask for it nicely.
Uh, will you get us the
hell out of here please?
There. That's
more like it.
Here we go...
[Chad]
It's cramped in here.
[Ichigo]
And it stinks!
Hey, Rukia--
Stop calling me that!
I'm Rukiruki!
Whatever, okay, listen,
I asked you to get us
out of there and you did...
But did you have to stick
us in an outhouse?!
[Orihime]
We're all safe and sound,
that's what's important!
[Uryu]
Right!
For a minute there,
I thought all of us
were done for.
What was I thinking?
I should have just used that
wish to wake myself up from
this ridiculous dream.
I'm such an idiot...
Okay, I've come this far, I
guess I might as well finish it.
So tell me what
your last wish is.
All right! I wish for
you to wake me from
this dream right n--
[in unison]
Ha! I wish for
the Snow Crystal!
What, all three of you?
Okay, majority wins.
Hey, hold on a second!
I'm the one who
summoned the genie
in the first place!
So if anyone gets dibs on
the last wish it should
be me, don'tcha think?!
I never knew you
were that kind of
person, Chigo.
Some people are like that,
they're just greedy.
Hmm. Some
friend you are.
Oh, who cares what
you guys think?!
This is my dream!
I get to do
whatever I want!
[Uryu]
What are you talking about?
You said yourself the Snow
Crystal was one of your wishes!
[Ichigo]
When did I say that?!
I never said that!
[Orihime]
Wait!
I know!
We'll decide it
with a vote!
You gotta
be kidding.
Who wants to wish for
the Snow Crystal?
Me! / Me! / Me!
Wait a second,
waait a second!
Hang on, this is
so unfair!
Come on out, Rukiruki,
we've got our wish.
I can't believe
you'd try to gang up
on me like that!
Three against one,
in my own dream!
Hey, what's going on?
She's not coming out...
You sure took your time, didn't
you? What's going on in there?
Uh oh, what happened?
That's a totally
different genie!
How'd you get in there,
Renji, and how come
you're full-sized?
I'm not Renji! I'm Ren Jin!
Yeah, never mind,
whatever your name is.
we don't need you.
Our business
is with Rukia.
If you mean Rukiruki...
she won't be coming out
any more.
[in unison]
Huh?
Rukiruki has broken the sacred
laws of the Lamp Society,
and for that she will
pay with her life!
Huh?
She is to be executed tomorrow,
at the stroke of noon.
Hey, why does this
sound familiar?
And what the hell is
the Lamp Society?
This is your fault!
She's going to die
because she granted
you those wishes!
I should curse you,
but instead I must...
swallow my pride and
ask you a favor!
Save Rukiruki,
before it's too late!
Things sure happen
fast around here...
Chigo, what are
you waiting for?
Let's go!
Hang on--
Hey, don't I get a say in this?
It's my dream!!!
[Uryu]
So this is the
Lamp Society.
Now all that we have to
do is find Rukiruki...
Huh?
What did I ever do to get
myself mixed up in this?
Is something
wrong, Chigo?
Carsick?
No, of course not.
Yeah, of course
he isn't, Ori Mei.
Hm?
After all, this isn't a car,
it's a carpet.
If he were
suffering from
anything, it'd be
carpetsickness.
Ah!
Who the hell cares?
That's all kinda beside
the point right now!
Man. All you ever
do is complain,
you know that, Chigo?
Okay, okay,
you're right.
[sigh]
As long as I'm here,
I might as well see
it through.
I'll stick with you
guys till the end!
[meow]
[Yoruichi]
Well said, Chigo!
Huh?
Just the words I've
been waiting to hear.
Yoruichi?
Why are you looking at her?
I'm right here.
Hwahh!
Yoruichi!
Heh-heh. What's wrong, Chigo?
surprised to see me?
Wait, then who is this?
That's just
a black cat.
Okay, I guess it's time I
brought everyone up to speed.
Rukiruki is going to be
executed at a place called the
Solamp, which lies deep within
the Lamp Society's territory.
In order to reach it,
we'll have to get past the
Thirteen Court Lamp Squads,
those deadly, highly skilled
guardians of the Lamp Society.
Oh, is that all we have to do,
take on 13 Lamp squads, really?!
I mean, gimme a break,
I wouldn't even know
where to begin!
All right, till
we meet again.
Hopefully alive.
[in unison]
Roger!
Wait, how are we
s'posed to land?
What happens when we
hit the ground?!
Don't worry,
the fall won't
kill you.
After all, this is only
a dream, isn't it?
Huh?
Ngh! Man, that hurt
so much I almost wish
it had killed me!
Anyway, I thought you
were supposed to wake
up from a dream before
you hit the ground!
Oh, don't tell me...
Oh no, oh no!
I have to go
through this again?
Not that I've got a
problem with that!
No, consistency is
fine! It's great!
I remember this scene...
Okay, where's the real Zangetsu?
There!
Wait a second, the real
Zangetsu has a design to
match this world, too?
[screech]
Ow ow! Ow ow ow ow!
Oh! Chigo?
Hi.
You idiot!
It took you
long enough!
That was cutting it kind
of close, wasn't it?
I could have been killed!
Oh come on, aren't you
exaggerating a little?
Oww, stop it, that hurts!
I could sense you
were there, Byakuya.
What the--? Whoa!
Ambassador Seaweed??
Oh wow, my big brother... I've
never seen you looking better.
If you ask me,
this family needs help.
All right, you can take
off that disguise now!
Mmf!
Ahahahaha!
Sorry! Sorry!
But where'd you
get that outfit?
Ha ha! It sure doesn't
go with your image--!
Beware, for it is a
dangerous thing to tread
on another man's pride.
Okay, bring it on! I've come
this far, I'm going to see
this through to the end!
[growl]
Grrrahh!
I concede the match.
You win this battle.
Hey I did it! It's all over!
It's all overrrrrrrrrr--!!
[crash]
Aah, finally! I thought that
dream would never end...
What?! No, no, you've gotta
be kidding! I'm still here?!
Ohh man, when am I gonna
wake up already??!
[Renji]
Well done, Chigo!
Uh?
It's thanks to you that
Rukiruki's life was saved.
Thank you. I'm very grateful.
That's okay.
It was nothing.
It's not like I had
much choice anyway.
As a token of my
appreciation, I will
grant you your third
and final wish.
Huh?
What is it to be?
Oh. Well, let's see...
[Uryu]
His wish is that you'll wake
him up from this dream.
Isn't that right, Chigo?
[Chad]
Yes. After everything he's
done, he deserves it.
[Orihime]
That's right. The last wish
has got to go to Chigo.
But, you guys--
Well, all right then.
[Ichigo]
No, wait!
The Snow Crystal!
Huh??
[Rukia]
The Snow Crystal?
Yeah. Shiny, cold
and beautiful.
A priceless
treasure.
Really,
Chigo?
[Uryu]
You sure?
You bet. Why shouldn't I let
you guys have your wish granted?
After all, I'll wake up
from this dream sooner
or later anyway, right?
Wow, Chigo, thanks.
Yeah.
Whoa, you're
deeper than
I thought.
Oh, shut up and go with it
before I change my mind.
[Uryu]
You may
regret it later.
[Ichigo]
This whole dream's
nothing but regrets.
Behold, the
legendary treasure:
the Snow Crystal!
Ahh!
Whoa!
So this is the Snow Crystal...
White...cold... beautiful...
...and squishy?
Huh?...
What?
Whaaat??
It's a fish cake?!
Oh, wow, only a dream.
Thank goodness.
Why do I keep having these
strange dreams?...
Uh.
[Byakuya]
This episode of Bleach was
made to celebrate the
manga's tenth anniversary.
On behalf of the entire
animation staff, I want
to thank all of you loyal
viewers for your support.
[Ichigo]
Hold it! Thanking the
fans should be my job!
I mean, I'm the main hero!