The only reason I
continue to fight, is
because I have to win!
Those are the words
of someone who doesn't
know defeat.
Sorry to keep you
waiting, Ulquiorra.
I believe this is what
you wanted to see...
My Hollowfication!
[yelling]
Come back here!
Damn it! How far is he
planning to go?
Wait a minute...!
Are we above Las Noches'
canopy?!
That's right.
Under Aizen's orders,
two things are forbidden
below the canopy of Las
Noches...
The first is... Gran Rey
Cero, which exists only
for... an Espada.
And the second is.. the
sword release of Espadas
with the rank of 4 and
higher.
They are both so powerful,
that if released, they would
threaten to destroy Las
Noches itself.
Imprison...! Murcielago!
[gasping]
Compose yourself.
You must hold your
stance...
...Extend your
consciousness. Do not
let your guard down.
[gasping]
[panting]
It's not possible.
That was too fast!
This can't be happening.
I couldn't react at all!
Even in my Hollowfied
state!
The power of your
so-called Hollowfication
has increased.
You're even capable of
wearing the mask longer.
And yet...
I didn't expect it
would shatter that
easily.
[gasping]
How unfortunate for you.
Watch closely.
I see it!
[gasping]
[grunting]
Look at that! There's
a hole in the sky!
The sky of Las Noches. It
was fake this whole time.
Orihime?
Uh?
We're not out of
the woods yet, but
I'm glad you're all
right.
Don't worry.
Ichigo will be
fine. He'll win.
Uhh... mm.
Come on, Ichigo.
Don't make a
liar out of me.
You can do it.
What is it
you're waiting for?
Fire your Getsuga.
[gasping]
Fire it at me.
That's when you are at
your most lethal. A form
capable of holding up
even against an Espada.
And we both know Getsuga
is your most powerful
technique.
Fire it. Show it to me
and I will let you see...
The difference in
our strengths.
[gasping]
You serious!? You want
me to fire Getsuga?
Well allow me to help
you with your request!
Getsuga tensho!!
It's just as
I had thought.
You are, after all,
merely human.
You're not hurt?!
No, not quite. Though your
black Getsuga is actually
very similar to our own
Cero.
Cero? Don't compare
it to something like
that!
Ah, that's
right.
I forgot you
haven't gotten
to see it, yet.
Since this is your last
battle, I will show it to
you. This is the black
Cero that an Espada can
discharge in a released
state.
Cero Oscuras.
[grunting]
[struggling]
Orihime!
Damn it, Ichigo, what's
happening up there?!
Uryu?
Do you think it's possible
that by using your powers,
you could lift us above
that canopy?
At that moment, I
might've known she
would request that of me.
But what was I to
do? I couldn't say
no to her.
Can you please?
I did want to help. And I
would soon come to regret
that decision.
Damn it!
[struggling]
[grunting]
Do you understand
it, now?
[struggling]
I'm afraid that no matter
how closely your form and
techniques resemble an
Arrancar's...
The difference in our
power will always be as
great as that between
heaven and earth.
Imitating Hollows seems
like a perfectly logical path
for you to follow in order to
gain more power.
It's not surprising you
would do that to become
stronger, but you will
never be my equal.
[struggling]
Getsuga...
I told you,
it's useless!
Why won't you
let go of your
sword?
[choking]
You've experienced the
vast difference in our powers,
and yet, you actually still
think you can defeat me?
[choking]
Difference... in
power... that doesn't
matter at all.
You think I'd give up
just because you're more
powerful than me?
From our first battle
together, I knew that
you were stronger.
At this point, no
matter how many times I
see how powerful you are,
it won't make a
difference to me!
I am determined to see
this through to the end.
I refuse to
give up!
You should've realized
that by now.
I... will find a
way... to beat you!
[choking]
Ul...qui...orr...a.
That's nonsense.
[coughing]
Ichigo Kurosaki, those are
the words of someone who
doesn't know the true
despair of defeat.
[struggling]
Since you don't
understand, I
will teach you.
This is what true despair
looks like.
How incredible!
I learned this when I
went through Garganta.
I realized on the way
here, I could use this
technique in Hueco Mundo
as well.
I wish I'd figured this
out a bit sooner, I could've
used this in some of my
earlier battles.
Uryu...
[gasping]
What the hell
was that?!
It came from
up above!
What's that force?!
Spirit Energy?!
It's too different...
This isn't like any
Spirit Energy I've ever
experienced before!
It's not just
powerful...
It feels... thick and
heavy. It's as if there's
an ocean spread above the
sky.
It's something other
than Spirit Energy.
I feel like it
could crush us!
I've never...
I know. Let's hurry!
Resurreccion Segunda
Etapa.
[gasping]
Among the Espadas...
I, alone, have found a
way to achieve this
second-stage release...
I have not even shown
this form to the great
Lord Aizen.
[struggling]
So you have seen my
imposing form and you
still have the will
to fight?
He's not so confused
that he can't feel
fear.
And yet, those are not the
eyes of someone who has
given up.
Does this mean he
actually believes
he can win?
Very well.
I will make you realize
the depth my power, even
if I have to grind your
body into dust.
You will understand!!
Uh!
[gasping]
[groaning]
You are a fool...
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Ah!
Why would you challenge
an enemy that you can't
possibly defeat?
Most beings want to
preserve their life!
I can't comprehend
this!
You must be doing all of
this because of what you
humans call heart.
If so, it would seem to
be more of a liability
than a strength.
What stupidity. Because
you possess this antiquated
concept of heart, you have
chosen to lose your life.
[grunting]
I didn't decide to
fight you because I can
see myself winning this
battle...
The only reason I
continue to fight, is
because I have to win!
Have it your way.
[grunting]
I don't sense Ichigo's
Spiritual Pressure,
where is he?!
[panting]
So you've
come. How nice.
[gasping]
Ichigo.
You're just in
time. Watch closely.
[gasping]
Here is the man to whom
you've entrusted all
your hope.
Bear witness as his life
comes to an end.
[screaming]
No!
What can we do?! Ichigo
was supposed to be in charge
of this episode's preview,
but he's in no shape to--
Relax. I'll take
over for him.
Great! Then would you
please dance wearing an
Afro wig and a tight
dress, just like Yoruichi
did in the end credits?!
Huh?