[theme music]
ICHIGO: [sigh]
We're still screwed.
Because even if that
bald guy I beat up
was telling the truth
about Rukia being
held in some white tower, we
still don't know where it is,
or which road we need
to take to get there.
-[gasp]
-Hey, wait a minute?
What about this map?
This would help us avoid
running into any more captains
out there.
HANATARO: It's Rukia Kuchiki
you're looking for, isn't it?
I thought so.
It all makes sense now.
And that means the white
tower you were talking about
must be the repentance cell.
If you'll trust
me, I can help you.
I know a hidden way
into that tower.
GANJU: [sigh] I have
to admit, I wouldn't
have thought of using
the sewer system.
-Yes.
Since it runs underground
throughout the Seireitei,
we can use it to go any
place we want safely,
without running
into any trouble.
-I don't get how
something so big
can be kept a secret
from everyone.
It wasn't even hidden very
well under that flagstone.
-Everybody knows that it
exists, but they don't use it.
No one will ever think of
looking for us down here.
-How do you know that?
-Only a small number of Squad
Four relief and aid workers
happen to know the
layout of these tunnels.
So besides me, there really
aren't very many people
who know their way
around down here.
-Oh, I get it.
You Squad Four guys have to know
your way around these tunnels,
because it's a supply
route for delivery relief
and aid to all the
different units.
-[laughs] Well, [sigh] it's
not so much that it's a supply
route, but rather that we're
the ones who have to keep these
tunnels cleaned up.
Actually, Squad Four
does seem to end up
with more than its share of
the menial chores. [laugh]
-You know, he's
actually got me feeling
a little bit sorry for
these Squad Four losers.
HANATARO: Oh, but
it isn't all bad.
There are some
advantages, too. [laughs]
-Hanataro.
-Yeah?
-Why are you doing this for us?
Why should our mission
be any of your concern?
After all, we're
still your enemies.
Instead of the white
tower, you could
be leading us into a trap.
-Ichigo, don't.
-Before we follow
you any further,
I want to know why
you're helping us.
-I know more about than you
think, from listening to Rukia.
She talked a lot
about Ichigo Kurosaki.
-Huh?
-Please save her.
You've got to.
Please rescue Ms. Rukia.
YASOCHICKA: Here's the
latest situation report.
Ikkaku Madarame and Yumichika
Ayasegawa, both of Squad 11,
have apparently been withdrawn
from the front lines, effective
immediately.
It's reported that both
high-ranking officers
have sustained serious injuries.
A detailed damage assessment
for the entire squad
is currently under way.
But at the moment,
all we have to go on
are unconfirmed preliminary
reports of the day's action,
which would seem to
indicate that Squad 11 was
almost completely annihilated.
[gasping]
-What?
That's impossible.
-Not Squad 11.
MAN: How could a
handful of Ryoka
have done so much damage
in just a few hours?
-Ugh, that Squad's pathetic.
-Three of the Ryoka have
been positively identified.
And two of these
are known to have
taken a member of
Squad Four hostage.
Intelligence indicates that
this group is heading this way.
However, since a
short time ago, we've
been unable to detect
their spiritual pressure.
So their whereabouts
are now unknown.
-[grunt]
WOMAN: Obviously,
our intelligence
leaves something to be desired.
-You know, now that
I think about it,
it's been awhile since our
fourth seat has reported back
in.
We better send someone to
check on the West 20 region.
Who knows?
He may have been defeated, too.
-Are you serious?
Isn't the fourth seat in your
squad Jiroba, the wind scythe?
-That's right.
-First Jidanbo, now his brother?
Can they both really
have been defeated?
-What the hell is going on here?
-[gasp]
-Ah, I've been
telling you for years
that Squad 11 is overrated.
-Well, what an unbelievable
mess this is turning into.
Right, Renji?
WOMAN: --that much is for sure.
RANGIKU: You're not helping
things by spreading rumors.
We don't even know
what happened here.
-What's that about?
MAN: Come on, come on.
Take it easy, Rangiku.
HANATARO: After
Rukia was captured
and before she was transferred
to the repentance cell--
or the white tower,
as you call it-- she
was held in a cell within
the Squad Six barracks.
At the time, I was assigned
to cleaning duty there.
So I saw her when
she was brought in.
To be honest, I was
scared of her at first.
I mean, she is
nobility after all.
But then, I--
-Then what?
-On that first day,
when I spoke to her, I--
I'm so sorry to
disturb you, Ms. Rukia.
But I have to come in and
start my cleaning chores now.
-There's no need for you
to address me formally.
HANATARO: Um, but I, um--
-I'd rather you
just call me Rukia.
-Uh, but, um, all right, then.
Rukia, thank you.
-No, thank you.
-[laugh] You're welcome!
Her voice was so gentle.
She was so much kinder
than I expected her to be.
It was such a relief to me.
From that day on, my cleaning
chores at the barracks
stopped being something I
dread and became something
I actually look forward to.
And little by
little, Rukia started
telling me all kinds of things.
Can I ask another
question, Rukia?
What it really like over there,
in the world of the living?
What kind of food do they eat?
And tell me, what kind
of drinks do they have?
I'm sorry.
I know I talk too much.
You don't have to
answer me, Rukia.
[laugh] I'm sorry.
-They have a drink called juice
that comes in paper cartons.
-Oh!
What kind of a drink is that?
What does juice taste like?
-It's good, but it's tricky.
-Oh.
Mm.
-[sigh] It was hard to open.
There was a certain technique.
-That's hard to imagine.
How could there be
any kind of technique
you couldn't have
mastered, Rukia?
-Well, it was difficult.
You might not have
been able to master it.
There was this guy who
showed me how to do it.
HANATARO: Tell me some more.
What else did you see in
the world of the living?
Were there any strange things?
-Did you know a mod
soul can be inserted
into inanimate objects,
as well as the living?
-Do you mean those
illegal things?
RUKIA: Yes.
I saw a guy put one
into a stuffed doll?
-You mean into a child's toy?
Some animal-shaped thing
with cotton and stuffing?
But why would anybody do
something so irresponsible?
That just seems crazy.
-You're right.
There are some crazy
ones, both there and here.
-She told me a lot about
the world of the living.
But almost all the
stories Rukia told
me had one thing in common.
It seemed there
was always mention
of this one person
in particular.
Until one day, an official
execution order came for her.
-It is as I said.
Do I need to repeat myself?
25 days from now, she'll go to
the central execution grounds,
where she will suffer
the ultimate punishment.
That is the final decision
of the Soul Society.
-Rukia, is the person you
gave your Soul Reaper powers
to the same person you always
mention in your stories
about the world of the living?
-Yes.
His name was Ichigo Kurosaki.
I only spent two months there
in that world with Ichigo.
But somehow, even after
such a short time,
I felt I could trust
him with my very life.
Because of me-- because of
me, Ichigo's own destiny
was changed and became twisted.
And he was hurt terribly.
There's no forgiving
what I've done to him.
HANATARO: Rukia sounded so
sad as she said those words.
-Sounds to me like this Rukia's
one strange Soul Reaper,
don't you think?
-Yeah.
She's something else.
-Huh?
-And that's why we're
going to rescue her.
-Hey, stop.
Where are you taking off too?
Wait for me, Ichigo.
-Did I say something wrong?
GANJU: Ichigo, wait up!
RUKIA: I only spent
two months there
in that world with Ichigo.
But somehow, even after
such a short time,
I felt I could trust
him with my very life.
Because of me--- because of
me, Ichigo's own destiny was
changed and became twisted.
And he was hurt terribly.
There's not forgiving
what I've done to him.
ICHIGO: You're wrong, Rukia.
All of this was my fault.
I swear, there's no way
I'm gonna let you die.
Rukia!
-OK.
The coast is clear.
You two can come up now.
This is the closest
opening to the white tower.
GANJU: [grunt] About time, too.
I've breathed enough
sewer air to gag a hippo.
-There it is, up there.
That's the white tower.
GANJU: This may be the
closest sewer opening,
but we've still got
a long way to go.
You know, I've got
a bad feeling this
isn't going to be an easy job.
-The mist is starting to clear.
Time to move.
-What, Ichigo?
What do you see?
-There's someone over
there by the stairs.
[gasping]
-It's been a while.
I wonder if you still
remember my face.
-Oh, you'll be gone and
forgotten soon enough.
But first, I've got a
whole mountain of payback
I'm going to extract
from you, Renji Abarai.
RENJI: You not only remembered
my face, but my name as well.
You're full of surprises.
-Thanks for the compliment.
-Whoa, who is this guy?
His spiritual pressure is on
a completely different level
from all those guys we
were tangling with before.
[whimpering]
-No, I can't believe it.
That's Renji Abarai.
He's the lieutenant
of Squad Six.
-A lieutenant?
-I must admit, I'm
surprised to see you.
I was certain you'd
be a dead man after I
saw Captain Kuchiki
attack you like that.
-Hey, wait!
Don't go rushing in, Ichigo!
-I don't know how you ever
managed to survive that.
But it would seem that
there is more to you
than I first believed.
But as I told you,
I'm going to kill
the one who stole
Rukia's powers.
So this is as far as you go.
Because as long as
you're still alive,
Rukia can never
regain her powers.
-What do you care about that,
when you've just sentenced her
to death!
[grunt] I'm going to
cut you to pieces!
-Just go ahead and try!
[grunting]
-They've just started.
He's going up against Renji.
The Ryoka defeated
the third seat.
Now we'll see if he can
defeat a lieutenant.
If so, then he may truly be
a worthy opponent for me.
-Kenny, I don't
understand something.
If you can't even sense
other spiritual pressuer,
then how could you tell they're
fighting from miles away?
-[laughs] I'm just
strange that way.
-Yeah, you got that right.
-Have you two found anything?
-No, not a trace of them.
-It's been hours since
these Ryoka crossed over.
Our casualties keep rising, and
we still can't track them down.
-Obviously, they've planned
this attack out thoroughly.
The way our response
has been handled so far,
I'm not even sure the
captains and lieutenants
even know what they're doing.
MAN: Come check this out!
They just found
Jiroba of Squad Seven.
And he's face down
and unconscious!
-What?
No way!
-Huh?
-(WHISPERING) They're gone.
-Indeed.
Obviously, Ichigo
and the others must
be doing quite a
number out there.
I've never seen
so much security.
And it just keeps
getting tighter.
-Mm, that's true.
But I think you and I can
handle whatever comes along.
After all, we've
done great so far.
What is it?
Are you sensing something?
URYU: I'm feeling strong
spiritual pressure
all of a sudden.
One of them is Ichigo, but the
other one-- it's Renji Abarai!
You sure ran into a tough
one this time, Ichigo.
[gasp]
[laughter]
-[gasp] [shout]
-Hey, are you getting
sick or something?
-You don't look so good.
Got a fever?
-Thank you.
But I was just fine
until you two appeared.
-That's good to hear.
I was just a little worried,
because you do space out
sometimes, you know.
Are you ready to go?
-Aw, that was no fun.
-Yeah, totally boring.
ORIHIME: Let's get going
while the coast is clear.
YASUTORA: Ichigo's spirit
energy is increasing.
I can feel it.
But his opponent's spiritual
pressure is so strong,
it's off the charts.
I better hurry.
[grunting]
-Now he's doomed!
No matter how strong
Ichigo might have become,
there's no way he could
hope to defeat a lieutenant.
-Hold on.
I wouldn't bet any money
against him just yet.
Take another look.
Something's happening.
[grunting]
-Oh, wow.
Ichigo just pinned
Lieutenant Abarai right up
against the wall.
Ganju, this Ichigo guy-- what
kind of a human being is he?
-Watching this
fight, I'm beginning
to wonder that myself.
-So, tell me the truth, Ichigo.
Do you actually
believe you're going
to be able to rescue Rukia.
-I do!
RENJI: Even if somehow
you were to defeat me,
there are still 11
more lieutenants left.
And then, of course, above
them are 13 full-fledged squad
captains.
You would have to utterly defeat
every single one us to even
have a chance of
reaching the tower.
You can't possibly believe
that you could pull that off.
-I don't care about the odds.
I don't care about how many
captains or lieutenants there
are.
I'll defeat them all,
every one of them.
I'll defeat anyone who makes the
mistake of getting in my way!
-Where does that come from?
You know, this confidence of
yours borders on the insane.
Such a quality would
almost be admirable
if it weren't so irrational.
So, your Zanpakuto
has changed, has it?
It's a mistake to think you're
stronger just because of that.
ICHIGO: Just like it's a
mistake to get to conceited!
[grunts]
-Now roar, Zabimaru!
[shouting]
-I can't stop it! [grunts]
-Ichigo!
-Oh!
Is he dead?
-You seem to think just because
you fought me once before, back
there in the world
of the living,
that now you know my true power!
Well, let me tell you
something, you amateur.
Whenever captain or
lieutenant-ranked Soul Reapers
are sent outside, severe
limits are placed on our powers
so that we won't adversely
affect the world of the living.
My strength right
now is five times
what it was that
first day we met.
So no matter how confident you
are, or how strong you become,
there's still no way
you can defeat me.
ICHIGO: I see.
-Huh?
-Hm?
ICHIGO: Then I suppose that
means that last attack of yours
was your best shot.
[grunt]
Because that didn't have
any effect on me at all.
So thank you.
If all I have to worry about
is 11 more like that one,
then I think I'm going
to be just fine, Renji.
Heh.
-[grunt] I'm going
to enjoy this.
[theme music]
-As I said before,
we Soul Reapers
have our powers severely limited
in the world of the living.
My strength right now
is five times greater
than it was when
I last fought you.
ICHIGO: I've been
training, and I'm
10 times stronger than before!
RENJI: Then I'm 100
times stronger than that!
ICHIGO: I'm 1,000 times
stronger than that!
-Actually, I'm 10,000
times stronger.
ICHIGO: Than I'm
100,000 times stronger.
RENJI: Well, I'm a million
times stronger than that.
ICHIGO: Too bad.
I'm plus 10 million
times stronger!
RENJI: Than I'm a million
bajillion times stronger.
ICHIGO: I'm infinity
times stronger!
And that's that.