Let's cut loose!
Ahhh!
[grunting]
Ready? Get 'em,
Stark.
You will regret your
insolence toward me! I
will turn you all to
dust!
I am the emperor!
Barragan Ruizenban!
I am the god of Hueco
Mundo!
[grunting]
As you are about to
discover, the only thing
that is absolute in this
world is my power!
The fact is, I am
supremely powerful. And
as such, the world should
be under my control.
What? What's happening
here?
You're the one who gave
me the idea.
That is your own power,
the only thing that is
absolute in this world.
[gasping]
You bastard! What have
you done with your right
arm?!
What game are you
playing?!
It's no game. My arm's
inside you!
Curse you, you ant! How
dare you defy a god in
this way?!
Your insolence will doom
you to destruction!
Farewell, King of Hueco
Mundo. In the end, it
turned out you shared the
same concerns as most mortals.
...A desire to avoid
aging, coupled with a
great fear of death.
My goodness, it appears
the Soul Reapers have
actually defeated him---
You should pay attention,
or those may be your last
words.
There's always time to
die. Why are you in such
a hurry? I'm not going
anywhere.
Hm.
Our Number Two just
died... and he doesn't
give a damn.
Shameful.
Rose! You can come out
now!...
Hachi crushed him!
Easy!
Aw, come on! Quit
goofin' around and
come out!
Hey!
You can let go!
There's a certain
artistic style required
when it comes to climbing
out of rubble!
Oh yeah? Well why
don't you work on the
art of not getting buried
in the first place?
So Hachi did it, huh? His
opponent looked pretty
powerful too.
Yeah. But I would have
liked it if we had
settled things a bit
sooner.
And why's that?
You don't know?
Once your comrade falls
in battle, you're gonna
want revenge.
You think so? He doesn't
seem like the type to me.
That what's unnerving
about him.
I mean who wouldn't be
affected by the death of
a comrade in arms?
If he's shaken up by his
death, we should strike
while his guard is down.
And if he's seething with
anger because of it, we need
to attack him before he snaps.
So then what you're
saying is that the more
losses they suffer, the
stronger they become?
Well, if that's the case,
perhaps we should consider
our next move cautiously.
Well, we can
talk all day.
Or we could
strike first!
Time to kick ass!
Slam Tengumaru!!
[roaring]
That won't work!
No way!
[grunting]
Hm?!
You won't escape!
He's moving slower than
before. Guess he is the
type that gets shaken by
his comrade's death.
Damn it.
Stark? Stark!
Stay focused will you!
I thought you were going
to handle avenging
Barragan's death?!
You are pathetic!
I told you revenge is not
my thing. I've had enough.
And it looks like Lord
Aizen has no intention of
helping us out either.
They're strong. I get
that. I've done all that
I can here.
If we continue to fight
them, someone's going
to die.
Let's just go home and
take a nap.
Stark!!!
What are you, stupid?!
You're Espada Number
One! Start acting like
it!
Up until now, all you've
been doing is trying to
act cool. You haven't
been seriously fighting
those wimps at all!
Have you completely
forgotten that Lord Aizen
made you number one?!
That means he's counting
on your power!
So if you don't want to
see all of your comrades
wind up dead and gone, then
you gotta get up and fight!
Fine!-Just lay there! Do
whatever you want. But
I'm doing my own thing!
Hm?
You got him?
Not exactly. He's just
not moving around yet.
He's either watching us
or planning something.
Whatever he's up to, we
can't really make a move
until all that dust clears.
So you have now lost your
chance to attack him,
because you botched your
previous attack.
I'm truly amazed.
Shut up! I'll still get
him, just wait and watch.
Huh?
There he is!
Yeah thanks! Man! Why
is he shooting like
that?!
Hey! Would you stop
firing like that!
Get ready-he's coming!
Only because you
decided to act up.
[yelling]
You kept me waiting up
there.
We didn't mean to keep
you in suspense!
Huh?
Up until now, you've
made it difficult for us
to attack you, you
coward!
Stop playin' hard
to get!
Wha--? You have a talking
gun? Now, that's what I
call weird.
What of it?! It's
nowhere near as weird as
that star-shaped hairdo
of yours, ya jerk!
I told you to
calm down.
You've got to be kidding
me! I'm the only one
taking any action here!
Hey!
[yelling]
The timing between his
shots is completely
different than earlier.
Does that mean he's not
the one doing the
shooting?
Stop it!-Stop shooting!
No!-Why should I??!
Bulls eye!
[grunting]
Ah-ha! I knew it! I
had a feeling you weren't
the one calling the shots!
What's your point?
Why is it you won't
attack me? Too stricken
with grief?
Yeah-something like that.
You idiot! Your opponent
is reading your every
emotion! You're an open
book!
Just shut up!
What a surprise! I was
under the impression that
Hollows ever had any
emotions or feelings!
You're one to talk. You
act like a Hollow yourself.
If I remember right, you
had a mask on earlier.
Oh, yeah. You're right.
You talkin' about this?
Let's cut loose!
Hey, come on! Do
something! NOW!
[grunting]
What are you waiting
for?! Go after him!
You know he's trying to
trick us into chasing him...
So what?!
There's no way you'd
lose to that clown!
Guess I have no choice.
Well hello there!
Now Stark!
Right.
Whoa!
Time to Play.
Kinshara!
You're late! If we don't
coordinate our attacks
better, there's no point
in fighting him two on one!
Sorry. As I've explained
to your earlier, there's a real
art to making an impression
in any kind of situation.
I don't care!
I'd say, he looks a
bit more motivated now.
I'm not too
sure about that.
Fighting cowardly types
who lack motivation is
just not my style.
It's not as satisfying
when we finally defeat
them!
Ahhh!
Stark!-Dodge it! Move!
I know what to do.
You're not in
the clear, yet!
That blast of yours
is not powerful enough to
knock out my Kinshara.
What?!
Nice work, Rose!
Huh?!
Here we go, Tengumaru.
It's about to get a lot
hotter, so deal with it.
Hifuki no Kozuchi!
[yelling]
[grunting]
Is she gone?! I think
not!
There you are!
If you think that's
enough to fake me out,
you're stupid!
[screaming]
What are you doing?!
Come on, what am I doing?!
What exactly do you think
you're doing, idiot?!
I've been charging at
this one for hours,
trying to lure her in for
my finishing blow!
You've got some nerve
interrupting my big plan,
shorty!
Huh?!
Hey Lisa! Just what you
do think you're doing?!
You two lovebirds can
settle your quarrel
later, after I finish
this battle.
What did you say?!
What was that? Do you
really believe you can
handle me all by yourself?
No-of course not.
Well then, if that's not
what you're thinking... are
the three of you going to
fight me?
No, that's not my
plan...
Enough already! This is
getting annoying, Lisa! I'm
ready to get this done!
Well, I'm aware of
that. I was making
sure.
Do you mind filling me in
on exactly what it is you
guys are talking about?
It has nothing to do with
you.
That's where you're wrong.
You two may be used to
fighting together,
but I haven't fought with
either one of you.
If the three of us are
going to fight together,
I need to know what
your plan is, so we can
coordinate our attacks to
achieve a successful
result...
What are you talking
about, shorty?! Nobody
said Lisa and I are used
to fighting together.
Huh?
Our personalities
are completely different...
And yet, there's one simple
understanding that both of
us do share.
The actual time we can
fight full power is very
limited.
That's why first, we needed to
find out what our opponent's
fighting style was.
[gasping]
You thought that three of
us would be fighting you.
Well you're mistaken.
There's two of us, and
one Soul Reaper. Got it?!
Hm. How amusing.
Are you all right?
No-I am not alright.
These two guys are
really strong.
There ya go-you're
whining again!
I can't help it. When
they put on those masks
their Spirit Energy more
than doubles in intensity
and besides that,
there are two of them!
And I'm here by myself.
You're not by yourself.
Hm?
The reason you were able
to make this far, is
because you weren't by
yourself.
Long ago, you were
alone.
But ever since then,
we've always been
together.
If we just fight
together, we can easily
beat those two.
Maybe you're right...
I get it.
Ready?
Let's do it.
There's been a change
in his Spiritual
Pressure...
Where is he?
Look-he's above us!
Huh? Up there,
what's that?!
[howling]
What the hell
is he doing?
Hey...
What?
You see that?
Yeah, I know-He's
unarmed.
Where did his gun go?
Who the heck knows? I'd
say he's taunting us.
He's saying he doesn't
need a weapon!
Ready? Get
'em, Stark.
He's coming!
I can see that!
[growling]
Slam! Tengumaru!
Play. Kinshara!
These things are like
flames! There's no end to
them!
How troublesome! I've
always hated peculiar
magic like this. It's
very annoying!
Kinshara Sokyoku,
Number 11.
Izayoi Bara.
It appears your technique
is even more like magic!
Surely you jest! My
technique is an art!
Magic and art have
similarities, but are
quite different.
Hm?!
Ah!
Move around all you want.
I'll still crush you!!
What?!
[coughing]
Damn it! Hey Rose!
Can you hear me?
What is it?
I figured it out! They're
not flames! They're a
Cero!
Every one of those wolves
came out from the
magazine of that Espada's
gun! Each one of those
creatures is a Cero that
he deliberately fired.
And they're dangerous
when they explode at
close range!
[howling]
[gasping]
Damn it!
They are not Ceros.
Regular Ceros don't have
enough power to mortally
wound Hollows with the kind
of strength that you possess.
I took my own soul and
tore it into pieces and I
have made those pieces
obey me like partners, so
that now I may use them
as weapons to destroy
you.
These wolf-shaped
warheads are a deadly
combination of both of
us.
You see-that is our
Ressureccion, the true
power of Espada Number 1,
Coyote Stark and
Lilinette Gingerback.
[groaning]
Stark.
What is it?
Looks like they can't
handle our power.
I'd say that
you're right.
Let's finish this-now!
Okay.
Get ready...
[howling]
[growling]
[gasping]
Let's go.
[panting]
This game's over. Run
and I'll let you live.
We don't run.
I see.
There's no choice. I
don't like the term
'finishing blow'.
But that's exactly what
this is..
[gasping]
I'm not alone...
No, I'm not alone
anymore...