THEME SONG: [SINGING
IN JAPANESE]
-Uh.
Uh.
Where am I?
But I'm not dead, at
least I don't think I am.
YORUICHI (OFFSCREEN):
Ah, you're finally awake.
-Huh?
You're Yoruichi Ah.
It was you who saved
my life, wasn't it?
Thanks for doing that.
-Be thankful to your
strong life force.
Without it, you never would have
survived such serious wounds,
no matter what I did.
-Wounds?
That's right.
In fact, I thought
he'd killed me.
Huh?
Oh no!
Dammit! [grunting]
-Hold still, you fool.
You're going to open
up those wounds.
Don't you realize how
badly you're hurt?
-I've got to go help Chad.
I think he's in danger.
Ah.
-Chad is OK.
Now just relax.
-Ah.
-Orihime and Uryu are fine, too.
-Huh?
-Chad was lucky to
fight who he did.
He left Chad wounded but alive.
Orihime and Uryu have
avoided confrontation
and so far haven't
gotten a scratch.
-That's good.
-So you just stay here in
the barrier and rest a while.
-Yeah, all right.
-Half of your organs
were crushed after all.
If it hadn't been
for this thing,
you would have been
sliced in half.
Fortunately for you
it looks like it
absorbed much of the impact.
-That thing was on me?
-Yes, it was.
I was surprised to
find you were still
carrying this object around.
-Are are you sure that
I was carrying it?
-What do you mean?
How could you have it
on you and not know it?
-Yeah, well, I um I had
it when I fought Renji,
and I think it saved my
life in that fight, too.
I figured that it was
a good luck charm,
and I should probably
hang onto it.
Hey, what are you
doing with that?
-I'm throwing it away.
There's something really
evil about this, Ichigo.
Having it makes me
feel uncomfortable.
-But you said it probably
saved my life back there.
-Uh.
-Wouldn't it make sense to
hang on to something like that?
-No!
I don't care.
-No, don't!
Ah.
And that was that.
It sank like a stone
in the waterway.
What?
Oh, you're probably wondering
about this Hanataro guy.
He's from Squad
Four, but he's OK.
Technically, he's
the enemy, but he's
the one who healed my wounds.
It is pretty weird that
I still have this though.
I could have sworn
he got rid of it.
-Give it to me.
I'll take care of it.
-Huh?
No way.
This is mine, and
I'm gonna keep it.
-Hand it over!
End of discussion.
-Uh, yes, sir.
Please, please take it.
It's all yours.
-Hm.
It's probably not possible.
But all the same,
can't be too careful.
-Well, you certainly are strong.
It's surprising.
-What do you mean by that?
You carried me all the way
here despite being so small.
-Oh, that.
Lifting things is no problem
for me, once I revert
to my original form.
-Ah, right.
Original form, I forgot.
Hm?
What do you mean, original form?
-Oh, that's right.
I've never actually shown you
and your friends my true form,
have I?
Having come this far,
there's no reason
to keep it hidden anymore.
-Huh?
-So behold, here is
what I really look like.
-Uh.
Uh-- uh-- you're a girl.
-Yeah, you're even more shocked
than I thought you would be.
Can't blame you.
I guess people always
assume I'm a man because
of the voice I use
when I'm in cat form.
-Eh.
-No matter how many times
I reveal my true form,
it's always fun to see
the reaction I get.
Though honestly,
I thought someone
like you would handle
it a bit better.
-But, but I-- I
thought you were a cat.
-Cats don't talk.
Use your head, Ichigo.
Anyway, I think that's
enough surprises for now.
Let's get back to
the business at hand,
and I'll show you how
I carried you here.
-Oh.
-First of all, I
used this device.
-Ah!
Will you please put
some clothes on?
-Oh, right.
Sorry about that.
It's been so long since I had
to wear clothes, I forgot.
Though I'm surprised at you.
You're more innocent
and naive than you look.
Was that the first time
you ever saw a girl naked?
Huh?
-Never mind.
-Do you want another look?
You never know.
Life is short, and you
might not get the chance
to see a hot young
girl like me again.
-Hey.
Shut up, will ya?
-Just kidding.
Oh, you have no sense of
humor, do you know that?
You really ought
to take it easy,
or you're going to open up those
wounds of yours all over again.
-Would you please just shut
up and put some pants on?
Dammit.
Now, I'm bleeding again.
-I had forgotten
how uncomfortable
it is having to wear clothes.
-So you put spirit energy in
this, and it allows you to fly?
-That's right.
There's not another
one like it anywhere,
not even here in
the Soul Society.
Impressive, wouldn't you say?
-Yeah, but I can't
help but wonder
how you got your paws on
such a valuable device.
-Hm?
-You can change forms and
do it so effortlessly.
And you have the
ability to heal wounds.
Now this.
Yoruichi, who are you?
-I am-- Ah.
-Eh.
That spiritual pressure.
It's him, again.
-It's coming from the Senzaikyu.
Stop, Ichigo.
-The tower is where I told
Ganju and Hanataro to go to.
I have to get there
and save them.
-What good do you think you
can do in your condition?
-Just who do think is going
to save them if I don't?
Fly.
Eh.
-Ichigo.
Uh.
You're such a fool.
-I sensed some faint,
spiritual pressure
moving toward the Shishinro.
And I thought it was some
powerful presence suppressing
its spiritual
pressure to hide it.
But it was only a big fat bug.
-Uh.
-Rukia, no.
Stay out of it.
-Ah.
I've got to stop this
or the Shiba clan's
going to lose another one.
Oh.
-Oh, no, Rukia.
-All this time I've spent
in this Sekkiseki cell
has weakened my spiritual power.
I-- I can't even move.
-Dammit.
What incredible
spiritual pressure.
Just standing here,
facing him is taxing.
No measly little tricks
are going to do me any good
against a superior
power like his.
Huh.
Oh.
I'm just going to have
to take my chances.
Now, let's see how you
like my tears of blood.
-Huh?
Be gone.
My sword is not for
killing insignificant pests
such as you.
-Ah.
Ah.
Oh.
Where do you think you're going?
-Apparently, I didn't make
myself completely clear.
I spared you and
told you to be gone.
-Ha ha.
Maybe your noble
families have cowered
to run from a threat like that,
but no Sheba man ever would.
-I see.
You're from the
Shiba clan, are you?
-Oh, no.
-Forgive me for
taking it easy on you.
Now, I'll make sure you
don't leave here alive.
-Ah, what's this
from so far away?
-Brother, please, no.
-Scatter.
Senbonzakura.
-Ah, what the hell?
A blade just disappeared.
-Run away!
-Ah.
-Oh, Ganju.
-Brother, please stop.
Ah.
-Hm?
-Whew.
Close one.
Pretty dangerous.
Why don't we leave it at
that, Captain Kuchiki?
-Captain Ukitake.
-Hey there, Rukia.
It's good to see you.
Are you all right?
-What are you doing
here, Captain?
-Well, I could ask
you the same thing.
After all, releasing a
Zanpakuto on a place like this
is a first class offense,
even if it's to repel Ryoka.
What were you thinking, Kuchiki?
-The wartime exemption
allows the unrestricted use
of Zanpakuto.
-War exemption?
Has the Ryoka infiltration
gotten that bad?
Was it a Ryoka
that killed Aizen?
What spiritual pressure is this?
Clearly, it's at the
level of a captain,
but I don't
recognize him at all.
-That spiritual
pressure, impossible.
Ichigo.
(MUSIC LYRICS): If you
want to see some action,
gotta be the center
of attraction.
Make sure that they
got their eyes on you,
like the face that
they see on a magazine.
-It's it's-- huh?
-Are You OK, Hanataro?
I wouldn't have
sent you on ahead
if I'd known it was
going to be so rough.
-Thanks, but it's OK.
I'm fine.
Rukia, I've come to
get you out of here.
-Uh huh.
-Uh.
What kind of look is that?
I've come here to save you.
You could at least try
to act like you're happy.
-Ah.
We should go now, brother.
Take even one step or try to
come after me, and I'll, I'll,
I will never ever forgive you.
You are going to die,
so why not stay put
and live a few seconds longer?
You're a fool, Ichigo.
I told you never to
try and come after me.
I told you, I'd never
forgive you if you did.
Now, you're all cut up, and
there is worse yet to come.
-And maybe so.
Some other time
you can yell at me
all you want to about my coming
here, after I defeat him.
-Ichigo.
-What?
Don't tell me you actually
think I would give up
after I came all this way.
-It's just--
-'Cause I won't.
Don't even ask me.
I came here to save you, and
that's what I'm gonna do.
Oh, and from now on, I'm
ignoring all your opinions.
You're coming with me whether
you want to or not, dammit.
You got that, huh?
I'm the rescuer here.
You just shut up.
-What, what did you say?
Who do you think you are,
ordering me around like that?
A rescuer isn't supposed
to ignore the rescuee.
-Yeah?
And what kind of rescuee
complains about the rescue?
Why don't you just go sit
down and tremble in fear
and cry out, save me, save
me, like you're supposed to.
-Uh, I don't need to be saved.
And I do not tremble.
-Bluh.
-Hm.
You haven't changed a bit.
What's the use?
I might as well save
my breath, since you
don't listen to anything I say.
-Well, what do you expect?
All you ever do is worry
about me and scold me.
Maybe you should try worrying
about yourself for a change.
-Ichigo.
-Don't you worry.
I'm not dying today.
Fact is, I've gotten a lot
stronger while you were away.
Byakuya, what do you
know of this man?
-I know enough.
He has no relation to the
man you're thinking about.
This one here is nothing,
nothing but a Ryoka.
I'll destroy him, and
this will all end.
He'll be dead, and this trifling
invasion of his will be over.
-Look at you, taking
everything so slow and casual.
All that time Rukia
and I were talking,
you could have been attacking.
But you just stood there.
-Who do you think
you're talking to?
Do you suppose that
I need an opening
to come after the likes of you?
You should know better
than to talk so big, boy.
-Eh.
-Uh.
Just stay down, and
you'll be OK, Hanataro.
-OK.
-Oh.
To be so unaffected by
the spiritual pressure,
you must have improved
a great deal indeed.
I don't know how you managed
to regain the powers of a Soul
Reaper, but I can
tell you that you
should have stayed peacefully
in the world of the living.
Instead, you made the
mistake of coming here,
to throw away the life
I mercifully spared.
-I'm not going to
be throwing it away.
I'm gonna beat you
and then leave.
-I thought I warned you about
not talking so big, boy.
-He's gone.
-Flash step.
-Uh.
I saw your every
step, Byakuya Kuchiki.
Well, what do you
think, Kuchiki?
A little surprised?
Your movements were
all visible to me now.
-Don't confuse skill with a
little luck, you daft fool.
-So maybe you'd like to find
out if it was just luck.
Deh.
Yeh.
Huh?
Tsu.
-Ah, amazing.
Somehow Ichigo's got Captain
Kuchiki battling against him
as an equal.
-It's true.
I can't believe how much
Ichigo's strength has grown.
The fact that he was able
to read Byakuya's flash step
is simply astounding.
Still, Byakuya's power
is much more than that.
The flash step is mere
child's play for him.
I have to find a way
to stop this fight,
before he attacks in earnest.
Otherwise, Ichigo will be--
-Very well.
Obviously, you have
improved even more
than I would have
thought possible.
So you leave me no choice.
Before you become
too full of yourself,
I shall show you the
difference between us.
-Uh.
-The gap in power you
could never hope to bridge,
not even if you had
1,000 years of training.
-Run, Ichigo, run.
-Hm.
-Scatter.
-Uh.
-Ah.
-No way.
-It can't be.
-Been a long time,
hasn't it, Byakuya.
THEME SONG: Happy people.
Happy people.
Here we go.
Everybody stand up.
[singing japanese]
Keep your head
right up to the sky.
[singing japanese] Oh yeah.
Just call me anytime.
Oh, yeah.
[singing japanese]
Happy people's in the house.
[singing japanese] Happy
people's in the house.
[singing japanese]
Happy people in the house.
All right.
Happy people.
-Yoruichi, how'd you
transform yourself into a cat?
-Yeah, did you use a
special Kido or something?
-No, I just wore a cat costume.
-I see.
Is that really all it was?
-Sure, that makes sense.
If it was just a
costume, that'd be
pretty easy to transform for--
-What?