[THEME SONG IN JAPANESE - "AFTER
DARK"]
NARRATOR: In order
to save Orihime,
who was kidnapped
by the Arrancars,
Ichigo, Chad, Uryu,
Rukia and Renji
have snuck into Hueco Mundo.
On their journey to
Aizen's fortress,
they struggled against
endless attacks
from the Arrancar forces.
Upon breaking into the
fortress, the group
took five different paths
in search of Orihime.
Each of them
encountered an Arrancar
who, unknown to Ichigo and the
others, had been lying in wait.
A fierce battle begins.
Uryu is in a perilous
situation, as he
fights with Arrancar number
105, Cirucci Sanderwicci,
and her devastating
weapon, Golondrina.
Pesche, who has become lost
while searching for Nel,
walks right into the
middle of the fight,
and is surprisingly
able to help.
Furious, Cirucci initiates
her release state,
and the battle intensifies.
-Rip, Golondrina!
Which one of you shall
I slice up first?
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Ha!
Not so fast, four-eyes!
I haven't started carving yet.
-I see.
Those wings are shielding
her from my attacks.
That explains the reverberation
I've been hearing.
Those feathers are all
vibrating at very high speeds.
-All right!
Let's see you get
away from this!
-I have no choice.
-(GASPING) No!
What the hell?
What is that?
-It's too bad.
I was really hoping to
hold off on using this
until much later in the battle.
So, shall we continue?
I'm glad that I
took precautions.
-Huh?
-Before Kisuke and I
snuck out of the hospital,
I took a few useful items.
Using Kisuke's skills, we were
able to find a hidden storeroom
where I borrowed this.
Seele Schneider, the only
bladed quincy weapon!
It cuts through spirit pressure.
-He borrowed it from
a hidden storeroom
without getting permission?
You-- you thief!
-Shut up, will you?
Did you actually
ever hear me say
that I took it
without permission?
-Well then, did you
take it with permission?
-No, I didn't!
-See?
You took it without
permission, you thief!
URYU: I don't believe this.
Whose side are you on?
Argh!
Shut up, already!
-How can you talk to someone
like that who saved your life?
You're pathetic, Ichigo!
-I'm Uryu!
-What?
-How can you be this stupid?
-So, you're Uryu, huh?
-Yes, that's right!
-Say for a moment you are
Uryu, then who is Ishida?
-I told you before,
I'm Uryu Ishida!
-Ah ha!
I see!
Which means that
you're not Ishida Uryu!
-Just drop it, OK?
-You're a quincy.
Hm.
Look at you, a quincy
standing right before me.
-You know about us?
I suppose I should be honored.
-I know about them.
They're that poor tribe that was
wiped out by the soul reapers.
But that's all I
know about them.
-You're exactly right.
-So tell me, quincy,
why would someone
like you want to
help a soul reaper?
I find that hard to comprehend!
-Look, I don't have
to answer to you.
I suggest that you pay
attention to those wings instead
of the history of my tribe.
Did you forget about earlier?
That wasn't a fluke
or a temporary rise
in spiritual pressure.
-Whew!
You were in the air
so long I didn't
think you'd ever come down!
-Do you think you could
be quiet for five minutes?
-Hoo!
I save you and this is
the gratitude I get?
-High-speed vibrations
are destroyed
by even greater
high-speed vibrations.
Seele Schneider is also
known as a soul cutter,
and is made of Reishi.
The Reishi that
make up its blade
oscillate at three million
revolutions per second.
Quincies are skilled
at perceiving Reishi.
From what I can see, the Reishi
on the surface of your feathers
oscillate at about 1.1 to 1.3
million revolutions per second.
That's less than half
of Seele Schneider.
-So, in short,
what you're telling
me is that my feathers won't
work against you anymore.
Is that right?
-Yes.
That's correct.
-Well, OK then.
That's quite a
surprise, Cirucci.
I never would have guessed
it you could freely
shed your released
form in that way.
Can all Arrancars do that?
-We can't freely do this.
I discarded it.
-What?
-I can't go back
to that form again.
The formal name for our
release is Resurreccion.
It means "returning blade."
It resembles a regular
sword when sealed.
It enables us to
become manifestations
of our former Hollow selves.
The only way we return
to our normal form
again is by returning our
abilities back into sword form
again.
Changing our forms without
returning powers back
into the sword would
cause serious damage
like losing an arm.
I'm very bad at
conserving energy.
You'd be surprised at how
much spirit energy I end up
expending by wearing
these arms and feathers.
It's immense.
So if I can't use them, then
I might as well discard them!
This will enable me to
concentrate my spirit energy...
...into one powerful attack.
-Tell me, Cirucci Sanderwicci,
is this battle so important
that you'd go this
far to win it,
to lose your arms and feathers?
-Huh?
Don't you have a brain
inside that head?
Think about it.
If we didn't have
to win, we wouldn't
have started a war
in the first place!
An Arrancar is a loyal soldier.
They obey their
commanders, the Espada.
We were born to defeat and
kill every single enemy.
To be defeated is unforgivable!
In our world, there's
no such thing!
This is a lot of fun!
I should have done it sooner!
Take this!
There!
When I stop and think
about it, quincy,
I really don't have
any desire at all
to fight you in a
form that leaves
me so vulnerable to
attacks from your sword.
If we both have swords
with equal power,
then the one with the
longer reach will win.
How about it?
Do you surrender?
-Both with equal power?
I think you are mistaken.
Seele Schneider's
Reishi vibrations
aren't meant for cutting.
Its vibrations weaken the bonds
that hold Reishi in place,
making it easier to steal.
I collect all of that
Reishi from my opponent.
The way a quincy battles is
by gathering all of the Reishi
from the surrounding area, and
then utilizing it as a weapon.
That which is the most powerful
embodiment of this method
is right before you,
the Seele Schneider.
All of your Reishi
belongs to me now!
-Not a chance, quincy!
-Also!
You've got another thing wrong.
You should be aware that Seele
Schneider is not a sword.
Quincies don't use any weapons
other than bows and arrows.
You cannot win,
Cirucci Sanderwicci.
As you said, one's reach
was the winning factor!
All right, let's go, Pesche.
-Are you sure?
I don't think she's dead yet.
-As you see, I defeated her.
Now, as the victor,
it's up to me
to decide what fate
awaits this worthy foe.
I pierced her soul
chain, the source
of spirit energy production.
Arrancars are
Hollows who've gained
the powers of soul reapers.
Their anatomy should be alike.
I don't know how she feels
about it, but letting her live
may be an even greater
insult than death.
But I assure you,
I have no intention
of playing by their rules.
Even if she recovers and
decides to come for her revenge,
the truth is, she won't
have the power to fight me.
-I see.
If that's the case, that's fine.
C'mon!
Let's go, Ichigo!
URYU: I'm Uryu!
-Damn quincy.
Damn him!
That quincy!
How can he insult me like that?
RUDBORNN: Cirucci Sanderwicci!
We've come for you.
Please, do not resist.
CIRUCCI: Dammit!
GANTENBAINNE: Pathetic.
You are completely loco, man.
There's no way you could
ever be a match for me.
I am Arrancar number 107,
Gantenbainne Mosqeda!
That'll never work.
A human who can't
even use a Sonido
will never connect with
his weak little punches!
I've tried to tell
you again and again,
but you're just too
stubborn to listen.
If you still want to fight,
I won't try to stop you.
But you should know--
you're gonna die.
-We'll see about that.
My plan's to win.
-You'll need more
than strength, Sado.
You'll find that attacks
like mine are hard to beat.
Like I said before,
you're going to die, man.
-Yeah, well, I'm not going
to give up that easily.
-You got guts, man.
There's no doubt about it.
-I told you, I'm
not ready to die.
-Now I understand.
I can see where you're
coming from, Sado.
What you really want is an
all-out fight with everything
I've got.
-I'm ready.
Time to fight at full strength
so I can move on from here.
-Sounds like fun.
I'm not done yet.
You idiot!
Uno!
Dos!
Cientos!
Get on your feet, Yasutora Sado.
Get up right now.
I know what you're
doing, hiding your power,
the true strength you possess.
Yes, you are very strong.
Someone like you shouldn't
be fighting like this.
This should be a fair fight.
So use all your strength,
and don't hold back!
No answer.
Is that it?
You're breaking my heart, buddy!
-Sorry.
In truth, I wasn't
trying to hide it.
It's just that, ever since
I came to Hueco Mundo,
I sensed something
about my power,
something different from when I
was in the world of the living.
I was puzzled by
that difference,
and I wasn't able to control
all of my power until now.
But I have finally
gained control of it.
The time has come,
and I can fight
with my full power from now
on-- Brazo Derecha del Gigante.
Take note.
What you see is my right
arm, but in its true form.
[END THEME IN JAPANESE -
"KANSHA"]
SADO: Ichigo and the others
have Nel in her group with them.
They're all together,
but no one's come to me.
URYU: If you're jealous, I'll
trade places with you any time.
PESCHE: What're
you saying, Ichigo?
We're best friends!
URYU: Oh yeah?
Well a best friend would
never get my name wrong!