[theme music]
-Rukia Kuchiki is
hereby found guilty
of all charges against her.
Twenty five days
from now she will
go to the central
execution grounds
to suffer the
ultimate punishment.
That is the final decision
of the Soul Society.
GIN (OFFSCREEN): My
compliments, squad six captain.
You handled yourself very
professionally in there.
I thought that condemning
your own sister to death
might be difficult for you.
You're truly an example
for all Soul Reapers.
ZARAKI (OFFSCREEN):
Are you joking?
The only Soul Reapers
who are scared of dying
are you and the
captain of squad 9.
GIN (OFFSCREEN): Oh, is that so?
-If this were official
business, you two
wouldn't be without
your agitants.
So what do you want with me?
-We were just concerned.
We wanted to make certain that
one of our esteemed colleagues
wasn't feeling badly about
having to pass sentence
on a member of his own family.
-Our family lineage is
none of your business.
-Good to know you're not upset.
Criminals can do such damage
to a noble family's image.
-Oh?
And since when does
a commoner like you
know anything about nobility?
-Huh, well I guess you
could say I've always
been a keen observer.
For that matter, I'd be pleased
to offer you my services.
Perhaps you'd like me
to behead the criminal
before the execution.
-I don't think that even
you, squad 11 captain,
has the skill required
for something like that.
-Why don't you test me then.
-I don't think you
really mean that.
-Try me.
-My most sincere
apologies, squad 6 captain.
I assure you it was
not my intention
to offend you in any way.
Please give my regards to
your sister, all right.
ZARAKI (OFFSCREEN):
Untie me damnit!
Let me at him!
-Finally.
-Oh, there you are Mr. Tessai.
Are you all right?
-No, I'm not all right.
My glasses nearly fell apart.
-As long as you're
still breathing then
you're all right.
And even if your
glasses are cracked,
you'll probably
want to keep them
on just to see
what happens next.
Just a minute ago Mr.
Kisuke got out his sword.
So this should really be good.
[scream]
-Hey not bad, considering you're
using a little kiddie sword.
-Oh, what a compliment, student.
Don't expect me
to go easy on you.
[laughing and labored breathing]
-(IN HEAD) Hey wait a minute.
Why am I running?
I thought that only
a Zanpakuto could
kill Soul Reapers and Hollows.
But I saw mister hat and clogs
pull that little sword out
of his cane.
So it can't possibly
be a Zanpakuto.
So even if he hits me
with it, he can't cut me.
-You let your guard down.
You thought because
I'm not a Soul
Reaper I couldn't
have a Zanpakuto.
And you're thinking there's
no way I can hurt you.
You are so naive.
Awaken now, Benihime.
I assure you this is a
real Zanpakuto, very real.
Awaken, Benihime.
-Roar, Zabimaru!
You can't even ask your
Zanpakuto its name.
I knew it!
-A name for my Zanpakuto?
-Yes.
Each Zanpakuto carries a
unique name and this one
is Benihime, the red princess.
Let us show you.
[bang]
[gasp]
-I'll give you credit
for not running away
at least and for parrying
with that broken stump.
You're not short on nerve.
Just the same, Benihime
is much too fierce
to let a blade
like that stop her.
[groan]
-(IN HEAD) Damn!
It can't be.
He just cut right through my
Zanpakuto like it was butter.
-Don't you get it Ichigo?
Your sword has no concentration
of spirit energy in it.
It has size, but
that's all it has.
It carries a Zanpakuto
shape but has
none of the necessary
internal strength.
So I can cut it, just like that.
Now you no longer
have any sword at all.
Do you plan to
continue attacking me
with nothing but the hilt?
I suppose you could still manage
to knock my hat off with it.
But this time
Ichigo, you're going
to need a lot more than
just blind luck or courage.
I think it's only
fair to warn you--
if you try to go against me
with that inferior weapon I
will kill you.
[gasp]
-(IN HEAD)I've got to get away.
I don't think he's kidding.
He's really going to
kill me this time.
[scream] This is so pathetic.
What am I doing?
Why am I running away?
Is this is all the
backbone I have?
Am I just a coward after
all, a complete phony?
I'm so disgusted with myself.
How pathetic!
It's pathetic, pathetic!
-Yes, that's you.
-Master?
-Why are you
running away Ichigo?
You still haven't called me yet.
Face forward Ichigo and you
should be able to hear it now.
The only thing plugging
your ears is your own fear.
There's only one enemy
and there's one of you.
So what is there
to be afraid of?
-Hey, what's up?
He just stopped
and so did Ichigo.
ZANGETSU (OFFSCREEN):
Abandon your fear.
Turn and face him.
Don't give an inch.
Now, Ichigo!
Advance!
Never stop!
If you retreat, you will age.
Be afraid and you'll die.
Now shout out my name!
-Zangetsu!
-Whoa!
What's going on out there?
[music playing]
-What kind of Zanpakuto is that?
It doesn't even have a
hilt or a guard on it.
It's not even shaped like
a normal sword. [gasp]
If you ask me, his
old one was better.
-Well it's about time.
Now that you've managed
to draw your Zanpakuto,
time for lesson number three.
Are you ready for that?
-Don't take this the
wrong way Mr. Urahara,
but I hope you dodge this.
-What?
-Because I can't control it yet!
-Scream Benihime!
[music playing]
-Phew, good thing
I protected myself
with my blood mist shield.
Without it, I probably would
have lost an arm just now.
That wasn't very nice.
I do believe you've
killed my hat.
Impressive.
I didn't expect
you could do that
with a single swing
of your sword.
Ichigo, you are one
frightening kid.
You know that?
Lesson three cleared.
-At last it's complete.
I owe it all to you, Sensei.
[crash]
[gasp]
-You did it!
Chad that was so amazing!
Way to go!
Wow!
-You clumsy fools!
That explosion is causing
a panic in the streets.
Quick!
Out the back door!
-OK, OK!
-I can't believe how
quickly they've both
awakened their powers
and become capable
individuals. [scream]
What happened?
-Oh no!
Chad just tripped and
fell down the stairs!
Somebody call the--
-Then again.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
After completing training
at Urahara's shop, I was
told to go home and wait
for the opening of the
gate into the Soul Society.
So here I am for what could
be my last summer vacation.
-Isn't this exciting everyone!
We're finally here at
the fireworks festival!
-You're so enthusiastic.
-Why not?
Who doesn't love to watch
stuff catch fire and explode!
-Hey, don't forget about me.
In fact, I slept over
there on the sidewalk
last night in order to
save the very best spots.
Follow me and
we'll go there now.
-(OFFSCREEN): Hey, for a
grown-up you're all right.
Fantastic.
-(OFFSCREEN) Let's go!
-How about you
two lovely ladies.
Care to join us?
We'll be there a little later.
-Suit yourselves!
Come on everybody!
The sun's going down and
it's almost explosion time!
-Well, might as well.
I guess I'll go too.
Sorry, Tatsuki.
It's always like this.
You don't have to come
along if you don't want to.
-Oh, don't worry
about me, Ichigo.
I'll probably catch up
with everybody later.
You just go ahead and have fun.
-All right, see ya.
-They're all so energetic.
-I'll say.
It wears me out
just watching em.
-Is your hand
bothering you, Tatsuki?
-Huh?
No actually it
doesn't hurt at all,
except for hurting my
pride a little bit whenever
I think about how it
cost me first place.
-Yeah, but taking second place
in the national tournament
still makes you the
second strongest
girl in the whole country.
-Huh?
-That means you're great!
-I hadn't thought
of that before.
-See!
Tatsuki you're amazing!
-(SIGHING) This is one of my
favorite places in the whole
world to relax.
-We haven't come here since
last year about this time.
-Did I ever tell you about
coming here with my brother?
He and I used to come
to this place too.
And he had this amazing ability
to catch red dragonflies
on his fingertip.
He would is just point
his finger to the sky
and right away a
dragonfly would land.
It was like magic.
I always wanted to be able to
do that too, but I never could.
I'll protect you this
time Tatsuki, I promise!
-So, you're going to visit
some relatives next week?
-Uh, mm hm.
-Ichigo said he was
taking a trip then too.
-Uh huh. [nervous laugh]
-What you said about
winning second place
was pretty cool Orihime.
-Hm?
-You're right.
Because even though
I didn't come
in first in that tournament
I still gained something.
There are always things
you discover just
by doing the best you can do.
So I think that
for you-- if you've
decided to do something you
should go ahead and do it.
[gasp] And do the best you can.
But please, just promise
that you'll come back, OK.
I'll be waiting, Orihime.
[fireworks]
-Oh yeah!
-Oh, yeah!
-Ichigo's dad rocks!
-This is a great spot!
[fireworks and crowd]
-Well, I guess it's about time.
All I can do now is wait.
-Seven days from now at 1:00 AM
be ready with your window open.
-I've got a really bad
feeling about this.
Huh?
There's a nice breeze
tonight at least.
Hey!
[crash] [gasp] What the hell?
Huh?
URAHARA (OFFSCREEN): I Meet
us outside the Urahara shop
immediately.
[screams]
-Who the hell contacts
people like that?
This is like some TV
crime scene message
written in the
victim's own blood!
And it better not stain my wall!
Hm?
What now, a PS?
URAHARA (OFFSCREEN):
PS-- if you're
thinking that this messages
is like some written
in the victim's own blood
cliche from some TV show,
then you obviously
have no sense of humor.
-Oh shut up!
[breathing] [snoring]
-Well dad, Karin,
Yuzu-- goodbye.
-Good morning Ichigo!
[crash] Way to dodge
the attack, my son.
-This is how you say goodbye?
What's wrong with you?
-Before you left
Ichigo, I wanted
to make sure you had
this to take with you.
-What am I supposed to do
with some dirty old charm?
-Watch your mouth.
That talisman was given to
me by your mother long ago.
It's precious.
-And what are you
giving it to me for?
I can't keep this thing!
-Of course you can't!
Who ever said I was giving
it to you permanently?
You have to give it back to
me as soon as you come home.
Sheesh!
It should bring you luck.
It always has for me.
Think of it as a gift
from your mother.
Well, what do you say?
Hey, I'm offering you a
magic talisman and I swear,
if you don't bring it back
I'll shave my beard off.
-All right already.
-Now answer me already!
-I'll take it.
I'm going now.
Goodbye dad.
-Bye!
-I will tell you.
I'm a Soul Reaper.
You'll learn that
exorcising a Hollow
is not the same
thing as killing it.
Could she have been
killed by a Hollow?
Do you think that it's possible?
-(IN HEAD) So many strange
things have happened lately.
-You are just a lowly human.
How dare you grab my
brother like that!
-(IN HEAD) But now I swear--
-You are going to die so
why not stay put and live
a few seconds longer?
-(IN HEAD) I can't pretend
like all that never happened.
-Well, well.
If it isn't Ichigo.
And right on time.
Welcome to the club.
-Hey Chad.
What are you doing here?
-Rukia saved me once.
I want to help her out if I can.
I'm going too.
-Huh?
-What's the matter?
Are you hard of
hearing or something?
-What?
Uryu?
-I don't take defeat
well, especially when
it's at the hands
of a Soul Reaper.
So I'm going too.
-So I guess we're all
present and accounted for.
-Orihime?
-Yes, I got the message too.
-Hold on a second.
Can somebody please tell me
what the hell is going on here?
-You're a little slow on
the uptake, aren't you?
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): Yuruichi!
-Kid, don't tell me you
didn't notice the increase
in the hidden powers of
these three friends of yours.
There have been so many clues.
You need to be more
observant than that
if you want to survive.
While you were
training and trying
to regain your Soul Reaper
powers, the three of them
were also training
in their own way.
Instead of asking stupid,
meaningless questions,
you ought to be thanking them.
-Uh.
A freaking cat just spoke to me!
-His name is Yoruichi
and he's not just a cat.
-It is hard to get used to.
-I'm still adjusting
to it myself.
-All right, all right.
Come on everybody.
Let's take this little
party inside the store.
There are things we can't talk
about out here in the open.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Orihime.
[gasp]
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN):
What is it Ichigo?
-How much do you know
about what's going on?
I mean, this is going
to be dangerous.
-Yes, but I gave my promise.
I promised that I'd go with you.
And I told Tatsuki
I'd come back to her.
-What?
Hm.
-Wow!
This is so incredible!
Who knew there was something
this humongous right
below the shop?
Isn't it amazing?
-I guess.
-Oh, what a
heartwarming reaction.
It's such a pleasure to have
you on this trip, my dear.
-The pleasure is all
mine, Mr. Tessai.
-All right everyone.
Your attention, please.
All eyes right
over here-- voila!
This is the gate that
leads to the Soul Society.
It's called the Senkaiman,
or Tunnel World Gate.
I'm going to tell you all how
to successfully pass through it.
But first we need
to change one thing.
-Wow!
-Hey, how about
giving me a little
warning next time Urahara.
-So Ichigo, you're not
inside this Ichigo anymore?
-Don't talk about me like
I'm some kind of doll
with changeable outfits.
-All right, listen up.
Unlike normal gates, this
one has a spirit particle
conversion machine.
-What the hell are
you talking about?
-I'll explain.
As you already know, the Soul
Society is a spirit world.
Unless you're in spirit form
it's impossible to enter.
Right now only one of
you can cross through
as a spirit-- Ichigo,
a Soul Reaper.
The conversion machine will
transform the rest of you
into spirits as well.
-So you're saying the gate
will let us pass through
without extracting our souls?
-Yes.
Passing through the
conversion machine
will allow you to stay
in your present forms.
-All right, we understand.
Let's get going!
Ah!
-But there's a catch.
The window of time the
gate can be kept open
for you is only
four minutes long.
-But is that enough time?
-Ordinarily no.
In fact, the whole
scheme is a little shaky.
Four minutes with the gate
is all I can give you.
After that it will
close and anyone
who hasn't made it through
yet will be trapped forever
in the Dangai, the
precipice world
between this world
and the Soul Society.
-How will we ever make it?
-Go forward.
Remember what I told you about
the connection between heart
and soul.
You must have no doubt.
Have no fear.
Do not think of those
you are leaving behind.
The will to go forward
will be your guide.
And don't look back.
Only those who can
do these things
can follow me through
the gate and survive.
-We all know this already or
we wouldn't still be here.
Quit with all your preaching
and let's do this thing now!
-And you understand
that if you lose
you can never return to
this life again, right?
-Then all I need
to do is win, huh?
-Exactly.
-So, everybody ready?
As soon as it opens, run
in as fast as you can.
-Right.
-Good luck.
Ah!
Ooh.
We're all counting
on you, Ichigo.
[theme music]
-What is that thing?
CHAD (OFFSCREEN): A mountain.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): A whale?
YORUICHI (OFFSCREEN): No,
it's a gatekeeper giant.
URYU (OFFSCREEN): Well,
there you have it.
OK, Kurasaki.
You handle him.
CHAD (OFFSCREEN): Go for it.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN):
You can do it.
-You're the man!
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
OK, I guess I am.
-Long hair is not allowed!