I must apologize for
the wait, everyone.
I'll be done with the
adjustments in just a minute.
Will we really have to pass
through the Precipice World?
Wait, hold on.
Isn't it completely under
Kageroza's control?
Well, I wouldn't
say completely.
What does that mean?
Y'see it appears that
Kageroza has control over
many of its aspects,
but not the Cleaner.
Of course, you might
be wondering,
"then how did the Cleaner
show up at just the right
time to get in our way
when it usually only appears
once every seven days?"
Glad you asked!
I have a hypothesis
about that.
Never mind the
lengthy explanation.
He set the time axis of the
Cleaner's appearances so that
it would arrive whenever we
entered the Precipice World.
Yes, exactly. Astute as
always, Captain Kuchiki.
However, this suggests that
Kagerosa has some limits to
his control of time in the
Precipice World.
Otherwise, why would there be a
delay between when someone
enters the Precipice World and
when the Cleaner arrives?
So what exactly do you
want us to do, then?
All right, what I've
done is secure a space
behind the Cleaner that
Kageroza can't control.
Meaning, you'll be able to move
within that time axis without
any interference.
I'll arrange your entry into
the Precipice World so you
end up inside that space.
Of course, that makes it sound
a lot easier than it is.
You'll only have a window
of less than a minute.
If your timing's off and
you enter the Precipice
World too soon, you'll
become the Cleaner's prey.
And if you leave the reserved
space I've created, you'll fall
into the area Kageroza controls.
You might never be able to leave
the Precipice World again.
Huh?
[gasp] Ichigo!
You all right?
Yeah, Orihime.
Just barely!
And the others?
They're all here
and accounted for.
They have already been
treated, and are resting now.
[Ichigo]
Oh, great.
Glad to hear that.
Can you take a look
at her, too, and see
if she's hurt at all?
Sure.
Hey, what's wrong?
You okay?
Yaaagh!
You pervert!
She sure seems fine to me!
Stop goofing around!
You lousy guys are all alike!
You're perverts!
Don't go lumping
me in with him!
I could say the same
thing to you, you know!
At least I'm not afraid
to admit I'm a pervert!
Nyaah!
Why you!
[beating up sounds]
Hngh!
Ah! Are you all
right, Ichigo?
Ngh... Yeah...
Here, let me take a look!
No, it's nothing!
[Kenpachi]
Really?
Huh?
Huagh!
Ichigo!
Is he dead?!
One little kick
sends you flying!
I sure wouldn't
call that nothing!
I was just off-guard!
Anyone would've gone flying!
Besides, I thought you
went to the Soul Society!
I'm on my way
there right now.
What? Then I'm
going with you!
Forget it! If this is the
condition you're in, you'll
just end up getting killed.
Just shut up!
Try not to get
yourself killed.
Huh?
He'll be fine!
There's no way
Kenny's gonna die!
You keep out of
this, Yachiru.
Oh, stop. Right, Ichi?!
Aw.
Relax. Till you and I fight
again, I don't plan on dying,
even if I do get killed!
Okay, I get it!
Hurry up and go!
Later, Ichigo.
Bye-bye!
About time!
You're late.
We were going to
leave without you two.
Don't worry
about it.
Now, before you go,
here's a warning.
Don't need one.
Could we just
get going!
Aren't we running
out of time?
Yes, you're right.
Okay, be careful.
Here goes!
[Inaba]
Well, well.
It appears that the
captains have entered
the Precipice World.
Doesn't their arrival mean
your attempt at invading
the World of the Living has
ended in failure, Kageroza?
You're a scientist,
and a smart one at that.
If they return to the
Soul Society, it's only
a matter of time before
they shut down your plans.
Surely you must
understand that.
Captain Unohana.
You sound almost like a
teacher admonishing a student!
However, you're gravely
mistaken about one thing.
Do you think I'd simply wait for
them to come without doing
anything to prepare for it?!
Hmm, hmm.
What? What is it?
Something isn't right.
Ah! Restrictive Current!
Keeping up with the Cleaner in
itself isn't all that difficult.
The real problem is the
captains' powerful Spirit
Energies.
The walls of the Precipice World
react to Reishi.
In other words, the higher
their Spirit Energies, the
faster the Restrictive Current
pursuing them becomes.
Is that what
you're saying?
Yes, but they probably
accounted for that.
Of course that's not
everything, is it?
You're very astute.
I'm not able to control
the Restrictive Current.
But I am able to
manipulate time around it.
[Toshiro]
That bastard Kageroza!
He set a trap for us,
didn't he?!
So what? We'll
force our way
through!
What do you think
you're doing?!
Come on!
Just leave this to me!
Bankai!
Kokujo Tengen Myo-oh!
No, you fool! You're going
to be swallowed by it!
Go!
Sajin!
Quick, up there!
I can't believe
he did that!
Let it go. We have no time
to go back for him now.
Besides, he won't let something
like that kill him so easily!
We can't waste time;
we have to keep moving.
I can sense three Captains.
Kuchiki, Hitsugaya, and
Zaraki.
But not Captain Komamura!
Only a single one
brought down, eh?
Well, it appears that
my science is still
far from perfect.
I have much to learn.
Don't move!
Hado Number
Thirty One!
Shakkaho!
There's no hurry.
Lieutenant Kotetsu.
Takaoni!
That's it?!
Sogyonokotwari!
Thank you, Jushiro.
It is rather amusing!
What is that, old man?
The two of you are.
Both of you talk
like the real thing,
act like the real thing,
and even fight
like the real thing.
But the reality is
that you are Reigai.
Nothing about you is truly your
own, not even your intentions.
Now, now, don't say that,
Old Man Yama.
Master Genryusai.
As you say, all that
we are is derived
from the originals.
However, it doesn't mean
that we've lost what's
really important.
Oh?
Yes, that's right.
We still have our honor.
If that is so,
then show it to me,
this "honor" of yours!
Hah!
My shadow?!
Kageoni.
Ah!
Guess they're on their way.
This'll be good fun.
Huh?
Are you seriously
trying to stop me?!
I'm not. Besides,
that would be useless.
Listen, it is their sole purpose
to utterly destroy us, right?
We'll have to fight
them sooner or later.
But now, the only target we
have to worry about is Kageroza.
We'll split up and head
for Squad Twelve's
barracks separately.
Sure. Right after I'm finished.
Fine.
Kenny, it's that way!
Yeah, yeah; I know that!
We're gonna go that way.
We'll meet at
Kageroza's location.
I know the Spiritual Pressure
he's tracking down.
Huh.
Kenny?
Yeah.
Hey. I've been waiting.
Heh.
Gotta hand it to you.
It's like you read my
mind, coming here.
No, I didn't.
Then why are you here?
I wanted to find out
how strong I am,
that's all.
Heh! You can read
my mind, then!
Bring it hard from the start.
I don't mind losing to you.
As long as
you're stronger!
Hm!
Now it's time to
have a little fun!
[growl]
Heh heh!
Oh, he's just like
the real Kenny!
You'd better go all-out.
Yeah, or else,
You're gonna die!
No, you!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
Augh!
Ha ha! What's wrong?
I'd heard that a Reigai
is supposed to be stronger
than the real thing!
Don't disappoint me now.
Just relax.
Huh?
G'augh!
Huh, I guess I AM
pretty strong.
Nice try.
Remember what I said about
not minding losing to you?
Forget it.
No way am I gonna lose
to the likes of you!
Wait! Don't!
Kageroza Inaba.
Don't let this folly
go any further.
Oh?
[Unohana]
You might think everything is
going according to your plan,
But killing Head Captain
Yamamoto is impossible.
No. Not just Head
Captain Yamamoto.
It seems you're underestimating
all our powers.
[Kenpachi]
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
And what's so funny, huh?
This is such a blast!
I haven't laughed
this hard in ages!
Reigai, you have the same
memories as I do, right?
It's just like that time.
It's so fun,
I can't help myself!
Egh!
Haaaah!
I feel bad for you,
Reigai.
If you really are stronger,
then I'm the one who gets
to enjoy this fight!
Huaaaaa!
Augh!
[wet choke]
Heh! Don't you dare say
it's over yet, you hear?
Not when things are just
starting to get seriously
fun around here.
Damn right I won't!
I'm finally starting to
really enjoy myself too!
Hyaah!
Huaah!
The same trick works
only so many times!
Iro Oni... "White"!
Hah!
Not good enough!
Huah!
Shunsui!
Man, this sure isn't
proving to be too easy.
The goal of these
Reigai is to stop me.
But they must realize that
even fighting to a draw
will prove very difficult.
And yet, they don't
hesitate at all.
They're fighting as
though they're willing
to fall right here.
Like they're on a
suicide mission.
Heh.
What does this mean?!
[wet cough]
Ha ha!
Kenny!
Hah. So that's it, huh?
I never thought...
I'd be killed by...
myself.
Well, it's survival of
the fittest, I guess.
I have no regrets.
[Yachiru]
Kenny!
What is it, Yachiru?
Heh.
You're right.
I totally forgot about that.
Heh heh. We've been
together all this time.
So I'm not supposed
to die just yet.
What are you talking about?
I'm also going to take back
what I said earlier, about
not minding if I lose.
I want to win.
And I'm going to!
Even if it's just against some
cheap imitation like you!
Tch! Don't make me laugh!
Haaaaa!
[gasp]
Kenny!
Heh.
So, it's all about winning, huh?
Tch.
Makes perfect sense.
H'augh!
Heh.
Kenny!
You aren't dead,
are you?
Heh. No way, of course not.
Ah!
[giggles]
[Inaba]
I've underestimated
all your powers?
Is that what you said?
Yes. Is it not true?
I've never been
very interested in
what others do.
So it's difficult for me
to say that I truly know
all of you thoroughly.
But, Captain Unohana.
Don't you think that the
same could be said of you?
What do you mean by that?
Oh, you'll find out.
Captain Unohana.
You'll have to forgive me.
[Inaba]
I certainly wouldn't face a
captain of your caliber without
a plan, now, would I?
You already know that many
lieutenants passed through
the Precipice World
to the World of the Living
to work on cleansing the
Tenkai Zone.
Well during that time, I made
a few modifications to the
Soul Society's Senkaimon.
I collected a small amount of
Reishi from the Soul Reapers
who passed through it.
With that, I created Mod
Souls indistinguishable
from the originals and
placed them inside Reigai.
And that is how I built
my invading force.
The Senkaimon.
Do you understand now?
I've already collected
your Reishi.
And it's all thanks to
the Lieutenant Kotetsu
that I created!
What are you going to do now?
Heh heh heh heh heh!
[Toshiro]
We must stop the enemies who
stand before us, Byakuya.
[Byakuya]
I'll be the first one
to get to Kageroza.
[Toshiro]
Slow down. Focus on
the enemy before us!
[Byakuya]
I'll be the first one there.
[Toshiro]
But-
[Byakuya]
I'll be the first one there.
[Toshiro]
All right, fine!