[theme music]
-But this is Sokyuko Hill.
AIZEN (OFFSCREEN):
Welcome Renji.
-Captain Aizen.
How did-- Then Gin
must have-- What the?
What's going on?
-Leave Rukia where she
is, Renji, and back away.
-Captain Aizen.
How can this be?
And what was it you just said?
-How odd.
I'm sure you must have
heard me the first time.
I said leave Rukia there, and
I told you to back away, Renji.
-Hearts of the south,
eyes of the north,
fingertips of the west,
heals of the east,
gather holding the wind,
scatter, sweeping the rains.
Bakuro 58.
Kakushitsuijaku.
31, 64, 83, I've
pointpointed where they went.
3 32 degrees east
by 15 66 north.
It's the Sokyoku.
-Ah yes.
I see.
I want you to stay
here and locate
all of the captains,
all lieutenants,
all seated officers.
Report to them
everything we've just
learned about what
Sosuka Aizen has done,
and make sure to tell
them where he's gone.
-Right.
-And then I want you
to be sure to get
the message to
those Ryoka as well.
-Yes.
I understand.
-I'm counting on you.
I must go now and try to save
the lives of Captain Hitsugaya
and Lieutenant Hinamori
before it's too late.
-Black and white net, 22nd
bridge, 66 crown and cincture.
Footprints, distance
thunder, sharp arrow,
rotating land cover of night.
Sea of clouds, pale soldiers!
Form a circle, and then
charge through the heavens!
Tenteikura!
Connections complete.
All court guard squad
captains, lieutenants,
and seated officers, may I
have your attention please,
and also, the Ryoka.
This is squad four
lieutenant Isane Kotetsu
with an urgent announcement.
-Isane.
ISANE (OFFSCREEN):
Listen closely,
as the message will
not be repeated.
This is an emergency report
from Captain Unohana regarding
the traitor in our midst.
As grim as the
following facts are,
what I'm about to
tell you is the truth.
-Impossible.
Not Aizen.
-This cannot be.
-Well, you heard the lady.
What do we do, old man?
Doesn't this fight seem
a little pointless now?
-I can't believe it.
My captain lost.
-How could he?
He said that he wouldn't.
That he wouldn't harm Momo.
-You mean he
murdered all of them?
All of central 46?
-No way.
We've been betrayed.
By my captain.
-Kaname.
-Sir.
Did you hear the
report about Aizen?
-Of course I heard it.
Do you think I'm deaf?
-What shall we do?
-Hm.
I don't really care.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Do
you this is all true?
GENJU (OFFSCREEN): Maybe.
It might also be
the enemy's trap.
-Possible, but I think
it's probably true.
-Hm?
-Don't you sense the
spiritual pressure
that just appeared back
up at the execution site?
-Rukia.
-What's that?
-I told you.
I won't leave Rukia.
I refuse to let her go.
-Very well then.
-That won't be necessary, Gin.
You are stubborn, Renji.
Since you won't let go
of her and stand down
as I ordered you,
I have no choice.
But I'll take your feelings
into consideration,
and I will let
you have your way.
She can stay in your arms.
The rest of you goes.
-Renji?
-My, my.
I can see your defensive
skills have improved
a great deal, Renji Abarai.
I am happy to see that
you've continued to progress.
But I hope you won't
struggle for too long.
It's difficult for me
to control my power.
It's difficult to step on
ants without crushing them.
And as your former
superior, I would
prefer not to kill you
if I don't have to.
-Renji.
It's OK, Rukia.
Just shut up.
Yeha, right.
You don't want to kill me?
Then what about Momo?
You killed her in cold blood!
-What happened to Momo
couldn't be helped.
I had trained her so that
she couldn't live without me.
So don't you think that killing
her was an act of mercy?
Still, what I said is true.
I did not want to
kill her myself.
That's why I went to all the
trouble of forging the letter,
leading her to attack
Izaru and Toshiro.
But that didn't work out.
So I had no choice.
I had to finish her myself.
-So Momo, and Izaru.
They were all just puppets
in your twisted scheme?
-And you, too, Renji.
-I see.
I don't know who the monster
in front of me really is,
but you're not the Aizen I knew.
And I don't know why
you want her so badly,
but I'll never hand
Rukia over to you.
Even if it costs me my life!
-I've got some news
for you about the Aizen
you used to know.
I'm sorry to break
it to you, since you
seem to remember him so fondly.
That Aizen you knew was
nothing but an illusion.
He never even existed
in the first place.
-Roar!
Zabimaru!
-Shikai, huh?
You're probably at your limits.
But that won't even
buy you any time.
-That's what you think!
-Petulant as ever.
-He stopped it with
his bare hands!
-Of the three of
you, I always thought
you would turn out to
be the most troublesome.
And I was right.
-Renji!
-I was right.
When I first met
the three of you,
I felt sure I could use you.
That's why I had you all
assigned to squad five
as soon as you joined
the 13 court guard
squads I made Izaru
and Momo subordinates
for myself and for Gin.
You, however, were different.
So I decided to send
you, the problem
child, away to a
different squad.
And, as it turns out, my
instincts were correct.
I'll give you one more chance.
Put Rukia down and
get out of here.
-He'll do it, Captain Aizen!
I'll go with you if you want!
Just leave him alone!
-Shut up, Rukia.
I refuse!
-Renji, no!
-I won't let him
have you, Rukia.
You thought I'd give her up?
Are you that dumb?
-Then so be it.
Too bad.
-Hey, there.
-Huh?
-What's the matter, Renji?
The way you were
crouching down, I'd
almost think Rukia's too heavy
for you to hold, or something.
Good thing I came
to give you a hand.
Right, friend?
-Ichigo.
-Yeah?
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry you had to come.
-What happened to you?
-Huh?
-All you had to do was carry
Rukia away, and look at you.
Either she gained a lot
of weight, or you're weak.
'Cause you look all beat up.
-Hah!
Yeah, look who's talking.
Maybe instead of
coming here, you
should have gone back to bed.
-You've got a lot
of nerve talking
like that to the guy who
just came to save your butt!
-I was about to
thank you, you idiot,
but I'm not going to now!
-Hm?
[muffled gasps]
-Huh?
-Thanks, stupid!
Do you think I'm trying
to make a new world
record for holding my breath?
You were crushing
the wind outta me!
You almost killed me!
-Sorry about that.
I didn't think you'd want
me to interfere, Sosuke,
so I let the Ryoka get by.
-No matter.
It's fine.
When you're cleaning the house,
it doesn't make any difference
whether there's one
piece of dirt, or two.
-So, this is Aizen, then.
-That's him.
-Do you think you still
have enough strength left
to get away?
-I have enough to
stay and fight.
I know that for certain.
And that's what I'm going to do.
You know damn well that
it's useless for us to run.
Zabimaru may be
broken, but he still
has a few surprises left in him.
Let's just slow him
down enough to get away.
-Hah.
Who needs a plan B?
If we join forces and battle
together, what could go wrong?
-Right.
I can only use this
technique a single time.
But if it connects,
it'll leave him
wide open for a second or two.
You've got to strike
in that opening.
-I gotcha.
-This may hurt a bit, Zabimaru.
I'm sorry.
But you've got to hang in there.
Here we go!
Zabimaru!
Higa Zekko!
-Yah!
Ah!
-Well, now.
I thought I had succeeded in
cutting you completely in half.
But I didn't strike deep enough.
-Ichigo.
Where' he go?
Dammit.
-Ichigo.
Renji!
I-- I can't move.
-Come, now.
Stand up, Rukia Kuchiki.
Hm.
Oh.
I see.
My spiritual pressure has
caused your body to go limp.
[gasping]
-Ichigo.
-Poor doomed thing.
Is he actually still conscious?
Your stamina is
amazing, but your spine
is barely connected
to your body.
You should lie still.
At any rate, you have
each served your purpose.
Your job in all
this is done now.
-Our job is done?
-That's correct.
I knew you were coming.
I even knew from where.
I knew you would arrive in
the West Rukon district.
That's why I had
security increased there,
with squad members
stationed at the gate.
I had Gin go there as well,
in case something went wrong.
I lowered the wall around
the Sereitei wall right
after your arrival, and
placed third and ninth squads
behind the gate.
I knew the only way
you'd be able to get in
would be with Kukaku
Shiba's Flower Cream Cannon.
A very flashy entrance
that everyone would notice.
A bold approach.
It helped that you Ryoka
were skilled enough
to get past the captains.
As a result, the eyes
of all the soul reapers
were focused only on you.
The perfect diversion.
Your actions after you entered
the court and all the turmoil
that you caused were
actually quite impressive.
As a result, there wasn't
very much fuss at all over me
when I faked my own death.
You made it easy for
me to make my move.
-But-- hold on.
How did you know
for sure that we
were going to come in
through the West Rukon
district in the first place?
-That's an odd question
for you to ask.
Where else could you
possibly have entered?
The Western Rukon district is
Kisuke Urahara's headquarters,
after all.
It's the only place
you can break through
with his Senkaimon.
Why do you find
that so surprising?
After all, you work
for him, don't you?
Surely the reason you're
here in the first place
is to retrieve Rukia
Kuchiki under his orders.
-I-- I don't--
-Oh, I see.
You poor boy.
You weren't told
anything, were you?
Oh, well.
Since this is the end anyway,
I'll tell you one last thing.
Did you know that soup reapers
have four basic fighting
methods?
Zanjutsu, Hakura,
Hoho, and Kido.
Those are the four.
But there is a limit to how
strong a soul reaper can
become in any one of them.
No matter which of the
techniques he chooses,
there comes a point at which
you will have mastered it.
And all his growth
will stop there.
As a soul reaper, he
has reached his limit.
However, for some it is
possible to get past that wall,
and to exceed the limit that's
built into all four techniques.
And to do that,
there's only one way.
The soul reaper has
to become a Hollow.
Either that, or a Hollow can
become like a soul reaper.
Either way, what is
required is the removal
of the barrier between those
two opposing existences.
That is the key to making the
spirit's power even greater.
In theory, the idea
seemed plausible,
so I studied it in secret.
I started testing,
focusing mostly
on the transformation of
Hollows into soul reapers.
I was successful in creating
Hollows which came close.
Hollows that could hide
their spiritual pressure.
Even one that could
zanpakuto with a touch,
and fuse with
other soul reapers.
But, in the end, none of
them worked out as well
as I had hoped.
It appeared that
the theory was only
that, destined never
to be a reality.
But, Kisuke Urahara
succeeded where I had failed.
The mechanism he invented
removes the barrier
dividing Hollow and soul
reaper, instantly making one
into the other.
It defied all logic
within the soul society.
It's called hogyoku.
I knew immediately
how dangerous it was.
I think Urahara
felt the same way.
He tried to destroy
it, but he was
unable to find a way to
undo his own creation.
Instead, he reluctantly
resorted to another method.
He created a shield around
the hogyoku and activated it.
Then he enveloped it
deep within a konpaku
in order to try to conceal
its location from anyone
who would want to
use it for evil.
You know, don't you?
You know that's why I want you.
Because the place Urahara
decided to hide the hogyoku
is inside you.
-What did you just say?
-When I learned
you had disappeared
in the world of the living,
I realized right away
that Urahara had
something to do with it.
All soul reapers and gigai are
traceable by the Soul Society,
no matter where they go.
This is because of the
gigai's healing energy.
But the gigai Urahara
gave you was different,
created by him without reishi.
As a result, it was untraceable.
For this offense, Urahara was
cast out of the Soul Society.
There is also one other
reason Urahara was exiled.
A gigai like the one he
gave you, one without reishi
will constantly
break down and devour
the reishi of the
soul reaper using it.
He will never be able to
completely recover his power.
It will fade, and eventually
the connection with you
gigai will dim.
Finally, the soul reaper
is reduced to a mere human.
Do you understand?
Urahara didn't give
you any strength.
He didn't help you at all.
He used you, Rukia Kuchiki.
He turned you into a human, just
so he could hide the hogyoku.
-What's the matter, Rukia?
You seem upset?
Can I help you?
With a gigai, perhaps?
-Fortunately, before
it was too late,
you were found in the
human world and arrested.
I went immediately to
central 46 and kill-- Hm?
-Aizen!
[theme music]
-Did everyone understand
what I was talking about?
I tried to make it simple
enough for even stupid people
to understand.
-What'd you say?
We just me!
How'd you already know I'm
stupid, you arrogant jerk?
-So, you don't deny
that you're stupid.
-I guess you got me there.