[theme song]
NARRATOR: 110 years
ago, the 13 court guard
squads were led by a different
command than they are today.
However, they were still
a very familiar group.
The captain of Squad
5 was Shinji Hirako,
who currently
resides in the world
of the living as a Vizard.
Other members of
the Vizards also
held positions as
captains and lieutenants
in the 13 court guard squads.
At the time, Kisuke Urahara
was made captain of Squad 12
based on the recommendation
of Squad 2 Captain Yoruichi
Shihouin.
-I'm in the process of creating
an organization unlike anything
ever seen in the Soul Society.
It'll be under the
control of Squad 12.
It's the Department of
Research and Development.
I would like you to assume
the seat of deputy department
head, Mayuri Kurotsuchi.
NARRATOR: Meanwhile, at
the Kuchiki Clan residence,
a young Byakuya practiced
his swordsmanship.
At Squad 13's
barracks, Kaien Shiba
was persuaded by Jushiro
Ukitake to accept a promotion
to lieutenant.
With so much change,
the soul reapers
spent their days thinking
of the future for the Soul
Society and the 13
court guard squads.
But glimpses of a
growing nightmare
were already starting to show.
-Nice.
Your skill is even
better than I was told.
And how did you
find our third seat?
-Terrible.
No competition at all.
-Interesting.
Glad to hear it.
NARRATOR: After swinging
back to the past
and giving a glimpse
of a moment in time,
the pendulum swings
several years forward.
A new incident
occurred nine years
after Kisuke Urahara
became captain.
-[whimpering]
-[screaming]
-[choking]
-Huh?
-Eh?
-Wha?
-Oh.
-Huh?
Oh, good morning, Kisuke.
-Hey.
And a good morning to
you, too, Captain Hirako.
-I told you before,
just call me Shinji.
You're such a pain sometimes.
-[laughing]
-Good morning, Mayuri.
-How many times have I told you
to address me by my last name?
Kurotsuchi isn't hard.
-[groan] You are a pain.
Oh, by the way, have you heard
the latest news yet, Kisuke?
-No, I haven't.
What happened?
--[screams] Hey, what's the
big idea kicking me like that,
Hiyori?
-You said good morning
to everyone but me.
What?
I'm not good enough to say
good morning to anymore?
-If I said good
morning, you'd kick me
for saying good morning.
-[growling]
-Is this the mouth you
say good morning with?
-[laughing]
-By the way, I was
wondering, have you
heard the latest news yet?
-No, I still haven't.
-You don't know about
the violent deaths
in Rukon District?
-Hold it.
I was just about to tell him.
Way to bring it all
back full circle.
-Violent deaths?
-Yeah.
In the past month
or so, there's been
a series of residents
disappearing in the Rukon
District.
The reason is unknown.
-Disappearing?
As in, they went somewhere
and then never came back?
-You dumbass, that's
not disappearing.
That's called running away.
And if they just ran away, then
nobody would care about them.
No one would go looking.
Not this.
This is different.
They literally disappear.
Gone without a trace, leaving
only their clothes behind.
If they died and became reishi,
the clothes they were wearing
would disappear as well.
They didn't die.
They vanished alive, unable
to retain human form.
That's the only
explanation I can think of.
-Alive but unable to
retain human form, huh?
-I wasn't there, mind you.
I'm just telling
you exactly what
I heard from Captain Unohana.
Now you know what I know.
Well, at any rate, Squad 9 has
already arrived on the scene
to investigate.
-Hey.
Hey!
Are you listening to me, Kensei?
What do you mean by unknown?
-Quiet already!
Unknown means unknown!
Quit babbling!
-What's wrong with you?
A captain doesn't just go
investigate something unknown
without knowing
what it is first!
-We can't know!
It's unknown!
-Yeah, but an advance
party was sent out first.
10 people!
You could have just waited
for them to report, but no!
I'm Kensei!
I can't wait!
-Lieutenant, please.
You're doing it again.
-I'm Kensei, I'm--
-Captain, please
try to calm down.
-She acts like this
just to annoy you.
-In the first
place, I don't ever
remember asking
you to come along.
You can leave this
investigation anytime.
As a matter of fact,
I wish you would.
-Ooh, don't you know that
it's against the rules
for a lieutenant to
leave her captain's side?
Shame on you for not
knowing that, Kensei.
-[growl]
-Stupid!
-Oh, you're so stupid!
I can't believe you
don't know the rules,
and you're the captain!
Maybe I should be the captain,
because I know the rules
and you don't.
[interposing voices]
[screaming]
-Huh?
-Wha?
-[whimpering]
-[roar]
-If I don't get away,
I'll end up like that.
I have to run.
But I can't yell.
And my legs won't move.
-[roar]
-[scream] Run away!
Run now!
Or we're dead!
-[screaming]
-[roar]
-Faster!
Run faster if you want to live!
-Didn't you hear me?
You have to get out of here!
Run and don't stop!
[screaming]
-It's a Hollow.
-Enormous.
-[whimpering]
-What's that?
-It's a child.
-Let's go.
-[roar]
-[scream]
-Damn it.
-Four strikes and it
still won't let go.
-Move!
-[roar]
-[screaming]
-Hey, hurry up and
get out of here.
You don't want to die, do you?
-[roar]
-Men, back off!
-Yes, sir!
-Now, blast away.
Tachikaze!
-[growls]
-Is everybody all right?
-Yes, sir.
-[crying]
-Hey, what are you
crying for, kid?
At least you're alive.
You should be happy.
Laugh, or else!
-That's a bit much,
don't you think?
-No, I don't.
Come on, stand up.
What's your name anyway, huh?
-Shu-- Shuhei.
Shuhei Hisagi.
-Shuhei Hisagi.
A mighty strong sounding name.
Stop crying!
-[crying]
-What are you crying
about now, kid?
I said stop crying.
You've got to be kidding me.
-[crying]
-Kensei!
-Mashiro.
Where the hell did you
go during the battle?
-Listen, while I was
hiding in the bushes,
look what I found on the ground.
See?
A squad uniform.
-Hmm.
-But wait.
There were a whole
bunch of them there.
10 of them.
-10 uniforms?
-Captain, they must be--
-What?
What?
Does 10 of them mean
something important?
Well?
-You're such an idiot.
10 was the number of men
in the advance party.
-Wait, I don't understand.
These were taken
off way over there.
-How could they
have been removed
with the sash still tied?
How could they have taken off
their socks with their sandals
still on?
-Huh?
Hmm.
-Shinobu!
-Yes, sir.
-Contact Central 46.
Souls have vanished, and we
have our first Soul Reaper
casualties.
-Yes, sir.
-Izaemon.
-Sir.
-There's a possibility
of an unknown pathogen
that disintegrates souls.
Request that Squad 12
send lab personnel.
-Yes, sir.
-Heizo.
-Sir.
-Have the rest of the squad
standing by and send for tents.
We'll set up camp here tonight.
-Right.
-If this is the work of an
enemy targeting Soul Reapers,
then they will eventually
target the Seireitei as well.
We'll crush them here
before they get anywhere
near the Seireitei.
-Sir.
-Go!
-Captain, what about me?
-You and I will check the area.
Let's go.
Hey, kid.
You should go on home now, and
quickly, before it gets dark.
-Uh.
-Understand, kid?
-You weren't serious about
camping out, were you?
I'm not really a tent person.
-Sorry.
We're all out of
four star hotels.
-Kensei, you're such a jerk.
-Hmm.
Hmm.
Nice.
Very nice.
Hey, I'm still waiting
for container number 22!
I can't believe
how slow you are.
Move!
Hurry it up!
Damn it, at this rate, it'll be
dark before you bring it over.
-Shut your hole!
I was being nice
and helping you,
so that's no way to
talk to me, you jerk!
You better change your attitude!
-What are you so angry
about all of a sudden?
Honestly, that side of you.
It's quite a turn-off.
-Would you shut up already?
In the first place,
why do I have
to assist someone
as rude as you?
After all, I'm a lieutenant.
What in the hell is your rank?
Tell me that?
-Absurd.
Ranks are for commoners.
I have no need for
such silly labels.
-And yet you have a rank.
I'll tell you what it is.
You're a third, and
I'm a lieutenant.
I outrank you!
Which means you're not
allowed to order me around!
-You're misreading the
situation completely.
Here at the Department of
Research and Development,
I am the deputy head.
You're the laboratory chief,
which means I outrank you.
If you insist on quoting
squad rules to me,
then as long as you're
here, you must obey my
every command and not
the other way around.
-Kisuke!
-Yes?
What is it this time?
I was trying to get some sleep.
I thought I asked you
to be quiet, didn't I?
-Do something about this guy!
You obviously haven't
trained him well.
Huh?
What is that thing on your back?
-Oh, you mean this thing?
It's my prototype
for a new gigai.
Do you remember what Captain
Hirako said this morning?
About the incidents
in the Rukon District
where he believes
people vanished
without being able to
retain their human form?
Supposing that what
he says is true,
I thought that if
we were to place
a soul on the verge
of disintegration
into a human mold, the
soul would not vanish.
I'm trying to see if I
could apply gigai technology
to making that mold
into a reality.
-You're what?
IZAEMON (OFFSCREEN): Excuse me.
I'm Izaemon Todo,
Sixth Seat of Squad 9.
Is Kisuke Urahara,
Captain of Squad 12 here?
-Hm.
IZAEMON (OFFSCREEN): I've come
to convey a request from Kensei
Muguruma, Captain of Squad 9.
-Interesting.
I understand.
I'll select personnel
immediately and send them
tonight.
In the meantime,
I would like you
to go back and
help your captain.
-Yes sir.
Thank you very much.
-Now then, time to
select personnel.
Go on, go.
-Why the hell do I
have to go there?
Can't you send someone
lower in rank than me?
-All you do is complain.
You find everything
disagreeable.
Why don't you just quit
being a lieutenant already?
-Why don't I just
quit letting you live,
Akon, you disrespectful
little worm?
-It's ready, Deputy Head.
-Good work.
Thanks.
-Ugh, I hate all of you!
-I'm sorry, Hiyori, but
you're the only person
that I can confidently entrust
with a task as important
as this one.
Take anything you thank
you're going to need,
even if you have
to take something
from the Captain's office.
Remember, get a sample
from the site of the souls
that vanished.
It'll prove to be very valuable.
I'm counting on you, Hiyori.
Don't let me down.
-Aw, damn it.
OK, but I'm gonna need a
pretty big expense account!
Remember that!
-Huh?
I must say, when all
is said and done,
that I got off pretty cheap.
-What took you so long, Izaemon?
-I'm sorry.
I had to go to the Squad
12 barracks for assistance.
Please forgive me.
I'll relieve you now.
You can go inside and rest.
-You really shouldn't be so lax.
Now that you're back, the
three of us will keep watch.
-We'll take turns, one man
at a time, every two hours.
Heizo is resting inside with
the captain and the others.
You take watch over there.
-Right.
Understood.
MASHIRO (OFFSCREEN): [snoring]
-Huh?
-How can she fall
asleep so nonchalantly
under a condition like this one?
Hey, your collar fell open.
-Kensei, you're such
a pervert. [laughing]
-Ugh, you're even
annoying while asleep.
MALE SPEAKER
(OFFSCREEN): [groan]
-Huh?
What happened?
-Izaemon?
What in the world?
-[groan]
-Izaemon!
-Damn.
Keep your guard up, Heizo.
The enemy is still nearby.
Mashiro!
Wake up, Mashiro!
-[groan]
-Heizo!
Huh?
What-- what is this?
[groan]
You?
Not you.
[theme song]
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Captain Hirako,
why was Squad 9
sent to investigate?
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Kensei and Mashiro
are constantly fighting.
It's so noisy.
The Head Captain hasn't been
getting much sleep lately.
It's part of his
solution to the problem.
MALE SPEAKER
(OFFSCREEN): Really?
Look who's talking.