Now then.
Shall we get on with it?
Captain!
Yeagh!
Huh?
Hm?
Damn! Damn!
DAAAAMN!
Brother, are you...
[sigh] What are they
doing down there?
Well... the good news is, no
matter who lives and who dies,
I'll still acquire some
excellent research
specimens afterwards.
That was an impressive Cero.
That damn bastard.
I guess he still
has some power left.
[Byakuya]
It seems so.
You said he was
almost finished.
From over here,
it certainly doesn't
look that way.
Your assessment of
his condition has
proven very foolish.
Ha! I wasn't wrong. I told
ya all that guy needed was
someone to finish him off!
The only foolish part was
thinking (that) you could handle
it!
Is that so?
You doubt my abilities, do you?
Why don't you judge them for
yourself!?
Good idea.
I've always wanted to
fight you! And now's
as good a time as any!
Huh?
RAAAGHH!
[Both]
You're in the way.
Get lost.
Augghh!
Now then.
Shall we get on with it?
Hrrrnghh...
Ahh!
Hah??
He is persistent.
What a nuisance.
Heh heh heh heh...
Hah hah hah hah hah hah!
That hurts... You two are
starting to piss me off.
Ha ha ha ha!
What's with him? Has he
gone crazy or somethin'?
Unforgivable! Unforgivable!
Unforgivable!
[gasps]
What happened?!
[gasp]
What is that!?
Very good, you two. By all
means, keep annoying me.
Heh heh heh heh heh.
The name of my Resurrección
is Ira. I'm a beast of rage!
Anger fuels me,
it becomes my strength!
Come on! Keep at it. Make me
angrier! //
It will only make
your deaths... that
much more pathetic!
My word... Those two are
making things difficult.
I wish they'd just hurry up
and kill each other already.
I mean, if he gets
any larger...
it'll be difficult
to dissect his body.
Raagh!
Kaname!
[Sajin]
Kaname!!
Come back, Kaname!!
Have you forgotten?
You once told me why
you became a soul reaper.
Wasn't it for your friend who
lost their life? Wasn't it to
carry out your justice?!
I thought I had made
it clear to you.
My eyes can only see one path,
and that is the path with the
least amount of blood.
Justice is always there.
And the path I
follow is justice!
rrrr...RRAHH!
Friend of Kaname Tosen,
you whose name I do not know,
What would you have done?
What would you have said to
stop him?
Captain Komamura...
Do you think
he'll come back?
Or is Captain Tosen
gone for good?
He'll be back.
[Sajin]
But we must find a way to
open his eyes to the truth.
Well at least now
you are leaving us.
Hiyori!!
Hiyori...
I'm so sorry Shinji...
Don't speak...
I... did
hear you...
But I just couldn't
hold back.
How ferocious.
Your eyes look as if they've
come back to life for the first
time in a hundred years..
...Shinji Hirako.
[pained panting]
[Aizen]
Do you hate me?
If you do, by all means attack.
I'll make an exception,
And I'll only fight you
with my sword.
Hachi.
Yes, Shinji?
Sorry to ask you this in
your current state, but
please take care of Hiyori.
Do whatever you can
to keep her alive.
At least until
Ichigo returns.
Yes.
Shin... ji.
"Until Ichigo returns", eh?
You must trust that
boy quite a lot.
How very touching.
Yes, that must be
unfathomable,
...For someone who doesn't even
trust his own people.
You don't get it. Trust is the
same thing as reliance.
It's a fault of cowards.
I have no need for
such weakness.
That's pretty rich coming
from a guy who surrounds
himself with henchmen.
But you trick your subordinates
into trusting you.
With that fast-talking
silver tongue of yours.
Not quite.
I have many subordinates, many
who've pledged themselves to me.
But I've never asked
for any of their trust.
Yes, I've asked for their
allegiance. But faith is
another matter altogether.
In fact, I always told them
to never trust anyone...
including myself.
Unfortunately, though, I've met
no one who is strong enough to
actually heed that warning.
All creatures need to obey.
No one can survive without
trusting someone;
someone they feel is
better... more worthy
than themselves.
To avoid that responsibility,
those who are worthy look
even higher, searching for
more superior beings.
And those superiors do
the same, looking for
even stronger individuals
they can believe in.
That is how all
kings are created.
It is also...
how gods are born.
But please, don't believe
me yet, Shinji Hirako.
I am going to take my time,
and show you which god you
should have faith in.
And afterwards,
you'll decide
what to believe.
I'm surprised.
Frankly, I never
expected Lord
Aizen to go to
the front lines.
However, since Lord Aizen
has made his move,
I suppose that I
should take you on
with my true power.
Your true... power?
You mean your Bankai.
Very well, then I
shall use mine also.
My Bankai?
Hm?
Ridiculous.
Lord Aizen has granted
me a power that is far
more powerful than a
simple Bankai.
[gasps]
Damn you, Kaname!
It can't be!
That's a...
Stop now! Kaname!
Is this how far you've
fallen, bastard!?
Captain!
Hollowfication.
Is that... Is that
Hollowfication,
Captain Tosen?!
It is.
Ngh! But sir, why?
Shuhei, no!!
[pain grunts]
Agh! Tenken!!
Raaaghh!!
Hraaahhh!!
What?!
What... is this power?!
Eaauugh!
[Kaname]
It's odd.
You know, that half-Soul
Reaper boy you consider an
ally possesses the power
of Hollowfication as well.
I'm curious... why do you
scorn me like you do for
gaining this same power?
It's different...
Ichigo Kurosaki did not
Hollowfy by his own choice.
He's not the same as you.
As a Soul Reaper, you had more
than enough strength already.
And yet, you couldn't contain
your desire for more!
What you did was depraved!
Depraved?
How is it depraved for
Soul Reapers to become
closer to Hollows?
That's a simplistic
judgment from one who sees
all as soul reapers as good
and all hollows as evil.
You're wrong!
You betrayed your comrades,
you betrayed your friends,
you even betrayed your
followers.
All for the sake of
gaining excessive power.
That is the definition
of depravity!
Sajin...
[gasp]
It seems I didn't step close
enough to you. A naiïve mistake.
Not quite. I instinctively
dodged your blade by a hair.
Once you've drawn your sword,
always position yourself to be
able to sidestep an attack.
Captain Tosen, you taught me
that. In fact, it's because of
you that I was able to--
[Kaname]
What's wrong, Shuhei?
Why have you called me here?
You wished to speak with me.
What's troubling you?
Captain Tosen...
I beg you, relieve
me of my post as a
seated officer!
Ah. I understand.
Don't worry about your
mistake during training
yesterday. Everyone
starts off like that.
This is different!
I didn't fall behind because
I made a mistake or
because I was careless...
I was... I was just afraid!
My right eye was wounded
when I went to the World of
the Living for a drill.
Since then, I've been unsteady.
Whenever I draw my sword,
whenever I face an enemy,
I lose my confidence!
Captain Tosen... I'm just...
I'm too afraid to do battle!
You're afraid of battle,
are you?
That's exactly why you
should remain an officer.
The most important asset for a
warrior is not power... No...
It is a heart that
fears conflict.
A heart,
that fears?
That's right.
Even I fear
entering a
battle.
You, Captain Tosen?
I cannot see.
How could I not be
afraid to fight?
Gripping my sword...
even taking a step
forward like this...
it's incredibly terrifying.
Fear gives you the courage
to raise your sword, it
gives you the strength and
will to fight for others,
for those who
also fear battle.
Those who are unafraid to
hold their swords in battle,
don't have the right to
hold them at all.
(ct stunned)
Shuhei... if you are truly
afraid of fighting...
Then you have already
gained something
invaluable to a warrior!
But now...
I don't
understand,
Captain Tosen.
Those were
your words.
So why discard
everything for
mere power?!
What is it you fear now?!
Tell me, Captain, where is
that fear that guided you!?
Ngh... Agh...
Cap... tain...
Why...?
I am afraid.
I had the same fear
for a hundred years.
The fear of assimilating
and dying as a Soul Reaper.
[Sajin]
Bankai!
Kokujo Tengen Myo-oh!
[Sajin]
Kaname!
I swear, I will do
whatever it takes...
to open your eyes
to the truth!
[Shinji]
Like hell I'd believe
you, Sosuke!
[Sosuke Aizen]
A shame. I would have given you
a huge feast and a castle,
as well as anything
you could desire,
if you'd only believed me.
[Shinji]
What?!
[Sosuke Aizen]
Oh well...
[Shinji]
Wait! Give me a second
to reconsider!!