[theme music]
HITSUGAYA (OFFSCREEN): So
Aizen wasn't enough for you.
You couldn't be happy until
you'd hurt Momo as well.
You slid your lies into
her mind like a dagger
and twisted them until they were
so painful that her hands bled
from gripping her sword so hard.
ICHIMARU (OFFSCREEN): I'm sorry.
I'm afraid I don't follow you.
HITSUGAYA (OFFSCREEN):
I gave you a warning.
I told you that if you ever hurt
Momo, I would kill you myself!
ICHIMARU (OFFSCREEN):
[laugh] This will never do.
If you insist on drawing your
sword in a place like this,
then afraid you leave me no
other choice than to stop you.
IZURU (OFFSCREEN):
But Captain Ichimaru--
-Better move back, Izuru,
unless you feel like dying.
-[gasps]
HITSUGAYA (OFFSCREEN):
Don't be stupid, Izuru.
Just moving back isn't
going to be enough.
In a few minutes, I
promise you, you're
not going to want to be within
10 square miles of this place.
So start running,
and don't look back.
Because if you stay here, you're
liable to get drawn into this.
And I can't guarantee I
won't kill you by mistake.
[grunting]
ICHIMARU (OFFSCREEN):
An opening.
Evidently, the rumors about
Squad 10's Captain Hitsugaya
are true-- a child
prodigy of the sword
that comes along only
once every few centuries.
How very dangerous you are.
You're really serious.
-[growl]
IZURU (VOICEOVER): Incredible.
The level of his spiritual
pressure is crushing.
-Now, die!
-Hm.
-[shout]
[grunting]
-Well, Squad Captain,
what do you think now?
Do you still like your chances?
I see.
I had better not underestimate
you, Toshiro Hitsugaya, or else
I may wind up regretting
it afterwards.
-No, you're wrong about that.
Because you're going to start
regretting this day right now.
Remember, it's you who
forced me to do this, Gin.
And now you're going to pay
for what you did to Momo!
-[gasp]
-[shout]
Rain over the
frosted, frozen sky!
Hyorinmaru!
IZURU (OFFSCREEN): So this is
Hyorinmaru, a dragon of water
and ice created by overflowing
spiritual pressure.
In fact, they say it can
even affect the weather.
I've never seen it
before, but there's
no mistaking what it is--
the released form of Captain
Hitsugaya's,
Zanpakuto, Hyorinmaru.
-[shout] [grunt]
IZURU (VOICEOVER):
So much water!
Such velocity.
I couldn't dodge it!
[gasp] [scream]
-[shout]
-My captain!
-Now you're done, Gin Ichimaru.
-It appears his flesh.
Shinso.
Really?
Are you sure you
want to dodge this?
If you do, she'll die.
-[gasp] Momo!
Rangiku?
-Please forgive me, sir.
I was returning to my
quarters as you ordered.
But then I-- I felt
Hinamori's spiritual pressure
and thought you might need help.
Now, Captain Ichimaru,
please put away your sword.
If you refuse, then you're
going to have both of us
as your opponents.
-Hm.
[laugh]
YORUICHI (OFFSCREEN):
Day is breaking.
Only two days remaining.
Ichigo is growing
with startling speed
compared to ordinary
Soul Reapers.
The rate of his progress
is hard to believe.
But only his combat
techniques have improved.
His spirit energy has
barely changed at all.
-All right.
Exercise is finished.
I wonder where Yoruichi
ran off to now.
It's about time to get started
with the day's training.
YORUICHI (VOICEOVER):
At the rate we're going.
I don't know if he's
going to make it.
Can he achieve the Bankai
release in only two more days?
Or should I extend his training?
According to the
information I gathered
after we entered the
city, the grace period
between Rukia's execution date
was supposed to be 25 days.
We've used up 21
of them already.
That would mean that after
Ichigo's three days of training
here, the execution would be
the following day, with no time
to spare.
It turned out we were
chased by that Cleaner
inside of the Senzaikyu, and the
time frame shifted in our favor
when we entered
the Soul Society.
In other words, even after
our three days of training,
we still have eight days left
before Rukia's execution.
So there's definitely time
to extend the training.
But the question is, should I?
This three-day program
was created by Kisuke
and tested using his own body.
In fact, he's the only one
who has ever succeeded.
No one else has ever made
it to Bankai this way.
-Hey, Yoruichi!
YORUICHI (VOICEOVER):
In the process,
Kisuke determined that three
days was both the minimum
and the maximum amount of time
needed to acquire the release,
and that it would be
dangerous to continue
any longer than that.
-Yoruichi, where are you?
YORUICHI (VOICEOVER):
I remember him saying--
-Don't worry.
Ichigo's abilities are
far superior to my own.
YORUICHI (VOICEOVER):
I believed him.
And here we are, fully
engaged in training.
-Hey, Yoruichi!
YORUICHI (VOICEOVER):
But there's no guarantee
that Ichigo's soul will
be able to withstand
an extended training period.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
Yoruichi, damn it!
Come on out here.
What are you, afraid of me
all of a sudden and ran away?
Quit playing games with
me and let's get started!
You hear me?
YORUICHI (VOICEOVER): I'll
give him an extra day.
And after that, if there's still
no change in his spirit energy,
then we'll just have to risk it.
-What did you say?
[gasp]
-Did you not hear
the first time?
Very well.
I shall repeat
the pronouncement.
By executive order,
your execution date
has been changed once again.
Rukia Kuchiki, your execution
will be carried out tomorrow.
-If you hadn't shown up
there right when you did,
Momo would surely be dead now.
Thank you, Rangiku.
-You're welcome.
-[grunt]
[gasp]
-Hm.
-I'm not done with you yet!
-Instead of coming
after me, maybe you
should look after the
Squad Five lieutenant.
RANGIKU (VOICEOVER):
Once again, you
disappear without telling
me where you're going.
That's one thing about
you that's never changed.
Gin, tell me, where
are you going now?
HITSUGAYA (VOICEOVER): That
letter of Captain Aizen's-- I
wish I knew how much
of it was forged.
-(SCREAMING) Captain Aizen!
[cries]
HITSUGAYA (VOICEOVER):
The part in there
about using the power of Sokyoku
released by Rukia Kuchiki's
execution-- is that real?
Is thre really a plot
to use that power
to destroy all of
the Soul Society?
Could line have been true?
If it is true, if
that's Ichimaru's aim,
then I know what I have to do.
-A hell butterfly?
The following is
an urgent message
for all squad captains
and their lieutenants.
A change has been made regarding
the execution of Rukia Kuchiki.
Be advised that this convicted
prisoner's execution is now
set for 29 hours from now.
This decision is
final and irrevocable.
There will be no further
changes to the execution date.
That is all.
-[grunt]
-Captain?
-The execution and the
release of Sokyoku's power--
if Gin really is
the one behind this,
then there's no way I can
just stand by and let his plan
go forward.
Let's go, Rangiku.
You know what we have to
do-- stop the execution.
MAN (ON PA): The following is
an urgent message for all court
guard squad captains
and their lieutenants.
Another change has been
made regarding the execution
date of Rukia Kuchiki.
Be advised that the
prisoner's execution
is no set for 29 hour from now.
I repeat, the execution
of Rukia Kuchiki
is set for 29 hours from now.
This decision is
final and irrevocable.
There will be no further
changes to the execution date.
That is all.
-There's no doubt.
That's his spiritual pressure.
[fighting noises]
YORUICHI (VOICEOVER): Ichigo's
making steady progress.
But still, I just
can't seem to shake
this uneasy feeling I have.
I'm sensing something out
there, something ominous
approaching this place.
-[gasp]
RENJI (OFFSCREEN):
I was wondering
what you could be doing,
holed up in this place.
I take it that's the true
form of your Zanpakuto there
with you.
So, you're hiding out here and
secretly training for Bankai,
are you?
Looks like fun to me.
-[gasp]
-Let me train along with you.
-RENJI (OFFSCREEN).
-You seem to have that "what
are you doing here?" look.
Hell, I guess I can't
blame you for wondering.
But the fact is, I'm not
here for any special reason.
It's just that we're
out of time now.
So I needed some place where
I could concentrate and train
in peace, just like you.
-What do you mean
we're out of time?
What the hell are
you talking about?
-Well, all right.
I guess I can at least
tell you that much.
It's about Rukia's execution.
They've changed the time.
-Changed the time?
-They've announced it's going
to be at noon-- noon tomorrow.
-[grunt]
-[gasp]
-And though I hate
to admit it, the fact
is, at my current level,
I'm not quite good
enough to save Rukia.
That's why I came
here-- to train.
Don't worry about me.
I don't have any
intention of getting
in the way of your
Bankai training.
In fact, I'm close to achieving
the Bankai release myself.
I've already mastered
manifesting it, like this.
So, if it's OK
with you, I'm just
going to do my own thing here.
-Noon tomorrow?
No way.
There's no way he can
reach Bankai that quickly.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): What?
Are you just going to
give up on me then?
Come on, Yoruichi.
You're the one who started
me on this training program.
It was your idea, so you can't
be the first one to quit on it.
-Ichigo, no.
What if tomorrow comes and you
still can't achieve Bankai?
-We can't waste time
worrying about what-ifs.
Failure is no longer an option.
If they have changed the
deadline to tomorrow,
then the only option there is
is to finish training today.
YORUICHI (VOICEOVER):
His spiritual pressure.
Ichigo.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
So tomorrow I die.
I wonder if before
the execution,
it would be worth begging
for Ichigo and the others
to be allowed to return to
the World of the Living.
I belong to the Kuchiki
clan, after all.
They might allow it.
It seems strange,
but even when I
heard that my execution was
set for tomorrow, I wasn't sad.
It must be because
of the dream I
had last night, that dream about
the night I can never forget.
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN): Kaien, sir.
Kaien!
Kaien.
[crying] Don't.
You can't die on me.
[crying] Kaien, you can't go!
[music - "happy people"]
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
Kaien, I'm afraid there
is nothing of me
that's worth saving.