[music playing]
[THEME MUSIC - AQUA TIMEZ,
"VELONICA"]
NARRATOR: Ichigo
and his friends had
entered Hueco Mundo to
rescue Orihime Inoue.
But one by one, the powerful
Espadas took them down.
Running out of
options, they were
shocked to find themselves
saved by Soul Reapers who
were supposed to have pulled
out of the battle earlier.
KENPACHI ZARAKI:
What's going on here?
You're in a real
fix, aren't you?
[laughs]
ICHIGO KUROSAKI: Kenpachi.
-I swear I already said that
I could more than handle this
by myself.
No one hears or
believes what I say.
So you finally attack.
Unh!
Hunh!
Huh!
Hnnh!
Hah!
-We are here only to
heal everyone's wounds.
We have no intention
of fighting you.
-Huh.
After all, no matter
what, I'll crush you.
Finding out your name would
really just be a waste of time.
-Oh, really?
And yet I'm thinking it could
end up being quite a problem
if I don't get
your name from you.
-Why is what?
-Why?
Only an idiot would ask that.
It should be rather obvious why.
So that when I stuff
you into a jar,
I'll be able to write
your name on the label.
-Hm.
I've decided after all that
I will ask you your name
so you'll have a pet name
when you become my marionette.
-This is bad.
Those things are fatal.
-Captain Kurotsuchi!
NARRATOR: Byakuya Kuchiki
faced Espada Number Seven,
Zommari Rureaux.
Under Zommari's
overwhelming power of Amor,
Byakuya gradually lost
control over his own body.
When Byakuya could
not be swayed,
Zommari was forced to
change his mode of attack.
He turned his
attention to Rukia,
who was still
unconscious following
her battle with Aaroniero.
Zommari took control of
Rukia's mind and subsequently
her entire body.
He used Rukia to cut
down Hanataro Yamada, who
was trying to offer her
emergency first aid.
Then Zommari resorted
to a most cowardly move,
setting sister against brother.
ZOMMARI RUREAUX: Don't move.
You see the dilemma.
Throw down your sword,
Captain Kuchiki.
Face the fact you have lost.
-Bakudo number 61 Rikujokoro.
--[grunts with effort]
What is this move?
Move.
Move!
[grunting with effort]
BYAKUYA KUCHIKI: You
wanted to control me?
Let me tell you, you don't
have nearly enough power
to ever make that happen.
Bankai.
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
-What?
What is this? [gasps]
[explosion]
[rubble clattering all around]
ZOMMARI RUREAUX: Oh, ah!
Oh!
Damn you.
You want to see power?
I will control everything
using every ounce of Amor
in my spirit!
BYAKUYA KUCHIKI: Gokei
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Senbornzakura Kageyoshi's
billion blades.
It engulfs the enemy in a
sphere and tears them apart
from every direction.
Be swallowed by a hail
of steel and perish.
[explosion]
[rumbling]
[dripping]
-You're very stubborn.
[wet ripping]
ZOMMARI RUREAUX:
[breathing with difficulty]
-Bastard!
What you've done is
totally unforgivable!
-Bakudo number 81 Danku.
[smash]
-Oh!
What is that?
-It is a protective wall that
completely shuns any Hado
techniques under number 89.
I was able to stop
Rukia using Rikujokoro.
Therefore I ascertained that
your power is similar to Kido.
It seems I was correct.
[grunting]
[shouts]
-Accept my Amor.
Accept it!
Oh!
BYAKUYA KUCHIKI: Your impatience
limited your field of vision.
I guess you're not as
fast as you claim to be.
-Show mercy.
Why are you looking
at me like that?
You're going to refuse.
You're going to kill me.
Stop torturing me
with your silence.
Your arrogance makes me sick.
(SHOUTING) Makes me sick!
Did you ever stop to
consider what you're doing?
You go around so
righteously killing
those who live in existence
of complete futility.
Have you thought
about what you do,
about the meaning
of killing Hollows
like us as though it
was a natural thing?
Soul Reapers kill us Hollows
without the slightest
thought of remorse, as if it
were a natural thing to do.
[laughs quietly] Who
do you think you are?
(SHOUTING) Do you think you're
a bunch of gods or something?
Who gives you the
authority to kill?
Why do you target us Hollows?
Is it because we devour humans?
Yes, it's true, we
do devour humans.
But who gave the Soul
Reapers the right
to protect human beings?
Did someone give you that right?
I don't think so.
The answer is no!
No one has given you any such
right to protect the humans.
You label us as evil creatures
and go to great lengths
to try to get rid of us, and
all because you arbitrarily
decided that justice is on
the side of the Soul Reaper.
That's the arrogance I speak of.
That smug look you all have,
it makes me want to throw up!
Nngh.
BYAKUYA KUCHIKI:
It's funny, I don't
remember saying that
I would kill you
because I'm a Soul Reaper.
-Oh.
BYAKUYA KUCHIKI: The reason
I'm killing you is simple.
It's because you aimed your
blade at my only pride.
Now this is your fate.
[clink]
[rushing hiss]
[breathing jaggedly]
-(SHOUTING) Banzai!
Banzai!
Buh-- banzai!
Long live Lord Aizen!
Banzai!
[strangled cry]
[fwoom]
BYAKUYA KUCHIKI: It's over.
Come on out.
Isane Kotetsu, did
Captain Unohana send you?
-Yes.
We sensed from a
spiritual pressure
that the Seventh Seat Yamada
had been seriously injured
in battle.
-I see.
Take care of them.
[breathing with difficulty]
[laughter]
[whimpers]
[breathing with difficulty]
-Aaaaaagghhhhh!
SZAYELAPORRO GRANZ: [laughs]
How very disappointing.
I mean, really, I expected
much more from a captain.
Before my power, you
are completely helpless.
[crack]
[retches]
-Oh no!
Master Mayuri!
[crack]
[retches]
SZAYELAPORRO GRANZ:
[sinister laugh]
-Unbelievable.
-Not Captain Kurotsuchi as well.
-Down on your knees,
unslightly for a captain.
That venomous outward
appearance you
have is all just a big show.
-How dare you?
You will pay for this!
No one can do this to
me and get away with it.
Do not underestimate me!
-[laughs]
[crunch] [snap]
-Aaaaghh!
-Aren't captains
supposed to be strong?
All of you have been
such disappointments.
-Why, you-- [grunting]
[snap]
MAYURI KUROTSUCHI: Gaahhhh!
-[giggles quietly]
MAYURI KUROTSUCHI: Aahh!
Gaahh!
Ahhh!
-Master Mayuri!
-[panting] I never thought in my
wildest dreams that I would end
up here, dying in
a place like this.
-It's all over.
[snap]
--[gasp] (SHOUTING)
Master Mayuri!
-[gasp]
-It can't be!
[roars with laughter] This is
so easy it's become boring.
I thought there would
be more to it than this.
-I got you!
-[gasp] What's going on?
-My, my, my.
-I don't get it.
How are you still
standing in front of me?
Nngh!
-Come again?
-Ngggh!
[crack and crunch]
[retches]
-I'm glad to see the
doll is still working.
[crackle]
[retches]
-[laughs quietly]
MAYURI KUROTSUCHI:
You should stop that.
-Uh?
-I'm getting awfully tired
of that parlor trick.
Get up, Nemu.
-Yes, sir.
-I never thought
that the Captain
could be defeated
easily, but this?
Let me tell you
something, it's sick
that he could endure
that much pain.
-Hold it.
Just what's going
on here, anyway?
SZAYELAPORRO GRANZ: [scoffs]
[stomp]
-Oh!
-Damn!
Damn!
[grunting with frustration]
-[laughs]
-It can't be!
I smashed your organs
and your muscles,
so why aren't you dead?
Just what kind of
power do you have?
-Stop being such a loudmouth.
It's not about the
power that I have.
It's just that the power that
you have is pretty damn boring,
that's all.
-What?
Boring?
MAYURI KUROTSUCHI:
See that Quincy?
I have a very cautious nature.
When I fight someone
new, I always
try to lay a trap
during the battle.
A favorite is when I
infect my enemy's body
with infinite quantities
of surveillant bacteria.
-You what?
MAYURI KUROTSUCHI:
Through the bacteria
I was able to observe
every battle that you had.
Therefore, just
before coming here
to take part in this
battle, I created
replicas of every single
organ and muscle in my body.
-Ridiculous!
I mean, not even a full hour
has passed since I first
revealed my power to the Quincy.
You couldn't have done
it in such a short time.
It's not possible.
You lie!
-On the contrary, I can, I
did, and that is why I'm here.
[sputtering with rage]
[thud]
-Hey, hold it!
-Oh boy, here comes
another speech.
-You're damn right.
I've got something to say
and I'm going to say it.
Bacteria?
When did you infect me?
During our battle?
I don't appreciate being
spied on like that.
How much did you
observe, anyway?
You can't spy on
my private life.
That's against basic human
rights, an invasion of privacy!
I demand that you remove
the bacteria right now.
Hey, what's with you, anyway?
Are you listening to me?
-Quiet, you fiend.
-I was going to call you that!
You're the fiend, you-- you--
RENJI ABARAI: Stop it, Uryu.
Don't get yourself so worked up!
URYU ISHIDA: Don't
stop me, Renji!
RENJI ABARAI: But why do you
have to discuss this now?
URYU ISHIDA: If
not now, then when?
[rumbling]
-Hah.
-Oh no!
-Careless again, you
so-called captain.
You didn't pay enough attention
to your subordinate's foothold.
-It seems to me
that you're possibly
under the wrong impression.
True, you can capture me, but
I'm useless as your hostage.
-Silence!
You will only speak
when spoken to, captive!
Are you listening,
so-called Captain?
I'm speaking to you.
MAYURI KUROTSUCHI: My goodness.
Everyone keeps chattering.
It's so noisy.
Bankai.
Now claw out!
-[gasps]
[bells ringing]
[baby cries]
MAYURI KUROTSUCHI:
Konjiki Ashisogi Jizo!
SZAYELAPORRO GRANZ:
What is this?
Where did it come from?
[hiss]
-What the hell?
This gas, some kind of bacteria?
Really, I'm sure I can
easily counteract this.
MAYURI KUROTSUCHI: [chuckles]
-Huh?
What's wrong?
What's going on
with this poison?
MAYURI KUROTSUCHI: [snickers]
-Ahhh!
Ah!
Impossible!
Yah!
Nnngh!
[panting] If only I
had time, I could--
I could-- damn, damn, damn!
[screams]
[MUSIC - STEREOPONY, "HITOHIRA
NO HANABIRA"]
BYAKUYA KUCHIKI: Isane
Kotetsu, why were you hiding?
ISANE KOTETSU
(VOICEOVER): I heard
the Arrancar confessing
its love to you, sir,
so, well, I-- isn't it
embarrassing to have someone
witness a declaration of love?
BYAKUYA KUCHIKI:
I don't understand
a thing you're saying.