That's right... Come on.
Getsuga... Tensho!
Los Nueve Aspectos.
Shall we end this now?
What do you say?
Justice...
...isn't something that's
seen with your eyes.
Justice is something
mere words can't
completely describe.
Forgive me, Kaname...
I cannot kill you...
I know you too well.
That's enough. You're not
really Captain Tosen anymore.
Before this, when you
couldn't see, you could have
easily dodged my attack.
Reap...
...Kazeshini!
[choking]
Over here!
What's wrong, Sosuke?!
You look quite confused!
I've got you!
So that's it...?
Your whole strategy was nothing
more than an optical illusion.
Yours was a parlor trick. It's
quite a far cry from my ability
to control all five senses.
It was child's play for me,
Shinji Hirako.
Mm.. Uh?
Sajin...
Shuhei...
Don't speak. Your Hollow
powers are allowing you
to breathe, but your
throat's been torn open.
You don't need to talk
right now. It's better that
you save your strength...
Our relationship has been all
too superficial until now.
Even as friends,
it was our fate to
fight each other.
And by fighting,
We have come to a
greater understanding
between us.
I can't ask you
not to hate me.
I know you'll probably
hold a grudge after
what's happened.
Just don't allow your
hunger for revenge to
change who you truly are.
I feel just as you
must have felt when
you lost your friend.
If we were to lose you,
it would leave a
hole in my heart.
I thank you... Sajin.
Uhng!
Captain!
Aizen!!
I won't forgive you... Aizen!!
You're mine!
Yeeeaaah!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Ichigo!
Yahhh!
[panting]
What ?!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
...Ryoka boy.
Damn it... He blocked my attack!
Your attack was good, but
your aim was predictable.
The back of the neck is every
creature's worst blind spot.
Did you think I would come
into this battle without
protecting my point of
greatest vulnerability?
Let me guess what you're
thinking at this moment.
You think you made an error
of judgment just now.
That you should have
Hollowfied before attacking.
You think if you had done that,
this would all be over.
Tell me I'm wrong.
He's not wrong. I had to take
him down with the first blow.
I knew that!
I can't look at his Shikai!
My one hope is to take him
down quickly!
The only strategy
is to kill him!
There might not be
a second chance!
I was careless!
Somewhere deep inside,
I was scared!
I thought I might lose
control of my Hollowfication.
It WAS an error
of judgment!
Attack me.
[gasp]
Take your best shot.
It'll only prove to you
how arrogant you've become.
That's right. Come on.
Getsuga... Tensho!
[gasp]
What's wrong?
It didn't reach me.
Is that all you've got?
You're wasting your
time, Ryoka boy.
You can attack me all you
like, but your efforts
will be meaningless.
You seem very confident.
So my Hollowfication
doesn't scare you, is that it?
That's not what
I'm talking about.
Then what is it?
Are you saying that my
Zanpakuto is incapable
of killing you? Huh?!
Apparently, you don't
understand.
I guess I'll have to
explain it to you in
much simpler terms.
I'm telling you that no
matter what you do, your
blade cannot touch me.
That's quite the claim!
Care to put it to the test?
It's not a test if
I know the outcome.
But you won't believe
it unless you see it
for yourself.
You got that right!
So let's see if
you're lying or not!
I don't believe it.
He says he can dodge
my Getsugatensho any
time he wants.
All right,
then...
Yahhh!
What's wrong?
You seem to have missed me.
I don't understand! My timing
was perfect! I was sure of it!
Is his Zanpakuto that strong?!
Just so you know...
I haven't been using my
Kyokasuigetsu's power
in our fight so far.
What you're seeing is
just my basic strength.
What?!
(Small nervous breath as he
jumps back)
Why are you
pulling away?
If you intend to attack me,
you'll have to come closer.
Or maybe...
...you're afraid that
getting any closer will
put you at a disadvantage,
and make you vulnerable.
If that's the case,
you need a reality check.
Keeping a distance between
yourself and your opponent
is only meaningful when
you're fighting someone equal
in strength and skills.
It's pointless for you
to do that with me.
See...?
I can reach out and
touch your heart.
Without even
breaking a sweat.
Let me just ask you
something, Ryoka boy.
Do you have any idea
why you're fighting me?
What?
Do you have a grudge
against me or something?
I don't really think you do.
I have to assume from the
fact that you're here,
that you succeeded in
taking back Orihime Inoue.
And from the expression on your
face, I can also assume that
none of your friends have died.
With that in mind, do you
honestly despise me, from the
very bottom of your heart?
I don't believe that.
At the moment, you
have no deep-seated
hatred of me.
You're fighting me out
of a sense of misplaced
responsibility.
You weren't motivated
enough to defeat me.
A fighting spirit that
lacks hate is like an
eagle without wings.
You have the will,
but you don't have
the tools to do the job.
And your powerless friends
are no help, either.
They only serve as weights
to restrict your movements,
and drag you down.
Concentrate, Ichigo!
Don't let him into
your head!
Captain Komamura...?
He's a master at undermining
your confidence. If you let
him do that, he'll destroy
you for sure.
You mustn't let your guard down.
Keep your mind clear.
I know why the captains
who went to Hueco Mundo
sent you here first.
You haven't fallen
victim to Aizen's Shikai.
Our job is to make sure
you remain unaffected
by that weapon.
Ichigo, we will all
fight to protect you.
You're gonna fight
to protect me?
What are you saying?
It's just crazy! Look at you,
You're all in terrible shape!
That's a matter of perspective.
We think letting you fight alone
would be even crazier.
Besides, if we allowed that,
we wouldn't be able to
settle our own personal
grudges with Sosuke.
It would be selfish of you to
take him on by yourself.
This... is a battle...
for all of us.
You charged in without any
thought as to strategy or
strength. That was very reckless
of you, Captain Hitsugaya.
We won't be able to win this
battle unless we attack first.
Missing this opportunity would
be playing into your hands.
I must commend you
though, Aizen, for not
using your Kyokasuigetsu,
right from the start.
I commend you as well,
for having the wisdom
to not face me alone.
Are you saying we're
playing dirty with you?
How very insulting.
If that's how you're taking it,
I stand corrected,
Captain Kyoraku.
Can the two of them
get past his defenses?
We'll see, won't we?
Thank you, by the way, for
coming to help me earlier.
I won't forgive you... Aizen!!
If you hadn't jumped in and
attacked Aizen when you did,
I would have lunged
at him in a fit of
uncontrollable rage,
And I would be dead.
I'm glad I could help.
Aizen said, without hate in
your heart, you would never
be able to defeat him.
But the fact of the
matter is, we know that
statement's not true.
Even without hatred,
you've won countless
battles.
And you've protected countless
numbers of people. You need to
know that your desire to protect
people is enough to do the job.
For you, it's a stronger
emotion than hatred.
You just have to focus
on that. The positive
will outweigh the
negative.
And that will be
enough to reach Aizen.
And when I say 'reach' him,
what I mean is,
It won't be your blade,
but your soul.
That guy sure likes to
talk a lot, doesn't he?
Man, Ichigo, Why didn't you
bring Orihime with you when you
came for this fight?
I mean, doesn't it make
perfect sense? If she
was here, she could have
healed all our injuries.
Then we would have been
in great shape to help
you take on Sosuke.
Hirako...
But...
You did bring back
Captain Unohana, who's more
experienced, so I have to
give you credit for that.
[Shinji]
Now that I think about it,
it was definitely the right
choice for this battle.
Listen to me, Ichigo. We're
going to protect you as much as
we can. Just make sure...
...you're fighting to protect
what's important to you.
[Soi Fon]
How long are you going
to just stand there?
They can only create an
opening for an instant.
You need to take advantage
of that opportunity.
Don't assume that we're
prepared to die in this
battle. We're actually
fighting for our survival.
Saving the world puts a
nice gloss on the mission.
But the bottom line is,
we're all desperately trying
to defeat this monster,
so we have a future
that doesn't involve
being enslaved by him.
It's a pretty strong
motivation, and in the
process, the world ends
up getting saved anyway.
Don't fall behind,
Ichigo Kurosaki. You're
the key to this battle.
Hold on! I'm
coming, too, Wait
for me captain!
That's right...
What is your duty?
You know the answer.
Your duty is to
protect Karakura Town.
Go on... You are their
Substitute Soul Reaper.
What is there for
me to worry about?
The Visoreds and the
Captains are behind me!
I have to believe in them...
They're committed to
this battle. They'll be
there if I need them!
Focus on their fighting! Wait
until they give me an opening!
Good thing you
moved when you did.
I almost had you.
You seem quite confident,
Captain Kyoraku.
If that's how it appears,
I must be doing pretty well.
Thank you.
For someone who's
launching sneak attacks,
you are.
Aizen...
I heard what you
said to Ichigo,
At the moment, you
have no deep-seated
hatred of me,
You're fighting me out
of a sense of misplaced
responsibility.
You aren't motivated
enough to defeat me.
(Small CT defiant breath as he
sets himself)
A fighting spirit that
lacks hate is like an
eagle without wings.
You have the will,
but you don't have
the tools to do the job.
I want to explain
something to you.
The only time a Captain ever
swings his sword, is when
it is clearly his duty.
Swinging a sword out of
hatred is nothing more than
mindless violence. There is
no honor in such behavior.
Aizen...
Your words and actions
prove that you were never
worthy of being a captain.
Hmf.
How interesting.
You hate me more than
any other Captain in
the Thirteen Court
Guard Squads.
I never expected you to
make such a statement.
Can you honestly say you're
not directing hatred at me
with your sword right now?
Or perhaps, when Momo
recovered from her
injuries and came to the
World of the Living,
...all your anger
evaporated and disappeared?
How rude...
I'm talking right now,
Captain Kyoraku.
You still love to interrupt
people's conversations.
It's a bad habit of yours.
I guess I'm busted.
I'm not very good at
listening to men carry on.
The fact is, I usually
find them quite boring.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
But you might as well
know, I intend to continue
talking as I take on the
two of you in battle.
[Toshiro]
Say what you will.
But you can stop
talking for now, Aizen.
Bankai!
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!
I guess what you said
earlier was right.
This sword is filled with
hatred, hatred of you!
I realize now I didn't
come here to fight you,
I came here to destroy
you and end your terror!
Hrraaaaahh!!
[Ichigo]
Komamura! What the hell?
What happened to you?!
[Komamura]
What are you talking about?
Your fur! It looks so weird!
It's all fluffy!
Sorry about that. Captain
Hitsugaya's Spiritual Pressure
was so cold, my body reacted
this way instinctively!
You mean that's
your winter coat?