[theme music]
[crying]
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): The
dirt and depression
of the Rukon District
hasn't changed at all.
Hm?
[coughing] Huh?
-Huh?
Well, well.
-It can't be.
-It's you again.
What a coincidence.
This'll be fun.
[inaudible] Nieder.
Let's go.
Ha!
Hmph.
What's this?
You don't even have a zanpakuto?
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
She's much stronger
than she was the last
time I faced her.
-It's one of the Bounts!
Rukia.
But you can't beat her
without a zanpakuto.
-Huh?
Hmph.
Worthless trash.
From what I heard, Mabashi
had no trouble making you
into his personal plaything.
-You certainly are cute.
It's making me excited.
[laughter]
-Shut up!
-Yeah?
So you want a fight?
-Oh, my, my.
Do you mean another fight?
And I was right in the
middle of my tea time.
-And I remember distinctly
telling you never
to call for me when I'm
in the middle of my nap.
-Quit complaining, and
just follow orders.
I've got work to do.
-Rukia.
You fool.
How could you have
let yourself get
talked into this by a Bount?
Never let your
emotions rule you.
And what could you
possibly do now
with that old piece
of garbage sword?
-Are you just going
to stand there?
-Then you won't mind if I go.
-It's starting!
-I guess I'm going in.
Oh!
She got me!
-I'll take care of you.
-Ha!
How could-- Whoa!
-Oh!
Rukia, get up!
Get up and run away!
I've been trying
to tell you, you're
no match for her in
the state you're in!
Why won't you just run?
-Don't you understand?
You cannot defeat me.
I doubt that you'll even
be able to touch me.
[laughter]
-Those who underestimate
me will pay the price!
-What a clever little
saying that is.
Let's go ahead and prove
it wrong, shall we?
-Beautifully.
And with flawless technique.
Now let's torment her.
-Oh!
No!
I can't just stand here
and watch this happen!
-Huh?
What?
-Come on, Rukia.
Why are you just standing there?
Hurry up and defeat her
while you have the chance!
I can't keep this up
forever, you know.
-Ririn.
All right.
The one who reigns, mask
of flesh, all creation,
flap of wings, the one who
carries the title of human!
In the name of truth
and temperance,
dig your claws into the
wall of sinless dreams!
Hado 33, Sokatsui!
[scream]
-Ah!
Why didn't you defend yourself?
-You're still not worthy.
-Why's she raising
her arm like that?
Does that mean
she's surrendering?
-Is she--
[shout]
-Could she be absorbing reishi?
-If she's absorbing reishi,
she'll turn into a monster!
-Ririn--
-You've gotta run
away now, Rukia!
-Ha ha ha ha ha!
This taste, no matter how
many times I taste it,
I can't get enough!
Ha ha ha ha!
-Come on, Rukia.
We've gotta get out of here.
This way.
-Was that on purpose?
-It would seem you
have a deathwish.
-Argh!
-Look out!
-Witness the result
of my life's devotion.
-Rukia!
-There you are.
There's no use running from me.
You should have
learned that by now!
Was that an illusion?
Huh?
-Ah!
-That was your
handiwork, wasn't it?
I must admit, it's
impressive that you
were able to trick
me with that twice.
-Please don't kill me.
-No?
Then what exactly do
you want me to do?
Do you want me to let her
escape, and fight you instead?
Huh?
Do you think that's
a good decision?
-I don't remember
saying that, exactly.
-I'm gonna turn you--
-You're going to be
sorry you attacked Ririn!
Hado number four!
Byakurai!
-Rukia!
-You saved us by distracting her
long enough for me to counter
attack.
-No problem.
[laughter]
-You're both slow
learners, aren't you?
The real fun is just beginning.
-She really is a monster.
And an incredibly dangerous one.
Come on, Ichigo.
You've gotta save both of us.
-After conducting
extensive research
into old historical
documents that
were provided to us
by the Kuchiki clan,
there is a fair amount
of new information
that I can report to you.
-Oh?
-At one time there was a series
of experiments conducted here
in the Seireitei, the very
nature of which would now
be strictly prohibited.
These events occurred long
before the establishment
of our Department of
Research and Development.
The instigator of these
experiments was a scientist
named Ran'Tao, was
is also referred
to in the Kuchiki's historical
documents as the evil
researcher.
Ran'Tao's work was apparently
centered on the study
of eternal life.
But at some point there
was a serious accident,
and a number of souls
in the cycle of rebirth
were directly effected.
A mutated strain of humans
with abnormal abilities
was born in the
world of the living.
These are the Bounts.
After the accident, Ran'Tao
accepted responsibility
for the tragedy, and was
subsequently banished from
the Seireitei.
As for the Bounts, they
were purged, so as not
to cause harm to the
world of the living.
-Was it to protect the
world of the living?
Or did some superior just want
to bury the evidence in order
to conceal his own involvement?
-Careful, Shunsui.
-It doesn't matter.
All that matters now
is that we recognize
this is a problem
of our own doing.
-This would seem to confirm
that the Bounts are here
for revenge, just as Lieutenant
Matsumoto reported to us.
-Hm.
Possible.
But regardless of their
reason for coming here,
the Bounts must now be
completely annihilated.
There is one last bit of
news I shall impart to you.
The Substitute Soul
Reaper, Ichigo Kurosaki,
has reentered the Soul Society
from the world of the living.
-That Ichigo is one
hardworking boy, isn't he?
-A thousand pardons, captains.
I have come with an
emergency dispatch.
Bount waves and Rukia
Kuchiki's spiritual pressures
have been detected.
-Open the gates!
Onward, to the East
Rukon District Area 43!
Help is on the way, Rukia!
-Ichigo!
Is that you?
-Orihime?
What's the matter?
-W-w-w-we found them!
We found the Bounts!
Or one of them, at least.
We're detecting a
Bount's presence.
This is very bad.
-What are you talking about?
[gasp]
RUKIA: Hado 33, Byakurai!
-What happened to you?
Your power seems a lot
weaker than it did before.
That's surprising.
I didn't think you had that
kind of strength left in you.
But, what'll you do now?
-Let's end this
fight beautifully.
-And then end her
life perfectly.
-That's the idea.
-Bakuda One!
Sai!
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): Good.
I've stopped her
movement for now.
[scream]
-Hado 33!
Sokatsui!
She's not hurt.
[scream]
[laughter]
YOSHI: You don't give up easily.
I'll give you that.
Which means that for me,
the fun just lasts longer.
[laughter]
-Ririn.
-Rukia.
Come this way.
I have something for you.
It's not much, but
it's something.
What happened to your arm?
You're wounded.
Why didn't you heal it with
that Kido you're so good at?
You can, can't you?
-Well, normally I'd
be able to, but--
-Rukia.
Is it because your spiritual
pressure is completely--
what is it?
-Shh.
You got left behind here.
-Rukia!
-I know.
The Bount's here.
Take this girl and run.
-Huh?
But I can't leave you alone.
-Please don't argue.
Just get this child
to a safe place, now.
[clattering] Ririn, over here.
[scream]
[coughing]
-Throw away your sword.
Now.
-Get your hands off her!
-Well, that depends
on what you do.
I have a lot of patience,
but your silly games
have taxed me to the limit.
-Oh, Rukia.
Grr.
-And don't try
anything funny, or I
promise I'll crush this girl's
head before you can move.
-You monster!
-I guess you don't care
about her after all.
[scream]
-How foolish you are.
Interesting.
I find myself
getting excited just
thinking about all the different
ways I might finish you off.
-Rukia!
-Finally, it's almost over.
[scream]
-I prefer the quick,
bloody finish.
[groan]
-Do it all at once.
Let's slice her up until
her flesh and blood
are indistinguishable
from each other.
-Excellent.
-You're killing her!
Stop this, you murderer!
-You sure are noisy.
-Ah!
Ichigo.
-I feel so beautiful right now.
-Witness the perfection
of this technique.
-Scatter, Senbon Zakura.
[groan]
ICHIGO: Rukia!
Byakuya.
Orihime!
Take care of the little girl.
I'll get Ririn.
-All right.
-Rukia!
-Is she all right?
-Oh, it's you, Captain Kuchiki.
-Send for the relief
team immediately.
-Right away, sir.
-How's she doing, Orihime?
-She's all right.
She's just unconscious.
-Come look at Ririn, then.
She seems to be pretty bad.
-I-- I tried.
-You did just fine.
Orihime's going to fix you up.
-Byakuya?
[laughter]
-My job here is done.
For now.
-Come back!
[theme music]
VOICEOVER: Rukia's brother sure
showed up in the nick of time.
VOICEOVER: He was probably
just waiting around
for the perfect moment.
VOICEOVER: How tricky.
Obviously he knows how
to make a grand entrance.
VOICEOVER: Maybe he's more
than just a spoiled boy
from a rich family.
VOICEOVER: You'd
better hope he doesn't
slice you both to
pieces later on.
[theme music]
VOICEOVER: Illustrated
Guide To Soul Reapers.
VOICEOVER: Golden!
-What a nice moon.
-Sure is.
-Have a cup of sake.
-Oh.
Thank you.
-Oh, moon watching should
always be like this.
MAN: Hey, what's going on
with the moon all of a sudden?
-All of you, quit making
fun of my bald head!
-The moon's smooth!