[theme music]
-[gasp] Renji.
Renji!
Why, why'd you do it?
Huh?
[gasp]
-Good morning.
How are you today, Rukia dear?
-Ichimaru.
Gin.
ICHIMARU: Such bad
manners, Rukia.
But I see you are just the
same as you always were-- still
rude.
You know, you must
always address me only
as Captain Ichimaru.
If you're not careful, you
may get a serious scolding
from your brother, Byakuyu.
-I apologize, Captain Ichimaru.
-[laughs] Oh, no.
Did you think I was serious?
Don't worry.
I'm about to turn you in.
I really don't even
mind, since you and I
have known each
other for so long.
-I know that you didn't come
by to make small talk, Captain.
Tell me, why are you here?
-Well, I suppose no
particular reason, Rukia.
I was out taking
a walk and thought
I'd visit, just to
tease you a little bit.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): I
never liked this man.
The first time we met was before
I joined the 13 Court Guard
Squads, just after my brother
was made captain of Squad Six.
Gin became captain of Squad
Three about the same time.
And I remember him
chatting with Byakuyu
whenever they happened to meet.
It didn't look like anything
other than two captains
exchanging pleasantries.
There was never anything
of any substance said.
So to an outsider,
they would have
seemed like normal
conversations.
But they never seemed
that way to me.
From the first time I
laid eyes on this man,
I broke out in a cold
sweat all over my body.
His fingertips, his
lips, the way his eyes
narrowed and shifted-- he
reminded me of a snake.
And though he was
speaking to my brother,
I felt as if he had his
hands around my neck.
I was frozen, afraid
even to blink my eyes.
I've always hated this man.
It seemed like he could find
the smallest crack in those
around him and seep deep
down into you, like venom.
That's the kind of
fear he arouses.
I've never had any rational
reason for feeling this way.
But something
inside me has always
rejected everything about him.
Despite the many times
we've spoken over the years,
those feelings
have never changed.
Even now, I still feel
that way about him.
ICHIMARU: What's the matter?
It seems you fell
into a trance there.
-Sort of.
-By the way, seems he
isn't actually dead yet--
Renji, that is.
-[gasp]
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): It's true.
I have to concentrate
and search,
but I can still sense
Renji's spiritual pressure.
But it's so weak.
-But he will die soon.
It's kind of the pathetic.
He tried to save your life,
but he just got cut to pieces.
-Don't you dare
make light of him!
-Are you afraid?
-Afraid?
Of what?
-You don't want
Renji and the others
to die trying to
rescue you, do you?
Knowing they're
trying to save you
must make this all
the more painful.
Want me to save you?
-Ca-- Captain Ichimaru.
-You don't mean it.
-What are you saying, sir?
-I could rescue you
from this execution
and save your life right
now-- you and Renji,
and the others, too.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
Is he serious?
What could he possibly
have to gain by saving me?
There's even less
reason for him to want
to save Ichigo and Renji.
Why would he say such a thing?
-You think I'm kidding?
I am.
Bye bye, Rukia.
I'll see once more
at the Sokyoku.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
I can't believe
I let him do that to me.
After I had abandoned all
hope, accepted my fate
and my impending death, he
was able to shake my resolve.
By holding out that
small sliver of hope,
he managed to make
me yearn just a bit.
He made me want to live again.
How could he have shattered
my strength so easily?
-[screams]
-Hm?
-Huh?
KENPACHI: Don't let
your guard down.
You make it too easy for me.
-Kaname!
-What are you looking
around for, idiot?
This is ridiculous.
How did the two of you
ever become captains
in the first place?
Come on and stand up.
You don't look to me
like you're dead yet.
At least die like a captain
and release your Bankai first.
-What would you know of a
captain's honor, traitor?
You're not even
worthy of Bankai.
TOSEN: Hold it, Sajin.
Leave this to me.
There are three ways to become
a captain in the 13 Court Guard
Squads.
The first is to pass
the captain's exam,
presided over by three other
captains, including the head
captain himself.
The second is to receive the
recommendation of six or more
captains and be acknowledged
by at least three
of the remaining seven captains.
The only other way is to
defeat the previous captain
in a one-on-one
battle, which must
be witnessed by 200
or squad members.
-[laughs] So what's your point?
-Ever since the moment you
killed the former captain
of Squad 11 and replaced
him Kenpachi Zaraki,
I felt a deep unease
about you, unease
that has become a certainty.
A certainty that you're a demon,
that you thrive on violence
and blood, that you're
different from the rest of us.
And a certainty that
you are bound someday
to destroy the peace.
And sure enough, now you
have saved the Ryoka.
And here you fight
against us, threatening
to bring even more
chaos to the Seiretei.
And it's all because of
your insatiable bloodlust
and your love of fighting
for its own sake.
Am I wrong?
-I don't know about
right or wrong.
But I can see you sure
have a problem when
it comes to getting
to the point.
Enough babbling.
If you hate me so much, then
there's no need for speeches.
Just shut up and
attack me already.
-No hatred.
I never actually said that
I hated you, Kenpachi.
I simply find you unforgivable!
Everything you do
threatens the peace
we have worked so hard
to establish here.
So in the name of
justice, I now have
no choice but to erase you.
-Kaname.
-Bankai.
Suzumushi Tsushiki, Emma Korogi.
So you wanted to see my Bankai?
This is it.
This entire space
is now my Bankai.
So, tell me, Kenpachi
Zaraki, what do you think?
You can see nothing
and hear nothing.
KENPACHI: What is this?
I can't see.
And I can't hear a sound.
-Do you find it a
little frightening,
a world without sight or sound?
The Emma Korogi steals
all spiritual pressure,
all perceptions and
sense of those within it,
and creates in their
place a dark, silent hell.
There is only one man
who can escape this cell,
and that is he who
wields Suzumushi.
It's useless.
You are far too
slow to counter me.
No matter how
skilled one may be,
when deprived of light so
suddenly, it is the end.
With the sudden darkness,
a tiny fear is born.
Total darkness always causes
at least a twinge of fear.
But I, who have known
only darkness since birth
have no [inaudible].
-[grunt]
-[gasp]
-[laughs]
-I was right.
You are some kind
of demon after all,
with no fear of the
dark to begin with.
Then I shall attack
first and not
give you a chance to feel fear.
-It's not over!
[shouts]
[fighting noises]
YORUICHI (VOICEOVER):
Ichigo, we're out of time.
-After all that, I can't believe
that my resolve was so weak.
How depressing.
SHUHEI: Whoa.
That's Captain
Tosen's Emma Korogi.
He must've been in trouble
if he had to use his Bankai.
Whatever it is, I had better get
up there in case he needs help.
YUMICHIKA: Not so fast.
You haven't finished
me off yet, you know.
SHUHEI: Who do you
think you're kidding?
You're beaten.
YUMICHIKA: Sorry to disappoint
you, but in Squad 11,
you're not beaten
until you're dead.
SHUHEI: That's different
from Squad Nine.
YUMICHIKA: As different
as black and white.
And that's why we never
give up on a fight.
-Maybe.
But you ought to
give up on this one,
because there's no way a
lowly Fifth Seat is ever
going to beat a lieutenant.
YUMICHIKA: Shall I tell
you a little secret?
The only reason I'm
still a Fifth Seat
is because I really don't like
the look of the number four.
-What do you mean?
YUMICHIKA: I think the number
three is the most attractive.
But of course, Ikkaku
already has the Third Seat.
So I chose the Fifth
Seat, five being
the closest in resemblance
to the number three.
And there's more to my secret.
You see, in Squad 11 we
have an unspoken agreement.
We live to fight.
And in keeping with
that, we believe
that Zanpakuto should be used
strictly for direct attacks,
and that all those Kido attacks
are for idiots and cowards.
Let me show you what I mean.
I would imagine
that by now, you're
curious about the true
power of my Zanpakuto.
What I'm about to show you
is confidential, of course.
My captain and Ikkaku will be
mad at me if they find out.
-Why, you--
-How can I still be alive?
-Oh, hello there.
-What are you doing
caring for me?
RIKICHI: I brought him here.
RENJI: Rikichi?
I don't understand.
-They threw Hanataro in jail
for trying to help Rukia.
So I thought since you
both have the same goal,
he'd be willing to help you.
-Rikichi waited until
no one was around,
and then he unlocked my cell.
-Thank you for helping me.
HANATARO: Actually
I didn't do much.
I don't know who did it,
but your wounds had already
been very well treated and
bound by someone else when
I got here.
There's only one
could have done it.
But don't worry about that now.
You just get
stronger, Lieutenant.
You can count on
Ichigo to save Rukia.
I just know he can do it.
RIKICHI: Yes,
Lieutenant, get well.
I was shocked that you
actually lost to the Ryoka.
And then to make
matters worse, we
learned you had broken out
of jail and disappeared.
And I couldn't believe
you would raise your sword
against members
of your own squad.
But then I remembered
the only reason
I joined Squad Six
in the first place
was because you were my hero.
And so no matter
what happens, I want
you to live, Lieutenant,
and keep on battling.
I want you to be the Lieutenant
I know, who's always cool
and always fighting for
what he believes in.
-Rikichi.
TOSEN (VOICEOVER):
How can this be?
He has no sense of
sight or sound or smell.
He cannot sense
spiritual pressure.
-So then how is he
able to counter me?
KENPACHI: [laughs]
TOSEN (VOICEOVER):
Once again, he
dodges a fatal blow
at the last second.
-[grunts]
TOSEN (VOICEOVER):
Every time he parries,
his counterattacks get
more accurate, too.
Is he really a demon after all?
KENPACHI (VOICEOVER):
I got a hit this time.
Just a graze, but still.
This Bankai that destroys
senses is a nuisance.
But at least I still
have my sense of touch.
And as long as I
have that, I can
feel the moment his
blade makes contact,
then dodge and counterattack.
So I know he's not going
to be able to kill me.
And I'm starting to
inflict some damage on him.
But this is a
boring way to fight.
It's so much more
fun to cut and slash.
I have to concentrate since
I can't see or hear him.
And I never felt much spiritual
pressure to begin with.
Damn it.
Why do I have to waste
time thinking instead
of just fighting him head on?
-Use your instincts, Kenny!
KENPACHI (VOICEOVER): What
do you think I've been doing?
-Maybe you should be
using that mind-eye thing
to try and visualize
your enemy, you know?
KENPACHI (VOICEOVER):
If I could do that,
I wouldn't be
having this problem.
-Let's me think.
What would I do?
I would give up in
a beautiful way.
KENPACHI (VOICEOVER): You'd die.
Huh?
That's it.
That's what I'll do.
Then I'll know
exactly where he is.
TOSEN (VOICEOVER):
He's smiling again.
Even though, he's losing,
he's still enjoying the fight.
You're dangerous,
Kenpachi Zaraki, far too
dangerous to be allowed to live!
What?
No.
He didn't even dodge.
-Well, hello.
So we meet again.
-Impossible.
-Now I can see you
again, and hear you.
Is that just because I
have a direct hold on you?
Or is it because my
body and your sword
are in direct contact?
Either way, it doesn't matter.
Come over here and attack me.
I know your trick now.
Next time, before you
even penetrate my body,
I'll be able to grab your arm.
TOSEN (VOICEOVER): Damn you.
I must not lose.
I must destroy you.
I can never lose to
the likes of you.
-I wish I could gather all
the clouds so they would never
again obscure the light
that shines from the stars.
-That's beautiful.
-I'm going to be a Soul Reaper,
Kaname, and let justice shine.
TOSEN: But she
died much too soon.
If it's not enough to believe
in justice, then for her,
I swear I will become
justice and seek out
all the evil in this world
so that I may wipe it out,
like the wind casts away
the clouds in the sky.
[shouting]
-Kaname.
TOSEN: [gasping]
This isn't finished.
Not yet.
-Yes it is.
I quit.
I have no interest in
fighting a man with one foot
already in the grave.
I'm out of here.
Dying is futile.
What can a dead man do?
He can't fight anymore,
that's for sure.
-I swear it, if it takes my
very life I will stop you.
I will use every ounce
of justice in my being.
-What an idiot you are.
If you want to die so
badly, I'll help you.
Hm?
-No, Sajin.
-Don't sacrifice
yourself Kaname.
This man will never understand
your quest for justice.
-Sajin, I-- I.
-I know.
-So that's what's
under that basket.
I always wondered.
But I have to admit that it
wasn't what I was expecting.
-You don't seem shocked
by what you see.
-Outward appearances
have nothing
to do with fighting abilities.
The only question is if
you're beastly appearance also
means you fight with a
beast's strength and tenacity.
That's what matters.
KOMAMURA: You see only
what's on the surface.
You have no respect for an
opponent's inner strength.
That is your weakness.
I am not like Kaname.
I will not show
the same kindness.
Bankai!
Kokujo Tengen Myo'o!
Now it begins in earnest,
Kenpachi Zaraki, our fight
to the death-- just
the kind you love!
KENPACHI: [laughs] A
fight to the death, huh?
That means I can come at
you with everything I got.
And then after you're dead,
go reincarnate yourself
so I can kill you all again!
-Now the time has arrived.
Let us begin the execution.
SUI-FENG (VOICEOVER):
It seems odd
that so few people showed up.
Captains and lieutenants from
Squad One and our Squad Two
are here, plus
Kuriko's Squad Eight.
It's no surprise Squads
5, 11, and 12 are missing,
given their casualties.
And I think Zaraki's lost it.
But what about all the
rest of the officers?
I thought that at least Unohana
would have wanted to be here.
[gasp]
-[gasp]
My brother.
-Rukia Kuchiki, it is time.
Any last words before
your execution?
RUKIA: Yes.
Just one.
[theme music]