[theme music]
NARRATOR: Under orders
from Genryusai Yamamoto,
the captains of the
13 Court Guard Squads
came to Hueco Mundo to rescue
Ichigo and his friends who
had been defeated by
the powerful Espadas.
Without hesitation, each
captain flung themselves
into battle against the Espadas.
In defense of Uryu and
Renji, Mayuri Kurotsuchi's
took on the Espada Szayelaporro.
Although his opponent
had taken Nemu hostage,
Mayuri swallowed him using
Konjiki Ashisogi Jizo.
Mayuri thought he had
destroyed the powerful Espada,
but it turned out
Szayelaporro was still alive.
It was soon revealed
that Szayelaporro
had revived himself by invading
the body of his captive, Nemu,
and sucking out her Reishi.
-How delightful.
Really, such an
amusing little power!
It tickles my fancy.
And is that's all you've got?
Well, I suppose this means you
have no other hidden power.
In that case, why
don't we move along?
I'd like to use you as a
test subject for a new drug
I've developed.
There's no need to
put up your defenses.
The drug I'm testing is
(SLOWLY) already inside you.
-What?
His voice.
What the--
NARRATOR: In
appropriating Nemu's body,
Szayelaporro had been
tricked by Mayuri
and drugged without
his knowledge.
The drug was a
superhuman potion which
appeared to make
Szayelaporro perceive time
at an extremely slow pace.
It made instantaneous
movements appear
as though they had
actually stopped.
-Now, then, this sword, does
it appear to have stopped?
With what's coursing
through your veins,
one second will
feel like 100 years.
Take this sword, for instance.
As I move it closer to you,
your superhuman alertness
makes the movement
appear agonizingly slow,
as if it will take several
centuries to reach you.
It's delightful.
But while your senses are
sped up to superhuman levels,
your non-superhuman body
will fall painfully behind.
In fact, your body cannot
possibly keep up with
the incredible amount of data
your sharpened senses are
sending it.
Well, we're in no
hurry, I suppose.
Yes, take your time.
Enjoy the everlasting
agony of my sword
slicing through your heart.
Savor it till your
blood turns to dust.
For now, I bid you adieu.
You'll be seeing me
again in about 100 years.
SZAYELAPORRO (VOICEOVER):
It's been so long.
How many years?
How many decades have come
and gone since he-- no, wait,
it's been longer than that.
It's been centuries.
I know this much, an immense
amount of time has passed.
How long will it take?
When will the sword go
ahead and pierce my heart.
This waiting is unbearable.
Hurry, hurry, hurry,
hurry, hurry, hurry.
[heaves]
Hurry up and kill me!
-The perfect being, you said?
Well, I have to tell you the
honest truth as I see it.
In this world, nothing
perfect exists.
It may be a cliche after all,
but it's the way things are.
That's precisely
why ordinary men
pursue the concept
of perfection.
It's infatuation.
But ultimately, I
have to ask myself,
what is the true meaning
of being perfect?
And the answer I came
up with was nothing.
Not one thing.
The truth of the matter
is, I despise perfection.
If something is truly
perfect, that's it!
The bottom line becomes there
is no room for imagination.
No space for intelligence
or ability or improvement.
Do you understand?
To men of science,
like us, perfection
is a dead end, a
condition of hopelessness.
Always strive to be better than
anything that came before you,
but not perfect.
Science has agonized over the
attempt to achieve perfection.
That's the kind of
creatures we are.
We take joy in trying to
exceed our grasp, in trying
to reach for something that,
in the end, we have to admit
may, in fact, be unreachable.
In other words, you may
think that we operate
on the same level,
but you are wrong.
The moment you started
talking about perfection,
you embraced that
impossible concept
and had already lost to me.
That is, of course, if you are
indeed a scientist at all--
-[gasps]
Huh?
Wait a second.
Don't you have a problem?
Your Zanpakuto is broken.
-Heh, it's not broken like that.
I broke it myself.
-What's the difference?
-As long as the hilt remains,
it can be reconstructed.
And really, the
sword deserved it.
It's a fitting punishment after
it disobeyed my instructions.
Nemu, get up and come here.
Nemu!
NEMU: Tch.
-Good grief.
She's becoming more
trouble than she's worth.
-Huh?
What's he up to?
Is he reviving her?
NEMU: [moaning]
[both gasp]
NEMU: [shrieks]
[moans]
[sighs]
RENJI AND URYU: She
came back from the dead!
-What?
We were watching.
How in the world
did you do that?
-Unbelievable!
You couldn't
understand something
this obvious happening
right in front of you?
What idiots!
-Don't turn this back on us!
Admit it.
You did something
to her just now,
and you couldn't even
show the audience!
-What are you talking
about, you Neanderthal?
I never do anything that isn't
suitable for family viewing.
Get your mind out of the gutter.
[both grunt]
-Humph.
Never mind.
I've learned from experience,
describing my techniques
to ordinary people is just
a complete waste of time.
-So then, you refuse
to explain yourself?
[coughs]
-Are you all right over there?
Try not to get so excited.
-What?
What are you talking
about excited?
I have every right to
get upset about something
as blatant as what we observed.
I was simply standing
up for public decency!
Whose side are you on?
-On yours.
I'm just saying that even
though the poison has
gone from our systems, our
organs are still crushed!
We have to be careful, or
we'll injure ourselves.
-But the way you said
it wasn't very clear.
-Cool it.
You're way too sensitive.
Nobody thinks of you as
a four-eyed pervert--
-You're not helping things here!
-Both of you stop!
Your stupidity is overwhelming.
It's starting to mess
with rational mind.
Really, it's turning to mush.
Nemu, dig this place up again.
-Yes, Master Mayuri.
-(IN UNISON) Tadaah!
We're finally free!
Two out of three
great desert brothers
have been released
from deployment
and are back in business!
[shrieks]
-Wai-wai-wait!
Stop trying to attack us!
We've met you once before.
Don't you remember?
It's Pesche and Dondochakka.
We're friends!
We're on your side.
-(IN UNISON) On your side!
-You're in the way!
I don't know who they are.
Let's be safe and
get rid of them.
-Yes, Master Mayuri.
[drilling motor]
PESCHE: Wait a minute!
All right, you don't
know who we are.
We get that.
I guess we can't blame
you for not recognizing us
since we arrived right in
the middle of everything.
-Mm-hm.
-That being the case, allow
us to refresh your memory!
-Yes, we're very good at that.
-I've seen you before.
You should be dead, right?
-Now, that's just cruel.
It's true, but it's cruel!
-We're still there.
[both shrieking]
PESCHE: Huh?
What?
Goodbye, everybody!
-Where did this
big door come from?
-Good question.
And why is it undamaged
when everything around it
has collapsed?
-[scoffs]
Silly question!
It's perfectly obvious to me.
When a scientist
goes to the trouble
of building his
own laboratory, he
builds one place
much more sturdy
and secure than any other.
[clangs]
And that is not the room
where the costly equipment
for his experiments is located.
Nor is it the archive
where he files
the reports he stayed
up all night writing.
No, the place a scientist wants
to preserve more than anything
is where he keeps his
most irreplaceable items--
the research materials he
crawled over glass to obtain.
[both gasp]
-What's in there?
-Just what I expected.
-Heyahh!
-[grunts]
-Is it over?
-Huh?
-[laughs]
Rrrargh!
-Ugh.
Ugh.
[grunts]
Aagh.
-Rrrh!
[laughs]
-[grunts]
-Don't make me keep
repeating myself.
My Hierro is the hardest amongst
all the Espadas in Hueco Mundo.
There's no way a
Soul Reaper's blade
is able to cut through me!
[both gasp]
-[slurps]
URYU: [grunts]
Stop it!
Let go of me!
I won't put up with it.
What are you going to do to me?
-Oh, please.
I would think that
would be obvious.
I'm going to fix you.
URYU: Let me go!
You're not talking
about healing!
You want to rebuild me!
-[scoffs]
-I knew it!
I'm not going to be a guinea
pig for your experiments!
MAYURI: His squawking
is very annoying.
When it comes down to it,
you're quite a coward.
Come on, now.
Quit fighting and
think about it.
You have internal injuries.
And if they're not
tended to, you might die.
I'm doing you a favor.
I'm willing to fix
your wounds for free.
It's reasonable to be grateful,
no matter what you look
like afterwards.
-Well, guess what?
I'm not grateful.
And I'm not interested in
any new look you're planning.
-Please don't move.
-Aaah!
Too close, too close, too close!
-What do you mean?
URYU: Aargh!
[muffled cries]
-Oh, very good, Nemu.
Stay on top of him
until he suffocates.
Even if his heart stops.
Excellent!
This should make
everything so much easier.
-Capt. Kurotsuchi.
-What is it, Lt.
Abarai?
-Can you please heal me first?
-Why?
-Because I want to fight
as soon as possible.
I know there are still
Espadas out there who
are a serious threat
to my friends.
I have to get back on my feet
so I can help protect them!
MAYURI: You're not needed.
There is only one big
fight still going on.
And that is Kenpachi Zaraki.
He went to help Ichigo Kurosaki.
But if you want my
personal opinion,
I think you just enjoy
stretching out the battle.
-Huh?
-You'd be no help to one
who needs that stimulation.
Stepping into the middle
of a battle with someone
like Kenpachi would
be like throwing
raw meat in front of a beast.
You get in his way, you'll
be an obstacle to chew up.
And I'm sure you'll agree,
getting eaten by a beast
is about as stupid a
way to die as there is.
-[growls]
-Agh!
-Eyah!
-Heyah!
[snickers]
-Hm?
[whooshing]
-[gasps]
-[grunts]
Nyah.
-Die!
-[grunts]
-You dodged.
And if you dodged, that means
you must have felt threatened.
Am I wrong?
You said you couldn't be cut
by a Soul Reaper's sword.
But judging from your actions,
I think you've been lying.
-Ugh, hah!
You don't know what
you're talking about!
Dodging an attack is nothing
more than a fighting instinct.
The natural reaction
developed from years
of hand-to-hand combat.
But it changes nothing!
No matter what you do,
your sword cannot cut me.
That's why you are doomed
to lose this battle!
[pants]
KENPACHI: There are many
different personalities
within the Soul Society.
I've come across
annoying guys like you
before who say they
can't be cut by my sword.
But guess what?
-[gasps]
-In all this time, I
haven't met a single person
whose eyes and throat
can't be speared!
-Ugh!
[both gasp]
-How many times are
you going to make
me say it until you believe me?
-[gasps]
-No matter how much you
try, I cannot be cut!
-Kenpachi!
-Hah, I guess you can't
understand it, can you?
How can someone still be
alive after you've just
run a sword through their head?
Isn't that what's going
through your head?
[laughs]
Well, here's your answer.
-Bastard!
I can't believe this.
-Surely, no one
could survive when
their head's been run
through with a blade.
But just look at
me, I'm still alive.
Have you figured it
out, Soul Reaper?
Your sword didn't
pierce my head.
Oh no, not at all.
It simply passed
through my head.
Now, do you understand?
You can't defeat
me, Soul Reaper.
You don't have the power!
You might as well give up.
-Yeah.
[theme music]
PESCHE: We have to
go save master now.
DONDOCHAKKA: We can't.
I hear there's a
beast threatening her.
PESCHE: What do
you mean a beast?
DONDOCHAKKA: He's a
spiky-haired warrior
with scars and a
threatening gaze.
PESCHE: He's our ally.
DONDOCHAKKA: Tell me,
is he really our ally?
PESCHE: I wouldn't
stake my life on it.