[struggling breaths]
Leave him alone!
Huhh?
I also... want to protect.
I want to fight too!
For everyone's sake!
I can't just watch!
Huh?
What's this?!
[roar]
Haaaa!
Haah!
There you are.
I was wondering where
you'd gone off to.
Don't know if you're
hungry yet, but
dinner's almost ready.
What's the matter?
Nothing important.
But while I'm thinking about
it, it would be nice if you
knocked before you came in.
Oh. Sorry about that.
Hey! Wait a minute,
it's my room, you know!
Are you coming
or what?
D'agh! Listen,
this isn't a hotel!
Do you have
a minute?
Why, of course,
Captain Kuchiki.
What is it you're doing?
Well, I'm still working on
repairing the invading forces
whose cores were destroyed
from the last battle.
It won't be
long now.
How are you doing, personally?
Not so bad, as you
can see for yourself.
Then we may proceed?
Yes.
Inform Captains Zaraki,
Hitsugaya, and Komamura.
It's now time for us
to re-enter the World
of the Living.
According to Captain Unohana,
who escaped from the Soul
Society,
the Reigai are intensely
dangerous, now that their
powers are not restricted.
Even the Head Captain's
wounds will take time
to heal completely.
The situation, she says,
is critical.
At least we know what
the enemy is after.
We must hide Nozomi
Kujo immediately.
And in the meantime,
we have to come up
with counter-measures.
What kind of
counter-measures?
It's so upsetting.
Do you think the
other Captains
are really dead?
Don't be ridiculous!
Huh?
Don't you have any faith?
Captain Zaraki would
never die that easily!
But if they're alive,
then where are they?
Stop whining!
Or I'll kill you!
I'm not hiding!
I'm gonna fight!
[gasps from all]
Nozomi...
Just a minute, young lady!
Don't get carried away!
Just because you got your
Zanpakuto back, doesn't make
you a match for these guys!
[Nozomi]
Kageroza's Zanpakuto has the
power to cut time and space,
and restore it at will.
But I'm not worried about that.
My Zanpakuto can counter his.
...At least I think so.
You don't seem
all that confident
about it.
What can you do
with your power?
I'm not sure just yet,
because I can't
remember everything.
But I still know
it'll be effective!
Hah! And we're
supposed to
trust that?
Maybe you'll be effective,
and maybe not.
You're not completely
sure yourself!
I'm not willing to risk my
life on your faulty memory!
Why are we basing our
whole strategy on
protecting this girl?
We should fight the enemy
head-on and defeat them!
It's as simple as that.
Where are
you going?
I don't see any point
in further discussion!
He's never been much
of a team player.
Regardless, what are we gonna
do, I mean about the girl?
Nozomi, listen.
Since you're the enemy's
target, and you don't know
what your powers are,
we really can't
allow you to fight,
do you understand?
But I can help you
defeat them, I know it!
Its name is on the edge
of my consciousness!
I'm so close to
remembering
what it is!
[Ichigo]
Nozomi, with everything at
stake, you can't expect us
to believe your story.
But if your power's dormant,
Let's awaken it.
Huh?
Got 'em, boss.
Good. It looks to me like
our trap was effective.
Shall we proceed
with our next step?
Go right ahead.
Obviously, we can't expect any
support from the Soul Society.
As a result, we have no choice
but to freeze the space
ourselves.
I'm tellin' you, it's
going to be a huge job.
So that little trick was
Kisuke Urahara's doing.
Well played.
[chuckles]
So he managed to scatter
my Invading Forces into
separate locations.
But this contrivance
isn't going to buy
them much time.
Yaaaaah!
Huaaah!
That won't do it! I need more!
Yaah!
Agh!
Come on, Nozomi!
This training is
going too far!
It's dangerous!
Just keep out of
this, pervert.
It's the only way to
re-awaken my Zanpakuto.
Whatever's
necessary.
Your body can't take
the punishment!
Shut up!
Agh!
Huaah!
This is how Kisuke helped
me awaken my power.
I know it'll work for her too!
[gasp]
Huh?
[amazed]
Oh!
Did she just?
...suck away Chad's
Spirit Energy?
It's working!
Who's next?
Me!
Any progress
to report?
Ikkaku, what's the matter?
Are you worried?
Yeah, right.
[Ikkaku]
All this means nothing.
What I'm concerned about
is when the Reigai will
be showing up.
[panting]
Let's take
a break.
I don't
need one.
Don't rush,
Nozomi!
Believe me, you're going
to fail if you try to do
everything at once!
That's right! You
tell her, Orihime!
Nozomi, have some of
Orihime's special sports drink
and try to relax a little.
It might help you
recall things.
I don't want any!
Baah!
Where are
you going?
To go wash my face.
No sense in rushing
things, right?
You really think this
exercise is going to
help you remember?
Uh?
You might as well stop.
You're just gonna
hurt yourself if
you keep this up.
You're wrong.
I'm right on
the verge--
On the verge of what?
I'll concede
you've got some
sort of power.
But that's no guarantee
you'll be able to
survive in a real fight.
[light gasp]
Even if you regain the
power to fight, it'll only
lead you to your death.
When I first
came here...
I intended to die.
Hm?
Instead, I was
told to live.
Since then, I've tried to
take those words to heart.
So this time, it's my turn
to help everyone else live.
To accomplish that,
I'm ready to die
fighting.
[gasp]
[Ikkaku] [flashback]
I have a dream as well;
To fight and die as
Zaraki's subordinate.
End of discussion.
You're a fool.
I don't give a damn
about your problems.
But you won't be
protecting anyone
if you're dead.
If you want to live,
you'll have to learn
how to strike back.
You ready?
Bring it!
[rumble]
What is this
Spiritual Pressure?
[gasp]
Renji!
The enemy's attacking.
A few of Kageroza's Reigai
got caught in the trap Kisuke
set in the Precipice World.
You're serious?!
But we're not ready!
Nozomi still hasn't
regained her Shikai.
Then we have to get
her someplace safe,
and quickly!
Let's continue, Ichigo.
Hold on! Don't you
understand what's
happening here?!
If the Reigai are
coming here, there's no
safe place to hide me.
I need to power up as
quickly as possible.
Yeah. I think
Nozomi's right.
You sure about that?
Mmm...
Well fine, then.
If that's how you
feel I guess I'd
better lend a hand.
Thanks, buddy.
No time to waste talking.
We'd better get started.
Right!
Well well. Looks like
I'm the first one here.
Hm?
Haaaiii!
So does this mean
you're my opponent?
That's right, pal.
I have no intention of going
along with the others.
When an enemy shows up,
I fight to win!
[gasp]
Now what's happening?
That's Ikkaku's
Spiritual Pressure!
What's he up to?
Is he fighting one
of those Reigai?
We've gotta help him!
[Yumichika]
Don't do it, Ichigo.
If you interfere,
you're only going to
undermine his efforts.
Don't you get it?
He's out there, trying
to buy us some time...
to help that girl.
Heh.
Ikkaku!
We'll all take
him out together.
Keep out of this!
It's my fight,
and mine alone!
Are you gonna pull
that crap again?
Besides, you guys are
gonna be busy fighting
your own opponents.
What do you mean?
[gasp]
He's sent more Reigai!
Damn it all!
I'll handle this one.
You guys take care of
the rest.
Guess we have no choice.
Don't die, Ikkaku!
Heh!
Sorry for the wait.
Now that there's
no one in our way,
let's have it out once
and for all, you and me!
Fine, but it's futile.
You can't beat me!
Hey! You took that very well!
Shut up!
Extend, Hozukimaru!
Haiiyayaa!
Is that all you've got?
Auugh!
[gasp]
Raagh!
Ah!
Nozomi! No!
Are you all right?!
You look like you're hurt!
You need a break!
Just shut up!
Ichigo, keep going!
As you wish!
Heeeaah!
Aah!
One more time!
Fine!
Hey!
Huh?
Tell me something.
How long are you gonna
keep up this farce?
Come on, this is a waste
of effort on your part.
You need to hit her with
some serious Spirit Energy.
What are you
talking about?
Hmpf! As usual,
you're nothing
but talk.
We're done here.
Time to grab that girl.
Hm?
Is this some
kind of joke?
Heh heh.
It's not
over yet.
Hmpf!
Augh!
This is
becoming
boring.
You might as well
accept it, kid.
I'm telling you,
you're no match
for me.
Don't be so sure about that.
You can decide better,
after you see this.
Huh?
What do you mean exactly?
Just what I said.
You both say you're going
all out but the truth is
you're holding back
without realizing it.
At this point, you're
spinning your wheels.
The girl's Zanpakuto
will never wake up.
You'll have to throw
a Spirit Energy attack
powerful enough to kill her.
(Small CT nervous breath)
Stop the attack,
and you live.
Fail, and you die.
It's as simple as that.
All right, then.
Let's do this!
[gasps]
Hey! Now hold on!
This is way over the top!
Have you lost your mind?!
Whatever it takes!
But why Nozomi?
Ichigo! Come on,
say something to her!
You're sure you want to do this?
Whaaaa?
Yeah. I am sure.
This'll be... your last chance.
Bankai!!
Eh?
Ryumon Hozukimaru!
This one's just for you,
my friend!
Oh? If you're so sure
you've got the goods,
then let's go ahead
and mix it up!
Hyaah!
Ha ha ha ha! All right,
now we're having fun!
I don't think you'll be
laughing in a few minutes!
Oh really?
This particular Zanpakuto
only awakens during a battle!
Huh?
Here we go!
Huaah!
Raagh!
Bankai!
[Ichigo]
Damn it!
Yaaaah!
Haaaaaa!
Heh.
Raaagh!
Getsuga...tensho!
I don't give a damn
about your problems.
But you won't be
protecting anyone
if you're dead.
If you want to live,
then you have to learn
how to strike back.
Gotta strike back...
[gasp]
That's it! I remember now!
My Zanpakuto's name!
Arazomeshigure!
[gasp]
Nozomi!
[panting]
Are you finished?
Damn it!
Hmpf! I did enjoy that a bit.
But now, it's over!
[Nozomi]
Stop!
[gasp]
Huh?
Well, well! Did you come all
this way, just to be captured?
In your dreams, Reigai!
Rain down,
Arazomeshigure!
Interesting!
Haa!
Engh!
Heh! Now that was
pretty awesome!
[collapses]
[Kon]
That was amazing, Nozomi!
You defeated Kenpachi's Reigai!
[Nozomi]
I owe it to everyone
who helped--
[Kon]
Now that I think about it,
maybe I'm the one who's amazing!
[Nozomi]
S'cuse me?
[Kon]
I'm the one who discovered
you, which means you owe
me your life,
[Kon]
which means I'm that
much superior to you,
which means--
[punch]
[Nozomi]
Loud mouth!