[music playing]
[theme music]
[birds chirping]
-Where are Ichigo and Renji?
Did they stay out
training all night long?
-Who knows.
It's probably best to
just let them both get it
out of their system.
That fool shouldn't let a single
defeat get him so depressed.
-Yeah, that's true.
-But that's stupid!
How is fighting going
to make him feel better?
Are men really
that simple-minded?
-Speaking of men, I wonder
what's up with Uryu?
Something happened with Yoshino.
It was obvious.
At the mansion, Uryu was
really worried about her.
-Ah, why?
Bounts are our enemies,
and always were.
Why waste time
worrying about a Bount?
-Hmm.
There are a lot of things we
need to ask this one though,
one she's recovered a bit more.
-I'm exhausted.
-I can't believe we trained
until the sun came up.
-Good day, men.
I have your breakfast
prepared for you.
I feel generous today, so I even
prepared some for the moocher.
-I really hate it
when you call me that.
Where's Kisuke?
-He's is in back,
making some repairs
to the [inaudible]
and the others.
-Want some coffee?
-Sure.
-Coffee?
-Thanks.
-Here you go.
-Ah, what the hell?
What's wrong with you?
-That's disgusting!
What is this stuff?
-I told you before, it's coffee.
-Well it's horrible.
-You're serious, aren't you?
You've never had it before.
What a child.
-What did you say?
-Want some sugar?
-Sugar?
You mean you're supposed
to put sugar in it first?
Well, it couldn't hurt.
One more.
Maybe two more.
-Oh, come on.
Why not just eat
the sugar cubes.
-What's all the commotion
in here this morning?
-Hi, everyone.
-Oh, hi.
-What is it?
-Well, it looks like you're
finally over your depression.
-Yeah, but it took him forever.
I thought he was never
going to cheer up.
-Hey, it was not
that big a deal.
-Oh?
-Don't give me that look.
-Ugh.
Let's forget about that.
-Right.
-Wow, looks good!
-I really hope you like it.
I started with a
French toast as a base,
then I spread a melted
bean jam, instead
of just going with
the usual syrup.
-Another experiment.
-Bon appetit!
-Hey, Rukia.
Have you tried this horrible
stuff they call coffee?
-Yes, I'm familiar with that.
I got used to coffee
a long time ago.
-Oh, but how?
-Hm.
You're surprised?
-It's nice to see them enjoy
a little rest between battles.
Just a normal bunch of
friends, sharing talk
over a good breakfast.
So Noba, why are you
looking so miserable?
-That's the Bount.
-Ah, you noticed that Yoshino
has left the building.
Yes, I noticed too.
She seems to have left awhile
ago without telling any one.
But then we're all adults here,
who can take responsibility
for our own actions,
wouldn't you agree?
It's hardly our place to
monitor the comings and goings
of everyone in the
group, now is it?
Besides, it doesn't
seem right to disturb
this happy morning circle
with such bad news.
Let's wait until later, when
things have calmed down a bit.
-Master Kariya, I
had all the others
proceed to that location
ahead of us, as you ordered.
-All right.
-By restarting the
hands of the clock,
you restart the
motion of time itself.
Right?
-For Bounts, time stopped
from the beginning.
We can fix the gears,
but the hands of time
will never move for us.
-Human lives are all
governed by time.
That's why they reject us
Bounts, because we simply
exist.
And that's all.
-It's true.
For Bounts, time does not flow.
And it's for that reason
that the humans despise us.
Still, we will try to force
those intractable hands of time
into motion.
We will take things into our own
hands and then change our fate.
[bell tolling]
-Where are you going?
So your wounds are
all healed all ready?
I thought you were
seriously injured.
But I guess it's none of
my concern what people do.
[screaming]
Put me down!
What do you think you're doing?
You can't just grab a girl
and haul her off like that.
Where are you taking me, anyway?
-Can you track Yoshino's
spiritual pressure?
-Yoshino?
You mean that Bount you
were so determined to save?
Come to think of it, I didn't
sense her presence in the house
this morning.
-Just tell me where she is now.
-Oh, all right.
-Sad to say, it seems one
of them has disappeared.
-What do you mean?
-Well, Noba here detected it.
-Oops!
Another one, now.
So I guess that two
have disappeared.
-But two of what?
-Hm.
How shall I put this?
-Their presence disappeared.
-Presence?
-Yes, their presence
has disappeared.
It's disappeared.
-Hm, are we playing
a game in here?
-Come to think of it, I
haven't seen [inaudible] today.
Maybe I should go and wake her?
-Let me explain it
to you one more time.
-What's the game?
Can I get in on it too?
[wind]
-You're back.
-Are you serious?
-What are you talking about?
-Are you really going ahead
with this plan of yours?
-Why do you ask?
-I won't let you.
-Oh?
-Which way?
-Stop swinging me
all around like that.
You're only making me dizzy!
-This way?
Or is she that way?
Come on, hurry up and tell me!
-Stop it!
Stop it!
You're making me so confused
I can't tell anything.
-I thought you
said that it still
wasn't the right time yet.
-Well, the situation
has changed somewhat.
-What could have changed
between now and then?
-You want to know?
-Hm.
-I need your help.
In fact, the whole
thing depends on you.
-Stop it!
Help you?
I'm going to stop you.
Zeige Dich!
Goethe!
-What is your command, Yoshino?
-Goethe, are you my alter ego?
-Why do you ask?
-Tell me, do you have any
problem with dying here?
-So we're going to die together?
All right.
-Back here again.
What's going on in there?
-Bounts are fighting each other.
-My, how dangerous.
-Running away?
-Goethe, stop!
Don't chase him!
-Yoshino!
-Stay out of this!
If you get involved,
you'll only be in her way,
and you'll make things worse.
-So that's pretty
much the whole story.
Yoshino left sometime
during the night,
and then Uryu and Ririn
went after her this morning,
but who knows--
-Idiot!
Why'd you wait so long?
-I've been trying to
tell you for a while now,
but no one seemed to listen!
-Just stop it!
This is not the
time to be arguing.
-Deal.
-We've got to drop
everything and go after them.
Noba, we'll have to count
on you to lead us to them.
Can you?
-Yes, I think so.
-All right.
Let's get moving.
-One moment.
-Hm?
-What is it, Kisuke?
We have to do this, so--
-Yes.
But since this is a
race against time,
you and Renji should
use Flash step,
and go on ahead as
fast as you can.
The rest of us will
catch up with you.
-Right.
-One more thing.
Since getting Uryu back in one
piece is our only goal here,
we should avoid fighting
if at all possible.
[music playing]
-Yoshino!
-I'm all right.
Goethe!
You just fight,
don't worry about me!
-Why are you in
such a rush to die?
-Jin!
-Yoshino!
-It's surprising that you can
use a doll, in your condition.
The thing is, we utilize
these crests of ours
to harness the greatest
power in this world.
But if our balance is lost, then
that power goes out of control.
It can even turn on its
user and attack him.
Weakened by injury
as you are, you're
lucky to even summon a
doll, much less control
one with any degree
of accuracy or power.
-As long as I stop you, I
don't care what happens to me.
That's not right.
You don't seem to realize
how incredibly valuable
you really are, Yoshino.
Haven't you noticed
it with Goethe?
Those aren't feelings of
subservience he has for you.
He has feelings of love.
Bounts cannot leave descendants,
so it is truly special to be
a Bount like you.
A Bount who has
a maternal power.
-What?
What are you talking about?
-Come on out, Quincy.
I know you're there
behind me somewhere.
I knew that both of
you would come back.
-No!
Why have you come?
-My guess is he has some
old-fashioned idea about being
a hero, and saving
a woman in distress.
Is that it?
-What do you plan to do with me?
Just because I'm a Quincy I--
-There's nothing more
useless than a Quincy
whose powers have disappeared.
I have no further use for you.
But seeing as
you're here, let me
show you something interesting.
-Let go!
-Yoshino!
Yoshino.
I can't move.
-Goethe!
-Over there!
-Uryu!
-That's far enough.
-It's you again.
-Sorry, but we
can let you go in.
An important ritual
is just starting.
-Ritual?
You're not calling the
shots around here anymore.
Roar!
[inaudible]
-Come, doll, and attack.
-Too easy.
But I guess I'll play with
you for a little while.
-What the hell is this ritual?
-That's nothing you
need to know about.
-Just what do you
plan to do to her?
-Yoshino has as a
rare maternal power.
-Maternal?
-Over long years of
personal experience,
I've come to learn that
the level of power I desire
can't be achieved by sucking
out living human souls.
And then, when I
began to research ways
to absorb souls
for maximum effect,
I discovered this
woman's incredible power.
So don't be afraid.
You're about to become
a new mother, my dear.
Soon you're going to give
birth by breathing life
into hundreds of new dolls.
-Stop it!
[screaming]
-Yoshino!
-Goethe!
-Your desire to keep fighting
is admirable, but it's hopeless.
-Uryu!
-What the hell?
-Better not look away!
-The crest is etched
into his body.
-Jin has fused his own
body with that of his doll.
-That is correct, my dear.
-Of course.
You've always been so strong.
And you'll continue
to be strong.
All this time I've
been so foolish.
You were just using me.
But now, Goethe!
-Yoshino.
-Forgive me.
-What are you going to do?
-Do it!
-As you wish.
-Come to me, Goethe.
-Yoshino.
-We're together,
to the very end.
-Mother.
-Yoshino.
-So you fused with your
doll, just as I thought.
-Goethe, let's go.
-She wasn't absorbed
by the doll,
even though
[inaudible] was gone.
So this is Yoshino's
maternal spiritual power.
-They're just floating up there.
-Don't interfere!
-Damn!
What are they doing up there?
-Don't ignore me,
or you'll be sorry!
-This is the power I
have wanted for so long.
But I can't afford
to let you waste it.
-Jin!
-No!
Stop!
Yoshino, no!
Oh Yoshino, don't die!
You can't die now.
-At least, maybe I
can die the right way.
-There's no right way to die.
Not now.
No!
-This will be fine.
This way of dying is just fine.
-Don't go!
-Your eyes are so intense.
I thank you.
For everything.
The proud last Quincy.
[crying]
[scream]
-I've waited a
long time for this.
[speaking foreign language]
-Yoshino, from out of death,
you shall now be reborn.
-Hey!
Come back!
-You all right?
What in the world is that?
-Wonderful.
Just as we had hoped.
The birth of thousands
of new dolls.
Oh yes, more still!
More still must
be born this day.
[laughter]
-What are those
disgusting things?
-Look!
[theme music]
-What were those
bat-like things?
More of [inaudible] friends?
-How insulting!
Everyone knows I'm the
bluebird of happiness!
-Is that really how
you see yourself?
You're more like a cursed
doll of bad luck and disaster.
-How dare you say
such a think about me?
I'll put a curse on you!
[theme music]
-[inaudible] the Soul Reapers!
-Golden!
-Captain Kyouraku!
-Stop right there!
Old man Yama summoned
me here suddenly,
so it must be important.
Obviously something very
unusual is going on.
Old man Yama!
-Oh, for heaven's sake.
-Is he?
-Let's leave him alone, Nanao.
-Huh?
-I don't know why he called me.
But old man Yama
is sound asleep.
-Well he is old.