[theme music]
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN): A
Menos Grande appeared,
and somehow he defeated it.
It won't take long for
the news to get back
to the Soul Society, Ichigo.
[screaming]
[crying]
[yawn]
-What's the big idea of
waking up so early, fuzz ball?
You have a nightmare?
-Oh, I'll say it's a nightmare.
Just look what your
sister did to me.
This is an outrage.
I'm calling the stuffed
animal protection--
-Quit complaining.
They usually wash you
because you were filthy,
besides you shouldn't be
running around naked anyway.
-Listen, the bath and
the froufrou outfit
were bad enough, but
then she took super glue
and stuck this flower to my ear.
-So?
-Oh, right.
Like you don't see the problem
with a boy wearing a flower?
Yeah, you're right, Kon.
That sucker's really on
there to say, isn't it?
Well, let's see.
I could surgically
remove your ear.
-Wha?
-Whoa, how'd it
get to be so late?
I've got to get moving.
Breakfast, here I come.
-What did I ever do
to deserve this kind
of humiliating treatment?
Aren't I on of the team, too?
Am I'm not an equal?
Don't I deserve some respect?
Fine, then.
They don't want me around?
I'll fix them.
I'll take off.
I'll go on a journey
of my own to someplace
where I'm appreciated.
Someplace where I truly belong.
-Hey, Rukia, time
to leave for school.
Hey, now.
I'm serious.
-I heard you.
I'm not deaf, you know.
-Hey, is something wrong?
-I'm fine.
I think I'm just a little tired
after yesterday's incident,
you know?
-You're not upset
about anything?
-No.
I'll see you at school.
-That's weird.
-Running away to start a new
life seemed like a good idea,
but I wished I'd remembered
to bring along a little lunch,
plus I don't have any money.
Hell, I don't have any pockets.
Huh?
Jackpot!
-Huh?
-Come on, pick me up.
You know you want to.
All girls love cute
little stuffed animals.
And these are
Orihime's classmates.
Perfect.
-Oh, look at that.
Someone left a cute little--
-Filthy stuffed animal.
-Huh?
Uh-oh.
I said that out loud, didn't
I. I just blew my cover.
-It just talked, didn't it?
-Yes.
It sure did.
-OK, Kon, let's think calmly
how to get out of this.
Get up and run like hell!
-No stuffed animal outruns
track star Rio Kunieda.
I run the 100 meters
in 12 seconds flat.
-Oh, why me?
All I wanted was
a little kindness.
Instead, I keep running into
people who want to stomp on me.
[humming]
-Huh?
Hi, Rukia.
How are you?
-Oh, hey there, Orihime.
I'm fine.
-Can I walk with you?
-Of course, you can.
I didn't know you were
an early riser like me.
Do you always come
to school this early?
-No, I'm usually late.
But somehow this year, I'm so
excited that I can't sleep,
and every morning I pop
out of bed all sparkly.
Yay.
-Nice.
-Summer's just the
best season, isn't it?
What are you going to do
for your vacation, Rukia?
-Uh, oh, I have no idea.
-There's a fireworks festival
in August and Tatsuki
and a bunch of us are going.
You should come
along with us, Rukia.
We go every summer, and
it's always really fun.
What do you say?
-The fireworks festival?
-Um-hmm.
In fact, we should ask
Ichigo to go with us, too.
It'll be just like
the time we all
went to see Don
Kanonji together.
Now that was fun.
-Oh, yeah, that certainly
was interesting, wasn't it?
-Um-hmm.
Of course, Ichigo
came along that time,
because his family was going.
He can be so
thoughtful sometimes.
-Huh?
-And his family's so fun.
Sometimes I wonder how
he's related to them,
because he's so
serious all the time.
If I didn't know better,
I'd say it's almost
like Ichigo has a permanent
frown on his face.
-Yes, I know what you mean.
Funny, though, I
always thought you
didn't like Ichigo
very much, Orihime.
-Well, let's just say when
you take a good look at him,
he has a really
interesting face.
I hope you come to the festival.
You'll have fun.
I promise.
-All right, I'll think about it.
-I'm ready to go, Tatsuki!
Give me your best fastball.
-Oh, I found you,
my goddess Orihime.
Things didn't work out so
well the last time we met,
but this time will be different.
All I have to do is just
lie there helpless right
in her path, and
when she sees me,
have no choice
but to pick me up.
Then my life will be complete
as she cuddles me and holds me
tenderly, in the valley
of stuffed pillows.
Yes, I have finally
devised the perfect plan
to achieve my goal.
Now to put it into action.
Oh, beautiful Orihime, your
awesome cuddles await me.
Wait!
This is not part of the plan.
-Pitch coming.
Dragon bazooka kick!
-Here we go!
-Orihime, how could you?
-Yeah, nice hit, Orihime, but
it was a pretty easy target in
and really the defense
didn't have a chance.
One measly run hardly
seems like a reason
to break out the champagne.
-Huh?
Oh.
-Are they playing or what?
-Yo, Ichigo.
Checking out the girls, huh?
Oh, I gotcha,
staring at Orihime.
Ooh-wee, she is quite
the boobalicious babe.
-Hey, I thought I told you
to never do that again.
-Oh, right, like
you don't know it's
totally normal for teenage boys
to be obsessed with hot cuties.
-OK, I admit there's
nothing wrong with that.
-What did you say?
Oh, I get it.
Orihime's just not your type.
-Quit all that messing
around and get over here
and help me out.
-Oh, right.
Sorry.
There.
That does it.
-Thanks a lot, Ichigo.
-Hey, that reminds me, have
you guys seen Uryu anywhere?
He's not in school today.
-Yeah, yesterday I
saw him in the park.
He was talking to himself
and running around
and acting like a weirdo.
It's like he was having some
battle with imaginary monsters
or something.
-Was Asano yesterday.
That could be trouble.
-Hey, now you mention it,
maybe that's his deal.
Maybe Uryu's in
some drama class,
and he was there
rehearsing for a play.
Come to think of it, there were
three other weird people there,
too.
Those must have
been his co-stars.
I think there was
even some kind of--
-Thankfully, Keigo's
a total idiot.
It looks like I
dodged another bullet.
-Uryu, what in the
world happened to you?
-I, uh, fell down the stairs.
-Hmm, whatever you say.
Well, take your seat
and turn to page 110.
-Don't let it bother you.
-Hmm?
-His injuries aren't your fault.
He brought it on himself.
Besides it would
have happened anyway.
-You've got to be kidding.
I'm not the least bit
worried about Uryu.
-Interesting.
I never suggested you
were worried about him.
If you recall, all I said
was don't let it bother you.
-Why you.
-Do you think he was in a fight?
-Uryu?
No way.
I can't believe
he came in so late
in the middle of third period.
-All right, class, quiet down.
-Ichigo, ready to go
have lunch, big guy?
-I guess I'm ready,
but how about if I
invite someone new to join us?
-Oh, you want to invite
the new girl, I bet, huh?
Go mister.
-Hey, Urju, what's up?
You want to come have
some lunch with me?
-Ah, what is Ichigo doing
inviting the freakazoid
to eat lunch with us?
He must have blown a fuse
to do something so stupid.
I can't be seen with that geek.
Anyone but Mr. Bandages.
Ichigo, have you gone crazy?
-I think you're the crazy one.
-No thanks.
-Oh, how rude.
-Oh, come on.
It's no big deal.
Besides, Asano's buying.
-I'm buying?
-Well, if you insist.
-Oh, it's like that, huh?
-I've been under suspicion
from the very beginning,
and it won't be much longer
before they come for me.
-There she is.
Hey, Rukia.
Come on down.
Why don't you join us for lunch?
-Yeah!
Oh, wow.
-Jinta, stop.
You're supposed to
be helping me sweep.
-Nah, put a sock in it, OK?
Boys don't do that stuff.
Jinta swings, it's a home run.
Yay!
-Excuse me, Mr. Urahara,
Mr. Tessai, there's a cat.
-Is that right?
Well, let's see who it is.
Yes, it's Yoruichi!
You've come back.
Come here you little devil.
Let me take a look at you.
-Not just any cat.
It's Yoruichi.
That feline happens to
be the boss' best friend.
Whoa, it kind of leaves you
feeling sorry for the guy,
having a cat for a best
friend is pretty pathetic.
KISUKE (OFFSCREEN): You're
my fuzzy little troublemaker,
yes you are.
Now, who's your Daddy, hmm?
-Oh, this is the most
miserable lunch ever.
What am I'm doing with
these lameoids anyway?
It's like eating in a
graveyard or something.
-What's wrong?
-Oh, it's just you, Chad.
-You seem a little
on edge, Keigo.
-I am not.
Shut up.
-Hmm?
Hey there, Keigo, if
you're all done eating,
why don't you tell us a story?
-Aah!
No way, I'm not in the mood.
-Then get in the mood.
Pronto.
-No fair.
If you wanted happy
times, then you
shouldn't have invited that wet
blanket, Uryu, to eat with us.
But I'll do my best.
So there I was,
dudes, out on the town
on a Saturday night
trolling for Sushi.
The first place I went--
-Hey, Ichigo, why did
you invite me to lunch?
It's because you're feeling
responsible for my injuries.
You're wrong, and you're
wasting your time.
I don't need anyone's
pity, and I certainly
don't want your friendship.
-Eat your lunch and shut up.
I just felt like it.
That's all.
It certainly had nothing
to do with sympathy
or because I like you.
Consider yourself lucky
to not be eating alone.
-Oh, I'm supposed
to be grateful here?
You have a lot of
nerve, especially
since I prefer eating alone.
-I prefer eating alone,
too, so why don't you
just look the other way?
-Why don't you look away?
This whole thing was your
idea in the first place.
-Man, these two are a lot alike.
-I had a date with Destiny,
and Destiny had just
ordered the lobster.
Get it?
-Ta-da.
It's a choco-sugar
jelly death tart.
It's eggplant cream sponge cake
with green bean jelly filling
and chocolate frosting.
-Ooh, how can you eat
stuff like that Orihime?
-The question is how
can she eat like that
and not be as big as a blimp?
-I guess her boobs
absorb the calories.
-Hey, can I ask you something?
Do you have a crush on Ichigo?
-Huh?
-I'll take that as a
maybe, but what exactly
is your relationship
with that guy?
-Well, he is my friend.
-Mahana, that's not
the kind of question
you ask straight out like that.
-I don't see why not.
It's the question you
wanted to ask her yourself,
but none of you were
willing to do it.
So I just did it for you.
-Hey, just who said I wanted to
know anything like that anyway?
-Well, I still want
to know the answer.
-What do you have against
Ichigo anyway, Michiru?
-It's not that I have
anything against him.
I just think there's something
kind of scary looking
about his face, that's all.
-Scary looking?
Well, I don't think so.
I like his face.
MICHIRU (OFFSCREEN): Really?
You must have changed
your mind then,
because I know you used
to be afraid of him, too.
-Well, what's the story, Rukia?
-Ichigo and I are, uh--
Ichigo and I are just friends.
That's that's all
there is to it.
-For real?
-Yes.
-You mean you don't feel
anything special for him?
Not at all?
-No, there's nothing
else going on.
-That's too bad for us girls.
If Rukia liked Ichigo like
me, that would make two of us,
and we'd have so
much to talk about.
And if Tatsuki decided
she liked Ichigo, then
pretty soon we would
all start liking him.
And we could sit around and
talk about all the reasons
we like him, and it would be a
sure win for the girls' team.
-Someone stop her
before her nonsense
starts to make sense to me.
-Say, it's actually
not a bad idea
to have an affection
competition.
But I have to make sure I get
first dibs on the beautiful
smile of Orihime's.
So let's go with a one-on-one.
Just you and me.
Give it to me Orihime.
Not exactly what I had in mind.
-Just give it a rest, Chizuru.
-Anyway, Rukia, tomorrow
I'll be sure to bring you
some of my other
yummy desserts, so you
can try them out yourself.
Then we can enjoy them together.
-OK, I'll think about it.
-Aw, that's the same thing
you said to me last time.
You keep saying that, Rukia.
I'll think about it.
-Oh, really?
I guess I do.
This is nice.
I know I don't belong here.
-What did I ever do to
earn such shabby treatment?
But none of this
would have happened
if it hadn't been for Ichigo.
You just wait, Ichigo,
because now I'll
use the deadly weapons that
weird hat and claws guy
has collected in his store
to get my revenge on you.
Heh, heh, heh.
Huh?
Ah, what's with you?
Trying to sneak up on me, huh?
I'll make mincemeat outta ya.
Don't think you got a chance
just because we're both cats.
I'm a lion.
Ha, scared you off already, huh?
What a pussy.
That was too easy.
Now to steal me some weapons.
-Check it out.
Who knew Mod-Souls could be
put into stuffed animals?
-Huh?
-Hi, little fella.
-Little fella?
-Yoruichi here told
us all about you.
KON (OFFSCREEN): You mean
that stupid cat can talk?
JINTA (OFFSCREEN):
You know, coming in
through people's windows
is a serious crime.
Ururu, grab him!
KON (OFFSCREEN):
Wait, go of my leg.
Wait, stop that!
-One, two, three.
-Yow!
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN): Ichigo.
-Hmm?
What's up?
The Hollow?
-No, it's not that.
-Then?
-Ichigo, are you feeling OK?
-Hmm?
Yeah, now I feel great,
but why are you asking?
-No reason.
I'm just glad you're OK.
-Is there going to be
another one like yesterday?
If Menos Grande showed up
everyday, we'd be in trouble.
-Rukia, you know you're
acting a bit strange today.
Did something happen?
-Uh, uh, it's just.
-Aah!
Aah!
-Huh?
Huh?
-Ichigo, forgive me.
I shouldn't have run away.
I realize now that
my place is with you.
I'll promise I'll
never, ever do it again.
Oh, Ichigo, what was I thinking.
-Kon, I'm over here.
And why did you run away
you worthless piece of fuzz.
-I won't make the same
mistake again, Ichigo.
The world was not kind to
this brave little wanderer.
Take me, take me
back to your room.
That's where I belong, and
that's where I'll stay.
-You want to go back, huh?
-Hey, what's wrong?
-Nothing, I'm fine.
It's obvious he's become
quite attached to you.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): He's
become quite a pain in the butt
if you ask me.
What happened to
you anyway, Kon?
Your stuffing's coming out.
-I'm surprised he's still alive.
-Yeah, me, to, but I know
just the guy to fix him.
-What brings you here?
I need a favor and needle craft
is your specialty, isn't it?
-Can't help you.
-Why not?
-I don't have to
give you a reason.
-Good one.
Oh, I get the picture.
You won't do it,
because you can't do it.
With those hands all
bandaged up Mr. Handicrafts,
you're completely useless.
-How insulting.
These wounds are nothing.
Give me that.
Now step back and watch
the work of a master.
-Oh, what's happening to me?
I don't know if I like this.
-This is a piece of cake.
It's finished.
-Nice job.
-You think?
-Is that thing really Kon?
-Well, it used to be.
-What the hell do
we call him now?
-A nightmare.
-What have you done to me?
-I've replaced your stuffing
with a fire proof polycarbonate
blend and refurbished
your outer coat
with the broad
weave crushed velvet
brocade in the style
of Marie Antoinette.
-I'll never be able
to show my face again.
Huh?
I'm running away
again after all.
What you doing, Yoruichi?
Ah, checking the sky for rain?
-You can quit with
the act now, Urahara.
We both know what's
really coming.
The two of them
are already here.
-Do you want to talk
about this before or after
you have your milk?
-Hey, Rukia, I've
got your dinner here.
Huh?
Damnit.
Why does she always have to
disappear right at dinnertime?
-Thank you for everything.
-Rear conformity 113.
Neuro union
coefficient at 80.5%.
Is this for real?
I didn't think we'd actually
finally her in a Gigai.
But it looks like the data
from the visuals department
was reliable.
Rukia Kuchiki.
Yes, we finally found you.
Heh.
[theme music]
Hi, I'm Uryu Ishida, home handy
crafts club president
and this episode did not
showcase my talents very well.
If the producers had just given
me more time like I asked for,
I could have come up with a much
cooler. . .aarrgh
Yaaahhhhhhh