I will use my greatest
strength to finish you,
in order to minimize
your suffering.
[grunting]
You have to stop now,
Ichigo!
If that's what you
want, that is what
you will get.
[roaring]
That's enough.
[gasping]
Come back here!
Uh!
[grunting]
Impossible!
With his bare hand?!
[gasping]
Damn it all. I never
thought it was possible...
... to be defeated by
a Hollowfied human.
It's completely
ludicrous.
[gasping]
Do it.
[laughing]
As you can see, you are
outnumbered. Any further
resistance is meaningless.
El Directo!
[laughing]
What's the matter? Didn't
I make myself clear?
There are no limits
to my powers!
My branches can grow
forever, and give birth
to countless soldiers!
Damn! He produced a
whole army in moments!
And he's using them as
a shield!
There's only one way. But
how do we create that
opportunity?
Hey, Rukia...!
Am I mistaken, or weren't
you the one who said
'Leave him to me'?
[grunting]
We're not gonna get anywhere
if we continue to fight this
way.
Chad!
Renji!
I'm gonna use Hakuren
to stop the soldiers
from moving on us.
Chad, at that point, you
take the frozen soldiers
and destroy as many as
you can.
Renji, you deliver the
finishing blow with
Zabimaru! Everyone
ready?!
Time to kick
some ass.
Tsuginomai... Hakuren!
Brazo Derecho del
Gigante...
[grunting]
Hikotsu
Taiho!!
Damn it!
[laughing]
I must say, I was
impressed by that
team effort.
Very smart. First you
freeze my soldiers to
create an opening...
... then you attack me
without a moment of
hesitation.
It was an inspired
attempt, but you made a
critical mistake in your
planning. Regardless of
what technique you use,
there's no way it will ever
be effective against me!
For my loyal and
infinite army of soldiers
will protect me from harm!
This fight is coming
to an end. As a show of
respect for all of your
hard work,
I will use my greatest
strength to finish you in
order to minimize your
suffering!
Hm?
Huh?!
What's this?!
Juhaku!
It seems you were the one
who made the a mistake
here.
Damn you! You were after
my branches all along!
Exactly. Our combined attacks
were all part of a plan to get
close to you.
If your power was the
ability to produce soldiers
like fruit from a tree,
then the answer to
stopping you was simple.
All we had to do was
freeze the branches where
the soldiers were
growing.
We all know fruit doesn't
grow on a frozen tree.
You shouldn't have been
so cocky in displaying
your powers. It helped me
understand how to stop you.
Dammit!
[roaring]
What?!
[growling]
What the hell was that?!
I think it's...
...Yammy!
Yammy?! The Espada
Captain Hitsugaya talked
about?!
That's right, but he's
not the same.
I fought this guy once
before, back in the World
of the Living...
He was a pretty big back
then, if I remember right.
But he wasn't this big!
Are you saying he can
just change his size at
will?!
How in the hell did he
get bigger? Was it some
kind of growth spurt?!
No. But something weird
definitely happened...
He looks to be twice as
big as before.
Dammit! That four-eyed
bastard is not getting
away with this!
I've had it with you
miserable piss-ants! I'm
gonna squash you like the
bugs that you are!
I promise, I'll be
the one that kills you!
Ahhhh! What the hell
is happening now?!
It's coming from outside
of the canopy!
That Spirit Energy...
could it be... Ichigo?
[gasping]
Stop, Ichigo.
It's over.
You've won the battle.
It's true that he
was our enemy,
but there's no
need to mutilate
his body.
You've won, Ichigo.
Let it go.
Didn't you hear
me? You've won. You
have to pull stop now!
If you go through with
this, you will not be
human anymore.
You have to stop
now, Ichigo!
No, Uryu!
Help... her.
Must... protect... her.
Help her...
I must...
I will... protect
help her.
This is all my fault! I'm
the one who's responsible
for this!
It's because of what I
said... I made Ichigo
help me!
How could I let
this happen?!
I trained because I didn't
want to be a burden to him.
I chose to come to Hueco
Mundo. I did this so I
could protect Ichigo
from getting hurt.
So why did I rely on him
for help... at the very
last moment?
Ichigo, don't do
this! Please!
Listen to me,
Ichigo!
[gasping]
[struggling]
Ichigo!
[panting]
Don't leave me,
Ichigo! I need you!
My arms, legs, and torso
are regenerating, but
it's all just for show.
The internal organs that
he blew away will never
come back.
If it hadn't ended with
that last strike... I would
be the one lying there...
dead.
[gasping]
Uh!
Unbelievable. The hole
closed up!
It's high speed...
regeneration.
Ichigo...
are you...?
[gasping]
I'm still alive?
Wait a minute...!
Didn't I...
... Didn't I have a
giant hole in my chest?
Yes, but you're healed.
Orihime... Are you all
right?
[gasping]
[struggling]
Uryu.
I see you finally...
snapped out of it.
Am I the one
responsible
for that
wound?
You're a hard guy to
kill.
Ulquiorra...
[groaning]
Pick it up. Let's
finish this battle now.
The one who stabbed
Uryu... Was it me?
What difference
does it make?
Am I also the one
responsible for cutting
off your left arm and leg?
If that's what happened,
then you should cut off
my left arm and leg!
What are you
talking about?!
The entity fighting you
earlier was a Hollowfied
being with no consciousness.
It was not
really me.
If we're going to
settle this fight,
I have to be in the
same condition as you, or
we won't be evenly matched!
Hold on, Ichigo!
Are you crazy?! You
can't be serious about
this! It's suicidal!
I'm fine with it. If
that is what you want,
that is what you will get.
[gasping]
So this is how it ends.
Kill me, Ichigo.
You don't have much
time left. I won't
resist you.
I no longer have the
strength to even walk.
If you don't take this
opportunity now, our duel
will remain unsettled
forever.
I can't do it.
What are you saying?
I don't want to.
Not like this.
It's wrong.
This is not the way
I want to defeat you!
[panting]
To the very end...
you just won't do
what I want.
And just when I was
finally becoming...
...a little bit intrigued
with the way you people
behave.
Are you afraid?
It's over.
You will die here. You
will die all by yourself
with no one to witness it.
So I want to know, how
frightened are you?
I am not. At all.
You see, now I know that
my friends came to rescue
me. So right now...
My heart... my
heart is with them.
What nonsense.
You're not scared,
because your friends have
come for you?
You can't be serious.
You really think they can
save you?
Absolutely.
Tell me, what is a
'heart'?
If I tore a hole in your
chest... would I see it?
If I split open your
skull... would it be
there?
So, let me ask
you again, girl...
Are you afraid of me?
No, I'm not afraid.
Really... I'm not.
I understand.
I see now...
... In the palm
of my hand...
...is a heart.
This guy Yammy, who fell
down from the tower---
Who does he belong to?
If we find someone's
belonging, we have to
return it to the owner!
If that's the case, then I
think we should be getting
20% of Yammy as a reward.
You know, I don't think
I'd really want that.