[running breaths]
[gasp]
We've expected
you.
[angry exhale]
Damn! We're
surrounded!
Just because
we're outnumbered
doesn't mean
we'll give up!
Ichigo...
Yeah?
I'll keep these
guys occupied
while the two of
you get past them.
What are
you saying!?
(Yoruichi)
A suicide dash!?
-Huh?
-Wha?
-Hm?
How pathetic
of you...
What are
you doing
here?
I'm not
alone.
You're all
here! You're
all alive!
Now then! It's
time for a real
fight!
So tell me,
Yoruichi, where
were you guys hding
this whole time?
Kukaku was the
one who ended up
helping us.
She saved us
from a close call.
[attack grunt]
[attack yell]
Soi Fon!
[painful shout]
[attack yell]
[gasp]
[evil laughter]
Hey! Kukaku!
It's you!
Damn it! Who
are these
intruders!?
I didn't expect
reinforcements!
Huh?
I anticipated this
possibility, and
made preparations
before hand.
(Yoruichi)
We healed our
injuries at
Kukaku's place.
And then we
waited for the
opportunity to
strike back.
[attack yell]
You're in the
way, Ichigo!
Get lost!
What'd you
say!?
Listen to him,
Ichigo!
We'll handle
things here! You
better get going!
Yoruichi!
Come on,
Ichigo!
Damn it! Come
back, you cowards!
Hiya!
Now there's
nothing to stop us
from finishing this.
How many times
must we go
through this?
You're going
down!
Hiya!
I'm going to
end your existance
once and for all!
{struggling breaths]
Ahhhh!
[running breaths]
Hey! Ichigo!
What's up?
You okay?
I'm doing fine!
Don't worry
about me!
We need to
find Kageroza's
lab!
[gasp]
[gasping breath]
(Kon)
Ichigo!
[grunt]
(Ichigo)
Kon...
Kisuke...
(Kon)
Listen up, Buddy!
You almost turned
into a Hollow again!
(Ichigo)
I did..?
(Kisuke)
Here's what I think,
Ichigo... I'm guessing
that inside you--
--the balance between your
Hollow Powers and your Soul
Reaper Powers is beinning
to break down.
[gasp]
Believe me, this
isn't easy for me
to say, Ichigo--
--but I think you
should stay here
while we continue
with our mission.
[gasp]
No wait! I--
[painful grunts]
You've gotta hang
in there, Ichigo!
Come on, pal!
Let's not
kid ourselves
here...
You know your
body best, it's
for your own
good.
[gasping]
Ichigo, he's
right! You should
stay here.
Let me handle
this!
I'll find a way
to fully restore
your Spirit Energy,
i promise you!
I appreciate
the thought,
but...
Why can't you just
for once say something
like, "Thanks Kon!"--
--"I'm counting on you!"
I'm more than just
some talking stuffed
anumal, you know.
(Ichigo)
What is
it, Kon?
I'm going too!
(Ichigo)
That's noble
of you, but--
I don't know
if I'll be any
kind of help,
really...
I mean, you know,
since I'm soft
like this...
But well, I
wanna try and
save Nozomi too!
No! I will
save her!
Know what,
you're right.
Huh!?
I'm counting
on you, Kon.
I've gotta tell you,
I wasn't expecting that.
It kinda give me the
creeps.
And, another
thing--
I want you to
take this with
you.
You want me to
take the Reishi
collector? Thanks.
It's in good
hands, Ichigo!
Hey Clog-Dude, did
ya really have to
leave him the way
that you did?
Well, I thought
just to be
safe...
...but I have
no idea if it's
gonna help him
get through this.
[grunting]
In any case, time
is of the essence.
Let's finish our
job and get
back here as soon as
we can, Kon.
Hmm, I hope this
guy knows what
he's doing!
Did you say
something?
Oh! No! I
was just mumblnig
to myself!
No matter how many
times we fight, it's
not going to change
anything--
--the bottom line
is this: There is
only one true head
of the Kuchiki Clan.
You do speak
the truth.
The fact is, that
one head of the
Clan, is me.
[attack yells]
[grunts]
Hiya!
Ha ha ha, I guess
you've still got it.
You still want
more, I assume?
And you know
that's the way
I like it.
Let's throw
down then! The
fun's just
beginning!
Lady Yoruichi!
Right!
Hiya!!
Ahh!
She seems to
have good
reflexes.
A little
too good.
Obviously their
capabilities have
been improved.
We may have
a little problem.
[attack roar]
Arg!
Haven't you
learned that you
have no chance
of winning?
Please, why don't
you just give up
and run away.
Or will your pride
get in your way when
you try to retreat
from a Reigai?
You've got it
all wrong.
I won't run, because
I'm committed to a
mission.
The Thirteen Court
Guards are here to
protect the Soul
Society!
Hey, Clog-Dude?
What is it, Kon?
Isn't this the place
we just escaped from!?
Why are we going
back in there!?
(Kisuke)
You're right, it is.
Which is why we are going
through the back door.
That's not
what I meant!!
Why in the heck
did we go the long
way around just to
come back here!?
Well, do you know the
old phrase, "To decieve
your enemies, you must
decieve your friends first."
I get that! That's not
the point. Can you
explain why in the world
we took our sweet time!?
The truth is, I wanted
to investigate Kageroza's
unit Squad Twelve before
we went any further.
But to prevent
suspicion, I needed
to come up with a
strategy.
I needed to make our
persuers think we
went somewhere else.
Okay...
Well, here we
are.
Unfortunately there's
nothing left from my
time here.
Wait a minute!
You used to be in
Squad Twelve like
Kageroza!?
Oh my! Did I
forget to
mention that
part?
Are you kidding
me!? You know
damned well
you didn't!
That means all
this time you've
known about
Kageroza!
Actually, he came
along after me.
He wasn't even
inducted yet when
I was here.
You're a useless
resource!
Here we go! Let's
see. I hope we can
find something in
their database.
Hey, it's
asking for a
password.
Yes, I was
expecting that.
Every peice of
equiptment in here
has been programmed
by Mayuri.
He's not that
hard to read...
I don't think it
will be too difficult
to figure out what he'd
use for a password.
Let's see now.
First try...
Too bad!
You're wrong!
Oh my...
Come on!!!
Alright then, how
about this.
Idiot!
What? Alright, I've
got another one.
Ha!
(Kisuke)
See!?
You sure that
wasn't just a
lucky guess?
I can't make heads
or tails of this
stuff. Is this what
you were looking for?
Yeah. According to
this, Kageroza was
inducted into the Soul
Society about 60 years ago.
Really? That long
ago? And Nozomi?
I don't see
anything about
her in this
database.
[gasp]
What is it!?
Hey Clog-Dude!
Stop ignoring
me!!!
What's going
on!?
Let's get out
of here, Kon.
Huh!? Hold on,
where are
you going!?
(Kon)
Are you gonna
answer me, or
not!?
(Kisuke)
I have to go
to the library.
(Kisuke)
There are some
records I need
to check.
Wow! Look at
all of the books
they keep in
this place!
So what are you
checking on here?
I'm going through
the background files
of each Squad's recruits
and discharges as they--
--were recorded between
the time I was banished
and the time Kageroza
first appeared.
Oh...
[gasp]
As I expected.
We need to go
to Squad Ten
barracks.
For what reason!?
Will you stop keeping
things to yourself!
Jeeze! This bastard
is all about
keeping secrets!
[struggling grunts]
(Kon)
Are they gone?
(Kisuke)
Looks like it...
So, did you learn
anything? If you
did it's time you
told me!
Cause if you
don't I'm
gonna lose it!
Kon, you need to
calm yourself down
and lower your voice.
Now think back...
Do you remember what
Nozomi said to you before?
What are you
talking about?
He's the one...
I'm the one...
...who originally
developed the
Mod Souls.
And that wasn't the
only thing she said,
do you remember?
(Nozomi)
Out of all the Mod
Souls that have
been created...
...I was the
first.
Then Kageroza
explained it further...
(Kageroza)
It's quite simple
you see.
(Kageroza)
Nozomi and I were both
from the Reishi of a
single Soul Reaper.
No one knows
her better
than me.
Did you notice that
their two stories
differed in one
important aspect?
[mmuffled shouts]
And because of
that, isn't it
obvious that one
of them is lying!
Well it's certainly
possible. But there
might be another
explanation.
What if what
they both said
was actually
true?
Hm?
What I'm trying to say
is, what if Kageroza
is a Mod Soul himself?
Hm?
(Kisuke)
In other words,
the two were once
a single Mod Soul.
I don't get it!
If Kageroza is
also a Mod Soul,
then how could
he be the one who
developed Mod Souls!?
It sort of begs the
question, who
created his Mod Soul?
[gasp]
Like the invading army
Mod Souls were originally
created from the Reishi
of a particular Soul Reaper.
And then imbued with
enhanced capabilities.
And if that's true,
then there can only
be one answer.
The person who developed
Mod Souls had to use
himelf as the basis for
their creation!
Exactly right, which
would mean then, that
tboth Nozomi and Kageroza
are representations of
the same Soul Reaper who
originally developed them.
Wait but that still
leaves one question!
Who in the world could
that Soul Reaper be!?
I'm thinking we
might find the
answer at the
Squad Ten Barracks.
If we can figure
out the true
developer--
I'm hoping that
we'll be able to
locate the original
lab as well!
And if we can find
the lab, we can
probably restore
Ichigo'sSpirit Energy!
Hey Clog-Dude! When
did you figure this
whole thing out!?
I have to admit, I
had my suspicions
before we came here
to the Soul Society.
Then you should have
told us, instead of
keeping it to yourself!
That was really
selfish of you!
I didn't really
want to tell anyone
until I had more
proof of my theory.
At the Squad Twelve
barracks, I began
reviewing the records
from the time I left
the Soul Society, until
the time Kageroza assumed
his post at the Department
of Research and Development.
(Kon)
And..?
I expected to find a
Soul Reaper who disappeared
before Kageroza showed up,
but I found something
else instead.
The records in which
I was interested, had
all been erased.
And that's why
you went over
to the library?
Yeah. I thought whoever
had tampered with the files
might have overlooked the
archives in the library.
--and the records
would still be in
tact.
(Kon)
So, how did that
work out?
I found nothing
listed in Squad Twelve's
registry of names--
--and no signs of
alterations...
But I did find
indications of tampering,
in the books of another
squad.
Really? Intersting.
In which particular
book was that?
It was a book of
Squad Ten's records
from a long time
ago.
Ninety-six years
ago to be exact.
(Kon)
Come on! Haven't you
found it yet!?
No, nothing that
looks even remotely
like it.
(Kisuke)
There's no way that
these particular records
could have been changed.
(Kisuke)
Bring me more books.
Ahhhh!
[gasp]
Arrgghhh!!
(Kisuke)
Here it is...
Huh!? Really,
you found it?
Yes, I'm sure
this is it.
It's dated ninety-six
years ago. The man was
transferred to Squad
Twelve.
So?! What is
the guy's name!?
(Kisuke)
Ouko... Yushima.
(Kon)
Hey! This guy
sorta does look
a little like Nozomi!
So, where do we
find him!? Where
is this guy!?
What does that crossed
out part of the page mean?
What it means, is that
the man doesn't exist
within Squad Twelve anymore.
But I believe
I know where he
is today.
This is the Special
Underground Confinement
Station, also known as
"The Maggot's Nest"
Why would he
be here?!
The Thirteen Court
Guard Squads make no
provision for resignation.
That means if no
records exist after
their time of service--
--this is the only
place a Soul Reaper
could be!
How come there's
no one here!?
I mean really! There
wasn't even a guard
at the entrance back there!
Doesn't that seem
strange to you!?
Yes. It's unusual.
I wonder if--
(Soi Fon Reigai)
We thought you might
show up here,
Kisuke Urahara!
We've been waiting
for you!
And now that you've
arrived, I'll put
an end to you myself!
Hey! It's the Bee
Chick, and Slim
Fatso!
Who the hell are
you calling "Fatso!?"
I'm nothin' at
all like that guy
so back off!
Are you ready to
complete the
mission, Kon?
You go on ahead,
I'll hold them
off here.
Right! I won't
let you down!
Why are you
waiting! Go
after him!
Gotcha!
I was right. Just
as I suspected.
This is where you're
holding Ouko Yushima,
the developer of
Mod Souls.
How mart of you.
Sting all enemies to
death! Suzumebachi!
Arghhhhh!!!
Ahhhh!
Ahhh!
Hey! Come back
here ya little
pibsqueak!
Ahhh! I'll never be
able to out-run him!
Hey Clog-Dude!
I need some
help!
Heh heh
heh...
[gasp]
[running]
Psych!
[laughing]
[pained grunt]
Shibari
Benihime.
[gasp]
Hiasobi Benihime!
Juzutsunagi!
Damn it!
We did it!
The Doppelganger
Plan worked!
Yes! All thanks
to you, Kon!
[chuckles]
Thanks, but I
really didn't do
that much.
Come on.
Let's go.
Right! We've come a
long way. Let's go
meet the real developer!
[nervous groan]
So.. You really think
he's down here?
This is the facility's
lowest level. If he's
not down here, then I
have to believe that
those two Reigai we met
earlier, were wasting their
time, guarding this place
for nothing.
True. You have a
good point there.
Are you
Ouko Yushima?
He's not
responding.
Hey, you there!
Get up!
Wakie wakie!
Hey, anybody
in there?!
It's no use.
Huh?
I hate to say this, but it
doesn't look to me like he'll
ever regain consciousness.
Are you
serious?
[pained groans]
[roar]
I'm tired of
being so small
and helpless!
I wish I were in
a bigger and
stronger Gigai!
All right!
You agree?
Yeah, you can take
my place and go up
against Marechiyo
and Soi Fon,
and get beaten
to a pulp!
Uhh, my size isn't
so bad after all.