ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
I'm Ichigo Kurosake,
and other than having the
ability to see spirits,
I used to be an ordinary
high school student.
But the day I met
Rukia Kuchiki, I
was given the powers
of a Soul Reaper
in order to protect the
world of the living.
As I began my work as a
substitute Soul Reaper,
I found myself thrown into
a never ending battle.
In the midst of everything,
my best friend, Orihime Inoue,
was abducted by ex-Soul
Reaper captain, Sosuke Aizen.
My friends Chad
and Uryu joined me
as I raced to rescue Orihime.
Once we arrived in Hueco
Mundo, we entered a fight
with powerful enemies
known as Arrancars.
We were too late to
keep Aizen from entering
the world of the living,
but luckily the 13 court
guard squads were
already there to stop it.
An all out war was
about to begin.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: In order to prevent
Sosuke Aizen from wiping out
Karakura town, the Soul
Reapers moved the town
to the Rukon District
in the Soul Society.
Then they positioned themselves
in the world of the living,
where they placed an exact
replica of Karakura Town
to fool Aizen and his forces.
Head Captain Yamamoto assigned
each of the Soul Reapers
to protect the town,
having them face off
against the Espadas
and Fracciones.
Sui-Feng, the
captain of Squad 2,
was assigned to face off against
Barragan's Fraccion Ggio Vega.
They engaged in a midair
battle, with Sui-Feng fighting
Ggio Vega in his released
form, Tigre Estoque.
But as the speed and strength
of his attack increased,
Sui-Feng found herself weakened
by his relentless onslaught.
Meanwhile, another
Fraccion, Nirgge Parduoc
is locked in combat with
Marechiyo Omaeda, who
appears lost in trying
to deal with Nirgge's
powerful released form, Mamut.
The only difference
Omaeda could manage
was running away from Nirgge,
who used his trunk as a weapon,
chasing after Omaeda with
surprising quickness.
It seemed certain Nirgge's
overpowering attacks
were about to spell defeat
for the hapless Omaeda
when the unthinkable happened.
-How did you do that?
-Who do you suppose
you've been dealing with?
-What?
-I'm the lieutenant of Squad 2,
and the head of Stealth Force
2nd Unit, known
as Patrol Troops.
My name is Marechiyo Omaeda.
If you knew about
the Stealth Force,
you'd know I'd
never be that slow.
Now smash them!
Gegetsuburi!
All right, I won!
Hey, look at you now.
You got exactly
what you deserved.
Talk smack to me, will you?
You see what
happens, butterball?
You thought you were
pretty damn smart, right?
You've got no somethings.
Oh, sure big man.
You and your tricky
body, hopping around.
So, who's in charge now,
you with your weird nose
like a vacuum cleaner.
Maybe I should tear that
think off your face.
what do you think?
-I see.
So, your running away
was all just an act?
-No, I'm not that
good of an actor,
and I'm really sorry
about trying to run away.
Come on, how about
giving me a break?
My nose is still here.
It feels in one piece.
Whoa.
What just happened?
Oh no.
Captain.
C-C-Captain!
Are you all right, Captain?
I mean, what have you
gotten yourself into now?
Captain!
From the look of things,
you must be injured.
-Shut up.
Don't make such a big
fuss over nothing.
You're stifling me.
-But Captain.
-Turning your back on your
enemy any time during a battle
is inexcusable.
Even if you see your
superior go down.
-But ma'am.
What subordinate wouldn't rush
to their fallen superior's
side?
You are my captain.
Besides-- (IN HEAD) That guy
must have overwhelming strength
to be able to put the captain
in a position like that.
I strongly suggest that we
fight this opponent together,
Captain.
-Do I hear compassion
for your superior,
or do you speak out of loyalty?
-That's not it at all, ma'am.
It's just--
-It's just what?
I really do my best to ignore
your recklessly arrogant
attitude, but you
repay my efforts
with simply more
insulting behavior.
Stand back.
You're in my way.
-You done saying your farewell
to that lousy lieutenant
of yours?
-And just why would I be
saying farewell to him?
-Obviously it's because
you're about to die.
-Even if I should
die fighting you,
it would serve no real purpose
for me to tell him goodbye.
-Then let's get started.
-What's the idea of
treating me like I'm
a big pain in the
ass when all I did
was express concern for her?
I mean, she was flat
on her backside.
No matter how you look
at it, it was mean.
She pisses me off.
Wow, that bastard's impressive.
It really looks like he's
got the captain working hard.
In fact, against the captain,
I'd say he's an even match.
Wait.
I can't really call this even.
-It's nice the way our
weapons are so similar.
That way, you can fight using
techniques familiar to you
and make full use of
all your strength.
You see, even using
all your strength,
I know this is the
best you can do.
-I knew it.
He's actually pushing her back.
Is she putting on an act?
No way.
The captain has so much pride,
she rejected my offer to help.
Even if she were acting, she'd
never pretend to be losing.
So, should I go
help her out now?
I can't.
If she acts the way
she did last time,
I'll just catch another brick
and a bucket of complaints.
-Ha.
If that's how she is, let
her fight her own battles.
Why should I care
what happens to her?
NIRGGE: Is that so?
-Yeah, damn right.
-Guess you forgot about me.
-Worried about your
lackey after all?
-If I worried about
my subordinates
whenever they're
challenged, I'd never stop.
-Really?
Well, it looks
like you won't have
to concern yourself worrying
about your little lieutenant.
-Why's that?
-I doubt that loser will
be alive much longer.
-Oh well.
That's his problem.
He's just too weak.
MAN: You're quite a
cold one, Captain.
-Maybe I over did it
with that last punch.
I should've held back a little.
But that fat wise ass
was really annoying.
It's just no fun what
it's one and done.
-Well now, you have no one
to worry about anymore.
I think it's time for
me to finish this off.
-I wasn't worried.
I have no such feelings for
the subordinates in my squad.
And besides--
-Huh?
Ow, my head.
-Damn you.
-I have such good luck.
I don't know why, but
since I was a kid,
my body's always
been pretty sturdy.
Maybe it's because
us rich people
are built to handle tougher
stuff than most poor folks are.
-I've heard enough.
I'm shutting your wise
ass mouth for good.
-I'm not falling for that again.
Now smash them!
Gegetsuburi!
How about a little payback?
Come on, Pal.
What happened to all
that tough talk of yours?
Now that I'm not
running, you look scared.
Yeah, the tables have turned.
You hear that, Captain?
Hey.
What the hell is she doing?
She'll wind up dead!
You won't get away with this.
You stinky bastard.
-Take another spin.
-Looks like our roles have
switched, captain of Squad 2.
And it certainly appears your
second in command's battle
will be settled soon as well.
But you won't live
to see the end of it.
-Now you know.
-Damn bastard.
-It's useless.
You can't get out
of this this time.
Hey.
Looks like you're going to get
to see your captain's fight
finish up first.
-That's not my main concern.
(IN HEAD) She's really
in trouble over there.
Should I go to help her?
I want to, but if I don't do
something about this guy first,
he'll attack me
from behind again.
I can't do anything unless I
get this trunk of his off me.
Damn.
That's a Cero!
-Here we go.
You ready to get hit by
this at point blank range?
-Now that I think of it,
I did tell you my name.
But things have happened so
fast, I still don't know yours.
Not that it really matters.
See you, Captain of Squad Two.
[shouts]
[groan]
-You're in the way.
What is this?
You can't appear out of nowhere.
-Gotcha.
-Hold on.
Didn't Nirgge kill you?
-Who's Nirgge?
Oh, yeah.
You mean that elephant creep?
[scream]
-Hey, I can use this
force against him.
Yah!
Idiot!
I just took the strength of your
pull and used it to nail you!
Captain!
That's how it happened.
Anyway, Captain,
I really did it.
I have him locked.
So Captain, now,
this is your chance.
-Her chance?
You're not being serious?
-Huh?
[groan]
-Now fly away.
-Who told you to come rescue me?
Didn't you hear me earlier?
You are quite arrogant.
And when you operate this way,
it's quite insulting to me.
-Um, but I-- well, you see--
-As I was fighting
him, I was holding back
because I wanted to gauge
the strength of an Arrancar's
Resurreccion attack.
I was merely preparing
for my next battle
against the Espadas.
Oh, never mind.
I think I've seen
enough of his limits.
-Well-- you-- you-- you don't
have to put it like that!
I came on the double
to rescue you, Captain,
because I thought that you
were gonna be wiped out.
Hey!
Who told you to
come and rescue me?
What the hell did that mean?
You said that like
I did something
I shouldn't have done.
You witch!
You're wicked!
You mean-spirited creep!
-Lend me your ear, Omaeda.
-Huh?
What is it?
-Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
-Moron.
My guess is that you were
worried that if I was killed,
then you supposed
you would be next.
That's why you came to help.
Well then, am I correct?
-I never thought that.
SUI-FENG: What if
I had been killed?
I never taught you
to come to my rescue.
Think.
What did I teach you?
When one of us dies, that
gives the other of us
a chance to strike.
Don't get in between.
Stab him from behind.
If the enemy is too powerful
for you to do even that,
then abandon your
fellow squad member.
That is the way of
the Stealth Force.
Look.
Your enemy is still
alive and well.
-What?
-Go on.
Get going.
-Come on!
You don't have to speak
to me so harshly, do you?
-Never mind.
You need to go now.
Go defeat him.
Quickly.
-Sorry to keep you
waiting, Arrancar.
Now, listen to me.
Earlier you mocked what you
thought were my best efforts,
so allow me to show you
a real assassination.
-What?
[shouting]
OMAEDA (VOICEOVER):
That bastard's
seriously on a rampage.
I can't go attacking him when
he's swinging his trunk around
like that.
-I'll show you.
Get ready to be
smashed to death!
[shout]
-Ha ha ha ha!
What a way for this to end.
You're mine!
Huh?
OMAEDA: Sorry.
-Where are you?
-Earlier I learned
something important.
-When one of us dies,
that gives the other of us
the chance to strike.
Don't get in between.
Stab them in the back.
-It's not only when
one of our squad dies.
Our own crisis can give us
a chance to strike, as well.
-You bastard.
You mean you went
down on purpose?
-You're through.
Yah!
[scream]
-So, you're going to show
me a real assassination?
Heh.
Go ahead.
SUI-FENT: Wait.
I take back what I just said.
-Huh?
Why is that?
-This will end so quickly,
you won't even notice it.
-Don't you mock me!
[shout]
-What was that?
-Look, you.
I'll show you what
true strength is!
[shouting] Behold, Tigre
Estoque's actual battle form.
This is Tigre Estoque Sabre!
-Sorry victims of my Suzumebachi
are killed by the two stings
that I deliver.
But I'm betting
you only felt one.
[gasping]
-Dammit.
[scream]
-Yeah!
Way to go, Captain!
Incredible!
You did it!
-I'm confused.
So Suzumebachi is effective
even if it doesn't sting twice
in the same place?
-It did.
-What?
SUI-FENG: I struck him
twice in the same location
in his right lung.
One from the front,
and one from the back.
I went for his internal organs
from the very start, not
the wound.
But enough, already.
We don't have any time
for a chat, Omaeda.
-Huh?
-A new opponent.
Don't say anything that
might compromise us.
-Right.
-And this time,
follow me closely,
so that you don't
get in the way.
-Right.
[theme music]
OMAEDA: That Mamut
what's his name
wasn't much of an opponent.
NIRGGE: Rawr!
My name is Nirgge Parduoc!
Mamut is my name in my giant
elephant soldier Resurreccion
form!
OMAEDA: It doesn't really
matter, "Pardukey."
You're already did.
NIRGGE: Oh, shut up!