[theme music]
-What?
What did you just
say, Captain Kuchiki?
What do you mean?
-It is as I said.
Do I need to repeat myself?
25 days from now, she'll go to
the central execution grounds,
where she will suffer
the ultimate punishment.
That is the final decision
of the Soul Society.
And this will be the last
time that you and I shall ever
exchange words.
Rukia, the next time that I see
you will be at your execution.
[door closing]
RUKIA NARRATING: We are
taught never to shed teams,
for to shed tears
means that the body has
been defeated by emotion.
And to us, that simple
act of crying only
proves without question that
the existence of emotion
is nothing but a burden.
-Lesson 2, Shattered Shaft.
-May I have your
attention please?
You have a period of
72 hours at the bottom
of Shattered Shaft, Ichigo.
That is how long it will
take for the chain of fate
to be completely encroached.
By the end of that
time, if you have not
returned to the top of the
shaft as a Soul Reaper,
then we will have no choice,
Ichigo, but to kill you.
-You bastard.
So you intend to kill me?
-That's right.
I do, once you've given up.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): [grunts].
CHAD (OFFSCREEN): [grunts].
-You're both
completely hopeless.
At this rate, I'll
never be able to let
you enter the Soul Society.
-Wait, that's not fair.
-Quit it, stop whining.
Unless you are able to
activate your powers at will,
you will die like a dog
in the Soul Society.
Do you understand me?
-Hmm.
-It's not that hard.
Just remember the first
time you used your powers
and retrace those steps.
-Well, that's easier
said than done.
I was so desperate
that first time.
-What were you so
desperate about?
-Huh?
-Think about it this way.
A person picks up
a sword when he's
trying to protect something.
Perhaps it's your
life, or social status,
maybe a reputation, a loved
one, or personal beliefs.
The motives may be completely
different, but in the end,
it's the same desire
to protect something.
Think back.
What were you trying to
protect when you first
called upon your powers?
-Let's see.
-Hmm, I was-- I was trying
to protect Ichigo's kid
sister, a red cap, long hair.
And since she's Ichigo's
sister, she looks like Ichigo,
but she's still a girl.
[groans]
-It seems you
failed to remember.
And what about you?
-Well, I-- [sighs].
I, uh, at that time-- I was
so desperate, so desperate.
[tinkling]
-It shined.
-Huh?
Really?
Hey, guys.
-You summoned?
If you ever need
us, don't hesitate.
Just call and ask for help.
-But considering this situation,
for what possible reason would
you need our help?
-Because that's our job.
-I'm sorry.
I was remember all sorts of
things, and then-- [shrieks].
-You weren't even in danger,
and yet you called for us?
You terrible little hussy.
-Ow.
-Tsubaki, you stop
that right now.
-Shut up.
Can't you see I'm pissed off.
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
-Stop running, you little hussy.
-Ow.
-You heard me.
-Tsubaki, stop chasing her.
-Oh, dear me.
He's on a terrible rampage.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN):
Ow, the hair.
-Sometimes Tsubaki is so rough.
-Well done, Orihime.
Although it seems to me that
you're going to need a bit more
practice when it comes
to taming your own power.
What about you?
Any luck yet?
Tell me, why are you
going to the Soul Society?
[chewing sounds]
ICHIGO (IN HEAD): The fifth
encroachment has just ended.
There seems to be a
cycle to all this.
First they start chomping,
then they fall asleep.
During these periods
of encroachment,
I can hardly move.
The chains are so painful.
So if I'm gonna move, it'll have
to be while they're sleeping.
[groaning]
-It makes no sense
what he's doing,
but he's still managing to climb
up a practically straight wall.
For a human, this guy
sure takes changes.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): [screams].
-Oh, you don't say?
-Idiot.
-Dammit.
-Hey?
Are you getting
hungry down there yet?
-No, I'm not hungry, yet.
Besides, jerk, I'm
in my soul form.
Why the hell would I be hungry.
-Well, that's great
to hear, because I'll
let you in on a little secret.
If you're in soul form and
then you start to get hungry,
it's a dangerous sign.
It means you're just one step
away from becoming a Hollow.
It's OK to feel thirsty though.
Oh, and if you do get thirsty,
go ahead and drink my spit.
-Why, you little.
-Come on, Ururu, get over here.
You can do it too.
-OK.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Come
down here and try that.
You brats!
Stop drooling.
Cut it out.
Stop it or I'll beat
the crap out of you.
Hey, I'm not kidding.
-Hmm.
I wonder if it's dark outside.
In this room, it's difficult
to tell the time of day.
ICHIGO (IN HEAD): Dammit,
I can't climb out.
How much time has passed?
I can't tell.
How can I climb
out of this place?
Huh?
-Yo.
Thought I'd bring you a
little food down here.
I figured you'd be feeling
pretty hungry right about now.
-Ha, you must be nuts.
I'm not getting hungry at all.
Take a good look.
The way I see it, there
are still quite a few links
to the chain of fate.
-Hmm, well, that
can't be helped.
You'll find you lose track
of time in a place like this.
-Time?
-You know, you've been
down here over 70 hours,
and I'm just thinking,
some of the other souls
started turning
into Hollows by now.
Oh, and, uh, one more thing.
The final encroachment, it's
nothing like the other ones.
-The chains.
No way.
Stop, all of you.
Stop!
[screams]
-All right, looks
like he's gonna
become a Hollow after all.
[screaming]
-I've got to help.
It's time I rescued him.
-Hold it.
-But Mr. Kisuke--
-Watch him closely,
nothing more.
Usually, when a hole
becomes a Hollow,
first the spiritual body
explodes, and then it reforms.
But in his case, the
order is all mixed up.
The mask is being created
while the body is still a hole.
This is a sign that
he is resisting.
There is still a
strong possibility
that in time, he'll
become a Soul Reaper.
So let's watch a while and
see if indeed he truly becomes
a Hollow.
Just a little longer.
-[screams].
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Ichigo can you hear me?
-Where am I?
MALE SPEAKER
(OFFSCREEN): Over here.
-So tell me, who are you?
-Who?
What are you talking about?
It's me, Zangetsu.
ICHIGO (IN HEAD): I
couldn't hear his name.
-I see.
So I still can't reach you?
How very sad.
Perhaps you can tell
me how many times
I must cry out before
you can hear me,
for there is no one
in this world that
knows me better than you do.
-Huh?
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry, but unfortunately,
I don't know anyone
as depressing as you are.
How did you-- it's like
you're just floating in air.
-You surprise me.
How can you just sit there
in a place like that?
-[screams].
-If you can scream, then
you've got time, time to spare.
Why are you worrying?
Don't you know Soul
Reapers rule death?
In fact, they control
many spiritual beings.
-Uh, look, whatever you're
saying, I am not a Soul Reaper.
-Remember this.
The Soul Reaper power that
Byakuya Kuchiki managed
to remove from you was
nothing more than power
that you received
from Rukia Kuchiki.
Apparently, he had hoped to stop
things by taking your power.
By destroying it, he
thought he could end things
once and for all,
but he was careless.
His mistake was that he
failed to realize one fact,
you have Soul Reaper
power of your own.
-You mean I have it?
I have Soul Reaper power?
-Yes, the Soul
Reaper power you have
was awakened with the help
of Rukia Kuchiki's own power.
It hid itself in the very
depths of your soul an instant
before Byakuya Kuchiki's
thrust, and it is still there.
Now, find it.
If there ever was
a time when you
must find the power
of the Soul Reaper
that has hidden itself in
you, then that next time
is now since the world
has begun its collapse.
See these boxes raining
down, surrounding you?
Inside one of them lies
your Soul Reaper power.
It is up to you to find it.
-What?
This doesn't make sense.
ZANGETSU (OFFSCREEN): not
tolerate any more excuses.
There is no time left.
You must find it before this
world is completely destroyed,
or you will become a Hollow.
ICHIGO (IN HEAD): Yeah,
so what am I gonna do now?
How am I supposed to find
the one box out of all these
that contains my
Soul Reaper power?
What do I do?
What was he thinking?
I just don't have the ability
to search out spirit energy.
It's not possible.
Hey, Uryu once said
the same thing to me.
Uryu, wait.
How did Uryu find out
that I was a Soul Reaper?
You know, it was
some simple method.
-Did you know?
ICHIGO (IN HEAD): He bragged
about it, but what was it?
-Did you know that a Soul
Reaper's spirit ribbon is red?
-That's it.
I found it!
What the hell?
The handle of a zanpakuto?
-You have done
well in finding it.
It is my hope that the next
time you will hear my name.
-You couldn't possibly be--
[explosion]
-What do you think you're doing?
It's crumbling.
Hurry up.
You must pull me up now.
-[grunts].
[screams]
-That is absolute limit, boss.
I am switching to
suppression mode.
Bakudo 99, Part 2, [inaudible].
First incantation, bandage.
Second incantation,
[inaudible] deadbolts.
-Hey, be careful down there,
Tessai, If you do all of that,
there's a good
chance he could die.
-I can't hold him
down any longer.
He must be destroyed
immediately.
Right now, before
he becomes a Hollow.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): [screams].
-Final incantation, fatal seal.
This is it.
-Look at that.
Something's shooting out of it.
That thing-- just
what the heck is that?
Hey?
Is that you?
Answer, Carrot Top.
If you're alive, answer me.
Oh.
A shihakusho and a mask?
Is he a Hollow, or
is he a Soul Reaper?
I may be small,
but I'll fight you.
Hey, wait a minute.
Aren't you supposed
to be a Hollow?
[clapping]
-Congratulations.
It seems you went and
became a Soul Reaper again.
Well done.
Lesson two completed.
-Shut up.
-Ow.
[sobs]
-Well, well, well.
I bet you weren't expecting me
to come back alive, were you?
I swore to myself that if
I made it out of that hole,
I would kill you the
first chance that I got.
-Your timing is perfect.
With all of your
spirit, we should
be able to get you
started on lesson three.
-What did you just say?
-And the best part is, lesson
three has no time limit.
Knock off my hat
with your zanpakuto,
and the lesson will be cleared.
Hmm.
Not bad, considering that
your zanpakuto is broken.
-I wouldn't be so smug,
because I haven't really
gotten down to business yet.
Look, why don't we just forget
about your concept of no time
limits?
I think we could end this
lesson in five minutes.
-Sounds good.
Five minutes.
And you say that's all
the time you need, right?
[music playing]
-In order to release the
power of the zanpakuto,
one has to first discover
its name and then summon it.
Now then, the question remains,
can Ichigo find it in time?
-Bet you 1,000 yen he can't.
-Bet you 2,000 I can.