[theme music]
VOICEOVER: Soul Reapers.
The spiritual guardians to
the world of the living.
Their job is to maintain the
balance between the myriad
of good and evil souls
that fill this world.
Ichigo and Captain
Hitsugaya's troops
barely managed to
defeat the Arrancars
that Aizen had created.
But both sides
suffered major damages.
ICHIGO: The truth is I haven't
been able to protect anyone.
I couldn't defeat our enemies.
I was useless.
I lost.
-Good job of
finding this Ichigo.
VOICEOVER: Ichigo
tracked down the Visored
with one goal in
mind-- to learn how
to suppress his inner hollow.
[shrieking]
-You pass.
We'll teach you control.
You'll learn how to deal with
that hollow inside of you.
-Hey.
Long time no see.
King.
-Where the hell is Zangetsu?
Answer me.
[chuckling]
-When you talk about
Zangetsu, do you
mean the one you're
holding in your hand?
Or is it this one in mine?
[gasp]
-I'm Zangetsu!
[deep exhale]
My name is Lisa Yadomaru.
Nice to meet you.
-You can't beat me.
[chuckling]
-Ban!
Kai!
[groaning]
-This is it.
Here it comes.
-Bastard!
Now tell me where
the hell did you
learn to use bankai like this?
-Isn't it obvious?
I learned at the
same time you did.
[groaning]
-Wait a minute.
This is the Soul Society!
How did I-- what?
BYAKUYA: Scatter.
Senbonzakura.
-What the hell's happening?
Byukuya!
-Pathetic.
Is that all the
power you have now?
-What are you talking about?
Tell me what the hell
is going on here!
Answer me!
Where are we?
And why are you here?
-You're a disappointment,
Ichigo Kurasaki.
Bankai.
-What are you doing?
-Scatter.
Senbonzakura.
Kagayoshi.
-Damn it.
[grunting]
-Byakuya, stop!
This is no time to be
fighting each other.
[grunting]
[panting]
-Why?
-Amazingly you haven't
even acknowledged
the confusion in your heart.
-What you mean?
How exactly have I failed?
-Stand up, Ichigo Kurasaki.
Or else.
-Byakuya!
You're starting to piss me off!
[groan]
[grunting]
-It is clear to me, Ichigo.
In spite of your
best efforts, I now
see that it's impossible
for you to truly use Bankai.
-Byakuya.
You're out of your mind.
I'm using Bankai
right now, aren't I?
This is crazy.
I'm tired of all this
nonsense, you jerk.
-The truth is those who don't
have the will to fight cannot
deflect my blade.
It's over.
-Why are you getting so upset?
We should have some fun.
-Shut the hell up.
Wait a minute.
Why does Byakuya
keep popping up?
I haven't got a clue
what's going on here.
-Concentrate now.
Don't lose your focus.
-Believe me.
I won't!
-Oh really?
Then why were you just staring
off into space a minute ago?
-I said I'm not losing focus!
Zen Getsuga Tensho!
-Hm.
-He blocked it with one hand.
-Heh.
Getsuga Tensho.
[grunting]
-All right.
That's it.
10 minutes.
Hachi.
Time to switch out.
Now.
-Yes, sir.
[shrieking]
[grunt]
-Your time's up.
My turn.
[shrieking]
-I'm Kensei Muguruma.
And I'm going to kill you.
[shrieking]
-Stop messing around, Ichigo.
If you don't finish this soon,
we'll be forced to kill you.
-I told you.
You're not good enough, Ichigo.
Didn't you notice?
I was the first to
use Getsuga Tensho
after we released our Bankai.
And you?
All you did was
watch my technique.
You tried to imitate me
and failed miserably.
You're incompetent.
But you know that don't you?
Ichigo.
You might as well give up.
You're not good
enough at Bankai!
[gasp]
-You're completely useless
and always have been, kid.
-Huh?
-Kariya?
[panting]
-How much of a break do I get?
-If all of us rotate
in on schedule,
It's 10 minutes
times eight people,
so that makes it 80 minutes.
-It isn't times eight, idiot.
You can't count her,
so it's only seven.
-Fine.
10 minutes times 7
is 70 minutes then.
-Wait a minute.
This doesn't sound good.
I'm only supposed to
form the barriers,
but they're including me
in the fight calculations.
-Ichigo is strong.
A lot stronger than
I thought he'd be.
You'd better be very
careful while you're
fighting out there, Kensei.
Because if you aren't--
-Instant regeneration.
-He's pretty serious.
What's up with him?
-Don't be so critical.
You'll see why
when you get there.
[cough]
[shriek]
[grunt]
-What the hell is this?
[shriek]
[gurgling]
-You're transforming
faster than we expected.
[shrieking]
-Ichigo's internal battle
to control his hollow
needs to be finished
within one hour.
Not counting
[inaudible], there's
six of us to go before
it becomes my turn again.
If this battle gets all the way
back to me, he'll be done for.
-Kariya.
I'm not seeing you.
-Hm.
-You're an illusion
of some kind.
-Maybe you're right.
But--
-But what?
-Well, it all depends on
what you think you're seeing.
Most illusions are seen with
the heart, not the eyes.
You made a replica of me
from deep within your soul.
That in itself suggests that
your heart is full of doubt.
It reveals you
regret defeating me.
The truth is whenever you finish
a battle, the fallout from it
weighs heavily on your mind.
Afterward, you turn your back
to the enemy you defeated,
and the friends you
couldn't protect.
Be honest, Ichigo.
go Are you that afraid of
moving forward after the fight?
Are you that afraid of
walking the same path as me?
-No!
I'm different from you.
-You don't sound so convincing.
What happened to your Zangetsu?
[groaning]
-Do you think you can defeat
me with your bare hands?
[groaning]
-What a shame.
You've lost your Zangetsu.
Now you know how it
feels to be helpless.
In your current state you're
as vulnerable and defenseless
as a newborn.
-Damn it.
-Do you want a
weapon that badly?
Well then, I'll give you one!
[scream]
[groaning]
-Hold on.
Hey, is that Zangetsu?
-Sorry, kid.
It's just me.
You wanted a weapon, right?
Choose whichever one you like.
-No.
Zangetsu isn't here.
I almost forgot.
Zangetsu lives within me.
-What's wrong?
Aren't you going
to pick up a sword?
If you don't then, how
will you deal with this?
-I've got a surprise
for you, smart guy.
Zangetsu!
-Heh.
Does this zanpakuto
look familiar?
What do you have to say now?
-You're certainly confident
with a weapon in your hand.
But you know something?
You're truly pathetic.
-Shut up!
-If you're so confident,
then try to take me down.
[grunting]
-You will never
be able to cut me.
Especially with a
sword that regrets
having defeated me
in our last fight.
[grunt]
-Let me be perfectly
honest with you.
[groan]
-This is something you
don't know about battle.
The fight never ends.
After you've defeated one
enemy, a stronger opponent
will appear.
Then if you're
able to defeat him,
an even stronger
one comes along.
If you don't have
the inner resolve
to endure this eternal
struggle, then you
will eventually succumb and die.
But it doesn't end there.
The battles always continue
elsewhere, fought by others.
It's an endless cycle.
And it's not only limited
to a person's existence
on the physical plane.
Believe me.
As long as people and
their souls exist,
there will be disputes.
And those disputes
will lead to fights.
And those fights go
on for all eternity.
No matter how much you
try to run from them.
-That's not true.
You're full of it!
-You fool!
You refuse to see
the truth before you!
-Trust me, Ichigo.
Those who have power
will eventually
be drawn into battle.
That's how it happened
for most of the Bounts.
I was a witness.
And naive idealists like
yourself were among the first
to lose their lives!
[groaning]
-Damn it.
Damn.
-You still going to fight
with this weak sword?
What's the matter with you, kid?
Don't you even have
a little pride?
Disappointing.
Za--
-Zangetsu.
-That isn't Zangetsu.
I keep saying that
I am Zangetsu.
[groaning]
-I must admit it.
It never ceases to amaze me
how brainless you can be.
You've lost your weapon.
Why are you just standing there?
Ichigo, what's the difference
between a king and his horse?
-What the hell are you saying?
-I'm not talking
about obvious stuff.
Like one's an animal
and one's a person.
Or one has two legs
and one has four.
Form, ability and power!
That's what's puzzling.
If their form, ability and power
are exactly the same, why is it
that one becomes the king
and leads them into battle,
while the other becomes the
horse and carries the king!
So what's the
characteristic that
distinguishes these two beings?
There's only one
answer-- instinct!
In order for identical beings
to get stronger and gain power,
they need to develop
a killer instinct.
And that instinct is
mostly forged in battle.
They must develop an insatiable
hunger to engage in battle.
They must live to mercilessly
crush, shred and slice
their enemies.
This thirst for power is
not an unnatural desire.
In fact, it forms the
very essence of our being.
Deep within our body
lies the honed instinct
to dominate and
slaughter our enemies!
My friend, you don't have that.
You use your brain to
try and win a fight!
You attempt to defeat your
enemies with reason and logic.
You don't tap into those
pure, base instincts that
exist within your core
waiting to be released!
And the simple matter
is it does it work.
You're weak, Ichigo!
-I won't put up with that.
Am I clear?
I don't know about
Zangetsu, but I
refuse to play horse to a
king who's weaker than me.
Someone whose uncertainty
and hesitation
will end up getting
us both cut to pieces!
If you aren't willing
to assert your strength
and retain the crown,
then I'll destroy you.
Which means I'll be king.
[labored breath]
-Instinct.
The desire to seek battle.
Sword-- I won't let
you Have my sword.
[grunt]
[gasp]
[groaning]
[instinct]
[theme song]
ORIHIME: Ichigo has a
pretty happy expression
on his face for someone in the
middle of an internal battle.
He must be having a great dream.
RUKIA: Men only
have erotic dreams.
ORIHIME: What?
That perverted dumbass!
After all we've done for him!
Ichigo: Perverted--
Perverted dumbass?