[theme music]
-Outrageous.
Don't you see the damage
that you kids have done?
This ridiculous
show was broadcast
on national
television yesterday.
Just look.
With two of our students there
for all the world to see.
Rukia and Ichigo, this
is a very serious.
Never in the history
of this school
has any student ever
dishonored this institution
by committing such an act
of civil disobedience.
-Mr. Kagine?
-Huh?
-Sir, I can
understand why you're
angry with Ichigo
and Rukia for acting
like a bunch of stupid idiots,
but why are Orihime and I here
when we didn't have
anything to do with this?
-You were there with them the
whole time this was going on.
-That was a coincidence.
We were just walking
by and suddenly got
dragged into the whole mess.
-Great, thanks a lot.
I'll remember this the
next time you need someone
to bail you out.
-[mocking sounds]
-Anyway, this has
been fun, Mr. Kagine,
but we're going back to
class if you don't mind.
Come on, Orihime.
-Goodbye, Mr. Kagine.
-Yeah, me too.
I've got some homework.
-Not so fast, Mr. Asano.
You were there with them, yet
you did nothing to stop them,
so you're just as
guilty as Ichigo.
-I still don't get
what the big deal is.
It was just a stupid TV show.
-You don't get much,
do you, mister?
That's the trouble
with you kids today,
no awareness of the
consequences of your actions.
It's depressing.
-I'm so sorry.
I really did try to stop
Ichigo, but he wouldn't listen.
All he ever thinks
about is himself,
and he was so obsessed
with getting on television.
-[sobs]
-The whole thing's all my fault.
Go ahead and punish me.
-Please don't cry, Rukia.
I understand.
I'm sure you did
everything you could have.
-Oh, thank you, Mr. Kagine.
So you'll punish
Ichigo and let me go?
-Huh?
You puns come back
here right now.
You're not gonna
get off that easy.
I know where you all live.
Oh, great, now Rukia
Kuchiki's gotten away too.
What should we do?
-Just do me a favor.
When you do find Ichigo, could
you get his autograph for me?
-Has everyone around
here lost their minds?
-Wait to go, Rukia.
Your awesome performance
got us off scott-free
with no detention.
-Oh, you guys.
It was nothing, really.
-What are you talking about?
She was trying to
sell me up the river.
-You gotta admit that her phony
crying covered your getaway.
You ought to be thanking her.
-Actually, I kind of enjoyed
putting on the big act
and fooling Mr. Kagine,
so no thanks necessary.
But you have to
know I would never
sell out a good
friend like Ichigo.
-[grunts]
[beeping]
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN):
Oh, Ichigo, can I
talk to you for a
second in private?
-Huh?
-Would you guys excuse
us for just a minute.
-Well, that's weird.
-Huh.
-I never noticed before, but--
-Hmm?
-Those two seem to like
each other, don't they?
-No, you're imagining things.
Ichigo might like
Rukia, but there's
no way she'd be
interested in him.
-Well, something's suspicious.
-Hmm.
[whimpering]
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
What's going on?
There's no stinking Hollow here.
Don't tell me I got all
dressed up for nothing.
I think your pager
needs new batteries.
-That's really weird.
It was a strong signal, but
now there's no trace of it.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
Hey you, spirit guy.
You didn't by any chance cut
the head off a Hollow recently,
did you?
-I'm not sure what
you mean by a Hollow,
but I sure did see
something scary.
This thing was so big.
It looked like a
huge, slimy black bug.
When I saw it, I
almost peed my pants.
-I don't care about
your problems.
I want to know what
happened to it.
-Let me talk to him.
Since can describe
the Hollow so clearly,
no doubt then you must have
also seen who killed it and how.
-Well, not really, because I had
my eyes closed the whole time.
I was so scared.
-Well. it's konso
time, I suppose.
-Huh?
What's a konso?
What are you gonna do?
No, no, get that
sword away from me.
No!
[gasps]
-Did you find your name?
-Third in the class?
Pretty smart for
a girl, Orihime.
-[giggles]
-This sucks.
Orihime has both
brains and boobs.
It's just not fair.
-If it makes you feel better,
she's a terrible cook.
-Orihime, you're my best friend.
I'm so proud of you.
-Whoa.
Aw, let the girls get
their high scores.
At least none of our
gang embarrassed us
by making it into the
top 50, right, Mizuiro?
-Take another look.
-Huh?
What?
Ichigo is ranked number 23?
You cheater.
There's no way you could have
possibly scored that high.
-Shut up, Keigo.
I score high on tests
because I study for them.
You should try it sometime.
-Aha, so that's what you were
doing all those nights when
I was asking you
to come hang out.
You always said
you were too busy,
but the truth is you were
studying like a total nerd.
Oh, no.
I'm friends with a nerd.
Maybe you need some thick
nerd glasses like these, pal.
-No thanks.
-It is a bit of a surprise
to learn you really study.
-My hair gets me enough abuse.
I'm not gonna be an
academic loser on top of it.
-Good point.
Sorry I ragged on you.
So how about-- if I gave
you this complimentary nerd
headband instead.
-I told you, no.
-All right then,
have it your way.
But see if I ever ask you
to hang out with me again.
[MAKES MOCKING
SOUND] Well, at least
you wouldn't go and do something
embarrassing like score
in the top 50,
right, Chad, old pal?
-[grunts]
[screaming]
-I'm horrified.
I had no idea I was hanging
out with such a bunch
of complete geeks and brainiacs.
I'm through with all of you.
-Oh, well.
They'll be back.
-I guess it's lucky
for him one of us
isn't in the number one
spot, like Ametasu Ishida.
I've never even heard of him.
-That's Uryu, Uryu Ishida.
-You mean you know him?
-Yeah, of course.
He's in our class.
-You'll find that Ichigo has
an uncanny knack for forgetting
people's faces and the
names that go with them.
Come on.
-Oh.
-Hmm, that's weird.
[phone ringing]
-How come he's not answering?
Urahara, why don't
you ever pick up
when I call you in
emergencies like this?
You call yourself a businessman?
Then why do you show up
when you're not wanted,
and then when I really
need you, you won't answer?
[sighs] I need Urahara
to come and take
a look at this Soul Pager.
I mean how am I supposed to know
if this stupid thing is working
right or not?
[beeping]
-Let's go to that
new karaoke bar.
There's this hot hostess there.
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN): Ichigo?
-Huh?
-Come here.
I need you.
-That Rukia is one
aggressive chick.
-Maybe they really
are seeing each other.
-We have a Hollow alert.
-A Hollow?
Well, there better
actually be one this time.
-Just shut up and run.
-[grunts]
Sorry.
-Damn it.
Again, you drag me
all the way out here,
and there's no Hollow.
-Shut up.
Stop whining and get
back into your body.
-Fine, but would
you do something
about that stupid Soul Pager?
-These false alarms
aren't my fault.
When it goes off, I have to
assume a Hollow has appeared,
so I report it.
What else can I do?
-Well, get it fixed because
it's obviously busted.
-They don't fix them at
television repair shops.
-Huh?
-How unprofessional.
Good evening, Ichigo, Rukia.
-Who the hell are you?
And how do you know our
names you don't mind--
-I don't mind.
I also know you can
see spirits, Ichigo.
-How do you know that?
-Another Hollow
has just appeared.
-No way.
[beeping]
-There's a new one
here all right.
How did he know?
-All right.
Which way?
-It's over there.
Can you not sense
such a simple thing?
And you call yourself
a Soul Reaper.
[chimes]
-The signal just vanished.
-So tell me, who
or what are you?
-Uryu Ishida.
I'm a Quincy.
Soul Reapers are my enemies.
-Just what do you mean?
-Is that too
complicated for you?
I'll tell you again
then, slower this time.
Ichigo Kurosaki,
you are my enemy.
[bells ringing]
-Damn, what's the
story with that guy?
-And you call yourself
a Soul Reaper?
Can you not sense
such a simple thing?
-Who does he think he is
insulting me like that?
I'll mess him up the
next time I see him.
Besides, who uses a
bow-and-arrow anymore.
What's his name?
Uh, Mac?
No, I think it
was Iki-something.
Ikibo?
Ikimo?
Metasu?
No.
Ichi-- Ichiarmadillo!
No, that's not it either.
Dammit.
-Do you mean Uryu Ishida?
-Orihime.
Uh, yeah.
-It's a pretty cool name, huh?
-Uh, yeah, I was just
saying it because it's
such a cool-sounding name.
-I agree.
In fact, I say his name to
myself all the time when
I'm sitting with him in
the home handicrafts club.
-Home handy what?
-You see?
There he is, right there.
-That's him all
right, but I can't
believe he's really in
the home handicrafts club.
Look at him.
He's reading, not doing macrame.
-Yeah?
You wait.
It looks like Michiru's
got a job for him.
-Like he's gonna sew it for her?
-Just wait and watch.
-Hey, it's almost
as good as new.
Thanks so much, Uryu.
-It's all right.
Don't mention it.
In fact, don't talk
to me anymore at all.
-Uh, I'll see you later then.
-Why would he do
something so nice
and then say
something so unkind?
-Because he's
insane, that's why.
-Ichigo, wait a sec, Do you and
Uryu have some kind of problem?
-Well, you could say that, but
it's nothing I can't handle.
-That's good.
[giggles]
[sighs]
-Do you intend to follow me all
the way home, Ichigo Kurosaki?
-Guess I'm not as sneaky
as I thought I was.
So when did you first notice me?
-From the time you and Orihime
saw me in the classroom.
You've been ducking in and
out of shadows behind me
ever since.
-That long, huh?
Now that's impressive.
-The careless way you let
your spirit energy leak out,
even a monkey would
have noticed it.
Amateur stuff
-What did you say?
-You heard me.
It's obvious that you lack
even the most basic ability
to detect those around you
with high spirit energy.
How else can you
explain the fact
that you weren't even aware
of my existence until today?
-Yeah, sorry about that.
It's just that I've always been
really bad at remembering names
and faces.
-That's not what I mean.
There's a difference
between you and me.
When you first started
at this school,
I sensed your high
spirit energy.
If you were any good, you
would have sensed mine.
I even know the day in mid-May
when you became a Soul Reaper.
And I know Rukia
Kuchiki's true identity.
-Spirit ribbons.
-For a change, you're right.
Spirit ribbons are the
physical manifestation
of spirit energy
in the atmosphere.
And--
-What is that?
-This is your spirit ribbon.
You didn't know that?
Soul Reapers' spirit ribbons
are a different color
than normal ones.
Why don't we play a little
game, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Let's have a duel to
determine which one of us
is stronger, the Quincy
or the Soul Reaper.
I'll show you just
how unnecessary Soul
Reapers are in this world.
JINTA (OFFSCREEN): All
right, practice duel.
Rock, paper, scissors.
Rock wins!
Ha ha.
This one's for real.
Know Rock, paper, scissors.
-It looks like you lose.
-Argh.
-I get to choose a
chore for you, Jinta,
and I choose sweeping up.
-Oh, no, not so fast.
You haven't won yet, Ururu.
I said it's not over till
you win two out of three.
-Hey, you never
said that before.
No fair.
No, Jinta stop it.
-Aw, quite your
complaining, Ururu,.
The rules are whatever
I say they are.
MALE SPEAKER
(OFFSCREEN): Maybe you'd
like to try that technique
on my head, Jinta.
-Ow, put me down.
I was just trying to teach
her rock, paper, scissors.
-Huh?
-Oh, hello there, Miss Kuchiki.
I didn't see you come in.
Is there something
wrong with your foot.
-Never mind.
Urahara here?
-If it isn't my
favorite customer.
What can I do for you?
-Don't play innocent
with me, Urahara.
I had to come in
person because I've
been calling for days
with a major problem,
and you don't respond.
-Oh, sorry about that.
It's just we've been
really busy lately,
but I was gonna call you today.
-Where's your friend?
You know, that weird,
orange, spiky-haired dude.
I don't see him.
I guess he must have
broke up with you.
Can't really say
I blame the guy.
-Cut her some slack, Jinta.
-It's serious.
I need information.
-About what?
-So when is this duel between
us supposed to take place?
-Right now.
-That idea is ridiculous.
-Why do you say that?
-Because it would
be a waste of time,
and I've got nothing
to prove to you.
I've never heard
of Quincys before,
and I don't know what you
have again Soul Reapers,
but it's got nothing
to do with me.
-What a surprise.
You're afraid to fight.
-Forget trying to
goad me into it.
Besides, I'd mop
the floor with you.
-Oh, now I get it.
You don't have permission.
I forgot.
Your Soul Reapers
powers came from Rukia.
You're actually just a
substitute Soul Reaper.
That probably means
that on your own,
you can't so much
as lift a finger.
You have to have her
permission to duel, don't you?
-That does it.
URAHARA (OFFSCREEN): A Quincy.
I haven't heard that
word in a long time.
-It does have kind of an
ancient ring to it, doesn't it?
If I'm not mistaken,
it's been 200 years
since I've heard anyone
speak of Quincys.
-Well, who are they?
-Who were they, you mean.
The last of the Quincys
became extinct centuries ago,
but they were once a clan that
specialized in killing Hollows.
And at one time,
there are many of them
scattered throughout the world.
-So what happened?
-Well, I suppose I should
begin at the beginning.
The clan started out
as a group of humans
who had powers like Ichigo to
sense the presence of Hollows
in the world and began to
train to fight against them.
The whole mission of the
Quincys was to defeat Hollows,
just as it is for Soul
Reapers like yourself,
but there was a deep
division between the two.
It was a question of whether
to cleanse Hollows or just kill
them.
Soul Reapers, as you know,
seek to purify Hollows
with their zanpakuto
and thereby allow
them to pass over
into the Soul society.
But the Quincys
believed the Hollows
deserved only destruction and
sought to annihilate them.
[screaming]
URAHARA (OFFSCREEN):
When you think about it,
it was a natural reaction.
Hollows devour human Souls.
They kill and maim our
friends and family.
Why should they deserve the
peace of a Soul society?
The Quincys couldn't
understand showing such mercy,
and eventually began to hate
the Soul Reapers for it.
They were sure the only
answer was to kill Hollows.
They believed in
doing so that they
were avenging their
fallen comrades.
But then, it was
this same belief
that eventually led
to their destruction.
-All right, if a
duel's what you want,
then a duel's what you'll get.
-It's about time, Ichigo.
-Huh?
-Why'd you leave me in
that stupid bag all day?
You trying to kill me?
I don't care what Rukia says,
don't you ever do that to me
again.
-Cough it up.
-Wait a sec.
Forget what I said
about the bag.
You can put me back there--
-Aha.
Ko, you better get back.
I'm about to give Mr.
Handicrafts some stitches
to sew.
-Uh, I'll be over here.
-So, how does you
little duel work?
Tell me the rules,
and let's get to it.
[music playing]
Hi its Rukia Kuchiki the
prettiest girl in the Bleach
cast
And I'd like to read you one of
my many fan letters.
Momako Inakino asks, "Rukia,
what's the secret to your
beauty?"
This is not a gossip column.
You're just jealous because you
didn't get any fan mail yet.
What!
Ha Ha Ha