[theme music]
SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Good morning, Ichigo!
Ya!
Ha!
Aw!
-You nuts?
What kind of sick, twisted
freak attacks his own son
while he's just
lying there sleeping?
-You are getting good!
It looks like
there's nothing left
for me to teach you, my son.
-[grunt] Huh?
Wait a minute!
What about Kagine and Yuzu's
injuries from last night?
-Huh?
Injuries?
What are you talking about?
-What?
-It's a miracle!
A truck plows right into
our house and none of us
even get so much as
a single scratch!
-What's more miraculous is
the fact that none of us
even woke up when it happened.
-I don't get it.
Their wounds are
completely gone.
They think that a
truck did all this?
Could this have been the
work of that soul reaper?
-Ichigo!
You better hurry up
and eat breakfast,
or you're going to be late!
-Yeah.
I wonder if she went
back to that place
she was talking about.
The Soul Society.
-Orihime!
Did you bring lunch today?
Mm-hm!
Leftover Taiyaki-style
Ramen with Wasabi and honey.
Would you like some, Tatsuki?
-That's OK.
-But it's really good!
Ah!
-Oh, it's you.
Hey, Orihime.
-Oh no, I'm sorry!
-Ichigo!
You knock her down, and
that's all you can say?
What the heck's the
matter with you?
-Sorry about that.
You going to be all right?
-Uh-huh.
-Here.
-Huh?
Ah!
Oh no!
That's all right, really!
I-- I-- have v--
v-- v-- volleyball!
That's right!
Volleyball!
-Orihime!
-What's the matter with her?
-What could it be?
Maybe it was your ugly mug!
By the way, why are you so late?
I mean, it's time
for much already.
-Yeah, don't worry about it.
I'll tell you later.
SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Hey, Ichigo!
I heard a truck crashed into
your house last night, dude!
-Pretty much.
-So, did you clean
it all up yet?
-What are you, kidding?
It's going to take forever.
-Need any help?
-Uh?
Huh?
That's OK.
-Yeah, Chad.
I mean, you could end up
bringing the whole house down,
you know?
-Hey, what have we got next?
SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Language lab.
-Hello.
You're Ichigo, aren't you?
-Uh?
Wha?
-I'll be sitting next
to you from now on.
My name is Rukia.
-[scream] It's-- it's you!
-Hey, Ichigo!
What's wrong with you?
-You two know each-other?
-Course not!
We've never met before!
Isn't that right, Ichigo?
-[sigh]
-Rukia's a brand new
transfer student.
-Nice to meet you!
-It's a pleasure!
-Uh?
[shock] All right, you
freaky little nut job.
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
-How scary, you big brute.
Jeepers, you're not going
to hurt me, are you?
-First of all, you can knock it
off with that goody two shoes
act, OK?
-Well, I think it's
pretty good, considering
I learned it overnight.
-All right, forget it.
So tell me just what you're
doing here now, anyway.
Weren't you supposed
to be heading back to
your Soul Society
or whatever it was?
-I can't.
Only soul reapers can go
back to the Soul Society.
I haven't the power
to return anymore.
-What you mean?
-Last night, I lost almost all
of my powers as a soul reaper.
I'm afraid they were all
absorbed into you, Ichigo.
-Huh?
I wouldn't know
anything about that.
Thanks to you, for
the time being,
I'm stuck in this
ridiculous gigai form.
-What do you mean by gigai?
-It's a temporary
body that serves
as a vessel in an emergency.
If the soul reaper is
drastically weakened,
they reside inside of a gigai
until their powers come back.
-Oh, now I get it.
So that's why the others were
able to see you before, right?
-Precisely.
And so, until all of
my powers come back,
it's up to you,
Ichigo, to perform
the duties of a soul reaper.
-Huh?
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN):
It's only natural.
You now possess the
strength of a soul reaper.
You do not have the right
to refuse your calling.
-No way!
-What?
-My monster fighting
days are over.
That was a one-time deal.
-Don't be ridiculous Ichigo.
You did just fine yesterday.
-That was only because
my family was in danger.
But it's not like I'm
ready to go and fight
for complete
strangers or anything.
Sorry to disappoint you.
-I see.
Guess there's no
other choice, then.
Hey.
-Huh?
Huh?
-[grunt]
-Ah, crap!
What happened to my body?
What in the world
did you do to me?
-Follow me.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
Hey, you going
to tell me where
we're going, here?
-We're getting close.
-Close to what?
-Our latest orders
from the soul society.
It looks like a spirit of a boy
that dwells here in this park
is likely to come
under attack soon.
-[boy screaming]
-[grunt]
-[boy screaming] Help me!
-Wait!
Hold on!
-What is it?
-Just where are you going?
-That boy's a complete
stranger, isn't he?
-So what?
I can't just stand by
and let this happen.
You expect me to watch him die?
-Don't be such a fool.
-In the eyes of a soul reaper,
all the spirits of this world
are equal.
Getting involved simply
because spirits are nearby
or they need help
isn't how it works.
-Huh?
RUKIO (OFFSCREEN): Leave him be.
If you intend to
help this child,
then commit yourself
to saving every spirit.
You must be willing
to go to any length,
even to sacrifice your life.
[gasp]
-Have you made your
decision, Ichigo?
-Like hell, I have.
-Huh?
-I haven't decided to do squat.
I saved this kid
because I wanted to.
You hear me?
What about you?
-Me?
-I seem to remember you
putting your life on the line
to save me last night.
Tell me.
Were you really
thinking about your duty
when you rushed to help me?
Of course not.
That's the last thing on your
mind when you save someone.
-Huh?
-At the very least, I
choose to be different!
You OK?
Hey, kid.
If you don't want to
go through that again,
you better hurry up
and pass on already.
[gasp]
-You did that quite beautifully.
-I'm gone.
[sigh]
[gasp]
[scream]
-What are you doing?
Stop!
[scream]
[slow footsteps]
[growl]
[roar]
-What's happening?
Where am I?
I don't understand.
What are you going to
do to me? [moaning]
SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN): You
are a lost little spirit.
Now, let's devour this soul.
[crying]
-Get him!
[panting]
[maniacal laughter]
[muffled cry]
[roar]
-Hear my voice, oh Lord. Help
your humble child understand
why she was born.
And if your divine
will wishes it,
summon her back to your side.
I await your-- G
-Jeeze, would you
shut up already?
-What is your problem?
I am studying
contemporary language.
-You're off by a
couple centuries.
So tell me.
How long do you plan
on following me around?
-Until you answer your
calling as a soul reaper.
-Yeah, right.
Whatever.
-Hey!
Orihime!
-Uh, Ichigo!
-Did you just get
hit by that car?
-Oh!
Maybe.
-What you mean, maybe?
Are you going to be OK?
-Mm-hm!
It was just a little
bump on my head.
Don't worry!
I'm fine.
I swear!
-You sure you're OK?
Where did that car
go that hit you?
-Hm?
It drove away.
-Orihime!
-Oh, sorry.
[grunt]
-Well, all right.
I guess as long as
you're OK, then.
-Rukia?
-That's right, and
just who are you?
-Hello!
She's in the same class as you!
Her name is Orihime!
Get your head out of your butt!
-Huh?
Oh, of course!
Orihime!
How are you?
-Oh, I'm great, thank you!
-Well now, it appears
that you've been shopping.
-Huh?
Oh, that's right!
Dinner!
My leeks, bananas, butter, and
bean germ seem to have made it,
too!
-Ugh.
I don't want to know what
she's going to make with that.
[gasp]
-How did you get that
bruise on your leg?
-What bruise?
Oh, I guess that happened just
now when that car ran into me.
-Jeeze!
Does it hurt?
-A little bit!
But I'm OK.
-You sure?
-Um, what's the matter, Rukio?
-Huh?
-Is Anything wrong?
-Right, well, you take care!
-Thanks!
-So you want me
to walk you home?
-Oh!
Uh, I'm OK, really.
See ya!
-Man, she needs to
be more careful.
-Hm.
-So then, that girl.
-Huh?
Oh, do you mean Orihime?
-Are you close to her?
-Naw, I'm not really.
I barely know her, and we
don't really talk much.
But she's friends with a buddy
of mine from the neighborhood,
so I see her around.
Although--
-Yes?
-Around three years back or
so, her older brother Sora
was in this terrible accent
and died at our clinic.
-What?
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
He was in a car wreck.
He was the only family she had.
-Big brother!
Big brother!
You can't die!
Please!
Don't leave me all alone!
-I'd never realized that she was
the girl I saw crying that day.
I only found that
out just recently.
-How in tune to the
spirit realm were you?
-Huh?
Not as much as I am now.
I mean, it's really
only recently
I've been able to fully
see and communicate
with the spirit realm.
-Just as I thought.
-Why?
What's up?
What are you thinking?
-Nothing.
See you later.
-Huh?
Hey!
Where are you going?
-Back home.
-Where's that?
-You really want to know?
-I guess not.
-Then don't ask me.
-Huh?
Yeah, right.
[doorbell]
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): Coming!
Oh, hi, Tatsuke!
-My mom thought that I should
bring this over for you.
It's stewed beef and potatoes.
-Wow!
Great!
Home-made beef and potatoes!
Oh boy!
This is delicious!
-I swear, if I bring
meals over for you to eat,
you always end up cooking
the weirdest stuff.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): I
never thought about it.
You really think so?
TATSUKE (OFFSCREEN): Um, Yeah.
I mean, what is this stuff?
-Hey, Ichigo?
You haven't seen my
pajamas, have you?
-Yuzu, come on!
Knock before you come in here!
-Well, I'm sorry I asked.
You've been so mean since
you started high school!
-Have not, and I don't know
where your pajamas are.
-That is just so odd.
One of my dresses
has gone missing too.
-Why do you feel the need to
ask me about every little thing?
Do I look like I care?
-OK, goodnight.
[phone ringing]
-Hm.
An order?
-What the?
Huh?
[beep]
[gasp]
-Hey, Ichigo!
-What the heck?
What are you doing in there?
Are those my sister's
PJs you've got on?
-I'll explain later.
We got orders.
-Orders?
-We're not alone.
-Wait, what are you saying?
-Get down!
[grunt]
-Why are you standing there?
Do something!
You have to aim for its head!
-Huh?
[scream]
[grunt]
-Ichigo!
-Ugh.
[scream]
-You need to focus!
Don't just swing
your sword around!
-Shut up!
Who cares, as long as I kill it?
[growl]
[shout]
You're mine!
Ya!
-Too shallow.
[gasp]
[struggle]
[roar]
-What?
-It's getting away.
Let's go.
Ichigo, what's the matter?
-Something's not right.
-What?
-I got a look at
that thing's face.
And it was Orihime's
dead brother!
-Are you certain?
[groan]
[roar]
-Here's a word of advice.
-Uh?
-When attacking hollows,
come from behind
and cleave their
heads with one blow.
Don't forget.
It's basic theory
for any soul reaper.
-Why?
What do you mean?
-It will keep your
injuries to a minimum.
Also, with any luck,
it will keep you
from learning the
hollow's identity.
-Wait a minute.
What do you mean, the identity?
-You just saw for yourself.
-Hm.
-Do you understand?
The hollows were once
souls of human beings
no different from anyone else.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): You--
you've never told me that!
So that thing I saw was
just a monster, wasn't it?
it was some beast
from the underworld
that needed to be wiped out.
-That is correct.
He is just a monster now.
And he must be destroyed.
-But it was human once.
-It can't be helped.
Souls that hold onto feelings
of resentment or regret
will sometimes resist konso and
linger on alone in this world.
Should that happen, they either
become hollows on their own,
or they're devoured
by other hollows
and become one of the fold.
-But that's--
-What?
They were together?
-Mm-hm.
But they were just walking
home together, Tatsuke.
What's the matter?
-Oh man.
I never knew Ichigo was
such a smooth operator.
I mean, honestly.
He didn't even walk you
home when you were hurt!
-Well, no.
I mean, he did ask me if I
wanted him to walk me home.
But I-- I'm warning, you!
You better watch out, champ.
Because I'm winning this match!
-Yeah, hey, wake up!
You're daydreaming again!
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): I'll
give you a right, and another!
Bam!
Ah!
Look out!
He's got a gun!
[bang]
-Huh?
Hey, what was that?
[bang]
[roar]
THEME SONG: Nobody
knows who I really am.
I never felt this empty before.
And if I ever need
someone I'd come along
Who's going to comfort
me and keep me strong?
[foreign language]
DON JANONJI (NARRATING):
Greetings, viewers!
It is I, the century's premiere
spiritualist and messenger
from hell, Don Kanonji!
Remember, the spirits
are always with you!
Wa ha ha ha!
ICHIGO (NARRATING): It's
not even your cue yet!
Ah, we're out of time again!