[music playing]
[theme music]
-Soul Reapers.
The spiritual guardians to
the world of the living.
Their job is to maintain the
balance between the myriad
of good and evil souls
that fill this world.
Ichigo and Captain
Hitsugaya's troops
barely managed to
defeat the Arrancars
that Aizen had created.
But both sides had
suffered major damages.
Realizing that they could not
defeat the stronger Arrancars,
the Soul Reapers decided
to prepare themselves
for their next encounter
with the enemy.
Feeling useless,
Uryu and Chad also
began training to
become stronger,
so that they could fight
alongside their friends again.
Meanwhile, Ichigo,
sensing that he could not
suppress his inner
Hollow any longer,
decided to call
upon the Visoreds
for some greatly needed advice.
-Good job finding
this place, Ichigo.
The fact that
you're here tells me
that you finally decided
to come over to our side.
Am I right?
-Huh.
I'm here to use you, Shinji.
I came here with
one purpose in mind,
and I'm not leaving
until I get it.
I want to teach me how to
control the Hollow inside me.
Guess I'll beat it out of you.
[crashing noises]
-Hachi, are you sure
your barrier will hold?
-Actually, I'm not sure at all.
-Hm.
-Stop holding back.
You still don't get it, do you?
What are you afraid of, Ichigo?
-I'm not afraid of you.
-I'm going to give
you a little tip.
Use your Bankai.
-Shut up.
-Just as I thought.
You're scared that
every time you're
forced to use your
Bankai against someone
powerful like me, you're going
to lose control of your soul
to that frightening
inner Hollow of yours.
-I said shut up!
-Dumb ass.
Just looking at your
face pisses me off.
You're so terrified
it's pathetic.
That's fine with me.
Fight scared if you want to.
You don't have to use
your Bankai or Hollowfy.
It'll save me some
effort while killing you.
Your choice.
-Think.
How is she able to Hollowfy
without losing her sanity?
How can she just
take her mask off
and put it back on like that?
I have to pay more attention.
Watch her every move.
Find out how she does it.
That's why I came here.
I won't use my Bankai.
I'm not going to Hollowfy.
I refuse to let him
control my soul.
Never again!
[fighting noises]
[screaming]
[maniacal laughter]
-OK, that's enough.
Well, Hiyori?
Are you satisfied?
You understand now,
don't you, Ichigo?
Your Hollow can't be
suppressed just by simply
focusing your mind
on stopping it.
And it can't be stopped
with your body, either.
You pass.
We'll teach you control.
You'll learn how to deal with
that Hollow inside of you.
[crying]
-Ichigo didn't come
home last night!
-Calm down.
Just relax.
I'm sure he's fine.
He'll come wondering back
after a day or two like nothing
happened.
-How can you be so calm
at a time like this?
He could have been
kidnapped, or in an accident.
Or even worse, murder!
-What's wrong with my baby girl?
Why is my little Yuzu crying?
I can't stand seeing you sad.
Hey, look at me!
This'll get her to stop crying,
it's a gag that never fails.
This used to have them
rolling in the aisles
back in the good old days.
Look at my funny beard!
-You always have a funny beard.
[laughter]
[footsteps]
-Rukia.
It's you.
Did you find my brother?
-Sorry, I didn't find him.
-I see.
[crying]
[music playing]
I can't find any trace of
his spiritual pressure.
Where did you go, Ichigo?
Where are you?
-Ichigo.
-How could you make this
poor kid cry, Ichigo?
What a worthless big brother
you turned out to be.
[heavy breathing]
-Where's Mashiro with lunch?
Hiyori, lunch is late
again, and I'm starving.
Make something to eat.
-Yeah, dream on.
You'll starve to death waiting
for me to cook for you.
And even if I did cook a meal,
I wouldn't let you have any.
Dumb ass.
-Hey, Love.
Have you heard that new song
from the Prince of Darkness
that just came out?
It totally rocks.
-No, but have you read
the latest issue of
Shonen Jump magazine?
-How could I?
You never let anyone
read it but you.
-Hysterical!
-Lisa, I want you to keep a
sharp eye on that Soul Reaper
and look after him.
-Don't worry, I won't
let him out of my sight.
-Yeah, but you're
not watching him.
You're just sitting there,
looking at swimsuit catalogs.
-Can it.
I can see the Soul Reaper fine.
-That's not the point.
You're on duty
today, aren't you?
You're supposed to
be training him.
-Fine, have it your way.
One, two.
-It sure is late.
-Stop talking about it.
You're already making us more
hungry than we already are.
-One, two.
One, two.
One--
-I can't take it anymore!
-What's the idea?
You try something like
that again, dumb ass,
and you're dead!
-I was, I was just going
to say that to him.
-I should be saying that to you!
You bragged about how you were
going to teach me control,
and how to suppress the
Hollow inside me forever.
So why the hell are you idiots
making me run all day long
on this cheap, homemade, poor
excuse for a cross country ski
machine?
Wait, scratch that.
You're not the idiots.
I'm the idiot for
listening to you.
-You are an idiot if you
think it's a cross-country ski
machine!
-Lunch is here!
-Ah, sounds good.
I'm starved.
---you whine about our
training methods, dumbass!
-Quit call me dumb
ass, snaggletooth!
And how the hell can you
consider this training?
-I'll call you dumb ass
any time I want, dumbass.
-Should I interrupt them
to tell them lunch is here?
It might get cold.
-Ah, don't bother.
I'll eat theirs.
-They seem to be awfullly angry.
Why are they fighting?
-Well, he doesn't seem to
like the Hiyori super-trainer?
-What?
He was still on it?
-If you ask me, I don't
think Hiyori explained
the theory of the
training treadmill
very well, so I can see why
the Soul Reaper might be upset.
-I have to agree.
When giving orders,
she always leaves
out one or two key details.
-Hm.
-Quit complaining, and keep
running until you drop!
-Why you!
-Calm down, Ichigo.
The stupid Hiyori
treadmill trainer--
-It's super!
---is foundation for
your future training.
-Foundation?
-We determine the level of
your next training program
based on how long you
can run on the treadmill.
-What exactly do you
mean, when you say level?
-Just listen to Hiyori, OK?
Quit complaining,
and get back on
her senseless treadmill trainer.
-For the last time, it's the
Hiyori Super Trainer, dumb ass.
-After about three days, you'll
collapse from exhaustion.
First we break you down,
and then we build you up,
by teaching you how to control
your Hollow transformation.
-What?
That's a joke.
Well you can forget
about three days.
I can run on that
thing for almost a week
without getting tired.
I get it, OK?
That stupid machine is
designed to drain me
of all my spirit energy.
Well big deal!
You want to measure my
maximum spirit energy output
by seeing how many days I
can run before I collapse.
You idiots.
With the spirit energy
I have right now,
I can go at least five days
straight on that thing!
There's no point in
testing me like this.
Just teach me how to control
my Hollowfication, already!
I don't have time to waste
on this crap, damn it!
I cannot afford to lose any more
time playing around with you
Visords!
-Shut your mouth!
You don't have time?
Oh, that's really
something, coming
from a guy who doesn't
even know how long it
takes for the Hogyoku to awaken.
-Wait a minute.
What did you just say?
-I said, stop blabbing,
when you don't really
know anything about
the Hogyoku or anything
at all about Hollowfication.
-What is this?
How do you know about?
How is it possible you
know about the Hogyoku?
-I know all about it.
The Hogyoku, the Arrancars,
even Sosuke Aizen.
I've known all about them
for many, many years.
Don't worry, I'll give you
all the details another day.
I thought it would
be a good idea
to take some time
at the beginning,
so you can get used to us.
But, now that I
think about it, you
can already turn
into a Soul Reaper.
You can use your Shikai.
And you have a Bankai.
-You know about all that, too?
-But I can see it would be
better if we just jumped right
into teaching you how
to control your Hollow.
Just like you
originally asked us to.
Are you ready, Ichigo?
I hope you don't regret this.
Hachi, give us a two-layered
fault force field.
-All right, then.
-Can you hear me, Ichigo?
In a moment, you're going to
fully transform into a Hollow.
Don't let it consume you.
Consume it, instead.
If it eats you, it's all over.
Hey Hachi.
Throw up a force
field here, too.
-Whaaat?
-Don't whaaat?
Me.
You're standing there
with your mouth open,
looking like you're
trying to catch flies.
Just do it, OK?
And seal off Ichigo's
body as well.
-As you wish.
Wall of iron sand.
Tower of the Shaven Priests.
Glow incandescent iron,
tranquil and soundless.
Bakudo #75.
Gochutekkan!
[music playing]
[wind]
-Hey!
Long time, no see, King.
What's wrong?
By the expression on
your face you look glum.
[music playing]
-Where the hell is Zangetsu?
Answer me.
I want to know now, dammit!
-I'm confused.
When you talk about
Zangetsu, do you
mean the one you're
holding, in your hand?
Or is it this one, in mine?
Beautiful, isn't it?
-A white Zangetsu?
-You asked me a question.
Where's Zangetsu?
Well here's your answer.
I am Zangetsu!
[music playing]
[explosion]
[rumbling]
-Here it comes.
-You think maybe it
would be a good idea
if we hid his Zanpakuto?
-Wouldn't make any difference.
If he couldn't find it, it would
just make him more frantic.
[music playing]
-Hachigen.
Open it up, please.
I'm the one on duty today,
so I'll be going first.
-All right, Lisa.
-Let's try not to
kill him, Lisa.
-Yeah, if he doesn't
kill me, first.
[music playing]
My name is Lisa Yadomaru.
Nice to meet you.
-Say it!
Why won't you tell me
what happened to Zangetsu?
-You're persistent,
making me repeat myself.
I told you, I'm Zangetsu!
[explosion]
-Ichigo.
Maybe you aren't aware of this.
But Zangetsu and I have
always been one and the same.
Together we're
your spirit energy.
I used to be part of him.
We share the same body.
But, as our relationship
began to change,
so too, did our
individual appearances.
When life is in control,
flesh covers the bones.
When death takes over,
the bones become exposed.
It's the same with
Zangetsu and I.
Over time, my power increased.
Control started to
switch over to death,
and Zangetsu became
a part of me.
The more you try draw
on Zangetsu's powers,
the easier it became for
me to dominate your soul.
-Is that so?
Then that means, if
I defeat you here,
then Zangetsu will
once again become
the center of my spirit energy.
-That makes sense.
In theory.
But you won't win.
-Is that right?
Don't be so sure about that.
I wonder how confident you'll
be, after you see this!
-You just don't
understand, do you?
It's not like you might beat me.
You can't beat me!
[music playing]
-Bankai!
[theme music]
-You there, in front of the TV!
Need some exercise?
Now the Hiyori Super Trainer can
be yours, for a low, low price.
Buy it now, and get it
signed by Hiyori Sarugaki.
-Wait, didn't you break it
when you threw it at Ichigo?
-Quiet, dumbass.
You're blowing my sales pitch.