Your Bankai intrigues me.
I want to see it.
Bushogoma!
Kick about... Los Lobos!
Hyoten Hyakkaso!
Hirvi--!
Hyoten Hyakkaso.
Anything that snow comes
in contact with, freezes
instantly into the shape
of a flower.
By the time these hundred
frozen flowers have
blossomed...
Your life will have
disappeared.
Ahhhhhh!
All right, attack!
[grunting]
Damn you! Give me back
my sword, now!
What's wrong? You
worried about that kid
down there?
No, it's not that.
Don't worry. Jushiro
won't do anything to
hurt that kid.
You should be concentrating
on our battle instead.
I said, that's not it!
I'm just not
gettin this.
Ah! Oh, no!
I must say, you're very
good at running away for
a fat chunk of meat!
This isn't going to
work! It's obviously
not going to work!
I'm screwed! I'm
gonna get killed!
Save me!
Time to end this.
What the hell
is that?
Gran Caida. A
guillotine too
good for a coward.
Rot and die!
Ah!
Bankai!
What??!
Hunh?!
Jakuho Raikoben!
So that's what your
Bankai looks like.
Ca- Captain!
So that's Captain Soi
Fon's Bankai. This is my
first time seeing it!
What's with that
shape?! How's she going
to fight with that?!
Huh?!
That's a ginjotan! A
steel band used as an
under layer for armor!
Why did she wrap herself
in something so heavy?!
With that steel sash
wrapped around her...
... even the Captain
won't be able to move
freely!
If possible, I had hoped
to end this without
using this Bankai.
This Bankai, it violates
my standards as a member
of the Stealth Force.
[gasping]
This Bankai's too big
for me to conceal it.
And it's too heavy to
move freely.
And its attack...
It's too flashy for an
assassin.
Uh!
Captain Komamura!
[screaming]
[groaning]
Dammit!
Did I... did I hit him?
[grunting]
Captain!
I gotcha.
That you, Marechiyo?
Yeah. Captain,
look over there.
You did it.
Captain!
[screaming]
Get off me. It's
disgusting.
[grunting]
You gonna play defense
all day or what?
Stay focused.
Or you'll get hurt.
You're distracted.
What's wrong?
Aren't you Arrancar
number one?
Don't tell me you're
still worried about
your friends.
Come on, spill it.
My friends...
Don't worry about it.
It's not important.
Hey.
Hm?
The Bankai all you
captains have... are all
of them that powerful?
Huh?
I know you heard the
question. Are they just
as strong!?
I think so. I mean, the
Bankai... is our ace in
the hole.
So all of 'em are
pretty damn powerful.
I see.
Then how does
yours stack up?
For example, between the
Bankai of that ice guy over
there and yours, which is
stronger?
Kinda hard to say, ya
see, Captain Hitsugaya is
what you'd call a prodigy.
If I had to guess, I'd
say he'll surpass my
strength in about a
hundred years.
Interesting.
So that means at this
moment, you're still
stronger than him.
[chuckling]
Jushiro!
[grunting]
What's this,
Shunsui!?
Hold my kimono,
would ya?
I'll need a minute.
Looks like this guy's
ready to throw down.
Yeah.
Your Bankai intrigues
me. I wanna see it.
He sheathed it?
What's he thinking?!
Lilinette!
Come!
Don't bark at me like
that! I'm not your
slave you know!
Why do you need the kid?
Because this kid
is my other half.
Hmm?
The Zanpakuto is the
heart of an Arrancar's
power, sealed in the form
of a sword.
Therefore, whenever a
sword release is
performed, an
Arrancar's true form
and essence is freed to
the world.
Over the centuries, most
Arrancars have confined
their Hollow powers to
their swords.
But ours works a bit
differently.
When the others evolved
from Hollow to Arrancar,
they divided their powers
into a body and a sword.
We, on the other hand,
divided ours between two
bodies.
And when we are reunited
as one... our power
becomes fully released.
Kick about... Los Lobos!
Katenkyokotsu!
All right...
Round two. Let's
go, Lilinette.
Ah, this Spiritual
Pressure...
It feels almost as if
everybody has released
their Resurrecion.
And it also appears that
the Soul Reapers are putting
up quite a fight. Don't you
agree, Captain Aizen?
I wish I could see it in
person. I would assume this
show is quite the spectacle.
Can't we do anything about
this wall of flames? It's
rather annoying.
Listen, Gin...
Yes?
Try to be patient. The
time to act will come
soon enough.
Hm.
Uh!
All right.
Round two.
Let's go.
Uh, Lilinette?
Are you listening?!
Don't ignore me!
Answer me!!
Ow!!
What?!
Did that pistol
just talk?
Are you trying to kill
me!? You almost cracked
my skull, dummy!
I don't care! It's
your own fault for not
cooperating in the first
place!
Plus, how the hell am I
supposed to know where your
head is when you're in pistol
form, anyway?!
The end of the barrel is
my head. I've told you
that hundreds of times!
What now? Ouch! That's
my butt! Stop it! Ow! Ow!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Come on! You're
killing me
me here! Ouch. Ouch.
Take it easy back
there! Hey, hey!
You bastard!
You're doing this on
purpose, aren't you?
Owwww! Okay, okay,
already! I'm sorry!
I apologize!
A sneak attack in the
middle of our conversation?
That's quite...
Bushogoma!
[gasping]
Takaoni.
You didn't let me
finish my sentence.
I was saying that's
quite a desperate move,
Captain.
It's not like you.
Not at all.
Well, actually, I was
hoping to spare you the
pain and kill you with my
first strike.
But then you went and
dodged it. I gotta say,
that release of yours is
no joke.
And that counter attack
packed a punch. Damn,
I'm impressed.
Why thank you.
While we're on the
subject...
Your two pistols... I
bet both shoot Ceros,
don't they?
Very astute.
Yeah, but that's not
the only thing they
shoot... am I right?
You're wrong.
And you're a terrible
liar. Come on, there's no
point in hiding it any
longer.
You're quite
presumptive.
I went through all the
trouble of a sword
release.
You can at least show
me what I want... your
Bankai.
Stark, your aim sucks!
You couldn't hit the
broad side of a barn!
Shut up! Just do your
job and keep firing!
That won't work.
It's nearly impossible
to hit a moving target
with one of those things,
let alone someone who
moves this fast.
Yes. I'm aware.
Oh, good.
Then maybe you shouldn't
be wasting all those shots!
Stark!
They're not a waste if
they help me track you
and learn your pattern.
You blocked
that rather well.
I'll be sure and take
that into consideration as
I predict your next acts of
futility.
Bushogoma!
Don't bother.
Ah ah ah.
I know your right pistol
is empty!
[gasping]
Now I'm confused.
Your right pistol packs a
wallop, but needs to be
recharged in the holster
after each shot.
Your left gun is weaker,
but can blast away
repeatedly.
At least, that's how I
thought it worked a
second ago.
Like I said, you're
rather presumptive.
You got me pegged there!
So how will you
evade me now?
Well, I guess I won't.
Don't act shocked. You
know I don't need to.
Up 'til now, you've
only been firing a Cero.
I know their power like
the back of my hand.
So what's your point?
Dodging your random shots
is pretty annoying,
I'll give ya that.
But no matter how
powerful you might be in
that released state of
yours, a Cero blast
isn't enough to kill
me.
And pretty soon... Huh?!
Uh oh.
Cero Metralleta.
It's no use running
away.
Hey! Hold on,
wait a second!
You had your chance!
When fired like this,
even a Cero blast should
be enough to destroy you,
right?
I dunno, isn't that
kinda like cheating?!
Seems fair to me.
What's wrong? Have
you had enough, Captain?
Maybe it's time you
show me... your Bankai!
Looks like I don't
have a choice...
Sogyonokotowari!
Jushiro?
What the hell? Did
he shoot... a Cero?
Captain Ukitake shot a
Cero?!
What are you worried
about this time,
Lieutenant Kira?
No, there's no way the
Captain would betray us!
Oh, you're such a
positive thinker!
Wait! Captain Ukitake has
white hair! Which means
he's a traitor like
Captain Ichimaru.
[sighing]
Same old
Lieutenant.