[theme music]
[panting]
-Where could they be?
KON (OFFSCREEN): Ichigo!
-Kon.
Where the hell have you been?
-Where have I been?
What are you talking
about, Ichigo?
You're the one who
took off without me.
-Shut up.
You need to help me
find Yuzu and Karin.
-What's the big deal?
They're back home.
I just saw both of them.
-You sure?
-Yeah, I'm sure.
They're safe and sound.
So what you been up to?
-Good.
Then I'll go find Uryu.
You take care of my sisters.
-Good luck.
-Geez, if I knew they were
gonna make us clean up,
I never would have come
to see what happened.
Instead of lecturing us, why
not make the ones responsible
do the grunt work?
-It's because you made
such a big deal out of it.
-What about you?
-What?
-Yeah, what?
TATSUKI (OFFSCREEN):
Anyway, didn't it
seem like every one of them
was acting kind of strange?
-What the-- what's
up with Orihime?
Orihime, you keep looking
so cute and spacey,
and I'll just have to kiss you.
[puckering]
-Just what the hell
kind of nonsense
are you blabbering about?
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah, you heard me.
-Oh, guess what?
You guys, there's
this TV show I watch.
It's a new episode
I don't wanna miss.
So let's go home.
-Huh?
-Let's hurry.
I'll make us curried
popcorn, Tatsuki.
-Hey, what's the rush?
Take it easy, Orihime.
-I don't wanna be late.
It's gonna start any minute.
The first thing I thought
was, I wish I didn't notice.
Then I thought, we have
to get away from here.
I'm certain of it now.
If we stay here,
we're in danger.
Somehow, every cell in my
body is tingling, warning me.
We've got to get away before
the situation gets worse.
But I have to appear calm.
I don't want the others
to know something bad is
about to happen.
It disappeared?
TATSUKI (OFFSCREEN):
Orihime, look, I'm sorry.
You two can go ahead.
I've gotta go change.
I'll catch up with you later.
-Tatsuki, no!
Wait!
Come back!
-Don't worry.
I'll be there in no time.
-But what if it's still here?
Tatsuki, don't go!
[gulps]
-You can see me, can't you?
[gasp]
-Damn.
Damn it.
Damn.
Uryu!
-20.
Sensei, this is for you.
I will win.
-What's wrong now?
Wh-- what are you looking at?
-Run.
-Hmm?
-You have got to run, Chizuru.
Now.
Get going.
-I won't let you get away.
[screams]
-What?
Not again.
So are you--
[screams]
-What just happened?
Chizuru!
I don't know what to do.
Chizuru.
[groaning]
-What's this?
Tears?
How cute.
Wow, I don't know what
it was that just hit me,
but I'm bleeding.
Still, it doesn't
really hurt that much.
-But, uh--
-No, really.
I'm fine.
Look, everyone knows you're
adorable when you're crying.
But I like it much better
when you're laughing.
-Stop.
You're hurting me.
-What?
My hand-- I don't
have control of it.
No.
What's going on?
Why is this happening?
[beeping]
-What's going on here?
All hell is breaking loose.
Damn.
-What's going on?
-What have you done to Chizuru?
-Orihime.
-I just used a bit of my powers.
-Powers?
-I don't like violence.
That's why I use these
seeds from my forehead
to take control of others
to make you humans fight
amongst yourselves.
[chuckles]
-But why?
-Now, everyone, it's
time to get started.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): What?
What's going on?
What's happening?
What have you done to them?
[screaming]
-What the hell are
you people doing?
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): Tatsuki.
-Hey, Orihime, about
that thing over there.
I should've noticed it sooner.
-So you can see that
creature as well?
-No, I don't see it.
But I can sense its presence.
I know exactly where that
thing is that made you cry.
Hey.
Yeah, you, you big blob.
You picked a fight with
the wrong person this time.
See, we have this
longstanding arrangement.
Anyone who makes Orihime cry
gets the snot beat out of them.
-You don't say?
-Move back.
Ha.
Isn't there even one of you
who can give me a fight?
[growls] Let go.
Huh?
-Run, Tatsuki.
-Chizuru?
-Look.
What's happening to my arm?
[groaning]
-Can't you stop?
-So how do you feel now?
The seed I shot
into you has begun
to take root in your body.
And in just a little bit,
it'll take control of you.
Soon your body will be
mine to manipulate at will.
Now how shall I make you suffer?
-Shut up.
-What?
-I said, shut up.
Let go of her now.
-Don't you realize the
position you're in right now?
Soon, you'll have almost
no control of your body.
Here, I'll show you.
See?
[screams] What do you
think you're doing?
Let go.
Leg go.
Do you hear me?
I said let go!
You're not worth controlling.
Now die!
-Tatsuki!
-O-- Orihime.
Please, don't cry.
Ori--
[spluttering]
-Orihime, you have
such beautiful hair.
It's so long and shiny.
-That made me so happy.
But when school started--
-What's with that
ridiculous hair?
We'll teach you to
be such a show off.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): I
couldn't tell Sora the truth.
-What happened?
Why did you cut your hair?
-I just felt like a change.
That's all.
He died soon after that, and I
just got lonelier and lonelier.
-Hello?
Earth to Orihime,
anybody home in there?
Hey, so what do you say?
Let's go home.
-Uh-huh.
You know, it's
because of you that I
was able to grow
my hair long again.
And I'll never
cut my hair again.
That's because my long
hair proves something.
It proves my trust
in you, Tatsuki.
Thank you for doing
everything you
could to protect me until now.
So please, don't cry!
-Orihi-- Orihime.
-Tatsuki, this time,
I'll protect you.
-Impossible!
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN):
Tatsuki said to you,
you picked a fight
with the wrong person.
That's not quite right.
What she should have said was,
you picked the wrong person
to hurt.
Anyone who tries to hurt Tatsuki
will have to answer to me.
-Just what exactly are you?
Using those strange powers.
But how?
-Huh?
Who are you?
-Come on.
Don't tell me you didn't
notice us until just now.
-Sure, she noticed us.
I'm certain she knew
that we existed.
-Hmm?
-After all, once
you think about it,
haven't we always been
the ones closest to you?
Hello, Orihime.
We are the Shun Shun Rikka, your
six princess-shielding flowers.
And we've come here
to protect you.
-Now, wait a second.
Why are there a bunch of
little fairies flying around,
talking to me?
-Geez, that was some reaction.
But to be accurate,
we're not fairies.
-Huh?
-You see, we are the powers
from inside your soul.
And each one of us
is a part of you.
And only you are able to see us.
Uh, well, maybe people like
Ichigo Kurosaki can see us too.
-Ichigo?
Why him?
-Well, it's because of
him that we were born.
-You talk too much.
All right.
Listen up.
You don't need to know who
we are or where we came from.
All you need to know is that
we're a part of your powers.
-You're pretty bossy
for somebody so tiny.
-Real funny.
Just shut up and learn
how to use us right now.
-Learn how to use you?
-That's right.
-You can use our power
to construct a shield
to reject any spirit attacks.
-In order to
activate this shield,
you must use your heart and
our kotodama, a spirit chant.
-K-- kotodama?
-Wait a second.
It's coming.
-So what are you doing
mumbling to yourself?
Tell me, young girl.
-It's time, Orihime.
Now, call out our names!
-I am Hinagiku.
-I am Baigon.
-My name's Lily.
-Stay calm.
You must summon them
with your kotodama.
Now repeat after me.
Hinagiku, Baigon, Lily, hurry!
-Hinagiku, Baigon, Lily.
-[speaking japanese].
I reject.
-What?
-Their powers let them
create a shield between you
and your enemy and then reject
what's outside that shield
so they're able to protect
you from any outside attack.
You see, we have the ability to
reject what is within a shield.
We are able to make a defined
space with our shield.
And then we can
reverse any damage
that has been inflicted
inside that space.
Now, say our names.
I am Shuno.
-And I'm Ayame.
-Shuno, Ayame.
SHUNO (OFFSCREEN): Now
recite our kotodama.
-[speaking japanese].
I reject.
Tatsuki.
-Quit it.
This is no time for tears.
I'm up next, missy.
I'm able to reject on both sides
by blowing a hole in the enemy
and creating a shield inside,
which cuts the enemy in half.
Now you must say my name.
It is Tsubaki.
Then recite my kotodama.
-Tsubaki.
[speaking japanese] I reject.
[growls]
-Impossible.
[screams]
[panting]
-I did it.
-Orihime.
-Oh, well.
I guess using all of our powers
at once was too much for her.
-On the other hand, Orihime
did really well, didn't she?
[panting]
-Huh?
The man's not here.
-Are you sure that
this is the place?
-I'm sure this is it.
The man was beaten up and
left lying right here.
ISSHIN (OFFSCREEN): Karin,
I cannot believe this.
You are such a liar.
-I'm not a liar.
The guy was right
here, and he was hurt.
-That's all right, Karin.
I think I know what
you're doing here.
Daddy's been so busy
with his work lately,
he's had almost no
time for you, has he?
But there's no need to
make up wild stories just
to get your father's attention.
Karin, come on over and give
your hunky dad a big old hug.
That-a girl.
-You're an idiot, Dad.
-I think maybe we
should go home now.
This place gives me the creeps.
-My nose.
-You're hopeless.
-Looks to me like
another happy ending.
Good.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): Chad?
-You're up.
Good morning.
-Hi.
Um, Chad?
So where are we?
-Don't know.
MAN (OFFSCREEN): I see
you're finally awake.
-Him?
-I'm not too sure.
But apparently, this guy must've
been the one who saved us.
-Well, I suppose that's
one way to look at it.
Now then, where should I begin?
-Damn it.
Damn that Uryu.
I'll make him pay
for doing this.
-I can't kill them with
just one shot anymore.
Something's wrong.
I'm losing my strength,
and there are far too
many Hollows coming for
that small amount of bait.
It's as if they were lured here
by an even greater force yet
to reveal itself or its purpose.
But none of that matters.
Sensei, I swear to you I
will avenge your death.
- Hakuro , number four.
Yakura .
Damn it.
These Hollows are small
fry, practically harmless,
yet I can't beat them.
After two months in
this Gigai, I still
don't have my strength back.
Huh?
Is that Ichigo?
-I've wanted to do
this for so long.
-You're Kon, right?
-It even feels good to
get kicked like this.
-Kon, this is no time to
be acting like an idiot.
Wait.
If you're back in
Ichigo's body again,
then Ichigo must've gotten
transformed into a Soul Reaper.
-Check it out, sis.
Look behind you.
-What?
-That's a good sign.
Apparently, this area's safe.
Rukia Kuchiki.
So this is actually
the first time
I've spoken to you face to face.
-Is he ignoring me?
[growls]
Ow.
-I get it.
So this is all your doing.
-Yes, I started this contest
between me and the Soul Reaper.
-Now what?
-No need to worry.
I have no intention of letting
any innocent bystanders die.
Ichigo may run out of
strength during the battle.
But even if he
does, I will protect
the citizens of this town.
Then, while the Soul Reaper
stands by and watches,
I alone will kill the Hollows.
-Huh?
-If I can't accomplish
that, then this whole battle
is meaningless.
-I hope you mean it.
-Now just what are
you saying here?
-Excuse me, but all this stuff
about Soul Reapers and Hollows
is just so sudden.
-Then tell me, do
you deny the fact
that you were attacked just now?
-Well--
-Um--
-Ichigo Kurosaki, a Soul
Reaper, is fighting Hollows
even as we speak.
And the strong
spiritual energy he
has released during that fight
has had an influence on you.
So now you know.
However, it's all up
to you whether or not
you choose to open the gate
that has appeared before you.
-Oh.
-Excuse me, boss.
-Hmm?
-The Sky Rift is
beginning to open.
-And the preparations?
-All set.
-Well, then, let's go.
You did want proof?
Then come see for yourself
what lies beyond the gate.
[roaring]
-Huh?
-So I found you, Uryu.
-Kurosaki.
-Ichigo.
THEME SONG: Nobody
knows who I really am.
I never felt this empty before.
And if I ever need
someone to come along,
who's gonna comfort
me and keep me strong?
[theme music]
ISSHIN NARRATING: Time for
Isshin Kurosaki's Fatherly Love
101.
Now everyone, all together,
a father's love is strong.
A father's love will win.
A father's love is beautiful.
A father's love is-- [screams]
ICHIGO NARRATING:
How many times have
I told you this is a preview?
ISSHIN NARRATING: But son,
the next episode is great!