[theme music]
-My research was
made even harder
because of the poor
quality of the specimens.
The last one was a
grubby old man who
kept screaming out the
name of his student.
It was all so pathetic.
[music playing]
What was that student's name?
My, my.
I can't believe I've
forgotten it now.
It just seems like
after the experiment
I lose all interest in--
[explosion]
-What's this?
-Do you want me to tell you
the name you can't remember?
That student's name was Ishida.
Uryu Ishida.
This man is Soken Ishida.
He was my teacher, as
well as my grandfather!
-Oh?
And?
-Now I swear by the honor of the
Quincy, I'm going to kill you,
you monster!
-Oh?
KUROTSUCHI (VOICEOVER):
I immobilized his limbs
with the Ashisogi
Jizo, yet somehow he
managed to stand up again.
Oh, I know.
This is Ransotengai.
[music playing]
It involves taking countless
threads of spirit particles,
bundling them together,
and then connecting them
to the immobilized
limbs to forcibly
move them, like a
puppet on strings.
The technique was developed
by elderly Quencies
so they could continue
fighting Hollows
with their clumsy old bodies.
Dislocated joints and
torn flesh mean nothing
to those who have mastered it.
It will allow a
Quincy to continue
fighting until his body has
literally turned to dust.
I thought it was a lost art
existing only in history books.
Of the thousands of
Quincies I dissected,
none could use
Ransotengai, so to find
that you are able to use
it at such a young age,
you may be something
special after all.
Perhaps even a genius.
-A genius.
Such a generic term doesn't
even begin to describe it.
-Oh?
-For me, Ransotengai is
more than a defense or a way
to protect my life.
Even if I'm reduced to a corpse,
until I avenge my Master,
it's the expression
of my will to fight!
-I'll retract the word "genius."
You're just a neophyte with
a big chip on your shoulder.
-Uryu, I understand you went
to see your grandfather again
today.
How many times do I have to
tell you, stop going over there.
-But dad--
-Don't argue with me.
If I've told you once,
I've told you 100 times.
It's pointless to
try to save the dead.
-Father--
-Let the Soul Reapers
take care of that.
The only thing you should
concern yourself with
is how to save the living.
I have no interest in this
and you have no talent for it,
so the Quincies
will become extinct
when your grandfather passes on.
Do you understand me, Uryo?
-But father, why do you
hate being a Quincy so much?
-Because there's
no profit in it.
[music playing]
-You must realize that there is
truth to what your father says.
These days being a Quincy
doesn't put food on the table.
And with a family to support,
that is a real problem.
-But still--
-Now, you must try to see
things from his perspective.
-I can't.
I saw them attack.
Hollows.
I saw them kill people.
I saw it with my own eyes.
And I know something
else about Hollows.
The Soul Reapers
can't handle them all.
[sobbing] And I'm sure my
father knows that, too.
So how-- how can he
say those things?
Master?
-Hmm?
-I want you to make me strong.
I want to become powerful.
If I'm a strong Quincy, I can
protect everyone from Hollows.
And if I can do
that, then I know
my father will see he was
wrong about the Quincies.
SOKEN (VOICEOVER):
Thank you, Uryu, my boy.
-Not bad.
You may be a more
interesting specimen
than I had thought at first.
Maybe I won't kill you.
I could take you
back to my lab alive.
You might be useful as a
research subject after all.
SOKEN (VOICEOVER):
But Uryu, I hope
you will try to understand your
father's point of view as well.
What you believe
to be right depends
on what it is you
wish to protect.
-I don't understand.
What is father protecting?
Money?
-There will come a time when you
will know the answer to that,
and by then you
will also know what
it is that you truly
want to protect.
In preparation for that day,
I shall entrust you with this.
-What is it?
-[laughing]
[music playing]
SOKEN (VOICEOVER): This
is the Sanrei Shuto.
It is a glove that gives
its wearer the power
to disperse Reishis,
spirit particles,
at a very high level.
[music playing]
SOKEN (VOICEOVER): When
you put on this glove
and manifest a
bow, and if you can
train for seven days and
seven nights without stopping,
you will reach the very
pinnacle of the Quincy's powers.
-[laughing] Yaaaa!
[laughing]
SOKEN (VOICEOVER): However,
you must take care, Uryu.
For once you have
reached that point,
you can never remove
this glove again.
The moment you do, your ability
to draw in spirit energy
will exceed your physical
limits as a Quincy.
Exposure to such a strong
flame will burn you.
And even though
removing the glove
will allow you to temporarily
gain enormous power, when that
fades away, you will lose
your Quincy powers completely.
-Let's stop this tedious
fighting before I accidentally
kill you.
Why don't you just come
back to my laboratory now?
SOKEN (VOICEOVER): When the
day comes that you finally
understand your
father's feelings,
and when you know what it
is that you want to protect,
then you must decide if you
still want to be a Quincy.
For if you do,
understand there will
be times when you find yourself
in unavoidable battles,
perhaps some day in a
battle that requires power
far greater than
what you possess.
When that time
comes, that is when
you should use the Sanrei Shuto.
But I will tell you once more,
once you put this glove on,
you must never take it off.
-I can think of
many creative ways
to take you with me without
having to kill you first.
If you don't mind experiencing
some hellish pain that is.
Maybe you'd be interested
in a demonstration
of one of those methods now.
URYU (VOICEOVER): I'm right at
the limit of the Ransotengai's
properties.
I can't hold out much
longer against him.
I'm sorry, Master.
I still don't understand
my father's feelings,
and I still don't
know what it is
that I truly want to protect.
But that which could
not ever be forgiven,
I think I do know that one.
[music playing]
I'm sorry, Master.
I'm afraid once more
I must disobey you.
-Oh!
What did he do?
What just happened here?
[music playing]
How did his outfit
suddenly change,
and where did this immense
spiritual pressure come from?
I've ever seen such a thing.
Amazing.
KUROTSUCHI (VOICEOVER):
He seems be
be absorbing the
buildings around him.
Everything in the Seireitei is
composed entirely of Reishi,
but does this mean he can
break down their bonds
and forcibly absorb
them, transforming
them to increase his power?
It would be he has achieved
complete dominance over Reishi.
You have gone beyond the
power limit humans can handle,
you neophyte.
[music playing]
KUROTSUCHI (VOICEOVER): He's
face, but I can still dodge it.
Huh?
-Bed for mercy, and I just might
let you live, provided you go
and never appear
before me again.
Refuse, and the next shot
will be three times stronger.
-Don't get carried away!
A mere Quincy taunting me?
The nerve.
If that's the way
you want it, I'll
return the favor and
attack with equal power.
[laughing]
Bankai.
URYU (VOICEOVER): What is this?
"Ban" what?
-Behold, Konjiki Ashisogi Jizo!
-But how?
I thought that Zanpakuto
was already released.
-[laughing] You didn't know?
All Zanpakuto have two stages
of release, not just one.
-What!
-Ashisogi Jizo is
only the first stage
of my Zanpakuto, the Shikai.
Konjiki Ashisogi Jizo
is the second stage,
called the Bankai.
The deadly poison gas it spews
will cause your painful death
in minutes.
A shame that I won't
be able to do research
on such an excellent
specimen as you.
[laughing]
Attack!
[music playing]
-Master?
Is he--
-[gagging]
-[gagging] Damn you,
you Quincy bastard!
[gagging]
URYU (VOICEOVER):
His sword can also
liquefy things that it cuts.
KUROTSUCHI (VOICEOVER): That
was a close one, Quincy.
-Huh?
KUROTSUCHI (VOICEOVER):
One's last ace
in the hole should only be used
after careful consideration.
-I should have known better.
He had one last trick
to help him run away.
Damn!
KUROTSUCHI (VOICEOVER):
Your arrows
are worthless now, Quincy.
In this state, although I
can't fight back, neither can
I be attacked or
harmed in any way.
It will take me a few days to
return to my original form,
but I can retreat
to my base like this
and tend to my wounds.
Goodbye, Quincy.
This encounter may
not have turned out
quite the way I had hoped,
but in the end I will live
and you will die, so the
final outcome will not change.
URYU (VOICEOVER): Damn it.
It can't end this way.
The poison is
taking effect on me.
At this great I'll--
NEMU (OFFSCREEN):
Quincy, listen.
-Huh?
-Come here.
Behind the emblem on my
left arm I have an antidote.
-Are you sure it wouldn't be
more comfortable lying down?
-No, thanks.
Hurry now.
Take it.
-You should go first.
-That's kind, but you go ahead.
I'll be OK.
My body's the same substance as
the Captain's, so this poison
has no effect on me.
Are you suspecting this
is some kind of trap?
If you'd like, put
the bottle to my lips
and I'll drink some to
prove its all right.
-No.
What would be the
use of poisoning
an already poisoned
and dying man?
NEMU (OFFSCREEN): Thank you
for showing my Captain mercy.
If you had aimed for the
head, you most certainly
would have killed
him, but instead you
chose too let him live.
-Don't thank me.
I intended to kill
him, but I missed.
-Well, in any case,
he is still alive,
and the antidote is a
token of my appreciation
to you for that.
-I don't get it.
How could you ever have such
feelings for someone like him?
It's hard to explain, but when
he realized that he was still
alive, I felt such
a sense of relief.
You should hurry up now
and drink the antidote,
and then you'd better go.
After the release of
Konjiki Ashisogi Jizo,
there'll be troops
on the way here soon.
URYU (OFFSCREEN): Thank
you for the antidote.
Farewell.
[wind blowing]
URYU (VOICEOVER): Damn.
The pain's getting
worse, and I can hardly
lift my arms and legs.
The Ransotengai is fading away.
I guess my time as a Quincy
has about reached its end.
I hope Orihime is OK.
Her spiritual pressure
was a lot stronger
than that guy form
Squad 11, so she
should have had the upper hand.
Ichigo, Chad, Yoruichi, Ganju.
I wonder how they're all doing.
I have to believe they'll find
their way here eventually.
Wouldn't it be funny
if after all this
I somehow got to
the Senziku first?
What if I was the one
who rescued Rukia?
I bet that would
really piss off Ichigo.
Everyone knows he wants
to be the big hero
and rescue her all by himself.
I'm sorry, but for the sake of
peace, I must terminate you.
Cry, Suzumushi.
[theme music]
MALE SPEAKER (VOICEOVER): Naimi,
once I'm assumed this form,
it seems to take forever
to get back to normal.
Never mind eating.
I can't even take a shower.
I wonder if I had a
big enough container?
Ah!
Hey, don't throw water on me!
You're diluting me!
MALE SPEAKER (VOICEOVER):
It's more inconvenient
than I imagined.