-I'm Ichigo Kurosaki.
And other than having the
ability to see spirits,
I used to be an ordinary
high school student.
But the day I met
Rukia Kuchiki, I
was given the powers
of the soul reaper
in order to protect the
world of the living.
As I began my work as a
substitute soul reaper,
I found myself thrown into
a never ending battle.
In the midst of everything,
my best friend Odi Hemayinoui
was abducted by ex-soul
reaper Captain Sosuke Aizen.
My friends Chad and
Udi are joining me
as I race to rescue Odi Hemay.
Once we arrived in Waco
Mundo, we entered a fight
with powerful enemies
known as Arankars.
We were too late to
keep Aizen from entering
the world of the living.
But luckily the 13 Court Guard
squads were already there
to stop it, and all that
war was about to begin.
[theme music]
-In order to prevent Sosuke
Aizen from wiping out
Karakura Town, the soul
reapers evacuated the residents
using tenkaicatch, and
relocated the entire town
to the Rukon District.
Ikkaku Madarame, Izuru
Kira, Yumichika Ayasegawa
and Shuhei Hisagi were assigned
to defend the four sinkaymon
pillars that masked the
appearance of the town.
They found themselves
facing a force
of Fraccions sent by Baraggan.
The battle between Charlotte
Coolhorn and Yumichika
escalated into a
confrontation over beauty.
Yumichika won by
unveiling ruidiro kujako,
his Zanpakuto's true form.
Izuru also emerged victorious
by entrusting his Zanpakuto,
wabiske, with the squad's
philosophy of despair.
Shuhei Hisagi fought
against Findorr Calius
who boasted that
he could control
the level of his strength.
Shuhei used his
Zanpakuto, kazashini,
and proved to Findorr that a
man who did not fear his sword
had no right to hold one.
The last battle was
between Ikkaku Madarame
and the Fraccion named Poww--
this fight didn't go as well.
[gasp]
-Ikkaku's down.
-Then he was defeated?
[zap]
-One pillar down,
that's three to go.
-Impossible.
-It can't be.
[grunting]
-Ikkaku!
[bam]
[grunt]
-Stop it.
How are you going to be able
to win against an opponent who
defeated Ikkaku?
-I'll just have to find a way!
Uh, let me go!
If you continue
to block my path,
I'll have to go through you!
-Don't be stupid, Yumichika.
Calm yourself down.
-Shut up!
I'm warning you, move away!
[whiz]
[whack]
[grunt]
-Uh.
Uh.
-What the hell?
-He's very disrespectful
for a 5th seat.
I know he's upset, but he
still has to control himself.
-Izuru.
-I simply used Gotin.
He'll be fine.
More than that, if one of the
pillars was destroyed then--
[gasps]
[whoosh]
-It's a Tensokaki.
With the pillar destroyed,
the real Karakura Town
is starting to reappear.
-This is bad.
We've got to stop
that process somehow.
[whoosh]
-This bald guy acted
like he was concealing
some kind of hidden power,
but he never revealed it.
Oh, well, if he's dead,
I guess it doesn't really
matter anymore.
[cough]
-Not so fast.
[growl]
Who are you calling dead?
You're getting a little ahead
of yourself, don't you think?
I should be the one who
decides if I'm dead, not you,
and I'm breathing fine!
[whack]
-This is futile.
[pow]
[gasp]
-Hyaaaaa!
[whack]
-Huh?
Uh!
[thud]
Ya!
[struggling]
[groaning]
Ah!
[grunting]
[smash]
Ugh!
Hya!
[whoosh]
[grunts]
[thud]
[yelling in pain]
-If you want to live, show
me the power you're hiding.
Show it!
Now tell me you understand.
Tell me.
[choking]
You're going to
die if you don't.
[yelling in pain]
-I understand nothing!
[grunt]
You think I'm hiding
some kind of power.
I have no such
thing, believe me.
And even if I did
have it, I wouldn't
be wasting it on somebody as
weak and insignificant as you!
-Is that so?
Goodbye, you pest.
[whack]
[grunt]
[crash]
-Captain Komamura.
-Tetsuzaemon, right!
[whoosh]
[grunt]
[whack]
[whoosh]
[heavy breathing]
-Ugh.
-That should stop the reversion.
They're made for
emergencies, and as long
as you don't break them
they should be all right.
-Tetsuzaemon.
[evil laughter]
[boom]
[thud]
-He's humongous.
He's bigger than
Captain Kamamura.
-I really felt that
one, soul reaper.
Or should I be saying,
nice one, little doggy?
Anyway, it was a good punch.
Not as good as mine.
See, this is what
I call a real--
[boom]
--punch.
[groaning]
[explosions]
-Captain Komamura!
-Tell me, did you feel that one?
I kind of thought you might.
But as long as we happen
to be on the subject,
let me demonstrate
my best punch.
I'm sure you'll find
this interesting.
Real Caldero!
[zing]
[boom] [boom] [boom]
[boom] [boom]
-Ah!
Ah!
What the hell is that?
[screams]
-Uh!
Is that even the same creature?
[groan]
-I should smash
you all to pieces,
but at the moment
it's too much trouble.
[straining]
-So, you have finally
shown your true form.
Well, the bigger they
are, the harder they fall.
Wha?
Ugh, hey!
What did you grab me for?
I was about to take him down!
-Shut your mouth.
You are no match
for an adversary who
was able to send the captain
flying with a single punch.
-Huh?
Wait a minute, when did you
turn into such a little coward?
-I'm not even going to
dignify that with an answer.
-I feel heavy, and so weary.
But it doesn't matter.
It can't be helped.
It's Lord Baraggan's orders.
[straining]
[whoosh]
[explosion]
-Ah, damn it!
He's worse now than before.
-No kidding.
If he'd hit us, we would
have been done for.
[grunt]
Quit dawdling, let's go!
-Ah.
-Uh?
-No way.
I want to fight this guy.
If you're going to run
away, do it on your own.
I'm not leaving here!
-Have you lost your mind?
How are you going to fight a
guy you couldn't handle when you
went up against
him the first time?
Or has he been right?
Did he have you
pegged all along?
Do you have some secret
power you've been hiding?
-Course not.
There's nothing hidden.
-Then shut up and
let's get out of here!
-Wait!
[groaning]
-There they are.
Those little insects.
[heavy footsteps]
-Strai is huge.
He's going to catch up to us.
-Shut your mouth!
-Let go of me!
We'll never outrun
him like this!
-I said keep quiet!
-You two are done!
[screams]
[whoosh]
[boom]
[groans]
[groaning]
-Ahhh!
[boom]
[groaning]
[crash]
[groan]
-Captain.
-Do not retreat,
Tetsuzaemon, ever.
Stand behind me while
we end this fight.
-Sir!
[evil laughter]
-I have a surprise
for you, pesky insect.
That had no effect.
But I will say this
much, I was surprised
at the extent of your strength.
I never imagined
a maggot like you
could throw me, a
fraccion of Lord Baraggan.
-Damn it, this is nuts!
[groans]
We should be helping!
-Just keep still.
-What?
-Watch very closely, Ikkaku.
You're going to bear
personal witness
to what our captain
is all about.
-You lowly maggots have the
audacity to stand right there
and defy Lord Barragon?
It's so unbelievable, it
just makes me want to yawn.
[whoosh]
-Unfortunately, allow
me to shut your mouth
so this doesn't happen again.
[whoosh]
Bankai!
[boom]
-Kokujo Tengen Myoo!
[whirring]
[whoosh]
[zing]
[muffled grunts]
-What?
Why, you--
[grunting]
Ah!
[grunt]
-Too bad for you,
I've become accustomed
to your size,
weight, and methods.
[grunt]
-Hi-ya!
[bam]
[grunt]
Ah!
[boom]
[groaning]
[bam]
Oh!
[groaning]
[gurgling]
[crash]
[grunt]
-Damn it.
[grunting]
[bam]
[straining]
[laughing]
-I've got you this
time, you pest.
[whoosh]
-The captain can't use his arms.
-If he gets hit at
point blank range,
he's going to be thorough!
[zing]
[whoosh]
-Captain!
[evil laughter]
-Ra!
[roars]
[rumbling]
-Uh!
[choking]
[groaning]
[boom]
[grunting]
[crash]
-Ugh!
-What the hell?
It can't be.
[grunts]
Wait a minute.
Something's wrong here.
This is impossible!
Who are you?
-Oh, you're right.
I guess I forgot
to identify myself.
My name is Sajin
Komamura, and I am
the Captain of Soul
Reaper Squad 7.
And ashamed as I am, I have
to admit you were right.
I am nothing but a lowly maggot.
[bam]
-Ugh!
[explosion]
[heavy wind]
-Yaaaa!
No mercy!
-It's for the best.
-I don't think it
matters whether it
was the real or the replica
town that was destroyed.
Squad 7's going to be
in the red for the rest
of the fiscal year.
-The captain won't let the
squad shoulder the bill.
He'll pay out of his own
pocket for any damages that
may have been caused
during the operation.
That's the kind of leader
Captain Komamura is.
-Is that for real?
All right!
Then I'm not going
to worry anymore.
Yeah!
-That doesn't apply to you.
Anything you break will
be immediately deducted
from your salary, no arguments.
-Oh, you tightwad.
Oh, and there were
so many things
I was hoping to buy this month.
-Just get over it.
-Ah, ah, boy.
I'm thinking it's a good
thing we didn't get over there
in time.
-Yeah.
[whoosh]
[boom]
-Amazing.
-See what I meant?
His Bankai and yours are as
different as night and day,
Ikkaku.
[gasps]
-But--
-You didn't think
we knew about it?
You're an idiot.
Relax, I'm not going to
tell your captain anything.
But I want you to give it
some hard thought, Ikkaku.
You were the only
one of the four
who allowed his pillar
to be destroyed.
Your job was simply
to protect it.
Do you know why you failed?
Because you attempted to keep
your strength camouflaged!
It's your prerogative
to die while keeping
your strength hidden,
but never, never
at the cost of
failing your mission.
You can't put your
selfish pride ahead
of achieving your
squad's objectives.
As long as you're a member
of the 13 Court Guard Squads,
your orders will
take priority-- even
if it means suppressing
your individual vanity!
You will never be
an effective leader
unless you're willing
to accept that.
-Tetsuzaemon, I do understand
that, but there's one--
[bam]
Gah!
-What do you
understand, you moron?
You're acting like some
kind of spoiled brat.
You're convinced that
if you were to die,
someone would automatically
take your place.
So you fight as if the
consequences don't really
matter.
-Hold on a minute.
You can't get away
with that statement.
Who says I fight like the
consequences don't matter?
-You mean you deny it?
You think I'm wrong?
-Damn you.
You bastard!
[whack]
-Why did you charge him
head-on when you were injured?
Can you explain that?
[grunts]
[boom]
-Ugh.
-Charging him head-on would
have meant nothing, especially
if you ended up getting crushed.
Do whatever it
takes to win, even
if it means running away
from or outfoxing the enemy.
-I can't do that.
I can't carry out
such a cowardly fight.
-Then you'd better find
a way to get stronger!
If you insist on having
things on your terms,
you'd better put
on some strength.
When you fight an
enemy you have to win,
even if you die in the process.
That's what it means to
stay true to yourself.
-Hm.
-Uh, uh, captain.
-Calm down, both of you.
Unfortunately, I seem to be a
little hard of hearing today.
-Coolhorn, Aberama, Findorr,
Poww-- useless fools!
[crunch]
[theme music]
-How'd I look back there when
I was pricking my ears up,
Tetsuzaemon?
-I think you made a great
impression on the audience.
Fans from all over the
country sent in gifts.
But I got to tell you, they were
mostly doggy toys and biscuits.
-That's perfect.
-Captain?