The Zanpakuto... Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined
by its Soul Reaper
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper...
And dies with its Soul
Reaper.
That is the existence
of a Zanpakuto.
We seem to be
outnumbered. The rebel
forces are growing daily.
Have you thought of
how we should proceed?
There's no time to come
up with a plan. I'm going
down there.
Don't be rash.
This is war. It can't be
waged by one person.
That's true... But we
both know if I don't do
something, we're likely
to lose the battle.
Your reaction seems odd,
Father.
Koga, in battle, you will
address me appropriately.
My apologies, Sir Genrei.
I'll be going then.
Always willing to rush
headlong into danger...
Who's he?!
Identify yourself!?
Wait! I know him!
Is... he one of the
Kuchiki's?!
Surround him!
He's our enemy!
You will curse your
misfortune for having ever
laid eyes on this sword.
Don't be afraid! He's
one man, that's all!
Is everybody ready?
Let's get him!
Whisper, Muramasa...!
[struggling]
What's this?!
My sword! What's
happening to it?!
What's wrong?!
I don't know! My
Zanpakuto is moving
on its own!
Stop that! What's come
over you?!
Ah, what the---?!
Have you gone
completely crazy?!
Of course not! My
Zanpakuto has a
mind of its own!
That's ridiculous!
What do you take me
for, an idiot?!
What?! Impossible!
My own sword is
turning on me!
No! Stop this! No!
No! No! No!
Raise up your head, Koga
Kuchiki...!
Sir...
Your work on our behalf
has been quite impressive.
The rebellion in our land
is still far from over.
But today, we
made progress toward
restoring peace.
You are too kind,
Head Captain.
There is great turmoil
in the Soul Society over
this revolt.
The challenges that we
face are going to test
our resolve.
We will soon learn if we
are truly capable of bringing
eternal peace to our world.
In order to succeed in
our mission, we will need
great strength like your own.
Please continue to further
your efforts for this cause.
Yes, sir. I pledge my
life in an effort to
bring peace to this world.
Did you hear
about Sir Koga?
No. What
happened?
Everyone's talking about
it. He took out several
dozen rebels by himself!
Are you kidding?!
That's amazing!
The rumors are that a
Third Seat position is
being secured for him.
He probably deserves it.
But why does he dress
just like the people of
the Kuchiki clan?
Come on, you mean
you don't know his
background?
He's an accomplished
scholar and warrior. He
married into the Kuchiki
clan.
What's wrong, Sir Ginrei?
You seem upset.
Is it something I've
done?
Yes. Let me ask you
something...
During the battle, why
did you launch an attack
on your own?
I was confident I could
handle the situation.
I knew I could defeat the
enemy... as long as I
could wield the power of
my Zanpakuto, Muramasa.
Koga...
I don't think you realize
what is happening...
People who have access
to great power need something
extra in order to control it.
Do you know
what that is?
I'm not sure,
father.
They need heart.
What do you mean?
Power must always
be controlled by
its possessor.
And at times, power is
too great to wield.
In order to obtain balance,
you will require a heart
that is sensitive to the
use and limitations
of that power.
I am well aware of the
tremendous scope of your
abilities.
However, you still lack
the heart to make the
most effective use of
those powers.
You should use this
incident as a warning
to yourself.
Don't forget you bear the
title of our clan, and
responsibility for your
actions on its behalf.
But...
That is all.
You may leave.
Thank you, my lord.
Why do you seem so
troubled, Koga?
What makes you
think I'm troubled?
I can sense that something
is bothering you...
Heh! That's just your
imagination.
You cannot hide from
me. We are one.
Our trust in each other
is what makes us strong.
Tell me. Am I using my
powers incorrectly?
I don't know. Your power
has not yet reached its
full potential. There's
no telling how much of it
you can produce, or what
you may be able to to do
with it.
I see...
But let me say this. We
are a Soul Reaper and a
Zanpakuto that were meant
to be together...
Trust in me, and at the
same time, trust in
yourself.
You're right. Trusting in
myself is the answer.
And that, in turn,
will lead to peace.
Sir. Is there anything
else I can do before I go?
What is Sir Ginrei
thinking?
What are you talking
about, Koga?
He never seems to accept
me, no matter how great
my achievements may be.
In fact, he seems to look
down on me.
Have confidence.
You are strong.
Do you have a
moment, father?
Huh?
It's about Koga.
He's been acting different
lately. And he refuses to
talk to me about anything.
Try not to worry, my
dear child...
Koga is a sensible man. And
as a Soul Reaper, his powers
are far greater than my own.
He just needs more time
to develop them properly,
and learn how to use them
responsibly.
Run for it! Retreat!
From all the reports
coming in, it appears
that most of the rebel
forces were suppressed
after the last
battle!
Great work, Sir Koga!
We're very proud to be
working with you, sir.
You're an inspiration to all
the men under your command.
Thank you, men. But
there's no need to
flatter me.
I'm not doing this
for the recognition.
I want order restored to
the Soul Society. Huh?
I wonder what
that was about...
I'm not sure who those
guys are, but I've seen
them skulking around.
I guess they enjoy
keeping secrets.
They're probably jealous
of your accomplishments,
Sir Koga.
You want my help? I'm
honored that you would
ask, Head Captain!
This is the
issue, Koga.
I am in the process of
organizing a Special Task
Force to deal with the
remaining Rebel Units.
I want you to become its
leader, to make sure the
job gets done properly.
Of course, Head Captain!
Sir Ginrei...!
Head Captain Yamamoto has
put me in charge of his
Special Task Force!
I'm supposed to begin
immediately!
I see. Try not to tarnish
our Clan's name in the
process.
Are you not unhappy to
hear this?
Your son-in-law...
of the Kuchiki Clan...
... now has an important
assignment to carry out!
I understand your
enthusiasm. But be careful
not to misinterpret the
Head Captain's intention.
I shall leave you now.
Koga Kuchiki. I don't
know why he was chosen,
but the Head Captain
has picked him to head
up the Special Task Force.
We're close to restoring
order within the Soul Society.
If he continues to
accumulate power, it will
be difficult for our faction
to override his position...
That's right. He's
already surpassed his
contemporaries.
At this point, there may
not be anything we can do.
Not true. I
have a plan.
Sir Koga...!
It's over!
The rebellion's been put
down!
You did it, Sir Koga!
What is this?!
Have you
gone mad?!
Koga Kuchiki, our master has
decided that you shall die as
a casualty of war!
I am ready for
you. Attack.
We will!
You're finished!
You won't defeat me with
sheer numbers!
Mukojochu! Muramasa!
What's he doing?!
Is that--?!
Who the hell
is that guy?!
I doesn't
matter! Get him!
Hear my voice.
What's happening?!
My Zanpakuto...!
What the hell?
Who are these guys?!
They're manifestations of
each of your Zanpakuto!
They have heard my voice,
and it has awakened the
desires within their
consciousness...
What?!
You will be unable to
touch us, and in a few
moments, you will die at
the hands of your own
individual weapons.
It appears everything's
been settled.
Yes.
Don't move!
What is this?
We have you surrounded,
Koga Kuchiki!
You have finally gone too
far, Sir Koga! These
warriors are not part
of the rebel faction!
They were members of
the Court Guard Squads!
Is it true?! Did you
attack and kill your
own allies during this
battle?!
That would have been
absurd! Of course not!
They showed up out of
nowhere and attacked me,
so I defended myself...
Koga. What
have you done?!
Sir Genrei!
It's a good thing you
came by. This is a bad
situation!
Your son-in-law Koga, who
married into the Kuchiki
Clan, has murdered his
fellow Soul Reapers!
It's true... He
attacked us!
He had no provocation.
We just wanted to ask
him a few questions.
He did it to show off
his power in front of
the other Soul Reapers!
You're lying!
He's out of control, I
tell you! He's mad with
power!
You bastard!
Arrest him! Arrest Koga
Kuchiki and take him away!
Just wait! Listen,
this is not what happened!
What now, Koga?
Damn it!
Stop, Koga!
Just stand still Don't
make any sudden moves.
Sir Genrei!
But why?
Do as they
say for now.
Koga...?
Koga. Your punishment has
been decided. They asked
me to come and tell you
in person.
After much discussion, it
was decided that you will be
deprived of the position you
have held for the last century.
Your Zanpakuto has been
deemed dangerous, and
will be neutralized.
What?!
Sir Ginrei, you can't be
serious! Do you believe
these accusations?
Do you think I killed
those men just to satisfy
my own ambition?!
You should know that
I'm not one to make
rash decisions.
Right...
Your superiors are
not worried about you...
They believe that the
power of your Zanpakuto
is an urgent and growing
problem.
They believe that
Muramasa will eventually
gain control over you.
What?! They're worried
about Muramasa?!
As I told you before,
Koga, those with power
must have a heart that is
sensitive to its limitations.
You were overconfident in
your Zanpakuto's powers,
and you were blindly making
the wrong decisions.
You lost balance. And
that is the reason Sir
Genryusai placed you
under his direct command.
This is unbelievable! I
was set up by those who
were jealous of my power!
No!
You are wrong! It was
your overconfidence that
brought all this about!
What choice did I have?!
The men who confronted me
were there to kill me!
They made that perfectly
clear! What, was I supposed
to stand there and be murdered?!
Calm yourself.
There's still time until
your punishment is carried
out. Use that time to show
some patience.
It might be hard to
understand, but this
will do you good.
I hope he was
paying attention.
Either way, I must do
something quickly. If I
don't, the boy will indeed
lose his powers.
And the end result
will be catastrophic!
I don't get it!
He completely dismisses
me! My own father-in-law!
He doesn't respect my
power! He doesn't
believe in me!
The fact is, you don't
need him to believe in
you. Believe in me.
And more importantly...
believe in yourself.
Muramasa! How? How have
you manifested?!
I'm here because of you.
Your anger, your inner
desire, has reached out
to me...
...and I came.
My desire?
When you call to me,
Koga, I'm compelled to go
wherever you are. I am your
Zanpakuto, after all...
You must live.. and
follow your desires.
What's happening?!
Let's go... Koga.
You don't need to abide
by the rules of a world
that despises and envies
your power.
There's a simple solution.
You should use that power
to change the world.
Let me make one thing
clear, Muramasa
I am the master
here.
And as such,
I am in charge!
I will not be ordered
around... by a Zanpakuto!
Damn it, he was able
to revive him!
Let's move, Ichigo!
Right!
He is powerful.
It's amazing. How can
the man still have so
much power...
... after being sealed
away for so long?!
You've awakened...
Finally!
Koga. I've waited for
this moment for so long.
Together, we can now
complete the task we began
all those years ago...
Mura... masa.
Why... Koga?!
In the next episode,
you'll witness our
perfect teamwork!
We're not ready to give
in to the younger
generations yet!
We encourage you to join
our fan clubs!
If you sign up now,
you'll get a special
invitation to our secret
concert!
Are there any other
membership benefits?!