The Zanpakuto... Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined
by its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper,
and dies with its Soul
Reaper.
That is the existence
of a Zanpakuto.
Damn it! He was able to
revive him.
Let's move, Ichigo!
Right!
He is powerful!
It's amazing---How can
the man still have so
much power...
...after being sealed
away for so long?
You've awakened...
finally!
Koga, I've waited for
this moment for so long.
Together, we can now
complete the task we
began all those years
ago.
Mura... masa.
Why... Koga?
About now, I'd say Koga
must be feeling pretty
frustrated, having been
locked away in a dark
prison cell somewhere.
[chuckling]
What a shame, but it
serves him right.
[chuckling]
That's very true.
Remember how proudly he
used to boast to everyone
about his power?
I bet he isn't boasting
anymore. I just wish I
could see his defeat with
my own eyes.
[chuckling]
That's so mean of you!
I must tell you... When I
first heard about this plan,
I had serious doubts about
whether or not it would work.
However... He fell for
it hook, line, and sinker.
[chuckling]
He won't be bothering us
anymore.
You're right. He's now
irrelevant!
What's the problem?
Huh?
[terrified reax]
Koga!
What?! Koga!
How did you--?!
Pardon the interruption!
What is it?
Sir! Third Seat Kuchiki
broke out of the barracks
jailhouse!
He killed the three Soul
Reapers who had him
arrested---He cut them to
pieces.
Are you satisfied?
Was it not enough?
No. When I think back
about what they did, it
still makes my blood
boil.
It's time for us to
forget.
Those men are no longer
around to torture you.
Let's use this opportunity
to forget the
past, and live our lives
looking forward.
Sir Ginrei...
Stop, Koga...
You must know why I've
come looking for you.
Tell me... why did
you have to kill
those men?
I presume you must have
had a reason!
Because they betrayed me.
And they did it on purpose!
I thought they were
misguided. I assumed
they made a mistake about
my intentions, and were
feeling guilty about
their behavior...
I was wrong!
They knew what they had
done, and were laughing
about it!
Killing them was the only
option!
But it didn't help.
Even though it was just,
it didn't make the empty
feeling go away!
I still feel like an
outcast! And what am I
supposed to do now?!
By your actions, you've
lost any chance of proving
your innocence before a
tribunal.
If you had reflected on
your situation, and remained
in your cell until a proper
investigation could be
conducted, you might
have had a chance.
Locked iIn a cell?!Why
should I have done that?
I didn't do anything!
You may not have done
anything at first...
that is true.
But what about your
actions now?
You may even have
had good cause...
But you committed the grave
crime of killing men whose
swords were not drawn.
It's likely you
will be put to death.
I am well aware of the
tremendous scope of your
abilities.
However, you still lack
the heart to make the
most effective use of
those powers.
You were not set up---It
was your overconfidence
that brought all this
about.
You bear the name of our
clan. And responsibility
for your actions taken on
its behalf.
[screaming]
Ginrei....
Hmmm?
I get it now.
You have the same
attitude!
You're just like those
other men!
You pretend you're on my
side! You 'befriend'
me! Put me off-guard!
However... That's not
how you really feel!
The truth is you hate me!
/You and the others are
jealous of my power!
Koga!
Whisper... Muramasa!
Ginrei! You bastard!
You can't escape so
easily! Undo that
barrier!
Damn!
Well, fine! I can
wait! I'll just save
killing you for last!
I have big plans! There
are plenty of others I
need to kill!
What happened to my
sword?
Koga... Koga....
Koga...
Why is your soul in such
an agitated state?
I'm surrounded by
enemies.
It's obvious everyone
hates me. I'll have to
kill them, all of them.
I have to do whatever is
necessary to survive.
You should try and forget
about the past. It's better
for you to live your life
looking forward.
Why does everyone around
here hate me so much?
Is it because they're all
jealous of my power?
Koga.. Let's you and I
create a new world.
I'll help you do it!
That has to be the
reason... they wanna
bring me down.
I'll just have to strike
back at them first.
Koga...?
There's only one way to
deal... (voice fades...)
Koga...
I can't hear your voice.
[laughing]
Now whisper...
Muramasa!
Muramasa... that's
an order!
Head Captain, I have
news. As of yesterday,
Koga Kuchiki has killed
several dozen Soul Reapers.
Because of his unique
abilities, even veteran
squad members seem to
have no defense against
his assaults. They lose
control of their swords,
and are unable to fight
back.
There is one defense.
The only way to resist
and overcome Koga's
illusion-type Zanpakuto,
is to understand the
nature of his power, and
close your mind to the
assault at the moment
he turns it on you.
But in order to
effectively block his
attack, one must possess
considerable Spiritual
Energy, and an
unyielding mental
fortitude.
Aside from myself, if
there is one other person
in our ranks who could
cross swords with Koga,
while holding off the
effects of his powerful
Zanpakuto, we might have
a chance to defeat him.
Volunteers?
In that case, we have no
choice. I shall personally
help you seal Koga away.
Koga...?
Oh, it's you.
Why did you kill all
those innocent people in
the Rukon District?
The reason was simple.
I wanted to send a clear
message to the Soul
Society.
A message? What for?
To show the hopelessness
of ostracizing me from
this world. And to show
everyone how helpless the
Soul Reapers are in the
face of my power.
[chuckling]
To accomplish that, you
go out and kill innocent
people on the street?
I don't see why that's
necessary to help create
our vision of an ideal
new world.
It seems pretty
excessive.
"Our vision...?"
What do you mean by the
word 'our'? You've got
a lot of nerve!
Tell me something---Do
you actually consider
yourself my equal?
Koga...
Let me remind you, you're
my sword! So don't get
too cocky!
Just do as you're
told and keep your
mouth shut!
You're obviously
exhausted. You
should rest.
Stop talking! You're
nothing but a sword, so
quit trying to give me
orders!
Well, well---What brings
you two senior citizens
out in the rain?
Let me guess---Did you
come to kneel down before
my power?
Apparently, that's not
the reason.
Koga...
Weren't you always planning
to use your power to help
make your ideals come true?
Ideals? Don't make me
laugh... There are no
ideals in this world.
We're all left with only
one thing... The despair
of not being able to make
those ideals come true.
But... I've now
discovered that despair
releases my true power.
Despair is the force that
breaks my shackles and frees
my heart to do as it truly
wishes!
Koga... you are
greatly misguided.
Those with power are the
ones who get to impose
order on this world!
And in the midst of
chaos, that order
prevails, right or wrong!
If that power is
victorious. Even if it's
dark, black will become
the color of what's right!
Koga...
You're wasting your time,
Ginrei...
This man is completely
consumed by power!
He can no longer
hear what you're saying!
How interesting! I
always hoped I'd have the
chance to cut the two of
you down to size, one day!
Tell me, Ginrei, do you plan
to close off your mind again
in order to fight me this time?
I'll let you know now that
you won't be able to use
all of your strength that
way!
Bakudo Four... Hainawa!
Have you forgotten, Koga?
I know the extent of your
powers better than anyone
else in the Soul Society.
Damn you all...!
Whisper...
...Muramasa!
What's the matter with
you? I command you to
appear!
I am your master, and I
order you to release!
Muramasa! I know you can
hear me!
You're my sword, and you
must do as I say!
Something's gone wrong
with Koga's powers!
We have to strike! At
once!
Yes!
When you're
ready... Ginrei.
Right!
Good!
Shiso... keppu!
[screaming]
Forgive me...
Muramasa!!!!
Koga...
Tell me, Koga. Why did
you...
...do this to me?
What the hell?
What in the world
is going on?
Koga...?
You never... answered
me when I called.
When I was on the verge
of being sealed away, I
called for you.
But I never heard that
call!
I called over and over,
but you never came to my
aid.
How could it be? I
didn't hear you? Koga...
Your voice did not reach
me. Not even one time.
And there I was,
waiting so patiently
to receive your call.
If I had heard even one
word, I would have come
to you at any time.
I would have assisted you
with all the power within
me. That is how I felt.
But for so long... I
never heard your voice.
Eventually, of course,
I learned that you had
been sealed away.
You have to believe me
Koga, from that time to
this... every day...
...I've tried to break
that seal.
If you had been there in
the first place, I would
never have been sealed
away!
As a Soul Reaper and your
master, I was the one who
gave birth to your power!
All you ever needed to do
in your life after that,
was simply obey me!
But Koga... weren't
we both of one spirit?
One spirit...?
To me, you've always been
nothing more than a sword!
Simply a tool of mine!
And a mere tool shouldn't
be so conceited!
Koga, you call your own
Zanpakuto nothing but a
tool, and then you try to
kill it...?
Disgraceful---You have no
right to call yourself a
Soul Reaper.
I don't get it. Muramasa
wanted Koga, Koga stabbed
him, then Byakuya appeared.
What's the deal?
You can straighten it all
out when Senbonzakura
explains it to you. Even a
monkey can understand him.
A brilliant idea, thank
you so much, Byakuya.
Wait a minute, he's
makin' fun of us!