The Final Getsugatensho,
Is about me,
becoming Getsuga itself.
Mugetsu.
Repair work complete!
Final check!
Number one thousand
ninety seven, okay!
Numbers one thousand ninety
eight, one thousand ninety
nine, and one thousand one
hundred, Okay!
We've secured every member
of the World of the Living
within the boundaries of
the Tenkaiketchu!
Hmpf. Preparing to
activate Tenkaiketchu.
Just a minute, sir, you
can't do this yet!
There are still squad
members left in the town!
Bringing them to the World
of the Living without a
Senkaimon is dangerous!
[sigh] I guess I have
no choice. I'll count
slowly from ten.
Honestly, sometimes
my indulgence makes
me sick!
Ruuuun! Hurry,
before we all
get killed!
Ten...!
Nine...!
Eight...!
Seven...!
Here comes six...!
Then five...!
Captain, we need to confirm
the safety of the World of
the Living side, as well!
And four...!
Three...!
Aah!
Two...!
One!
[in unison]
Please don't press
that button!
What in the world do you
people think you're doing?
[in unison]
Please don't, Captain!
Think about the consequences!
Be patient a while longer!
[frustrated]
Rrrrrgh!
I don't give a damn about the
slowpokes on the other side! I'm
going to activate it right now!
[in unison]
Have mercy, Captain!
I'm finished. That should
do it for the time being.
You say 'for the time being'!
You mean she might not make it?
What I can do with Kido
is really no different
from medical treatment.
We've completely
healed the body.
Eventually, as long as
she doesn't give up her
will to live, she will
regain consciousness.
As to whether or not her
will is strong enough,
Well, you know her a
lot better than I.
You have more insight
into her state of mind.
Thank you, Unohana.
Why are you thanking me?
You must know that a
thank-you isn't necessary,
for saving a friend.
What makes you think
we're friends, you fool?!
Well, I'm sure that's
what Hiyori would say.
Thank you so
much, Unohana.
[Chojiro]
Listen to me, everyone!
Huh?
You have to get
away from this
place, quickly!
It's Captain Kurotsuchi!
He's about to activate
the Tenkaiketchu!
It's very dangerous here!
[Kurotsuchi]
Egh! Agh!
Let go of me!
If you don't let go right now,
I'll use all of you as guinea
pigs, and put you through the
worst kind of horrors!
Back! Back!
[electronic squeaking]
Huh?
Rrrgh!
Are you trying to make a
fool of me?! Give me back
the real switch right
this minute you morons!
[in unison]
Please wait a little
longer! Just a
little longer, sir!
[in unison]
Captain Zaraki!
Captain Kuchiki!
[in unison]
Welcome back, sirs!
[giggles]
What about me,
you turkey!?
I was on the mission
too, you know!
Don't you think I'm
also important enough
to welcome home?
Who do you
think you are!
I'm sorry!
[in unison]
We're glad to see your
safe return, sirs!
Med crew, stat!
They're walking, but
they've been injured!
Welcome back home!
Good to see you, sir!
Y'aaahh!
Sorry! So sorry!
I apologize!
I'm sorry for
coming back here!
Lieutenant Kotetsu!
Seventh Seat Yamada!
A job well done!
Huuh?
You may have been just
supporting, but you
didn't hesitate when you
stormed into Hueco Mundo!
Very impressive work!
[soul reapers, in unison]
Good job, sirs!
Uh, heh-heh. Actually, I
got knocked out as soon as
I got there, so I really
didn't get to do much.
Captain!
Tell me, if you don't mind,
how did the battle go?
Captain...?
Yeah.
[small dog yapping]
Mmh.
[small whimpers]
[yaps]
[Yammy]
What the hell did
you come here for?
Dumb dog.
[yaps]
[whines]
[whimpers]
I have to say,
it was a lousy battle.
[Kisuke]
Ichigo.
Hm?
Kisuke. Where is everyone?
I sent them
all back home.
The truth is, they all wanted
to speak to you, Ichigo.
But it seemed they were very
hesitant to approach you.
You didn't erase their
memories, did you?
No. Well, not this time, anyway.
I follow you.
That's a good thing.
I was tired of hiding
it all from them.
When I get back, I'll explain
things to each one, personally.
The Cross Seal
containing Aizen was
taken to the Seireitei.
As I understand it,
Central 46 will make a decision
shortly on his disposition.
I see.
Why the sad look?
You should be happy
that it's all over.
I'm not really
sure, frankly.
I'm having a lot
of mixed emotions.
You saved everyone's life,
and this entire world,
All because you were willing
to risk everything to stop
Aizen which you accomplished.
I know that.
You did the right thing, Ichigo,
believe me. There's no reason
for you to regret anything.
There was no other way.
So, let me ask.
About Aizen.
Is it true that
he was really...
...rejected by the Hogyoku?
My old man told me that
the Hogyoku's power
is to take in the heart of
the people surrounding it,
and then manifest
their heart's desires.
If that turns out to be
the case, could it be
that Aizen lost his
powers by his own choice?
When I battled Aizen,
I finally had enough power to
be able to feel his sword.
And I can tell you with
certainty, there was nothing
but loneliness in that weapon.
It's very sad, when you think
about the implications.
If his powers were superior
from the time he was born,
perhaps he's been searching
all these years for someone
he could regard as his equal.
It must have been
frustrating at first
and then just depressing.
At some point,
he must have given up thinking
he would ever find such a being.
I imagine he's been wishing,
somewhere very deep in his
heart,
that he could once again
become a simple Soul Reaper,
like the others.
[Orihime]
Is that... Ichigo?
Hm?
Orihime! Uryu! Rukia!
Chad! Renji!
I'm surprised to see you.
Is it all right for you
to be up so soon?
Don't project your own
weakness on me, Ichigo.
Thanks, but it's not
really an issue.
Are you all right?
You look a
little different.
[sniffle]
It's really you, right, Ichigo?
[sniff] Your hair has
gotten so long.
[sniff] I thought maybe for a
minute, it was somebody else who
was standing there.
[sniff] I'm glad...
I'm so glad.
[sobbing]
Come on now, Orihime,
there's no need to cry.
Is my hair that bad?
I'll get it cut, if
that will help.
[gasp]
Ichigo!
[Rukia]
Ichigo?! What's going on?
Talk to me!
[choking, gasping]
[scream of pain]
HRRAAAAGHH!
We will now pass judgment!
Former Squad 5 Captain,
Sosuke Aizen!
We sentence you to the
lowest level of Underground
Prison 8, 'Muken'.
where you will remain
for 18,800 years!
Oh, really?
Hm?
Interesting. The likes of you,
passing judgment on me.
It strikes me as a bit comical.
Rrrgh!
Incredible! You believe
you can sit there and
push your luck, just
because you're immortal?!
We don't have to listen to this!
Restrain his mouth and eyes!
The years of your sentence are
increased, to twenty thousand!
Just what he deserves!
Lock him up forever!
[Yamamoto]
You idiots!
Each of you is telling me you
lost your Captain's coat?!
Damaging it is one thing,
but losing it is outrageous!
How can the three of you
stand there, looking so
nonchalant about it?!
Really, Head Captain...
You make too much
of the situation.
In the end, they were
just cheap coats.
We will pay for them
to be replaced.
You think that's going to
resolve the situation?
That's not even the
primary thing I'm
concerned about here!
And by the way, for your
information, you smug
know-it-all, those coats
were anything but cheap!
Battles are not
just about winning!
What do you people
think the captain's
coat is, anyway?!
A royal pain.
A cheap garment.
A fashion statement?
You're nothing but a bunch
of ignorant baboons!
The Head Captain seems
to be in good spirits.
You're right.
[Yamamoto]
Now listen up!
[Jushiro]
It's been ten days since he
lost his left arm in battle.
I was worried that he would see
himself as crippled, and lose
his spiritual vitality.
But his strength seems
to be back, so that's
been a relief to me.
There's no Soul Reaper here
who'd be able to take his place.
Captain!
Captain Kurotsuchi,
where are you?
Sorry, the Captain's not here.
He went to Hueco Mundo to
research something.
Again?! What am I
supposed to do?
Maybe you can help.
So, Lieutenant Hinamori's
been left in our care for as
long as it takes to heal her
internal injuries, right?
Well, Lieutenant Matsumoto's
here to pay her a visit, and
I'm not sure what I'm
supposed to do.
[Akon]
Lieutenant Hinamori is
not allowed any visitors.
Besides, we cannot allow
outsiders into the research
facility when Captain
Kurotsuchi isn't here.
I'm sorry, Lieutenant Matsumoto,
but you're not really--
Hm?
I don't see her anywhere.
What happened?
Huaah!
This isn't good enough!
At this rate--
At this rate, I'll fail!
I'll never be strong
enough to protect Momo!
I have to keep practicing!
Whatever it takes to become more
adept at using my own Bankai!
Haaaaaaaa!
[Rangiku]
You've gone away.
And you didn't even
leave behind a keepsake
to remember you by.
That's exactly the type of
thing I didn't like about you.
[gasp]
Everyone's moving on.
[Rangiku]
Neither Shuhei nor Renji
were at the barracks.
They must be somewhere,
brushing up on their
skills and strength.
I need to do the same thing.
You're right, of course.
You had to make a clean break.
If you had left behind a
momento, it would have probably
kept me from moving forward.
And that would
be terrible.
You must have seen that weakness
in me, and knew the only path
you could take was separation.
Thank you, Gin, for being
strong. Now that I think back on
it, that is exactly what I...
...loved about you.
[gasp]
[Orihime]
Ichigo!
Where am I?
We brought you
to my house.
Huh?
What happened to
your injuries?
We all healed a
long time ago.
What are you talking about?
You've been unconscious for
the last ten days, Ichigo.
You've gotta be kidding.
[gasp]
My powers,
are they gone?
[Rukia]
Don't worry.
They haven't
faded away yet.
So you already know.
Yes. Kisuke told
us everything.
I see.
Are you all right, Ichigo?
It was very strange.
At the moment we all reunited,
you collapsed, and we had
no idea what happened.
Ichigo!
Are you okay?!
Ichigo! Can you talk?
Open your eyes!
Captain Urahara.
Do you know
what's happened
to Ichigo?
If you do know, please tell us!
Is he going to be all right?
According to what
Kisuke said,
there are several stages you
can expect to go through,
in the course of losing
your Spirit Energy.
What did he tell you?
Everything. First you
lose consciousness,
and the time that
your body spent inside the
Precipice World immediately
begins to flow in reverse.
Did you notice your
hair is shorter?
Your height has returned to
what it used to be, and your
Spirit Energy is stable now.
And of course, you
still retain your
Soul Reaper powers.
Eventually, however...
It will move to
the next stage.
When that happens, there won't
be any question, because he will
black out once more, this time
accompanied by intense pain.
When he regains
consciousness,
he'll have lost all his
Soul Reaper powers.
That could happen next week,
next month, or a
year from now.
Even I don't know how long
his current state of
instability will continue.
Oh well. When that
time comes, it comes.
Ichigo, are you--?
Don't worry, I'll be
all right, Orihime.
More importantly,
I'm glad all of
you are okay.
Wait a minute!
What the hell are
you talking about?!
How can you act like it's
nothing?! You're about to lose
your Spirit Energy, you know!
Come on, Uryu.
Ugh!
Heh. I got into this, knowing
all the consequences.
I have no regrets
about what I did.
Okay then.
[Ichigo]
Anyway, now that
we're all healed up,
I guess there's no
reason for us to hang
around here, right?
We should head on back
to Karakura Town.
Everyone there is
probably waiting for us.
[Byakuya]
Head Captain.
[Yamamoto]
What is it?
[Byakuya]
As an apology,
I had someone make
you a new coat.
[Yamamoto]
You still don't get the
issue here, do you?
[Byakuya]
I had it assembled by the
finest craftsmen, using
the very best materials.
[Yamamoto]
Very well. In that case,
I guess I'll keep it.