[Aizen]
Yes, it's true. This is
an inexcusable breach,
isn't it, Hogyoku?
I'll show you my Final...
Getsugatensho!
Impossible!
He caught it?!
[Ichigo]
You look surprised.
Does that scare you?
That something you can't
comprehend, happened right
before your eyes?
And you couldn't stop it?
[chuckling]
Heh heh heh heh he.
Hado Number 90!
Kurohitsugi!
[Aizen]
A full incantation Kurohitsugi
performed by one who transcends
both Hollow and Soul Reaper!
[Ichigo]
You still haven't realized it,
have you?
The power I have is
greater than the power you
possess, even right now.
[gasp]
[Ichigo]
What an odd reaction.
When I backed away from
you in our last battle,
you stopped and asked me why.
Now you're doing the
exact same thing.
So let me ask you
the same question.
Aizen, why did you
back away just now?
I get it now.
You're pleased that you
stopped my sword, aren't you?
I assume, then,
that you're also
pleased that you
overcame my Kido!
I suppose that you're
equally pleased that you
put a scar on my body!
Well don't be so full
of yourself! Human!
Rauughh!
[heartbeat]
[choking gurgles]
[heartbeat intensifies]
[Aizen]
[big roar]
Rwaaaaaaaaa!!
AAAAAAAAAHH!
[Aizen] [Hollow voice]
Yes, it's true.
This is an
inexcusable breach,
isn't it, Hogyoku?
That I, with my power,
should allow a human to
get the better of me.
- Augh!
- Aah!
- Oof!
Ichigo!
I see you were able to
withstand my attack with
very little damage.
However, your left arm
is no longer usable.
[growl]
Can you hear me,
Ichigo Kurosaki?
I have to give you credit.
For one brief moment, you
broke the boundary between
Hollow and Soul Reaper, to
become a transcendent being.
But that power is no more!
It has completely dissipated,
and not a trace of it remains!
You're not even worth trying
to understand any more.
Now it's my turn.
I, a true transcendent being,
will cause your death!
I must say, it will
be quite a victory!
By eliminating you,
I will completely
break free!
From Soul Reapers and
Hollows alike! It's over!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Is it, Aizen?
Huah??
This the best you can do?
Aizen. Let's end
this already.
All this
rambling you do.
Well.
I'm sick of it.
So prepare yourself.
I'll show you my Final,
Getsugatensho!
What is that...
What is that form
he's taking?!
You still refuse to
stay down, Ichigo?
I told you already I
won't accept defeat.
Not until you describe to me
the nature of the Final
Getsugatensho!
I have no intention
of telling you,
As I already said!
[Ichigo]
Something's not right.
If he were really serious
about killing me in battle,
he could have accomplished
it before now.
I was never a match for
him in any confrontation.
There was that great a
difference between our powers.
If he has no serious
intention of telling me,
he should stop fighting,
and keep himself hidden.
It would have been easy
for him to just do that.
[Ichigo]
I don't understand.
He has me at a
complete disadvantage.
So why is it I only sense
sadness flowing from his blade?
Hm.
[gasp]
[Zangetsu]
You finally figured it out.
The only way to acquire the
Final Getsugatensho was to
give up all resistance and
accept my blade.
I feel no pain.
Of course not. You still
don't understand, do you?
I, Tensa Zangetsu,
am part of you.
If you accept me, there
can be no pain when I
run you through.
Why are you crying then?
Because of the path
you have now chosen.
Ichigo. Do you recall
what I said when we
first fought?
You need to
understand something.
What you want to protect,
Ichigo, is not the same thing
that I want to protect.
Right.
What I wanted to protect,
was always you, Ichigo.
[gasp]
What do you mean?
The answer will be conveyed
directly through this blade,
along with the
technique's secret.
Ichigo, if you use this
technique, you will...
The Final Getsugatensho,
is about me,
becoming Getsuga itself.
Now I understand.
If I use this technique,
I will lose all of my Soul
Reaper powers.
That's what
'Final' means.
[Aizen]
I still can't sense his power.
I have evolved into a
being far beyond that
of a Soul Reaper.
Just as two-dimensional beings
can never interact with
three-dimensional beings,
No Soul Reaper or human
will be able to detect my
Spiritual Pressure,
unless I deliberately
bring my powers down to
their level of awareness.
Wait a minute!
If that is the case...
Then that means...
he is at an even
higher level...
than myself?
Rrrgh!
No, no, no, no, no, noooo!
It's absurd! A mere
human can't surpass me!
It couldn't possibly be!
[gasp]
Mugetsu.
[Zangetsu]
These are my final
words for you:
If you use this technique,
you will lose all of your
Soul Reaper powers!
Farewell... Ichigo.
[small gasp]
He's still able to regenerate?
Damn!
My Soul Reaper powers,
...are disappearing!
[groan]
Mmmmrrahh...
Ichigo Kurosaki.
You've lost this battle.
Observe.
My Zanpakuto is fading away.
I assume you know
what that means.
The Hogyoku has determined
that I will no longer have
any need for a Zanpakuto!
Like you, I have become one with
the Zanpakuto and its power!
However, you no longer
have that power!
So watch as I reach a
level that will be
far beyond yours!
It's all over,
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Huh??
What the hell is happening?!
Is it a Kido?!
I don't get it!
When was
I attacked?!
[Kisuke]
It seems it's
finally taking
effect.
Tch!
[Ichigo]
Kisuke!
Kisuke Urahara!
Are you responsible
for all this?
Yes.
I set up this offensive
before you were able to
completely transform.
When you were most vulnerable,
I planted that Kido onto another
Kido and shot it into your body.
Rrgh.
What I put in you is a seal.
I knew that once you fused
with the Hogyoku,
killing you would end up
being very difficult,
if not impossible.
So I was forced to invent a new
Kido, which possessed the
capability of sealing you off.
Is that so? Too bad.
I hate to disappoint you!
But, at this moment, I'm
about to evolve even further
than you can imagine!
As much as you think you're
in control of things,
You won't be able to seal me
off with this level of Kido!
What?!
What's happening to me?!
[shaky, choked breaths]
It is the
Hogyoku's will.
The reason the seal I
shot into you is only
now taking effect,
is because your powers
have started to weaken.
This is all thanks to Ichigo.
The seal was able to take
effect because he fought
so hard, and pushed you
to your limit.
The Hogyoku is saying
that it does not recognize
you as its master.
You're wrong!
It can't be, it's impossible!
I control this power!
D'aaghh!
[pained groans]
Urahara...
Kisuke Urahara! Do you know
how much I despise you?!
With your great intellect,
why is it you don't take
independent action?!
Why in the world is it that
you choose to subjugate
yourself to that thing?!
When you say 'that thing',
Are you talking about
the Soul King?
I see. So you saw it,
didn't you?
Without the existence of the
Soul King, The Soul Society
would split into pieces.
The Soul King is the
keystone to it all.
Without that keystone in place,
the system would fall apart.
That, my friend,
is how the world
works.
That's an argument only
a loser would make!
A victor should speak of
how the world should be!
Rather than how the world
currently operates!
I refuse to accept a world
ruled by that thing!
I am a victor;
I shall decide how
the world should be!
Ichigo...
It's over,
isn't it,
Ichigo.
[Ichigo]
Hey, Kisuke.
Training in the Precipice
World has made me physically
older by a bit, right?
[Kisuke]
You could easily say that,
I suppose.
[Ichigo]
Oh yeah! It's not a bad feeling,
being more mature than my
friends.
[Kisuke]
Although, when you think about
it, it means you're an old man
compared to the others.
[Ichigo]
Damn...!