The Zanpakuto. It's unique
shape an abilities are defined
by its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able to
harness the power of the
Zanpakuto, by learning its
name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born with
its Soul Reaper and dies with
its Soul Reaper.
That is the existence of
a Zanpakuto.
It's no good. I can't
sense any Spiritual Pressure.
This is outrageous! What
are you planning to do,
Captain Kurotsuchi?
Nothing that really
affects you at this
point.
Silence, Lieutenant! I'm
just going to run some tests
on this sample in order to
figure out what caused the
Zanpakuto rebellion
Nemu...
Sir...
Let's begin,
shall we?
Please! Hold on
for a second!
Let's talk about this! You
might wanna re-think it a
little more!
What will happen to my
Zanpakuto if you just
cut him up?!
You know, that's a very
good question. I don't
have the answer, but we
can test to find out.
Here we go...
Come on, stop
this, just stop!
What is
it now?
He may just be a lab sample
to you, but at the moment,
he's the only Zanpakuto
we've captured!
Think about what you're doing!
He's all we've got,
shouldn't we treat him
a little better?!
Mm-hm--Mm-hm!
You're beginning
to annoy me.
I guess we have no choice.
Nemu...
Yes, Master
Mayuri.
Who are you aiming at?!
Don't point that thing
at me!
You're a crazy girl
stabbing at me like that!
Did you forget, I'm not
the one you should be
cutting open?
He's the one you're
supposed to slice up!
Sorry, pal The deal's
off. Better you than me!
Oh! That's amazing! You can
understand what your Zanpakuto
is saying
even though he's
been gagged?
The connection between a
Soul Reaper and his
manifested Zanpakuto
is more intricate and complex
than we had ever imagined.
Yeah, that's very true! It
isn't easy to comprehend us!
It could take many, many
years of research, and
then you could still be
way off-base.
Why bother? Experimenting
on us is going to be a big
waste of energy.
That's not necessarily
true.
Huh?!
I believe he's dead.
What do you mean? How
can he be dead?!
What are you going to do
about my Zanpakuto?! I
want him back!
According to the reports, when
a Zanpakuto is killed by its
owner, it reverts back to its
normal state.
Yeah?
But not this time. You
see, it appears that when
someone other than the
Zanpakuto's owner kills
it, a whole different set
of rules apply.
Wait a minute! Don't walk
away from me! I'm the owner!
Keep your voice down.
You must be quiet in the
lab.
Why do you keep pointing
that thing in my face and
exactly why should
I keep it down?
Be quiet.
That's dangerous! Get
away from me!
Be quiet.
Back off! Get
away! Noooo!
Well, it certainly looks like
I'm going to have a lot of
difficult, but intriguing
work ahead of me.
Come on! Pay attention!
We want out! You hear me?!
You women are very mean
and nasty!
How can you keep your own
Zanpakuto locked up in here
like we're some kind
of circus animals?!
Yeah, what she said!
I was hoping they'd be
quiet after we caught
them.
Just take them both away,
please, and deliver them
to Squad Four's barracks.
Yes, ma'am, no problem.
We'll get them to the Squad
Four Barracks safely.
Hey, what do you think you're
doing?! You can't just let us
be taken away like this!
You cruel and heartless
monsters! Hey!
Ugh! I can't hear
what you're saying!
We should go
as well.
Oh, you're right. We
shouldn't waste anymore time
here. Come on.
You ready?
Yeah.
Rangiku...
Maybe I'm mistaken, but
I'm not sensing anything.
Yeah, I know what
you're saying.
I can't sense the Captain's
Spiritual Pressure either.
I know he's not dead, but
where is he?
Let's hurry!
Right!
Huh?
Wow! Wasn't I wasn't
expecting that...
Are you okay?
I'm just fine, thanks for
asking. I feel quite comfy.
Glad you're comfortable, but
can you get off me?!
Oh, hey Ichigo. I wondered
what happened to you.
That explains why I
didn't get hurt.
Would you mind moving? You're
no lightweight, you know.
How rude! Watch your mouth!
Don't speak to a lady like that!
Toshiro?
Yes. Is my captain all
right?
Yeah, you don't have to worry.
My master hit me with all
of his strength.
It restored my memory, but
it took a toll on him.
Let him rest
for a while.
Honestly, my captain
sure is hopeless.
I know, but I figure he
must be relieved now. Good
for him.
My body still isn't
accustomed to Vasto Lordes.
Well. So we meet again.
I knew you'd come looking
for me. Ichigo Kurosaki.
Huh?
What is that supposed
to mean?
Whether you choose to admit
it or not, you know we are
linked to one another.
You think that we're
linked?
That's correct. Your power will
be very valuable in helping me
to achieve a long term goal.
I'm sure you know what I
mean...
If not--let me remind you
that your excess power
doesn't have anywhere to
go.
What are you talking about?
As far as I'm concerned, I
know one thing.
I'm determined to defeat you.
That is the only business I
have with you.
How foolish.
What is he doing? Is he
trying to take control of
Zangetsu again?
Do not worry!
He no longer has even the
least bit of control over
my mind.
He speaks directly to one
subconscious, but now that I
know his voice...
His corruption will not have
an effect on me. I am now
immune to his influence.
So, just let him try and see
how far he gets.
How very strange, it looks
like you're no longer afraid
to face me.
That will be a
fatal mistake.
Something's wrong
with that guy.
Not only is he acting
weird, but his Spiritual
Pressure is unstable, as
well.
I am not as incapacitated
as you think.
Dammit, not
this again.
What did he
just do?
What happened?
I've gone stiff!
It's useless.
What?!
What's going on?
This power isn't
enough to sustain me!
What?
Are... you a...
...Zanpakuto?
Looks like you're right.
Tell me now! Whose
Zanpakuto are you?!
So you refuse to
answer me, huh?
You will find out
soon enough.
Scatter...
His Spiritual Pressure.
Senbonzakura!
Scatter...
It's Byakuya's!
Bakudo Number
Thirty-Nine! Enkosen!
Watch out!
I sure haven't forgotten
that power.
Byakuya's Zanpakuto
Senbonzakura!
So you remember me.
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Whoa!
Yeah, I sense it too.
There was a sudden rise
in Spiritual Pressure.
I've felt this pressure
before.
Me too. If I'm
not mistaken...
Yeah, it has to
be Captain Kuchiki.
Hey, look.
Sorry, we didn't know
you were here, sir.
What is this?
What do you think
he's here for?
Wait, why are
you... doing this?
Stand back.
Hmph!
It all makes sense now. Your
Spiritual Pressure's the same
as Byakuya's.
Which means you're the one
who attacked me last
night, right?
You don't want to give me
an answer?
Fine with me.
There you are!
Did you really think you
could defeat me with such
a cheap trick?
Not even close!
Not very impressive.
Brings back memories...
... My fight with
Byakuya.
Getsuga tensho!!!!!
You are good!
Let's test your ability!
Gokei Senbonzakura Kageyoshi!
What?!
Kageyoshi has a billion
blades. They surround
the enemy in a revolving
sphere, and cut in every
direction. I suspect this
is the first time you
ha've had to deal with
this, am I right?
I've got him now!
Ichigo!
I am impressed.
Ichigo Kurosaki.
...There you are, still
standing after that
attack.
I don't have a choice. If
I don't kill him, he'll
kill me!
Sorry, Byakuya. I have
to destroy your Zanpakuto.
Please forgive me.
Why do you hesitate? If you
do not plan to attack, then
I will.
I'm not hesitating.
Senkei Senbonzakura
Kageyoshi.
Getsuga...
... tensho!!!
As you hesitated, I was
able to gather enough Spirit
Energy to withstand your attack.
I wouldn't be too sure
about that.
What?! It
can't be!
Sorry, Senbonzakura...
I'm not sure this would
have happened if you and
Byakuya had come at me
together...
...But without him, your
Spirit Energy wasn't strong
enough to defeat me.
You have humiliated me.
And I shall make you
regret that!
You just don't
give up, do you?
Do not be so condescending,
you disrespectful--
That's enough.
Byakuya!
Captain Kuchiki!
As far as I know, he's
been missing a long time.
I wonder where he's been.
Sorry, Byakuya. I decided to
take care of your Zanpakuto
since you were gone.
Ichigo. Step aside.
You want to fight him
yourself?
Well, he is your Zanpakuto,
so it probably makes more
sense for you to take him on.
You are misinterpreting
my intentions.
Which are...?
Hado Number Thirty-three,
Sokatsui!
Captain Kuchiki
What are you
doing?!
Hey, what's going on?!
Answer me, Byakuya.
What the---?
Ichigo Kurosaki. I will not
allow you to decide the fate
of this Zanpakuto.
What is he thinking?
Hold on a minute! Have you
joined up with Muramasa?! Is
that what this is all about?!
Or have you gone and
surrendered to your
Zanpakuto?!
Surrender? I would will
never surrender to a
Zanpakuto, no matter what
the circumstance.
I have made this decision
after much thought.
You and many other Soul
Reapers were witnesses,
watching as the Zanpakuto
released themselves. Once
they were free, they set
their own goals...
and then they soon
followed their desires.
I understand their
motivation...
I too, am free.. to
follow my desires,
wherever they take me.
You say very interesting
things, Soul Reaper. So
tell me, what are your
desires?
Perhaps there's one
stronger than the rest.
I'm wondering which one
motivates you the most?
It is really quite
simple.
My desire...
Is to uphold my self respect.
That is all.
Ichigo. You will not
interfere with Muramasa.
If you can't live with
that...
...then be prepared to
die.
Byakuya!
It appears that Captain
Kuchiki has betrayed us.
I've always wanted to
experiment on him and
now's our chance! Let's
go catch him! Get a
basket, a stick and some
bread crumbs!
A photo of Rukia Kuchiki
might be more effective.
A brilliant idea!
Are you serious?