[theme music]
-No matter what
you're planning, you
are too late to save the Bounts.
-Even if you're the last
one, I can still save you.
-No.
I think I'll kill you
right here and now.
[jingling]
[grunt]
-And with help from
the Soul Society,
you can build schools
down here as well.
You have my promise
that we will do all.
-Who's that lady?
-She's a Soul Reaper.
-You don't have to be afraid.
She came here from a place
called the Soul Society
in order to help and
protect the Bounts.
-Remember.
These things will take time.
-Soul Reaper.
-Are you all right little one?
-Uh.
Uh.
Uh-- yes.
I'm-- I'm OK.
-You're a very young
Bount, aren't you?
-I guess so.
-I understand it's very
rare for Bount powers
to have already awakened in
someone as young as you are.
You probably don't
realize it yet,
but your people are expecting
great things of you.
-Huh?
-Try to do your best.
We all need to work together
in order to help you
and the Bounts live a life
without worries or fear.
-Oh.
Well, I'll try.
-Shortly after that,
the Soul Reapers
left us and returned
to the Soul Society.
We were left behind to continue
building our underground city.
And to wait patiently for the
Soul Reapers to return one day.
Though I was still very
young, I did my best
to help the adults
with the work.
They had invested
all their hopes
in the Soul Reapers' promises.
But their dreams were about
to be cruelly shattered.
[cries]
-What was that?
-He's hurt pretty badly
-Seize them all then!
Kill any who resist!
[gasp]
[screams of pain]
-I'm getting out of here!
[screaming]
[panting]
-Keep searching!
Find that boy!
Don't let a single
Bount leave here alive!
Do you hear me?
-Yes sir!
-They won't get away!
[gasp]
-There you are!
Are you all right?
-She's helping me but
she's a Soul Reaper.
[quick footsteps]
-I'm going to stay here and try
to keep them busy for a while.
I want you to go on
ahead without me, OK?
-Huh?
-You can do it.
The other Bounts are
waiting for you outside.
I want you to escape
with your friends.
-But then they'll get you.
-Don't worry.
I'll be just fine.
Take this amulet.
The bounts have a great
deal of power within them.
This will help draw
out that power.
I'm sorry, little one.
You'll be forced to
endure much suffering.
But I believe one day
you will rise again.
And to see that
day, you must live!
-Yes, but--
-You have to go!
Now!
-Hey!
-That was the last time
I saw that Soul Reaper.
-But I managed to
escape from the caves.
And with the few other
Bounts who survived
I returned to a
life of wandering.
But back above ground
we were like food
thrown into a den
of wild animals.
Those Bounts who
possessed spirit energy
were little more than
bait for the hollows.
Pursued by hollows,
my bitterness
toward the Soul Reapers
only grew stronger.
[scream]
[grunting]
-Huh?
[gasping]
[scream]
-Eh?
-Hey you?
What are you?
-I feel some power inside me.
-That was the first time
I felt the sensation
of merging with a doll.
[grunting]
-There had always been some
Bounts who could naturally
summon the power
to control dolls.
Alongside them I fought and
fought with everything I had.
By utilizing this
strength we could finally
confront the Soul Reapers.
I realized that
with this power we
could create a place
where the Bounts.
But my power gradually
changed the attitude
of the other Bounts.
And before long, I came to
realize that I was all alone.
Even so, I stayed
with my comrades.
That is, until that fateful day.
That day the Bounts decided to
use the power of the Quincies
in order to enter
the Soul Society.
-Think about what you're saying.
You must be insane
to want to go there.
Why do you want to cling
to the Soul Reapers?
We don't need them!
With the power we have now we
can create our own paradise
in this world!
-We have to face
that in this world
the existence of the
Bounts is an abnormality.
Even if we used our power to
build a home for ourselves,
it would be doomed in the end.
For us it is safer to return to
the place where it all began.
-You must accept that for
Bounts the Soul Society
is that paradise.
-Not one of those fools
would listen to my pleas.
-And then the fighting began.
-Stay close!
[yelling]
-Make short work of them!
-We got them this time!
-In the end, they were
destroyed by the Soul Reapers.
[scream]
-At one point I was
injured by a blast.
And before I could do a
thing, the battle was over.
To some extent I felt the weaker
Bounts deserved their fate.
But I was not about forgive
the Soul Reapers or the Soul
Society for what they had done.
I gathered the strongest
surviving Bounts around me,
and vowed to destroy
the Soul Society.
The ability to activate and
use the dolls was sporadic.
I knew I would have to refine
and perfect the technique.
First, I set out to find
the most powerful Bounts.
In that process many
Bounts lost their lives.
But the ones who
survived were truly
committed to attaining
great strength.
And I rose higher and higher.
All in order to one day
destroy the Soul Society.
To think I had somehow
forgotten all about you.
You who gave us so much false
hope and eternal suffering.
Perhaps it's because of
the Jokai crest's power.
But it doesn't matter now.
For all of the weak
and useless Bounts
who clung to your empty words,
and for the Soul Society who
used us so
mercilessly I will now
destroy everything
that you hold dear!
-It's you again.
That Quincy.
-Kariya, I'm the one you want.
Not her.
[chuckling]
-Come on now.
What can you do?
[gasp]
-Amazing.
The Quincy has completely
mastered his weapon.
-How is this possible?
I thought you had already
reached your limit with that
accessory in the course
of your battle with Yoshi.
-This ancient artifact
amasses reishi very quickly
and then multiplies
it automatically.
For a Quincy with
weakened spirit energy
it's quite useful.
In other words, it
accumulates reishi
even if the one wielding
it does nothing at all.
Up until now, all
I did was attack
and then adjust the power.
But doing that is a sure
way to make the artifact
reach its limit.
Unable to handle the
load of the reishi,
it would eventually
discharge spontaneously.
However, there is
another method.
The artifact can be used
solely as an amplifier,
with me using my own power to
adjust and control the reishi.
Then the stress on
it is greatly reduced
and I can still battle
even in my present state.
It took the extreme battle
conditions with Yoshi
to help me realize it.
-He said that he's
using the accessory
because he lost his
own spirit energy.
It's amazing that
he can do all this
in such a weakened condition.
[chuckling]
-What are you laughing about?
-I'm just wondering why
with such great power
you're fighting on the
side of the Soul Reapers.
I thought they were the
Quincies' greatest enemies.
-Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm certainly no ally
of the Soul Reapers.
The fact is I'm here
because I intend
to stop this senseless fight.
-Hah.
Noble but foolish words.
-Yoshino gave her life
to try and stop you.
Do you know what you said to me?
She said, Kariya not only
hates the Soul Reapers,
he hates the Bounts too.
And someday his consuming
hatred will end up
destroying all off us.
Even his own people.
Yoshino understood
what you were.
She knew that everything
you'd been doing
was meaningless to the
Bounts right from the start.
In the end no one
could stop you.
Not her or any of the others.
Maybe it's too late now.
Just the same, I'm going to
give it everything I've got.
-You won't stop me either.
-We'll see.
-Hm.
[kiai]
[grunting]
-I've got you now.
-Don't bet on it.
[kiai]
-The quality of the reishi
here in the Seireitei
is much higher than
in the Rukon district.
As long as I have this ability
to continually regenerate
myself, your attacks
are pointless.
-Hm.
Huh?
[gasp]
-A crack in his artifact!
-You may have reduced the stress
you're putting on your bow.
But it would it's
still weakening just
when you need it most.
-It's not a problem.
The bow will certainly
hold together
long enough for me to
bring you down, Kariya.
You really think you can do it?
I have all the reishi within
the Seireitei at my disposal.
-And so do I.
[grunting]
[kiai]
-It doesn't matter how
much power your arrows have
if you can't aim more
accurately than that.
And you don't seem to
have sufficient power
for another kind of attack.
Plus, it looks to me like
you don't have much time
before your weapon comes apart.
-If things keep
going like this--
[gasp]
-What's the matter?
Your aim is getting even worse.
[kiai]
[grunting]
-This is it for you, Quincy.
-Kariya!
-What?
[grunt]
-What's the source of
this spiritual pressure?
Why you!
-Huah!
-Back away from him!
-Do it!
Shoot him now!
Quickly!
-Uh.
-Let go!
-Hurry up!
-But I'll hit you.
-Forget about me.
Shoot now while
you have a chance!
Right now I'm intercepting
the power of the Jokai crest
and using it to increase
my spiritual pressure.
But I can't keep it
up for very long!
-No I can't-- I can't
risk hitting you!
-Just shoot!
Don't you dare let this
Bount add to his crimes.
Yes.
That's how it must be.
-Let go of me, damn you!
-I'm sorry, Rantao.
Tell me you're all right.
-Where's Kariya?
-I he's still alive.
-Oh no.
You fired at half
strength, didn't you?
-Yes.
But don't worry.
Because now I'm going
to finish him off.
[groaning]
-Hu-- hurry, Uryu.
[painful groaning]
[screaming]
-What's this?
Her spiritual pressure
is out of control!
This must be a result
of the Jokai crest power
she intercepted earlier.
If I don't do something,
her body will disintegrate!
I know.
I can use the artifact's
reishi accumulation.
Rantao, hang on!
I think I can use the artifact
to remove the unstable spirit
energy inside you.
-No!
Don't you dare do that.
We both know that you Soshingu
is almost at it's limit.
You have to use its power
to destroy Kariya and not
for anything else!
You don't have to
worry about me.
This is no surprise
to me, Quincy.
I used this power knowing full
well that this would happen.
-Yes, but Rantao--
-No more talk!
You've got to hurry.
Before Kariya can recover.
[whimper]
Hurry!
This is your only chance!
-You will pay for that.
[gasping]
-Uryu.
[grunt]
-Rantao.
I can't let you die like this!
-Quincy.
-I-- I've reached my limit.
[grunt]
[gasp]
-We're not safe here.
We'd better go.
-You think you can
just walk away?
You had your chance to kill me.
But you chose not to take it.
Now it's your life that's about
to come to an end instead.
[grunt]
[kiai]
-Heh.
-Huh?
-Having problems, Uryu?
-Ichigo.
-You again.
[ending music]
-Oh wow!
That girl in the
teashop was so cute!
-Oh, you mean that one
in the Rukon district?
-How do you know about her?
You sick creep!
-Hate to break it to
you, but she's a he.
Isn't that right, Hisagi?
-Everybody knows that.
[screaming]
[japanese pop music]
-Illustrated by
the Soul Reapers!
-Hard to believe the
Bounts got this far.
We need to improve our security.
-Yeah.
-Lt.
Gira, we've arrested
a suspicious person.
Another Bount?
-I'll lead you to him.
-Oh no!
-What the hell?
-Hey there!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
But now here I am.
The ultimate assistant!
-We really need to
improve security.
-Mhm.