Hyaahh!
Ginjo!
Huh?!
Raaaghh!
Yaaagh!
You have done it. It's complete.
"Complete"?
Yes. The moment Fullbring is
completed, someone has to take a risk
in order to contain the massive explosion
of energy that's produced by it.
Ginjo...
Hey, sorry. I know I was a
bit cheesy as a bad guy.
Welcome to X-cution.
Now you're one of us.
[alarm bell]
[Orihime]
Nnggh... Nmm...
[humming]
Hm!?
[Ichigo] [straining]
Whu... ONE...
One Hundred!
Agh!
I'm done! That's my limit!
I can't even do one more!
You gotta be kidding!
What, you're worn out already?
What d'ya mean "already"?!
Just how many sets of a hundred pushups
are you really expecting me to do?!
That was only your
fourteenth set.
Only fourteen hundred?
Are you crazy?!
Are you trying to turn me
into a body builder?!
Nobody ever becomes great
without stepping up a little.
"Pushing out one more set can keep
a guy from becoming a pushover".
Really?! Where the hell did you get that?
Off the back of a cereal box?
What if I did? I'm tryin' to turn a
medium like you into an XL like me.
Buh?? Since when do you
care about my size?!
The fact that you're
sounding like some obessed
stalker is kinda
givin' me the creeps!
It's great to see
Ichigo working so hard.
[knock]
Coming in!
[gasp]
Shouldn't you wait for someone
to answer before barging in?
Oh shut up.
Here, I brought you a
hot dog for breakfast.
Ah! Wait! It might be fun for us
to eat together, don't you think?
I already ate some donuts and eating
with you wouldn't be fun, so no.
Oh... okay bye!
[sigh] Oh well.
It seems all Riruka
ever eats is donuts.
There. You're done loading.
Well we'd better get going.
Thanks Yukio!
Hey, it's no big deal.
I do this all the time.
[Orihime]
C'mon Chad, we'll be late.
How's Ichigo?
He's not going
to school today.
Mr. Ginjo said he completed his Fullbring
but he still has a few kinks to work out.
Then I suppose he'll be
all done by tonight.
So Chad. You've decided to
come back to school, huh?
What changed your mind?
I guess you just really missed
all those math tests huh?
Heh...
If Tsukishima's goal is keeping
Ichigo's powers from returning,
Then what was his purpose in attacking
you and going after Ichigo's family?
Seems like that might have
been counterproductive.
Maybe he was trying to
corner Ichigo on purpose,
so it would force him
to master Fullbring.
Hm?!
Why would he do that?
Hard to say, but there has to be
some reason he acted the way he did.
I think the key to answering
that question lies in one thing.
This is about
Tsukishima's powers.
Have you noticed anything different
since the day you were attacked?
Yeah. Remember what I
tried to explain to you?
How I said it suddenly felt like
Tsukishima was part of my old memories?
Somehow he was able to make me believe
that he and I are very close.
There are times I even find
myself thinking of him fondly!
I see.
That tells me that we can't just
leave things the way they are.
I suggest we carefully go
over everything that's happened to us so far.
I agree.
Hey, hi there!
Huh. You're not here.
You go and put me through all this trouble
and then disappear without a single word.
I'll bet you're just an airhead that
all the boys fuss over for no reason.
Hmm?
[Orihime] Dear Riruka, Breakfast
was delicious. Thank you so much!
PS-Let's have donuts
together again.
Ugh, stupid airhead.
So, how's Ichigo doing?
Good. He's doing well. He'll be a
complete Fullbringer by tonight.
Oh yeah?
Oh I gotcha.
You really don't care.
No, that's not it. Don't you think Mr.
Tsukishima will sense he's ready too?
Sure. I suppose he'll start
making some kinda move soon.
[Yukio] What do you mean START
making some kinda move??
Yukio.
Let me out.
[sigh]
Isn't Ichigo who Tsukishima's
really after here?
His last attack made it obvious.
Even I knewwhat was going on then.
And before that, lots of strange things kept
happening around Ichigo,
and they all seemed to
be Tsukishima's doing.
So saying he's starting to move is wrong.
He's already made some moves.
What's wrong??
I gotta question. Why do women
always have to nitpick everything?
Chauvinist!
Oww! Gahh!
Why'd ya do that?!
It's safe to say you just
got what you deserved.
Hmf!
Hmf! All right.
So far Tsukishma's only been
playing with Ichigo and
putting up this front that
he's not that dangerous.
But now, Ichigo's Fullbring
is about to become complete.
This time his approach
will be much more serious.
You think so?!
Hey wait...
So how 'bout finally explaining what you
think he wants with Ichigo's powers?
Who knows?
What DO you
know then!?
Listen, this won't be a
walk in the park for him.
Ichigo's Fullbring
will be tough to beat.
And Tsukishima's too smart to go after
Ichigo directly. Not now at least.
Instead, he might try
to isolate Ichigo, by
eliminating anyone who
would try to protect him.
If what you're saying is true, then
all of us are in danger as well.
That's right.
We are.
Though I would expect that
the people closest to
Ichigo are at the highest
risk of elimination.
Orihime!
Morning Tatsuki!
Good to see you
back, Chad.
Mmm.
Hey stranger!
Where ya been?!
You haven't been to
school in almost a--
Whoaa!
Are you okay?
[laughing]
I'm solid as a rock.
'Course I've been keeping my eyes
open for an Ichigo sighting.
Ichigo said he wouldn't
be here today.
What?! So how is it that
you know Ichigo's business?
He told both of us. He's doing his
best to get himself together.
He told you that?! What's he gotten
himself involved in this time?
Move it.
Don't touch me!
Try minding your own
business, ya big Snoop.
[bell]
C'mon or we'll be late!
Orihime,
let's go!
[Riruka] Wait! So those
two might be targeted?!
Why did you let
them leave today?!
What could we do?!
We can't just lock them up here just
because it's convenient for us.
I expect they
can handle it.
If they want to help Ichigo, they're bound
to check out Tsukishima themselves.
Huh?
But right now, we can't
afford to help them.
It's pointless for us to even try to
figure out what Tsukishima is up to.
We must stay here
to reach our goal.
And protect Ichigo, no
matter what that costs us.
How can you say that?!
I'm sorry, but that's
all we can do now.
Yukio,I'mgonna
getsomesleep.
[Yukio] Sure, I'll
take care of things.
Hrmmmpf.
[Chad]
Orihime!
[giggle]
How'd it go?
I checked the whole school for
traces of Spirit Energy.
But I didn't sense any of it
coming from anyone else around.
I see. That means it was only from
Tatsuki and the boys then, huh?
Yeah, you're
probably right.
those three definitely came in contact with
someone who possessed strong spirit energy.
I can't prove it, but it
felt like it was Tsukishima.
Oh no! You think he could
have done something to them!?
It's all right. Nothing really
seems to be different about them.
They're fine. But I'm pretty sure we're
gonna find him somewhere near Ichigo.
[gasp] So Mister
Tsukishima's close!?
[exhale]
Uh?
Ah!
[Chad]
What is it?
Ah! Uh-nothing.
Let's go!
Okay.
What was that?
Strange.
[chuckle]
[whisper] What's with that girl?
Beats me. She's
looking for someone.
Ugh! I can't see anything
with these sunglasses on.
That girl's turning into nothing
but a giant pain in the butt.
You're acting silly.
Be nice to her.
C'mon! you won't admit it, but you
really care about "that girl."
[all snickering]
You're all dead wrong! I only came
over here to buy some donuts!
It just so happens I passed by the
school where Chad and that girl go,
so I thought maybe I'd check things
out for a bit, and check to see--
Wha-!!?
Did I just overhear you say
"Chad and that girl"?
What?! And just who are you?
And why would you care?
By "that girl," did you
mean Orihime Inoue?
I might've meant that.
Okay sure I came to see her. So do you
know where she and Chad might be?
They've already left.
Huh? So where've
they gone off to?
I don't know what you
want with them, but I'm
not telling someone
like you where they--
Just tell me. This
is really important.
Thank you
very much.
Chad!
Well?
What'd they say?
Big news. Uryu was told he couldn't
be released from the hospital yet.
But he left at noon anyway.
I see.
I'll try
calling him.
Good.
[comical crash]
Agh!
Oww my head!
[Orihime]
Riruka!?
Huh?
What're you doing way over
on this side of town?
Uh! It's not what
it looks like!
I only came over here to
buy myself some donuts!
At the hospital?!
They have great ones!
You'd never guess it!
But never mind that!
What are you two doing here?!
We just stopped by here
to visit our friend!
So you were visiting
Uryu Ishida?
Uh!
I see!
So you two are racking
your little brains
trying to figure out
what Tsukishima's up to.
Why do you
think that?
Don't try to fool me!
You already know.
Tsukishima's been making contact
with some of Ichigo's friends.
You think I don't know
what's going on around here?
We weren't trying
to hide anything!
But Ichigo's been working
so awfully hard, we thought
we'd lend him a hand and do
some investigating ourselves.
Wait! How stupid are you?!
This guy is a monster!
Didn't Ginjo tell you?!
Tsukishima...
is the kinda guy who had
no remorse after killing
that Substitute Soul
Reaper and his allies!
And you're trying to investigate
this shark by yourselves?!
You guys are in way
over your head here!
Yeah, you're right.
My powers really aren't that strong.
And I'm not
sure anything I could
possibly do would help him.
But I do know that Ichigo
has always protected me.
It may not make sense to you,
but if he's in danger,
I will do everything in
my power to protect him.
Even if it's only a little bit,
I have to try.
[gasp] Um!
What's going on?
Nothing.
It's all good.
Well, regardless, the last thing you
want to do is track down Tsukishima.
There!
I've warned you.
Uh, Riruka!
Thanks for that.
I don't get you at all.
You creep me out!
[Uryu] [over phone] Hi this is Uryu.
I'm not available right now.
please leave a message at the tone,
and I'll get back to you.
He's not answering.
Why don't we start heading back to
where Ginjo and the others are.
If we keep calling we should be able
to reach Uryu before it gets dark.
We'll come up with a new plan
after we all talk it through.
Like Riruka said earlier, going after that
guy by ourselves is way too much of a risk.
Chad?
Hunh!?
Is something wrong?
No, nothing.
Everything's fine.
[sigh]
We need to come up with some other way
for us to learn more about Tsukishima.
[gasp]
[Chad]
Sushigawara?
Isn't he that little punk guy you told me
was with Tsukishima when you were attacked?
I guess he might
know something about
Tsukishima's power, but
he's also a Fullbringer.
So he could be dangerous.
Maybe. But...
He really didn't come
across as that strong.
[Orihime]
What's this?
[Chad] If he said he was from Miyashita
High School, then this is it.
I don't like the vibe
I'm getting here.
Hello!
Excuse me!
[Orihime] We're here
looking for someone.
Huh?! And who the hell are you?
Huh?
Heh heh!
Hey! You don't belong here!
- The matter, you lost?
What you doing here anyway?
- Heh heh heh heh.
Jeez, what're
those two doing?!
I warned them looking for
him would lead to trouble.
Great! If they go and cause a big scene,
Tsukishima'll be sure to notice them.
Yes, I will.
What are you
doing out here?
Riruka.
[terrified breaths]
Haugh!
Get back here,
dammit!
What in the world
just happened?!
Guess they weren't in the
mood for conversation!
[panting]
You were right,
they wouldn't listen.
Sorry, it seemed like a
good idea at the time.
Don't worry about it.
It's too bad, we
didn't learn a thing.
Mh!
What's wrong?!
So as for Mr. Tsukishima, just when
exactly did we become friends with him?
What're you talking about?
Didn't we go with him to the
Soul Society to rescue Rukia?
Uh?
Hold on, that
isn't right.
Orihime!
I know. Something's
changed in me.
[Tsukishima]
Shall I tell you what?
[gasp]
Hello there.
Riruka was telling me that
you've been looking for me.
What do you want?
Tsukishima! You hurt
her, didn't you?!
I did.
But there's nothing
to worry about.
It was all in the plan.
Raaggh!
How impressive!
In such a very short time, you
increased your power ten fold.
I did it to defeat you!
Haaaa!
Oh,soYukio
helpedyou.
I thought all he did was
play video games by himself,
but it seems now he's learned
how to play with others.
Shitenkoshun!
Ngh!
Chad!
You alright?!
Yeah. I'm doing fine!
I think we can beat him
with just the two of us!
Not bad. You might be
quite useful to me.
Like hell I will!
[gasp]
No you don't! Brazo
Izquierdo Del Diablo!
Now, Orihime, do it!
Tsubaki!
[chuckle]
[gasp]
There! Mr. Bunny is done!
[Tsukishima]
Orihime.
Oh? Hah!
Were you waiting
for me again?
[laughing]
How did?
What is it?!
What's wrong?!
I don't know why this
is happening to me...
Orihime!
Well, I suppose it's about
time for you to wake up.
So now, who am I?
[gasp]
Auugghhhh!
[Chad]
Damn you!
You bastard! Just what
did you do to her?!
What did I do?
The same thing I did to you.
[gasp]
[freaking out grunts]
Aarrgghhh!
Tsukishima
[chuckling]
[Kugo] Okay, Ichigo! Show everyone
your completed Fullbring power!
[Ichigo]
Huh? Wait, why should I?
[Kugo] You've become stronger.
Admit it, aren't you curious too?
[Ichigo] Not really. I don't feel
like showing it off right now.
[Kugo] [whining] But I want to see it
right now! Show it to me! Pretty please!