[MUSIC - BEAT CRUSADERS,
"TONIGHT, TONIGHT, TONIGHT"]
-Heh.
You know, you don't have to
watch me like I was-- huh?
-Huh?
-What the--?
Who is it?
YOSHINO: Koga!
-Your time is up.
YOSHINO: I am not coming.
KOGA: The choice is
not yours to make.
Kariya is waiting.
-I refuse.
If you want me, try and take me.
Zeige Dich, Goete!
-[laughs]
-Zeige Dich, Dalk.
-What is that?
-What is it?
Do you need some
help with something?
-Yes.
-See how pathetic you are.
But it's all right,
because I do love to fight.
[laughs]
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
-It makes it even more fun
for me when you try to run.
-Goethe, destroy it!
-As you wish.
-[laughs] Good.
This will be fun.
-[roars]
-[shout]
[fighting noises]
-[grunting]
-This is not good.
[shouting]
-Goethe!
-[shout]
YOSHINO: Can you move?
We've got to get to the stairs.
[groaning]
-Now's our chance!
-[laughs] Oh, my, my.
See how hot my love burns now!
-How is she able to move?
-[laughs] I believe I'm
falling in love with you.
[laughs]
[sputtering]
-Goethe!
-Ah, where are you going?
Now what I am supposed to
do with all these feelings?
Who am I going to
give my love to?
-Look out!
Goethe!
-Oh, you came back.
You've made me so happy.
Will you accept my love?
[laughs]
-Watch out!
[shouts]
-Oh!
-[shouts]
-Well, they never stay for long.
[laughs]
-Come on.
-I know, I know.
You want me to hurry
up and finish the job.
But it's not good to rush
these things, don't you agree?
I want to take my
time and enjoy this.
KOGA: You're not
to harm the Quincy.
-Then I take it I can do
what I like with the woman?
-Oh, no.
-Ah, you just made it.
-[groan] What are you doing?
Now's not the time for
you to be protecting me.
-No, it's not that I was
trying to protect you.
-What?
-It's just that I decided
not to run away anymore.
I don't want to be
a burden to others.
And I don't want to be a victim.
-Oh, what a wonderful,
sentimental thing to say.
Such a manly attitude you have.
Ha!
In fact, it just makes me
want to hug you. [laughs]
-The traces have
disappeared now,
but there's no doubt about it.
There were two
Bounts here recently.
-I believe you.
But can't you try harder to
keep yourself out of sight?
-Oh, so now you're going
to insult my looks, too?
-[sigh] It's not that.
I'm just afraid
people will notice
four strange stuffed
animals walking around.
-Oh, so no I'm strange, am I?
Well, listen here, Mr. Perfect.
[sigh] None of us chose the
appearance of these animals.
But this is what we got.
And we all just have
to deal with it, OK?
-All right, all right.
I get it.
-[gasp] It's here!
Up there!
KON: Aha.
Definitely suspicious.
-Traces of his
spiritual pressure.
-[gasp]
-I feel it.
ICHIGO: Uryu!
-Uryu.
-No doubt, he was brought
here by someone not long ago.
-And the fire must
be from that woman.
-But the other one is
someone we don't know.
-Hm.
-It looks like they had
quite a battle, and probably
over the Quincy.
-I would agree.
That's the most likely scenario.
-So then both sides were
trying to take you Uryu.
-Hm?
Tug of war?
Wait a minute!
Uryu Ishida can't play
the role of a princess.
Ah!
So wrong.
But he did look
good in the dress.
Hm?
Ah!
I'm on fire!
My head's engulfed in flames!
Oh!
Oh, I'm a hot head.
-Noba, I didn't know you
could suck in fire like that?
-It didn't burn you?
-It's not a problem.
CHAD: Ichigo.
-Huh?
-It's Uryu's bandage.
-Hm.
Can we track his spirit ribbon.
RUKIA: I don't think so.
His spiritual
pressure is very weak,
and he's suppressing it
in order to stay hidden.
-That's just great.
He's not even going to
let his own friends know
if the Bounts have caught him.
NOBA: It's all right, Ichigo.
-Huh?
KURODO: There's still
a way we can track him.
-There's a good chance that we
can follow the Bounts' Reishi
residue.
-Wait, are you sure?
-Yeah.
But it is frustrating.
My powers would be stronger
if I were in a Gigai.
Unfortunately, the real
bodies of us Mod-Souls
are just little pills.
We can't walk or even speak,
unless someone helps us
by putting us into a Gigai.
-Hm.
You know what, there's something
that I've always wondered
about.
If you need someone
else, why don't you
all just put each
other into Gigais?
-Uh.
-Hm.
-Big deal.
I didn't need him to come
up with this idea, you know.
I always knew.
I just pretended I didn't know.
-I'm not ashamed to admit that
I never thought of it before.
How amazing, though.
Talk about failing
to see that which
is right there in
front of your face.
-Well, I was acting
dumb on purpose,
as anyone can plainly see.
Otherwise, I would have
suggested the same thing
anytime.
Now, let's go find those Bounts.
KURODO: Absolutely!
-Hey!
What about me?
I'm still a stuffed animal!
Wait!
How am I supposed
to keep up with you?
Wah!
RANGIKU: Squad 10.
Captain Hitsugaya and
Lieutenant Matsumoto reporting.
YACHIRU: Squad 11.
Captain Zaraki and Lieutenant
Kusajishi reporting as well.
KUROTSUCHI: Come in.
-So sorry to keep you waiting!
-I have no interest in
your sniveling apologies.
If you were members of my
squad, I'd turn all of you
into dog food for
this insubordination.
RANGIKU: Captain Ukitake,
why have you summoned us?
-The one who wanted to
talk to everyone was me.
-Huh?
UKITAKE: Thank you for coming.
Something like this
would ordinarily
have been handled by
General Captain Yamamoto,
but he's away.
[clears throat] We
have an urgent security
matter to discuss with you.
Captain Kurotsuchi
has the details.
-Wrong.
There are no details.
My data bank has
been compromised.
Someone has been
breaking in and reading
highly classified information.
-Information?
On what?
-Well, now.
Would you believe on Bounts?
[gasping]
KUROTSUCHI: Furthermore,
the intruder
left behind a booby trap
buried deep in the data bank,
one that will destroy all
the data if it's disturbed.
Do any of you have the faintest
idea what all this means?
Do you?
This is a challenge
and great insult to me,
captain of Squad 12,
head of the Department
of Research and Development.
And I will not stand for it!
If someone in this
room is involved
in this insidious
plot, come forward now.
Confess!
I will pickle you limb by
limb in a vat of hot acid!
-Don't go looking for
a fight, Kurotsuchi.
All those here are high-ranking
officers of the 13 Court Guard
Squads.
-You have a short memory for
current events, it would seem.
Was it not a high-ranking
officer who betrayed us?
UKITAKE: I'm just
saying that this
is a dangerous
problem which involves
all of the Soul Society.
We should avoid acting rashly.
KUROTSUCHI: Hmph.
Some good you are.
Very well.
But if I find out one
of you are behind this,
I suggest you beware,
because I have a plan.
KENPACHI: [groan] I have a
bad feeling about all this.
-Hm?
About what?
-This Kurotsuchi thing, and
the fact we found Ichinose.
-Huh?
But why?
-I'm not sure.
-Hm.
Sounds to me like you're
worried about Maki after all.
KENPACHI: No, it's not that.
Something's wrong, somehow.
ORIHIME: I think I've got it!
There's a mansion
just a mile from there
that fits the description.
-Oh, yeah?
ORIHIME: They say the man who
lives there is incredibly rich.
But no one I asked has
ever actually seen him.
-Hm.
-[groans]
-Kariya has forgiven
your insubordination
for the last time.
And if you don't believe me,
you can go and ask him yourself.
That is, if you can manage
to get out of this room.
Hm.
It seems that you can't
even get up off the floor.
-[groans]
-I hope you know better
than to try anything stupid,
like using your doll
in that condition.
It would just be
the death of you.
-So this is it.
-What a huge yard.
Can't even see the house.
-There's no mistaking it.
-The Quincy's in there.
-OK.
Now, let's split up.
[knocking]
-Come in.
-Excuse me, sir.
Would you like to
see the Quincy?
-Koga is the one
who brought him in?
-Yes.
We're holding him
in the main foyer.
-The Quincy is the
joker in the deck.
I say it's time we meet.
UTAGAWA: Shall I put
the plan into motion?
KARIYA: No.
-Why are you holding back?
I don't understand.
KARIYA: We have lived for a long
time, a very long time, which
coats all of our memories
in shades of gray.
For the first time, I am able
to see the world in color again.
Is it so wrong for me to want
to enjoy this a little longer?
-I understand, sir.
But still--
-Silence!
No, Utagawa, you
don't understand.
-Are you ready?
-[gasp]
-What is it?
What's Wrong?
-The Bounts' spiritual pressure.
Now that we're
here this close, I
can tell that there are a lot of
them inside that house-- seven,
eight, or nine.
Maybe more.
-There are that many?
But we don't have
any idea what they're
up to, so we have to act.
Let's go.
-What's wrong?
Afraid?
[laughs] [gasp]
-So, you're Uryu Ishida.
[laughs] I can't blame
you for being suspicious.
We haven't given you
a very warm welcome.
-Who exactly are you?
-I'm Kariya.
And I've had you
brought here because I'm
interested in borrowing
your Quincy powers.
-In order to gain the
power of Wekomundo?
-[gasp] We're a lot
alike, you and I.
We've suffered rejection
because of our unique abilities.
I know the pain you've endured.
-Abilities?
-That's right.
And I have a proposition--
that you and I live together
symbiotically, rather
than as mortal enemies.
Bounts will be able to protect
you from any other enemies.
And there is also a
good chance we will even
be able to revive your
lost Quincy powers.
-[gasp]
-Not a bad proposition, eh?
-But if you already know I don't
have any powers, then why--
-I told you that already.
We're the same, you and I.
-I see no reason to trust you.
-[sigh] I understand
your suspicions.
Besides, we have all
the time in the world.
Give him time.
I'm sure he'll come around.
Believe me.
Please, make yourself
at home here.
-So I'm your captive?
-Let's say you an
important guest.
-Dalk, you can release him.
-Oh, too bad.
-Not bad, I guess, as
far as prison cells go.
-Kariya is a kind person,
but very dangerous, too.
You should consider
it a warning.
-Thank you so much.
-You'll soon learn.
-Huh?
We headed toward the
mansion, but now I
don't even know where we are.
-Hm.
-Huh?
Oh, I don't know
which way to go.
Since we got hear,
it seems like I've
lost my sense of direction.
-Yeah, me too.
-Hey, hold on!
Oh.
Wait for me!
-Damn it.
Another wrong turn.
-This house has too
many doors and hallways.
-That's the only reason
we're disoriented.
-What?
-Something is messing
up our senses--
maybe a strong magnetic
force, or-- [gasp].
It sees us.
-What is it?
[gasping]
-Bastard.
RUKIA: [inaudible].
-What the hell was that?
-I don't know, but it's
definitely trouble.
-Huh?
-Hm?
-Oh, no.
[whimper]
-Let's try to outrun them!
-Right.
ICHIGO: Oh, no.
Could this possibly
get any worse?
Ririn!
-Ichigo!
-Hm?
What?
Are those things following
you what I think they are?
-Noba, can you
erase these things?
ICHIGO: You saved us.
RUKIA: But what are
you doing up here?
-We had to escape outside.
Everywhere we went
in the house, we
ran into those
flying eyeball dolls!
-They gave us no choice.
Noba erased as many
as he could, but it
began to seem as if
they would never stop.
They were coming out of
the woodwork everywhere
we turned in there.
-And now it seems
they're outside as well.
-I'm tired.
-Huh?
-And it doesn't look like
they're about to give us
a break, either. ,
KURODO: Oh, no!
[grunting]
-Let's go!
Where are we?
KURODO: I don't know, but
that's an amazing tapestry.
And it would appear to
depict a witch hunt.
KARIYA: You are correct.
[gasping]
-Who said that?
[laughter]
[gasping]
-Welcome to our mansion.
-Substitute Soul Reaper.
[music playing]
ICHIGO: Ririn, where
did you hide your Gigai?
RIRIN: Under your bed.
ICHIGO: What?
What if someone found it?
RIRIN: [giggle]
Oh, it's all right.
I hid it along with
a doll, set to make
it look as if it was a
secret hobby of yours.
ICHIGO: What if
someone found it?
RIRIN: A secret hobby.
[music playing]
KON: It must be the
guide to soul reapers.
ALL: Golden!
TETSUZAEMON (VOICEOVER):
I must endure this.
I must not show my pain.
TETSUZAEMON: Where is it?
Tell me where it is, somebody!
-Is something the matter
with you, Tetsuzaemon?
-No, Captain.
It's nothing.
I just have a bit
of a stomach ache.
-The, bathroom is
right there, you know.
-Thank you, sir.
Excuse me.
Huh?
RIRIN: Captain?
Gah!
Oh.
CAPTAIN: Hey,
what's the problem?