[theme music]
ICHIGO (IN HEAD): Nothing
feels real to me now.
It doesn't feel real
being here in school,
that I was beaten up and
almost killed by those two guys
from the Soul Society.
And the strangest thing of all
is that she isn't here anymore.
Not a single one
of my classmates
even remembers that
Rukia ever existed.
-[laughs].
-Man, are you still
doing that stupid laugh?
You're just jealous
because I can
imitate the coolest guy on TV.
-Have you made any plans
for the summer yet, Orihime?
-Nope, I don't have a clue.
-Here's a great idea.
You should stay the
summer at my house.
My parents will be on vacation,
and it'll be just you and me.
-Oh no you don't.
-Well, why not?
It's not like I'm inviting
her to take a bath with me.
ICHIGO (IN HEAD): Is
this what it really
means to be returned
to the Soul Society?
You just disappear from
this world completely?
You're erased from
people's memories?
Every trace of Rukia is
vanishing right before my eyes,
fading away into white.
FEMALE TEACHER (OFFSCREEN):
All right, students.
I only have one more
assignment for you.
Everyone try to get
yourselves back here
in one piece in September.
Class dismissed.
Have fun.
[cheering]
ICHIGO (IN HEAD):
And for some reason,
Uryu, the one person I
thought might remember Rukia,
decided to cut the
last day of school.
KEIGO (OFFSCREEN): Ichigo, ha,
round and around and around
you go.
Now then, see if you
can hit the watermelon.
Nice try, but that was my melon.
It's OK though, because
I don't need a head
to think about anything anymore.
School's out for summer,
and summer means the sea.
And the sea is where we're all
going because I, Keigo Asano,
have planned a super
trip for us to the beach.
Ten fun-filled days of
sunbathing, swimming, fireworks
and lots of unsupervised and
questionable activities, right?
-Sorry, but I'm afraid I've
already made other plans?
-Huh?
-I'm not too keen on
the ocean either, Keigo.
-Huh?
-I've got the nationals
tournament to go to.
-Well, if Orihime and [?
Totski ?] aren't going,
then neither am I.
-Sorry, but I have some
things I have to take care of.
-[sobs].
-And I'm flying to
Hawaii tomorrow.
-What could possibly be better
than going on vacation with me,
you jackass?
-I'm going o this great trip
to Hawaii with my girlfriend
and nine of her friends,
so that's like 11 of us.
-Hawaii?
Just you and 10 girls?
So how'd you forget
to invite me?
How dare you leave me out
of a sweet deal like that.
-It wasn't my idea.
I promise.
I won't have any fun.
I'm not even bringing
a bathing suit.
ICHIGO (IN HEAD):
It feels weird.
Everyone's acting normal.
Our world still
rotates without Rukia.
But then why shouldn't it?
Rukia's originally
from the Soul Society.
I guess she never really
belonged over here.
But what if that's true?
What does that mean for me?
What do I do now?
[footsteps]
-Orihime, what are you doing?
Is something wrong?
-Ichigo, where is Rukia?
-Huh?
-Why has everyone
forgotten about her
like she never even existed.
I need you to explain what's
happening around here.
So you're saying Rukia went
back to this other world
she came from?
-Yeah.
I gotta admit.
I am surprised.
I really had no idea you've
been able to see us, Orihime.
For how long?
-Ever since the incident
with my brother.
-Oh, makes sense.
-I don't think I've ever
properly thanked you
for everything you did for him.
By guiding his spirit
on the other side,
he's finally in a place
where all he knows
is peace and happiness now.
Somehow I can just feel it.
-Is that so?
-Uh-huh.
I imagine Rukia is happy
on the other side as well.
She probably has friends
and family waiting for her.
-I have to go and
bring her back.
-But why should you bring her
back if she's happy there.
-Because I know she's
in serious trouble,
and they just might kill her
if I don't get her out in time.
-Here's what the
Ichigo I know would do.
Hmm, he'd make a mad face
and tell Rukia she can always
visit with friends and
family later if she lives,
but she won't have that
chance if she's dead.
I bet you've already made
up your mind, haven't you?
[giggles]
-You really were here.
I know that.
And you belong here, Rukia.
Thanks a lot, Orihime.
-Huh?
Chad.
[meowing]
-I still can't believe Ichigo
would take off on a summer
vacation and leave
the rest of us behind.
-Grow up, Yuzu.
He's always taking off.
-We don't need
Ichigo to have fun.
Why don't you play
a game of truth
or dare with your dear old dad.
-You're so weird.
Couldn't you act a little
bit more like a grownup?
-Oh, it hurts me to
see you two fighting.
-Oh, not half as much
as it's hurting me.
I guarantee you that.
GIRLS (OFFSCREEN): Good
morning, Lieutenant Abarai.
-At ease.
-Wait, wait, come back here.
I'm gonna get in so much
trouble if they find out
I let you get away.
Oh, I'll have to lure it back.
(FLIRTILY) Hey,
there, big butterfly.
Come here and check
out these antennae.
I'm a Pisces with double
D buttercups and--
-You still can't handle
hell butterflies?
-Uh, I'm sorry, sir.
I didn't know you
were coming in today.
I had to come in and
check on the prisoner.
Is she still insubordinate
and difficult?
-I'm not insubordinate.
-If you're not insubordinate,
then why do you refuse to eat?
-Maybe I'm just not hungry.
Does that bother
you, Mr. Lieutenant?
-Oh, so you resent that I'm
the lieutenant now, is that it?
I can hear it in the
tone of your voice.
-Hit a nerve, did I?
Well, don't worry,
Mr. Officer, now you
have the rank and the pompous
attitude and the weird eyebrows
to go with it.
-[growls].
How dare you mock me.
I could kill you for
an insult like that.
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN):
Tell me something.
Am I really going to die, Renji?
-Oh, absolutely.
For what you did, I expect
you'll be executed immediately.
-Very well.
I understand.
-Huh?
What do you mean you understand?
I was just kidding, Rukia.
It was only a joke.
-So which one is it, you idiot?
-An idiot, huh?
If I'm an idiot,
then how come you're
the one locked up in the cell?
You're pretty lucky
Captain Kuchiki is probably
pleading for clemency
for you even as we speak.
-Well, I doubt that.
-How can you say such a thing?
A man like Kuchiki would
never stand by and do nothing
while his own sister
faces a death sentence.
-You're quite
correct about that.
He'd rather kill me himself.
-Huh?
-I know it for certain because
I know full well the kind of man
he is.
40 years have passed since I was
taken in by the Kuchiki family,
and in all those years, he
has never once looked at me.
[dog barking]
-No way, this place is amazing.
Who would have guessed
that all this time, there
was a huge subterranean
training ground under my store?
-Oh, forget the acting.
Obviously, you knew this
place was down here,
but I will admit
it's impressive.
-So then, you wanna
get down to business?
-Yeah, let's just
get on with it,
this training session
or whatever you call it.
-Always be careful
what you ask for.
-[grunts].
What's the big idea of knocking
me down like that, you--
[whooshing sound]
-It's hard to breathe when
you're in the form of a soul,
isn't it, Ichigo?
Right now, your
Soul Sleep, which
is the wellspring of
your spirit energy,
and your Soul Chain, the
booster, have been destroyed.
So now, your soul is
like any ordinary human
with no spiritual power.
And so before we can
proceed, we must first
restore the spiritual
power you have lost.
-All right already,
just tell me what to do.
-You're so impatient.
All right, let's bring
out your opponent,
and then we can start.
Warrior, are you
ready for battle?
-Nice to see you again, Ichigo.
-Huh?
-Here's your first lesson.
You must go up against
Ururu one on one.
-Huh?
-The rules are quite simple.
Lesson one is over
when one of you
is no longer able to
continue the match.
If you can, I suggest going
for the knockout punch.
-Are you kidding?
You expect me to
punch a little girl?
-It's always dangerous
to underestimate
your opponent, Ichigo.
URURU (OFFSCREEN): Please put
on all this protective gear,
Ichigo.
I don't want to kill you.
-This whole thing's ridiculous.
I'm not fighting her.
-We tried to warn
him, didn't we?
-So where'd he go?
I don't see him anymore.
-Do you suppose he's dead?
Hard to say.
-[grunts].
-It looks like he's
going after her.
-Hey, he just ran
right past her.
-If little miss muffin
hits me with another punch
like that one, I'll be
taking a long dirt nap.
Hat-and-Clog, how do I
put this gear on anyway?
-Strap the headgear onto
your forehead, Ichigo.
-Like this?
-That's right.
Now yell as loud as
you can, "Amazing
headband of justice in place.
Amazing armor of
justice protect me now."
Go on, say it.
-The amazing headband of-- what?
Ah, that's just stupid.
-Interesting how the
fear of imminent death
can change one's mind.
-All right, I'll say it.
Here goes nothing.
Amazing headband of
justice in place.
Amazing armor of
justice protect me.
-Well, what do you know?
I can't believe he
actually said it.
-What?
You're gonna pay for that.
-Look outside behind you.
-Oh, great.
All right, bring it.
[screams]
Amazing armor of justice my ass.
More like armor of junk.
Running for my life is the only
thing that's saving my life.
ICHIGO (IN HEAD): Wait a minute.
If I'm outrunning her, it must
mean my speed has returned.
And that means maybe I
can dodge her punches.
-Here goes.
-Whoa.
-Huh.
-[chuckles].
ICHIGO (IN HEAD): I can do it.
I won't aim for her face.
I'll just give her a tap on her
headgear to make her back off.
And then because of my
size, I can-- oh, damn.
I cut her.
-Safe.
-Hey.
Give me one more
crack at her, please.
-Congratulations.
I pronounce lesson one cleared.
-What the hell are
you talking about?
She kicked my ass just now.
I lost.
-I never said anything about
you having to actually win
the fight in order to
clear the lesson, did I?
-I thought--
-The fact is, Ichigo, Ururu
here has the fighting skills
to counter even
full-fledged Soul Reapers.
A mere human would
never have a chance
of defeating her outright.
By the way, are you still
having difficulty breathing?
-No, now that you mention it.
-Which means that
we've successfully
restored your spirit energy.
The entire point
of that lesson was
to determine in
a one-shot battle
whether or not you could
dodge Ururu's first attack.
Spirit energy
increases a lot faster
when the soul is in
danger of being destroyed.
We just needed to
find out if you'd
be able to raise yours fast
enough to dodge that fatal
punch.
-And if I hadn't succeeded?
-Then you would've died.
-Why the hell didn't you
say so in the first place?
-I wasn't worried about it.
I had a lot of faith
that you'd be successful.
-Huh?
-Well, so far, so good.
Now then, let's celebrate the
return of your spirit energy,
shall we?
Now, let's continue
with your second lesson.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): Lessons?
-You'll need them if
you want to learn more.
-I suppose I do, but
this all seems so sudden.
-Plus, it's a little weird
dealing with a talking cat.
-You think so?
-Your friend Ichigo is preparing
to go to the Soul Society.
If you also want to learn to
use the new powers awakening
inside you, then you will have
to agree to take my lessons.
After that, the choice will be
yours whether you want to go
or not.
-Well, I'm going to go.
-Are you really?
Aren't you scared?
I am.
-Uh-huh.
-I won't force you.
URYU (IN HEAD):
Excellent, this will
be the perfect place for me
to train in complete solitude.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN):
There he is.
We found him.
Hi, Uryu.
Whatcha doing?
-I could ask you the
same question, Orihime.
So how did the two
of you find me?
-Yoruichi.
He just followed your aura,
and it led us right to you.
-Yoruichi?
-Did you come out
here to go camping?
-Huh?
Not exactly.
YORUICHI (OFFSCREEN):
You're training, aren't you?
-Huh?
Who said that?
Huh?
-It was me.
I'm right over here.
I'm Yoruichi.
-Ah!
No, a talking cat.
No way!
-What?
You've never seen a
talking cat before?
Honestly, don't be such a wimp.
-You are making kind
of a fuss, Uryu.
What's the bid deal?
-Well, if it makes you
feel any better, Uryu,
I'm having a little trouble
with the talking cat myself.
-Some humans have
so much trouble
adjusting to the unexpected,
especially the males.
-Excuse me.
Why did you come here anyway?
-Actually--
URYU (IN HEAD):
Ichigo is planning
on going to the Soul Society?
-Yes, he's going to go there
to try to rescue Rukia.
We thought you'd want to know
so you could help him too.
-What Ichigo does has
nothing to do with me.
-But what about Rukia?
Her life is in danger.
-You're forgetting
that I'm a Quincy,
and the whole reason
I'm out here training
is that I'm angry I
lost to a Soul Reaper.
Rukia doesn't mean
anything to me.
-[sighs].
Too bad, but I understand
that you're only
doing what you
think is best, Uryu.
It's completely confusing
to me at this point,
but I'm going to
keep on listening
and try to learn all I can
about these changes that
are happening.
It's a little scary to have
new powers awakening inside me,
but I want to know what
I can do with them.
Be careful, Uryu.
URYU (IN HEAD): Sorry
to let you down,
Orihime, but this
training is too important.
I can't let anyone see
what I'm about to do.
Please watch over me, sensei.
-(STRUGGLING) I feel
like I'm-- I'm dying.
-That's because you are.
You see, once the chain
of fate has been severed,
you can no longer return
to your physical body.
Death comes quickly.
-Do you have to be
so casual about it?
-That's not even
the worst of it.
Your chain will begin
the encroachment
where it was severed.
When the end reaches your
chest, you will become a Hollow,
and that will be the end of you.
-What do I have to do?
-If you don't want
to become a Hollow,
you must become a Soul Reaper.
-Huh?
-If you manage to
clear lesson two,
you will find that
in the process,
you have regained your former
powers as a Soul Reaper.
Of course, which path
you choose is up to you.
-As if you even needed to ask.
-All right, then.
Let's get this party started.
Go!
-[screams].
-Well, what do
you think of that?
We really suckered him
that time, didn't we?
-Yeah, good one.
-That's one deep whole, Ururu.
-I do my best.
[hitting bottom]
[coughing]
-What the hell have
you done to me?
-Bakudo, 99, Part 1 [?
restict. ?] No doubt
you think it rather harsh of
me, but until you have cleared
this lesson, your arms
must unfortunately
remain bound, Ichigo.
-Ah you-- dammit.
HAT-AND-CLOGS
(OFFSCREEN): Ichigo?
-Huh?
-Start climbing back
up the shaft, Ichigo.
That's all there is to this
lesson, otherwise known
as the Shattered Shaft.
-Yeah, that'll work with my
arms tied behind my back.
HAT-AND-CLOGS
(OFFSCREEN): I wouldn't
waste time arguing
about it if I were you.
-[screams].
-You have a period of
72 hours at the bottom
of Shattered Shaft, Ichigo.
That is how long it'll
take for the chain of fate
to be completely encroached.
By the end of that
time, if you have not
returned to the top of the
shaft as a Soul Reaper,
then we will have no choice,
Ichigo, but to kill you.
[music playing]
-Hey, Jinta and
Ururu, how quickly
do you think Ichigo can
come back as a Soul Reaper?
-I say five hours.
-More like 12 hours.
-I'll bet you 1,000 yen he
never makes it back at all.
-I'll teach you
guys to doubt me.