[theme music]
-This is no good.
-Hey Karin, wait for me!
There have been so many
incidents like this lately.
So many UFO sightings and all
of those poltergeist weirdos.
-I think this is
probably because of them.
-What, do you see something?
-Yeah, and it's better
you can't see them.
It'll Will only drive you crazy.
[high pitched sound]
KARIN (OFFSCREEN): Huh?
What was that?
It's-- [screaming] a cat?
Great, now it looks like that
other thing is heading right
for us.
Damn!
If those things came to fight,
let's get this party started!
I guess that should teach 'em.
-Ah!
That was sure scary.
[gasp] Karin, look!
What a cute little kitty.
It kind of reminds
me of our brother.
KARIN (OFFSCREEN):
Oh, yeah it's him.
Um, do you think there's
something wrong with this cat?
-Uh, well I-- I had this
really strange feeling like I'd
seen him somewhere before.
Hm, but now that
you mention it, it
does seem like there's something
wrong with this little kitty,
right?
[cat meows]
-Hm?
Meow?
[cat meows] Oh really
now, is that so?
-Uh, what'd it say?
-He said that he's hungry.
-Are you serious?
-Yep.
Let's just call it
a woman's intuition.
-OK, but uh-- do you
at least remember
where you saw this cat before?
-Hm, no I don't.
-I see.
YUZU (OFFSCREEN): Cat food!
Let's go buy cat food!
KARIN (OFFSCREEN): I
guess we can do that.
-Ugh, man what a waste.
It's useless cleaning
up around here.
I mean, it's not
like anyone's ever
going to be coming to a
store like this anyway.
-That's not true.
Why would you say that?
-OK, then tell me how many
customers we've had this month.
-Well, uh--
-Not one!
Not one!
-Come on Jinta, stop it.
[stomping] Hollow spotted.
Disposal complete.
-You know since old
carrot top left here
there've been a lot more
Hollow sightings around town.
Aha!
-Lately I don't think I'm
getting enough exercise.
I have a feeling that I've
put on a little weight.
-Well, I've got
something for you
that should take care of that.
It's a foolproof weight loss
remedy-- Ginkgo Below the Belt.
I got it on the Grasshopper
shopping channel and it works.
-Wow, that's hard to believe.
TESSAI (OFFSCREEN): Ach!
-Hey now, now,
don't get me wrong.
But it's just that I've
never really believed
in a quick fix that
comes out of a bottle.
-Well boss, I'm here to
tell you I'm living proof.
I tried it myself and the
results were truly amazing!
[stomach growling]
-Did you hear that?
Sounds like
something's growling.
-Uh, Gita.
-Quiet!
Now's the time for us to act.
It's up to us to get
rid of the Hollows
for the sake of the
town. [doorbell]
-Hm?
-I don't know what
you're saying!
KARIN (OFFSCREEN):
I think there might
be something wrong with
this cat after all.
[cat meows]
-Huh?
Why is that?
-Uh, well it's just a hunch.
-There's nothing wrong
with you, is there Cammy?
[cat meows]
-What do you mean, Cammy?
-It's his name.
It's short for camel.
Because he's the same color
as my camel-colored underwear.
-Um are you kidding?
Camel-colored underwear?
-Huh?
-Look at that car that's
parked in front of our house.
It's huge!
-It's obstructing our business.
-Huh?
-Wha!
Whoa, what the?
-How's it goin' little ladies?
-Uh-- ah!
-The spirits are
always with you!
-Ah!
Look!
It's Don Kanonji!
[yells]
-Are-- are you all right?
-Ha ha!
I am so sorry.
I guess I kind of
startled you, huh?
Wait, don't tell me.
You're the kid's family, right?
-Huh?
Wh--what kid?
-Of course, these
beautiful ladies
must be related to my
number one pupil, Ichigo!
-Are you serious?
Do you mean to tell
me my brother's
your number one pupil?
-But of course!
-Really?
That's so cool!
Can you believe it?
Ichigo's your number
one pupil, wow!
-And since I had a rare day
off, I came here in cognito
to hang out with him but uh--
uh, have you two seen him?
-In cognito?
Looks to me like you're
doing a bang up job of that.
-Actually our brother
isn't home right now.
-Oh my goodness!
-Guess you're done here.
So why don't you go on home?
[howling overhead] Wait,
what is that?
Oh, you bad spirits.
Step away, children!
[yells]
-Don Kanonji!
Karin, what do you
think those things were?
-Uh, you mean you can
actually see those things?
-Uh I guess I can.
-Now I get it.
It looks like you're
able to see them too.
-And now for the big finish!
Golden cannonball!
Ah!
Whoops, uh-- my bad!
Hey, listen-- don't
underestimate the enemy!
They show no mercy! [yells]
-Don Kanonji!
-Uh, what?
-It's time for the
legendary red bat!
-Mission accomplished!
[screams] [crash]
KARIN (OFFSCREEN): Hey!
-Don Kanonji!
[moaning] Are you all right?
-So now little girl,
are you sure you're OK?
-Uh, I'm fine, I guess.
[crowd chattering]
-Huh?
-Hey, Yuzu, Karin!
I don't believe
it you lucky dogs!
Don Kanonji saved you!
I'm so jealous!
-Mission complete!
Wa ha ha ha ha!
-Hey Don Kanonji, why
not join us for some tea!
-Come on!
You two come with me!
-It's a pretty good tea,
even if I-- huh, you're gone?
Well then I guess I'll
just see you at home!
[gasping for breath]
-Pardon me for asking,
but who are you anyway?
-I'm Ginta, the one who'll be
batting cleanup in the majors
someday.
-And I'm Ururu.
-I'm Yuzu Kurosaki.
-Kurosaki?
Then I'm sure you
must know carrot top.
-Hm?
-You mean you know our brother?
-Sort of.
See that cat?
-Seems a number of
Hollows are popping up
lured here by its
spiritual power.
-Huh, Hollows?
That's what you call them?
-That's right.
And it'd be best for everyone if
we just let that cat's spirit--
uh, pass on peacefully.
-Wait, what are
you talking about?
Cammy isn't a ghost.
-Huh?
You got it all wrong.
That cat is a spirit!
-Is not!
How dare you say such things!
-But it's true!
Believe me, that mangy
old cat's already dead!
-No way this cat is dead!
Why are you being so mean?
[crying]
-Jeez, come on!
You're both carrot top's
sister's and you can't even
figure out what's going on?
-Wonderful and totally great!
[laughing] I've got to be the
luckiest man in the world.
Imagine kinds with such talent
gathered here before me.
Though your skills
are weaker than mine.
You know what's next?
You are all going
to be my pupils!
-Not interested!
-Yeah, [coughing] Let
me tell you something.
I'm starting to really
like you boys and girls.
I have been looking for
sharp kids with young power
just like all of you.
So come on kids, let's go!
What are you waiting for?
Hey kids, chop chop!
Come on the spirit
hunter says let's go!
-Listen to me mister.
You want another one?
-Such a pity.
There is power
hidden within you.
I do know that much.
But I'll do it.
So much power, so little time.
Yes, all right.
The first thing I need to
do if I'm going to help you
is to take a good
look at your powers.
-I don't understand
what this is all about,
but I guess this
is my one chance
to explore my true power.
-Just in case you
couldn't tell, I
haven't had the chance
to get serious either.
-I've never seen such
energetic children!
-I'm taller than you!
-Yeah, I got news for you!
-Come on, follow me!
-Height's got nothing
to do with it!
-Come on kids!
KARIN (OFFSCREEN):
Of course it does!
-It's in your hands.
JINTA (OFFSCREEN): Does not!
Hey don't stand
up in front of me.
-Do you know what?
Without protection that
cat'll be attacked again.
-Do you think so?
Before we had Don Kanonji
to make sure we were safe.
What do we do now?
-I could ask my boss
if he would help.
-Ah.
YUZU (OFFSCREEN): Out to lunch?
-Sorry about that.
-Oh, it's all right.
Don't worry.
-What do you want to do?
-Well if you think this man
Kisuke can do something,
then I guess I'll wait
till he comes back.
There's really nothing
else we can do.
-Mm hm.
[cat meows]
-Thank you, Ururu.
-Hm?
[gasp] Hollows!
They've come here now.
Hurry, inside!
[howling]
-Go out the back door!
-Ururu!
[cat meows]
Everything's all right.
Don't worry.
I'll protect you.
-Damnit!
How long is he going to
keep us waiting like this?
DON KANONJI (OFFSCREEN):
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Boys and girls!
[coughing] The century's
premiere spiritualist,
Don Kanonji, at your service!
-You wanted to
see my true power?
Then ready or not, here I go!
-I'm coming too!
-Hold your horses!
[yelling] Now just
wait a minute, kids.
You don't think that
I'm the enemy, do you?
-Huh?
-Come on now kids,
think about it.
What's the point in heroes
trying to fight each other?
-Well.
-There is none.
But seriously, I've
been kicking around
the idea of creating
a special team of kids
just like you-- kind-hearted,
self-sacrificing kids
with their own special
powers who share my vision
and want to join me in keeping
the peace in this town!
-Huh?
-And this team would be called
the Karakura Superheroes!
You know the entertainment
world is youth-oriented.
Everyone's looking for any grade
schooler with special talents
to become the next big thing.
Well if you ask me, you
two have the potential
to shoot right to the top.
Well how about it?
Will you form a unit--
-(IN HEAD) So long winded.
-(IN HEAD) This is stupid.
-And I'm happy to inform
you that since both of you
are the first two Karakura
Superheroes I've recruited,
guess what!
It's your lucky day!
The red position is still open!
-Uh, red?
-It's the lead.
Oh and did I mention
that I intend
to turn this little
project into a segment
on my top-rated
Spirit Hunter TV show?
-Television!
-I'm in!
-Well, then I guess I'll
have no choice, since it's
an opportunity to keep the
peace in Karakura town.
-OK!
Your enthusiasm has gotten
you a place on the squad!
-Great since no one
objects, I'll be red, OK?
-Hey!
You can't just decide like that!
I'm red!
You got that?
Me, red!
Red, me!
-Shut your pie hole.
Come on, you know
better than that.
No girl can be red.
-What?
Are you looking for a fight?
-Oh man, what a
pain in the butt.
-Ugh!
There is absolutely no way
I'm going to let you be red!
-That's it.
Get ready for our first job.
She's in terrible danger.
Bad spirits are
after your sister.
-I can't understand a
single word he's saying.
[panting] [gasp]
[gasp]
-Cammy?
[hiss]
[roar]
[yells]
-Smells like bad spirits!
Huh?
-Not this time!
[bang]
[screaming]
-Cammy?
[cat meows]
-Oh Cammy.
Huh?
-Sorry to have kept you waiting
little girl but there's no need
to worry anymore
because we're here!
-Karakura Red-- Karin Kurosaki!
-And the real Karakura
Red-- Jinta Hanakari!
-Hey, just one minute
there jerk face.
What do you think you're doing?
Didn't you hear me?
I'm red, got it?
-Would you shut up?
It's already decided!
I'm red!
-No way I'm definitely red!
Red is me!
-Look, this is what
we're going to do.
We'll decide who will be red
based on your performance
today, OK?
-Huh?
-Yeah!
-I'll show you who's red!
-Don Kanonji!
And Karin, too!
[howling]
-Secret attack!
Super spirit javelin!
With this device you can
reach any bad spirit.
With detachable
saw and solid grip,
even high branches are a breeze.
These extendable pruning sheers
are so easy to manouv-- oh!
How dare you!
Come back and fight
me you coward!
-You're too slow!
Beat it!
Go on, scram!
-Oh yeah, come on!
You show 'em, sister!
I shall entreat the super
spirit of the javelin to you!
[laughing]
-The lead is mine!
-And now batting cleanup,
number 55, Jinta Hanakari!
-Aha!
Excellent swing!
Who could ever forget
an effort like that?
You're the super star of suave!
-That's right!
It's only natural
because I'm red!
-Karin!
-Hey Yuzu, get away!
-OK.
-Oh?
Huh?
-Hey wait hold it!
I'm right behind you Yuzu!
-Huh?
-Stay down!
-Ururu?
-Huh?
What is this?
Another one of the
new generation?
Wonderful!
There are so many
red candidates here!
-Aw, Ururu, showing up
out of the blue like that.
Well listen, you're not
taking the red title from me!
-How many times do I have
to tell you, you're not red!
-OK, rule number
one-- only the recruit
who gives a number
one performance
deserves the title of red!
-I am not going to lose!
-Oh yeah?
I'll show you!
[yelling]
-This is great!
The Karakura superheroes
are born right here today!
[laughing]
-Aren't you going to
fight too, Don Kanonji?
-Hey kids!
That kind of fighting won't
earn you the title of red!
-(GROANING) Useless!
Hey, maybe I can use that
soccer ball over there!
[grunts] Score!
So, do you see the power of red?
-Like I said, I'm
red, understand?
[gasping]
[howling]
-What's that?
-So you're finally making an
appearance, eh, bad spirit
king?
[stomping]
-It's coming this way!
-What do you say there children?
This looks like a job for
the Karakura Superheroes!
-Yeah!
-But before we attack,
let's go over our strategy.
-Are you nuts?
We don't have time!
[howling]
[yelling]
[crash]
[screams]
-Yuzu!
-Cammy.
[roar]
[gasps]
-Yuzu!
No!
-What's that down there?
URURU (OFFSCREEN): Do
you think it's an ally?
DON KANONJI (OFFSCREEN):
It's a miracle!
Our combined desire for
just called forth a miracle!
[crash]
[screams]
DON KANONJI (OFFSCREEN):
That is the hero
robot sent to us by the gods.
Karakura's sonic lion!
[screams]
-It's time for us to
join the sonic lion too!
Let's go!
[yelling]
-Hold together!
Karakura attack formation!
Karakura canon!
Karakura gold [gong] Yeah!
Feel the wrath of the golden
cannonballs of justice!
Wah!
-Ah!
Jinta home run!
-Karin style!
Dance shot!
[crash]
-It's coming, Ururu!
-OK!
[roar]
-The Karakura
Superheroes prevail!
And our mission
was accomplished!
Wa ha ha ha ha ha ha ha ha!
KARIN (OFFSCREEN): Did
that thing really work?
DON KANONJI (OFFSCREEN):
Why of course it did!
It delivered the final blow!
JINTA (OFFSCREEN): No way.
YUZU (OFFSCREEN):
Oh, I remember now.
I did meet Cammy before.
It was raining.
[gasp]
[cat meows]
-Oh, here, here you go.
See you later.
Oh.
[cat meows]
[tires screeching]
[gasp]
YUZU (OFFSCREEN):
If I hadn't come by,
then Cammy wouldn't
have had to die.
I thought maybe you'd
hold a grudge against me.
But--
[cat meows]
-Cammy.
-Yuzu.
[gasp]
-Karin!
-Thank goodness!
-Huh?
What happened?
-You see, the legendary
Karakura sonic lion,
which was properly summoned
through our extreme power
of justice, was responsible
for saving your life.
-He's right!
Together we all summoned this
absolutely amazing thing!
-Hey, I don't see him anywhere.
Where'd he go.
KARIN (OFFSCREEN): That's right.
[cat meows]
KARIN (OFFSCREEN): He's gone.
JINTA (OFFSCREEN): Too bad,
you should have seen him.
[laughing]
-Secret?
[cat meows]
-All right then.
I guess that it can
be our little secret.
-What!
-What's happening?
[gasps]
-It's for the best.
I'm glad though.
I think that it was
able to pass on.
-Um, so then does that mean that
the cat was really a spirit?
-If that's what happened
then it was probably
able to come to terms with
whatever regrets it had.
[crying]
-Huh?
-I wasn't able to do
anything for Cammy.
Nothing!
I couldn't do
anything for Cammy!
[crying]
-Hey, uh-- see that was just
his way of saying thanks to you
just now.
-Is that true?
-Of course it is!
A man senses these things, OK?
-I hope it's true!
I hope it's true!
[crying]
-There, there.
-(IN HEAD) Cammy, thank you.
-Karakura pink--
Ururu Tsumugiya.
-Karakura red-- Karin Kurosaki.
-Karakura red-- Jinta Hanakari!
-I said I'm red!
Do you hear me?
-Shut up already!
I'm red!
-Well you're not fit to be red!
-You're more like yellow!
-And Karakura gold, the leader
producer of the Karakura
Superheroes, is the charismatic,
highly-rated television
personality and natural
born hero Don Kanonji!
-Leader?
-What do you mean,
Karakura gold?
That's a bunch crap!
-Tune in every one!
It's time you put
aside your differences
and follow your leader producer!
-We quit!
[theme music]
-Oh, that was such a nice story.
Everyone did their best.
Not!
What about everyone's idol, Kon?
What happened to him?
Who's responsible?
-No one cares about
your existence.
-Hey, I even got new stuffing!
And I was waiting,
all by myself!