[theme music]
NARRATOR: Sosuke
Aizen was the man
who revolted against
the Soul Society
and brought Hueco Mundo
under his control.
Aizen set out to
create a key that
would open a portal to the
Soul Society's Royal Palace--
a key known as the Oken.
Karakura Town is
the location that
was targeted as the site
for the Oken's creation.
When Ichigo and the
13 Court Guard Squads
caught wind of his intent,
they began training
for a winter showdown
with the Espada,
as they would need all the
strength they could muster.
However, after learning
of Orihime's ability
to reject all
forms of phenomena,
Aizen ordered
Ulquiorra to kidnap her
from the world of the living.
Determined to rescue
Orihime, Ichigo, Renji, Uryu,
Chad, and Rukia broke into
Aizen's stronghold, Las Noches.
But what awaited them was
a battle more demanding
than they could
have ever imagined.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
I'm going at this guy
with everything I've got!
Bankai!
-A Bankai, is it?
-[growls]
-[gasps]
-Aaah!
-Ungh.
Ungh.
Impossible.
-[gasping]
Ungh!
-Impressive.
Even using both my hands,
I couldn't stop it.
I am quite surprised.
Was that it?
Finished, Ichigo?
-[gasps]
You can't.
-Hm.
How unfortunate.
-[groaning]
-It's time to give up.
Ugh!
-[panting]
I'll never surrender.
[panting]
So it's very simple.
What I have to do is
defeat you in battle,
then this war is
as good as over.
-I see.
It looks as if you
have been misinformed.
[rips]
-[gasps]
You're the fourth.
-Correct.
Espada number 4,
Ulquiorra Cefir.
Of all the Espada, my
power is ranked fourth.
-Ugh!
Uhh.
ULQUIORRA: Ichigo
Kurosaki, it is pointless.
You cannot defeat me.
Even if you were lucky
enough to succeed,
there are three
Espada ranked above me
or much stronger than I. Try
as many times as you like--
-Uhh.
Ugh.
---the results will
always be the same.
This is the end, then.
If you can still move
in that condition,
leave Hueco Mundo immediately.
If you can't move,
then die there.
-Hmmm.
Hm.
[gasps]
[sobs]
-You know what I
brought you here to do.
Now, heal.
-[snickers]
[laughs maniacally]
It's about time.
Now, we can get
down to business.
Grind!
Pantera!
[roars]
-What the hell?
The shock wave.
He generates that much
power just by screaming?
-Hah!
[grunts]
-Damn it!
-Uh.
Oh!
-Eeyah!
-Ugh!
-[laughs diabolically]
Come on, Ichigo Kurosaki,
is that all you've got?
[whooshing]
-[grunts]
-Rrgh!
Argh!
Eeyah!
-Ugh!
-Eeyah!
-Yah!
-[grunts]
[heaving]
-It was fun.
But now, it's over.
-[heaving]
-Please don't die.
Don't die, Ichigo!
You don't have to win. [sobs]
And you don't have
to fight for me.
Just don't get hurt.
I couldn't bear it.
-Desgarron.
It's my ultimate technique.
Haaargh!
-Ugh!
-[laughing]
It's over.
You're finished, Ichigo.
ICHIGO: Now, you make me sick.
I'm going to wipe that
smirk off your face!
GRIMMJOW (VOICEOVER):
They are all cowards.
Fine, if that's what you
want, I'll eat you all,
become my flesh and blood,
and see what lies ahead.
I am, I am the king!
ICHIGO: You know,
I got news for you.
You're not the only
one who wants to win.
Hrgh!
-[gasps]
Eyah!
ICHIGO: So I'm going
to destroy you!
And Ulquiorra!
I'm going to defeat Aizen!
And then I'm going to take Rukia,
and Chad,
and Uryu,
and Renji!
I'm going to take Orihime!
All of my friends!
And bring them
home safe with me!
I won't lose to you!
-Ugh!
Damn you!
Ugh, hah.
Uh, ohh.
-Hm.
-[sobs]
Are-- are you--
---hurt?
I was going to I ask you that.
I'm fine.
Good.
That's a relief.
-[chuckles]
Well, you know me, I'm
made of pretty tough stuff.
Even when I was a kid, I never
caught colds and-- [gasps]
Ichigo, what are you doing?
Get me down.
-Well, yeah.
That's what I'm trying to do.
With all this rubble
everywhere, it
would be much easier to carry
you than look for a stairway.
-But I'm, oh, oh--
-What is it?
Did I do something wrong?
-Well, I'm heavy.
-Nah, don't sweat it.
You're not as heavy as you look.
Agh!
-[shrieks]
Ack, uh!
What the hell?
-That is not how
you speak to a lady.
There are rules you
got to stick to when
talking about certain topics!
No matter what she
weighs, you always
tell her she's light as
air, even if she's a hippo!
ORIHIME: Please stop now.
You're actually
making me feel worse.
-All right, then.
I got to go.
After all, somebody's got
to go help Chad and Rukia.
-Hey, what about us?
-Huh?
-You're not just going
to leave us here?
-Nah, I wouldn't do that.
Just come with me.
It's too dangerous
to stay here anyway.
[rustling]
-[whimpers]
-Uh!
-Huh!
-Ungh.
[heaves]
-It's Grimmjow.
-[grunts]
-Ichigo.
GRIMMJOW: [heaving]
Uh.
[panting]
You can't defeat me.
Look at you.
You're too weak.
I'll never lose to you!
-Just let it go, Grimmjow.
You've already lost.
You say you're
some kind of king?
But killing everyone
you happen to dislike
makes you a king
with no subjects.
What's the point in that?
If you truly hate me, I'll
fight you anytime you want.
But for now, you
need to give up.
-Never!
I'll show you!
Ugh, uh.
[groans]
MAN: You just don't know
when to call it quits.
Hurry up and die.
I want him for myself.
-What the hell?
Who are you?
Are you an Espada?
I asked you a question!
Answer me!
-[grunts]
Nnoitra, you bastard.
Uurgh.
-What is this?
Are you still alive?
Huh?
Well, what are you doing?
-You tell me first.
Why would you attack a
guy who can't even move?
-Haargh!
-Uaargh!
-Grimmjow, you are
a miserable sight.
Haah!
First, you lose to this
guy, then he protects you.
Ridiculous!
All right, Soul Reaper,
what's your name?
-I'm Ichigo Kurosaki.
-Ichigo, ha?
I'll remember that.
But the thing is, you
won't be alive much longer!
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
What the hell?
He's scrawny, but he
has incredible strength.
I can't hold it!
Aagh!
-Ichigo, no!
-Tesra!
-Sir!
-Ugh!
-Orihime!
-What are you looking at?
-Let Orihime go!
-Oh, you're one of those.
The kind of hero who
thinks if your girl's safe,
you actually have a
shot at taking me down?
Well, I have news for you.
So now, you know.
That's my rank.
That careless piece
of garbage you barely
managed to defeat back there,
I rank higher than he does.
You're as good as dead.
Look at that, I
forgot your name.
-[panting]
Why are we running away again?
Why?
-Isn't it obvious?
Our only goal is to
find and rescue Orihime.
We don't have time for Espadas.
You want to wait around
for that guy in a room
where we can't use our powers?
-No way.
And besides, now
it looks like we're
going to have to save Rukia
and Chad as well as Orihime.
-It certainly does.
[panting]
Huh?
-What?
It can't be.
-Is this--
-Welcome back.
-Huh?
-Now, then, shall we raise
the curtain on Act 2?
[theme music]
SZAYELAPORRO: Next time, I'll
show off my best illusion.
The spectacular Szayelaporro
will be in rare form.
RENJI: Oh, yeah?
Well, we've got our own trick
where I saw Uryu in half.
URYU: You have done that
trick before, right?
RENJI: Nope.