[music - aqua timez, "velonica"]
NARRATOR: In the Soul
Society, mysterious deaths
began to occur in the Rukon
District where people vanished,
leaving only their
clothes behind.
Squad Nine was investigating
these incidents
when someone attacked them.
During the fight, both
Captain Kensei Muguruma
and Lieutenant Mashiro
Kuna's spiritual pressures
suddenly disappeared.
The 13 Court Guard Squads
investigated, and determined
that a worst-case
scenario had occurred.
Kisuke Urahara, who had sent
Lieutenant Hiyori Sarugaki
to the scene following a
request from Squad Nine,
tried to mount a rescue attempt.
-[gasps] Let me, sir.
Please, sir, let me go there.
[breathing heavily]
-No.
-I have to go!
My second in command is
already heading there!
I should--
-Kisuke!
Just control yourself.
You're making a scene.
You were the one who made the
choice to send her out there.
Can't you see that
you begging to go
save her is an insult
to her abilities?
NARRATOR: Ultimately,
five officers
were dispatched-- Rojuro
"Rose" Otoribashi, captain
of Squad Three; Shinji Hirako,
the captain of Squad Five;
Love Aikawa, captain
of Squad Seven;
Hachigen Ushoda, lieutenant
of the Kido Corps;
and Lisa Yadomaru,
lieutenant of Squad Nine.
Each was a skilled warrior.
When the members arrived
at their destination,
they were confronted
by a strange figure.
-[grunts]
-[gasps] Shinji?
-Hey, Shinji!
-Hiyori, you all right?
-Kensei.
-[growls]
-Just what the hell
is going on here?
-You think that
thing's really Kensei?
WIth that mask,
spiritual pressure,
it's almost like
he's become a Hollow.
-I'm not sure what
to think either.
There's a chance it's
Kensei, but maybe not.
-[growls]
-Anyway, there's one
thing I'm sure of.
If we don't draw our swords
right now, we'll be dead.
-[growls louder] [screams]
NARRATOR: What
Shinji and the others
saw standing before
them was Kensei,
transformed into something
resembling a Hollow.
He had lost complete
control of himself,
and attacked the others.
Everyone reluctantly
fought back.
However, Kensei now had
tremendous strength.
And when he was joined
by Mashiro, who had also
been transformed,
they both began
to slowly overpower
the Soul Reapers.
-Hey, Rose!
Behind you!
[explosion]
[groans]
-Gochutekkan!
[both grunting]
-Bakudo number 63-- Sajo Sabaku!
-[grunts] [groans]
-[groans] Aaah!
-[both gasp]
-Glad to see you're
alert during your rounds.
-Captain!
Captain Kyoraku!
Is there something going on?
You're almost never
out at this hour.
-Well, I had a little trouble
falling asleep tonight.
Maybe I'm getting
paranoid in my old age.
-(BOTH) Huh?
-Forget it.
Looks like Lieutenant Aizen
had trouble sleeping as well.
--[both gasp] (BOTH) Have a
good evening, Lieutenant Aizen.
-Keep up the good work, men.
And stay alert.
-(BOTH) Good night,
Captain Kyoraku.
SHUNSUI KYORAKU: Good night.
-Huh?
-Evening, sir.
-Uh, let me see.
Ah, yes.
You're Nanao Ise.
Am I right?
-Um, yes sir.
I'm honored that you
remembered who I was, sir.
-Of course. [laughs] Well,
you are the youngest child
we have around here now.
I try to make it a
special point to remember
the names of every girl
that's training with us here.
And in your particular case,
that was especially easy,
since you come to
see me every month.
Oh, that's right.
The first of the month
happens to be today.
-Yes.
I'm aware of that.
I was on the way to see
Lieutenant Yadomaru because she
offered to read with
me again this month.
-That makes sense.
But I'm afraid it will
be impossible You see,
Lieutenant Yadomaru
isn't here tonight.
-Nobody told me What happened?
-She's on an important mission.
-Oh.
-But don't worry.
She'll be back in the morning.
You can count on it.
-[grunts]
-Stop this, Kensei.
What's happened, my friend?
This is completely out
of character for you.
You've never been
the kind of weakling
who would strike a girl.
-[growls]
-Are you going to
be all right, Lisa?
Are you hurt?
-I got this.
-Don't try to be strong
if you're injured.
It puts us at risk.
-I'm fine.
-I'm not sure it matters
one way or the other.
If things keep on like this,
we're all going to be defeated.
-Hachi, is there any other
way we can neutralize him?
-Yes, there is.
But there's a problem.
He easily broke
through Sajo Sabaku.
This time, we'd have to go
at him with maximum force.
And to do that,
I'd need all of you
to create a surefire opportunity
for me to use my Bakudo.
That's the only move
I can see that would
have a chance of working.
However, the problem is that
my Bakudo could take all of us
with it as well.
-Is that all?
LISA YADOMARU: Love?
-I'll try to distract
him, all right?
While I'm doing
that, you'll have
to find a way to capture him.
-I'm going along with you.
-And me as well.
-With the injuries
you've suffered?
You've both gone crazy.
I'll handle it myself.
I need you to watch my back.
-Big showoff.
-Look who's talking.
-Rose!
-I'm on it.
Everyone get back.
-Aaah!
[grunts] (VOICEOVER)
Damn, how solid can he be?
[grunts]
-Aaah!
-[growling]
-Hachi!
-Bakudo number 99-- Restrict!
-[grunts]
-[breathing heavily]
-A level 90 Bakudo without
an incantation, eh?
That was a nice trick.
-Yes, well, I outdid
myself this time.
-OK then.
How are we supposed to
reverse his condition?
Are you able to do
something using Kido?
-Even if I could, I'm not
sure what got him this way.
I might damage it
even more before I
could get him back to normal.
-[coughing]
-What's the matter, Hiyori?
You feeling all right?
Hachi, forget about
Kensei for now.
We'd better start
healing our friend here.
-Shin-- Shinji-- let go of me.
-[gasps]
-[grunts]
-[all gasp]
-Aaah!
-Hiyori!
-What's happening to her?
-What?
-[gasps]
-[grunts] Is this-- Lisa!
Rose!
Hachi!
[grunts]
-Ohh.
-[grunts weakly]
-Hold on a minute.
Kaname.
Tell me, why did you
do that to Kensei?
You betrayed him,
your own captain.
SOSUKE AIZEN: He
didn't betray him.
He's actually quite loyal.
As a matter of fact,
Kaname was just
loyally following my orders.
You of all people
can understand that,
so please don't hold it
against him, Captain Hirako.
-Sosuke I should have
known it was you.
-You mean you were onto me?
That was very good.
-Of course.
That's why I'm a captain.
-When did you suspect?
-From the beginning.
From the time you were
in your mother's womb,
and maybe even before then.
-How witty of you.
-To be perfectly
honest, I always
felt you were someone dangerous,
someone who could never really
be trusted.
And as long as we're
telling the truth here,
that's the real reason I
chose you to be my lieutenant.
I only did it to keep
an eye on you, Sosuke.
--[chuckles] Yes, I must thank
you for that, Captain Hirako.
I depended on your
deep distrust of me
to make sure you kept watching.
That's what made
misleading you so simple.
-You were never out of my sight.
What are you saying?
-You were keeping an
eye on the wrong person.
-[gasps]
SOSUKE AIZEN: During
this past month,
when you were so
aware of my presence,
it wasn't me who
was following you.
-What?
SOSUKE AIZEN: I have
a very useful ability.
I can make anyone
mistake any phenomenon
for something else at will.
That is the true power of my
Zanpakuto, Kyoka Suigetsu.
I refer to it by
the common term,
complete and utter hypnosis.
-You're saying
you hypnotized me?
-You are a sharp
intellect, Captain Hirako.
But you're suspicious, and
that gave me an opening.
You never received me as your
second in command the way
the other captains did.
If you had, perhaps
you might have
been able to see through me.
However, you did not.
And because you didn't
trust me, you always
kept me at arm's length,
never opening up to me
or giving me information.
And of course, you never
tried to get closer to me.
That's why I was able to take
advantage of you so easily.
The fact is, you never realized
that at a certain point,
I switched places with a
completely different person.
I made sure the man who took
my place memorized everything
about my normal behavior
patterns, and especially
my patterns of
interaction when dealing
with you and the
other squad members.
If you had really been
paying attention to me,
even slight differences
in habits or behaviors
would've seemed out
of place to you.
You were too arrogant to
believe that I was smart enough
to be one step ahead of you.
Because you never
really knew who I was,
you now lie there
completely helpless.
Do you understand the
depths of your situation
now, my dear Captain Hirako?
-[breathing heavily] Sosuke.
-Oh, and one more thing.
Let me enlighten you
about your assertion
that you chose me
as your lieutenant
in order to keep an eye on me.
Actually, you're mistaken.
It was the other way around.
-What are you talking about?
SOSUKE AIZEN: Think back to
the start of our relationship.
Just as captains have the right
to select their lieutenants,
squad members have the right
to refuse an assignment.
And while that right is very
rarely exercised, particularly
when you're starting
out, it still exists.
I had the choice of not
becoming your lieutenant.
So why didn't I do that?
Because it was the
ideal situation.
You didn't realize
it at the time,
but your excessive
suspicion and wariness of me
was just what I needed.
It played perfectly into
the successful completion
of my plans.
Now do you understand what
I've been talking about?
You did not choose me.
I chose you, Caption Hirako.
I suppose when it
comes right down it,
that you owe your
friends here an topology.
Because you were chosen by me,
they ended up on the ground
as casualties, through
no fault of their own.
-Sosuke!
[gasping]
-I wasn't actually sure it would
work, but thank you, Captain,
for going for my cheap taunt.
-What's happening to me?
[gasps]
-Sosuke!
[gasping]
-What's happening to me?
[all choking]
-Sosuke, what's going on?
[explosion]
[shinji gasping and struggling]
-As we thought, it appears
that an agitated state
helps to accelerate the
Hollowfication process.
-Hollowfication.
What have you done to us?
-I see no reason to
explain, Captain.
[shinji gasping and struggling]
HOLLOW (VOICEOVER): Shinji.
-Kaname?
-Yes sir?
-No!
Don't!
I don't know what's
going on here,
but if you think everything is
going to go smoothly according
to your plan, you're
gravely mistaken.
-Hmm?
Surprising resistance,
considering
the progress of
the Hollowfication.
-Hold on.
What was it that Sosuke
said a few minutes ago?
-As we thought, it appears
that an agitated state
helps to accelerate the
Hollowfication process.
-That was it, which means
that I maintain my composure,
this transformation
process won't progress.
[exhales heavily]
-What shall I do, sir?
-Go ahead and continue.
We'll just have one
less sample, that's all.
--[gasps] So, I'm
just a sample to you?
Interesting way to
describe a comrade.
[both grunting]
-It appears he's
about to get defeated.
-Yes, you may be right.
SHINJI HIRAKO (VOICEOVER):
What's going on?
I have almost no
control over my body.
I can't feel any pain.
It so strange.
It's almost like someone other
than me is doing the fighting.
-[grunts]
[both grunting]
SHINJI HIRAKO
(VOICEOVER): No wonder
we had such a hard time
dealing with Kensei,
even when we outnumbered him.
But at this rate, I
may have a chance.
-[grunts]
-I'm sorry, sir.
But don't worry,
I'll finish him now.
-Don't concern yourself over it.
I actually expected
this would happen.
In fact, I theorized
that the speed
at which Hollow
transformation would occur
would differ from
individual to individual.
[grunts, gasps]
-I must admit, it was quite an
interesting process to observe.
However, your continued
existence is immaterial.
I believe it's time to finish
you off, dear Captain Hirako.
In the end, I hope you'll
remember one thing.
Any betrayal you
can see is trivial.
What is truly frightening,
and much more lethal,
is the betrayal you ca see.
Goodbye.
I must commend you.
You people have provided
wonderful research material.
[shinji screaming]
-Well, unexpected guests.
How very interesting.
[MUSIC - SHION TSUJI, "SKY CHORD
- OTONA NI NARU KIMI HE"]
ICHIGO KUROSAKI
(VOICEOVER): The storyline
from the past comes
to an end next time,
and I finally get
to appear again!
WOMAN (VOICEOVER):
Not so fast, Ichigo.
There's another plot line coming
in following this story arc.
ICHIGO KUROSAKI
(VOICEOVER): What?
You mean--
WOMAN (VOICEOVER): You'll
be stuck in the "Illustrated
Guide to Soul
Reapers" for a while.
ICHIGO KUROSAKI
(VOICEOVER): But I'm
supposed to be the
star of this series!