[music playing]
[theme music]
NARRATOR: In order
to save Orihime,
who was kidnapped
by the Arrancars,
Ichigo, Chad, Uryu,
Rukia, and Renji
have all snuck into Hueco
Mundo, the realm of the hollows.
The journey to Aizen's
fortress, Las Noches,
has been hard fought, as
our heroes have struggled
against endless attacks
from the Arrancar forces.
-All right, let's go, Renji.
-Hey, you're not the boss, here.
Smart ass.
[roaring fire sound]
-(TOGETHER)Yee-ah.
NARRATOR: Meanwhile,
in Las Noches,
Aizen has shown
Orihime the Hogyoku
as a sign of good faith.
This has prompted Orihime
to make a decision.
ORIHIME (VOICEOVER): Thank you,
Ichigo, for coming to save me.
But now I know what
I have to do here.
It's something
that only I can do.
I have to use my power to
erase the Hogyoku's existence.
NARRATOR: Upon
entering Las Noches,
our heroes find themselves
in a room filled
with disturbing spiritual
pressures and five doorways
with five separate
paths into the fortress.
At Rukia's request, they split
up to investigate each one.
[smacking]
-As we approach the
crucial battlegrounds,
believe that our blades
will not shatter,
believe that our
resolve will not weaken.
Though our paths may
diverge, our iron hearts
will remain together.
Swear that though the land
itself may break asunder,
we will come back here alive.
[rushing wind]
-Uhn.
[panting]
-Hm.
[sound of running feet]
-[panting] Huh?
-Ichigo!
-Eh?
-What the?
No.
-Wait.
-I can't.
You're not supposed to be here.
Go away.
-Don't leave me, Ichigo.
Nel wants to come.
-What a pest.
OK, fine.
If that's the way
you want to play.
-Ooh, super-acceleration.
-Huah!
Huah, uhn.
Ahh.
-I wanted to see you, Ichigo.
I missed you. [sobbing]
-What?
Are you nuts?
-Ichigo.
[sobs]
-Give me a break, will you?
-[crying]
-Stop crying.
-Ichigo.
-What happened to
all the others?
-Oh, you mean Bawabawa?
I left him outside.
He wouldn't be happy in
a building like this.
To live, he has to
eat sand all day long.
-I didn't mean him.
I meant, you know,
Don what's-his-face?
Uh, no.
Not him. [buzzer]
-Nel's confused.
Who?
-Come on, those guys who are
always traveling with you?
-Oh, Dondochakka and Pesche?
They're right behind, now.
They follow Nel everywhere.
[hollow footsteps]
-They're missing!
Nel's lost them.
This is horrible.
Nel never goes anywhere
without those two guys.
Nel's doomed.
Nel won't make it.
-You know, I think the
only thing lost around here
is your mind.
Eyuh.
-Ichigo, is there
something wrong?
-Be quiet.
-Mm.
-Come on out.
You might as well come out here!
I know you're somewhere
in the corridor!
Eyuh.
Damn.
You're not getting away.
-Heh, who said I wanted to.
Hyuh?
Doh!
Eeah!
-Um, hey, are you all right?
-Yee-ah!
-(TOGETHER) Ahh!
-Hieah!
Rhuhh-hey ahh.
Ha ha.
Ahh hoo.
Whoo.
Yee ahh hah.
[coughing]
-Uhhh.
-Ta da. [coughing]
-Hm?
What's with you two mocosos?
Aren't you impressed?
Why are you giving me that face?
-Well, I mean.
-Do not play stupid
with me, nino.
Tell me why you're
giving me that face!
-What's your problem?
And stop and repeating yourself.
-Are you trying to tell
me you're not completely
blown away by my magnificent
entrance just now?
-Magnificent entrance?
Excuse me, but didn't
you just slip and fall?
-What?
That was all planned.
How can you pretend
to be so calm?
-Believe me, I'm not pretending.
I don't find you
all that impressive.
-You're trying to rattle me.
I see what you're doing.
Did you order the girl to
act unimpressed as well?
-Uh, ahh.
-Heh.
Well it won't work.
I am secure enough to
know that not everybody is
going to react in
the proper way.
And it hardly matters
to me, since you're both
about to be killed.
Now, prepare
yourself soul reaper.
I am know as Dordoni
the Magnificent.
I am Arrancar number 103.
And it is my job to destroy you.
-Tortolloni the what?
Is that some kind of pasta?
-No, you fool.
It has nothing to do with food.
Dordoni not Tortolloni!
Leave me a little respect, nino!
Now listen up and pay attention.
I hate repeating myself.
My name's Dordoni, and
I'm Arrancar number 103.
-103?
Oh, brother.
That's a pretty high
number isn't it?
-Yeah, really high.
-Didn't you say they
were only supposed
to have two digit numbers.
-That's right, two digits max.
And you know what?
I've never even heard of
one with three digits.
-Stop that.
What are you two whispering
about over there?
-Ahh.
-Huh?
-How dare you?
I can see that you
have no respect for me.
-I'm sorry.
It's just that you
seem really weak.
What was that?
Take me on, and we'll
see who's the weaker one,
you little smart-ass.
You're going to pay for that
mouth of yours, just you wait.
Prepare to be amazed
at my strength.
[whining grunts and groans]
-Hm?
-[WHINING, SHOUTING GRUNTS AND
GROANS]
-What the?
-What the hell's with
all these weird moves?
-[taunting laugh]
-[angry grunt]
-Hai-ee.
-Ta.
[angry grunt]
-Hoo-ey.
Hwee.
[taunting laugh]
-Damn it.
Are you going to fight or not?
-Ooh.
Ha ha.
Hm.
Well, now, what's the problem?
You're not even close
to landing a blow.
You're way out of
your league, nino.
You think you can challenge Lord
Aizen with your pitiful skills?
Ha-hee.
-Shut up!
-Wha?
You won't even last two seconds.
Aiee-hee.
Whoo-hoo.
Ahh.
Aahh, ahhh, oww.
Oof.
-Hah, serves you right. [laughs]
-Hm?
Huh?
Ugh.
-[laughs]
-What's so funny?
-Ohh!
Ah-uh-ahh.
--[laughs] Not so
funny now, is it?
That's what you get
for laughing at me.
-Ooh, oah.
-Eh.
Ah.
No!
-[whimpering]
-Sorry, I didn't know
you got hit so hard.
You all right?
--[whimpering] Got you
that time, Ichigo!
-Eyuh.
-It Nel's mask, so it
didn't hurt at all.
You should have seen
the look on your face.
-Ah, you little brat.
-You are not a bad
for an amateur, nino.
But guess what?
Most of your moves were revealed
in that skirmish we had.
With those skills, you
won't last very long.
ISHIGO: What a
freaking pain you are.
I was actually
worried about you!
-Hm?
-Nel wouldn't have done it if
you hadn't made fun of Nel.
It's your fault, Ichigo.
-You weren't supposed to
be here in the first place.
-Pay attention to me!
-(TOGETHER) Huh?
-Dude, I didn't even know
you were still conscious.
-Why are you awake?
-Because I'm amazing!
A little rock would
never hurt me!
-That's great.
So how about we stop
all this fighting,
and you let us get on our way?
We have things to do.
And we're kind of in a hurry.
-You are not going anywhere.
You don't have the
power to get past me.
Maybe you didn't notice,
but none of your attacks
were effective.
I don't know where you come up
with this superior attitude.
But you're annoying me!
-I was hoping to
avoid this, but I
guess I'll have to
start fighting for real.
-Ahhh!
-Yeee-ah.
-Ah, Kaname, I see you're
spying on our intruders.
That's not a very
sporting thing to do.
-Don't be a hypocrite.
You only came down here
to chat because you
were interested in how they were
progressing, the same as me.
Isn't that right, Gin?
-I was just joking.
Don't get so upset.
You take this much
too seriously.
Hm.
-Haaah.
-(PERTURBED) Oho.
Kaname, do something about
this crazy kid, will you?
-That'll do, Wonderweiss.
-Haaah.
Ahhh.
-That kid's a strange one.
But he's really taken a
liking to you, hasn't he?
-I believe those
with pure intentions
are drawn to each other.
The only problem
is I haven't quite
figured out what his intentions
are, pure or otherwise.
-Not being a person of
pure intentions, myself,
I can see why he doesn't
get along with me.
-That must explain why your very
presence makes him so nervous.
Come take a look at
what's happening.
The five of them have split up.
-Oh, you're right.
But that's good.
They'll have a lesser
chance of success
if they're each on their own.
I wonder if these
kids had any idea
as to the extent of
their strength levels?
-Indeed.
It looks like they've stumbled
onto an interesting area
of Hueco Mundo.
-Ah, yes, they're passing
through the Den of Tres Cifras.
-Tsuh.
-Ichigo!
-Eyuh.
What the hell?
How did he do that?
-Tres Cifras, ohhh.
-Yes.
Since you haven't
been here very long,
I'm sure nobody's bothered
to tell you about it.
Here's what it means.
-Getsuga tensho!
-Tres cifras is three digits.
If you mean an Arrancar
with a three digit number,
that being is inferior
and has been demoted.
That means it's done
something unforgivable
and been stripped of its rank.
All those with the
three digit number
are called Privaron Espada.
-Eyuh.
-Surprised are you?
Didn't your mother ever
teach you the lesson?
You should never judge people
by their outward appearance,
foolish nino tonto.
-Gah.
Uhn.
Eyah.
Heyah.
Uhn.
Hrm.
DORDONI: We are a group
known as the Privaron Espada.
-No.
What?
-Pay attention, soul
reaper, Privaron Espada.
It means one who has lost
his place as a full Espada.
In other words, any Arrancar
with a three digit number,
including me, used to be
a member of the Espada.
We're the most
powerful group here,
other than the current Espada.
Do you understand how
strong I am know, nino.
-Gyah.
-[roaring]
-Dyah!
Ehem.
He's been stringing me along.
-Hyahh!
-You bastard!
Eyah.
-Huah.
Huh, I see I have
your attention.
Huah!
-Gyaah!
-[grunting]
-He's faster than he was before.
Come back!
-Huah.
-Hiyai!
What?
DORDONI: Oh, come
now, you didn't
think that was the full
extent of my power, did you?
-Uhn.
Ahuh?
-Hoo-ah.
-Damn it.
-Yee-ah!
-Huah.
Yee-ah!
Huah.
Ee-ah.
Hai!
-[gasping] No way.
Eeahh!
Eyuh.
-Not very impressive.
You shouldn't have
to look down to find
your footing, soul reaper.
-Eyah.
-Hiyah.
-Hoo-ah.
Oohoo.
-Hah.
Eyahhh.
Your reactions are slow.
Your defense is weak.
You can't even deal with a
sudden change in your stance.
I cannot fight with you.
I mean, really, it's like facing
off with some kind of baby.
Pathetic.
-Uh.
Eh.
[gasping]
-You're about to
be destroyed, nino.
Go ahead, use your bankai.
-Ehh, ahh.
-Believe me, I won't
think badly of you.
But if you don't
use your bankai,
you're never going to
be able to challenge me.
-Ehh, uhn.
No.
I won't do it.
-Why not?
-Because I have a mission,
and I won't compromise it.
Privaron Espada aren't
Espada anymore now, are they?
-That's correct.
-Well there's your answer!
Hyuh!
Right now, I have one goal.
I have to defeat
all of the Espada.
Tay-yah!
-Huah.
Huah.
-Hiyuh.
Hai-ah!
-Hoo-ah.
-I can't afford to waste my
bankai against just anyone,
especially if
they're not Espada.
Teh!
Hurr ah-yah!
So I'll just have to defeat you
without the use of my bankai.
-I see.
I understand how you feel, nino.
So out of respect, I'm
going to tell you something.
Do not underestimate me.
Got it?
-[grunt] Hoo-ah.
-Huah.
Well, Giralda.
-Uhah?
Damn.
He can release his zanpakuto
without even drawing it.
Get ready nino, Go here I come.
-[grunts]
-Time to dance.
Giralda!
Hiah ooah!
-Eyuh.
Giyah!
-Huah.
-Teh.
Eyah.
-I have just begun to play!
Huah!
-Gah!
-Huah.
-Ee-ah.
-[roaring]
-Hyuh.
Ahh.
Eh.
Ee-ahh.
Gyah gah.
-Hm.
-Getsuga tensho!
-Uhee.
-[roaring]
-Eyuh.
Huah.
Ooah.
-Ahh!
-[groaning]
-Oh, ahh.
Ichigo?
--[laughs] Don't tell me
that's all you've got, nino?
[laughs]
-Ichigo? [sobs]
Ichigo's going to die.
[theme music]
[whining]
WONDERWEISS: No.
MALE VOICE: Hmm, I
guess Wonderweiss
isn't ready to do
this on his own.
GIN: I could have told you
that if you bothered to ask.
WONDERWEISS: Nyooo.