[MUSIC - BEAT CRUSADERS,
"TONIGHT, TONIGHT, TONIGHT"]
RANGIKU (VOICEVER):
Unbelievable.
YUMICHIKA (VOICEOVER): The
Zaraki Squad prides itself
on its lackadaisical standards.
RANGIKU (VOICEOVER): He just
said that and walked away.
I expect that from him, but why
did Shuhei and Izuru run off
as quickly as they arrived?
Since my captain is
the one who ordered
them to come to the
World of the Living,
shouldn't I be the one in
charge while they're here?
The captain's gonna hear
about this when I get back!
Huh?
Wait a minute.
Isn't that--?
SAWATARI: It's nice to be
young, don't you agree?
It's been so long, I'd almost
forgotten how good it feels.
-Tell me why you've been
taking souls of the living.
SAWATARI: Why not?
-Stop attacking the living!
-Why should I?
I still want more power.
-What are you going
to do with that power?
-What, indeed?
That is an excellent question.
Too bad you'll never know.
-Whoa!
Haven't seen you in ages,
Chad, what have you been up to?
-Uh, why are you here?
-Well, actually,
it's just dumb luck
that I ran into you like this.
Sounds like things
have been getting
a little crazy in the
World of the Living lately.
Out of the blue, my captain
just says to me, Rangiku,
I want you to go to the
World of the Living.
And here I am!
-You may not know this,
but we lieutenants
aren't allowed to come to the
world of living very often.
It's been so long
that I'm completely
out of touch with
what's going on.
Still, I think everything
is so fascinating here.
Everywhere you look, there's
always so much to see.
-Yeah.
Right.
Uh, listen, Rangiku.
-What is it?
Oh, are those two
friends of yours.
That's interesting, It
looks like they can see me.
-I'm Ururu.
-Noba.
-I'm Lieutenant
Rangiku Matsumoto
of the Soul Society's
Tenth Squad.
Pleased to meet you.
URURU: It's a pleasure
to meet you, too.
NOBA: Likewise.
-So what are the
three of you doing out
here at the park at this hour?
-[together] Uh.
RANGIKU: Huh?
-A Bount.
RANGIKU: A Bount?
CHAD: Yeah.
RANGIKU: You mean that old man?
NOBA: He's the one.
-The masked lad is
telling the truth,
my good lady Soul Reaper.
-Oh, really?
-So that there's
no doubt, perhaps
I should show you
a little proof.
That way, you can be certain.
[laugh] Baura, show yourself.
[gasping]
-So I take it that's your doll.
-That's right.
-Do you think this
is some kind of joke?
-[grunting]
-His spiritual pressure--
it disappeared.
-Noba, are you able
to sense anything?
-[gasp] Jump!
-[gasp]
[roar]
[grunting]
-What?
Huh?
-Is it a whale?
-Or a shark?
-Looks like a rockfish.
RANGIKU: I don't care
what kind of fish it is!
[shout]
Nothing happened.
-Behind you.
-[grunts]
-No, Rangiku.
RANGIKU: Ah!
-You did it.
-Hm.
RANGIKU: Ow!
Thank for helping out.
Hm?
Hey, what's the deal?
I said thank you, not zip it.
What the heck's wrong
with you, anyway?
-He's kinda shy.
-You have escaped death.
[gasping]
-Allow me to introduce
my doll to you, Baura.
BAURA: You called me
out on a nice night.
It feels good.
-It just talked.
-Dolls possess
independent minds.
-Oh, really?
That's interesting.
-Baura has a special
ability which
allows him to manipulate
space by creating
an alternate dimension, in
which he can swim about freely
unrestricted by objects
in this dimension.
It would appear that your
masked friend over there
possesses a similar ability.
[laughs] But
compared to my Baura,
his powers are insignificant.
-Are you sure about that?
-You're awfully arrogant
for one so young.
Perhaps we ought to
show him just how
different our powers really are.
Baura!
-Do what you want,
but we're the ones who
are going to show you
a difference in power.
Roar, Haineko!
-Baura.
BAURA: OK, boss.
-[gasp] Return!
-You backed off.
Why?
SAWATARI: That Soul Reaper's
judgment was correct.
-Huh?
-If she had not commanded
that ash to return,
it would have been
developed by Baura,
and she would have
lost her Zanpakuto.
-What do you mean by that?
NOBA: The doll's mouth
is also connected
to an alternate dimension.
-Here I thought I might
finally get my hands
on a real Soul
Reaper's Zanpakuto.
But you had to go
and ruin my plan!
[phone ringing]
MAN (ON PHONE):
Yes, Ms. Rangiku.
What can I do for you?
-Lock onto my
location and freeze
everything in a
500 meter radius.
And give me soul protection.
MAN (ON PHONE): Understood.
-You better do the same
for Shuhei and Izuru
just to be safe.
MAN (ON PHONE): Yes, ma'am.
We've just received a report
that Lieutenant Abarai
charged into battle
without protection
and was injured while
protecting a human.
We don't know the
extent of his injuries.
RANGIKU (VOICEOVER): Renji.
-Is something wrong?
-We're not the only ones
having a difficult time.
SAWATARI: [laughs evilly]
-I just contacted
the Soul Society
and asked them to use their
power to protect this area.
There's no need to
hold back anymore.
-I see.
All right.
[grunt]
-Hado Four, Byakurai!
NOBA: Your attacks
won't harm him
when he's in an
alternate dimension.
-[grunting]
He's heading right for you!
-[grunt]
[gasp]
-Persistent.
-[groan]
-For a little girl,
she's not bad.
NOBA: Over here.
-It just swallowed our attacks.
-A frontal attack is useless.
-So how are we
supposed to stop it?
Noba, the first
time it attacked,
you were able to
sense it beforehand.
How did you do that?
-As he surfaces from
the other dimension,
he creates ripples
in this dimension.
-Then can you use that
to predict his movements?
-I only sense him an
instant before he arrives.
-Then it looks like our only
option is to dodge his attack.
-Hm.
If he's in a
different dimension,
then how's he able to
sense where we are?
NOBA: I think he's probably
using something like sonar.
-Sonar?
NOBA: I've been
sensing subtle waves
of spiritual pressure
coming from the ground.
RANGIKU: What about tracing
that to find out where he is?
Is that possible?
NOBA: It's too weak.
-[sigh] Isn't there
anything we can do?
-He attacked us by swimming
through the ground before.
Now that we're up high,
we seem to be safe.
We should use this time
to come up with a plan.
-Right.
[gasp]
-Hm?
[gasping]
[roar]
-Ururu!
Ururu!
-I'm glad your safe.
That's all that matters.
-Ururu!
[grunt]
NOBA: Chad.
-This way!
Do you see him?
CHAD: He's not behind us.
RANGIKU: What's
the deal with him?
It doesn't seem to matter
if it's high or low, as long
as there's a large
surface to enter through.
SAWATARI: You're catching on.
-What?
-[gasp]
SAWATARI: That's one down.
Your little friend
is perfectly safe.
Baura's belly is connected
to an alternate dimension.
I can leave her there, out of
harm's way, for the time being.
However, she won't be
able to survive there
for a long period of time.
-What will you do with her?
SAWATARI: Bounts usually
absorb only souls.
But Baura and I have
a unique ability.
We are able to
engulf a human body.
Then we dissolve it and
absorb not only the soul,
but the entire body as well.
-Damn.
Return Ururu to us
now, you bastard.
-[laughs] You'll all be
joining her soon enough.
I intend to swallow you up
one by one into Baura's belly!
Baura, take them!
BAURA: OK.
-That's not going to happen.
Roar, Haineko!
-Pay not attention to their
feeble attempts, Baura.
Swallow them!
[roaring]
-Huh?
BAURA: Huh?
-Just what the hell was that.
Oh!
-You didn't think you were
the only one with the ability
to dive into the
ground, did you?
SAWATARI: You redheaded witch!
-But instead of
looking down here,
you want to pay attention
to what's above you.
-What?
Damn Soul Reaper thinks
she can make a fool of me.
BAURA: They haven't
gone very far.
SAWATARI: Let's
stop them, Baura.
BAURA: OK.
-Do you really think
we'll be safe here?
NOBA: As far as I can tell.
I'm guessing that in order to
move from the other dimension
into this one, he needs a
space wide enough for his body.
-That makes sense.
-An enormous amount
of energy is displaced
when he moves through space.
That would make it
physically impossible
to enter a cramped
area like this.
-Hm.
-[grunt]
-What is it?
It doesn't do any good to worry.
It wasn't your fault.
-[sigh] Then what good am I?
My power has always been
used to protect others.
But now this.
-But you must learn for
yourself what that reason is.
This amulet will
guide you and help
you to learn their purpose.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): If
there's ever anything
so important you'd
protect it with your life,
I'll protect it
with mine as well.
-And now they've
lost their purpose.
-Chad, you can't think that--
-Right now, the only thing I'm
thinking about is saving Ururu.
-Take it easy.
RANGIKU: You can't just
charge in without thinking.
You have to have
some sort of plan.
-I plan on taking her place.
-No, that's out of the question.
He wants to capture all of us,
so making a trade for Ururu
won't work.
You've got to remember
that he thinks
of humans as nothing
more than food.
-[sigh]
-We have to come up with
a plan of some sort.
NOBA: Wait a minute.
-What is it?
-What if I lure him
into my dimension?
-You know, you might
have something there.
NOBA: We know that he has
an alternate dimension
within his body.
If I can surround his
body with my power,
I should be able to
contain everything
within that dimension.
Once I've done that, I can move
the objects around at will.
-You think it's possible?
NOBA: Since we both create
alternate dimensions
with spiritual power,
it should work.
-Hm.
Well, unless someone
has a better idea.
-Fine, then.
What can we do to help?
-You'll need to
occupy him long enough
to lure him in front of
me without his noticing.
-I'll be the decoy
and maneuver him, OK?
-Wait a minute.
CHAD: Hm?
-If anyone is going to
be a decoy, it's me.
You can back me up if I need it.
-You can't do it.
I won't allow you
to put yourself
in that kind of danger.
RANGIKU: Danger?
Now, listen.
Maybe you have forgotten
who you're talking to.
-I-- I didn't mean to--
-All right!
Let's go catch us a fish.
[giggle] Come on, you two.
Don't just there.
Let's go!
Hey, Gramps.
I know you can hear me.
You move too slowly
to have gone very far.
Come on out!
I'm right here.
Mm.
[gasp]
Your attacks are
way too predictable.
-[shout]
-Stop it, Chad.
How do you expect me to see
him through all that smoke?
[gasp]
[roaring]
-What's wrong, Baura?
-What?
-You fell for it, old man.
-[shout]
-Whoa!
-You're going to pay for
that, you little urchin.
[grunting]
-You nasty little brats!
Your puny minds
can't comprehend what
it takes to gain
this kind of power,
the number of souls I've sucked.
I will not lose to you! [shout]
-[shout]
-What was that?
[groaning]
-Noba!
NOBA: No problem.
-Thank goodness.
-Are you all right?
-Where's Ururu?
NOBA: Right.
I got it.
[groaning]
-Noba, what's wrong?
What is it?
-Noba!
-Stay away!
-It can't be!
-Noba!
Noba!
RANGIKU: Try to hang on.
-[groans]
-Noba!
[gasping]
-You've all been
very entertaining,
but I'm afraid you're
about 100 years too early.
I won't be sealed away yet.
[gasping]
-I think it's time
we brought this fight
to its natural conclusion.
[laughs]
[theme music]
RANGIKU: I'm hungry.
Let's grab a bit to eat
after we defeat this Bount.
NOBA: Sashimi
would hit the spot.
CHAD: Maybe fish and chips.
RANGIKU: I want my fish grilled,
with a nice stiff drink.
ICHIGO: How can you even
think about eating fish
after fighting
someone like that?
NOBA: No problem.
CHAD: No problem.
[theme music]
MAN: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers.
WOMAN: Golden.
-We've received a report from
the Seventh Seat, Yamada.
-I see.
So what does it say?
-Lucky bastard.
Oh, uh, I mean, Hanataro
says, blah, blah, blah,
loving the World of the
Living, my job is so much fun!
He's down there in the World of
the Living having a great time,
while we're up here
working our butts off.
I'm so jealous I could spit.
-I see.
Thank you for that.
-Excuse me.
I can't believe
that little twerp!
He gets to have--
-It seems that Hanataro
is enjoying himself.