Jushiro, do you
have a minute?
Yes. So why is it that
you needed to meet
with me so urgently?
I have some serious doubts
about recent events.
And I thought it would
be better to talk to you
about it privately.
Would it be about Ichigo?
Mmm. I'm very
concerned about him.
Something about this incident
doesn't sit right with me.
I have to agree.
The part that bothers
me is that everything
seems too perfect.
Yeah. That's my point.
So, what do we do?
I'm thinking, we may need to
take another, more critical,
look at this incident from
the beginning.
[Yamamoto]
Captains Mayuri Kurotsuchi
and Kenpachi Zaraki,
who both disappeared into
the Precipice World earlier,
have now returned safely.
Kurotsuchi. Report on
what happened while in
the Precipice World.
Hmpf! It was horrible!
In fact, just thinking about
it makes my skin crawl!
I will never forget the nasty
smirk on the face of Substitute
Soul Reaper Ichigo Kurosaki,
as he stared down at us!
He interfered with our mission
inside the Precipice World!
We should send troops
to capture him at once!
Hmm. Captain Zaraki,
was there any question
about his identity?
You think I'd mistake
Ichigo when he was
standing right there?
Hmm.
[Unohana]
Not that it's proof-positive,
but we do have the Combat Pass
obtained by Captain Kuchiki.
Plus, the circumstantial
evidence of Ichigo's crimes
continues to accumulate.
And, of course, he refuses
to turn himself in to us,
or mount a defense of his
behavior.
Hold on there a minute!
Isn't it premature to draw
any conclusions just yet?
I don't believe Ichigo would do
the things he's accused of!
Captain Ukitake, I find it
hard to believe that Ichigo
is guilty, as well.
That is precisely why it's
so important that we hear
his side of the story!
Why are we wasting time
discussing this nonsense!
The man is guilty or
he'd come and face us!
Case closed!
Think about it! Even during his
battle with Aizen, he was doing
something in the Precipice World
he didn't want us to know about!
It's obvious! We must
capture and interrogate
him with whatever means
are available to us!
Okay, okay we get it.
Calm down.
The Soul Society owes
Ichigo Kurosaki a large
debt of gratitude.
But it does not
automatically clear him of
suspicion in this situation.
Send a team to the World
of the Living, to apprehend
the suspect, immediately!
I don't see how they can
commit the resources for such
an effort, just to capture
Ichigo. It makes no sense.
You hear that?
Yeah.
They're about to move out.
[gatekeeper]
Open the gate!
Hey Nozomi!
It's late, everyone's
gone to bed.
[muffled groans]
What's that?
Kon! What the hell?!
[more muffled moans]
[coughs]
That damn Nozomi!
She snuck up on me, tied
me up, and then split!
What's going on?!
Nozomi!
Nozomi, where are you?!
Come on, Nozomi!
Nozomi!
[panting]
Any sign of her?
Uh-uh.
It hasn't been
that long.
She couldn't
have gone far.
I can't follow her
Spiritual Pressure.
Are you sure this girl's
really a Soul Reaper?
Ichigo!
Rukia! Anything at all?
Nothing. Not a trace.
I put the lieutenants on it,
but they haven't had any luck,
either.
Kon said she was looking for
something yesterday, but since
we don't know what it is, it's
not going to be much help to us.
Damn! We don't have
time for this.
The Captains are preparing
some kind of operation.
If they call for us, we can't
just be 'missing in action'.
[gasp]
What just happened?
It looks like a Senkaimon
just opened up.
I can make out the Spiritual
Pressure of several captains.
Egh. Of all the
times for them
to show up here.
We need to find that
girl, and fast.
Yeah. Kon!
What?! Now HE decides
to disappear?
And I don't have my
Combat Pass either!
Rukia, I need your help!
Okay, I'm on it!
Are you ready?
Okay. Let's go!
[chuckles]
You can run all
you want, Nozomi.
But it's futile.
[panting]
[gasp]
Huh?
Rawwr!
You... stupid idiot.
What are you doing in
a place like this?
How did you figure out
where to look for me?
Oof!
Beats me!
I just figured it out!
Listen, you, don't
underestimate my intuition!
Now tell me...! Why are you so
intent on being alone, anyway?!
I don't get it!
Do you hate all
of us that much?!
Or is it something else?!
Do you have some other
agenda going on?
Well?!
Augh!
That is none of
your business.
[gasp]
They're here!
Hey, where are you going?!
You just can't run off
like that!
I found you once, I'll
find you again, I swear!
Nozomi should be
with Ichigo Kurosaki
and his friends.
If we track every strong
Spiritual Pressure we
detect in the town, we
should be able to find her.
I'm way ahead of you.
Tell me something I
don't know.
Why are you bringing this up?
Our orders were very clear.
We've been sent here to
capture Ichigo Kurosaki.
Ignoring commands for the
sake of Kageroza's personal
mission is madness.
I beg to differ.
Whichever one we give priority
to, the distance to our goal
will still be the same.
Heh. I have to tell you,
neither mission suits me.
But since we've
already arrived,
Wouldn't it be more fun to
fight with the original
versions of ourselves?
Yes, it would. I'm very
interested in taking on
my original form.
[Yumichika]
That's well and good,
but I'm not
interested in you!
So you're here!
Excellent.
The originals!
It's time to get rid
of these phonies!
We have an advantage
in numbers.
What makes you say that?
We always fight one-on-one.
It's a matter of honor!
Ikkaku, let's
not quibble--
[Reigai Omaeda]
Youdon'treally
haveanadvantage!
Now that I'm here,
it's four against four!
Heh!
[Akon]
Here are the records of
the recent traffic through
the Precipice World.
I'm not really supposed
to be showing it to you.
It's prohibited.
Make sure no-one sees you, and
don't take it out of this room.
Sorry to put you
on the spot.
I wouldn't ask, but Jushiro
didn't keep a separate record
of his subordinate's passages,
and now we have
to track someone.
Uh!
I have been asked to
put together a report,
but without Jushiro's squad
records, I can't finish it.
I could be in
big trouble!
Hey, wait a minute,
I really don't...
Of course!
Right!
What, uh, he said!
[sigh] Just remember,
if anyone sees you here,
I'm the one who gets
reprimanded.
I get why you're nervous.
I'll make it up to you,
next time I see you.
You say the same
thing every time.
I have things
I have to do.
Bye-bye.
I don't know
how you do it.
Heh heh heh heh!
[Shunsui]
[breath] Well, we'd
better get started.
Eh ha ha!
(Small OM grunt as he prepares
to fight back)
Eyaa-haa!
Get ready!
Where are they?
[Omaeda]
Huuaahh!
Hmm!
Who are you?
Hmpf!
What does it matter, anyway?
Now it's four against four!
Now we can face off
without worrying about
whether it's fair or not!
If that's the case and we
don't have to hold back,
then we should each take
on our own impostor!
Rrrgh!
Well that's fine for you guys,
but where does that leave me?
I have to fight this idiot!
I mean, look at him
with his silly hair and
his stupid outfit!
Not to mention that ugly
collar he's wearing
around his ne--!
Huh?!
What is it?
That collar he's wearing!
I've seen it before!
Yeah, I guess you have, chubs!
Say what?!
You don't recognize me?
Maybe this will do the trick!
Smash'em! Gegetsuburi!
Aahh!
Gegetsuburi?
Wait a minute,
that means you're--!
That's right!
Your worst fear!
You're looking at yourself,
Marechiyo Omaeda!
Huh?
Hold on, how can you be me?
[snort] Ha ha
ha ha ha ha!
HA HA HA HA HA!!
This bozo doesn't look
anything like you!
How could that
have happened?!
I don't know!
Why don't you give
me some answers?
Are you making fun of me?
What's with that look?!
There's a simple explanation!
You're so damned ugly,
I refused to take on your body!
What?! You're telling
me they allowed that?!
Oh yes indeed.
And now that I'm the
new Marechiyo Omaeda,
I'm afraid I have no
choice but to eliminate
you from this world.
Ah ha ha ha ha!
That's hilarious!
He he he! Best idea
I've heard today!
I mean, you are ugly,
so why not have him take over?!
Then he can be the real
Soul Reaper, and you
can be the fake one!
How dare an impostor
embarrass me in front
of my comrades?!
Raagh!
Smash'em! Gegetsuburi!
Yaaaah!
Hold on! What do you
think you're doing?
You can't just go and start
the fight without me!
I'm coming, too!
Hey, wait for me!
Take this
seriously!
Whoa! What?!
Nngh! This makes
absolutely no sense!
His Gegetsuburi is
way bigger than mine!
Naturally...!
Because everything about me,
is superior to anything you've
ever been in your life!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
[Omaeda]
That's not fair, you jerk!
[sigh]
Mmm. So beautiful.
I'm able to truly see my form,
which up until this point,
I have only been able
to admire in a mirror.
[chuckles]
That works both ways.
I have to say,
we look pretty good.
[Ikkaku]
Extend... Hozukimaru!
[swords clashing
and battle shouts]
Hyaaaa!
Just as I expected of me,
you're pretty good!
So are you!
Excuse me, Ikkaku.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but would you mind doing
me a favor?
Can't it wait?
I'm kinda busy!
I'm sorry, but it can't!
It's very important!
Let it go!
Concentrate
on the fight!
That's the problem I have.
I can't do it!
Huh?
I'm stuck! I tried and tried,
but I find I really can't
damage such a beautiful
specimen as myself!
So what do you think
about swapping opponents,
just for this fight?
Are you nuts?!
Heh!
[panting]
Whoa!
Ha ha ha ha! Is that
what you call running?
With your body, it would be
faster if you rolled along,
like you did a minute ago!
Shut your mouth, smart-ass!
I didn't roll!
That move was hakuda!
Fine! Whatever!
Augh!
Shuhei!
[Shuhei]
Nice move, me.
You blocked that last
attack pretty well.
But why aren't you
using your Shikai?
Gah!
You're not still afraid of
your Zanpakuto, are you?
That's foolish.
In a fight, power's
extremely critical.
Given the chance, I'd have
no hesitation using
this power, believe me!
You originals suck!
That's the lesson
from this fight!
You outdated older models need
to be replaced with more
efficient versions, like us!
Dgh!
Now Reap...!
...Kazeshini!
That won't work!
Why wasn't your
attack effective?
Your impostor doesn't have
any more power than you!
He's using the same
weapons you are!
Not my fault! Don't you
remember what Captain
Kurotsuchi told us?
Interestingly, you'll find that
Reigai possess the exact same
powers as their originals.
However, there is
one difference...
I've found that they become
much more belligerent.
Ifthey'reinvolvedin
a battleanditgets
progressivelymorebloody,
it seems to stimulate that
aspect of their personality.
That definitely gives them an
advantage, because they can go
beyond their natural limits!
Damn, we have to do
something about that!
Wait a minute!
I think I know
something that'll work!
Hey, Shuhei.
Just follow my
lead, all right?
Huh?
What's the matter?
Did you finally decide
it was time to give up?
I'm afraid you've got
this all backwards.
If you guys apologize now,
we'll consider sparing you.
You really aren't
very bright, are you?
Oough!
What the hell?!
Bright enough!
You'll regret that-- Huh?
What are you doing?!
Surprise. Your Gegetsuburi seems
to have gotten not only bigger,
but heavier as well.
With your movements that
big and heavy, capturing
you is an easy matter.
You little bastard!
Try not to forget that
I'm your opponent!
Ah!
Oof!
Whaddya know?
You guys
underestimated us.
You lost because you just
relied on raw power.
You wouldn't be cut out
for the Stealth Force!
Ngh. You bastard,
that was a cheap move!
Bakudo Number Sixty-Two!
Hyapporankan!
Damn it! I can't be defeated
by this sweaty pile of fat!
Ha-ha! Ha ha ha! Hey pal,
you run out of tricks?!
Not quite!
Hado Number Sixty-Three!
Raikoho!
Wait a minute! I can use
a technique like that?!
Move it!
Yaah!
That Spirit Energy!
There's a massive fight
in that direction!
[choke]
How could you?
You were under the
impression that in a
face-to-face confrontation,
I would never attack myself.
You were
mistaken.
Don't misunderstand me,
Yumichika.
I think you're beautiful,
just like you do.
However.
I thought your face would
look even more beautiful,
maybe transcendent, if it
was covered in blood!
I can see now that I was right.
There's a certain majestic
quality to your skin.
I wanted to try it
before this, but I
didn't want to damage my
own body in the process.
I'm so glad you became
available for the experiment.
Looks like their battle's
about over as well.
D'yahh!
Hah. What a bust.
I thought you'd put
up more of a fight.
Egh... Damn you!
What do you think?
Should we finish them off?
Might as well,
they're done anyway.
Who was that...?!
Are you people... Reigai?
Oh! So you know
about us, do you?
Don't move!
Like hell!
Hrgh!
Forget about it, Ikkaku.
There's no point
wasting our time,
fighting these
weaklings anymore.
We need to start looking
for Nozomi Kujo.
Heh! I guess you're right.
Hey!
Hold on now, this is
definitely weird.
But who from here would
go and do such a-- Huh?
Oh, it's you, Kageroza.
What's with that outfit?
Hm? What in the
hell's...happening?
[chuckle]
[Shunsui]
Hmm. That's what
I was afraid of.
This shows definite signs of
having been altered recently.
Then someone from Squad
Twelve must have-- Huh?
What do you want?!
Shunsui Kyoraku!
We're taking you into custody
on suspicion of altering
Precipice World records!
Are you crazy?!
Interesting.
I should have known.
[gasp]
[Omaeda]
Heh! The original
Marechiyo was nothing!
As his Reigai, I'm
definitely stronger
and more handsome!
[Shuhei]
Sure...
[Omaeda]
Hey, Shuhei. If there's
anything you need, just ask.
[Hisagi]
Sure...
[Omaeda]
Soon, I imagine they'll
make me a Captain!
[Hisagi]
Sure, whatever.
The bottom line is,
I don't really care.