[Genryusai Yamamoto]
I'm glad you're now a
monstrous creation, and
no longer just a child.
Haahho~!
Yeeaaayayayaya!
[pained grunts]
Uh. They did it!
They sure did!
[Tetsuzaemon]
The Captains,
they finally did it!
They defeated Aizen!
Hey, Izuru! Now we've got
something to celebrate!
We won, so you might try
putting a smile on your face!
Uh, right.
Hnh?!
Oh wow! I'm surprised
you're able to sit up.
I'm amazed.
Momo..?
Hey wait, where exactly
are you going, Momo?
Hey guys...
Hold on!
What the hell
are you guys doing?!
[startled gasps]
[gasp]
Momo?!
Ngh!
But how??!
Uh??
When did
you do it?
A good question.
So when did I do it?
[Aizen]
My Kyokasuigetsu's power
is complete hypnosis,
so I have the ability to alter
your perception of what's real.
It's so overpowering,
it can control all
five of your senses,
and lead people to hallucinate
all sorts of strange things.
Shut up, I know that!!
I'm asking you when you
used your Kyokasuigetsu!
So here's a question for you.
Now consider this.
At what time did you think that
I wasn't using my Kyokasuigetsu?
[gasp]
Shiro...
Why...?
Why?
YEAAAAGHH!
Captain! Control
yourself!!
Rrraaughhgh!
You've left yourself
wide open.
[gurgle]
Damn.
I won't kill you.
Your powers will
allow you to
remain conscious.
But your wounds have been
targeted specifically so
you won't be able to move.
I want you to watch the
outcome of this battle,
...as you lie on the
ground, paralyzed,
unable to do anything to
affect the end result.
He's... too strong.
[gulp]
Aizen.
It's the Old Man!
It's about time the
Head Captain showed up.
But you're too late, Yamamoto.
You have no support team.
You're the only Captain left
who can still oppose me.
The desperation is evident,
Your death will mean
the end of the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads.
You shouldn't have
come on your own.
You've missed your best
opportunity to defeat me,
old man.
Don't get cocky, boy.
Believe me, you would not
be the first fool who
thought he was strong
enough to take me down.
I'm not really worried
about whether I can or not,
...because I
already have.
Enough talk!
Hee.
Huh??
You can't slip away now,
Sosuke Aizen.
How very interesting.
You're sure you've caught me?
Think about it carefully,
old man.
Is the limb you're
holding so tightly
really my arm?
You know how powerful
my Kyokasuigetsu is.
Are you saying this
is part of your
Complete Hypnosis?
That may
be true.
You might have
clouded my mind,
despite what I can
feel and touch.
However...
...There is no
mistake that the
Zanpakuto running
through my stomach,
and its spirit energy,
belongs to you.
You think I've missed
an opportunity?
Well, you're wrong!
This is the
opportunity I seek!
[rumbling]
What's that noise?!
Ennetsu Jigoku!
All of your battles up to
this point were simply
preparations for the one
you're about to face.
You were setting up this
confrontation while your
subordinates were being
defeated, is that right?
That is quite
devious of you.
Call me what you want.
Prepare yourself!
You will die with me
in this blazing inferno!
[Genryusai Yamamoto]
Step away,
Ichigo Kurosaki!
You cannot sacrifice
yourself, You're not a
member of the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads.
It doesn't matter!
Do not make me
repeat myself!
[Aizen]
What about your own
squad members?
After all, this blazing
inferno of yours is going
to engulf them, as well.
They are prepared to die,
if necessary.
Whatever it takes to
exterminate your evil.
That is the will of the
Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
Behind you!
Watch out!
[moaning]
[Genryusai Yamamoto]
Why?
What caused Ryujinjakka's
flames to disappear?
Let me enlighten you.
Your Ryujinjakka is the
most powerful Zanpakuto.
There's no question
about that.
If I fought you head-on,
I would be at a distinct
disadvantage.
However, I have a strategy
to overcome your power.
It requires the creation
of a specific weapon.
One that can neutralize
your Zanpakuto.
Erk!
His name is Wonderweiss.
Can you tell me your
name, new comrade?
Wonderweiss.
Wonderweiss Margera.
You're going to have an
important role to fulfill
for me, Wonderweiss.
[moaning]
He is our only Modifed
Arrancar.
And the name of
his Resurreccion
is Extinguir.
He has but one role,
and nothing else.
He is here to
rob you of your
Ryujinjakka.
[moaning]
He was created for
this one purpose.
He sacrificed his speech,
intelligence, memory,
and reasoning,
to concentrate his
strength and carry
out this mission.
He's the perfect weapon.
[moaning]
You say he sacrificed
his faculties?
You robbed them from him!
This is simply the
will of the Hogyoku.
You have no chance
against this power.
The overwhelming force
that Wonderweiss has given
his life to acquire.
[Aizen]
Farewell,
Genryusai Yamamoto.
[Aizen]
Farewell,
Genryusai Yamamoto.
[moaning]
Destroy him,
Wonderweiss.
Huaauh!
Hmpf! You think you can
kill me that easily,
just by neutralizing my
Ryujinjakka? How naive.
I'm astounded by your
complete lack of insight.
How do you think I remained
Head Captain of the
Thirteen Court Guard Squads
for over a thousand years?
No Soul Reaper born in
that entire time has
been stronger than I!
[moans]
I must admit,
you're quite a
resilient opponent.
I held nothing back
in that last attack.
If my Ikkotsu couldn't
defeat you, I'll have to
try something else.
[moaning]
Are you prepared to deal
with my next attack?
It's going to hurt.
[moaning]
Oh, that's right.
I forgot, your creator
wiped away your
powers of speech.
[moan]
I see you give no warning
before you attack, that's
quite a handy improvement.
You're fast, no question
about that. But,
in spite of your
modifications,
you're still a brat!
[high pitched squeals]
Yaaaa-yayayayayaya!!
You're strong and quick,
but you have no
sense of strategy.
Because of your youth,
you think that I'll
succumb to your
relentless pounding.
Your attacks are
too predictable.
Yaaaa-yayayayayaya!!
[moaning]
(CM slightly surprised
reax)
Haaa!
Yayayayayayaya!!
Pathetic.
[disappointed moan]
huaahh.
Is that all you've got?
Eeeyaiii!!
I'm glad you're now a
monstrous creation, and
no longer just a child.
I can kill you without
being tortured by
feelings of remorse.
hu uh... aie...
Huuuuiai!
Sokotsu!
Hauee...
Grrahh!
Poor creature.
When he created you,
he didn't take away
your feelings, did he?
What a cruel thing to do.
What do you mean?
Creatures who become
Hollows have no free will.
Their one obsession in
life is to devour souls,
just for the fun of it.
How can you then say that
what I did was cruel,
when it gave him a purpose?
In fact, when you look
at it dispassionately,
you're the cruel one.
You crushed the poor
boy into pieces.
I won't waste time on
some foolish argument.
You can flap your jaw
as much as you like.
It will all end soon.
"Foolish argument"?
That's an odd response to
what I just said to you.
You're unaware,
because you chose to
ignore what I said.
What are you
talking about?
You have to think back on
what I told you earlier.
I said that Extinguir was
created for the sole
purpose of sealing away
Ryujinjakka's flames.
What that means is,
he prevented you from creating
new flames, by sealing your
Zanpakuto in his own sword.
But were those the only
flames you created?
Weren't there more?
What about the flames you had
already released earlier?
Huh?
So, what do you suppose
happened to them?
Where did those
flames go?
Augh!
You have a sharp mind,
Head Captain of the
Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
You're well aware of what
would happen if all the
power and energy you were
able to produce here today,
was suddenly released
in one huge blast.
[Exhausted panting]
[clapping]
Well done, Head Captain,
You were able to contain
the explosion.
A remarkable feat,
I must admit,
I'm very impressed.
If you hadn't thrown
your body over the
explosion to contain it,
the flames would have blown
away your barrier, this small
town, and everything around it.
All that you see here
would have instantly
been turned to dust.
I have to thank you,
Genryusai Yamamoto.
By your heroic actions,
you have protected my world.
Damn you.
Genryusai Yamamoto.
Unfortunately, I cannot
spare your life.
You are the embodiment of
the Soul Society's history.
Out of respect,
I have decided
I will finish
you off quickly.
Don't make me explain
it again, Sosuke Aizen!
You're a fool!
Hado Number Ninety-Six!
Ittokaso!
[gasp]
Heeaaaa!!
Yahh!
[Ichigo]
Here I come, Aizen!
[Genryusai Yamamoto]
Stop right there, Ichigo!
[Ichigo]
What now?
[Genryusai Yamamoto]
You're putting
your energy in
the wrong place!
Your sword skills cannot
improve unless you have
control over your mind.
We'll re-do your
attack from here in
the next episode.
[Ichigo]
Really? Are you serious?