[theme song]
NARRATOR: Ichigo reluctantly
became a bodyguard
for Rurichiyo Kasumioji,
the young princess
of a highly ranked noble family.
He soon found himself
battling assassins
sent by Gyokaku Kumoi,
the viceroy plotting
to take control of the clan.
Kumoi gave his assassins bakoto,
blades with special powers
that are made using secret
Kasumioji Clan techniques.
Armed with these unique
weapons, the assassins
attacked Ichigo and his friends.
But wielding the incredible
power of the bakoto
proved to be too much
for the assassins.
Unable to fully unleash the
power of their new weapon,
each of Kumoi's
men were defeated.
-[sigh]
-Ah, Lord Kannogi.
You look absolutely magnificent.
-Yeah, but what if
Rurichiyo doesn't come back?
I won't be able to go through
the wedding ceremony alone.
-You have nothing
to worry about.
There's no doubt in my mind
that Princess Rurichiyo
will be here for the ceremony.
-Really?
You certainly seem
confident about that.
-I am, so try not to worry.
-Wedding ceremony?
-That's right.
The Kasumioji Clan is
finalizing preparations
for the upcoming
wedding of Shu Kannogi.
-I've never heard of him.
Who is this Kannogi?
-Master Shu is Lady
Rurichiyo's fiance.
-Her fiance?
She never even told
me she was engaged.
-Well, that's the
aristocracy for you.
-There's talk that they've
skipped the formalities
and that Shu Kannogi has
already been installed
as the head of the
Kasumioji clan.
So now they want to push
through the wedding ceremony
as quickly as possible.
That way, it will
all be official.
-But they can't hold a wedding
ceremony without the bride,
and Rurichiyo is here.
-That's a good point.
Still, I suppose they
could get around that
by using a stand in, seeing as
how most people wouldn't notice
a difference.
-Invitations have
already been sent out
to all the prominent
nobles in the Soul Society.
On the day of the
marriage, they plan
to open the gates to the
Kasumioji clan's palace
and invite all the citizens
to get a glimpse of the bride
and join in the celebration.
-They're trying to
destroy our credibility
by having as many
witnesses as possible!
Damn that Kumoi!
He'll do anything to
get what he wants!
-When is the ceremony
scheduled to take place?
-The day after tomorrow.
-So we're not talking
about a lot of time.
I'm sure Kumoi will do
everything in his power
to get the princess back, so
we'll have to be wary of traps.
That would be just like him.
-He's anticipating our actions
and driving us into a corner
by removing our
options one by one.
-Pretty soon, we won't have
any options left at all.
-Orihime is doing her
best with Chad and Uru,
but it's going to
take time for her
to reject the damage
inflicted by the assassins.
-The assassin sword-- a bakoto.
That's what they
called it, right?
-Yeah.
It absorbed its
wielder's spirit energy
and converted it into power.
-I'm not familiar with it, but
I assumed you would be, Kisuke.
-I know it's hard to
believe, but there
are a few things that
I don't, uh-- huh?
-Enryu, is everything all right?
-No, Lady Rurichiyo isn't here.
Have you checked the guest room?
-Uh.
-You really understood all that?
-Lady Rurichiyo.
I thought that I
might find you here.
Try not to worry, your highness.
I'm sure they'll both
make a full recovery,
and we have to give
Orihime room so
that she's able to do her work.
It would be best
for us to leave now
so that we don't get in her way.
Uh, my lady?
-I understand how do feel,
but you needn't worry.
Wait a minute.
I hate to ask, Rurichiyo, but
mind wringing out these towels?
-Huh?
-Please?
It would help me out.
-[laughs]
-Here.
You can rinse them in this.
-Perfect.
Thanks, Rurichiyo.
-I am so sorry.
-Huh?
-I am just so useless.
-No, please!
Rurichiyo, that's not true!
This wasn't your fault!
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
So, here you are.
-Huh?
-They say that only smoke
and fools like high places.
So why do I keep
finding you up here?
-I am not sure.
-You know, you can stop feeling
guilty about Chad and Uryu
getting hurt.
It wasn't your fault.
-But it was.
-No it wasn't.
-You're just saying that!
All their pain and suffering--
it is all because of me!
-That isn't true!
Because you're not the one
those thugs were after.
Nukui only had one
thing on his mind.
He was coming after
me personally.
-Do not lie.
Because I also know
they weren't just
some bandits who
stumbled on us by chance.
They were assassins who
were sent here by Kumoi!
Kumoi will stop at nothing to
take over the Kasumioji clan,
and I'm standing in his
way, so he wants me dead!
-But Rurichiyo, I thought you--
-I acted like I had no idea,
but I have known for a long time
that Kumoi is after me.
And I know that none of you
talk about it when I am around,
because you don't
want me to worry.
I am grateful for all the
kindness you have shown,
but still, I can't--
-Listen, Rurichiyo, nobody
forced us to protect you.
We all chose to do it.
We couldn't let you
face those guys alone.
And besides, I'm a
substitute Soul Reaper.
If I find someone like you
wandering helplessly around,
it's part of my job
to take care of you.
-Ichigo.
-Aw, come on, quit crying.
-I'm not crying!
-Everyone's going
to be all right.
It may take a little
time, but Uryu and Chad
are going to be as good as new.
Orihime doesn't
give up so easily.
So stop your worrying.
We'll be fine.
-Thank you, Ichigo.
-Hey!
What do you think you're--
-Please forgive me.
Now unlock!
-[groan] Huh?
-Rurichiyo, no!
-Please don't think I'm
not grateful for everything
you've done.
But I will not sit back and
let you suffer because of me.
I'm gonna take back the
Kasumioji clan myself.
-Rurichiyo, don't!
-Ichigo, what's wrong?
-What's happening out here?
-Oh!
Lady Rurichiyo!
What's the meaning
of this, Ichigo?
-I'll explain that later, but
we've got to go after her!
What are you waiting for?
You've gotta open the Senkaimon!
-I know what to do!
-Unlock!
Huh?
-What is this?
What's the problem?
-The gate won't respond.
-How is that possible?
-Lady Rurichiyo must have known
that we'd try to follow her,
so she probably locked
it from the other side.
-Are you telling me that
you can't open that gate?
-I can't do it without a key!
-Damn!
-Ichigo, you need to slow down
and think about this situation.
If you go rushing
through that gate,
you'll fall right
into the enemy's trap.
-What do you expect us to do?
-You need to calm down, Ichigo.
-What could have
happened that would
make Princess Rurichiyo risk her
life and return to her clan so
suddenly?
-She knew.
She knew that Kumoi
was trying to kill her,
and that she was putting
us all in danger.
-What?
-And she thinks she's
responsible for Chad and Uryu
and everything else that's
happened since she arrived.
-Oh, no.
-I guess that explains it.
But what could she
possibly hope to accomplish
by going back alone?
-I think that she'll
try to deceive Kumoi
by submitting to his will and
proceeding with the marriage
so that she can take
over as head of the clan!
-I don't think he's naive
enough to go for that!
Rukia, you're the only one
who can open up the Senkaimon.
-All right.
Now, unlock!
-Ichigo!
You guys, be careful.
-Orihime, please take
care of Chad and Uryu.
Let's do this.
-Well, they're on their way.
I guess I could have tried to
stop them, but knowing Ichigo,
it wouldn't have matter.
-But this time, his opponent
is a high ranking noble clan.
It will not be easy.
-Princess!
The princess has
returned to the palace!
-Huh?
The princess?
-Forget about those dishes!
We have to go out and
welcome the princess!
-What?
-It's the princess!
-It's wonderful to see
you again, Lady Rurichiyo.
-Hold it!
-I'm Rukia Kuchiki of Squad 13.
-And them?
-This is substitute Soul
Reaper Ichigo Kurosaki,
and these two are Sir Kenryu
and Enryu of Kasumioji Clan.
-There's no
authorization for you.
You'll have to wait here
while we verify this.
-There's no time for that!
-Not now, Ichigo.
We have to do as they say.
-I'm glad you were able to make
it back in time, Rurichiyo.
They held a ceremony
and appointed
me lord while you were gone.
Sorry, Rurichiyo.
-It makes no difference.
It was never my intention to
become head of the clan anyway.
-The important thing is that
we can be together from now on.
There are so many things that
we could do, like play cards,
or have a fan toss.
Oh I completely forgot.
You like to play kenmeri, right?
-Why the hell did it
take so long for us
to get through the Senkaimon?
-When someone shows up
without authorization,
they're required to
follow procedure.
We're lucky we made it
through without complications.
-The ceremony takes
place tomorrow.
We don't have much time.
-Damn.
-What happens when
we get to the palace?
How do we get inside without
creating a disturbance?
-Don't worry!
You can leave that to us.
I can handle getting
Lady Rurichiyo out.
After all, I am Chief
Chamberlain of the clan.
-Does that mean you're
someone important?
-Not only does it
mean I'm important,
it means I'm the number one
guardian of Princess Rurichiyo!
And I have full
access to the palace.
Open the gate!
Chief Chamberlain of the
Kasumioji clan, Ryusei Kenzaki,
and Rusaburo Enkogawa
wish to enter!
-All this time, who knew they
had such impressive names?
-What are you waiting for?
Open the gates!
Huh?
What is the meaning of this?
-Silence.
I have orders for
your immediate arrest.
You are both being
charged with the abduction
of Princess Rurichiyo.
-That's ridiculous.
This is Kumoi's doing.
-We won't be much help
if we get arrested.
-That's not going to happen.
-So you've got a plan?
-Of course I do!
Run like the wind!
-Hey, hold on!
Why the hell are you
running away for?
I thought you were
supposed to be
some kind of
bigshot around here!
-We're not running
away from them!
We're just falling
back to regroup!
-Sure feels like
we're running away!
-This way!
-What?
Where did they go?
[interposing voices]
-Spread out and find them.
-It looks like
we're safe for now.
-Do you guys always have
a getaway room ready?
-It's common for
these old palaces
to have secret passageways.
-Is he making this up or what?
-I don't know.
-We have to decide what
we're going to do next.
If we stick to the
secret passages,
we might be able
to search most of--
-Hold on a minute.
-What's the problem?
-Judging by the reception
we got at the main gate,
I think it's pretty obvious
that the entire palace is
going to be under heavy guard.
-That's because it's the day
before the wedding ceremony.
-Then rather than
searching blindly
and taking the chance of running
into another bunch of guards,
I think we should wait
until tomorrow when
we know exactly where
Rurichiyo will be.
-But if we wait until
tomorrow, then she'll already--
-He's right.
I think Lady
Rurichiyo plans to use
her power as the head
of the Kasumioji clan
to publicly denounce
Kumoi, and that's
why she's chosen this occasion.
-We tried to protect
her, but ended up
backing her into a corner
by taking away her freedom
and treating her like a child.
And after everything
she's endured,
we couldn't even protect her.
Rurichiyo knew how dangerous it
was, but she came here anyway.
All she wants is to take
control of her own destiny.
So what do you say?
Should we give her a chance to
do what she came here to do?
-[sigh] It's worth a try.
-Kenryu, it'll be your job
to get us inside the palace.
-You can count on me.
-Hang on, Rurichiyo.
You're not alone.
-I hereby proclaim
that Lord Kannogi,
the 37th Lord of Kasumioji,
and Princess Rurichiyo,
are officially husband and wife.
[applause]
-Announcing the
arrival of Lord Shu,
the new lord of
the Kasumioji clan,
and his bride, the
Princess Rurichiyo.
Long live Lord and Lady Kannogi!
[cheering]
-Can you believe it, Rurichiyo?
Listen to that.
There must be thousands
of them down there,
and they're here to
celebrate our wedding.
-Rurichiyo!
Let's go.
-Stop right there!
-Intruders!
-Rurichiyo!
Rurichiyo!
Listen to me!
-Huh?
What?
-Rurichiyo, we've come for you!
It's me, Ichigo!
Hey!
-They fell for it.
-Don't move, Ichigo Kurosaki.
-Captain Soi Fon!
-What's going on?
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Rurichiyo!
[theme song]
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): When
we filled out those forms
to pass through Senkaimon, there
was a line for a guarantor.
Who did you put?
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): My brother.
So be careful, because if we get
in trouble, it'll be his head.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
It's a little late
for that now, isn't it?
That sucks for him.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): Damn.