[theme music]
[grunting]
-He's here, Captain.
It's the Ryoka.
Captain Kyoraku!
KYORAKU: Already?
I wasn't expecting
the guy so early.
But what the hell?
Guess I better head out there
and give him a proper greeting.
-I still don't get
why you won't send me.
Though I'm only your
lieutenant, for a single Ryoka,
I'd be more than enough.
-Nanao, we've been
over this already.
This is a direct order
from old man Yamamoto.
He doesn't want anyone
to know we're still
having problems with
these pesky Ryoka.
Don't look so worried.
I'll be fine.
It won't take long.
I'm just going to
go have some fun.
[explosion]
[shouting]
[groaning]
ENJOJI: Hold it
right there, Ryoka.
That's as far as you go.
No doubt you've heard of me.
I'm the assistant adjutant
and Third Seat of Squad Eight.
I am Tatsufuso Enjoji.
I'll bet you're wishing
you'd chosen some other path.
[laughs] Surely even you
realize that this road
became a dead end for you
from the second I appeared.
[scream]
[fighting noises]
What's the matter, Ryoka?
Are you confused now?
Afraid?
Can't even make a move, can you?
But don't feel bad.
That's a typical
reaction for someone
faced for the first time
with the incredible technique
of the great swordsman
Tatsufuso Enjoji.
Though for you, it will
also-- [grunt] [scream]
CHAD (VOICEOVER): In the
beginning, two blasts a day
was my limit.
Now I can strike like
that more than five times
and still not feel tired.
I'll have to remember
to thank Yoruichi
for training me so well.
MAN: Whoa, that was pretty good.
-Hm?
-My name is Shunsui Kiraku,
Squad Eight captain.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
-So I take it you're
that last guy's captain.
-Mhm.
For what it's worth.
[laughs] Hm?
Oh.
Hey, Nanao, enough with
the flower petals already.
Hm.
I guess she didn't hear me.
Hey, Nanao!
It's very nice.
But that's another enough
set decoration, all right?
I think we get the point.
Save some for later,
my sweet Nanao.
Lovely, lovely
Na-- [sputter] Ugh.
-Sorry, but I don't have time
to stay and watch your routine.
Please, just step aside.
-Oh, come on?
Can't you loosen up a little
and try to have some fun?
Life's too short to
take it seriously.
-I've asked you nicely.
I'm in kind of a hurry.
You seem like a
decent enough guy.
So if there's any way to avoid
it, I'd rather not fight you.
-[laugh] Then I guess we
have a slight problem,
since neither one of us
is anxious for a fight.
But of course, I can't just
let you through, either.
I don't suppose you'd be
willing to retreat, would you?
-I could never do that.
-I thought as much.
I guess that leaves
us no choice.
We'll have to have
a friendly drink.
-Huh?
-Why not?
If you won't
retreat, at least you
can take a break
here for a while.
Let me show you a
little hospitality.
-No, thanks.
-Come on, relax.
-It's a rule.
Miners are not allowed
to drink any alcohol.
-Oh.
Well, that's unfortunate.
I hate to drink alone.
But maybe it's just as well.
This whole thing
will be over soon,
now that the other captains
are all on the move.
Probably, if you were
smart, you'd just--
-The other captains?
Wait, you mean
Ichigo and the others
are being pursued
by captains, too?
-Hm.
CHAD: That changes
things, Mr. Kiraku.
So I suggest you move, now.
-And if I refuse?
Mm.
-I'll move you! [grunt]
-My, my.
-Huh?
-I had hoped that we
could avoid all this.
But here we are.
-[gasp]
[grunting]
-You missed again.
CHAD (VOICEOVER):
How is he doing this?
It's impossible.
He deflected my first
blast with one hand.
And since then, he's dodged
every one without any effort
at all.
I know I'm not that weak.
But somehow, I haven't even
put a scratch on him yet.
I had no trouble dealing
with that last guy.
And he called himself
an assistant adjutant,
so there should only be two
levels' difference between him
and this captain.
Just two levels.
And yet so very far apart.
Are captains really
that powerful?
-So are you ready
to reconsider yet?
Surely you can see
that this is futile.
You have great skills.
And for a human, your
destructive power
is impressive.
But you're never going
to be able to hit me.
You're smart enough to realize
how this is going to end up.
Why don't you go home
while you still can?
-Thanks for the advice.
But nothing's going to stop me!
-Have it your way.
You ought to know,
my friend, there
are two kinds of attacks-- those
that run out of gas completely
when you reach the
point of exhaustion,
and those where you can
still push beyond that point,
but at the expense
of your life force.
Your attacks are
obviously the latter type.
-[grunts]
-I'll spare you
the usual insults
and allow you to
withdraw now, gracefully.
You are quite stubborn.
What is it that makes
you so unreasonable?
What's your purpose?
Why did you come here
in the first place?
-I've come to save the
life of Rukia Kuchiki.
-Oh, come on.
You mean Rukia,
the Soul Reaper who
went missing in the world of
the living a few months ago?
That's not enough time
for a true friendship.
A relationship like
that can't be worth
risking your life over.
-I can't deny I don't know
very much about Rukia.
That's not the point.
I might not risk
my life for her,
but Ichigo wants
to save her life.
And that's all I need to know.
What may seem like an
unworthy cause to you
is more than enough
reason for me.
-Well, I tried.
But if you're that
determined, it
would be insulting for me
to ask you to back down.
I guess it can't be avoided.
Unfortunately, it
means now I'm going
to have to take your life.
CHAD (VOICEOVER): Ichigo,
I will defeat him somehow,
I swear-- even if
it costs me my life.
And should I
survive this battle,
I vow I will renew
the pledge I made
to you in the same
words that were spoken.
[fighting noises]
MAN: [laughs] Oh, come
on! [laughs] Oh, oh!
[laughs]
-Damn you, why
don't you go down?
-This'll finish him. [laughs]
[grunting]
-Not you again!
I'm out of here, man.
-Hey, wait for me!
-You're both dead!
You hear me?
-What I don't get is why you
were just standing there, Chad.
-Sado.
-Yeah, Sado, Chad, whatever.
The point is you're lucky
I came along when I did,
or you would've got your
brains bashed out with a rock
just now.
You're incredibly strong.
So why would you
just stand there
and let those two punks
wail on you like that?
Why the hell didn't
you fight back
like that time you saved my ass?
-The thing is, I made a
promise that I would never
use my fists for my own sake.
It's a vow I made to abuelo.
-A-what?
Is that name?
-Abuelo means grandfather.
His name is Oscar
Joaquin de la Rosa.
-Is he Spanish?
-Not Spanish.
He's actually Mexican.
You see, I lived down in
Mexico before I moved here.
-Wait.
When you and I first met, I
asked you where you were from,
and you said Okinawa.
-Hm.
Is that right?
-Damn it.
Oh, fine.
If you don't want to
tell me the truth,
you make up whatever
story you want.
Just don't expect me to save
your sorry ass next time.
-Hm.
-What is that medallion
thing you wear around
your neck, anyway?
Is it valuable?
-Hm?
Oh you mean this.
Absolutely.
Probably worth
more than my life.
-Hm.
Looks to me like it's
some kind of foreign coin.
Where's it from?
-From Mexico.
-Should've figure that.
Huh?
Hey, whose cell phone?
-It must belong to one of
those guys who took off.
Guess the thing to do
is to return it to them.
ICHIGO (ON PHONE): Heh.
You should throw it in
the river, if you ask me.
[crashing]
[beeping]
CHAD (VOICEOVER): Both
of my stories were true.
I was born in Okinawa.
And I lived for a while in
Mexico before I came here.
I lost my parents
when I was young.
And I didn't have any other
relatives to take me in.
So I ended up with
my abuelo in Mexico.
I was just eight years old.
-Yasutora!
CHAD (VOICEOVER):
But back then, I
was a rotten kid, completely
spoiled and always angry.
I relied on my size.
And if anyone so much
as looked at me wrong,
I punched them out.
The only one who ever even tried
to keep me in line was Abuelo.
But I was such a jerk back
then-- a hopeless case.
And then came that fateful day
when I was so utterly careless.
Huh?
[grunting]
[crash]
CHAD (VOICEOVER): These
ropes are awfully thick.
I don't think I can
break out of this.
-This is the end for Sado,
tough guy in middle school.
So, you scared now?
You're not going to start
pissing yourself, are you?
-I don't have to
go at the moment.
I guess you just aren't
quite scary enough.
Sorry, guys.
-[laugh] Aw, man.
Well, then, in that case,
I'll just take this.
Now what did you say?
Something about this being
worth more than your life.
Then if I take it
away from you, you
might as well be dead, right?
So then die, loser.
-We've got to now!
-[gasps]
[grunting]
-Do what you will.
[gasping]
-Mijo, you were given a strong
body and fists for a reason.
But you must learn for
yourself what that reason is.
This amulet will
guide you and help
you to learn their purpose.
CHAD (VOICEOVER):
Thanks to Abuelo,
I eventually grew up
to be a decent person.
I could thank him until
my voice failed me.
And still, it would
never be enough.
[grunting]
-Don't be stupid.
Give it up.
-[together] Huh?
-What do you know?
-Huh?
-What the hell?
-Oh, great.
That damn Ichigo again.
-Get away from him!
What do you think you're doing?
-You got a lot of never going
through the boss's pockets.
-Ah, here it is.
-Yo, Weasel, are you all right?
-Weasel?
-Damn it.
Didn't I tell you guys
never to call me that.
You're always supposed
to call me boss!
ICHIGO: Shut up, Weasel!
Oh, hello.
Yes.
I'd like to request
an ambulance, please?
-What?
Calling an ambulance?
-You think you're
getting pal Sado out
of here without even
fighting us first?
Ha!
You can forget about it.
-In fact, send a few down
to the end of Second Street,
right under the bridge.
How many?
One, two, three, four, five.
Yeah, five.
[shouting]
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
I've got an idea, Chad.
How about if you
just stay the way
you are and never throw
a punch for yourself.
Instead, throw those
punches for me.
And I'll throw my
punches for you.
If there's ever anything so
important you'd protect it
with your life, I'll protect
it with mine as well.
What do you say?
CHAD (VOICEOVER): Sure.
Yes, Ichigo.
I promised.
And that's why I
know I can't lose.
ABUELO (VOICEOVER): But
you must learn for yourself
what that reason is.
This amulet will
guide you and help
you to learn their purpose.
-[shout] [gasp]
-I'm sorry.
[gasping]
[theme music]
GIRL: Kenny, it looks like
one of your bells fell off.
-Oh yeah?
Hang on a sec.
I'll it back on.
-Did you do your
hair all by yourself?
-A man's got to look good.
GIRL: Kenny, you're so talented.
KENPACHI: Want me
to do you hair, too?
ICHIGO: No, no thank you.
-It'll make you look cooler.
ICHIGO: You think so?