[music playing]
NARRATOR: 110 years
ago, a new generation
of leaders prepared to take over
due to a number of turnovers
among the captains of the
13 Court Guard Squads.
As part of the promotions,
and at the recommendation
of Yoruichi Shihoin, who
was captain of Squad Two
at the time, Kisuke Urahara
filled the empty post
as the head of Squad 12
and became its captain.
However, Hiyori Sarugaki, who
was the lieutenant of Squad 12,
had a problem with Kisuke.
She disliked his
laid-back personality
and resented his history
with the Stealth Force.
As a result, their
relationship was strained.
HIYORI SARUGAKI: Wha--
-Huh?
HIYORI SARUGAKI: What-- what
the hell is all of this?
What the heck have
you done here?
This is the captain's room!
You got it?
You can't just go doing
renovations and change it all!
-Why not?
It's OK.
I mean, it's my room.
-What?
-Besides, I didn't renovate.
I just rearranged things.
-How is this rearranging?
Come on, absolutely nothing
from the old room's left.
It's all changed.
No way.
-Ow.
All right.
Hiyori, I need to ask
you to do me a favor.
-Wha-- what do you want?
-You're going to come with me.
And we're going to pay a
visit to the Maggot's Nest.
-The Maggot's Nest?
But--
All right.
We've reached our destination.
This is the place.
-Huh?
YORUICHI SHIHOIN: Kisuke's here?
-Yes.
He said he'd already received
your permission, Lady Yoruichi.
-Hmm?
Hmm, I can't
remember the reason.
SQUAD MEMBER: What
shall we do, my lady?
If you're not certain of
the reason for his visit,
shall I ask him to leave?
-No, that won't be necessary.
Let them go wherever
he wants to.
SQUAD MEMBER: Is his purpose
coming back to you now?
-Hmm?
Not a bit.
-Lady Yoruichi?
-What now, Sui-Feng?
Sometimes you're so annoying.
-Yes, but--
YORUICHI SHIHOIN:
Oh, stop worrying.
Knowing Kisuke, I'm sure
he has a very good reason
for coming here.
-Oh, they opened up.
That's good.
You just have to follow me.
-I don't wanna.
-Come on, now.
You don't have to
act like a child.
-I don't wanna!
KISUKE URAHARA:
Regardless, you're coming.
-I said I don't wanna!
KISUKE URAHARA: Now, now.
Don't have such a bad attitude.
Who knows, when you get in you
might think it's wonderful.
-What's the deal?
I thought we were going to
some creepy place called
the Maggot's Nest.
This is Squad Two's
barracks grounds.
-You've heard of
the Stealth Force,
haven't you, Lieutenant Hiyori?
-The Stealth Force?
Well, of course I have.
It's your old unit, Kisuke.
And stop trying to
change the subject.
KISUKE URAHARA: The Stealth
Force is quite unique.
It's an organization
whose origins
are separate from the
13 Court Guard Squads.
As one of the four
great noble families who
possess incredible
soul reaper powers,
the Shihoin Clan serves
as the supreme commander
of this force.
And whenever the head
of the Shihoin Clan
also becomes a captain of one
of the 13 court guard squads,
that squad invariably
forms a close association
with the Stealth Force.
-What, do they
merge or something?
KISUKE URAHARA: Almost.
Yoruichi, who is the
current supreme commander,
also serves as
captain of Squad Two.
That means the current Stealth
Force is an organization pretty
much under the direct
control of Squad Two.
The Stealth Force is
divided into five units,
and each unit leader is also
a seated officer of Squad Two.
I was the leader of
unit three, which
is also known as the
confinement unit.
-You mean you were a yard hack?
-I think a more accurate term
would have been prison guard.
My main duties at that time
were to confine and keep
watch over anyone who
committed punishable
offenses within the Seireitei.
-Which makes you a yard hack.
-I was just a guard.
-It's the same thing.
Your job was to swagger around
in front of the criminals
and keep them in place, right?
KISUKE URAHARA: The
confinement unit
had another duty you may
not have heard about.
We trained and deployed
special confinement officers.
-Huh?
And just what did they do?
-Their job was a
little more complex.
They were to investigate,
keep under surveillance,
and if necessary apprehend
any soul reapers within the 13
Court Guard Squads
whose ideas and actions
could put other
soul reapers at risk
or create an obstruction to
the performance of the squad's
duties.
-What are you saying?
-Hmm?
-You're very confusing
when you talk.
Can't you find a simple
way to say things?
-All right.
Here it is in a nutshell-- our
job was to catch and lock up
dangerous elements within
the 13 Court Guard Squads.
The facility where we put them
is located here, in Squad Two's
barracks.
It's isolated, on the northwest
side of these grounds,
beyond the huge
54-meter wide moat.
Here it is-- the underground
confinement station, also known
as the Maggot's Nest.
HIYORI SARUGAKI: Huh?
What is this?
It's nothing but a huge cave.
Do you really keep a
bunch of people locked up
in this dreadful place,
stuck way underground?
-I guess it does sound
cruel, doesn't it?
But the truth is it's not
really an underground prison.
Do you see?
It's still a prison, of course.
I mean, they're not allowed
to leave this place.
However, their activities
within the facility
are not restricted.
-I think I got this
thing figured out.
Listen.
KISUKE URAHARA: I advise
you to be careful.
Sometimes, without warning,
someone will attack suddenly.
-So tell me, what exactly
did these people do?
-Not a thing.
-What?
-As I tried to
explain, these people
haven't actually done
anything wrong yet.
According to the criteria
of the Seireitei,
they were people
who were determined
to be dangerous elements
within the Soul Society.
They committed no crime
so we cannot try them.
However, if they
were left free, they
could well end up
being dangerous.
That's why we keep them confined
in here, safely tucked away.
-That's crazy!
They haven't done a thing and
you still keep them locked up?
KISUKE URAHARA: Hiyori,
let me ask you something.
Up until now, do
you know anybody
who's resigned from the
13 Court Guard Squads?
-Well, I-- I suppose
there's been a couple.
But what's your point?
-Truth of the matter is, there's
nothing within our system
that allows anyone to resign.
Those who have no
choice but to leave
the squad for
personal reasons are
considered to be on
leave of absence.
If they're not able to
return after a specified
period of time,
they're discharged.
We cannot willingly accept the
resignation of a soul reaper.
HIYORI SARUGAKI:
Are you serious?
-If you leave the squad, you've
resigned from the organization.
And since resignation
is not allowed,
you're considered to
be expelled and brought
here and placed in confinement.
-I don't get it.
Why go through all that trouble?
KISUKE URAHARA: The
13 Court Guard Squads
are a noble organization,
and as such it must never
produce unsuitable
elements from among those
accepted into its membership.
That's the philosophy
of Central 46,
the group that
rules the Seireitei.
So rather than allow
unsuitables back
into the general
population, they're
taken away and dealt with
in secret as deserters.
Hiyori, something's
been on my mind
ever since I was assigned to
this place as a unit leader.
I don't argue that
the people here
are all potentially dangerous.
But in many cases, I
believe that negative energy
could be turned into
something extremely positive
if we could only provide them
an environment where they
could put their
abilities to use.
-You gotta be kidding me.
You're keeping them confined
because they're dangerous,
but now you want to somehow
use their abilities?
BIG MOUTH: Hiyori?
I can't believe it.
You're really here.
-Big Mouth is here?
-Hmm?
-We graduated together.
I thought he resigned
a while back.
He always used to boast
about things he was gonna do,
like one day being in
charge of the Seireitei.
That's why we all ended
up calling him Big Mouth.
BIG MOUTH: Hiyori!
Hiyori, oh, Hiyori.
Please, you've got to help me.
We were colleagues, weren't we?
I just want to go home.
Please, I just want to go home.
Please.
-Damn, I left my
Zanpakuto at the barracks.
KISUKE URAHARA: I'm sorry.
I knew you forgot
your Zanpakuto,
but I didn't say anything.
Bringing any kind of weapon
into the confinement station
is expressly forbidden.
That's why there's a hard and
fast requirement of anyone
leading the confinement
unit that they
have to have excellent
fighting skills-- enough
to subdue someone unarmed.
My, my.
You've already
forgotten my face.
It's only been two days.
And after I took such
good care of you.
-Hey, now's our chance.
Come on, let's go.
-Kill those guys.
-Take him down.
-Get him, come on.
-It appears as though you
all have forgotten me.
How terribly rude.
BIG MOUTH: Don't move.
Listen, I just want you to
get me out of here right now.
If you don't, I'll
cut her throat.
-Hmm.
Big Mouth, I must
tell you, you've
taken the wrong person hostage.
-Don't mess with
me, you big jerk.
KISUKE URAHARA: I didn't
think it was possible,
but his mouth got a lot bigger.
Oh, well, I guess we should go.
Hiyori?
-What kind of
environment are you
talking about that will
make these guys useful, huh?
I don't see how this
can possibly work.
These guys are dangerous.
If you bring them outside,
they'll just create problems.
-Don't give up on
the whole barrel
because of a few rotten apples.
KISUKE URAHARA: Take a look.
Beyond here is the only person
in this place dangerous enough
to be confined to his own cell.
HIYORI (VOICEOVER): More
dangerous than most guys
in the yard?
What business could he have
with someone like that?
MAYURI KUROTSUCHI: Is
that you, Kisuke Urahara?
What brings you to
a place like this?
-I came down here because
I wanted to have a chat.
Let me ask you something,
Mayuri Kurotsuchi.
Would you be interested in
leaving this place with me?
-Wait.
Who is this creepy guy?
-Oh?
You call someone creepy
the first time you meet?
From my point of view, you're
quite a disrespectful boy.
-Boy?
Who are you calling a boy?
What are you, blind?
I'm a girl.
You want me to
show you my boobs?
I'll do it.
I'll show them right here.
-She's upset.
Please forgive her foul mouth.
She happens to be my
squad's lieutenant.
Ow!
And she gets offended easily.
-Lieutenant, you say.
Guess you must have
gotten promoted.
Congratulations.
KISUKE URAHARA: Thanks.
It's not always a pleasant job.
But getting back to the
subject, can I have your answer?
MAYURI KUROTSUCHI:
Oh, of course.
You mean your crazy idea of
leaving this place with you?
KISUKE URAHARA: Yes.
MAYURI KUROTSUCHI:
I don't think so.
-OK, then.
Are we done here?
If the guy doesn't
want to leave,
we'd be wasting our time
trying to convince him, right?
-And why not?
-Over time, I've become
satisfied with my life here.
I have no need to go outside.
-Come on, Mayuri.
That couldn't
possibly be true, not
in a place such as this
where there's nothing to do.
MAYURI KUROTSUCHI: I'm not
so sure that's a bad thing.
Why is it you want to
get me out of here?
-Truthfully?
Because I need your assistance.
-Let's dispense with
the lies, shall we?
You don't really expect
me to believe that.
-When you put it that
way, I guess not.
You really don't
trust me, do you?
MAYURI KUROTSUCHI: The bottom
line is I can't figure you out.
You're really quite
an unpleasant fellow.
-Hmm.
I believe in your skills.
And that is the truth.
I'm in the process of creating
an organization unlike anything
ever seen in the Soul Society.
It'll be under the
control of Squad 12.
It's the Department of
Research and Development.
I would like you to assume the
seat of Deputy Department Head.
-What?
-You mean you want
me to work under you?
KISUKE URAHARA: That's correct.
It's not such a
bad offer, is it?
You'd be second
in command to me.
In other words, if
I were to pass away,
you would end up
having total control.
MAYURI KUROTSUCHI:
As I stated before,
you really are a most
unpleasant fellow.
-Wow, that's quite
impressive, Byakuya.
I see you're working very hard.
-Grandfather, what an
unsuspected surprise.
Did you decide to
rest here today
rather than at the barracks?
-Hmm.
-I'm so glad you did.
It's been a long time since
I've been able to talk to you.
I very much enjoy
our conversations.
-Hmm.
So what do you say, Byakuya?
How about taking a break
from practice for a while?
I brought someone
here to see you.
-Me?
It's you, cat monster!
-Cat monster?
That's what I get for
coming over to visit?
And I went out of my way
to make a special trip.
-Oh, please.
When did I ever say I wanted
you to come here and visit me?
As the next head of
the Kuchiki Clan,
I don't wish to be
involved in your games.
They're not fun.
YORUICHI SHIHOIN:
Oh, is that so?
It may be games
to you, but I'd be
worried about the clans
future if a mere girl was
able to steal a headband so
easily off its leader's head.
-Stay right where you are,
Miss Yoruichi Shihoin.
You haven't seen
my flash step yet.
-Oh, yeah?
Looks like you lost.
-I do see.
It appears you're trying
to make me really angry.
Fine.
I guess you'll have to
find out for yourself.
Fact of the matter is, I'm
about to prove that my flash
step is far superior to yours!
-Oh, that boy.
There's no telling
how far Byakuya
would go if he could just find
some way to control his temper.
Nothing I can do about it now.
Guess I'll have some tea.
-That's perfect.
-I see that smile of yours
is as powerful as always.
Hot!
-About my offer.
-Do you want me to say it again?
I'm not going to serve as
your lieutenant, captain.
-Why are you being so stubborn?
I'm starting to take
this personally.
-You know as well
as I do there are
lots of others who deserve to be
second in command more than me.
-There you go again.
You're always putting
duty before friendship.
By the way, have you heard?
KAIEN SHIBA: About what?
JUSHIRO UKITAKE: There's a
prodigy among this year's
recruits, the first one
to show up since you.
KAIEN SHIBA: Believe
me, I'm no prodigy.
-This young man was able to
graduate from Soul Reaper
Academy in only one full year.
-Hmm.
Is that right?
I admit that's impressive.
-I still can't quite believe it.
From what I hear,
he's just a kid.
He's about the same age as
Captain Kuchiki's grandson,
Byakuya.
-Oh, you mean the cocky one.
-I know what you're saying.
But apparently this prodigy
has the talent of a man
twice his age.
I hear an officer's position
will be ready for him
when he enters the squad.
-Oh?
Well, it looks like
we've got ourselves
someone with quite a future.
That should make my chances to
fill a lieutenant's position
even more unlikely.
-You don't have to
sound so happy about it.
-So who is it?
Who's the lucky squad that's
going to get the new recruit?
-Well now, from what I've heard,
he'll be joining Squad Five.
SOSUKE AIZEN: Nice.
Your skill is even
better than I was told.
What is your name
again, young warrior?
-Gin.
I am Gin Ichimaru.
SOSUKE AIZEN: And how did
you find our Third Seat?
GIN ICHIMARU: Terrible.
No competition at all.
-Interesting.
Glad to hear it.
NARRATOR: Having
swung through the past
to observe a quick
glimpse in time,
we now flash forward
nine years as we
move even closer to the
crux of the incident.
[music playing]
MALE VOICE 1: I want
you to be my lieutenant.
Let me be clear.
What that means is if I die,
you will have complete control.
MALE VOICE 2: Where is
this from out of the blue?
MALE VOICE 1: I was trying
to imitate Kisuke Urahara.
How'd I do?
MALE VOICE 2: It wasn't the
least bit funny, so stop it.