[MUSIC - BEAT CRUSADERS,
"TONIGHT, TONIGHT, TONIGHT"]
UGAKI (OFFSCREEN): How nice.
Fresh targets.
-Ichigo.
-Zabimaru.
-Hado Four.
Byakurai.
-Rukia, look out.
-Stay out of the shadows.
The shadows are where
this doll emerges from.
-What the hell?
Ichigo, Renji, you
go on ahead of us.
-Let's go.
-Yeah.
All right.
-It's Yumichika.
-Renji, I think
something's coming.
-What the hell's that?
-Time to witness
the real Gesell.
-Yumichika!
-What the hell.
[roar]
-He's huge.
-Yeah, I noticed.
UGAKI (OFFSCREEN): I
wonder which of you I
should crush first.
Or perhaps, before we start,
I should return this to you.
-Put him down now.
-Renji, is he OK?
-Hey, Yumichika.
-How'd I end up like this.
This is not the beautiful ending
I had imagined for myself,
not at all.
As one of Zaraki's
men, it is my duty
to lose only in
the act of dying.
Now, what do I tell him?
I can never face the
captain like this.
UGAKI (OFFSCREEN): Ah, so
he's still breathing, is he?
You soul reapers are persistent.
I must admit.
-Coward.
Why don't you come
out here and face us?
Are you afraid?
[laughing]
-All right then.
If he won't come out
on his own, then we're
just going to have
to destroy his doll
and then drag him out here.
-Hey, Ichigo, I'd like you
to stand aside and leave
this one to me.
Look, I have nothing
against battling as a team.
Kisuke Urahara taught me
that solo attacks aren't
the only way to fight
an enemy, and I finally
understand that now.
Just the same, I've
been thinking lately
that all this teamwork
has made me soft.
I think that I may have begun
depending on others too much
and letting down my guard.
-What exactly are you saying?
-It's like Yumichika said,
the way of the soul reaper
is the one-on-one fight, and
the only good way to lose
is to die in the end.
So if I'm going to die, then
I'm going to go all out.
-But Renji--
-I couldn't even save a
single child in that fight
the other day.
While it was happening,
there was a moment
where I hesitating, thinking
that somehow one of you
might come along to help me.
As a result, I put
that kid in danger.
I could feel it.
Since coming here to
the world of the living,
I've only gotten softer.
If I don't somehow get my spirit
back to where it was before,
then how can I return
to the soul society?
Besides, we know there
are other Bounts.
You're going to need
to save your stamina,
or else you won't have
anything left to finish this.
-Renji, wait.
I think that--
-A lieutenant of the
13 Court Guard Squads
is offering to fight
alone on your behalf.
Quit complaining.
-OK.
-All right, you.
I'm going to take you on myself.
-You really want to
fight Gesell one-on-one?
How reckless of you.
Gesell, crush him.
-Bankai.
Hihio Zabimaru.
-Renji, look out.
-Zabimaru!
I'm using my spiritual
pressure to hold
Zabimaru's blade
segments together.
As you can see, I am able to
separate or join them at will.
As a result, they're impervious
to your blade's attacks and you
cannot break them.
-Well, that's pretty
damn impressive.
-I suppose, but it's
lacking in beauty.
-I'll finish this
once and for all, now.
-It can't be helped.
[roar]
-What the hell's this.
UGAKI (OFFSCREEN):
Perhaps fighting
this battle your way wasn't
such a good idea after all.
-Renji.
-No.
Don't interfere.
-Why not?
-Remember what he told you.
Zaraki's style is one-on-one.
-But Renji isn't even
a member of Squad 11.
-Not now.
But he was once.
And anyone who's ever been a
member of Zaraki's Squad 11
carries that spirit with them,
even long after they leave.
-You've got to be kidding.
RENJI (OFFSCREEN): Ichigo!
Just shut up for a
change and watch.
Would you?
You get to see me turn this
whole damn thing around.
-Renji!
UGAKI (OFFSCREEN): Ah really?
But how?
You don't have many
options left now do you?
What's this?
Master Kariya, a
soul reaper has just
appeared before the Quincy.
-So they have arrived.
UGAKI (OFFSCREEN):
What should we do?
-This changes the situation.
Ugaki, you need to
finish your fight.
UGAKI (OFFSCREEN): I
understand, Master.
RENJI (OFFSCREEN): So
you've come out to play.
UGAKI (OFFSCREEN): Your fighting
spirit is quite impressive.
I didn't expect
you to confront me,
knowing it would
certainly mean your doom.
But regardless of how
foolish it would seem
and how easy it will be
for me to finish you off,
if it is death you want,
soul reaper, then I
will respect your feelings
and use Gesell's power
to destroy you and your snake.
I suggest you prepare to die.
Gesell, finish him off.
[roaring]
-All right.
Higa Zekko.
[painful screaming]
-What has he done to Gesell?
Damn it.
Now I've got to retreat.
-Who is that?
UGAKI (OFFSCREEN):
Renji, there's the Bount.
The bastard was controlling
his doll from behind there
all this time.
-Whoa.
How can this be?
Impossible.
-Ugaki, you have served me well.
UGAKI (OFFSCREEN): Master, help.
-I bid you adieu.
-Don't abandon me now.
Master, wait.
How dare you do this?
I've lost control of him.
Kariya, how could you turn your
back on me after all of this.
I fought this fight
perfectly just as you said.
Gesell, stop!
Gesell, it's me.
What are you doing?
[screaming]
-Renji.
Damn.
-You go on ahead, Ichigo.
I'll stay and take
care of Renji.
-Wait.
What are you talking about now?
-As it happens, I
owe a debt to Renji,
and now is the time
for me to repay it.
Go quickly.
-Hey.
Wait.
-Renji, where are you!
Yumichika!
Renji!
Where are they?
KARIYA (OFFSCREEN): Are
you the sole survivor then?
-You bastard.
-Just how many of my
precious and valuable Bounts
do you intend to destroy
before you're done?
We're a small tribe already.
Few in numbers.
-What's your point?
FEMALE WHISPER: Demon.
MALE WHISPER: Demon.
FEMALE WHISPER: Dream.
MALE WHISPER: Dream.
FEMALE WHISPER: Evil.
MALE WHISPER: Evil.
FEMALE WHISPER: Fallen.
MALE WHISPER: Fallen.
-I would have preferred that you
were buried along Gesell, but--
-What?
-No matter.
-You'll see you haven't
changed anything,
and I will still
get what I seek even
if it takes a little longer now.
-How can this be?
Impossible.
-You monster.
And I'll bet it was
you who deliberately
collapsed the wall
shielding him.
-No, I didn't.
I suspect the foundation
was weakened in the attack
by the red-headed soul reaper.
Believe what you like,
but the fact is the wall
came down on its own.
-And you call your
Bounts valuable.
How valuable can
they really be to you
when you used one of them
as a pathetic pawn just
to slow us down?
-Not part of the plan
I can assure you,
but events are moving
faster than anticipated.
My tribe and I must
begin making preparations
to leave the world
of the living.
-To leave the world
of the living?
So do you really
plan on connecting
this world with Hueco Mundo?
Could it be that you're--
you're in this with Aizen?
[laugh]
-I need assistance from no one.
Begin preparations.
-[speaking foreign language]
-What the hell is that?
KARIYA (OFFSCREEN):
It's our Senkaimon.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Impossible.
-Oh.
I think you understand.
Powerful Bounts
who have absorbed
a large number of souls are
able to manipulate space.
I, myself, have
long had this power.
-Shall I take over
the controls, Koga?
-Go ahead.
I wish now that I
had finished you
off when I had the opportunity.
-Oh yeah?
-Now, let's get started.
From what I know
about you I think
you'll be a good
test for my powers.
-All right.
But I intend to destroy
you and your damn gate.
[laugh]
-No way.
[grunting]
-What's going on?
I could have sworn
that I made contact.
He managed to block
Zangetsu unarmed.
-Mabashi.
-Huh?
-The next time you feel like
getting drunk off living souls,
you should remember what you
have just witnessed here.
That is the essence of a
Bount who has gained power.
-Ha.
-Are you finished?
[groaning]
-You've yet to
test my abilities,
even in the slightest.
And what about your Bankai?
-What?
-Oh yes.
I know all about it.
I know that you are
the only one who
can use his Bankai in
the world of the living
without restrictions.
That's why I thought you would
be a good test of my powers.
Get your Zanpakuto.
[grunting]
-I guess you're finished.
-You may think so.
But you're wrong.
-[laugh] I see.
Well, it would be
a shame for you
to die without knowing what
this was all about, so I suppose
there's no harm in
telling you what
the Bounts' true objectives are.
-Who cares?
-But Master, you can't.
-There's nothing to worry about.
As far as I can remember,
it's been out in the open
since the beginning.
Connecting the world of the
living with Hueco Mundo though,
that's just an explanation
the soul society came up
with on their own when
they couldn't figure out
what was really going on.
What good would something
like that do anyway?
The Bounts are not
heading to Hueco Mundo.
I can guarantee you that.
We're going to the soul society.
-What?
Why?
-To exact our revenge.
We're returning to the
soul society, where
all Bounts were first created.
[theme music]
RANGIKU (OFFSCREEN): Is
it true that the Bounts
plan to go the soul society?
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): That's
what that jerk Jin Kariya says?
RANGIKU (OFFSCREEN): Then
we've got to go back.
But I haven't even gone
shopping or sightseeing yet.
Ichigo, you have to tell me
about some interesting places
I can visit quickly.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Rangiku
will be leaving now.
Please show her the door.
[theme music]
-Jeez.
I guess it's not a problem since
there isn't much to do now.
But I wonder where the
hell Hanataro ran off to.
Come to think of it.
Why did I end up coming
here in the first place?
-Is that what you like?
-Huh?
-Hey, hold it a second, boss.
Oh no.
That's not good.