[theme music]
NARRATOR: In preparation for
their show down with Sosuke
Aizen, Ichigo, Chad, and Uryu
have started their training.
Rukia and Orihime have
headed to the Soul Society
in hopes of also
getting stronger.
Captain Histugaya's team have
remained in Karakura Town,
and to their surprise, an
Arrancar-like creature that
can continuously
replicate itself
began to appear randomly.
If they don't destroy the
original source creature,
the Soul Reapers fear
the mock Arrancar
will continue to multiply
until its numbers become
overhwelming.
AKON: That's probably why the
mock Arrancar was attracted
to her in the first place.
Yoi Toyokawa is a clone.
NARRATOR: Yui was used as
bait by the mock Arrancar
to lure her brother Shota so
it could absorb his spirit
energy as well.
-Yui!
What's going on?
-Shota, don't.
You've gotta get away from me.
-Yui!
-Stay away!
-Yui.
-Growl, Heineko!
Now!
-Yui!
No!
Yui!
Are you all right?
-Oh no.
-Is that the--
-Shota, get out of here.
Run!
You have to listen.
Run.
-Keep quiet, little girl.
-I am not gonna run.
I won't ever run away and
leave you behind again.
-So that's the
original Arrancar.
-You've got to listen to me.
If you stay, he'll eat you.
Run away!
-No.
Not this time, Tui.
I'm staying here to protect you!
-It's too late for that.
Save yourself.
-What's wrong?
Yui!
I can't-- I can't move.
Why won't my body listen to me?
Got to save Yui.
-This girl.
I never expected her to still
have the will to defy me,
but it ends here.
-Yui!
Yui.
-Hado 4, Byakurai!
Come on.
You need to get a
hold of yourself.
-Rangiku.
Yui was--
-Yes, I know.
-Soul Reaper.
-It's time for you
to prepare to die.
-You got it backwards.
When I ate that girl,
I got all her power.
-Get behind me
and hold on tight!
-Soul Reapers are nothing
compared to the kind of power
I've stored up!
-Obviously you
don't know who I am.
I'm the Lieutenant of Squad 10.
My name's Rangiku Matsumoto.
-A lieutenant?
Good.
Now I'm looking
forward to eating you!
-Too slow.
Now to finish you off!
Growl, Heineko!
-Don't underestimate me.
-Where'd he go?
[shouting]
-Shota.
I'm coming!
-Now.
Which one of you
should I eat first?
-Not gonna happen.
HITSUGAYA: Rangiku!
Step aside.
Rain over the frosted
heavens, Hyorinmaru!
-What's this?
-Captain.
-Get Shota.
-Are you all right?
-Rangiku.
-Get ready.
-Who are you?
-I am the Captain of Squad
10, Toshiro Hitsugaya.
-A Captain?
-Since you seem to
have no idea that we
are in the world
of the living, I
doubt that you're taking
your orders from Aizen.
So then, I guess
that also means you
must have mutated after
absorbing the girl's spirit
energy.
-You bastard.
-Like I said.
Prepare to die.
-Uh, uh, are you sure
you want to do that?
If you kill me, that girl
will go down as well.
-I know.
We already figured that
out based on the results
we got from the Soul Society.
But you and all of your weak
threats don't mean a thing to--
SHOTA: No!
-Shota.
What is it?
-Yui's still alive!
She told me to run away, but
I have to try and save her.
-I'm afraid I cannot save one
soul at the risk of losing
the entire city.
-No, you have to!
-Shota.
Stop.
-Watch out.
-Yui!
-I have to stay on him.
[evil laughter]
ARRANCAR: You missed your
best chance to defeat me.
-Oh yeah?
ARRANCAR: As long as
I'm in the subspace,
you won't be able to find me.
But I can hide my
spiritual pressure,
attack souls, and make
as many clones as I want.
Behold, my army of servants.
-Captain Hitsugaya.
-Ikkaku.
Yumichika.
Where did they all come from?
-No wonder there was no end no
matter how many we destroyed.
[laughing]
ARRANCAR: I can multiply
by about 16 times in a day.
Unfortunately, it took you
too long to realize that.
With this many of me, it'll be
impossible to stop them all.
Plus, I keep making
more everyday.
I've eaten most of the
souls in this town already.
I guess I'll have to
eat the humans next.
See you around.
-Come back here!
-Ikkaku.
Wait.
We're never going to end this.
Even if we were to cut
every one of them down.
-You may be right,
but we can't just
allow them to run around free.
-Squad 11 specializes in combat.
I'd rather be a man of
action than a man of thought,
so let's crush them until
we run out of spirit energy.
Let us go.
Please.
-In the meantime, you can think
of a way to deal with them.
-All right.
Go.
-Come on!
-Right.
-This is Hitsugaya.
-This is the Department of
Research and Development.
HITSUGAYA: We have encountered
the mock Arrancar's main body,
but unfortunately he got away.
Can you track him?
-We're doing that right now.
-No good.
We can't track him.
-No support.
We've lost sight of him.
There are no traces
of distortion either.
-He's gone.
I'm so sorry, but--
-What's this?
-Well, what is it?
-We've pinpointed the
location of the sound
that the Arrancar
uses to control souls.
-What exactly do you mean?
-It looks like the
original creature produces
the strange sound
while all of his clones
are acting as speakers and
spreading it all over the town.
-How is he doing that?
I don't know, but it's as if
the main body and the clones
are connected by a
wireless connection.
-Huh?
-I'm guessing that they
deliver the spirit energy
they absorb back to the
main body the same way.
Maybe we can try to pinpoint
the location of the main body
by figuring out the
distribution of the clones.
Or not.
-All systems, analyze
the distribution
of spiritual pressure!
-This could work.
-Send us the data, Rin.
RIN: Yes, sir.
[sobbing]
-Shota.
I want to give you some
information about this Arrancar
we're fighting.
Originally, they were
identified as Hollows.
They're very much
like a fallen soul.
A soul that still has an
attachment to the world
and becomes corrupted.
It then loses its heart
and becomes a Hollow.
We Soul Reapers exist
not only to save souls,
but to save Hollows as well.
We do that by cutting
Hollow with our Zanpakuto,
but this sends them back
to the Soul Society.
It's sort of like cleansing
Hollows of their sins in order
for them to be reborn.
I'm so sorry that we
couldn't protect your sister.
But it's not too late.
We can still save Yui's soul.
-OK.
-This time it's
gonna be your turn.
Hold on to this.
I think that you and I should
save Yui's soul together.
-'Kay.
-Are the two of you
finished talking?
Let's get going.
-Right.
-Ha!
-Heh, heh, heh.
You can't defeat me like that.
You're way too slow.
-Shoo!
Beat it!
Go away!
I wonder if these are the
clones of that Arrancar.
If so-- there are
so many of them.
Looks like my chores--
-Will have to wait.
-Hey, don't slack off.
-I knew it.
The clones aren't spread
out over a large area.
I'm calculating the
location out their source
by analyzing the distribution
of where they appear.
It's in the western
part of Karakura Town.
Near the river.
-So how do we go about
finding the original Arrancar?
-According to the Department
of Research and Development,
the Arrancar is only hiding
his spiritual pressure.
-The main body of
the original Arrancar
needs to be able to communicate
at all times with its clones.
There's no way that he'd
be hiding in a place that's
shut off from the world of
the living, like Hueco Mundo.
-I think he's probably hiding
within a special barrier.
-I see.
-I think that if we
were to hit his barrier
with our spiritual pressure,
we should be able to break it.
-All right.
In that case, I'll hit the
better with my full strength.
-No.
I'll do it myself.
In order to pry him open
from his protective space,
we need a proportional
amount of spiritual pressure.
You take care of the enemy
when it comes jumping out.
-Yes, sir.
-Good luck.
Bankai!
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!
[shouting]
-What's this?
What's going on?
It's that Soul
Reaper from before.
He's come this far.
But he won't be able to hit me
if he just aimlessly releases
his spirit energy!
-Get ready.
This'll smoke him out.
[shouting]
-Wait.
What's that?
Is it Captain Hitsugaya?
I wonder what he's
doing over there.
Huh?
These guys keep
coming and coming!
-OK, Captain
Hitsugaya's in place.
I sure hope he'll all right.
-I wonder if maybe he should
have applied for Gentei Kaijo.
-Damn.
-Be careful, Captain.
-Yui!
It's me, Shota!
Where are you?
Yui!
-Once more.
[shouting]
-Fool.
You're gonna try that again?
Even if you're a captain,
trying to destroy my space
with spiritual
pressure is ridiculous.
Huh?
What's that?
-That sound.
-It's Yui.
[whistling]
-Where's that
whistling coming from?
I should have absorbed
that girl completely.
How is this happening?
-Yui!
-I wonder where that
sound is coming from?
[whistling]
-Over there.
-We found it, sir!
[shouting]
-I've found you.
-How dare you.
You'll pay for this.
You'll pay!
Crush him to bits!
Dientes!
[growling]
-Let's go!
-Is that the best
you can do, kid?
-He might be right.
I'm pretty spent.
I'd better end this now, while
I still have something left.
Ryusenka!
[roar]
-My iron skin is as
strong as an Espada's!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
-So you don't even
think that I hit you.
Guess again.
Wha-- what?
[struggling]
-My legs!
-Rangiku!
Finish him off!
-Right!
Shota, grab a hold of my sword.
-OK.
-You and I will save your
sister's soul together.
-Yeah.
-I won't be defeated by you.
Huh?
-OK, he's stopped moving.
Now's our chance.
-Right!
-Shota!
[shouting]
SHOTA: Yui.
[screaming]
-All the souls he devoured
are being released.
-What?
-Look at that.
-What the hell is going on?
-It looks like they
suddenly disappeared.
-Shota.
-Rangiku?
Yui got to go to
the Soul Society.
Didn't she?
She can be reborn now.
Right?
-Yes.
Yes, she can.
I promise you.
-Well, then-- I guess
that I should follow her.
-Yeah.
Are you ready?
It really hurts without her.
[theme music]
ICHIGO: Everyone's going to
be training until winter,
but all you want to do is have
fun in the world of the living,
don't you, Rangiku?
RANGIKU: Not true.
And as proof, we'll
show you our daily lives
in the next episode.
ICHIGO: Still sounds
like all you're doing
is having fun to me.
RANGIKU: It's all right.
We've got permission from him.
ICHIGO: Who's him?