The Zanpakuto. Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined by
its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper and
dies with its Soul
Reaper.
That is the existence of
a Zanpakuto.
A man calling himself
Muramasa caused all of
the Zanpakuto to take
their physical form, and
attacked the Soul
Society.
Without the use of their
Shikai, the Soul Reapers
were overpowered. In one
night, the Zanpakuto
delivered a serious blow
to the Thirteen Court
Guard Squads and
vanished.
And now, the Seireitei is
in a confused, precarious
state.
Meanwhile, Rukia was
searching the Seireitei
for Byakuya, who had gone
missing. Then, without
warning, Sodenoshirayuki
appeared before her.
Sodenoshirayuki. You are
now free... forever.
Rukia!!
That was quite a
spectacle.
Who the hell are you?!
Can't you tell? I'm
a Zanpakuto.
Hey, what are you doing?
Yeah, do you see anything
interesting out there?
That is none of your
business.
What did you say?!
There's no need for
that attitude!
Hey, don't
ignore us!
Don't bother.
There's no point fighting
with each other.
Remember, our real
enemies are over there.
Yeah but still...
Heh. And they won't get
away next time. I'm gonna
crush that annoying
bastard.
Yeah, you're right.
Now that I think about
it, I am kind-of looking
forward to killing the
one who calls me that
insulting nickname.
Right. We'll teach
them a good lesson.
Did you say you're a
Zanpakuto?!
That's right.
Sodenoshirayuki,
you'd best make yourself
scarce at the moment and
leave this to me...
Thank you.
Hold it!!
Going somewhere,
Ichigo Kurosaki?
How do you know my name?
That is not important
right now.
What?! What are you up
to?
My goal is quite simple:
release all of the
Zanpakuto from the Soul
Reapers.
That is all I wish.
I see.
So you're the one
who's behind all of
this!
You know how Rukia can
get her Zanpakuto back!
Start talkin' now!
Tell me Ichigo, what
is a Zanpakuto?
What?!
Zanpakuto are individual
souls that are born
within the hearts of Soul
Reapers.
They draw their power
from the same source as
their Soul Reaper, and
are intertwined with
their master's soul.
Soul Reapers must reach
deep into their own
selves to find the power
hidden within.
They commune with their
Zanpakuto, bond together,
and harness their power
by learning their names.
What's more... A few
chosen Soul Reapers can
gain even more power. By
manifesting an
incarnation of their
Zanpakuto, and
controlling it, they
wield the mighty Bankai.
You and the captains have
done this.
But living alongside Soul
Reapers is not the only
way for a Zanpakuto to
exist.
What are you talking
about?
I'm saying that every
Zanpakuto has free will,
just like you do.
They have free will?
Yes. Zanpakuto are not
dependent on Soul
Reapers. We are
separate entities.
Two distinct beings, no
one greater than the
other.
Is that so hard to
believe?
More proof of how
arrogant you Soul Reapers
are.
You've got it wrong.
Your blindness is why
I'm here. I understand
how the Zanpakuto thinks.
I can see into their souls.
And I can grant physical
form to those who choose
to join me.
Impossible!
Any Zanpakuto who answers
my call will become
liberated from their Soul
Reaper, and manifest in
the world as their true
form.
That power is the gift
that I alone possess.
Why the hell would the
Zanpakuto listen to you?
Simple. Because
ignorant people like you
have oppressed them for
so very long.
You're wrong.
Huh?
What you're saying just
isn't the truth.
I have never looked down on
Sodenoshirayuki as my inferior.
Rukia!
Your Zanpakuto does not
share your opinion.
Clearly, Sodenoshirayuki
has confirmed what I'm
saying.
There's no need to push
yourself. You have served
your purpose well.
What do you mean?
Did you honestly believe
you were able to escape
the World of the Living
on your own?
What?
My objective is to free
all the Zanpakuto from
their Soul Reapers. No
exceptions.
And in order to do that,
I needed you, Ichigo
Kurosaki, to find your
way here.
You're saying...
you used Rukia?!
Welcome to my world.
Ichigo.
I'll handle this guy. Just
stay put and rest up.
There's no way in hell
you're gonna get away
with this!
Let's take this
elsewhere.
Whatever you want, boy.
Ichigo.
Getsuga tensho!
Where is he?!
What?!
Put down your sword.
Damn it!
This is useless.
What is this?!
Damn it! What did you do
to me!?
Bastard!
Now hear my voice.
Follow your instincts
and
release your soul from
this body.
Discard your fear.
Look ahead. Go forth.
Do not stop.
Turn back, and you will
age. Hesitate and you
will die.
Come now. I know your
name... Zangetsu!
Aaaggghhh!!
What happened?
Ichigo.
Zangetsu. How can you
be here!?
Zangetsu, what the hell?
Why are you doing
this?!
Answer me!
What happened to the two
of us being one mind and
one body!?
Dammit!
I'm impressed you can
still move.
But, it's over for you.
Zangetsu, I don't
understand. You're
with him now?!
Dammit!
Getsuga tensho.
Captain Unohana!
Oh, Isane? Is something
the matter?
Yes Ma'am! I have a
field report from Squad
Twelve.
You're saying that the
Zanpakuto have somehow
become separate entities?
Yes.
What does that mean?
I'm not exactly sure of
the ramifications, but
master Mayuri came to
this conclusion only
after testing the
phenomenon on his own
body.
Could you share the
details?
Yes.
Hmmm.
Well, it would seem the
Zanpakuto's spirit really
has left my body.
Fascinating. Most
fascinating.
Master Mayuri, I was
under the impression that
Zanpakuto and Soul
Reapers were different
manifestations of the
same essential soul.
Normally that is the
case. But now the two
have split into entirely
distinct entities.
That's impossible.
That's why it fascinates
me! And don't act like a
know-it-all, you useless
idiot!
Hmm... The real
question, is what
caused this change to
suddenly take place?
From what you're telling
us, it seems that our current
situation is actually worse
than I had imagined.
'Scuse me, but can I
ask a question about
something?
Since they aren't
connected to us anymore,
what'll happen if one of
the Soul Reapers defeats
a Zanpakuto in battle?
I don't know.
If that happened, is
there a chance we would
lose our Zanpakuto
forever?
It is possible, but without
more data, I can't tell you for
certain what would happen...
Oh no.
I understand. I suppose
the only thing we can do
is have faith in Captain
Kurotsuchi.
There's one more thing.
Master Mayuri had a request
for you, Captain Unohana.
What did he want?
He asked if you would
provide him with data on
the Soul Reapers
currently receiving
treatment from Squad
Four, so that he can
analyze it.
Of course. I'll have it
sent to you right away.
And also...
He wants to start
compiling a data profile
on you, as well.
You mean Captain Unohana
has to go all the way to
the Department of Research
and Development?!
That's right. He told
me he needs to start
collecting data on all
of the captains.
Very well then.
But Captain!
It'll be all right,
Isane.
Ma'am, but you--
You know Captain Kurotsuchi's
examination with be incredibly
personal and invasive.
Are you sure
about this, ma'am?
Isane, I'm afraid we are
in a race against time.
Yes, ma'am.
In return for my
cooperation, I ask that
you to report any new
findings to us
immediately.
Understood?
Of course.
Field report!
Large-scale combat has
been confirmed in the
Seireitei!
The Spiritual Pressure
detected at the scene
belongs to Rukia Kuchiki
of Squad Thirteen, and
Substitute Soul Reaper
Ichigo Kurosaki!
What's this?
And who might you be?
You're not Ichigo
Kurosaki.
No. What you're seeing
is the other soul that
lives within his body.
Other soul?
Getsuga...
...tensho!
Instant regeneration.
This Spiritual
Pressure.
As I thought.
What is this?
You can't have it! I
won't give it to you!
I'm not giving this power
to you!
I will not let you steal
what belongs to me!!
Zangetsu.
Zangetsu--
Who is this man?
Zangetsu, why?!
I've grown bored with
your internal world.
What?!
It's all buildings and no
greenery. I want to see
forests. I long for the
grandeur of nature.
I can plant a garden or
something.