[theme music]
NARRATOR: In order
to save Orihime,
who was kidnapped
by the Arrancars,
Ichigo, Chad, Uryu,
Rukia, and Renji
have all snuck into Hueco
Mundo, the realm of the Hollows.
The journey to Aizen's
fortress, Las Noches,
has been hard fought, as
our heroes have struggled
against endless attacks
from the Arrancar forces.
They enter a room with
strange spiritual pressures
and five separate doorways
leading into the fortress.
-As we approach the
crucial battlegrounds,
believe that our blades
will not shatter,
believe the result
will not weaken!
Though out paths may
diverge, our iron hearts
will remain together.
Swear that, though land
itself may break asunder,
we will come back here alive.
NARRATOR: Ichigo
proceeded down this path,
unaware that Arrancar 103,
Dordoni, was waiting for him.
Ichigo was initially confused
by the strange actions and words
of this triple digit
Arrancar, but when
Ichigo decided to take
the fight seriously,
Dordoni's whole persona
seemed to change.
-My, my.
Never judge people by their
appearances, [spanish].
We are a group known
as the Privaron Espada.
In other words, any Arrancar
with a three digit number,
including me, used to be
a member of the Espada.
Whirl, Giralda!
Don't tell me that's
all you got, nino.
-The spiritual pressure.
It feels like Ichigo.
Damn.
I sense a terrible presence
emanating from this place.
Wha-- What is-- What
the hell is that?
[grumbling]
[shouting]
-Don't speak up on me like that.
It's really annoying.
And what are you
doing here anyway?
-Ne-- ne!
-Ne?
What about [?
Ne?
Spit it out, will you?
-Nel!
I'm looking for Nel, know
what I'm talking about?
-Then why are you wasting
your time running after me?
Wait.
I know.
You're lost.
You got lost, didn't you?
-Where is Nel, man?
-What are you asking me for?
I don't know.
But even if you are lost,
this doesn't make any sense.
I mean, you don't
have any reason
to come after me, do you?
-But Nel.
Nel went after Ichigo!
If we don't hurry and find
Nel, it'll just be terrible.
-Stop it.
If she's with Ichigo,
then she's safe.
Now stop crying already.
It's weirding me out.
That's not why I'm so upset.
You see-- You see, if we-- If
we don't find Nel quickly--
[sobbing]
-I-- If we don't find Nel
and stop her, then Nel will--
Nel will--
[screaming]
-He's running away.
Wait up.
Why do you keep
running away from me?
-Because you're chasing me.
It's a reflex.
Your face is-- How
should I put this?
That face of yours is
scaring the crap out of me.
Please stop running
away and listen!
If you just give
me a chance, I'll
tell you the good
part of the story.
-You stop, then I'll stop.
Besides.
If you're looking for Nel,
you need to turn around.
She's the other way.
DONDOCHAKKA: Nel!
-Ichigo!
-Tonto.
Well?
Come on, come on, come on.
Do it!
Use your Bankai, nino.
Or you'll die!
Why are you saving
your spirit energy
against an opponent like me?
A sentiment as sweet as
chocolate, but foolish.
Don't you understand
what's going on here?
You're being very
unreasonable, nino.
Why not use your Bankai?
I'm interested to see
you at full power.
-Getsuga Tensho!
-Well?
-Ichigo!
Are you all right?
Ichigo, be careful.
-Ah.
I applaud the power
your displayed just now.
But still, you know what
you're facing here, right?
At this rate, you haven't
got a chance of winning.
-I wouldn't be so sure of that.
-I'm not making
assumptions here.
I'm merely stating the truth.
-Getsuga Tensho!
Not again.
-Now, check this out.
I'll just keep
beating you like this
until you change your mind.
This pains me, nino.
Correction.
Hardly pains is what
I really meant to say.
Let's see your Bankai.
And soon.
Because if I don't keep
holding back, nino, you die.
Got it?
What a waste.
All this would be for
nothing if that happens.
-Ichigo!
Ichigo!
This is bad!
If you don't do something,
you're gonna die!
Ichigo!
-Look, now you have upset little
baby and it's all your fault.
Come on, nino.
It's time to use your Bankai.
Ah.
-Getsuga--
-I already told you!
Don't underestimate me, nino!
-Bastard!
-Naughty boys who don't
listen will be punished!
Cero!
[gasping]
-Nel.
What the--
-What did she just
do to my Cero?
-Gah!
She swallowed it!
-What the hell?
You just-- are you
gonna be all right, Nel?
-Wah!
Listen, you!
Don't you be mean
to Ichigo again.
Ah!
-Oh, no!
-Heh.
I don't know who
you are, [spanish],
but you are impressive.
I never thought that someone
could deflect my Cero
while I was in my released form.
However, unruly children
need to learn their place.
Now get lost!
-If you want to
see it that badly,
then I guess I'll
show it to you.
I hope it was worth the wait.
Let me introduce
you to my Bankai.
-It's about time.
I knew you'd have to
use it eventually.
-Ichigo--
[coughing]
ICHIGO: Nel, I'm sorry.
You got hurt because
I was being stubborn
about something that
doesn't even matter.
When I came here I wanted
to do things right,
so I decided that
in order to fight
on the level of the
Espada, I shouldn't
use my Bankai
against anyone else.
That was stupid.
-You think so?
I think it's important for those
who want true strength to learn
to restrain themselves and
master the art of control.
I think it's a highly
empowering exercise.
-If my friends get
hurt because of it,
then the exercise becomes
stupid and pointless.
DORDONI: Wait a minute.
Are you saying that you're
not doing this for yourself?
You truly believe
there's no point
in being strong or powerful
other than to protect
your friends?
That's so kind, nino.
I think you must be a saint.
And yet, you have a
stronger form, don't you?
I know all about
your Hollowfication.
We're aware of what goes on
in your world of the living,
and all the battles
that you fought there.
You possess a technique that
makes you more like a Hollow,
and experimentally
increases your battle power.
I've seen it!
Now you'll need to use it!
Interesting.
Impressive spiritual pressure.
Still, I told you, I want to
see you release right now.
Show me your full power!
Do it now!
Or I'll force you to, nino!
ICHIGO: You bastard.
-Heh.
What's wrong?
Are you mad, nino?
What are you so upset about?
You're fulfilling
your saintly goal
of protecting your
little friend.
And my goal is simply
to defeat you in battle
when you're at full strength.
It's not a difficult concept.
If I can't get what I
want going after you,
I'll go after that
[spanish] instead.
-Is that so?
Don't you have any shame?
-Of course I do!
I'm ashamed of myself
for not getting
you to fight at full
strength before now!
Any other shame is
meaningless compared
to battling with you, nino.
-All right, then.
Nel, give me a little room.
That's fine.
You'll be safe there, Nel.
Don't worry.
I don't plan on letting any
spiritual pressure get past me.
-Ichigo--
-Let's get started.
-Sorry, but I can only show
it to you for an instant.
-Oh, really?
-Really.
Trust me.
It'll be enough.
[laughter]
-That's more like it!
What powerful
spiritual pressure!
I'm excited by the
prospect of what's to come!
At last, I will
fight a worthy enemy!
Come on!
The time is finally here!
Let the great battle commence!
Now, at full strength, fight!
Fight, nino!
Oh?
What's happened?
What's going on?
-I told you.
Only an instant.
-What a shame.
In my heart, I knew that
once we got the Hogyoku,
the former Espada would in
fact become ineffective.
Totally useless.
And yet I stayed
on with Lord Aizen.
Even knowing all
of that, I stayed.
Still.
[groan]
-Urk!
[shout]
-What the-- what the hell
do you think you're doing?
-Just drooling all
over your face.
-I figured that out myself!
What I want to
know is exactly why
you are drooling
all over my face!
-Quit your moaning, will ya?
I mean, it wasn't
that bad, Don Panini.
-It's Dordoni!
Do I look like a
delicious sandwich to you?
-Nel's drool is
no ordinary drool.
It's got all kinds of
healing properties in it.
Isn't that right?
-Yeah, that's right.
All Nel has to do is this.
-Blech!
-Gah!
Disgusting!
-It's only saliva, silly.
-No way!
That was vomit!
I saw!
-Whenever Nel's uvula gets
squeezed, a lot of saliva
comes out!
-Saliva or vomit!
A real lady doesn't spray
that stuff on someone's face!
-I'm a girl.
-Huh?
-Now, this is vomit.
Urk!
[scream]
-I have lost.
And yet it feels good.
So much power was
running through my being.
I was completely overwhelmed
with an obsession
to defeat you in battle.
I knew I could block
any of your attacks,
and after that, my counter
attacks could finish you off.
I did not let my guard down,
and yet, I never saw it coming.
You are strong, nino.
-I'm not as strong as you think.
DORDONI: I suppose I wanted
to become an Espada again.
-Huh?
-The Espada are Lord Aizen's
most dedicated servants.
But Lord Aizen views
the Espada another way.
He sees them as nothing more
than a tool to fight with.
I know that's how it
is, but still, that
has not changed what I want.
Those who have stood at the
top never forget the view.
I felt so incredibly
alive being up there.
I thought that if I defeated
you when you were at full power,
Lord Aizen would once again
acknowledge my strength,
and I'd be able to
take my rightful place
as a warrior of
the Espada again.
I wanted to force you to
complete your Hollowfication.
I wanted it so badly.
And that has not changed!
[laughter]
-You bastard.
-Are you really surprised?
How could you be foolish
enough to allow someone
to heal your enemy's wounds?
You honestly think
now that I'm restored,
I'm not going to
attack you again?
-That's insane!
You're barely in one
piece, and now you
wanna come back for more?
-Wounds can injure one's
body, but not one's spirit!
As long as my will to
fight remains strong,
my physical wounds
are insignificant!
You're just as sweet
as the chocolate, nino!
[theme music]
GIN: In our next
episode, there's
a stage show for the Quincy
boy that involves whips.
AIZEN: Please make sure I've
got a good seat, and a nice cup
of hot tea.
CIRUCCI: Ah, ha ha ha!
Take that, and that, and that!
URYU: Really!
How can I approve
of a show like this?