[Kugo]
Is your sister okay?
Yeah.
Why'd you come?
Look, don't get
the wrong idea.
Huh?
I didn't come 'cause
I feel like I owe you.
I want my power back
to protect people.
That's all. So let's do it.
Straight to the point, huh?
How did...?
It's my...
That's the symbol of your power, right?
Be sure to keep it safe.
Right.
And now here's your local weather
forecast for tonight and tomorrow.
Rain clouds covering
western Japan are bringing
intermittent showers
to the Shikoku region,
at about a half
an inch per hour.
This cloud cover will
continue in the Shikoku and
Kyushu region through at
least tomorrow evening.
[sigh] As a result, scattered
rain showers will continue
Yuzu, it's midnight.
So you going to bed?
No but you should.
I've got stuff to do.
Like what for instance?
It doesn't matter, but you can't stay
awake all night waiting for Ichigo.
I'll stay up
and handle him.
I'm telling you to go
to bed because you have
to cook in the morning
and go to school.
My staying up's got
nothing to do with Ichigo!
You think all I do
is worry about him!
Hey, it's okay for you
to worry about him.
He has been acting
strange lately,
and it's only natural
to worry when he comes
home so late a bunch
of nights in a row.
I said I'm not worried!
You are too!
I'm not! Now quit it!
What?!
[door opens]
Hnh?!
Huh?
[Ichigo]
I'm home!
- Hey there!
- Ichigo!
Oh wow, you're
both still up!
Uhh...
Get to bed or you'll never
wake up for school tomorrow!
Go on!
[both]
Uh! Sure!
Good night, Ichigo!
For the past week, I have been doing
everything that you asked me to do.
So, can you please explain to me
why the hell I'm back here again?
Even though you complain,
you still came in.
Thanks for that.
Shut up.
Heh. You want your Soul Reaper
powers back, don't you?
That's why I've shown up here.
I thought by now we'd be
starting some kind of
training-type thing at a
much bigger place than this.
[Riruka]
That's half right!
Tonight we're going to start
your training right here!
What're you
staring at?!
Uh. Nothing.
Here's a thought.
Maybe you should stop kicking the
door open when you come in here.
I say that 'cause I don't enjoy having to
see your panties every time you do that.
Really?
Hey Yukio.
What makes you think you have
the right to be such a smart
ass and speak to me in that
manner all of the time?
I bet it's 'cuz you think you
can get away with saying
whatever you want, just
because we have a guest here!
Hey well guess again!
A creepy geek like you
who sits around doing
nothing but playing
video games all day
has no right to talk to me like
he's in any way an equal to me!
Ya got that, big mouth?!
I have never ever, then
or now, thought of you
and myself as equals!
Sorry, I missed that,
could you say that again?
Hnnggh!
Reeeally?
Yukio. What makes
you think you--
You don't have
to repeat it.
Don't touch
me, Jackie!
O-kay, just forget that and begin
explaining that box to Ichigo already.
Stop bugging me! You don't have to
tell me, I'm gonna explain it now!
What're you just standing there for?! Get
over here so I can tell you about this!
Fine, sure. Are you going to tell
me about it by yelling at me?
[gasp]
Wait!!
Stop right there!
That's just fine.
Don't you come
another inch closer!
Hey, Make up
your mind.
See this box?
I see it.
Well?
Well what?
Isn't it cute?!
Huh?
You should
be thrilled!
This cute dollhouse is where you
will be doing your training.
What?
Don't ask questions,
I'll show you it soon!
Show me what?
My Fullbring power.
My Fullbring power is
called "Dollhouse"!
You see, my special ability is that
I'm able to move people or things
into and out of objects that
I love or I think are cute.
Eh?
That heart is your pass.
Okay, now you can go in.
Me, go in there?
Yes, I permit you to.
What're you--??
Oof!
Aagh. That hurt.
Damn! What the
hell just happened?
Hm?!
Hnh?!
You're kidding!
Well? Isn't it cute?
Yeah right, cute my ass!
What the hell is that?!
Defeat him!
What?!
I'm saying, defeat
him by fighting him!
That's your training!
He's not strong, you can
take him, it'll be easy!
If you can use
Fullbring, that is!
What?!
Hwaaaagh!
Yaaaaa!
Hunh?!
Yaaaagh!
Damn!
How pathetic!
Fight him!
Stop running away!
Act like a man!
I AM a man!
but I barely know what's going on and
you expect me to just fight this guy?!
Start by explaining
how I got so small!
Answer me will ya!
How in the hell did I get
shrunk down and end up
stuck in this toy doll
house with an angry pig?!
I told you. That's the power of my
Fullbring. My "Dollhouse" Fullbring.
Fullbring's the power of love.
It's a part of me.
Love?!
It's my ability to draw out the maximum
power from something that I really love.
For instance, a guy like Ginjo really
only likes that pendant of his.
So he turns that into a weapon
he can use when he fights.
But I'm not anything like him!
I have many things that I
love and cherish, and I
look forward to finding
even more things to love!
I'm positive that I'll continue
collecting things that I love,
and my greatest wish is that I'll
die smothered by those things!
My "Dollhouse" Fullbring
has endowed me with the
ability to give permission
to things that I love.
That way I can move them in and
out of my favorite objects!
That's what
just happened.
I gave you permission, inviting
you into my favorite dollhouse,
so you were transported
there and made to fit!
How nice for you.
Okay, that's enough
explaining for now!
I think it's about time
for you to defeat him.
Raaagh!
Why're you freaking out so
much in there? It's simple!
This is put together so
that you'll be able to
defeat him if you're
able to use Fullbring!
Go on,
give it a try!
You're totally nuts!
You're up there talking like
Fullbring is supposed to be
so easy that all I have to do
is try it to make it work!
Raaaagh!
I thought this was
supposed to be a training
program to regain my
Soul Reaper powers?!
Why do you have me trying to use
Fullbring instead of what I know?!
You sure talk a lot!
Stop complaining and just
do as you're told, whiner!
You don't want to
get killed, do you?
Rrrgh! You suck!
Do you even hear yourself?
You sound like a dictator!
Yeeaaaggh!
Well! At least you're
getting better at dodging!
Shut up!
Help me out! At least
give me a clue here!
It's insane for you to
expect me to use Fullbring
without even giving me a
hint about how to use it!
"A hint"?!
All of us were able to use Fullbring
from the moment we were born!
So I wouldn't have any
clues or hints for you!
You must be really stupid or something.
Wake up, stupid!
What a damn mess!
Hey! That's enough
already, kid!
Huh!?
Stop your running away and start
fighting right now! C'mon!!
Huh!?
Wait, that thing
is talking?!!
Of course it talks! Inside of "Mr.
Pork" is this big
scary dude that I abducted
from this neighborhood!
Wait, you abducted
who from where?!?
And did I just hear you say that
this thing's name is Mr. Pork?!
Where's the love in
a name like that?!
Hmph!
You just stay still now
and let me kill you!
Listen! If I don't beat you
to death within 15 minutes,
she told me that this spell I'm
under will become permanent,
and I'll be stuck here for the rest
of my life as a ridiculous plushie!
So he wants to kill me
'cuz you told him a lie!??
My plushie isn't
rediculous!
Ow! Oh! Sorry!
Enough! That's all the advice
you get 'til you're done!
Give me a shout
when you finish.
Hey! Hold on,
that's not fair!!
Too bad!
Hey! Let me out
of here, damn it!
Open the
lid again!
Hey. Think I'll
go have a snack!
Giriko, make me some tea!!
[screaming]
I want a nice hot
tea with milk!
The same kind they serve
over at Henri Dubois!
Will he
survive?
Who knows?
Stop running away!
Let me kill
you already!
Damn! I can't believe she's not letting
me out or giving me some any advice.
She acts like some
mean old witch.
I said stop! Hey!
All of this running
won't get me anywhere.
I've got to think
of something quick!
Fullbring's the power of love!
It's a part of me.
She said "It's the
ability to draw out the
maximum power from
something a person loves"
But it didn't seem to me like Ginjo
"loves" that pendant he wears.
If I had to describe
how he feels about it,
I'd say it was more he
was "attached" to it.
Which means that for me to
be able to use Fullbring,
I need an object that I feel
as attached to, as he does.
There's gotta be something
like that for me.
If you're so worried,
why don't you help him out?
Pfffff!
I! I am not
worried at all!
Fine then.
Hey, I mean come on, if he goes and gets
killed that easily, he wasn't the one!!
Know what I'm sayin?
But Riruka,
are you really sure?
That plushie has
a timer, right?
It's going to be
15 minutes soon.
Thank you so much for doing
the shopping, Mr. Chad.
Sure.
What's that?
[gasp]
This is crazy!
You didn't already start with his
Fullbring training did you?!
What do you
mean "already"?
Well of course I
got him started!
Don't tell me you're
criticizing my methods too?
Graaaaahhh!
Let me kill you!!
Think! There's got
to be something!
[gasp]
Hey!
[Chad]
Ichigo! Your Combat Pass!
Stop that Chad! What the
hell are you doing?!
You have to learn how to use Fullbring
in order to survive this fight, Ichigo,
so your Combat Pass is the
only chance you've got!
Thanks Chad! I was just having
the same exact thought!
[buzz]
[female announcer]
Time is up.
As predetermined earlier,
since use of Fullbring
was not detected within
the 15 minutes allotted,
"Crazy Beast Mode"
will now be activated.
Ah! Please!
Don't do it!
Brrlblblbgghln!
This is... cruel!
Don't!
Huh?! What the
hell's this?
Oh. It appears that the
timer has been activated.
[menacing breathing]
[roar]
Hey!
You didn't tell me he was
going to become that hideous!
Just what were you
thinking, Giriko?!
My, my.
You were the one who requested
my assistance in the training
of Mr. Ichigo, Miss Riruka,
and I did as you asked.
That's true, but...!
You didn't have to
make it so ugly!
there must've been other
ways you could've chosen!
Well. I couldn't think of
any other permutations.
Seriously?!
Riruka!
Huh?
Let Ichigo out of
this box right now!
No, you mustn't.
Huh?
As was the case
with the plushie,
that box possesses a
timer on it as well.
If the organism inside can
survive for 30 minutes,
then said organism will be
allowed to exit the box.
Clear?
And where'd that
condition come from?!
You did leave the conditional
restrictions up to me as well.
Agh!
Removing Mr. Ichigo from the box now
would be a violation of the terms.
If you were to do that, the God
of time will seek retribution.
"God of time"?
I believe that this is the first
mention that I've made of it.
The timer is set in such a way, that in the
event of a breach in its time requirements,
all objects being timed will be immediately
burned away by the Flame of Time,
until there is no trace left
of the offending objects.
You're lying!
Well you can choose
to believe me or not.
[Riruka]
It's not a bluff.
I've seen it
happen many times.
It seems you're
convinced.
But allow me to repeat the
restriction involved in this matter.
If, either Mr. Ichigo or Mr.
Pork are removed from the
box by anyone before another
15 minutes have elapsed,
All three objects involved, by that I
mean Mr. Pork, Mr. Ichigo, and the box,
will be completely consumed
by the Flame of Time.
That, you see, is my Fullbring.
"Time Tells No Lies."
Deactivate it!
Impossible.
Once Time Tells No Lies is set,
even myself, who controls its power,
cannot undo its time parameters.
So a mistake in setting the
terms, can lead to death.
Don't ever take
time so lightly.
Meddling with time is a
frightening proposition
that certainly should be
avoided at all costs.
[ring]
Oh my.
It seems the next pot of
tea is brewed and ready.
Would you care for
another cup, Miss Riruka?
Ah. A wonderful smell.
God and all that is important
dwells in exact time.
[roar]
[growl]
Raaugghhh!
Now what do I do?!
I need to manifest this Fullbring
thing using my Combat Pass.
But how do I do it?
What did he say again?
Our special ability is
to draw out the "soul"
in any object, and to
put that object to use.
So, I have to draw out the
soul of my Combat Pass.
Damn! How am I
going to do that?!
How?!
Use your pride!
Hunh?!
When I first used Brazo
Derecho Del Gigante,
I had pride in my heart.
A whole lot of it.
The material that forms the
basis for my Fullbring
is the skin that I have
on both of my arms!
Your skin?
My skin has always been darker,
because I have Mestizo blood in me!
My appearance, the size
of my body, those things
caused me a lot of rough
times in my life!
But I never lost the pride I had
in my skin's color or in myself!
I was able
to be proud,
because of my Abuelo!
He's the one who gave me the strength
to always have pride in myself!
Think back Ichigo!
Remember those times when you had all
that pride in your Soul Reaper powers!
That Combat Pass will respond to
what you possess in your heart!
Think back to then! Do it!
The moment I was proud of
my Soul Reaper powers?
Think back.
Everything.
I was proud at every moment!
[gasp]
Hnh?!
Ah!
[Mr. Pork] If I lose this fight, I'll be
stuck like this for the rest of my life!
[Ichigo] Relax. You'll
turn back to normal.
[Mr. Pork] I swear that
chick is an evil witch!
I'm going to be stuck
looking like this until I
get a kiss from some lady
who knows true love.
That'll break this spell!
[Ichigo] Good luck
with that, porkface!