[theme music]
-[grunt] Stay away from Uryu.
-I'm afraid that's impossible.
-Why's that?
-Striking at your opponent's
weakness is a given, is it not?
-Huh?
-Besides that, I'm
curious to find out
exactly what a Quincy's
soul tastes like.
-[grunt]
-[gasp]
-Heh.
What's this?
Five on one doesn't seem
very fair, now does it?
-It's fair enough!
Stay back.
Let us handle this guy.
-If that's the case, I shouldn't
hold back, should I, Fried?
-Definitely not.
-[grunt]
-No, I'd prefer it if you
stayed right where you are.
Five on two is better.
Although to be perfectly honest,
it's still not quite even.
-Damn you.
All this talk
about a fair fight.
You acted like there's only
one, but there are two of you.
-I think of Fried and I as
being of one mind and body.
But then again, if we're
being completely fair,
I suppose you'd have to count
your sword, in which case
we need to recalculate
the odds yet again.
-I've had enough
of your nonsense.
-Damn you!
What do you want with her?
That girl's done nothing.
-No need to worry
about the girl.
I have no intention
of killing her.
However, depending
on your actions,
I could make countless incisions
all over her beautiful skin
and let the snake's
venom turn her
into something unrecognizable.
That is a possibility.
-There's absolutely
no way either party
can win in a
situation like this.
The only thing we
can do is give up.
Am I right?
Ah!
-How can you be talking about
giving up at a time like this?
-I'm the one you're after.
So then, give up the
woman and take me instead.
-What are you doing?
Uryu, get back here.
We'll handle this.
-Uryu, don't.
You can't!
-[grunt]
-Don't do this.
-We don't have any other choice.
We can't just stand by while
innocent people get hurt.
You know I'm right, don't you?
-He's not only brave,
he's intelligent.
Now, come over here.
-No.
Let her go first.
-I can't tell you how much
it hurts that you would even
question my integrity.
-No respect.
-[grunt]
ICHIGO: Uryu!
-Stay right where you are.
-Ichigo, when he tries
to eat Uryu's soul,
he'll be distracted, and
we can make our move.
-All right.
-OK.
-[grunt]
-[laughs]
-[groans] Ah!
-You bastard!
-[groans]
-You've always been such
a realist Fried, never
trusting anyone.
FRIED: Heh and you've always
been such an idealist.
-Humans are such delightfully
whimsical creatures.
-Why are you torturing
him like this?
-Isn't eating his
soul enough for you?
-Sometimes I like to play
with my food before I dine.
It makes the meal that
much more enjoyable.
[laughs] Huh?
Fried!
-Huh?
ORIHIME: Uryu!
-It's that woman again.
-What's the deal with her?
UTAGAWA: So, Ms. Yoshino, you
managed to sneak out again?
Don't think this rebellious
behavior of yours
will go unpunished forever.
-Goethe, finish things here.
-Finish things.
Understood.
ICHIGO: Hey, wait!
[grunting]
-[gasp]
ICHIGO: You all right?
-Yeah.
RUKIA: Thank goodness.
At least we saved one person.
-Hm.
-Ririn, where'd that
woman take Uryu?
-That way!
And they haven't
gotten very far yet.
-Let's go!
[gasping]
-Get lost!
I don't have time to
deal with you now.
-I'm in a very
bad mood, and I've
lost patience with you humans.
-Please allow me.
-Go ahead.
Be my guest.
[fighting noises]
-Now, Tsubaki.
Koten Zanshun!
-[grunts]
--[laughs] You haven't
seen anything!
-Damn.
There's no end.
-Kill them all!
Huh?
TESSAI: Looks like we
got here just in time.
-Sorry to keep you waiting,
but it couldn't be helped.
-Blast him, Ururu!
-You got it!
JINTA: Did you get him?
-Damn it.
Looks like he got away.
-Yeah, well, you got
off easy this time.
But you better think twice
before you try-- huh?
What's the matter, Noba?
-You didn't do anything.
-Huh!
-Ririn, can you still
sense that woman?
-Not really.
She's too far away.
-Uryu.
-Hello, is anyone home?
Hm?
Looks like no one's here.
Well, I guess if that's
the case, then I'll just--
KUROTSUCHI: I don't recall
inviting you to come in.
-[groan]
-I'm surprised to find Captain
Kyoraku creeping around,
acting like a common criminal.
-I thought I was acting
like an exceptional thief.
-Why don't you tell me
exactly what you want?
I may not look like it, but
I'm very busy right now.
-I've been doing
a little research,
and there was some data I was
hoping you can provide me with.
-Really?
What sort of data?
-Regarding Bounts.
You must know them.
-Of course I do.
But that's a dusty
old subject that
hasn't been uncovered in ages.
-All the material on
them, which should
be preserved in the
central library,
seems to have disappeared.
So it looks like the only
data that's available
is what you have stored here.
And since it's such
a dusty old subject,
it shouldn't be
a problem, right?
-I decide what's a
problem and what isn't.
Seems to me that as the
captain of another squad,
you're overstepping
your authority
to be here in the first place.
--[sigh] But that's the very
reason I came to see you.
Who better to come
to than the captain
of the Department of
Research and Development,
as well as the greatest
mind in the Soul Society?
Am I right?
-If you want to
access our data, I'm
afraid you'll have to go
through the proper channels
like everyone else.
--[sigh] If I did that, it
could take a good three months.
KUROTSUCHI: That's true.
I know data such as
this might seem trivial.
But you must understand,
if everyone neglected
to go through the
proper channels,
my position would lose
all meaning and authority.
-So, I take it you're
not giving me the data.
-I'm afraid not.
-[sigh] I hope that you burn.
-Huh?
Did you say Something
-No, nothing at all.
Oh, by the way.
I made up that nonsense about
you having the greatest mind.
-Hm?
-There are some nasty
rumors about you, though.
But if you want to find
out more about them,
I'm afraid you'll have to go
through the proper channels.
[laughs]
-Damn!
I can't believe that
rude, arrogant son
of a-- [growl] Nemu, the key.
He thinks he can
talk to me like that?
I'll just delete
the data he wants.
Huh?
What?
What do you mean, access denied?
This is ridiculous!
I never gave that order.
Who could possibly
have done this?
Nemu, get over here.
What's this all about?
I left you in charge
of supervision.
How did this happen?
You're worthless!
-It appears this is more
complicated than I originally
thought.
Damn.
[clock ticking]
[sighing]
-Uryu.
-This sucks.
We can't just sit
here do nothing.
Where's Yoruichi?
-All I know is that she
hasn't come home yet.
-Where is she?
We need her right now.
-We need everyone we can get.
-I'll do what I can.
-[grunt]
-And you can count me in.
-Now, just take it easy.
-What do you mean?
We've got to find Uryu.
-Where exactly do you
plan on finding him?
Do you even know where
to start looking?
-Uh.
If we all split up, we've
at least got a chance.
URAHARA: Wouldn't advise it.
We don't really even know
what their objective is.
If we split up, we might be
doing exactly what he expects.
It's possible he'll come
after whoever's alone,
like the other day.
The dolls that these
Bounts manipulate
possess mysterious powers.
It seems they have
capabilities even
beyond those of our Zanpakutos.
If you're not fully prepared
when you go after them,
look out.
You'll be falling
right into their hands.
[sighing]
[fart]
-Huh?
-[clears throat]
[groaning]
--[laughs] I got you,
I got you, I got you.
[laughs] Boo-boo cushion.
That was great!
You should have seen the look
on your face when you sat down!
Whoa, take it easy.
I was just trying to lighten
the mood a little bit.
That's all.
ICHIGO: Get lost!
-[shout]
-[groans]
Where am I?
[gasp]
What happened?
Why am I still alive?
Did you save me because a soul
tastes better when it's alive?
YOSHINO: You're a
Quincy, aren't you?
-Seems like you're all
interested in that.
Is a Quincy some sort
of delicacy to you?
Do our souls make
your mouth water?
-Well, to be completely honest,
it doesn't smell very tasty.
And now that you've
lost your powers,
it's even less appetizing.
-Guess I should be insulted.
-What happened?
-Huh?
-I'm curious how you
lost your powers.
-When the time came,
I wasn't ready.
I went beyond my capability.
I think that sums it up.
-Is that a common
characteristic with Quincies?
URYU: What?
-This self-pity of yours.
[sigh] Guess I should have
looked for another Quincy.
URYU: There are
no other Quincies.
YOSHINO: Huh?
URYU: It's true.
I'm the last one.
-I see.
There's only you.
That must be a very
lonely feeling.
-[gasp]
URAHARA: I've been
debating whether or not
to tell you this.
The reason we were
initially interested
in researching Bounts is
because of a special substance
we discovered contained in
the residue they created.
It was harmless enough
in small quantities.
But if it became
more concentrated,
our research led
us to believe that
under the right conditions,
this substance could possibly
affect space.
-What do you mean, space?
And what does it do?
-Can you give us
any more details
so we know what we're
dealing with here?
-This substance causes a
reaction in the atmosphere,
forming what can
only be described
as a tunnel connecting two
separate planes of space.
-Well, if that's true,
then that would mean that--
-Quit drawing.
It's just confusing me!
-[sigh] Something like this?
-Uh, yeah, in a way.
But it's a bit more complicated.
You see it connects this
world with Hueco Mundo, which
is the world where
the Hollows dwell.
[gasping]
-But if that happens,
there's no way
of telling how many innocent
humans living in this world
could be sucked into that plane.
-Yes.
But perhaps a more serious
problem is that the Soul
Society has always used the time
it takes for a Hollow to appear
in this world to position
its Soul reapers.
[sigh] If the Hollows have
completely unrestricted passage
from there to here--
-All of the Soul Reapers in
Seireitei couldn't stop them.
URAHARA: Yeah.
With so many
unprotected souls, it
would be a Hollow
feeding frenzy.
Of course, what we're talking
about is only a possibility.
-How much of a possibility?
-Hm.
I'd say about this
much of a chance.
-What?
Only 5%?
URAHARA: Guess again, Ichigo.
-You mean 50%!
-Mhm.
-[gasp]
[knocking]
-I'm sorry to interrupt, but I
just received word from Uryu.
ICHIGO: What!
Where the hell have you been?
-I'm still kind of banged up
from that pounding I took,
so if you could keep
your voice below a roar,
I'd appreciate it.
-But it looks like
you're all right.
-I'm so relieved.
-Hm?
-Don't worry.
I'm not a ghost.
My legs are still there.
-Tell us what happened.
-What do you want to know?
-How the hell did you
even make it back alive?
-The female Bount
who captured me-- she
basically wanted to talk.
YOSHINO: I want you to
be quiet and listen.
If you give me a
chance to explain,
then I won't have to hurt you.
As long as I can
remember, we Bounts
have had a rule that
must never be broken.
We are strictly
forbidden from ever
taking the soul of a
living person, ever.
Do you want to know why?
-Tell me.
YOSHINO: If we
did so, the result
would be that we Bounts
would obtain immense energy,
so much so that it would
cause us to effect space.
URYU: I don't understand.
Effect it in what way?
YOSHINO: For example, we
could pass into the afterlife.
But as I'm sure you
can imagine, that
would completely destroy
the balance of the world.
And the knowledge
of that has been
enough to keep us from ever
attempting it until now.
However, a Bount
has recently emerged
who is trying to do just that.
The name of this
man is Jin Kariya.
-You broke the rule and
attacked live humans, too.
-Yes, but I failed.
I needed more strength
to fight Kariya,
and I knew there
was no other way.
But I realize now that
I was wrong to do so.
There was no justification
for ever breaking the rule.
That means I must
rely on whatever power
I now possess to
defeat Kariya and put
a stop to his twisted plans.
-Why tell me all this?
What's this have to do with me?
-Kariya has targeted
you, and I'm
sure he'll come after you again.
I will do whatever I can
to make sure you survive.
I brought you here
to tell you that.
-But why my soul?
Why me?
-There's a prophecy
about the final outcome,
that it will be
determined by a Quincy.
URYU: After that, I
lost consciousness.
I don't know what happened next.
But when I came to, I was
here in this hospital.
-But why a Quincy, I wonder.
-I never got the chance to ask
her that before I passed out.
-What do you think?
Was she telling the truth?
-It's hard for me
to know for sure.
Who knows?
Hm.
ICHIGO: Uryu?
-Huh?
Oh, sorry.
If it were a lie,
though why would she
bring me to the hospital?
It's hard to believe it's
all some kind of a bad joke.
-At any rate, I've got a feeling
that guy's coming after Uryu.
And we better be ready
when he gets here.
Yeah, you don't have to
worry about a thing, Uryu.
We'll protect you.
-Thanks a lot, you guys.
URAHARA: Well, if we're
going to come up with a plan,
we better get on it.
I'll head back to the shop and
see what I can come up with.
-Yeah, I need to talk to Mr.
Hat and Clogs for a minute.
-You should try to get some
rest while you can, OK?
URYU (VOICEOVER):
It's been so long,
but that face seems so familiar.
-Mommy.
Mommy?
What's the matter, Mommy?
Why are you crying?
URYU (VOICEOVER): Huh.
That's right.
I remember Mom looked like she
might be laughing, yet crying.
UTAGAWA: Are you sure that
letting Yoshino roam around
freely like that is
such a good idea?
Mr. Kariya!
-I can say with
absolute certainty
that Yoshino would
never leave me.
I have taken the
appropriate steps.
[theme music]
RENJI: What happens if we defeat
a doll being used by a Bount?
ICHIGO: I hear Bount dies, too.
RENJI: What weaklings.
Zabimaru's been broken
a bunch of times,
and I'm still kicking.
ICHIGO: Byakuya said they
deduct the cost of repairing it
from your paycheck.
RENJI: So that's why last
month's paycheck was so small!
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers!
GROUP: Golden!
KENPACHI: Everyone stay out.
You-- don't you dare come in.
IKKAKU: How much time
does the captain need?
It's been an hour.
-[groaning] It's no good.
[sigh] I hate this one.
It always takes the longest.
I can't even think of going
out there without my bells.
One more try.
IKKAKU: Three
hours and counting.