[theme music]
-Guys!
What happened?
How are you hurt?
-How should I put this?
It'll Sound strange, I guess,
but we kind of got ambushed.
-An ambush?
-Yeah.
It was.
Tell me who you are!
-We are the Kotei
Academy kendo team,
and we are going
to be victorious
at the regional tournament!
[shouting]
-You're calling that an ambush?
But they told you who they were.
-It was an ambush.
-You've got to be kidding me!
-I ran away, but I was too slow.
-No, it's not your
fault, Shinji.
It's those idiots
who are to blame.
But with the starters being
all banged up like this,
it looks like we've got
no choice but to pull out
of next month's
regional tournament.
-No!
Something this dumb is no
reason for us to give up.
I'll make arrangements
with Kotei Academy
to have a friendly match,
and then we'll destroy them!
-Huh?
-You were ambushed.
I think that it's
obviously they want
you to pull out of
the competition.
Aren't you agnry?
I sure am!
Get revenge at this match, and
come the regional tournament,
you'll have momentum!
-I wish we could.
-But we just got
ambushed yesterday.
[sigh]
-You freshmen look like
you're in good health.
-Huh?
We're not strong enough
to take on Kotei.
-You are completely pathetic!
Are you mice, or are you men?
You're giong to avenge your
upperclassmen no matter
what it takes!
Got it?
-She's completely crazy!
-Mizuho, I brought Ikkaku
and Yumichika here,
just as you ordered.
But who are they?
-We're freshman students.
We're here for the Karakura
High School kendo team.
Pleased to meet you.
It's an honor for us and
Karakura High School.
-OK, Mizuho, so what
do you want with us?
All of a sudden you just
make me put on this outfit.
-Uh, you don't seem
too upset about it.
-Oh, darling, you look
so handsome in it!
You look so heroic
standing there.
-This is bad, Ikkaku.
Now, it's true that I brought
you here, but be warned,
whatever she wants
will benefit her.
That's all.
-Keep your mouth shut!
-Listen, darling.
This very weekend we're
having a friendly match
between our kendo team and
the kendo team for the Kotei
Academy.
And I want you to prepare
them for the event.
-Huh?
Every one of these guys is weak.
MIZUHO: That's right.
I want you to make them
into real men somehow.
-I, uh--
-Hm?
-Um-- can I change
into a real man?
-No way!
Participate in your
youth club activities?
Ikkaku would never do that.
Right, Ikkaku?
-OK.
Count me in.
-You'll really do that?
-I'm in debt to
this strange woman
for giving me food and shelter.
-You're the sweetest man ever!
-I'm not getting involved.
-Yumichika, don't go!
-What an unmanly guy he is.
-But you can handle
it, right, darling?
-We'll depend upon you, sir.
-Yes!
-Good.
You'll find this
training very difficult.
-He really wants to do this.
-That's wonderful!
-But why?
-Come on, wimp!
Come on!
Pull!
You've got to put your
back into it and pull!
-Yes, sir!
I'll do my very best to pull it!
-You wimp!
Come on, come on, come on!
-Yes, sir!
-They're pulling carts?
More importantly,
that sword's for real!
-Come on, come on,
come on, come on!
Climb up, already,
you weaklings!
-Hopping up the stairs
while squatting like that?
Isn't that bad for your back?
-61, 62, 63!
-That's crazy, right?
-I don't know how else to say
it, but this is beyond heavy!
-I think I can endure it!
-That's right!
Real men endure pain!
Beyond that is victory.
-I can't fail!
-Stranger and stranger.
-We're doing it!
Everything's looking super good!
-This is good?
It doesn't even resemble kendo!
-Huh.
-I'm sorry, sis.
I'm sorry, I'm
sorry, but don't you
think the training's
going a little too far?
-Ikkaku won't kill 'em.
Don't worry about it.
Because my darling
has his own ideas!
-That's what I'm afraid of!
-Karakura students, I hope that
you haven't given up already,
men.
[groaning]
-It's all so bad.
-My aching body.
-So you quit?
-I will go on, sir.
-Hmph.
I thought you'd be the
first to give up, Shinji,
but I see that
you've got spirit.
Come on.
-Kya!
Ow!
-So, is that all the
spirit you possess?
-I-- I must work even harder
if I want to become stronger.
For the upperclassmen who
protected me from harm.
I must!
-You can't go charging
straight in like that.
Look for your enemy's openings.
-But I can't find any openings.
-Quit, kid.
Shut up.
We're going to keep going
'til you find an opening.
Come on, come on, come on!
SHINJI: Wah!
IKKAKU: Bring it on!
-Um, incidentally, I
must ask, why are you
working so hard for this?
-You're asking me why?
Well, because it's fun.
Heh.
-Oh.
Sure.
I see.
Because it's fun.
What?
That's it?
'Cause it's fun for you?
-It's been awhile
since I've seen it.
That look of desperation
that comes from one's desire
to get stronger.
-He is majorly wrapped
up in this kendo thing.
-What's wrong with you?
-We're sorry.
-We're beat!
-Thing is, I'd say that
the upperclassmen really
aren't injured this badly.
-Guess I overdid it.
-Oh, no!
Is it true that the team
members have all been hurt?
-Mizuho!
-No!
Whatever will we do, darling?
-I didn't think
that they'd break
from just a little
bit of training.
-I'm sorry.
-This is problematic.
Can the match be won with
those injuries, everyone?
-Absolutely not.
-Uh-huh.
-What?
But what about the match?
-Mizuho?
-Huh?
-Doesn't it make sense if
we just forfeit the match?
-No way!
The student body president
doesn't alter her schedule!
I always win my matches.
Get it?
Besides, we requested
the match, so we'll
look stupid if we forfeit.
We have to do it.
-But didn't you request the
match in the first place
in order to get revenge on them?
Not for the honor of the school?
-Huh?
-Dah!
Fine!
I'll be quiet.
-So you agree, darling?
-It's important, is it?
Then you've just gotta win.
Well, in that case,
my friends and I
can enter the kendo match.
-Your friends?
-I've go some friends who
are pretty skilled when
it comes to fighting.
-My darling!
You're so wonderful!
I knew I could count
on you, my darling!
[squealing]
-Ikkaku, isn't it
true that you really
wanted to enter
from the very start?
-Did you say something?
-Who, me?
No, I didn't say anything!
-All right.
I'm going to ask Yumichika
and the others for some help.
So, who's going to
participate in the match?
Do any of you have
the guts to do it?
-I-- um--
-Hm?
-I will enter, if I may.
No, I am entering.
-Now you're talkin'.
We just need three more.
-That's it?
Two?
Just two friends?
We're short three people.
We need three people
still, you got that?
1, 2, 3!
-Shut up!
Anyway, I'm going to
ask them for their help.
-Hm.
-Yeah?
And what exactly
would we be doing?
-I have an idea of
what it is he wants.
-Good.
That makes explaining easy.
-I want you to participate
in the match that we--
-No.
-Come on!
-There's absolutely
no way I would do it.
-That's right.
There's no way.
-But I'm begging you.
This match is really important.
-It's a shame that I
can't help you out.
-I guess we're the only ones
you can even ask for help.
-So participate, then, will ya?
-No. 'Cause the
protective gear smells.
-It what?
-The protective gear smells!
-Well, that sucks.
-We've just got to keep trying.
-Yeah.
The match is on tomorrow.
-We've got to make
some powerful friends
by then, who really like us.
-I blew it.
It never would've happened if
I had only run away faster.
-Now, if I had to
do it, you'd have
seen me run faster than
a speeding cheetah.
-Idiot!
What the hell's the point?
You never run away.
You make yourself stronger!
And you!
Stop your whimpering!
See where your bruises are?
Go ahead and take a
good look at them.
Those are the bruises of
someone that runs away.
Bruises don't affect men.
They ignore their injuries when
they confront things head on.
Don't worry at all about
the unfilled spots.
-You mean you're going to make
the new friends right now?
-Back off.
-I wonder if we're going to have
enough participating members?
-So, give me one good reason
why I should participate.
IKKAKU: Sorry,
Captain Hitsugaya.
Please accept this.
-Don't try to bribe
me with sweets.
-So, you say that,
but you're already
wearing the protective gear.
-That's because
you made a big fuss
and told me to put it on
without any explanations.
-I'm very sorry, Captain.
But this is a
token of my regret.
-You bastard.
-I'm glad my younger
brother in grade school
had protective gear
that fits you perfectly.
-A grade schooler?
Madarame.
You're going to pay.
-I want to win this match,
and I want to win it bad.
-I warned you that
it was a bad idea
to get yourself involved
in the lives of humans.
-Sorry.
You're right.
-Yeah, you should be sorry.
We're busy here with
training, and it's
a real inconvenience for us.
-Inconvenience?
Then tell me why you're here.
-Well, uh--
actually, Kisuke kept
pestering us to come today.
-Ah, Renji.
And Chad.
We're going to wrap up all
the training for today,
and I want you to go
over to the school.
-Hm?
-Huh?
-Yes.
Something troublesome's arisen,
and you must offer help.
You'll find that
all the other Soul
Reapers will be there as well.
-Why?
Did a Hollow appear?
-You'll know when you get there.
-And then what do
I find, but this?
-It's a shame I'm
taking your time up.
-Did you give Kisuke a box of
sweets just so he'd do this?
You should be ashamed.
-Bribes are always necessary
in this type of situation.
So, anyway, where did Chad go?
-I'm afraid that
he won't be here.
His policy is never to
accept a bribe, because--
-What was that?
Those sweets cost
me an arm and a leg!
-And I don't care what you paid!
-Guys we're still
a member short.
It's almost time for the match.
-Please help us out!
I beg you!
-I won't do it.
I don't want my
hair to be smelly.
-All right, fine.
We can manage.
[yelp]
-But someone has to volunteer.
You will!
-No!
I've never even held
a bamboo sword before!
-It's simple.
All you have to do is run away.
Really simple.
Only three of the five
of us need to win.
[whimper]
-His style can't be matched.
ANNOUNCER: The match between
Karakura High School and Kotei
Academy well now begin.
Because we are having
a friendly match today,
the person who gets the first
point will win the round.
-I'm second to last?
-Don't worry about it.
I'll win even if
you're defeated.
Your match doesn't make
any difference to me.
However, winning is crucial.
-Ah--
-Begin!
-Huah!
-Yay!
-Yeah! 'Atta way, little guy!
-Nice one.
-And you kept saying
that you didn't want to.
-Just shut your mouth.
-Second round
participants, ready!
-Ready.
-Begin!
-Hmph.
I can run away really fast.
Watch!
Ha ha!
Just look!
Catch me if you can!
-How pathetic.
-Check out my fancy footwork.
-What are you, a crab?
-Ha!
-What in the world is
my stupid brother doing?
-Start fighting!
-No way!
If I start fighting,
I might get hurt!
Huh?
Ah!
-Hit.
-A Hollow.
-ANNOUNCER: Begin.
-Yah!
-Ikkaku, don't be late.
-I'm going to have to
leave for a moment.
-Huh?
-We will win.
You see, my opponent will be
defeated, so we can't lose.
You're the one who
wants it most, so fight,
and become a real man.
-Ah?
Huh?
What?
Transforming?
I wonder where he went?
Huh?
-I'm scared.
-I'm going to lay here
on the ground 'til
my master gets back.
"Nyar."
-Huh?
-If you even look at me,
then be prepared to die.
-I'm not gonna leave.
I'll just stay put.
-There's so many men here.
-Have their personalities
all been altered?
ANNOUNCER: Round four
participants, come forward!
-Yes.
[laughing]
-(THINKING) Indeed, even if I
lose, Ikkaku will avenge us.
But, I have to try.
-Begin.
-Zabimaru!
Grow, Haineko!
-Extend, Hozukimaru!
Even though Aizen is using the
hogyoku to create a rankai,
small fries are all that
have been appearing.
I've got to get back there.
Fast!
-Run away!
Run away!
Wait for just the right
moment, then lose him, Shinji!
-Don't be stupid!
Koji's going to get
some divine retribution!
KEIGO: But even if he
loses, Ikkaku will win!
MIZUHO: Shut up!
-I can't go that.
There'd be no point
to this unless I win.
-Shinji, try to be more careful.
-Don't push it so hard.
-(THINKING) Upperclassmen?
I'm going to do is.
I'm going to beat this
guy and become a real man.
-You really are annoying.
-You wait for me, Shinji.
Don't you dare lose
before I get there.
-If they'd been
a little quicker,
they could've gotten away.
But now your teammates will be
shamed, as well as embarrassed.
That's all it took to do you in.
I guess there was no
need to ambush you.
-Damn!
This is for Karakura!
-Shinji!
[grunting]
[cheers]
-All right!
We won!
-We did?
ANNOUNCER: The match between
Karakura High School and Kotei
Academy, Karakura High
School wins 3 to 1.
-Hold on!
Hey, ref.
What happened to my turn?
-Huh?
-Actually, Karakura
has already won.
-There's no need to fight.
We already won.
We won all of it.
But I'll never
forget what you said.
It meant a lot to me.
Thank you for everything
you taught us, Ikkaku.
-Yeah.
It's my pleasure.
-Hey!
I want an opportunity
for a match.
-Karakura High School
won the match 3 to 1,
so you don't have a turn.
-What?
Bring your captain to me!
I want him dead!
-There he is!
This man is Igarashi,
and he's their captain!
-Ah-- sis?
-He's a bad man, and he
dumped me a long time ago!
What a heartbreaker!
[shriek]
-What?
Hey, so your method
of getting revenge
was using us to get even
with your old boyfriend?
Ikkaku!
[shout]
-Hold it!
Just what the hell
do you think you're
doing to our captain's toupe?
-Come on.
I'll scalp every
one of your wienies.
-Aw!
Yes, darling!
-Yah!
ANNOUNCER: Stop!
Stop!
Because of the unruly actions
of Karakura High School captain,
this match is--
MAN: Stupid.
I'm leaving.
ANNOUNCER: Stupid!
Get out!
-Their captain's defeated!
-Darling!
You're amazing!
You really were the
man I thought you were.
[laughter]
[theme music]
RIN: I'm Rin Tsubokura
of the department
of Research and Development.
HANATARO: And I'm
Hanataro of Squad 4.
MAN: You two seem
very much alike.
Are you sibl
BOTH: No. we're not
that alike at all.
MAN: Well, you're in perfect
harmony with each other.