[THEME SONG IN
JAPANESE - D-TECNOLIFE]
-Dammit!
Now where did Ganju run off to?
Ikkaku said the
soul reaper chasing
him was the Fifth Seat
from Squad Eleven.
His name was-- it
was-- it was-- gah!
Well, forget it!
All it means is that
he's the fifth-strongest
from the captain on down.
And all I know is I've
gotta rescue Ganju, 'cause
there's no way he can
beat him on his own!
All I see are these same stupid
walls all over the place!
That's it!
Now I'm really mad!
(SHOUTING) Hey, Ganju!
Where the hell are you?
If you can hear me shoot off
some fireworks to let me know!
-Huh?
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN,
SHOUTING): Dumbass!
(NORMAL VOICE) That's great.
Now I just gave myself away.
-There he is!
Guards!
Here!
Soul reaper!
-You won't get away!
-Let's kill him!
-For the glory of captain
Zaraki, capture him!
-He's getting away!
[all shouting at once]
-Dammit!
Ganju, where the hell are you?
-A hole?
A pit?
Dammit!
Not another one.
How many of these
things are there?
-You could say it's the
last one-- the last one
for you, anyhow.
-You can't be serious!
If you think something like
this will stop me, you're wrong!
Because I know damn
well that you'll never
be able to catch
me, even if I have
to fall into a pit to prove it!
-Hmph.
Well then, be my guest.
Oh, but there's one
thing you should know.
When these pits were
originally dug out
they were lined
with sekkiseki rock,
a stone capable of
neutralizing spiritual powers.
In other words, anyone
who happens to fall in
can never get out again!
[laughing]
I see the damage I inflicted
earlier is still affecting you.
Well, considering the
extent of your wounds,
it's certainly amazing
that you've still
managed to elude
me all this time.
I should commend you
for making it this far,
considering how
perfectly ugly you are.
-You really make me sick,
you self-serving bastard!
-Oh, is that right?
Well, that can't be helped.
It's only natural.
Ugly ones always envy
the beautiful ones.
This proves my point.
[laughing]
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Hey!
-Huh?
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Ganju!
-I guess that's
your comrade who's
been making all that racket.
He's been calling your
name all this time.
GUARDS (OFFSCREEN):
Get back here!
Bow down to your fate now,
you insignificant worm!
-Damn!
Those guys are
awfully persistent!
Ganju!
Hey!
-I'm sure that you're
aware of the fact
that your friend behaves in
the same ugly manner as you do.
Don't you know
these vulgar actions
will result in summoning up
a never-ending horde of soul
reapers?
Good sense-- it seems to
be something both of you
are lacking completely.
GANJU (OFFSCREEN): Now ain't
you the one without good sense.
-Huh?
-There's only one reason
why Ichigo's still here,
and that's because
of the fact that he
must have been able to defeat
your bald-headed partner.
-No, that cannot be right!
It makes no sense!
Squad Eleven is the best combat
unit of all the Thirteen Court
Guard squads!
And Ikkaku was our
third best fighter!
How could he have defeated him?
You bastard!
Your only worthwhile
skill is in taking
advantage of cheap diversions!
-You ain't seen nothin' yet!
Get ready!
Shiba-style Shooting Flower!
Senpen Banka!
-You underestimate me!
Like I said, you
call that skill?
My face-- how dare you do this!
-Maybe now with that little
scar you look more like a man!
-What a shame-- you
have no finesse.
You probably meant to use
one of the strange skills
in your measly arsenal to
collapse the surrounding
ground, and in that
way kill both of us.
-Me, die on purpose
alongside you?
You think I'd throw away
my life trying to kill you?
-Silence!
I have to admit that you
are a tough opponent.
Since our first
encounter, you've
exhausted yourself
running away from me,
while sustaining my attacks.
And yet you can still
move when you need to.
I can only marvel at your
pure physical strength.
-(THINKING) I must be patient.
Wait just a little while longer.
He still underestimates the
true strength of my power.
The only time to use Seppa is
now, while his guard is down.
-Unfortunately for you, to rely
solely on that is regrettable.
If only you had been
born more beautiful.
Your death at my hand
would most certainly
have been my very favorite.
-(THINKING) Can't dodge him!
-What's the matter?
Aren't you able to employ
that floating technique
that you used earlier?
What a pity.
What good is it for one who was
so ugly to persist in living?
I've always thought that
if one was born ugly,
he should at least
die beautifully.
-Well, I don't agree with you.
It comes down to the fact that
our ideas about aesthetics
are completely different.
I was taught the when it
comes to mortal combat,
it doesn't matter if
you're ugly or beautiful.
In the end what matters
is who survives!
-You bastard!
How dare you lay your
ugly hand on my head!
-It helped that you
continue to underestimate me
to the very end.
And it ends now, with a
Shiba-style secret move!
Renkan Seppa Sen!
-Dammit!
You can't finish me
with this puny attack!
Don't make me laugh!
Where are you?
Show yourself!
GANJU (OFFSCREEN): Hey!
Take this!
-What the hell?
-Enjoy!
-Uh?
Guess he's over there.
Well, it's a little
late for that.
Quiet!
-Look there!
They're close!
But, we can't go this way!
It's a dead-end, right?
I thought all along you
shouldn't have turned right
at that last corner!
-But you're the one who
said to come this way!
-Hey, c'mon, Kenny, its not
like you to blame someone else!
See that!
Wasn't I close?
Go over there!
-This way, right?
-Right!
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN):
They're gone, aren't they?
URYU (OFFSCREEN): I think so.
-He seemed terribly strong.
It's lucky he didn't
see us, don't you think?
-Yes, but he must be the
same type as Ichigo--
he has incredible strength
but his powers of observation
are quite weak.
Now, I know that we
should keep moving,
but the real question is,
where do we go from here?
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN):
Well, how about that way?
I can see a tower
in the distance!
-Yeah?
Where is it?
-Look!
Over there!
-Hm.
Didn't touch her.
I'm impressed that you
were able to dodge me
at such close range.
Very good.
If our paths had not
crossed this way,
then perhaps you might
have lived awhile longer.
It's rather unfortunate.
I'll count to ten to give
you some time to regret.
That's the least
I can do for you.
One.
-I sense clashes of spiritual
pressure everywhere.
Now stay alive, young friends.
-One.
Two.
-Uh, thanks for--
JIROBO (OFFSCREEN): Three.
---what you did, Uryu,
but I'm all right really!
JIROBO (OFFSCREEN): Four.
-Yes.
You'll be fine.
JIROBO (OFFSCREEN): Five!
-(THINKING) I believe him.
He's not--
JIROBO (OFFSCREEN): Six!
-(THINKING) --the same Uryu
he was a few minutes ago.
JIROBO (OFFSCREEN): Seven!
-(THINKING) He moved
so quickly just now.
For a split second, Uryu
vanished from my senses.
Then I was safe
before I realized it.
His transformation is
absolutely amazing!
Everything's turning out exactly
like Yoruichi said it would,
Uryu transforming at the
mere sight of a soul reaper.
I'm certain now he's a Quincy.
Soul reapers are
his mortal enemies!
-Ten!
Now it's time for us
to end this charade!
Hope you've had enough time
to reflect on your grief.
-He's coming.
-And so now the time
has come for you
to experience another
form of regret.
-Come on then, soul reaper!
I'm the one you should fight!
-It is not for you to
decide who it is I fight.
Now, allow me the opportunity to
end your regrettable misfortune
with your death.
-Orihime!
You must run!
-(THINKING) No, you're wrong.
I must not run!
I've got to stay and fight!
Otherwise, how
can I save Ichigo?
Tsubaki!
-At last!
Showtime!
Aim well.
-Not this time!
Koten Zanshun, I reject!
Tsubaki!
-You stupid girl!
What were you thinking,
hesitating like that?
-Tsubaki, no!
-I have never seen a
move like that before.
And yet, I sense no murderous
intent behind your attack!
Although you might be able
to kill certain hollows
with that type of
move, I assure you
it will have no effect
whatsoever on soul reapers.
-(THINKING) My body won't move!
-This is a battleground, and
by you not fighting to kill,
you'll never succeed
in stopping anyone!
-If you want to face an
attack with an intent to kill,
then why not fight me?
I'm sure you'll find
it here in my bow.
It's a thrill I'd
love to give you.
-Hanutaro.
-What do you want?
I'm sure you must know that
this is no place for your kind.
-Beat it.
We never sent for
anyone from Squad Four.
-Ah.
It's just that I was the one who
used to clean her cell when she
was held prisoner in
the Squad Six barracks.
And so I got to thinking that
this repentance cell might
be in need of some cleaning too.
-You should know this
repentance cell cannot be opened
for anyone until the prescribed
execution of sentence.
-Even a dumb halfwit
like you must know that.
-Now buzz off!
-Right, but--
-You heard me,
scram, or I'll hack
you pieces, you
insignificant maggot!
-As you command, sir.
-What's wrong?
Scared, ryoka?
You can't get away!
You'll get us a
special promotion!
-I let up for just a
minute, and what happens?
They get cocky and it
goes to their heads.
-All right, men!
Kill him!
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
I'm-- getting-- crushed!
Get off!
Give me some space,
you you bastards!
So I can get the
hell out of here!
-There he goes!
Get him!
-These guys are
freaking everywhere!
How many of them
are there, anyway?
-Ah, very interesting.
So I guess that
makes you a Quincy.
-You're right about that.
-Uryu's bow!
It's totally different
from the one I saw before,
both in its appearance and
even its spiritual pressure!
And that glove-- he must
have been practicing in order
to use it properly!
Learning to use it,
practicing all alone.
-How interesting.
One uses an unfamiliar
skill, the other is a Quincy,
and both employ
projectile weapons.
And you have both come to this
very place at this very time
to fight against me.
So do I call this an
amazing coincidence
or a brilliant twist of fate?
Either way, I must show you
the true form of my Zanpakuto!
Time to spread your wings!
Tsunzakigarasu!
So what do you think?
Time to lament?
I am the Fourth
Seat of Squad Seven.
I'm Jirobo Ikkanzaka, also known
as Jirobo of the Slicing Wind.
My nickname, Windscythe, proves
that I'm the most skilled when
it comes to dealing
with projectile weapons.
See how my countless
blades dance through space?
No one who has seen
my attack has lived.
So tell me, do you
like what you've
seen of my Tsunzakigarasu?
You can't even follow them
with your eyes, can you?
They're a prelude to
your glorious death!
Before my Splitting Crow,
your bows and arrows
are all but as helpless
as a newborn babe.
As a fellow master of flying
weapons, all I can say you'll
truly regret ever having
laid eyes on these--
-Interesting.
Unlike the outside world, in
here, the most skilled fighter
seems unfortunately to be the
one who ends up by circumstance
the most long-winded whiner.
-Absurd!
That was just a fluke!
You're too cocky
for your own good!
-You still don't understand?
If you're supposed to be
the most skilled one dealing
with flying weapons,
then I'd think
about getting a new
nickname, because where
flying weapons are concerned
I seem to be the better man.
Unfortunately, "Uryu Windscythe"
doesn't have as nice a ring
to it.
CAPT. MAIYURI (OFFSCREEN):
You men search over there!
If you find them,
take them alive!
They might make interesting
research specimens.
Don't let the other
squads capture them first.
GUARDS (OFFSCREEN, ALL
TOGETHER): Yes sir!
-Now go!
Still, since they're
only human beings,
I don't really expect
any good specimens.
A hell butterfly?
So tell me the message, Nemu.
-Sir.
Apparently Ikkaku
Madarame of Squad Eleven
has recently encountered
and fought against a ryoka.
-What?
How can you just stand
there and inform me
that Squad Eleven already
has their hands on a ryoka?
-No, apparently Ikkaku was
soundly beaten by the ryoka
and has been taken to the
Squad Four treatment room
1 for medical attention.
Unfortunately, the ryoka escaped
and his current whereabouts
remain unknown.
-An intruder defeated him?
It seems that among
these ryoka there
appears to be quite a
few interesting subjects.
Where's Zaraki?
-He's searching
for the ryoka now.
-Then he shouldn't know
about any of this yet.
In any event, before
he does get wind of it,
let us try to get some
information on these ryoka.
-Tell me sir, where
are you going?
-To see Ikkaku.
Have you not heard
a word I've said?
Come along, my dull-witted girl.
-I sense Zaraki's
spirit pressure.
So, he is on the move.
Be careful, Ichigo.
[THEME SONG IN
JAPANESE - HOKIBOSHI]
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
We're surrounded.
So many soul reapers!
ORIHIME (VOICEOVER): We've
got to find someplace to hide!
KENPACHI (VOICEOVER): We need
a plan to outwit the enemy.
URYU (VOICEOVER): Just blast
him with an attack right
through the middle!
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): OK, you go!
ORIHIME (VOICEOVER): You go!
KENPACHI (VOICEOVER): You go.
URYU (VOICEOVER): Go, Ganju!
-Actually I've got--
uh-- piano practice!