ICHIGO NARRATING: Ever since
the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me, my
whole world has changed.
Now, I'm Ichigo Kurosaki,
Substitute Soul Reaper.
And I'm combining my
powerful spirit energy
with this blade in order
to protect my friends!
[theme music]
YAMAMOTO: Former Squad 5 captain
Sosuke Aizen, former Squad 3
captain Gin Ichimaru, and former
Squad 9 captain Kaname Tosen.
The whereabouts of these
men is still unknown.
According to the report from
the Department of Research
and Development,
the Hogyoku known
to be in Aizen's possession
is still dormant.
It will require
quite a bit of time
before it can be completely
resurrected and used by him.
But here's my conclusion-- that
there is no immediate danger.
However, there is no doubt
these three men still
pose a grave threat
to the Soul Society
as well as to the
world of the living.
Therefore, to deal
with this danger,
I have formed a task force
to hunt down the three
and bring them to justice!
That is all for today.
Dismissed.
-So Old Man Yamamoto has
formed a task force, eh?
-Well, that's what he
calls it, but everyone
knows they're really
just assassins.
Aizen's in trouble.
But he certainly asked for it,
so I don't have any sympathy.
Hey, did you hear about Renji?
They sent him to the town that
the Ryoka Ichigo comes from.
-Yes, it would seem they're
interested in keeping him busy.
-Yeah.
-Why, what is it?
-Well, it's just that I heard
some rumors the other day about
what's been going on there.
And it sounded pretty dicey.
-[gasps]
-(IN UNISON) What?
-[shrieks]
-Orihime!
Ugh!
[grunts]
Damn, we've been
searching all night,
and we haven't even
found a trace of her.
-Yeah.
I don't sense her spiritual
pressure at all anymore.
-If only we knew what
that strange gate was.
-To me, it looked like the gate
straight into the underworld.
-Is there such a thing?
-You've never heard of it?
-Well, I have.
Saw it once before, in fact.
-That wasn't it, though.
There's no way hell would make
off with a living human being.
-I sure hope you're right.
And what the hell
are you doing here
at our school anyway, Renji?
-What do you think?
They gave me responsibility
for this town.
Obviously, if anything
strange happens here,
it's my duty to handle it.
-That's all well
and good, Renji.
But it isn't what he asked you.
We all know why you're
here in town, in general.
He just asked you what you're
doing here at our school.
-And I just explained
it, dumb ass!
-Yeah, and you're still
missing the whole point.
-[growls]
You're not helping!
Both of you, just shut up!
-The thing that
worries me is what
happened with the girls earlier.
-Hey, have you
girls seen Orihime?
-Who?
Orihime?
Is she a new student
or something?
-Oh, very funny.
You know who I'm talking about.
Orihime.
-Well, I sure don't know
anybody by that name.
Are you feeling OK, Ichigo?
-Uh.
-It appears as though
their memory of her
has been completely erased.
-The same thing happened
to everyone back
when Rukia disappeared.
-That's it!
-What's it?
-The fact that someone's gone to
all the trouble of using memory
replacement on these
kids means that they
knew, sooner or later,
we'd come looking for her.
And it also proves Orihime's
disappearance was no accident.
Somebody has kidnapped her.
-All right.
Then I think that we should
go back to Orihime's apartment
and take another look.
There might be some
clues we missed somehow.
-Good idea.
Come on, let's do it.
-Hey, wait!
You mean right now?
I thought you guys were
supposed to be in class.
-Oh, lighten up.
This is more
important than school.
-Ugh.
[doorbell rings]
-Ugh, I guess it's locked.
-I'll take care of that.
-Right, what are
you going to do?
Break it down?
-There is no need.
I can handle this.
-Hey, I think it's
illegal to pick a lock.
-Right now, we have no choice.
At least, it's better than
breaking down the door.
-Instead of jabbering,
why don't you
make sure no one is watching us?
-You know what?
You kind of seem to have
a knack for sneaky jobs
like this, Uryu.
-I don't think that I like
what you're insinuating.
[clicks]
-Hey, you find anything?
[gasps]
-She needs to go
grocery shopping.
-Hey, what the hell do
you think you're doing?
-I hardly had anything
to eat all day today.
Look, I'm starving, all right?
URYU: Hey, look at this.
Orihime had company.
There are two cups.
RENJI: Yeah, but no cookies.
-Why do you have to
keep talking about food?
-Because I'm hungry, obviously!
And your whining about
it only makes it worse.
-You've just emptied
the damn refrigerator!
-And it wasn't
enough to fill me up!
-Shut up!
Would you two remember
why we came here? [grunts]
That strange spiritual pressure
we sensed last night, whoever
it was was invited by Orihime
into this room to have tea.
-It was truly a strange
spiritual pressure.
She knew whoever it was,
and she invited him in.
Who the hell could it have been?
[phone rings]
-Hm?
You have a cellphone?
-It's my soul pager.
-Is it a Hollow?
-No, it looks like
somebody's calling me.
Renji here.
GIRL (ON PAGER): Hello,
can you hear me OK?
-Huh?
Hey, stop!
You guys quit crowding!
-Sh!
GIRL (ON PAGER):
I've got your friend.
She's here with me right now.
-A little girl?
-Ungh!
All right, who is this?
GIRL (ON PAGER): Hm.
That question's no fun.
I don't think I'll
tell you that.
-Why did you kidnap Orihime?
GIRL (ON PAGER): [giggles]
-Tell me why?
-Calm down, Ichigo.
-Oh, right.
GIRL (ON PAGER):
You really shouldn't
break into people's houses when
they're not home, you know.
Maybe I will call the police.
-She's watching us.
There's no one around.
GIRL (ON PAGER): Do you
want to see your friend?
-Of course, we want to see her.
Tell us where she is.
GIRL (ON PAGER): OK.
Let's play a game.
-What game?
GIRL (ON PAGER): You'll see.
And if you boys win, I just
might return your friend
to you.
-Hey!
Damn it, I'm going to--
-Don't let her provoke you.
Calm down.
-Fine.
What do we do then?
GIRL (ON PAGER): Get to
the park down the street
within the next three minutes.
You show up even
one second late,
there's no telling what
might happen to your friend.
Talk to you later!
-Within three minutes?
-So what do we do?
-Our only option right now
is to do what she says.
Whoever this is, she better
not have hurt Orihime.
Renji, it was your
pager she called,
do you know who this person is?
-I have no idea.
It's just a standard issue
soul pager. [panting]
Anyone could have
gotten that number.
-One minute left.
We better hurry.
-All right, then.
-Ugh, nyahaah.
[gasping]
You've been working out?
Looks like you got a little
faster since the last time
I ran with you.
-Hah!
I didn't get any faster.
You just got slower.
-Oh, yeah?
-You think you can keep up?
-Keep up?
Rrrh!
You'll never beat me!
-Ichigo, quit your yelling!
You're acting like a madman.
Everyone's going to think
you've lost your mind!
[all panting]
-We made it in time.
-Hm, there's nobody here.
-Then was it a trick?
-Hey!
We made it here in
under three minutes.
Come on out!
[phone rings]
[footsteps rushing]
-[grunts]
Yeah, hello?
GIRL (ON PHONE):
Congratulations.
You passed the first test!
-What do you mean
the first test?
GIRL (ON PHONE): Are you
ready for the next one?
-What?
We did what you said.
We got here in time.
Now, give us Orihime!
GIRL (ON PHONE): Oh, that
wouldn't be any good, silly.
The game's no fun if
it's over so quickly.
[giggles]
-Damn it, you stupid brat!
GIRL (ON PHONE): Next, I want
you to go to the supermarket.
The one over by the
big shopping mall.
I'll give you three minutes
to get to the phone, OK?
-But that's miles away, we'll
never get there in time!
GIRL (ON PHONE): You'd better!
Or something bad will
happen to your friend.
-Ugh.
Let's go, guys!
[all panting]
-We think we're
going to make it.
[phone rings]
-There's a phone!
-Yeah, hello.
-[grunts]
-Huh?
Haah!
-Give me that phone?
-Yeah, hello?
GIRL (ON PHONE): Aw, too bad.
You failed the test this time.
-What do you mean?
We got here in three
minutes, just like you said!
GIRL (ON PHONE): Sorry!
Someone else answered the phone.
So you lose!
-But you never told us that.
You're changing the rules.
GIRL (ON PHONE): I
must have forgotten.
Too bad.
Guess your friend's
going to die after all.
So long!
-Hey!
Don't hang up!
Hey!
Come back!
Hello?
Hello!
Damn you!
[dial tone]
-Orihime, what do we do now?
Damn, this sucks!
I feel so helpless!
-Just calm down, Ichigo.
-That's right.
The only way to get through
this is to keep a cool head
and think.
-Yeah, but we can't do anything!
She's gone!
[phone rings]
-Ha?
Yeah, hello?
GIRL (ON PHONE):
Ha-ha-ha, I fooled you.
Are you ready for
the third test?
-You damn brat!
When I get my hands on you--
-Ichigo, we've got to
keep her on the line
until we know Orihime is safe.
-All right.
Listen, we need to know
Orihime's not hurt.
Let me hear her voice.
GIRL (ON PHONE):
[giggles] I'll let
you hear her voice if
you pass the third test.
-OK, just hurry up and
tell me what we have to do!
GIRL (ON PHONE): [giggles]
Well, this time--
-No way!
[all panting]
-Hm?
[rumbling]
-Aah!
What are you guys, crazy?
-Hey, where's your phone.
We need to use it right away.
-Yeah.
It's a life-or-death emergency.
MAN: Well, look who's here.
-Welcome, Ichigo and friends.
What's all the excitement about?
Oh, the phone's inside
if you need to use it.
[phone rings]
-Excuse me, I've
got to get that!
-Out of the way!
-Man, what's the big hurry
for a stupid phone call?
-Is that lunch time yet ready?
-Maybe the moocher called in
for a pizza on our account.
-Yeah, I'm here.
GIRL (ON PHONE): Wow!
You made it just in time.
-Yeah, but how did
you get this number?
And where are you
calling from anyway?
-Doesn't that phone
tell you who's--
GIRL (ON PHONE):
Oh, I can't tell--
---calling?
GIRL (ON PHONE): --you that?
-Damn it!
GIRL (ON PHONE): That's
not how the game works.
-Can we trace it?
GIRL (ON PHONE): The mystery
is what's so fun about it.
-I think only the
police can do that.
GIRL (ON PHONE): For 50,000--
-I can record the
call if you think--
GIRL (ON PHONE):
--maybe I'll give you--
---it might help.
GIRL (ON PHONE):
--some hint. [giggles]
OK, I'll tell you what.
Try going back to your friend's
apartment at 8:00 tonight.
Who knows?
You might find her there.
-Then why should we
wait until tonight?
Why can't you
bring her back now?
GIRL (ON PHONE): My, my,
you're such an impatient boy!
-Hey, you at least,
let me hear her voice!
GIRL (ON PHONE): [giggles]
Tonight.
See you!
-No, don't hang up!
Hello?
Hello!
-What's all the racket in here?
Are you having a party?
GIRL (ON TAPE): My, my,
you're such an impatient boy.
ICHIGO (ON TAPE): Hey, at
least, let me hear a voice!
GIRL (ON TAPE): [giggles]
Tonight.
See you!
-Hm, it certainly does sound
like a kidnapping, doesn't it?
-Of course, it is.
What else could it be?
-And I seriously doubt
that whoever is behind this
is going to just give
Orihime back tonight.
I'm sure that it's a trap.
-The fact that she knew the
number to call here at the shop
also means it's not an ordinary
person we're dealing with.
-So she's a Soul Reaper?
-I didn't say that.
I just don't think there's
enough information for us
to act upon.
-Tell me what you think.
-I have to agree with Yoruichi.
We don't have
enough to go on yet.
-There must be something
you can do to help us out.
-Ah, I suppose I can try.
Don't expect too much,
though, because I haven't
done this kind of work
before, so I don't really
know what I'm doing.
-All right.
Thanks a lot.
-So 8 o'clock tonight, right?
-Yeah, I'll see you there.
We're going to get Orihime back.
And then I'll make them pay.
-All right, then.
-8 o'clock sounds good.
-Wait, you aren't going
with them, are you?
-No, but if they're going out,
that means Renji won't be here,
so we don't have to cook
dinner for the moocher.
-[groans]
-Renji!
-How pathetic.
-Hm.
[dog barks]
-Any signs of life inside?
-No, nothing yet.
And by the way, how come you're
not wearing that cape of yours?
-Um, well, I had to
take it to the cleaners.
-Your cape is dry clean only?
You serious?
-Yeah, so what's wrong
with looking good?
[static noise]
-What the hell?
That's Orihime's window!
Damn, it's still locked!
-You want me to
pick the lock again?
-No, there's no time for that.
We've got to get
in there right now.
Come on, Chad, break
this door down.
-Right.
-What's going on, guys?
-Orihime?
-Did she bring you back
like she said she would?
-I'm not sure what
you're talking about.
-You aren't hurt, are you?
-Huh?
Hurt by what?
-Orihime, you were kidnapped
by someone last night.
-Huh?
I was what?
He-he, no way!
-So you don't remember
a thing about it.
-Orihime, I want you to
think back to last night.
What was the last thing
that happened to you?
-Hm, well, I have
to think about that.
The first thing
that happened was
school since the new
semester started today.
I remember seeing
all my friends.
And after that, Tatsuki
and I got ice cream
and gave ourselves headaches
from eating them too fast.
Then I went home
and did my homework.
And after that, had
dinner and went to bed.
-But the new semester
started yesterday, Orihime.
-Huh?
-They erased her memory, too.
She lost a day.
-Well, at least,
they didn't hurt her.
She's OK.
-But whoever did
this is still around.
-So we'll stick around,
too, and keep our eyes open.
GIRL (ON TAPE): OK,
I'll tell you what.
Try going back to your friend's
apartment at 8:00 tonight.
Who knows?
You might find her there.
-Hm.
-What is it?
Did you find something?
-No, I ran the voice of the
analyzer twice, but no reading.
This voice has no reimon.
-No reimon?
-The equivalent of a hand
with no fingerprints.
Unusual.
-Very unusual, indeed.
-Excuse me, Master.
-Hm?
-What is it, Tessai?
-That cloud.
-Huh?
I've never seen a
cloud quite like that.
-Could it be a
Menos approaching?
-No, a Menos cloud is
somewhat different.
-Whatever it is, it's bad.
-Hm.
-Nothing's happening.
-Shall I make us some tea?
-Wait a minute.
Something's coming.
Huh?
[rumbling]
[gasping]
-What the hell is this?
-Stay away from the
windows, everyone.
It's not safe!
-[grunts]
I can't get the door open!
-Hey, what are you doing?
-[grunts]
Let go, Orihime.
-[snickers]
-Orihime, what are you doing?
Let him go!
-What do you think?
I'm killing him.
-You monster!
You're not Orihime!
Who the hell are you?
-Uhh, can't breathe.
-Chad, you shake her off!
Can't you just tear
her arms away from you?
-[grunts]
Aaagh!
-Chad!
-Come on!
-No, you can't use
your Zanpakuto!
That is Orihime's body
they're possessing!
-[snickers]
-[coughs]
[sinister laughter]
-Eugh, what the hell?
-It's about time you showed
your face, you bastard!
You're the one who called us!
-Oh, that's just ignorant.
Did you really think
that little voice
could come out of
someone like me?
I'm Kurodo.
And I've been looking forward
to this for some time.
And there's someone else.
-Pleased to meet you.
-Renji!
-[growls]
[both snicker]
[grunts]
-We'll be taking
this one with us.
-Uuhh, aaah!
-Chad, no!
Ugh!
[girl giggling]
-That stupid kid!
But where?
[girl giggling]
-I'm right here!
[giggles]
Hi there, boys!
-Who the hell are you?
What's this is all about?
-Ha-ha, my name is Ririn.
Nice to meet you, too.
-What do you want?
Why are you doing this?
-Hah, do you like my game?
[giggles]
-All right, that does it!
-I don't think I can
kill a kid, though.
How about I take out the
clown on the left side.
-And I'll take care of
the one wearing the hat.
Uryu, you go after
the kid, got it?
-[growls]
-Aw, such silly boys!
-Ugh, uagh!
-[giggles]
Pop!
-Agh!
RIRIN: I'll see you
later, boys! [giggles]
-Ugh!
Damn it!
-What the hell is going on here?
[theme music]
RENJI: I'm telling
you, there's got
be something wrong
with my Gigai.
I can never get out
of it quick enough.
-You want me to lend
you my Soul Candy?
RENJI: Oh, wow, thanks.
That would be great!
Uh, let's see yours was, uh--
-Hey, did you want
something from me?
-I changed my mind.
I don't want to get stupid.
-Wait a minute!
[theme music]
-Illustrated guide
to Soul Reapers.
KIDS: Golden!
-[snickers]
Can't make a sound.
Hm.
[snickers]
Ugh!
[groans]
-[snickers]
-That was really just too easy.