[theme music]
-NARRATOR: Shusuke Amagai
was named captain of Squad 3,
which had been
without a commander
ever since Aizen's rebellion.
Izuru Kira organized
a party to help
Squad 3 get to know their new
captain, who they're still
a little unsure of.
Unfortunately, the
party came to an end
when their new leader
couldn't handle his liquor.
Just then, an alarm
sounded that Menos
had infiltrated the Precipice
World, and the squad sprung
into action, leaving
their captain behind.
But the restrictive
current, which
should have been
quarantined, was
released, putting
the squad in peril.
Suddenly, Captain
Amagai awakened
from his drunken stupor,
and with impressive power,
saved the men under
his new command.
-We're early.
Sunrise is still
a few hours away.
The items I arranged
for haven't arrived yet.
We'll have to wait here
for the time being.
-I am hungry.
MAN: That's the last of it.
MAN: All right.
-Ichigo!
Morning.
Uh oh.
Whoa!
-Another morning
with a headache.
Why can't I trade that old
man in for an alarm clock?
-Don't talk about your
father like that, Ichigo.
It's disrespectful.
-Shut up.
-Hey, Ichigo.
Did you know that
Ms. Hosaka moved out?
-Yeah, I saw the truck leave.
-She came over to say
goodbye yesterday,
and looked like she was in
a real hurry to leave, too.
I wonder why.
-My guess?
She got tired of her neighbor
jumping through windows
every morning.
-Nothing is further
from the truth.
She respects me.
(HIGH PITCHED) Before
I leave, Mr. Korusaki,
I just want to say one thing.
You're a great father.
See?
I relate to my children.
-You mean you're
chilish and immature.
-Sticks and stones
may break my bones,
but not like I'm gonna break
yours if you keep this up.
Oh, the glass stuck in
my butt just went deeper.
ICHIGO: Thanks for breakfast.
-Are you all right?
ICHIGO: Let's go, Rukia.
-Ichigo!
Why'd you step aside?
-Habit.
From living with my father.
-You could've slowed me down
with a clothesline, like this.
Hi Chad.
-You all right?
-If that's your attempt at an
apology, I graciously accept.
Hey, don't leave me.
TATSUKI: Ichigo!
Oh, sorry.
-Hey, Tatsuki.
-Nice impersonation
of a pretzel.
-Salted?
-Why not?
-Ichigo, Tatsuki.
Morning.
-Hey.
-Looks like there's a
meeting going on here.
-I was showing my homework.
I think I've gotten
better in art class.
Look.
Ta-da.
It's a tyrannosaurus doing yoga.
-Oh, yeah.
Of course.
-Oh!
That is so avant garde.
-Is that the only
thing you think about?
-Show us what you drew, Rukia.
-This.
-Huh?
-Aw, they're cute
bunnies doing yoga.
That's so cute.
RUKIA: Yours is even
better, Orihime.
ORIHIME: Thanks.
[phone beeping]
-Rukia.
-Don't worry.
Its business as usual.
Ichigo?
-I guess so.
Be right back.
-What's going on?
-RUKIA: What is this?
-What's wrong?
-The number of Hollows
are steadily increasing.
30.
No, 50.
-You're kidding.
How can that be?
-I don't know.
Let's splut up and deal
with them separately.
[gurgling]
-I'm hungry.
-I have discovered what
the world of the living
calls a convenience store.
-Oh, is that so?
Quick.
Let me have something to eat.
-Well, the thing is--
-Come now, give.
I promise I won't be picky.
Hurry, I'm starved.
-The Gigai haven't arrived yet.
I couldn't buy anything.
-What?
-I'm terribly sorry.
I've contacted the dealer.
It shouldn't be too much longer.
-Argh!
No.
I will not wait any longer.
-You mustn't.
You need this veil to suppress
your spiritual pressure.
If your presence in the world
of the living is discovered,
it will be disastrous.
-But--
-Please bear it a bit longer.
The Gigai I've arranged for has
a spiritual pressure cloaking
function.
But, that aside, Enryu is
preparing valuable tests
as we speak.
From here on out, it's important
that you do not leave my side.
Huh?
Gah!
-That Kenryu is so frustrating.
I will just have to find
something to eat on my own.
[screeching]
-Huh?
Who's that?
-How many of these Hollows
are there anyway, dam it.
RURICHIYO: Over there.
Over here.
-Huh?
Excuse me.
Are you the Soul
Reaper of this town?
RURICHIYO: A soul?
Unless you want
to be eaten, you'd
better get the hell
out of here now.
-No.
I am the one who wants to eat.
-You do?
Who are you?
-That is not important.
What is important is--
-Hey.
You OK?
-Argh!
I hate this veil.
-Where are you from?
Who are you?
-Uh, ahem.
-Uh.
-Well, come on.
What are you waiting for?
-I don't know.
-You are supposed to help me up.
-Oh.
-Now, you are about to
bring me something to eat.
And be quick about it.
I am starving.
[screeching]
-Hey!
Did you hear me?
-Stay back.
-Argh.
I said I want food now!
-Huh?
-It can't be helped.
Just find her quickly.
We can't let anything
happen to Lady Rurichiyo.
By the way, you brough too many.
-Don't you understand
what I mean
when I say that I am hungry?
-I'm beginning to get the idea.
-Food, food, food!
Hungry, hungry, hungry,
food, hungry, hungry!
-Stop!
Will you please let go of me?
MAN: Lady Rurichiyo!
-Ah!
-Hey!
-Take care of them.
-Huh?
[roar]
-Oh, no, Kenryu!
That Soul Reaper
has just been eaten!
-Yes.
It is his duty to protect
you, Lady Rurichiyo.
We must get you to safety.
-But he-- huh?
ICHIGO: Bankai!
Tensa Zangetsu.
-Who is that?
Is he a Soul Reaper?
-No.
He's a substitute.
Ichigo Kurosaki.
-You're in my way!
Argh!
-Ichigo.
-Rukia?
-Why are you using
your Bankai and raising
your spiritual
pressure so recklessly?
-But those guys
down there-- huh?
-What's the matter?
-There were two strange Soul
Reapers down there, and a kid.
Where'd they disappear to?
-Don't worry about them.
We have to take care
of these guys first.
-Here we go again.
-Ichigo!
-Why are they here?
-It's starting to become
embarrassing that you still
can't control your
spiritual pressure.
-Let's make this quick.
We have to get back before
our next class starts.
-Thanks for helping out.
Those arrows are
handy for wiping out
large numbers of Hollows.
They're like a pesticide.
-I didn't come all this way just
to be insulted by you, Ichigo.
There were spiritual pressure
that I didn't recognize.
-Yeah.
I saw them, but just
for a few minutes.
-It seemed they used
some sort of bait
to lure those Hollows here.
-Hollow bait?
-Was it anything like that
kind of bait you used before?
-The composition's
probably different,
but the potency's the same.
-Did anybody see which
direction they went?
-No.
They disappeared.
-What were they
here for, anyway?
[beeping]
-Wow.
A princess?
-Ichigo said she spoke to
him like a princess, anyway.
-That's right.
-A princess.
-I mean, she was
bossy like a princess,
but not very lady like.
She kept screaming
about being hungry,
and ordered to me to feed her.
-Sounds like she
was patronizing you.
-A princess who'd make
Ichigo look silly.
Wait.
I got it.
Did she wear a revealing
black leather outfit,
with spiky black patent leather
boots, with lots of weapons?
And did she say something
like, who's hungry?
Me, that's who.
Like that?
-Orihime, that doesn't
sound like a princess.
It sounds like a dominatrix.
ICHIGO: This conversation
is ridiculous.
What are you fooling
with over there, Rukia?
-This?
I'm researching those two
Soul Reapers and the princess
you saw, but so far no luck.
[beeping]
-OK, enough already!
That beeping is so
damn irritating!
-You're pretty
irritating, yourself.
Soul Reapers have to pass
through the Senkaimon
to enter the world
of the living,
so there should be a record
of all such passages,
which I can access.
Argh.
This manual is so hard to read.
-Leave it to me, sister.
There hasn't been a manual
written yet that I can't read.
I happen to be known as the
world's number one manual
reader.
-What?
No way.
-Shut up.
I was created by the department
of research and development,
so don't take me lightly.
-OK.
Give it a try.
-My please.
I'm finally back in heaven.
RUKIA: Hey.
-Huh?
-Well?
-Heh, heh.
Oh, yeah.
Right.
Hm?
Mm.
I don't know.
[groan]
-Hey.
Ichigo!
-Huh?
Now what?
-They're moving.
-The neighbor already moved out.
The truck left this morning.
-Moving in, not out.
A Gigai's moving in.
-Huh?
-Be careful with those boxes.
They're fragile.
ICHIGO: That guy!
-Wait for me.
-Please just put all
of the furniture right
in the middle of
the living room.
I'll arrange it
all myself later.
-Hey!
Hey, you.
-Well, Well.
If it isn't the little low
life from the other day.
What do you want?
-Don't give me that.
Who the hell are you guys?
-I'm not obligated to answer
any of your questions.
-What was that?
You're the one responsible for
luring all those Hollows here,
aren't you?
-Not me.
In fact, I have no idea what
you're even talking about.
-Don't kid around.
RURICHIYO: Ichigo!
-Huh?
-It is Ichigo.
Good of you to come.
Thank you for offering
your greetings.
-Is that the princess?
-Yeah.
Hey, wait a minute!
I never told you my name.
How did you know it?
-Ever hear of a little
thing called research?
-Look, you--
-Insolent fool.
Isn't it obvious that there
is a whole world of difference
separating us and
the likes of you?
-Huh?
-If I have further use for
you, you'll be contacted.
Lady Rurichiyo, it
will be dark soon.
-Huh?
-Hollows, like those from
earlier today, may appear.
Please return to the
mansion immediately.
-Very well.
I guess that's for the best.
See you again, Ichigo!
-His name should be Byakuya.
-My brother's not like him.
-Hey!
I'm not don't
talking to you yet.
-Ah!
Gah!
Hey, you!
Don't you put up
a barrier on me!
Hey!
I'm talking to you!
Damn him.
-Don't exhaust yourself.
We don't know who he is, but
his Bakudo sure is impressive.
I've got to get going.
-No, don't go without me!
Please, wait!
Take me with you!
-Quiet!
We're outside!
-No!
I can't tell you that.
No!
Trade secret.
Sorry.
I can't tell you.
-I already know it's true.
Admit it, that we definitely
a Gigai from your place.
-As I said, it's a trade secret.
I cannot answer you.
[groan]
-Tea?
-If we can't tell you,
we can't tell you.
There.
After all, we're the ones
who'll get scolded by the boss.
-Where's Urahara, then?
I'll ask him.
-I'm not sure where he went.
He's been gone for
the past few days.
But I'll be sure to tell him you
stopped by for a little chat.
Let's go, Ururu.
-Wait for me, Jinta.
-Hey, Ichigo!
Those guys are all
done moving in.
Huh?
What are you waiting for?
Aren't you going?
-Naw.
-What do you mean?
This might be your only chance.
If you change into a Soul
Reaper, you can go down there
and break the barrier.
-Naw, it's OK.
-I can't believe this!
Do you know how much time
I've wasted keeping watch?
You sick, or something?
YUZU: Ichigo!
Dinner time!
-Ah!
Hey!
-Cam down.
I said it's all right.
-So you're telling me that
all that worrying I did
was for nothing?
It's dark!
KENRYU: Lady Rurichiyo?
Lady--
Shh.
Lady Rurichiyo is asleep.
Don't start crying just because
you were late with her meal.
I wouldn't worry about it.
Enryu.
You saw it today,
too, didn't you?
Substitute Soul Reaper
Ichigo Kurosaki.
His skill and power are genuine.
I'm sure he'll be able
to go up against them.
Coming to the
world of the living
was the best choice, after all.
-What?
The princess moved in next door?
Did you get to see
her too, Rukia?
-Yes, but I couldn't
get close to her
because she had
these two bodyguards.
-Oh.
She has bodyguards, too?
She's the real deal.
-So then, did you
find out anything?
-Naw.
They put up a barrier, and
haven't come out since.
-And you're just sitting
here doing nothing.
-Uryu?
You're here?
-You continue to amaze me.
-They're up to something.
That much is pretty
damn obvious.
Sooner or later, they're
going to come meddling.
-OK, take your seats, everyone.
All the students
are present today.
Good.
First I have an
exciting announcement.
We have new transfer
students joining us today.
And get this, there's
three of them.
Well, come on in, please.
-Huh.
-What is that?
-A giant?
-That girl has to
be in grade school.
-Two adults and a child?
-I am Kenryu.
On my left is Enryu.
And so my right,
let me present--
-Ahem.
I am Rurichiyo Kasumioji.
Pleased to meet you!
-Huh?
[theme music]
ICHIGO: Was it
Kisuke who arranged
for those guys to
move next door to me?
TESSAI: That is a trade secret.
ICHIGO: Who arranged
the school transfer?
TESSAI: Trade secret.
ICHIGO: And why is Rurichiyo's
uniform so loose on her?
TESSAI: Blame that
on the boss's taste.
ICHIGO: He has really
hardcore taste.