[theme music]
NARRATOR: In order
to save Orihime,
who was kidnapped by Sosuke
Aizen, Ichigo and his friend
snuck into Hueco
Mundo and infiltrated
Aizen's fortress,
known as Los Noches.
Upon entering the fortress,
they were engaged in battle
by some of Aizen's
most deadly Arrancars.
Renji was confronted
by Szayelaporro Granz
and soon found himself
in serious trouble.
Uryu arrived to
help but discovered
that his opponent was already
several steps ahead of him.
-I've just been toying with
you because I've already
finished analyzing all of
your strengths and weaknesses.
You're done, Quincy.
-Yaaaa!
-Don't stand around
doing nothing!
Find some way to defeat him!
NARRATOR: Renji
and Uryu realized
they would have to team up to
take on the powerful Espada
and came up with a plan
designed to catch him off guard.
-Even if the difference
in our powers is great,
you're going to
find it pretty damn
painful if you get
hit point blank.
Hado 31 Shakkaho!
-Exactly as planned.
Esta terminado.
It's over.
Szayelaporro Granz.
[music playing]
-Ahhhhhhh!
-Damn you!
-You survived our attack.
How is it possible that
you're still standing up?
[music playing]
-Ahh!
-Hold on!
Where are you going?
-Where am I going?
I'm going to change my clothes.
Put yourself in my
shoes for a second.
Do you expect me to fight
in this ragged attire?
NARRATOR: Meanwhile Orihime
was taken by Grimmjow
to heal Ichigo who had
been wounded in his battle
with one of Aizen's most
lethal Espada, Ulquiorra.
ORIHIME (VOICEOVER):
There's an incredible amount
of spirit energy swirling
around Ichigo's wounds.
I can't reject it.
Who would do such a thing?
-It was Ulquiorra.
I'm going to teach him something
about the nature of punishment,
punishment for daring to
take somebody else's prey!
[music playing]
-Are you all right, Renji?
-Ahh!
-What is it?
What's wrong?
Are you injured?
Do you need mouth-to-mouth?
-Ahh!
You're way too close!
I told you before,
when you sneak up on me
and get in my face
like that, it feels
like I'm going to
have a heart attack.
-That's a terrible thing to say.
I was worried about you,
and I was trying to help!
-In the future, help
me from further away.
-Fine!
-Hmm.
Those two should
be on television.
But now it's our turn to shine.
Let's show 'em
our best material.
What do you say, Uryu?
Huh?
Uryu, where did you do?
A comedy team doesn't work if
there's only one guy on stage!
-Stop shouting.
You're so loud the wax in
my ears is starting to melt.
-Oh, that's good.
Now I pretend I can't hear you.
How about this?
What's that you say?
They taxed the deer
when you sold the pelt?
-You don't feel Szayelaporro's
spiritual pressure either,
do you?
-I've lost him completely.
You really think he went
to change his clothes?
-Probably.
How do you feel about
getting out of here?
-Fine.
It makes sense to me.
-How about this?
You say your pants
slipped in the rear--
-And you need a belt.
-Now that's comedy!
-You two Belong in
a mental hospital.
-We're going to make a
run for it while we still
have the chance.
[music playing]
-Ulquiorra.
-What's going on here?
What are you doing?
It seems like a simple question.
Perhaps I need to rephrase it.
Why are you healing an
enemy I already defeated?
-Hm!
-You refuse to answer?
[music playing]
-Fine.
Have it your way.
Regardless, the bottom
line is Lord Aizen
has entrusted that
girl to my care.
Hand her over.
-I don't think I will.
-What did you say?
-You heard me, but just so
you're clear about my position
here, let me demonstrate!
Don't think I don't know what's
going on with you, Ulquiorra.
You're scared of fighting me.
You're afraid you'll
lose and be crushed!
-Hah!
You deflected that one.
How many will it take
before I get you?
[music playing]
-Damn it.
-What did you just do up there?
-Aizen gave each one
of the Espada something
called the Caja
de Negacion which
we can use to
punish subordinates.
I used mine just now.
-Caja de Negacion?
-It's a powerful tool that
can permanently seal away
the victim into
another dimension.
But its power is limited.
It's not made to be
used against Espada.
Considering the strength
of his spiritual pressure,
we've got two or three
hours before he breaks free.
There's no time to waste.
Come on, hurry up
and heal your friend!
-I won't.
-Perhaps you didn't hear what I
said, but it wasn't a request.
Get to work!
-I refuse.
If I heal Ichigo,
you'll just turn around
and hurt him some more.
I won't do it!
-You damn tramp!
-[gasping]
-Huh.
-Let go of her.
-Ichi--
-Orihime.
Please, heal me.
I'm asking you to
heal my wounds.
And I want you to
heal his as well.
-Listen, kid, you'll find
that's a big mistake.
I don't need your pity.
-Oh, it's not pity.
I assume you want us both to
fight at our full strength,
right?
Or am I mistaken?
Do you plan to use your
injuries as an excuse
when you finally lose?
[music playing]
-All right, then, bring it on.
Let's have a fight to the death!
-Sounds good to me.
[music playing]
-Come on, now.
Don't look at me that.
I'll be all right.
-But Ichigo-- Ichigo!
-The same goes for you, Orihime.
Trust me, I'll win.
-[sniffling] Ichigo!
-Let's take this battle
elsewhere, Grimmjow.
-Fine with me.
-Be careful, Ichigo.
[music playing]
-Are you ready?
-Ichigo!
Ichigo!
[sobbing]
-It'll be all right.
Ichigo will win the battle.
-But you don't really
know that for sure.
-But I do.
He said trust me, I'll win.
-Everyone says things like
that even if they're not sure.
There's no guarantee.
You can't tell anything
from those words.
-You think so?
-Absolutely!
Ichigo's probably scare.
People always say that kind
of stuff when they're scared.
-Ichigo wouldn't do that.
-Huh?
-He would never say he's going
to win because he's afraid,
and he wouldn't say it
to try to fool himself,
I can guarantee you that.
Ichigo is a very focused person.
Whenever he tells you
something this important,
he says it like he's
swearing an oath.
He did that when he
appeared before me
as a Soul Reaper
for the first time.
-If you want
Orihime, then you're
going to have to get
through me first!
ORIHIME (VOICEOVER):
The same thing
happened when he went to the
Soul Society to save Rukia.
-I guess we'll just
have to win, then.
-He's always been like that.
He does it to reassure us,
but more than that, he's
making a promise to himself.
He makes a promise to
himself, and then he
recites it out loud so
it will become a reality.
So he'll be all right.
If Ichigo says
he's going to win,
you can believe that's
precisely what he'll do.
-You mean it?
-Um-hum.
We just have to have faith.
So we'll wait here
and believe that he'll
come back to us very soon.
[music playing]
-Getsuga!
-[laughing] Nice!
I've been waiting a long
time for this, the chance
to crush you while
you're at full strength.
And you feel the same way,
don't you, Ichigo Kurosaki?
-You're wrong.
I didn't come here to take
you on so I can crush you.
-Don't give me
that pathetic lie!
Now say it.
Say that you can't
wait to get hold of me
and rip me apart for tearing
up that friend of yours.
The truth is you want
to kill me, don't you?
-Which one of you
is the strongest?
Who's going to take me on?
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): Retreat!
Ichigo, get out of here!
Run!
-No!
Rukia!
-Now I get my revenge.
You'll understand why I
kept this scar on my chest
to remind me of my humiliation.
-Getsuga Tensho!
-Let's get started.
I'm going to choke
the life out of you
and finally prove which
one of us is stronger!
What now, you little weakling?
After all this, you still don't
look like you want to kill me.
You're so pathetic.
-Is that right?
-I have a question for you.
Why did you bother coming
here in the first place?
-Are you some kind
of idiot, Grimmjow?
I came here to rescue Orihime.
-Hah!
Oh, really?
Well, if that's true, then
why didn't you grab the girl
and run the moment you saw her?
Tell me, were you relieved
to see that she was unhurt,
or at least appeared
to be on the surface?
Were you born naive or did
you just grow up that way?
-You bastards!
What did you guys do to Orihime?
-Good.
That's more like it, Ichigo!
You said you came here
to save that girl, right?
Let me enlighten you since
you don't seem to get it.
You're wrong.
The only reason why you
came here is to fight.
Come on, Ichigo.
Are you even aware
of the path to which
your instincts have led you?
You're a Soul Reaper.
I'm on Hollow.
The loser of this battle
will be slaughtered.
It's been that way
for over 1,000 years.
That's all the reason you
need to fight, got it?
So come on!
It's pure and simple.
The last one standing
gets to live!
[music playing]
-You've got a nice, murderous
look in your eyes now,
but that's not good enough!
You're not at the
level yet where
I want this battle
to take place.
This is the ultimate Cero
which only the Espada can use!
ICHIGO: Orihime--
Hold on!
Don't release it!
-Gran Rey Cero!
[music playing]
-Ichigo.
Ichigo!
-Well, it's about time.
[theme music]
GRIMMJOW: Nice, Ichigo.
Know it's my turn.
Grind!
But before I do that--
ICHIGO: What the hell?
If you're going to finally
release your sword,
then hurry up and do it.
GRIMMJOW: Shut up!
I've got to make sure no one's
going to interfere this time.
ICHIGO: Why are you being
so paranoid all of a sudden?