[theme music]
-Now that they've made
it, I'm interested to hear
how you plan on getting us out.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Like this!
Hargh!
-I like it.
Ugh!
-Let's go!
-Something to remember us by!
[both yelling]
-What's wrong?
-You made it!
-What are you standing here for?
Let's go!
[gasps]
Uh!
[pattering rain]
-[shrieks]
Oh, no!
This could be a disaster!
-What is it, Kon?
-I know what's going on here.
I just realized something
terrible is happening!
-Kon, settle down.
What's wrong?
-The only explanation
for all this
is that there's a
Rain Man involved.
A Rain Man right here
among us, and-- rrh!
[grunts]
-Your dumb superstitions
are not helping.
-Just so you know,
I am not a Rain Man.
-Don't even say that.
You'll only encourage him.
-Haah!
-Just give it up, would you?
-It's for real, this time.
Look!
[bubbling]
KON (OFFSCREEN):
(NERVOUSLY) Uh, I told you.
BOY 1 (OFFSCREEN): Sure
is a nice rain tonight.
BOY 2 (OFFSCREEN): The
conditions are perfect.
We told you before, but it
seems that you've forgotten.
-You can't escape from water.
KON (OFFSCREEN):
You three losers
with your so-called
detective skills,
why didn't you see this coming?
-Hey, cut it!
It's not our fault.
Things are almost
impossible to track
when they're covered with water.
-Yes, these two make the
most troublesome foe.
-Humph.
-You bastards.
-Don't you think it's time
that we finish them off?
-Humph.
Yes, that's a good idea.
-(HO AND BAN) Let's do it!
-Ugh!
They combined!
-Now, they're more
than twice as big.
-So now what?
-Chad and Orihime, take Uryu
and get him away from here.
-Uh-oh, look out!
-[grunts]
Aah, agh!
Aah, hah!
[grunts]
-Uh!
Roar, Zabimaru!
Ugh!
-It comes right back!
-Yeah, useless.
-Hado 31, Shakkaho!
-Direct hit!
-Did it do anything?
[shrieks]
-It's no good!
-Damn it!
[grunts]
-Ichigo!
Right-- uuh!
Ugh!
-You two get him out of here!
-You need some help.
-Just leave me, Chad.
There's no point in all
of you putting yourselves
in danger trying to save me.
-Quit wasting your
breath talking about it.
Just go!
You can't let them catch
all of us, damn it!
Get the hell away from
here while you still can!
-I can't just leave you!
-Orihime, he's right.
-Huh?
-Ichigo will be OK.
Right now, you and I just
have to protect Uryu.
-[gulps]
[panting]
MAN (OFFSCREEN): I didn't
know you liked marionettes.
That one looks valuable.
-Actually, it's just old.
I don't think it
really has any value.
-Master Kariya is worried
about you, Yoshino.
I think you should
consider going back to him.
-Just so you know, I refuse
to take orders from anyone.
UTAGAWA (OFFSCREEN): Really?
Even if the orders are
from the man you love?
-Even love must grow
old, eventually.
I have found that it
grows old even faster when
one is deprived of any
feeling of freedom.
-It would appear
Master Kariya is
planning to make his move soon.
-I don't care about that.
Bounts are self-reliant
to begin with.
Let him do whatever
he wants to do.
-I don't understand
why Master Kariya
is so tolerant of your behavior.
You seem unworthy of him to me.
-[chuckles]
You're much more
naive than you look.
-Oh?
-You'll learn that
the world doesn't
run on ambition alone, Utagawa.
-Hm.
-One of these days, your lust
for power will be your undoing.
-No comment there.
-But of course.
Huh?
BOY (OFFSCREEN):
I'm leaving, sir.
Good night.
MAN (OFFSCREEN): He-he.
And I'll see you first
thing tomorrow, sir.
It sure was nice of
your boss to give me
a job here at the store, too.
He even let me take
home his leftover lunch.
-Um, I was wondering, Ganju--
-Yeah?
-What made you come
here in the first place?
-Well, my sister
Kukaku sent me here
to investigate
because she said she
felt a strange presence coming
from somewhere in this town.
-That's funny.
That's the same reason I came.
Except in my case, it
was Captain Unohana
who gave me the
orders to report here.
-Well, we both have our work
cut out for us, don't we?
-Uh-huh.
-Huh?
-Do you feel that?
-Yeah.
-There's spiritual pressure.
Do you think--
[grunting]
-Shakkaho!
-Guhl, no!
-Watch out, Gunther!
[shrieks]
-(IN UNISON) Seal the hole!
-This is fun.
But we can't let the
Quincy get away, can we?
-No, we can't.
-Urrgh!
-Aagh!
-I can breathe again!
-What happened?
That thing suddenly
cracked open.
-It came apart as soon as
those Bount twins took off!
Because now, they're more
interested in catching Uryu.
-Damn.
-[panting]
Chad, where are we going?
-We've got to get
out of this rain.
Let's head for that old factory.
With any luck,
Ichigo and the others
will guess that's where
we went and follow us.
Ungh.
-[panting]
What is it?
-It's them.
-[gasps]
-Damn, they found us.
-This is not good at all.
[shrieks]
-[shrieks]
-[grunts]
-Agh.
Ugh.
-Uryu.
Santen Kesshun, I reject!
-Orihime!
-Ugh!
[shrieks]
-Did you really think
you can get away from us?
-Fool, there's no escape.
-Now, Kurodo, Noba,
you take care of Uryu.
-What?
The two of us?
What can we do?
-Hrrm.
-Hng?
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
-We always get lots
of chances to win.
-But there is no
chance for you, losers.
-At least, not as
long as it's raining.
-(IN UNISON) Get them!
-Aaahh, rrgh!
-Haven't you learned yet?
-It's just going to
reform itself again.
-Uuurgh!
-Agh!
-Ugh!
-Ban!
We have to stay together!
-Urgh!
-Aagh!
Ugh!
BAN (OFFSCREEN): Ho!
-[gasps]
-Aargh!
-Ban!
-Ho, just hang on!
[splash]
-Now's our chance to escape!
-Hm.
KURODO (OFFSCREEN):
Get me away from here!
-What do you think
happened back there?
-I'm not sure.
-One thing about those twins--
-What?
---they never attacked
us separately.
-Yeah, you're right about that.
-I think it's because the
only way they can control both
their Dolls is by always keeping
their powers combined together.
-So they're using that
resonance phenomenon
that twins are said to possess.
-That explains why they always
combine into one water Doll
and not into separate ones.
-If we're right about this,
then getting them separated
is how we win.
[thunder rumbling]
[door creaks]
-Koga?
-It's too dark in here.
-I can read fine.
I like it like this.
-You're just as
stubborn as ever.
-You should get dried off.
You're soaking wet.
A cup of hot tea would
do you some good.
-Eh, no, thank you.
So do you have any idea where
the others have gone to?
-I'm afraid you're the
first one to show up.
-I don't know how
you figure this
is a place with
no water in sight
when the roof is leaking like
it's made of Swiss cheese.
-Sorry, it's better
than being outside.
-Uh, Chad.
-Hm?
-I think his fever
is getting worse.
-That's not good.
-I told you before, you've
got to just leave me behind.
-No way!
-I appreciate your
concern, but I
don't want to be a burden
to you, guys, anymore.
-Oh, Uryu.
URYU (OFFSCREEN): There's a
limit to how pathetic I can be.
HO AND BAN
(OFFSCREEN): [laughing]
[gasps]
HO (OFFSCREEN): Then why not
just come with us, Quincy?
BAN (OFFSCREEN): You're
going to, eventually,
whether you want to or not.
[shrieks]
-Uurgh!
Ugh.
-Uryu!
Uugh!
-Looks like we've got--
---a Quincy.
-Don't do it--
---or your friend gets this.
-[groans]
-Don't hurt him!
HO (OFFSCREEN): Then back off.
BAN (OFFSCREEN): If you care
what happens to this Quincy,
that is.
[uryu groans]
-Chad!
Orihime!
-Ichigo!
-It's Uryu!
-Then we must be too late.
-You two, put him
down right now.
-Why should we?
And besides, if you
guys had any brains--
---you'd all be running away
right now while you still had
half a chance.
-What did you say?
-Just wait until you see Guhl
and Gunther's full abilities,
then we'll see if you
still feel that way.
-Guhl and Gunther can't wait.
They say they're just
dying to kill you all.
[popping]
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Yaah!
[coughs]
-What the--
-Urgh.
[choking]
-Mmph.
-Ugh!
-[groans]
-What's going on, Rukia?
-Uhrm, urhm.
-Ugh!
This is a disaster!
RIRIN (OFFSCREEN): Stop it!
What are you doing to them?
HO (OFFSCREEN): [laughs]
Isn't it obvious?
We can go anywhere
there's water, remember?
BAN (OFFSCREEN): And the
human body is 70% water.
Convenient isn't it?
-Now, Guhl and Gunther--
---fill them up with water--
---and tear their bodies into
pieces from the inside out.
-Hrmp, urmh, arrgh,
uhh, uhh, agh.
-Oh, Ichigo!
-(WEAKLY) Uugh.
-No, he's dying!
Do something, you idiot,
before it's too late!
-Well, what am I supposed to do?
I'm a stupid rag
doll, same as you.
We have no power.
-Aah!
This is hopeless!
There's nothing we could do!
-Not true.
-What do you mean?
-There is one thing.
-What are you talking about?
-It won't be long
before they're all dead.
-Then we can take the
Quincy and get out of here.
-Huh?
Ban!
What just happened?
-Uh, yeah.
-What could I do, Ichigo?
-Rukia, don't die!
-Ho!
Ugh!
-Ban, I'm coming.
Ugh.
Ho, help me!
Where did you go?
-Aagh!
-It's working.
It's working!
-Keep zapping them!
-They come back too fast!
-Can't you fly them
farther away, Noba?
-I'm doing my best.
That's as far as
I can send them.
-Ugh!
This is your doing!
Huh?
Whaaa-- ugh!
-Rrh, aah!
Uhh!
Ungh.
-Rhh.
-[coughs]
[gasping]
-Are you all OK?
-Yeah, you saved us, Noba.
It's just like we thought.
The two of them have to
be together and share
their thoughts to
get that resonance.
And that means, if one of
them loses consciousness,
they can't resonate.
And then they can't
control their Dolls.
Isn't that right, Noba?
-That's right.
-Ban!
Ugh.
Ban!
Ban, what happened to you?
Please, you've got to wake up.
-OK, now's our chance.
-Yaah!
-Uh, hah?
-You might as well just quit.
It's all over now.
-You think?
Ha!
I don't need him.
I'll destroy you all myself.
[inaudible], Guhl!
-Hado 31!
Shakkaho!
-Guhl, get them!
[shrieks]
-We don't have enough firepower.
-Hado 31!
Ugh!
-You can't even
aim those things!
[laughs]
I knew I can handle
this all by myself.
-You little bastard.
MAN (OFFSCREEN): This
has got to be the place.
Hurry up, Hanataro!
HANATARO (OFFSCREEN):
I'm coming!
-Huh?
MAN (OFFSCREEN): Seppa!
HO (OFFSCREEN): Guhl!
-I know that attack.
-It can't be.
MAN (OFFSCREEN): There they are.
I knew this had to be the place.
HANATARO (OFFSCREEN):
You were right.
-[gasps] What the hell?
-Hey, Ichigo.
Good to see you again.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Ganju?
-It's been a while, hasn't it?
-And Hanataro?
How did you get here?
-[laughs]
That doesn't really
matter right now.
What matters is that you said
you needed more firepower.
And excessive firepower
is a Shiba clan specialty.
-You mean fireworks?
-Go for it, Ganju!
Whip up a big one and blow
that thing to pieces, Ganju.
-Coming right up.
But you'd all better stand
back because this is probably
going to get a little messy.
-Guhl!
Why are you standing there?
Attack!
-Here goes.
-Move, Guhl!
Attack!
-Fire in the hole!
-You idiot, it's a dud!
GANJU (OFFSCREEN):
Just give it a second.
KURODO (OFFSCREEN):
Ow, hot, hot, hot!
RIRIN (OFFSCREEN): Ow!
Ow.
-Aah, huh, huh.
[gulps]
[twins groaning]
[gasps]
-[groans]
[crackling]
-Aah.
-[shrieks]
-What just happened?
-Whoa.
Where did they go?
-Their bodies just
turned to dust.
-Even though they
looked like children,
they were probably very old
and well past their limits.
As a result, once their
Dolls were lost to them,
there was nothing left at
all to hold them together.
-But wait!
Uh--
-What is it, Orihime?
-Where is Uryu?
He's gone!
-[panting]
-Welcome back, Master Kariya.
-Thank you.
Good work, Ichinose.
-It was nothing at all.
-(THINKING) Humph.
Disgusting sycophant.
-Utagawa, where are Ho and Ban?
There's no trace
of their presence.
-It would seem
they were defeated.
-I see.
[chuckles]
[laughs]
[theme music]
KON (OFFSCREEN): Damn
that no-good Uryu!
Where did he disappear to now?
Even if he lost
his Quincy powers,
we still need him to keep us
stitched and sawed together.
We've got to find him!
URYU (OFFSCREEN): Is
that all I'm good for?
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN):
Don't worry about me.
I don't have enough
clothes to get
far in the world of the living.
URYU (OFFSCREEN):
I'm not coming back.
[theme music]
-"Illustrated Guide
to Soul Reapers."
MAN (OFFSCREEN): Golden.
-[groans]
-It really hurts, oh, Shuhei.
-Izuru, I may not be able
to go on much longer.
You've got to promise me, if I
die, you'll take care of my men
for me.
Aagh!
-Come on, get a hold
of yourself, Shuhei.
Ga-aah!
Ugh.
-Boy, these two
sure do whine a lot.
Let's see how they
handle real pain.
[men shriek]