[theme music]
-I now call this captain's
meeting to order.
The Ryoka infiltration
has been confirmed.
Subsequently, here
are my orders.
All squads are on second class
alert, effective immediately.
In addition, because of
this serious situation,
I am taking this special measure
assigning Squad 10 Captain
Hitsugaya chief responsibility
for the Ryoka's capture.
-Yes, Head Captain.
-We are having difficulty
gathering reliable intelligence
at the moment, captain.
There is also a problem
with information leaking
from the Department of
Research and Development.
You must find out what
is really happening,
and disseminate the information
to all of the 13 squads.
-Sir.
-Finally, and this is the most
important directive of them
all-- anyone who
encounters a Ryoka
is to eliminate him
without hesitation.
-Look.
-Watch out!
It's coming this way!
[shouting]
-Have any of the other
squads been deployed?
-Yes they have, Captain.
Lieutenant Omaeda and
some other from Squad 2
were ordered to head out
a little while ago, sir.
-Were there any others?
-Lieutenant Iba
of Squad 7 is also
reported to be headed
to the Rukon District.
-Very well.
Continue gathering
any information
you can about squad
movements, and especially
reports on the Ryoka.
And make sure you
overlook nothing.
-Yes, sir.
-It's so quiet.
-For now.
But it will be
noisy soon enough.
MAN: There they are!
-I get to go first.
-No.
I get first crack at them.
Taking us all on in
broad daylight, huh?
You've got some nerve.
-Hmph.
-Kariya, sir?
May I request that you
leave this one to me?
-Ah, yes.
This will serve as
a good test for us.
-[inaudible] doll.
-Huh?
-Ha ha!
Hello.
Nice to see you all.
-Huh?
-The air here is
quite delicious.
It makes me feel wonderful.
-Heh.
I heard you Bounts used
strange techniques,
but I had no idea how strange.
-You mean cowardly techniques.
What's the matter.
You can't even fight
your own battles?
How is he doing that?
That bastard's absorbing reishi.
-That's impossible.
What are you?
-You look at me as if
I'm some sort of monster.
But that's where you're wrong.
Regardless of what you
think, I'm still a human.
Just an improved one.
-Get him!
-Now, Doll, take them out.
-I'm feeling especially
dangerous today.
-Hey!
-I'll make you pay for this.
[laughter]
-Wait.
Isn't there anyone
else to help out?
-I feel so strong right
now, it's amazing!
[laughter]
-Someone help!
There are too many of them!
-Don't bother.
It's a waste of your energy.
-What did you do to him?
I don't like attacking
unarmed opponents,
but you leave me no choice.
What the hell is going on?
-Ha ha ha!
Ah, ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha ha!
-You call yourself
a Soul Reaper?
You don't deserve the name.
Feel all right?
-It's wonderful.
There's an unlimited amount of
reishi of the highest purity
all around us.
-Excellent.
Then let us be off.
-Call for the med crew.
Now.
-Yes, sir.
-The rest of you,
full battle alert.
Fan out and see to the
wounded, on the double.
-Say something, lieutenant.
Can you move?
-Captain Hitsugaya,
it's Lieutenant Iba.
He was thrown through the wall.
-How is he doing?
-It's too soon to tell.
But at least he's
regained consciousness.
-Captain!
I'm sorry I'm late.
I've just returned from
the world of the living.
-Rangiku.
I'm afraid I've failed in my
mission, and now as a result,
I've allowed the Ryoka to
invade the Soul Society.
-As the officer who sent you,
the responsibility is mine.
Understand?
-Yes.
-What can you tell
me about the Bounts?
I'm afraid that I don't
have very much to report.
Locating Bounts by our usual
means is virtually impossible.
Even right now, the
only spiritual pressure
in detectable amounts is
that of the two lieutenants.
-More bad news.
Keep looking!
Report anything unusual.
-Yes, sir!
-Welcome back,
Lieutenant Matsumoto.
-Thank you, sir.
-Well, here we are again.
-Yes.
-Rukia, did you feel it?
A while ago?
-Yes.
It felt like a Soul Reaper
was fighting a Bount somewhere
nearby.
-But you probably couldn't sense
the Bount's spiritual pressure,
could you?
-Just like in the world
of the living, isn't it?
-What's with the two of
you all lost in thought?
Don't you know this is
a state of emergency?
-Huh?
-That's right!
No one wants to see you
looking all romantic.
You two were only supposed
to be friends, remember?
-Huh?
You don't know what
you're talking about.
-Oh, I don't, do I?
I've got eyes,
and I can see when
something suspicious
is going on.
-Come now, friends.
Everyone needs to calm down.
We have no chance of
defeating the Bounts
if we're fighting
amongst ourselves.
-Well, that's true.
-I don't care!
-Ichigo, Rukia.
Yoruichi.
We have some bad
news about Kukaku.
-What do you mean?
-I'm afraid that
she's not there.
-Huh?
-Well, Kukaku does have a habit
of picking up and moving out
all of a sudden.
-Is there someone we can ask?
Who would know where
she could have moved to?
-I think I have an idea of
where she just might be.
-There it is.
[laughter]
ORIHIME: That's Kukaku's
house, all right.
We found her!
-Nice remodel.
-You think so?
-Yeah.
-It's so odd.
Every time she
moves, she completely
changes the design of her house.
-And every time, she proves
she has no sense of style.
-Like the way you draw.
-Watch it.
-Gettin whacked by you is
supposed to be Kon's job,
isn't it?
And by the way, where is Kon?
-Huh?
-Come to think of it, I
haven't seen him for a while.
-That's strange.
I'm positive he came along
with us to this Kukaku--
-Oh!
If Kon is lost, we
have to find him.
Do you think we should split
up and start searching?
-I don't think we'll need
to worry too much about him.
He'll be all right.
Kon is bursting with energy.
-Well, that's true.
-That's right.
-All right.
[screaming]
-I know that scream.
-Ichigo!
Rukia!
Doesn't that figure?
We come all this way
together, and who gets lost?
Me.
It could have been one of
them, but no, it had to be Kon.
-Sorry, but no entry.
This area is sealed.
-What's this about?
Hello?
What's all the excitement about?
[gasps]
-What is that thing?
-It has to be some kind
of miniature monster.
-What?
I'm no monster.
-You can just tell
how dangerous it is.
-No, no.
You've got me all wrong.
I'm not dangerous at all.
I'm a Mod-Soul.
-If that's an intruder--
-Then we should
grab it before it
tries to destroy any
other walls and houses.
-Hey, wait.
I didn't destroy anything.
I couldn't do that
even if I wanted to.
-Get him!
-Stupid people
acting like they've
never seen a stuffed
animal before.
Well, they're not gonna
kick the stuffing out of me!
I'm gonna live if I
have to run all night!
-You're such a bumbling idiot!
The only reason I sent you
to the world of the living
in the first place was because
I heard something strange was
happening there, and
I stupidly thought
you could be of some use to her.
-Yes, but I got distracted.
-Your mission failed because
you were paying more attention
to your job as a
convenience store clerk?
Are ya kidding me?
-It's the same old story.
-I'm sorry he couldn't
have been of more help.
-How is it you know what a
convenience store is, Kukaku?
-Why?
Is that a surprise?
What do you mean?
Are you trying to
say I'm stupid?
-No, it wasn't that at all.
I was just--
-In case you hadn't noticed, I'm
not in the best mood right now!
-Just keep your mouth shut
around her for a while, Ichigo.
-But I don't know what
I said that was so bad.
-I can see now I'm going to have
to teach both of you a lesson.
[whimpering]
-Take it like a man!
-What did I say?
-Ah, Kukaku.
-You have to watch what
you say around her.
-I don't want to
take it like a man!
-Go on.
-We know that the leader of the
Bounts, a man named Jin Kariya,
said the reason
he was coming here
was to take revenge
on the Soul Society.
The Bounts were
originally created
by the Department of
Research and Development.
Despite that fact,
there's strangely
almost no record of their
existence in the Soul Society
files.
-Well, how can that be?
-People tend to put a lid
on anything that stinks.
That's probably
what happened here.
I don't have any details as to
exactly how the Bounts intend
to exact their revenge
on us, but at least we
know it will be very difficult
for them to gain entrance
to the Seireitei, since
it's heavily guarded.
-So, you want to
find these Bounts,
and then figure out
what they're up to.
Is that the case?
-That's right.
I know there are a lot of
us, and I'm sorry to impose,
but would it be all right if we
stay here for the time being?
The Rukon District
is a big area,
and this is a good
central location for us.
-Koganehiko, Shiroganehiko.
How are our food supplies?
-We'll put body and
soul into the task.
-We could feed up to 100, if
that is your wish, master.
-Very well.
It's the least I can do, since
the Bounts wouldn't be here
in the first place if it
weren't for my idiot brother.
-Huh?
Hey, why should
I take the blame?
I just did my job.
You're right.
The whole thing's all my fault.
-It's all settled, then.
Make yourselves at home here.
I am curious, though.
Have you thought
much about how you're
going to locate these Bounts?
-Tah-dah!
-That's where we come in.
Just leave the locating
to the three of us.
-What in the hell are these
bizarre little things?
-They're Mod-Souls that
Kisuke Urahara created
with the ability to detect
Bount spiritual pressure.
-I see.
Then these are Mod-Souls.
Who'd have thought to
use stuffed animals?
Leave it to Kisuke to come
up with something so strange.
-We're not that strange.
-And it's our
abilities that matter.
Sheesh.
-There's still one more item.
I have an important
request of everyone.
-What's that?
-I'd like you all to try to
collect information on someone
called Ran'Tao.
-Ran'Tao?
Who's that?
-Well, Ichigo, think back to
when Kariya was telling you
about the history of the Bounts.
He mentioned the person
here in the Soul Society
who was the lead researcher,
the one who actually created
the Bounts in the first place.
That was Ran'Tao.
ICHIGO: What?
RUKIA: Are you saying at this
Ran'Tao person is still alive,
and still here?
-Yes.
It's been more than 1,000 years
since Ran'Tao was expelled from
the Seireitei, but rumors
persist that he still lives
in Rukon.
-Let's track him down, then.
I mean, who would be able to
tell us more about the Bounts
than the one who created
them in the first place?
-Indeed.
-All right, now.
If that's all, then
let's have some dinner.
Koganehiko, Shiroganehiko,
is everything ready for us?
-Yes.
Right this way.
-Come to think of it,
I am pretty hungry.
I can't remember the
last time I ate anything.
-Mm.
-Thank you for your
hospitality, Kukaku.
-Yoruichi.
-What is it?
-Is there anything else
you want to tell me about?
-What do you mean?
-Come on, don't
play dumb with me.
If you want me to help, you
have to tell me everything.
Why stay here instead of
going into the Seireitei?
It's not just because it's
convenient for the search,
is it?
-I've learned that
among the Bounts,
there's a Soul Reaper
who's helping them.
He not only has the ability to
hide his spiritual pressure,
but he can make
himself invisible,
and he's broken into
the Seireitei already.
-Oh?
-That's why I have no
doubt that it was this Soul
Reaper, whose name is Ichinose.
He's the one who broke
into the archives
at the Department of
Research and Development.
He manipulated the data,
and then sealed the database
so that Mayuri Kurotsuchi
would become interested
in the Bounts.
Having fallen for
such a simple trick,
Kurotsuchi then
helped the Quincy
to regain his powers, which
then allowed the Quincy to let
the Bounts enter
the Soul Society.
-I understand.
So in other words, you
need to hide out somewhere
where this Soul
Reaper, Ichinose, won't
be able to track your movements.
-Sui-Feng is taking steps to
strengthen the Seireitei's
security, but given everything
that's happened so far,
I don't think much can
be done to stop him.
-Probably not.
-There's also the
fact that as someone
who left the Soul Society, it
would be a real pain for me
to go back after all this time.
-Forget the other stuff.
That sounds like the real
reason you don't want to go.
-Let's just say I want to
do things my way this time.
-Can you win?
-I don't know.
-Well, fine.
You know that I've never been
one to shy away from trouble.
I'll do whatever I can to help.
-Thank you.
-All of you will
split up and head out.
Use the Mod-Souls to try and
detect the Bounts' presence.
If you find any trace of
them, use a small amount
of spiritual pressure
to inform the others.
Is that clear?
-Mm-hm.
-Rukia, what are you
going to be doing?
-I'd like to go along
with you and help,
but now that I'm here,
I have to report back
to my squad for duty.
I'm afraid that I've already
put it off for too long.
-Well, take care, then.
-Try not to do anything stupid.
-All right.
-Not this again!
-Huh?
-I'm more valuable than
her, and I'll prove it!
I'm gonna go and
find a Bount myself.
And then you'll see!
I'll beat you, Rukia!
I'll beat you all!
-What was all that about?
-Nothing makes people more
irrational than jealousy.
-So true.
-She's such a pain,
but I need her.
-Yes, you do.
-Too bad she didn't hear that.
-Hey, where are you going?
-We don't have any
time to waste here.
I'm going to get
started searching.
Just leave me on my own for now.
-Uryu, wait.
-I'll be all right.
-Hey Kurodo, listen up.
-Yes?
-Take care of Orihime.
-Just leave everything to me.
-Orihime, don't push yourself.
-I won't. Don't worry.
-All right.
Let's move.
-The dirt and depression
of the Rukon District
hasn't changed at all.
-Damn, damn, damn, damn.
I'm just so mad!
But I don't even know
what I'm so mad about.
Argh!
I'm mad because I'm so mad.
Huh?
That presence.
I'd know that scary
presence anywhere.
They're here!
[shriek]
-Hm?
[coughing]
-Huh?
Well, well.
-It can't be.
-It's you again.
What a coincidence.
This will be fun.
Hah.
[inaudible] Nieder.
[theme music]
RIRIN: Are you the one in
charge of Bount countermeasures?
HITSUGAYA: Who are you?
RIRIN: I'm Ririn, a Mod-Soul.
I'm an expert at
tracking Bounts.
HITSUGAYA: Is that true?
ICHIGO: Unfortunately,
it is true.
If you want, I could
lend her to Squad 10.
HITSUGAYA: No thanks.
I have a bad feeling about her.
RIRIN: How insulting.
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers.
VOICEOVER: Golden!
-Hey, Hanataro.
How is that kid doing now?
-Oh, hi, Renji.
He's all right.
In fact, he's completely
out of danger.
-Oh, good.
I'm really glad to hear it.
-Where is everyone?
-At the Soul Society.
-It sure is a nice thing for you
to do, coming all the way back
here just to check on him.
-Well, that was one
part of it, but mostly I
came back because they told
me I had to clean the place up
before I left.
-Huh?