[theme music]
-[gasping]
[music playing]
-Let's go, Izuru.
-I'm going now.
I'll see you later,
little Shiro.
-Mmm!
Quit calling me little Shiro,
and don't pat me on the head,
either.
-When you finally go to the
same grownup school as I do,
I'll use your real name.
-Forget that.
Why would I go to some
stupid Soul Reaper school?
-I'll be staying in
the dorm from now on,
but I'll come visit you
soon, OK, little Shiro?
Bye!
-All right, thanks
for the warning.
Don't hurry, you bad wetter!
-Goodbye, mother and father.
I'll come visit again soon.
-[gasping]
-Great!
Now we're going to be late
to our first day at school.
-Don't you blame this on me!
What were you doing
sleeping in a tree?
I was looking
everywhere for you.
-I'll do whatever I want to.
It's none of your business
where I sleep, anyway!
-Oh!
I should have just
left without you!
It would have served you right!
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Welcome, new students,
to Soul Reaper Academy.
You are now part of a proud
tradition, a unique school
dedicated to building this
stealth forces in the 13 Court
Guard Squads of the future.
Apply yourselves
diligently to your studies
and uphold the
honor of our school.
-Let me introduce
myself, students.
My name is Gengoro Onabara.
I'm also pleased to
inform you that of all
the incoming freshman, your
test scores on the entrance exam
were the highest.
In other words, welcome
to the advanced class.
Congratulations.
Of course, this means
that expectations for you
are higher as well.
You must train hard and
strive to not merely serve
your future squad,
but to excel in each
of your various pursuits.
-Just because you're not
in the advanced class,
it doesn't mean you have
less chance of excelling.
In the end, what
matters is hard work.
If you train as hard as--
RUKIA (VOICE OVER):
Stupid Renji.
I should be in the
advanced class, not him.
-All right, group
one to the line.
ALL: Yes, sir!
-All of you, you will
now demonstrate Hado.
Begin!
ALL: Right!
MOMO (VOICE OVER): Ruler,
mask of flesh and blood,
all things in the universe fly.
That which names all in nature,
gathering of heat and war.
Beyond the seas in reverse,
take steps to the south.
Hado 33 Shakkaho
Red Flame Cannon!
INSTRUCTOR
(OFFSCREEN): Very good.
Next group.
ALL: Yes, sir!
-That was a great shot.
How'd you do it?
-I only hit the corner.
Probably just luck.
-Well, I'm still impressed.
Most of them didn't even
reach their targets.
[explosion]
-Huh?
-Was that the blonde kid?
-Amazing shot.
I think he hit a
perfect bullseye.
RENJI (VOICE OVER): Hmm!
That guy's pretty good.
I guess now I know my
competition is in this class.
INSTRUCTOR (OFFSCREEN):
Group three, to the line.
ALL: Yes, sir!
RENJI (VOICE OVER):
Well, whoever
he is, I'm not about
to let him show me up.
So he destroyed the
target, then I will, too.
[yelling] Hado 33
Shakkaho Red Flame Cannon!
[screams]
-He could have killed us all!
-What was he doing?
The fool!
-Uh--
-You!
Special instruction after class.
[laughter]
-Yes, sir.
-Ahhh!
INSTRUCTOR (OFFSCREEN):
Match, [inaudible].
-Are you hurt?
Can you up?
You didn't have to be so rough!
-Izuru, are you all right?
-Yes, sir.
-Huh!
-Resting up, I see.
-Hmm?
Oh, it's you.
-I wouldn't mind
joining you there.
That OK?
-Uh, sure.
-Thanks.
I got to admit, you really
let me have it in class.
I was so overwhelmed
by your strength
that I couldn't
even counterattack.
My whole arm is still numb.
-Well, I'm sorry about that.
I didn't mean anything by it.
But I kind of messed
up at target practice
earlier, so I felt like I
needed to make up for that.
-Zan, Ken, So, Ki.
Each of these four
disciplines must
be mastered before we
can become Soul Reapers.
We've definitely
got our work cut out
for us if that's
going to happen.
-Well, yeah, I guess so.
Name's Izuru Kira.
Hi.
It's certainly a pleasure to
meet you, fellow freshman.
-Introduction and
a handshake, huh?
Your family must be from
the good side of town.
-Huh?
-Manners aren't
exactly my style.
But my name is Renji Abarai,
and nice to meet you, too.
-Ah, think you, Renji.
[voices]
-Huh?
What's going on?
[chatter]
-I can see!
-Hey, what is
everybody looking at?
-Hmm?
Oh, one of the Court
Guard Squad captains
is supposed to be coming here
any minute to review the class.
-Really?
A full captain?
[chatter]
-Hey, stop pushing!
-A real captain.
-I wish you could have
seen him, little Shiro.
His spiritual pressure
surrounding him
was different from
anything I've ever felt.
Hey, it feels like you're
not even listening to me.
-I told you, quite
calling me little Shiro!
-Ah!
-Why do you always have to come
home on your days off, anyway?
If that school's so great,
you should just stay there.
-I come home to visit
you, little Shiro.
-Well, I don't
remember asking you to.
-I know one thing for sure.
Someday I'll be in Squad
5 with Captain Aizen.
Hey, come on.
I'm really serious.
[spitting seeds] To
-Ahhhh!
Hey!
What was that for?
-All this daydreaming
is a waste of time.
You've been here for
six months and you still
haven't started taking
your training seriously.
-Oh, yeah?
Well, who are you to--
You look like you're
going someplace.
Are you guys having field
training or something today?
-Yeah, we're going to the World
of the Living for a practice
fight against dummy Hollows.
-Why you?
Why is it only your class?
Not to mention you shouldn't
be in the advanced class
in the first place!
-What can I say?
They recognize talent
when they see it.
-Oh!
-And just you wait.
I'm better than you already,
and when I come back,
there won't even be any
comparison between us.
-Yeah?
Well, when you come back, I'm
going to be a-- I don't know.
-First, allow us to
introduce ourselves.
I'm Shuhei Hisagi, sixth year.
-I'm Kanisawa.
-I'm Aoga.
-The three of us will your
guides for this exercise.
-Wow!
-They're going to
take us themselves?
-No way!
-What's up?
Why are they all gawking?
Are they famous or something.
-How do you not know?
The one in the middle,
everybody knows who he is.
Shuhei Hisagi.
They say he's been assigned to
a post in the 13 Court Guard
Squads even before he graduates.
That almost never happens.
He's even supposed to be in
line to become a ranked offer.
RENJI (OFFSCREEN): Huh.
No kidding.
-Strangely enough, he also
failed the Academy's entrance
exam two times.
And given that my exam score
was the highest in our class,
I might be better than him.
-Oh?
-Now listen up.
We'll split up into groups
of three and get ready to go.
Everyone take out the lots you
drew when we first assembled,
and then find the
two students who
have the same mark as you have.
-Ah, so that's what these
little pieces of paper were for.
-You and I are together,
but who's our third?
-Excuse me.
I'm your third.
-Oh, it's you.
Hello, Momo.
-Welcome aboard.
-All right, not that
everyone's found their groups,
we'll brief you on
today's exercise.
-An advance party of
sixth year students
has already entered
the World of the Living
and constructed a
temporary barrier.
-Once inside that
perimeter, each group
will engage in practice
combat with dummy Hollows.
-The sixth year
students are here
only to create a combat-ready
environment for you.
They will not assist
in the combat itself.
Are we clear?
Then let's go.
ALL: Yes, sir!
SHUHEI (OFFSCREEN): Open!
-It's begun.
Maintain barrier strength.
Often the dummy Hollows
can attract the real thing.
-Right, right.
But this is a safe zone,
so it's not likely here.
-Just the same, make sure you
don't let your guard down.
This is part of our
training as well.
-OK, OK.
-Damn.
All right, Momo,
it's coming your way!
-Hado 33 Shakkaho
Red Flame Cannon!
Izuru, I missed it!
-[yelling]
-Good job, Izuru.
-Thanks.
You, too.
-That was even easier
than we thought it'd be.
-It's all because we
worked together as a team.
None of us would have done
as well as we did on our own.
-Nah!
By myself, I would have
done it much faster.
They should let me fight real
Hollows instead of dummies.
-Huh!
You're nothing but talk, Renji.
-Hey!
What do you mean by that?
-Come on, Mister Big Mouth.
-Hey!
-Let's go back.
-Stop it!
-Yeah, yeah, I know.
-Hey, what's the problem, Momo?
-Oh, it's-- it's nothing.
-I think that everyone
has returned safely.
-So the exercise was a success.
-This is Hisagi at
the rendezvous point.
Barrier Unit, what is
the situation there?
HISAGI (OFFSCREEN):
Barrier Unit, acknowledge.
Barrier Unit, can you hear me?
Report in at once!
Barrier Unit, report!
-What could have happened?
-I don't know.
It certainly is strange
for them not to answer.
-Oh, no!
-You just till we
get back, and--
-[scream]
-What the hell?
-Who was that?
-Let's go.
Come on!
-What is that thing?
IZURU (OFFSCREEN):
It's-- it's huge!
SHUHEI (VOICE OVER): Oh, crap!
It's a Hollow!
And a big one, too.
But why didn't we
sense it approaching?
-You bastard!
You killed her!
-Aoga, no!
-[yelling]
-Aoga!
Freshmen, get out of here!
Run as far as you can!
[screaming]
-Come on, follow me!
Faster!
Come on, everybody,
stick together!
-So that's what a real
Hollow looks like.
Come on!
Are you deaf?
Let's go!
Soul Society, come in!
Emergency!
Shuhei Hisagi
requesting assistance.
I'm in the World of the
Living, coordinate point 1026.
Huge Hollow attack
at this location!
[screaming]
-Run!
Let's go!
Go!
MOMO (VOICE OVER): Why
are they all running away?
Someone has to stay and fight.
-Momo, what do you
think you're doing?
We were told to clear the area.
You're disobeying
a direct order!
-Yeah, but--
-Hey!
That thing just killed
two sixth year students!
-I know.
-Momo!
SHUHEI (VOICE OVER): Damn!
I can barely see it.
-[yelling]
-Is that all you got?
Well, bring it on!
You three!
-We just wanted to help, sir.
Sorry to disobey.
-We came back to save you so
you'll remember to forgive us.
-Ruler, the mask
of flesh and blood,
all things in the universe fly!
-That which names
all, heat and war!
-Beyond the seas in reverse,
take steps to the south.
ALL: Hado 33 Shakkaho
Red Flame Cannon!
-I suggest we run, sir!
-Right!
-How could such
a gigantic Hollow
manage to sneak up
on us like that?
-I don't know.
It seems like it was able to
conceal its spiritual pressure
somehow.
-There's no way we're
strong enough to defeat it,
so what do we do,
just keep running?
I've already called the Soul
Society and requested back up.
Until then, we just
have to stay alive.
Hey!
What the hell?
Why is everything
getting all blurry?
-Ahhh!
How can this be happening?
-If must have
called its friends.
This whole thing is just crazy.
So many Hollows!
-No way.
No way!
I don't want to die like this.
I don't want to die
at all, you guys!
[screaming]
-Sorry to keep you waiting.
We got here as
quickly as we could.
-It's Captain Aizen,
leader of Squad 5,
and his Lieutenant,
Gin Ichimaru.
-You've done very well.
I'm sure you were scared,
but you're safe now.
We'll take over from here.
You go and get some rest.
-My, there certainly
are a lot of you.
Slay them, Shinso!
MOMO (OFFSCREEN): Captain Aizen.
[wind blowing]
-Excuse me, guard?
-Yeah?
What do you want?
[gasp]
[music playing]
[theme music]
MALE SPEAKER (VOICE OVER): Rats!
I'm too hungry to
concentrate on training!
FEMALE SPEAKER (VOICE OVER):
All right, then, here.
Take my emergency rations.
MALE SPEAKER (VOICE
OVER): Thanks.
Hey, wait.
What's this?
FEMALE SPEAKER (VOICE OVER):
This is chicken nibbles,
and this is to
remove hair balls.
MALE SPEAKER (VOICE OVER):
You're in human form now.
Why are you still
eating cat food?
FEMALE SPEAKER
(VOICE OVER): Try it.
It's pretty good.
MALE SPEAKER (VOICE OVER): Eww!