[theme music]
-Unbelievable.
How could something
like this happen?
To plant a bomb in the
Shishinro Repentance Cell.
What's the reason for it?
-It's a declaration of war.
The Shishinro Repentence Cell
was built from Sekkisekki rock
because it's
virtually impenetrable
to spiritual attacks.
It must have taken
a great deal of time
to devise such an
elaborate plan, which
means the ones responsible
have a deep seated hatred
of the Soul Society.
Increase the number of men
assigned to the search force.
We must discover
their whereabouts
as quickly as possible.
-Yes, sir.
-It's the Bounts, isn't it?
-I've failed.
I should have been
able to stop this.
-Let's stop them now.
-Hm?
Oh!
-How's Rukia?
Didn't you hear me, damn it?
I want to know if
she's all right.
-I expect she'll
make a full recovery.
However, the wound is very deep.
I would like for
her to rest here
until she's had a
chance to recuperate.
-Oh, thank goodness.
-Well, now, this recovery
never would have been possible
without the strong
will and determination
of her big brother.
Proof that one should
never underestimate
the power of sibling love.
-Yeah!
You did a good job.
You deserve a pat on the back.
-You saved her life.
I know she'll be safe here.
Thank you.
But I'm going after them now,
and I could use your help.
-What do you mean?
-They went after Rukia
knowing full well
that she hadn't recovered
from her wounds yet.
She was an easy
target, and they knew
it would distract
us for a while.
That kind of crap
makes me sick, and I'm
going to make them pay for it.
-I cannot help you.
-D'ah!
Why not?
-You're going to just stand
by and let them do this?
-The 13 Court Guard
Squads have already
been assigned to deal with this.
And I see no need for me
to join forces with you.
-How can you--
-Ichigo!
-Go back to the world of the
living, where you belong.
-Heh.
I get it now.
Yesterday's enemy
is today's enemy.
Is that it?
Let's go, Orihime.
-But--
-I'm trusting you to
take care of Rukia.
-I'm glad Rukia has
you to watch over her.
Hey Wait a second!
Where are you going?
Wait for me!
[laughter]
-Hm?
-Huh?
WOMAN: He's cute.
Hi, stranger.
-I've never seen him before.
-Nice place you've got here.
Mind if I join in
the festivities?
-Show me what you've got to bet.
-It's my pleasure.
You think this will be enough?
-I suppose you bet your life.
You're new around
here, aren't you?
This isn't the world
of living, friend.
We do things differently
in the Soul Society.
-Pain's the same
in either world.
-I like how you think
stranger, let's do this.
-Hey.
Uh--
-You come in acting all tough,
you'll leave in a body bag.
No way!
-It looks as though I win.
-You!
You cheated!
No one can be that lucky.
-Is something wrong?
You seem frightened.
And I had always heard
that the men of Kusajishi
were the toughest
in all of Rukongai.
-You stinkin'-- wha?
What kind of freakin'--
-Oh, come, now.
Is that it?
Surely you've more
strength than that.
-Whoa!
-Huh?
-Perhaps you'd like to
be my next opponent.
-Why, you-- What the
hell did you do to him?
-That's enough.
He's not someone you
could ever hope to defeat.
-That's too bad.
I was hoping to have some
fun before you arrived.
-Ichinose.
I could use your help
dealing with Kariya.
[gasps]
-A Soul Reaper?
What's someone from the
Seireitei doin' around here?
You are mistaken.
I'm not from there.
In fact, I'm no
longer a Soul Reaper.
-I don't know what
you're talking about,
and I don't care.
-There's only three of them.
Let's get 'em!
-Yah!
-Perhaps we should consider
being a little more subtle
next time.
-That's true.
I'll try to control my
urges in the future.
-The Rukon District is
large, but if you continue
to draw attention
like this, it won't
be long at all before
we're discovered.
-Not a bad idea.
-That's crazy.
-Huh?
Who the hell are you, anyway?
And what do you want here?
-Why does anyone come here?
We came to have a little fun.
So how about it?
You want to play with us?
-What do you mean?
-We intend to turn the
Soul Society upside down.
-Wait a minute.
You're not those--
-We searched the
entire south side.
There's no sign of them.
-All right, then.
Move on to the east side
and continue the search.
-Yes, sir.
-We know they're
hiding somewhere.
Don't let them slip though.
-I can't find 'em!
-Nobody's here.
-Over here.
-Over there!
-Come on, men!
Hurry!
Don't let the other squads
get there ahead of us.
-Wow.
This is so exciting, isn't it?
Just look at everyone
running around down there.
Oops.
He fell down.
Hey, I wonder if
baldy and Yumian
are out there searching, too?
It's like a race to see who
can find the Bounts first,
isn't it?
Are you gonna join the race?
-Why bother.
There's no sport in it.
-Aw.
-You starting to get bored?
Nuh-uh.
In fact, I'm a little relieved.
-What do you mean?
-Well, it's just that Maki's
out there with the Bounts right
now, so I thought you probably
wouldn't have any fun,
so why bother fighting him?
Am I right?
-That doesn't make
any difference at all.
He's shown how weak
he is by allowing
himself to be used by them.
-Huh.
If you don't care, I
don't care, either.
-I'm exhausted.
-Dammit.
We've been walking
around all this time
and haven't come up
with a single clue.
-I've been trying to figure
out why the Bounts would
go to all the trouble of
breaking into the Seireitei,
and then blow up Senzaikyu.
-Well, it definitely wasn't
subtle, so all I can think
is that they wanted
everybody in the Soul Society
to know they were here.
-That's crazy.
It's like announcing that
you're committing a crime.
Why would the Bounts want
to draw everyone's attention
like that?
-Why?
Because the only reason
they're here is to get revenge.
They want to make sure everybody
knows who's doing this.
-Well I, for one,
have never been
able to make heads or tails
out of the way they think.
Sneaking into the Soul Society,
then wanting to be noticed.
It seems like one
big game to them.
-Chad.
-Sorry.
I wanted to protect Rukia, but
I couldn't get there in time.
-Me, either.
Byakuya was the
one who saved her.
-Really?
-Yeah.
She's at his house
right now recuperating.
-I see.
-The three of us didn't do
what we were supposed to do.
If we had, none of this
would have ever happened.
-What's wrong, Master Ichigo?
You look worn out.
-What the hell?
-Just wait and see.
We've got something
interesting to show you.
-OK.
So what's so interesting?
Let's do it!
Shiroganehiko!
-Ready, Koganehiko!
-Heave!
-Ho!
Heave!
-Definitely impressive.
-Most definitely, brother.
-That's incredible.
The hands opened.
-What do you think of
that, Master Ichigo?
-Well, yeah.
I mean, to be honest, it's--
-What is it?
-What do you mean, what is it?
How can you possibly ask that?
-Yeah, what do you
mean, what is it?
How can you possibly ask that?
-What's that?
-Ganju!
-I think I recognize those guys.
Aren't they--
-Gah!
The great Kukkau
arms are broken!
GANJU: You're sure?
-Yeah.
Yeah!
-These guys came in and
started acting all tough.
You don't pull that kind
of crap in Kusajishi.
It's a pretty mean
town, but I've never
seen anything like these guys.
-Kusajishi, huh?
You think it's Kariya?
-Who knows?
But Kusajishi is just the
kind of place he'd look for.
-What do you mean?
-It's a tough town.
Real tough.
-That's putting it mildly.
It's one of the most dangerous
places in the Rukon District.
You've got to be tough
to survive in that place.
If they had a strong
enough leader,
they could be dangerous.
-Aw, sis, I was just
about to say that myself.
-Give it a rest, Ganju.
Any moron could have
figured that out.
Speaking of morons--
tell me, now.
What exactly were you two
doing in Kusajishi, anyway?
-Well, uh, you see, the
truth is we actually
went there to do
a little research.
-Oh, really?
-Yeah.
That was it.
You know what I mean?
Kind of a fact finding mission.
-Tell me more.
-We were just studying
their society.
-If you've got to lie about
something you've done,
then you shouldn't
have been doing it!
[screaming]
-I-- I apologize.
-So, what are you gonna do?
-I'm going.
It may turn out to
be nothing, but it's
the only lead we've got.
-I thought you'd say that.
URYU: I'm coming with you.
-Hm?
-What the--
-Uryu.
-You decided to come back?
-Yeah.
What do you say?
You got room for
one more, Ganju?
I'm ready.
Kariya is mine.
-Hmph.
Fine.
We leave bright and
early tomorrow morning.
-You'll never catch him
with that lazy attitude.
That's out there right and
strike while the iron's hot.
We'll give those Bounts an ass
whoopin' they won't forget.
-Uh-- yeah.
-Are you kidding, sis?
You could get lost
wandering around
that place in the
middle of the night.
-Does it look like I'm kidding?
-Ah!
No!
All right, then.
Let's move out, everyone.
-Right!
-Pigs, huh?
-Don't ever call
them pigs, got it?
Now listen, they've
all got names.
There's Bonnie, Connie, Cindy,
Mindy, Sunny, Hunny, Manny,
Nanny, and Kanbe.
-All right, what's up?
Why'd you give the last
one such a goofy name?
-Ah!
Kanbe's so cute.
You're a little
sweetie, aren't you?
-Hey!
Don't just stand there.
Let's get a move on.
-All right.
Saddle up.
-What?
Hey.
Are you insane?
You're not getting me on the
back of one of those pigs.
I'm outta here.
-I told you, they're not pigs!
-I'll see you there.
-Hold on, Ichigo.
No way.
If I had to ride
one of those things,
I don't know if
I'd ever get there.
-Son of a-- thinks he's too
good to ride on one of my boars.
-Ichigo's lucky.
He escaped.
-Mm.
-Wah!
Don't ever
underestimate my body.
Is everybody ready?
All right, light's
move 'em out, Bonnie!
Yeah!
-Whoa!
[giggle]
-The Kuchiki home.
I see.
They must have rescued me.
It's still warm.
Byakua.
-I'm so tired.
Who am I?
Where did I come from?
I can't go on.
No.
I can't let it end like this.
Not as a stranger
in a strange place.
-Thank you so much for waiting.
-Ah!
-This should warm you up.
-How kind of you.
-Here you are.
-Wah!
Even when I've forgotten
who I am and where I'm from,
there are two things that
I'll always remember.
Those sweet himilayas
of happiness.
So bouncy and alive!
I think I'm in love!
Oh, lady?
-How am I supposed to-- whoa!
-Beginners shouldn't talk.
You'll bite your tongue off.
-Look at me!
-Considering this is
the first time I've
ridden on the back
of a wild boar,
this is actually
quite exhilarating.
-It's so much fun!
-All right.
We're about to head into
the forest, everyone.
So hang on tight, and
look out for branches.
-Please feel free to relax
and make yourselves at home.
-Can you gather
some capable men?
-It shouldn't be a problem.
There's no one around here who
will go against what I say.
Give me until tomorrow, and I'll
gather as many men as you want.
-I'm glad to hear it.
-Now, if you'll excuse me.
-I apologize.
I never should have
brought you to this town.
-Why apologize?
I'm enjoying myself immensely.
Tell me, Ichinose,
what do you think?
-Hm?
Ichinnose.
-Sorry, Master Kariya.
-Ichinose's been acting
strange ever since we arrived.
I think perhaps
something's bothering him.
-I've sensed the
same thing with you.
-Hm?
-I've been getting this
almost imperceptible feeling
that-- well, not that you
haven't been in high spirits.
-I have been in high spirits.
I find this place exhilarating.
In fact, I haven't had
this much fun in years.
It's like something's
been holding me back,
but I'm free now for
the very first time.
-Master Kariya.
-I'm going out.
-Master Kariya
-I sense someone interesting
is about to arrive.
-I'll come with you, then.
-No.
I prefer you stay here
and organize the locals.
That way I can have
this one all to myself.
-Ganju's comin' through!
-Hey.
Ganju.
I gotta ask you something.
-Yeah?
So what is it?
-I'm not sure exactly
how to say this,
but unless you've been
meaning to take us in circles,
we're lost.
-Oh, no.
-Not again.
-Did you enjoy it?
-Oh, yeah!
-Just let me know if
you want anything.
Anything at all.
-Yeah!
That's it.
I wanna live here forever.
-All right.
Where are they?
Uh-- there's nothing here.
I can't sense anything yet.
-Well, that's that.
I think we can all agree that
this is this and that is that,
right?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
[grumbling]
MAN: What the hell
are we doing out
here in the middle
of the night, anyway?
-Hey.
You think it's OK just
to leave him there?
-Why ya askin' me?
You always think
you're so smart.
What do you think?
-I don't know.
It all stinks.
But that guy's got some
weird power, that's for sure.
-You are such a kiss
ass, you know that?
-Shut the hell up.
I just think we should
keep an eye on the guy.
Huh?
Who the hell are you?
-I'll ask the questions
here, if you don't mind.
-What are you talking about?
-Listen, numbnuts,
we're from Kusajishi.
-I see.
That'll make this easier, then.
-Huh?
-What the--
-Uh, is everything all right?
-I got the situation
under control.
After all, I'm Ganju
Shiba, the self
proclaimed former
differentiable deep red bullet
of the West Rukon district.
The self proclaimed fastest
cashier in Karakura.
Yeah!
-There's no doubt about it.
Ganju's definitely a
legend in his own mind.
-Hm.
[shout]
-Let's go, Bonnie!
-So, then.
You're Jin Kariya.
-I am.
-You seem to think that you
can do whatever you like.
-Huh.
This Rukia Kuhchiki,
the Soul Reaper
that Yoshi cut up so badly.
I understand she happens
to be your younger sister.
Do you seek revenge?
-That's not why I'm here.
I must protect this land.
And I will kill the enemies
of the Soul Society,
no matter who they are.
[theme music]
KON: Step right up.
The fight of the century
is about to begin.
Byakuya Kuchiki
versus Jin Kariya.
Get your tickets.
ORIHIME: We've got popcorn,
peanuts, and ice cold drinks
for sale.
MAN: Get your souvenir programs.
How about a Byakuya towel,
or a Senbon Zakura keychain?
ICHIGO: This isn't
some kind of circus!
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers.
KUKAKU: Golden.
-Your sister scares
the hell out of me.
-Yeah.
Just once I'd like to
get her under my thumb
and show her who's boss.
-Your wish is my command.
-Huh?
-I'll do whatever
you want, Ganju.
-Huh?
-Go ahead.
Now's your chance to tell
her what you really think.
-I get it.
Kukaku, you're nothing
but a big, stupid--
-What did you say?
Ha ha ha ha.
[shouting]