[music playing]
[theme music]
-You fight pretty well,
but unfortunately I
don't have the time to
mess with you right now.
I've got to save my
friend Keigo's life first.
-You fell for it!
Ha!
Goodbye.
-You idiot!
-Hado #33!
Sokatsui!
-You're too slow.
-Rukia!
-I'm all right.
-Are you sure?
-Is that all you have?
You didn't turn out to
be much of a challenge.
-Aikido without the spirit
chant isn't going to be enough.
But against speed
like hers, we'd
never have time
for a spirit chant.
-Hm.
In that case, leave it to me.
-Are you serious?
-Just what do you
have in mind, Kurodo?
-This is what I have in mind.
By borrowing Rejni's form, I
can distract her for awhile.
This should give you enough time
to do the spirit chant, Rukia.
-Ah, so he intends to
challenge us with a sword, now.
How amusing.
-Has he transformed?
-It doesn't make any difference.
We'll still defeat him.
-We'll see about that right now!
-Kurodo!
-I think he'll be all right.
When Kurodo
impersonates someone,
he gets all of their
fighting abilities, too.
Now, Rukia.
Do the spirit chant.
-All right.
-Here I come again!
I'm not finished yet.
-If you treat this
like some child's game,
you're going to die!
-The one who reigns, mask
the flesh, all creation,
flapping of wings, he who
carries the name human!
-Tsubaki.
Koten Zanshun.
I reject, I reject!
-I'm afraid that it is useless.
-Temperance.
Claw the wall of seamless
dreams, Hado #33.
Sokatsui!
Impossible.
How did she escape
that attack in time?
-What do we do now?
-So close.
But not close enough.
-Oh no!
Kurodo!
-Damn you.
-So then.
Do you have any other
tricks you'd like to try?
-I can't move my arms and legs.
-Somehow I must have been
fated to have to bear witness
to the deaths of young ones.
It saddens me to have to watch
young men, with their futures
still ahead of them,
die before my very eyes.
-Master!
Master!
I don't want to die.
I'm not ready to die yet.
[music playing]
-Kariya.
Yes, it's been a
long time, Claude.
Or do you go buy a
different name now?
-What do you want?
-I want to entrust this
young man to your care.
I want you to teach
him, so that he
may learn how to
live as a Bount.
-I'm sorry, but, I
cannot do that Kariya.
A Bount lives by
training himself alone.
And by believing only
in his own strength.
I cannot break this
principle for anyone.
-It's exactly because
of your belief in that,
that I'm entrusting him to you.
-It seems you did not
understand what I said.
I'm refusing your
request, Kariya.
-I am asking a
favor of you, Koga.
You have lived through
mind-numbing, endless oceans
of time.
That, and your strength, are
the reasons I came to you.
He is the seed of
hope for us Bounts.
-And what if I still refuse?
-Well, for one thing, we will
have lost a valuable friend.
You don't want that to happen.
His name is Cain.
And that name is all that
he has in this world.
-Indeed.
He is totally lacking
in self respect.
-It will take you a lot of time.
But then, that is something
you have a great deal of.
In your hands, he can
be molded into a person.
-Hm?
What's that?
-It's a book of Doll summoning.
I was finally able
to finish writing it.
My hope is that will allow
a comrade, who does not
have a doll, to succeed in
obtaining that bright light.
Glory to our tribe, my friend.
-Are you leaving?
Where's he going now?
-I feel the same way as
you about being alone.
Spending time with a fellow
Bount is the last thing I want.
Especially with you.
Ah!
Bastard!
You've got a lot of nerve.
What the hell do you
think you're doing?
-If you want to go,
I won't stop you.
But we both, that if that's
all the strength you possess,
you won't survive for very
long out there in the world.
-You go to hell!
-Now that we
understand each other,
come help me with my work.
[music playing]
How much will you
give me for this?
-Hm.
Well, this is very good.
Top quality.
How about 50, for all of them.
-That'll do.
Is that enough for the coat?
-Let's see.
Yes, that'll be fine, sir.
-You'll need a coat.
-This is for me?
-It gets very cold
here this time of year.
And you can't train if
your body is freezing.
-You know it's kind of funny?
-Yeah, what is it?
-I really want to thank you.
I realize now, being brought
to you was a good thing for me.
Up until that day I
first came to you,
I was living a kind
of life that I'm
ashamed to even think about now.
And even after I
came here, I know
that I wasn't very appreciative.
-You still must
learn to be proud
that you were born
a Bount, Cain.
-Be proud?
Hey!
Wait for me!
-Wow.
That's a pretty nice
coat you got there, kid.
-You ought to just hand it over.
You wouldn't want to
get blood on it now.
-And what's that
supposed to mean?
-No, Cain.
It's not worth wasting your
breath, talking to them.
-Watch it, old man.
-I'll show him.
Let's see how you like this.
-Think you're pretty tough, huh?
What the hell are you, anyway?
-Come, Cain.
-But what about the--
-It doesn't matter.
[nature sounds]
Hm?
-Hm.
[shouting]
-Bad luck.
They're coming after us.
[shouting]
-Not so brave now, are you?
Forest monsters like
you should no enough
to stay in the forest.
-You'll never show
your ugly faces again,
once we're through with you.
It's time to end this!
-That is true.
Zeige Dich.
Dalk.
[confused muttering]
-Did you call for me?
-Take care of them.
-Very well.
It's been awhile, but they
shouldn't be much of a problem.
-What is that thing?
[music playing]
-Incredible!
So this is your doll?
-Ha!
Ha!
You're still all
alone, aren't you?
-But don't worry.
Someday you'll have
a doll as well.
Don't think of yourself
as some stray dog.
You are a chosen human.
You are a Bount.
-I am a chosen human.
I am a Bount.
[grunting]
-Cain.
That's enough for today.
-It's OK.
I'm not tired.
-All right, then.
What is it you want to do,
when you're strong enough?
-When I'm doing training?
-Yes.
-Well, I really
want to be like you.
Also, if you'll let me, I'd like
to stay here and live with you.
I've learned from you how
to enjoy training my body,
and cooking and washing clothes.
And, well, the cleaning
isn't so much fun,
but I've realized that
these are all good things
to know about and do.
For the first time, I
feel like I'm alive.
-Is that so?
-Yeah, anyway.
-If that is the case,
then it may be about time
that you had a doll of your own.
-My own doll?
-The steps that one
must take to gain a doll
are here in this book.
The Book of Doll
Summoning was written
by Master Kariya himself.
-The Book of Doll Summoning.
-If you raise it
properly, your doll
can become a great ally, who
will help and understand you.
-Wow!
-However, when we decide you are
ready, I will do the summoning.
Whatever you do, don't
try this on your own.
-All right.
-But it was too soon.
Everything was too soon for him.
I am the one who killed him.
-Faithful.
Phosphor.
Colinstoph.
Und wasser.
Und fett.
Magnesium.
Caulk.
Salbershpuk, fuher deladu.
Oh great power, in
the name of my tribe,
graced with eternal life.
I now ask you for a way
to personify your power.
Awaken, awaken and
give your birth cry
with the crimson fire.
If you will do this, I
shall offer you my life,
as a token of my
heat's integrity.
At this moment, our
hearts stretch across
different worlds, and welcome
the moment when we become one.
Zeige Meine Doll.
Oh!
-Cain!
-Master.
Look.
I finally have a doll of my own.
Look at her.
Look at how small
and beautiful she is.
Just watch this now.
I'm going to give her some
orders, and she'll obey!
-Don't do that, Cain.
You can't control
what will happen.
-No, I can do it.
It'll be all right.
All I have to do is speak
to her kindly, like this.
And I'm sure she'll respond.
Open your eyes now, my doll.
Wake up and speak to me,
just the way Dalk would do.
-Ah.
I'm tired.
I still want to sleep.
-Oh please don't say that.
I need you to lend me your
power, for just a little bit.
Just a little while.
Won't you do that, please.
-Well, first show me your power.
I won't do anything
until you do that.
-Huh?
Show you my power?
-Yes.
-But I don't know how.
-Then I will test you.
-Hm.
-Cain!
Get away from it, quickly!
[screaming]
Cain!
-Master.
Master!
What's happening?
I'm not ready to die, yet.
-Cain!
No, don't tell me.
Cain.
[wind blowing]
[weeping]
-Please forgive me.
I lost the life of
an important comrade.
I am to blame.
[birds calling]
-I had hoped to have a chance
to show this to Cain someday.
The break of dawn.
-Yes.
-Bounts should no
longer live alone.
This sadness is much too painful
for us to bear in isolation.
We should live
together from now on.
-Yes.
And ever since that day,
Kariya has been my leader.
-This one refuses to die.
-Monster.
Just what is it you hope
to accomplish, anyway?
-Kariya's plans for this world
are actually very simple.
He wants to create
a new, clean, world.
A world that will
be ruled by Bounts.
-What are you talking about?
-When a Bount gains power by
sucking the souls from living
humans, it also
increases the power
of all the other Bounts, because
of the multiplier effect.
Soon we will rule the world.
-That's what you think.
I'm not about to let you use
Keigo's life for that purpose.
-It's useless to defy us.
Admit that you cannot defeat
the Bounts, young man.
-No, never!
-The fire in your
eyes spells danger.
Such power without
principle is dangerous.
You must understand, or die.
-Go to hell.
No matter what you say,
I want let Keigo die.
-Why am I destined,
again and again,
to witness the deaths
of young ones, who
forfeit their bright futures?
Farewell, young one.
-So, you want me to finish him?
-Do it now.
Hm?
Who's there?
-So then.
You are a Bount, are you?
From the Court Guard Squads, I'm
Squad 3 Lieutenant, Izuru Kira.
[them music]
-Orihime, we have to fight
together in this battle.
-This will be the first
time we've worked together.
Well then, you must be the
bridegroom and I'm the bride.
Or in this case, maybe
I'm the bridegroom
and you're the bride.
I know!
Could it be that we're
both the bridegroom?
-What in the world
are you talking about?
[theme music]
-[inaudible] the Soul Reapers.
-Golden.
In the world sorely
lacking justice,
I shall become justice itself.
Then will I erase
the world's evil,
like clouds in the night sky.
I risk it all, for justice.
Cry, Suzumushi!
-Aren't Bitto bugs
amazing little suckers?
-They sure are.