[MUSIC - BEAT CRUSADERS,
"TONIGHT, TONIGHT, TONIGHT"]
[crashing]
RIRIN: Emergency!
Emergency everyone!
-Ah!
-Danger, danger!
Warning!
Emergency, emergency!
[mumbling]
-Ichigo's in terrible trouble.
We've got to save him!
I tried to get here to alert
you as fast as I could,
but this stuffed buffoon
Kon got lost on the way
and it took us forever.
-Listen!
Ichigo needs us now! [cries]
URAHARA: Ririn, calm down now.
Calm down.
There's nothing to worry about.
Ichigo is fine.
-Sorry to worry you.
I was just so desperate to save
Keigo I left you behind, Ririn.
RIRIN: You insensitive idiot!
I was going crazy!
-Well, I didn't mean
to get you so upset.
-Oh, you've got a
lot of nerve to think
I'd be upset and concerned
about the likes of you.
-Sorry.
But, thank you anyway.
--[crying] You're
welcome, you stupid clod!
-Take it easy.
There's nothing to
be so upset about.
-Shut up!
-Come on, now.
You have to decide if
you're angry or just sad.
-[crying]
-Hey, Hanataro.
How's Keigo?
-He should be up
and around soon.
I was able to inject him
with some of your Reishi,
and that helped him
recover quickly.
I also went ahead and
replaced his memories.
So after just a
little more rest,
he should be able to go home
soon, like nothing happened.
-That's good.
Thanks Hanataro.
[door opening]
TESSAI: Excuse me.
All of the others
have just returned.
-About time you--
Rukia, what happened?
-It's nothing.
I'll be fine in a day or so.
-I am responsible
for Rukia's injuries.
I was there and
failed to protect her.
-Don't worry, though.
I'll tend to Rukia's
wounds myself, Ichigo.
-That's all right, Orihime.
The way you saved me in the
battle was more than enough.
Besides, you have your
own injuries to tend to.
You're covered in cuts.
-Oh, these?
It doesn't hurt.
-Enough, enough.
Let's go inside and get
everyone comfortable.
-Judging by your speed, I
assume you found the Bounts.
SHUHEI: Yes.
Apparently, while we
were busy fighting them,
Yumichicka was searching for
the Bounts hideout on his own.
RANGIKU: What happened
to Ichigo and the others?
-They're safe.
They have all gathered to
recuperate from their wounds
at Urahara's.
-Good.
In that case, we should
go join Yumichicka.
It's time we settled
this once and for all.
MABASHI: I made a mistake.
-Well, it's not serious.
And besides, you were able
to exercise your powers.
Even though you sucked
only a few living souls,
that's pretty good.
MABASHI: It still wasn't
enough-- nowhere near enough.
-Mabashi, don't get addicted.
I guarantee that you'll
live to regret it.
KARIYA: It's all right.
You did well, Mabashi.
Don't be too hard on yourself
over a single defeat.
-I didn't lose.
In fact, I have
never been defeated.
I would have beaten them,
except he stopped me.
-You would have
been turned to sand
if you had continued to fight.
And you know it.
-You don't know what
you're talking about.
You have no idea
what my limits are!
-They are coming.
Don't panic.
All of you are to
continue as you
were, using the Bittos
to absorb souls.
Ugaki.
-Yes, Master Kariya.
Is it time for me to
make an appearance?
-First a question.
-Yes, what's that?
-What's the status of the
young Quincy we encountered?
[laughs]
-He seems to be struggling.
He hasn't been able to
regain any of his powers.
-I see.
Go, then.
-As you wish, Master.
And may I suggest to all of
you that you watch carefully,
as I can guarantee you
will not be disappointed.
I shall give a demonstration
that will be truly magnificent.
The performance
shall begin soon.
-Ichinose.
-Sir?
-What about the other matter?
-Yes.
They'll soon make
their move as well.
-So be it.
-Are you sure?
-Mhm.
-Ah!
But that's impossible!
You must have done
something wrong.
He should be getting
better by now.
-Hey, Renji.
What the hell are
you doing to him?
RUKIA: Leave him alone, Renji.
-Stay out of it.
You're supposed to
be resting, anyway.
RUKIA: How am I supposed
to rest with fool like you
starting fights in the house?
Why can't you just act
normal for a change?
-Hey.
-Hanataro, so what's happening?
-Well, unfortunately,
this boy's injuries
are much worse than I
first thought they were.
I've tried my best
and done everything
I can think of, but--
-What are you saying?
-It seems like his
soul just keeps
getting weaker and weaker.
-How sad.
-Well, then, why don't you
try using my soul, Hanataro?
I'm fine.
I don't have any
serious injuries at all.
Let me do the same
thing Ichigo did for him
-We can't.
Unfortunately, it's
already too late for that.
All we can do now is trust
in the boy's own life force
to bring him back.
RENJI: It's all my fault.
I should have handled things
differently during the attack.
If only I had handled
the situation better,
he wouldn't be in this shape.
-Calm down, Renji.
-And just shut up!
-Listen, Lieutenant Matsumoto
and the others are on their way
right now.
And they're going to
confront the Bounts.
I understand your feelings.
But if we charge into this
with our personal emotions
getting in the way, things
really aren't going to go well.
-Damn.
-Look, the boy's
going to be all right.
I'm sure of it.
-Thanks, Ichigo.
-In the Soul Society, when
I thought I couldn't go on,
it was Hanataro who saved me.
We should trust him.
And then you and I can focus
on fighting these guys.
We can't just keep letting
the Bounts get away
with whatever the
hell they want.
-Ha.
Well, I must be getting
pretty soft lately
if you're the one
giving me the lectures.
-What do you mean by that?
URAHARA: Ichigo, can I
talk to you for a minute?
Would you agree that the Bounts
are stronger than we originally
expected?
-Yeah, I'd say so.
-Do you think you can win
without having your Bankai?
-It's strange, but even though
I can use my Bankai-- how do
I explain it?
I have this feeling I
can almost use it again.
I'm gonna be all right.
-I sure hope so.
Very well, my friend.
Then I'll leave it up to you.
-[sigh]
Hm?
-What are you
doing standing here
in front of the Bounts' hideout?
-What would you
have done if they'd
learned you were out
here by yourself?
-Well, it's too late for that.
They already know I'm here.
I hate to admit it,
but apparently we
have a formidable opponent
here in the Bounts.
-Pssh.
-All right.
Let's do this.
-I should tell you
that I've never
been very good
working in a group.
BYAKUYA: I see.
But--
YAMAMOTO: It is hard
to believe, I know.
But it is true nonetheless.
You know me well enough
to know that I would not
have called you here otherwise.
Captain Kurotsuchi may think
he can make a fool of me.
But he cannot.
No matter how hard he
may try to hide it,
something dangerous
is happening here ,
a devastatingly destructive
movement is in the works.
And it is related to
last night's ruckus.
Somewhere right here
in the very midst of us
there is a traitor
among the Soul Reapers.
-Could it be Sosuke Aizen again?
-We cannot entirely rule
out the possibility of that.
But I think it unlikely that he
would want to help the Bounts.
-Then--
-We know exactly how many
Soul Reapers have left us.
Soon we will have
investigated all of them.
That aside, I have a favor
I would like to ask of you.
As you know, of the
four great noble clans,
it is the Kuchiki clan
that has traditionally
been charged with
compiling and protecting
the Soul Society's history.
In those stories,
can you tell me,
do any records of
the Bounts exist?
I would like you to
research the matter for me.
-As you wish.
-Hey, Kon.
Are you coming, too?
-What do you think?
My sweet Rukia is going off
to kick some serious butt,
isn't she?
Of course I'm going with her.
And by the way, I'm sick
of you underestimating me.
I'm the one who's been
protecting her, not you.
-You know, he might come
in handy as a shield!
-What!
Oh.
-Ririn, Kurodo, Noba.
This is going to
be your assignment.
-You can count on us!
-We won't let you down, Master.
-Understood.
-Hey, you big moocher.
-What's this.
-Just some rice, you know.
I know what a pain you can be
when you're hungry, so just
take that with you.
-Mr. Moocher, Jinta made
that especially for you,
because he felt bad he
couldn't give you seconds--
-Ah!
No one wants to hear
your details, all right?
-Ow.
-Hm.
Thanks a lot, little man.
Hey, Hanataro.
-Yes?
-You take good care of that kid.
-I will.
I'll do my best.
-All right.
Let's go.
-It feels wrong somehow to let
them head out alone like this.
-From time to time, we
encounter challenges
where that is all we can do.
-Now then, it's time
to begin the game.
Zeige Dich, Gesell.
-Wait.
What's this?
-I'm getting an ugly
feeling about this.
-All right.
Let's go.
-What's that?
-Looks like an advance party
of four Soul Reapers being
led on a journey to
their own deaths.
But first, a little
test is in order.
-What do you think
this thing is for?
-Whatever it's for, it's
certainly no think of beauty.
-Look, there's
another one over here.
-Strange.
RANGIKU: They must
just be decoration.
SHUHEI: You're right.
Come on.
Let's keep moving.
-Huh?
We shouldn't have
let our guard down.
-Yumichicka!
-Where the hell did
all this come from?
-[laugh]
-Guess we're surrounded.
You think we should split up?
-That would give
us an advantage.
-Let's go, Shuhei.
--[laughs] Exactly
what I was hoping for.
RANGIKU: Roar, Haineko!
No one there.
[gasp]
-One down already.
[laughs]
SHUHEI: This way!
No good.
It's a dead end.
-Ah!
-Izuru!
-[grunting]
IZURU (VOICEOVER):
Something's keeping
the head from attacking him.
Maybe it can't come
out any further.
-Hado Four, Byakurai.
-Very well.
Then how about this?
[grunting]
[shouting]
-[laughs]
[laughs] Only one left.
YUMICHICKA: These things
sure are ugly, not beautiful
in any way.
I really don't
appreciate such things.
Now, bloom, Fuju Kugaku!
-Gesell, show him what your true
form is for just a few moments.
That should finish this.
-[gasp] [shout]
-[laughs evilly]
-What was that?
-It would seem that
it's already begun.
ICHIGO: Then let's go.
-Don't squeeze too tight.
Must pull straight back and
then release with my heart.
[sigh] Master, I--
[wind blowing]
-You?
-It has been quite
a while, has it not?
[theme music]
KON: Today, we're going to show
the faces of all the remaining
Bounts.
Gorilla man, scary old lady,
gross dude, grandpa fish eater,
old man with glasses,
and the big shot.
All together, that's, um, five.
RIRIN: That's six.
What are you, stupid?
ICHIGO: [sigh] This
nonsense is only
making things more confusing.
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers.
GROUP: Golden!
ICHIGO: Let's go.
-Wait, hold on a second.
-What is it?
-Well, I can't start fighting
until I've had something
to eat.
-Ah, the lunch Jinta
gave you earlier.
-Damn, we don't
have time for this.
-Shut up!
How am I supposed to have any
energy for battling Bounts
if I don't eat first?
[scream]
-Ah, this rice has flaming
hot chili peppers in it.
ICHIGO: Well, at least
he'll have his energy.