[theme song]
[gasping]
-Damn.
The pain's getting worse.
And I can hardly lift
my arms and legs.
The reiatsu is fading away.
I guess my time as a Quincy
has about reached it's end.
Wouldn't it be funny,
if after all this,
I somehow got to
the Senzaikyu first.
What if I was the one
who rescued Rukia?
Oh, I bet that would
really piss off Ichigo.
Everyone knows he wants
to be the big hero,
and rescue her all by himself.
-I'm sorry.
But for the sake of peace,
I must terminate you.
Cry, Suzumushi.
[gasp]
-Forgive me, Ryoka.
But these senseless battles
have to come to an end.
Rest now, for your
struggle will soon be over.
-Advancing from Shikai
to Bankai typically
requires well over 10
years of training, even
for those with
exceptional talent.
However, you must
achieve the Bankai
in a time span of
only three days.
-What's with the
weird looking cut out?
-It's tenchintei, an
important spiritual tool,
used by the Stealth Force.
It's specifically designed
to draw out the Zanpakuto,
and manifest its true form.
-Huh?
I don't get what you're saying.
How is that supposed to help
me complete my Bankai training?
-The Shikai must establish
a dialogue and a harmony
with the Zanpakuto.
The manifestation and
submission of the Zanpakuto
is necessary for Bankai.
In other words, instead
of us physically
entering the world
of the Zanpakuto,
manifestation refers to
summoning the Zanpakuto
into our world.
Normally, it requires several
years of training to do this.
But you, even though
it ended in a draw,
you founght on equal footing
with Kenpachi Zaraki.
So as unlikely as
it might seem, it
appears that you've actually
reached manifestation,
or a comparable level, already.
-Do you want to fight?
-It's coming back
to you, isn't it?
If you stab this
with Zangetsu, it
can forcibly bring it
into the manifested state.
In other words, we can bring
the Zanpakuto into this world.
However, with this
method, the manifestation
is a limited to three days.
During that time, you must
defeat the manifested Zangetsu
and force him into submission.
If you're unable to do that--
-You don't have to
go into the details.
If you're saying there's no
other way it can be done,
then I've got to do it.
[thunder]
-It seems to be recovered
quite nicely, Ichigo.
-So it's you.
-I take it you heard
our conversation.
-Of course.
-Then I'll leave the method
of fighting up to you.
I assume that you
can start right away.
-Of course.
-What, what the
heck did he just do?
-Somewhere amongst
these swords, there
is one that is the true me.
That is the only
that can defeat me.
The others are useless.
If you wish to force
me into submission,
you'll have to find
a way to locate it
before I can kill you.
And then, try to defeat me.
If you can.
[music playing]
-I can't believe it!
[shouting]
-They wiped out the whole squad.
We're walking wounded here.
Now let me give you a hand.
-Greetings, everyone.
And welcome.
It's I, Squad 4, third>
Seat, Yasochika Iemura.
I'm so glad you could make it.
What?
You don't know me?
You may have seen
me here or there.
I get around.
Since it appears some of you
are not familiar with me,
perhaps a fitting
introduction would
be to acquaint you with me
medical journal, in which I
have chronicled our Squad
Force strenuous activities.
Lately, due to the recent
reopen disturbance,
our Squad Four stations
is in daily chaos.
Especially considering
the recent plethora of men
from Squad 11, who
have been hospitalized.
Seriously, they have
kept us very busy.
As if it that wasn't bad
enough, yesterday evening
the Captains from Squad
8 and 13 requested
to have a Ryoka admitted.
As a result, the
entire squad has
been forced to implement
the triple shift emergency
protocol.
Things have gotten out of hand.
The squad's already
stretched thin,
and on top of that, being
asked to admit a Ryoka?
It's just incomprehensible.
Really, enough is enough.
Why anyone would want some Ryoka
to be hospitalized and treated
in the first place, it's
completely beyond me.
It's not as if dealing with
Squad 13's Captain Ukitake
wasn't enough of a challenge, we
got Captain Kyoraku of Squad 8
running around, chasing
women all over the place.
Not to mention the
trashy way he dresses,
and how he's always asleep
when you need something.
I'll never get how someone like
that became a captain while I--
-Uh, sir?
-What is it, nurse?
-We just received a request
from Captain Tosen of Squad 9.
He would like us to admit
a Ryoka for treatment.
-I see.
-And, uh-
-Hm?
-Sorry, but you were
thinking out loud again.
-Ah!
Well, of course it
goes without saying
that I have nothing but the
utmost respect for Captain
Kyoraku.
-In light, of all this evidence,
that they had no choice
and was held against
his will by the Ryoka,
that he was so
physically and mentally
brutalized by those
Ryoka, so brainwashed
that he had no choice but
to obey, it's a tragedy.
And as such, I wish that you,
Captain Unohana of Squad 4,
will judge this with
kindness and compassion.
This concludes the arrest
and investigation report
of this matter, delivered by
Captain Ukitake of Squad 13.
-I understand.
However, nothing in the
report changes the fact
that you aided the Ryoka, and
that the damage they caused
was substantial.
One must always be
accountable for one's actions,
and from the standpoint of
your tank and responsibilities,
I cannot condone your actions.
Do you understand?
14th Advanced Relief
Group Leader and Squad 4,
Seventh Seat, Hanataro Yamada.
-Hm?
-Hanataro, what is it?
-I'm beginning to wonder
if everything that I did
was a mistake.
If after all this,
I just ended up
creating more trouble
for Rukia instead.
-I don't know.
No one does.
But I believe you
listened to your heart,
and acted on what your
true feelings told you.
I wish I could be that strong.
-Lieutenant.
-We'll have to trust
Captain Unohana.
It's in her hands, now.
-Mhm.
[music playing]
-Time to go, Zabimaru.
[crying]
-I drew my sword against Momo.
How could I?
I'm wretched and disgusting.
I hate myself.
[screaming]
Snap to me.
Deflect!
-Raise your head
and prepare to die.
[crying]
-Who, who's there?
-My, this is just awful.
I almost can't bear to look.
-Captain Ichimaru?
-You look so haggard,
you poor thing.
Would you like me to help you?
Would you, Izuru?
-Stand up, Ichigo.
Three days.
You don't have time to
lie around feeling sorry
for yourself.
I'll tell you one more time,
up on your feet, Ichigo.
Stop stalling.
How much time do
you plan on wasting?
-Never mind.
If he hasn't the strength
to stand on his own,
then I'll just grab his scrawny
neck and drag him to his feet.
-Surprised?
I'll say I was surprised!
I never would have
guessed in a million years
that Lieutenant Kusajishi
would pick me up like that.
You may not believe this,
but I, Makizo Aramaki,
couldn't be happier.
-I hate to break it to you, but
I didn't really care about you.
-Can't you see that I'm
trying to rescue you here?
Ouch!
No, cut it out, will you?
Why you!
Take this, there!
Sorry about that.
Oh well, guess I'll owe you
an apology when you wake up.
Huh?
Oh.
-Hey Maki Maki.
What's that you
got under your arm?
That's spiritual pressure.
A Ryoka?
-No.
Well, you see, it's like this.
I was just, well--
-It's a Ryoka.
-I, I, you see, it was
kind of like, what you see,
what happened was, there
was this situation.
-Situation?
Really?
Tell me about it.
-Well it was, it
was kind of like--
-Hm.
-Well, you see, I was just kind
of minding my own business.
When all of a sudden,
out of nowhere, this girl
just squirted out!
-She squirted out?
-Yeah.
She did this weird
bubbly-bubbly thing.
-Bubbly bubbly thing?
-That's right, bubbly.
So I said to myself,
I said, I'd better
snatch her up and bring
her to you, right away.
-Really?
We should take her back
with us, to show the others.
-Huh?
Oh, yeah.
-I can't wait to see her
do the bubbly-bubbly thing.
I'm so excited!
-Yeah, about that.
-I wonder if Ichi does
the bubbly-bubbly thing.
What do you think, Ara, Ara, hm.
I forget.
Would you mind telling me
what your name is again?
-Oh, I don't expect
you to you remember.
After all, it's only been 10
years since you took me on.
Just call me Maki Maki.
Maki Maki's fine.
Plain old Maki Maki.
-Maki Maki.
That name's really weird.
-What do you mean, it's weird?
You're the one who came
up with the nickname!
-So Orihime, why don't you
tell us what's going on.
-She is so gorgeous.
-You think Ichigo's
still alive, or what?
-I hope he's still alive.
He must be.
I'm sure that he is.
-Orihime.
-He's alive, all right.
In fact, I'm certain of it.
He's alive, and he's getting
stronger, even as we speak.
As a matter of fact, I'm
going to help you out.
I get the feeling that
if I stick with you,
I'll see Ichigo again soon.
-Aye, aye, sir!
[music playing]
-Where am I?
Am I still alive?
How did--
[laughter]
-So you're awake.
[yelling]
-What are you?
Who are you?
Where'd you come from?
Are you a burglar?
-Yeah, right.
Why would anyone try to steal
from an injured man in prison?
It's me, you idiot.
-Ganju, is that really?
I don't believe it,
you're still alive!
You didn't look so strong,
so I thought maybe you had--
-I hear what you're saying.
I was thinking the exact
same thing about you.
-I don't get it.
Why would they want to
keep us alive, much less
take time to treat our injuries?
I mean, we're intruders here.
Not to mention their enemies.
I must be missing
something, because I
can't think of a
single reason why
the Soul Society would want to--
-The situation has changed.
-Sado!
-I overheard a couple of the
guards talking outside the cell
today.
Apparently a Captain
was assassinated
within the Seireitei.
They don't know who did it.
-Really?
-Since we're intruders
here, that would obviously
make us prime
suspects in the case.
-They're keeping us alive so
they can question us later.
-That sounds about right.
If only these things didn't
seal off my spiritual pressure.
I could use my seppa
and we could bust out
of this place with
no problem at all.
-I see.
These seal in the
spiritual pressure.
-Exposure to such a strong
flame will burn thee.
And even though
removing the glove
will allow you to temporarily
gain enormous power, when that
fades away, you will lose
your Quincy powers completely.
-No.
Even without this, my spiritual
pressure has already--
-It sucks.
Even though we survived,
we're stuck in this prison
with our spiritual
pressure sealed.
The situation couldn't
be much worse.
But there's still one
thing we can count on.
If they kept us alive, then
the others are probably alive.
So there's a chance they might
still be out there somewhere.
-Huh?
-However, considering
the fact that they
were able to capture us, they've
probably got Orihime as well.
She's not much of a fighter.
So the only ones left
are Yoruichi and Ichigo.
I'm content to wait here.
Ichigo will come for
us, I'm certain of it.
The best thing for
us to do until then
is to heal our wounds, and
prepare for the next battle.
I say we wait for Ichigo.
[grunting]
-Sword number 18.
[panting]
-That's it!
After all I've been through.
This time, I know this has
got to be the real one.
-Too weak.
[gasping]
-As I told you before, you
must look beyond the metal.
Each of these swords represents
a piece of your heart.
The purpose of this trial is to
find the one piece among them
that was forged for the
solitary purpose of combat.
That one there was
your heart's frailty.
You exposed it by
trying to depend on me.
-I depended on him?
The frailty of my heart?
-If you're incapable
of recognizing that,
then you can forget
about the Bankai forever.
-So all of these are
really my weaknesses.
Dammit.
-Come now, move on
to the next one.
You haven't the time
to be crawling around.
-You're right.
You're absolutely right.
[music playing]
[theme song]
-The Squad 6 jail
has lousy food.
-The Squad 3 jail
doesn't get any sunlight.
-The Squad 5 jail
has cockroaches.
-We prisoners deserve better.
-You nimrods don't
seem to have a clue why
you were put in jail
in the first place.
-Why don't you try it, Toshiro?
-I will not!