[theme music]
-Grimmjow Jaegerjaquez
was defeated
by Ichigo, who came to Hueco
Mundo to rescue Orihime.
But then Espada Number
Five, Nnoitra Gilga,
appeared and challenged him.
Although still injured
from his previous battle,
Ichigo was forced
back into the fight.
Ichigo's mobility
was greatly affected,
and the situation became dire.
-[grunt]
-Such a nice sword.
But it's a real shame
that it only looks sharp.
I shouldn't have
bothered dodging it.
[grunting]
ICHIGO: Oh!
-Ichi.
Oh!
[whimper]
-Are you Nel?
-[gasp]
-Huh?
NARRATOR: Meanwhile,
after coming in contact
with a purple ooze released
by Szayelaporro's Zanpakuto,
Uryu and Renji found
themselves facing off
against their own clones.
Mirror images of themselves
would become their opposition
before they would be able
to face their real enemy.
-Starting to get the
picture now, crybaby?
-Why am I always being
attacked by everyone.
I have no time this.
Someone's out there
waiting for me.
-Waiting?
-Who knows what's
happening to poor Nel?
We have to look
for her right away.
-I know we have to look for Nel!
But we can't do that until
we get out of here first.
-No, please.
Right away.
We have to find her
as soon as possible.
-Hm?
-I've been sensing
it for a while.
She's frightened.
Something terrible is
out there threatening her
and scaring her.
We have to get out of here now!
Please!
We can't let Nel get any
deeper into Las Noches.
-[whimpering]
-I wonder what
possible reason would
you have for coming
back here again?
Did you bring her
here, Soul Reaper?
Don't bother.
I can tell from your
expression that's a yes.
Funny you've been
dragging her around
without ever knowing who she is.
-What?
What do you mean?
NNOITRA: Well, if you
don't know, I'll tell you.
You only know her as Nel.
But her full name is
Nelliel Tu Odelschwank.
She's a former Espada.
-[whimpering]
-[gasp]
-She was an Espada?
-Surprised, huh?
So all this time you thought
she was a helpless orphan.
Such ignorance.
You've all been tricked
by that little witch.
It's an absolute fact.
She's one of the Espadas.
That right, Nelliel?
-It's a lie.
Nel could never be an Espada.
It's not even possible.
-Oh?
Stop all this joking around
and start telling the truth.
Don't try to tell me you've
completely forgotten your past.
-Nel knows it.
Nel knows all her past.
Nel didn't forget.
Nel could never be an Espada.
-Heh.
You know I haven't seen
you in quite a while.
But to me it's obvious that
your as devious as ever.
-Who, Nel?
-You've got them all
tricked into believing
you really need help.
You've used them to bring you
this deep into Las Noches.
-Nel didn't trick
anybody, honest.
Not Nel.
-So why did you come back here?
You must have a reason.
Did you come here
looking like you
do to finally settle
things between us?
-No.
Nel doesn't have a purpose.
Everything's been-- it's
all been fun for Nel
until now, really.
Nel remembers it all as fun.
What'd we do to you?
Stop picking on us, will ya?
-[together] Hm?
-[together] And together we're--
NEL: --the band of
three [inaudible]
DONDOCHAKKA: --the three
brothers of the [inaudible].
ICHIGO: You're not
on the same page.
-We never thought our
game of eternal tag
would cause such a
misunderstanding.
Nel is a masochist.
And it's no fun for Nel, unless
Nel is chased to the point
where Nel starts to cry.
-Why are you teaching this
kid words like masochist?
-Oh, Mr. Soul Reaper,
if you're not bad guys,
then play with us.
OK, here we go.
Let's start.
Tag!
You're it!
-What?
--[laughs] Try to catch Nel,
and then try to beat Nel up
and make Nel cry!
-Why, you little--
-[laughs] Ichigo!
-What the--?
Nel!
-Wait!
Super acceleration!
-[grunt] [shout] Your snot!
Make it stop!
It's touching me!
-Huh?
-Come on, now.
That's gross!
-You almost squished
me to death,
and now you're yelling at me!
I don't think you're very nice!
-All right, whatever you say.
Just stop crying, will ya?
Come on.
NEL: Now we're really
getting somewhere!
Faster, faster!
Nel still wanted to be with
Ichigo and everyone else, too.
It's just Nel didn't want
to say goodbye to them.
-Don't cry, Nel.
-Quit with your heartfelt story.
This little kid thing
you're trying isn't working.
I've blown your cover.
Your lying is over.
-[whimpers]
Nel never lied to you-- never!
Ichigo, please believe Nel.
Nel would never lie to you!
Ichigo!
Ichigo?
-Your blubbering
is so irritating.
I've heard enough.
-[whimper]
[gasping]
-Ichigo?
-We know you, Nel.
Of course you
wouldn't lie to us.
-Ichigo.
-No need for crying.
Me, Orihime-- all
of us trust you.
We don't feel like
you've been using us.
And hey, who cares if
you used to be an Espada?
I believe in the Nel
who's here, right now.
You hear me?
I've had to listen
to your nonsense.
And I've got some news for you.
I won't let you touch her.
-Ha!
Don't make me laugh.
[shout]
-[grunt]
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
It's sure heavy.
-Just what makes you
think you can stop me?
You can't, Soul Reaper.
[fighting noises]
-Ichigo!
-Ha!
Perhaps you really have lost
your memory of the old days.
I mean, it's possible.
After all, I did split your
head pretty well back then.
Maybe you couldn't avoid
losing your memory after that.
-[whiimper]
-Hold it.
You said you split her head?
-I did.
I'm the one who did it to her.
I'm the one who
cracked her skull.
-Nel, watch out!
-Stop it!
[grunting]
-Ah!
NNOITRA: You're not
worried about yourself?
You've forgotten, haven't you?
Your sword can't cut me,
so how will you stop me?
-[grunt]
-Oh no, Ichigo!
-[whimper]
-You always annoyed me.
You are becoming almost
as annoying as she is.
ICHIGO: Don't you
even touch her!
-That's why I threw
her out of Las Noches
after I was able to
sneak up behind her
and split her skull open.
-I told you not to go near her!
-You shut your mouth!
-[shout]
-Trying again, you loser?
-[grunt]
-What the hell is your story?
you can't beat me.
Why don't you understand that?
No matter how many times
you try to, it's useless.
-It doesn't matter to me
whether I beat you or not.
-Really?
-I will protect Nel no
matter what happens to me.
And that's all there is to it.
-Then you have chosen to die.
-He's coming.
-Heh.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
He's too fast!
-[shout]
-Please stop this now!
-It's over.
After that hit, your
Soul Reaper friend
won't be moving much anymore.
-[grunt]
-Sorry I kept you waiting, Nel.
Now it's your turn.
-[whimper]
-Wait a second.
This fight isn't finished yet.
You heard me.
While I'm alive, I will
not let you get near her.
-Such persistence.
-[fighting noises]
-Ichigo!
-You're lucky
you're still alive.
I hate your kind.
You just keep attacking
even though you
know you don't have
a chance to win.
-[groaning]
-No, Ichigo.
-Now let's end
this, Soul Reaper.
-[shouting]
-Ichigo, Ichigo.
-[shout]
-Ichigo.
What has Nel done?
Poor Ichigo.
[cries] Ichigo!
[gasping]
-Uh, are you sensing
this, P-- P-- Pesche?
-Yes.
-What's up?
URYU (VOICEOVER):
I remember this,
this spiritual pressure I sense.
-Huh?
I don't feel a thing.
[gasping]
-What's wrong with you guys?
-That's definitely it.
The spiritual pressure--
it belongs to Master Nel!
-Nel?
-Is that Nel?
-So, Nel, you've reverted
to your old form, have you?
Why, you.
ICHIGO: Nel?
Are you really the same Nel?
-I am.
Thanks to you, Ichigo, I was
able to return to my old self
again.
-You said thanks to me?
-Yes.
When I was in my
smaller form, you always
made the choice to protect me.
And then you brought me
all the way here with you.
Please stay still for bit.
I will protect you.
-Wait, Nel!
By protect, you don't mean--
don't stand there and tell me
that you're planning
to fight this guy!
-Don't be worried.
It'll be over
before you know it.
-[gasp]
You witch!
[shout]
[laugh]
[shout] What? [shout]
-Master Nnoitra!
-Wow, she's fast.
[fighting noises]
-Damn, she's strong.
-Not a chance!
NEL: Over here.
[shout]
-[grunting]
-I can't believe it.
-Is that the real Nel?
-[shout]
-It's a Cero, Nel!
-Impossible!
Damn her.
-[shout]
-Eh?
-What the hell was that?
-Huh?
Wait.
Did you hear that?
-No, I didn't.
But are you going
to tell me you don't
feel a sudden sense of anxiety?
Sure, I'm feeling anxious.
That's why my stomach
just produced that--
-Quit with that.
-That spiritual pressure
didn't belong to Ichigo.
But it definitely was
an intense output.
[gasping]
-Master Nnoitra!
-Are you all right?
Just a minute.
I'll hear you in a second.
Huh?
-Nel.
-Ichigo!
How great!
I'm so relieved
you're all right!
-Hey, wait a minute.
Hold on, Nel.
I mean, Ms. Nel.
You're crushing poor Ichigo.
Nel, quit it!
I mean, Ms. Nel.
His eyes have rolled
back and that's not good.
You're gonna kill him!
-[whimper]
-Oh!
Don't die!
-Ms. Nel, you're doing it again!
-Oh.
-[grunt]
-Who the hell told you
to release the girl?
-Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
NNOITRA: What is it?
I thought this was going
to be over quickly,
but I guess not, huh, Nelliel?
After all, you hit me with
the Cero that you absorbed,
combined with one of your own.
I can see in your eyes you're
asking yourself, why am I
still alive?
It had totally slipped
my mind, Cero Doble
being a specialty of yours.
I should have played
it more carefully.
But there is something
you've forgotten as well.
Many years have gone
by since he disappeared
from this place, my dear.
Don't tell me are
under the impression
that the Espada's
rankings are still
the same after all
this time has passed!
-Ichigo, you need to rest.
-But wait, shouldn't I--
-No, it's all right.
He's all mine.
This time, it's my turn
to protect you, Ichigo.
-Now I'll teach you a lesson.
You are about to learn firsthand
that the number you have
on your back is
totally meaningless.
[theme music]
URYU: I've sensed this
spiritual pressure for a while.
PESCHE: Yes.
You see, Master Nel is
actually a magical girl
who can transform into an
adult just by using a stick.
DONDOCHAKKA: And Pesche and
I are Nel's cute mascots,
who also double as her
personal sidekicks.
PESCHE: Don't lie.