[theme music]
-Take her and go!
Get her to safety!
Take her far away from here.
-Huh?
-That's your duty.
Protect her with your life.
-Renji.
-Renji?
-Don't just stand there
watching, you fool.
Go!
All lieutenants after them!
-Mm.
-Yes, sir.
-Go ahead.
-Right.
[gasping]
-Now run!
Itegumo!
-Bite.
Gonryomaru.
-Crush him!
Gegetsuburi!
-Huh?
ISANE (VOICEOVER):
It's impossible.
He's not even using
his Zanpakuto.
-I can see your moves,
Byakuya Kuchiki.
BYAKUYA: Tell me why.
-Hm?
-Why don't you just give up?
You keep trying to save
Rukia again and again.
ICHIGO: You're her
brother, aren't you?
So the question that
needs to be asked
is why the hell aren't
you trying to save her?
-Such a foolish question.
Even if I did have
the time to try
to explain the principle
to you, someone
like you would
never understand it.
It seems talking
serves no purpose.
Prepare to die.
[grunting]
-[shout]
BYAKUYA: There is only
one path before me.
I shall kill you,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
And then, once again,
I will capture Rukia.
And this time I shall
execute her myself.
-I won't let you do that.
That's the reason why I'm here.
-Renji, stop!
Put me down.
I've got to go back
there and help Ichigo.
-What part of our running
like hell for our lives
do you not understand?
Just try to keep that big
mouth of yours shut, all right?
(SHOUTING) We don't want
anybody hearing out voices!
-If one of our voices gets
us caught, it won't be mine.
RENJI: Explain something to me.
RUKIA: What?
-Well, one time, Ichigo told
me that he owed you a favor.
-He owes a favor to me?
RENJI: Uh-huh.
ICHIGO: You know, Rukia
actually saved my life in a way.
She changed my destiny.
That much is true.
If I hadn't met
Rukia, I never would
have become a Soul
Reaper, the ability
I have to fight the
way I do, and to be
able to protect everyone.
I owe her.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
Because of me,
Ichigo's fate has been changed.
I've put him in terrible danger.
And nothing I do can ever
make amends for that.
-Why are you blaming
yourself for everything?
It's pointless.
You've always been like that.
No one else thinks
this is all your fault.
So why don't you quit
being so hard on yourself?
No one person could
be strong enough
to carry all of
that responsibility
on their shoulders.
Certainly not you, Rukia.
Share it.
Share that burden with
Ichigo and with me.
Let us lighten your load until
you get your strength back.
That is the whole reason we
both made ourselves stronger.
Just have a little
faith in him, Rukia.
Huh?
RUKIA: I'm sorry, Renji.
RENJI: Don't be foolish.
You don't have anything
to apologize for.
-Thank you.
-Heh.
Silly girl.
There's no need to
say thank you, either.
Isane me
KIYONE: Isane.
Isane!
-Wait, Kiyone!
Don't!
[shout]
[gasping]
-No one move.
-But Captain Yamamoto.
-This crime-- a lieutenant
freeing a convicted criminal
and aiding in her
escape-- will be
solved by capturing
the treasonous officer
and putting him to death.
Thus, his fate is sealed.
But that is the least
of our problems.
What you two captains
have done here today
is a crime of far
greater magnitude.
Surely you both understand that
your actions are unforgivable!
-[gasp] Captain Ukitake.
You're in danger, Captain.
Get--
-Kiyone, stay back!
-Well, guess we've
got no choice.
Are you ready, Jushiro?
Looks like we're going to
have to make a run for it.
-Oh, Shunsui.
UKITAKE: Wait, Shunsui!
I can't abandon my squad!
KYORAKU: Just calm down.
Did you really want to fight old
man Yama with all those others
around?
If we did that, a lot of people
would have ended up dead.
Now it's only the two
of us-- for the moment.
Can't you feel it?
There's one more on our
side who's getting closer.
You'd better concentrate.
We're almost to the ground.
-Oh, Captain.
-How dare you stand there and
do nothing while they get away.
Traitorous scum.
With your filthy treason,
you and your bastard captain
and all the others
have brought shame
on the 13 Court Guard Squads.
-Ah!
-But rest assured, I'm going
to put you out of your misery.
You will never betray anyone
ever again, once you're dead!
-Ah!
-Let go of me!
And who the hell
are you, anyway?
-Such a fuss.
I see you haven't changed.
You have a quick temper,
just like you always used to.
-It can't be you!
It can't be you.
Yoruichi.
-Well, long time
no see, Sui-Feng.
-[grunt]
-How are you feeling, Isane?
Any pain?
Captain, I'm so sorry.
The Ryoka was ju--
UNOHANA: Easy, easy.
It's all right, Isane.
You were not hit as
hard as the others,
but you still
mustn't move around
too much until you've recovered.
Take us down now, Minazuki.
-Captain, we just
heard what happened.
Is the Lieutenant injured?
Were you hurt took ma'am?
What are your orders.
-We're all right.
Release the other
and return, Minazuki.
[groaning]
-Most of their wounds
are not life threatening.
The time spent in
Minazuki's belly
has accelerated the
healing process.
Take them to the relief
station and monitor them
until they awaken.
-Yes, Captain.
-Who is still up there?
Such strong spiritual pressure.
-Captain Kuchiki
is there, battling
against the Ryoka
who knocked you out.
The other captains
have all gone elsewhere
and are now fighting
among themselves.
Unfortunately, there's nothing
we can do now to stop them.
Come with me, Isane.
Right this way,
there's a certain place
that I would like to visit.
KYORAKU: That should do it.
We're pretty far
away from everything.
UKITAKE: Yes, far enough to be
out of danger-- for a while,
at least.
-Hey, Nanao, slow poke.
-You didn't have to leave
me back there, Captain.
[gasp]
-I must say, you got here
quicker than I expected you to.
-Chasing children.
It's been many years
since any mere juvenile
delinquent could
get away from me.
Let us finish this!
But I shall be using
far more than my fists.
NANAO (VOICEOVER): Head Captain
Genruysai Shigekuni Yamamoto.
Leader of Squad One.
Head Captain of all the
13 Court Guard Squads.
His spiritual
pressure is enormous.
Even two captains
together may not
be strong enough to
defeat such a man.
I must help them.
There's Only one thing I can do.
-[gasps]
-Listen well.
Be gone from here!
I have neither the
time nor the patience
to teach a mere infant
like you how to breathe.
-Take it easy,
now, little Nanao.
It's gonna be OK.
I'm so sorry.
I shouldn't have let you
follow us in the first place.
NANAO (VOICEOVER):
I can't believe it.
All he did was look
straight into my eyes,
and he completely
crushed my whole being.
I was so naive to
think I could help
Captain Ukitake and my captain.
I was worried that they would
have trouble defeating the head
captain.
Now I don't think
it's even possible.
-Please be all
right, my captain.
-Your flash step is impressive.
Obviously, you've worked
long and hard on it
to be able to cover so
much ground so quickly.
-Well, thank you.
YAMAMOTO: Looking
back, the two of you
always exhibited
exceptional strength.
You spent too much time
chasing girls, Shunsui,
and your behavior was wild.
But you were intelligent.
And your ability to
see the truth far
outshone that of the
others in your class.
And you, Jushiro, you
had a weak constitution.
But you more than made up
for it with your daring
and your popularity.
Everyone looked up to you.
And when it came
time to battle, you
both defied the imagination.
No one else could hold a
candle to either one of you.
You had such strong
will-- training endlessly,
continuously holding
your strength.
My faith in you
was rewarded when
you became the first captains of
this Academy, which I created.
You are my pride and
joy, like my own sons.
I believed in you.
And though we might have
thought different thoughts,
I always felt that we
walked the same path.
Now it appears I
was wrong about you.
I am deeply disappointed.
-Master Yamamoto.
-Do not say anything.
The time for words is long past.
Draw your swords.
What is the meaning
of this, you two?
Do not tell me you
intend to fight me
without even releasing
your Zanpakuto.
-We're still hoping to avoid
fighting at all, old man Yama,
if we can.
YAMAMOTO: Silence!
I taught you better than that.
You both know that there can
be no forgiveness for those
who defy justice.
KYORAKU: And you also
taught us that sometimes we
must carry out justice
on our own, Master.
UKITAKE: And that
is the reason we
carry these swords
in the first place.
Is it not, Master?
-Such foolish talk.
You have no right to
decide for yourselves
what is right and wrong.
It is your duty to accept the
true justice of the world!
-Well, then what is the
justice of the world, Master?
Who determines right and wrong?
-Did you not hear me before?
The time for words has passed!
[laughs]
[music playing]
YAMAMOTO: All things in
the universe turn to ashes.
Ryujin Jakka!
[theme music]
UKITAKE: Head Captain
Yamamoto, sir?
What would I have
to do to attain
a muscular body like yours?
KYORAKU: It is
truly magnificent.
YAMAMOTO: Well, you must
train each and every day.
KYORAKU: Maybe.
But it hasn't done
much for your hair.
YAMAMOTO: My hair
is magnificent too!