[music playing]
[theme music]
NARRATOR: Soul Reapers.
The spiritual guardians to
the world of the living.
Their job is to maintain the
balance between the myriad
of good and evil souls
that fill this world.
Sosuke Aizen, who
betrayed the Soul Society
and left the
[inaudible] in chaos,
has set his plan into motion.
Arrancars have arrived
in Karakura town.
Using the Hogyoku, Aizen
has created these Arrancars
by shattering the boundary
between Soul Reapers
and Hollows.
Meanwhile, Vizords,
Soul Reapers who
have awakened the powers
of their inner Hollow
have appeared and
confronted Ichigo.
-Besides, it's too late.
Once the symptoms
appear, Visords
can never become normal again.
And no matter what you may
think, the die is cast.
You're already on
our side, Ichigo.
NARRATOR: Once Aizen's
gang of Arrancars
appeared in Karakura town, they
moved into position to attack.
They were immediately
engaged by the advanced team
of Soul Reapers, led
by Captain Hitsugaya.
-Dance!
Sode no Shirayuki.
NARRATOR: Ichigo and
Rukia were attacked
by the Arrancar, Di Roy.
He was quickly
frozen and shattered
by Rukia's powerful
Zanpakuto, Sode no Shirayuki,
which can freeze anything
on land and in the air.
But no sooner had she defeated
Di Roy than she and Ichigo were
confronted by an even
more dangerous Arrancar,
named Grimmjow.
Now the entire team
is under attack.
Edrad confronts Ikkaku.
Renji takes on Eelfor.
And Hitsugaya and Rangiku face
off against Sawlong and Nakeem.
As both sides begin
to battle, they
start to reveal the
extent of the true powers.
-What's the matter, Soul Reaper?
If that's the best you've
got, you better give up now.
-You were so busy trying to kill
me, I didn't catch your name.
-I just realized,
there's no point
in giving out my name to
somebody I'm about to kill.
-Is that right?
It seems that you and I operate
with very different rules
of etiquette.
Maybe it's the fact
that you're part Hollow,
but we let our opponents know
the name of their killers.
It's something I teach
every pupil I train.
If you're prepared
to die in battle,
you should want to die knowing
the name of the person who
defeated you.
So allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Ikkaku Madarame.
Third Seat of the Zaraki Squad.
I won't bother
spelling it for you.
I doubt your brain can
absorb that much information.
Just know that I'm the one
who's about to kill you.
[fight sounds]
Come on you coward!
Are you afraid to
use your Zanpakuto?
Don't tell me you wear it
on your waist for show.
-We Arrancars have iron skin.
There's no sword that
can penetrate it,
because it acts as our armor.
Your weapon is useless.
I can take you barehanded.
-Is that so?
Good reflexes.
That's important.
You're going to need them.
But I don't think they're going
to work quite as well after I
cut off one of your arms.
-Huh?
I can't believe it.
Forced to draw my sword
against a mere Soul Reaper?
Disgraceful.
-Offended, are you?
You'll have to release it
if you expect to defeat me.
-What's going on?
Who are these guys?
-Weren't you listening just now?
He's Ikkaku Madarame.
He's the Third Seat
of the Zaraki Squad.
He also happens to be
the second strongest
man in that squad, the most
feared squad in the Soul
Society.
-Wait, you were
there this afternoon.
Hey, come on!
Aren't you going to go
out there and help him?
Come on.
You are his friend, aren't you?
-Don't you see what's going on?
Look how happy he is.
He's having fun.
It's been a long time since he's
fought such a strong opponent.
He's forced to use
all of his training.
-Huh?
-He would be furious if
I interfered in any way.
So I don't intend
to help him out.
You understand?
-No!
This makes no sense at all!
Check out his opponent.
He's a massive killing machine.
Is there some guarantee
your friend will win?
-There isn't.
-What the hell's wrong with you?
Aren't you going to feel
guilty if your buddy dies,
and you didn't do
anything to help?
-That's a risk each of us takes.
But he'd die doing
what he loves most.
-His style is rough, but
his skill is undeniable.
He provokes me just
enough to be annoying.
He keeps his sword in
his left hand to attack,
and a scabbard in his
right hand to defend.
He's easy to read.
An open book.
Since I know which
arm he'll attack with,
I can easily anticipate
his offensive strategy,
and look for
weaknesses to exploit.
Punching through his defenses
and finishing him off
should be easy.
Here comes his
attack from the left!
He switched hands!
[grunting]
-Darn, I missed.
I was trying to
chop your head off.
I aimed too high.
-Who is this guy?
He made me think his
attacks were predictable,
just so he could
catch me off guard.
And just as I made my
move, he switched his sword
to his other hand,
and slashed my face.
That's a crazy way to fight.
It's possible to score big.
But he's liable to
end up dead himself.
That's not fighting to win.
That's fighting for sport.
At first glance it may
seem clever, but it's not.
It doesn't make any sense.
He exposed himself in
order to lure me in.
This guy thinks this is a game.
He doesn't take the
danger seriously.
Is that all your
life means to you?
-That slap move,
where you focused all
your spirit energy into your
hand was pretty effective.
Hey, you even knocked
out a couple of my teeth.
Ah well, whatever.
When I'm done
here, I'll just get
Akon to give me a deal
on some replacements.
All right.
So let's get back to business.
Are you ready for
the second round?
I think I've got you
figure it out now.
Another five or six strikes
is all it should take.
And then you'll
release your Zanpakuto,
whether you want to or not.
-Oh really?
I've underestimated you.
I guess there's no
point in holding back.
You won't be satisfied
with anything less.
I should just release my
Zanpakuto to fight you, right?
-That's about the
size of it, now
that you know how
tough I really am.
-Fine.
A fool like you
who loves to battle
needs to be taught a lesson.
You need to know what it's like
to feel uncontrollable fear.
Something so
terrifying it makes you
tremble all the
way to your bones.
After this, you'll
never find it fun
to pick a fight
with an Arrancar.
Awaken, Volcanica!
[music playing]
-What the hell is that thing?
-I reveal my secret power,
and all you can say is that?
This, my naive friend,
is what happens
when an Arrancar
releases his Zanpakuto.
-Not good.
In fact, it's really bad.
-I recall you said
it was a courtesy
to tell an opponent the
name of this killer, right?
I am Arrancar 13, Edrad Liones!
[static]
-The spiritual pressure.
Is he an Arrancar too?
But he's not like that last one.
That guy was arrogant
and inexperienced,
and he paid the price.
[drums]
His spiritual pressure
is incredible.
-Which one?
Which one of you
is the strongest?
Who's going to take me on?
-Retreat.
Ichigo!
Get out of here, run!
-I figured it probably
wasn't you, no surprise.
[gasping]
-Rukia!
-Allow me to enlighten you.
An Arrancar's
Zanpakuto is sealed
with the core of his
power in his body.
It's completely different
from you Soul Reapers.
We Arrancar take
on our true forms,
and reach our full power,
through the release
of our Zanpakuto.
You were so anxious for me
to release my Zanpakuto.
Well here it is.
Deal with it.
This is my true form, and
this is my true power.
-Yes, My.
Ayasegawa, what are your orders?
-The destructive
power of the enemy
has vastly exceeded estimations.
We need to put up an area freeze
with a radius of 300 units,
around you Ikkaku Madarame.
The cost of the
damaged buildings
will come out of
the mission budget.
Unfortunately a
number of souls will
be caught within
the target area.
The protection of those souls,
as always, is our top priority.
-Understood, sir.
-I predict a similar
increase in power
will take place among the
remaining enemy units.
Put additional special freezes
around the following personnel.
Toshiro Hitsugaya, Rangiku
Matsumoto, Renji Abarai,
Rukia Kuchiki, and
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Additionally, please begin
Squad funeral preparation
for Ikkaku Madarame.
-A squad funeral?
You mean there's no
question in your mind
he's not going to make it?
-Goodbye, Soul Reaper!
-The battle strength
of an Arrancar
increases exponentially when
his Zanpakuto is released.
A weakling like you, with
such low spiritual pressure,
has no chance of survival.
-Extend!
Hozukimaru!
[music playing]
-That was almost too easy.
Hm?
[grunting]
You should give up now.
A truly wise warrior knows
when to admit defeat.
And though you didn't
win, you fought well.
If you don't
surrender now, I will
be forced to destroy
you completely.
As you wish.
[explosion]
What?
-I never would
have guessed there
would be this much
difference in our power.
I guess there's no choice.
I really didn't want
to use this here,
but since everyone's off
fighting somewhere else,
I suppose nobody's
going to notice.
Now.
Watch carefully, my
block-headed friend,
and don't tell anybody
you saw me doing this.
You think you have
me on the ropes?
Well I've got a
surprise for you!
Bankai!
[music playing]
-Ah!
This is getting out of hand.
What in the world
is happening here?
-So.
he decided to use it.
-Huh?
[grunting]
-You're planning to use Bankai?
-That's right.
Bankai.
Ryumon Hozukimaru!
-An impressive display.
-Don't try to throw me off.
I haven't released
enough spiritual pressure
yet to impress you.
But believe me, pal.
It's coming.
You can decide if
it's effective or not.
After I use it to cut
off your ugly head.
-Impossible!
He cut through my Volcanica!
I can still beat him.
His Bankai doesn't increase
his kido, his speed,
or his defensive abilities.
The Bankai is just a
huge mass of power.
A pure destructive force.
But it's only as effective
as the warrior who uses it.
There's a flaw in his strategy.
His reliance on
the power of Bankai
makes him slow to
counter my attacks.
He may be fearless,
but he's not stupid.
I need to find a way
to outmaneuver him
before he can cut off my limbs.
I have the will to win.
He'll never beat me in a
battle of pure strength.
It will be power versus power.
And I am fully armed.
Hm?
Wait a minute.
His Zanpakuto is
getting stronger.
His spiritual pressure
is increasing.
-Hozukimaru is
finally awakening!
He's such a slow starter.
He's usually asleep
when I use my Bankai.
And he takes his own
sweet time getting up.
But he's no good to me
unless he's fully awake.
That's when his power activates.
I'll have to force him awake
by slashing up my enemy,
or letting him slash me up.
I can monitor his progress
by watching the dragon slowly
light up on the blade.
When it's completely red, his
power will be at full strength.
When that happens, I
can start cutting you up
like a turkey on a platter!
[music playing]
-Are you ready?
-Uh-huh.
[theme music]
GRIMMJOW: It's time for
Grimmjow's Arrancar seminar.
Each of us has a number
to go with our name.
For instance, I'm
Arrancar number 6,
also known as Grimmow.
This will be on the test, so
make sure you pay attention.
-Uh, Professor, what about 15?
Which one's 15?
[theme music]
-Soul Reapers.
-Excuse me, sir.
I wanted to clear
something up with you.
When I'm not
available, you don't
have to fill in for me anymore
at lieutenant's meetings.
-Part of a captain's
duty is to make
sure all of the lieutenant's
responsibilities are being met.
-If that's true in every case,
Captain, then tell me this.
Whenever Rukia's not available
and has responsibilities,
do you represent her at the
female Soul Reaper Association
meetings?