Hraaah!
I've had enough of you!
What?!
G'ah!!
Rahhhhh!
Ichigo!!
Curse you, you ant! How dare
you defy a god in this way?!
Your insolence will
doom you to destruction!
[scream of pain]
Huaa.. Wauuugghh!
I can't believe this!
[Stark]
Why do I have to fight
someone this strong?
Lord Aizen.
What is it?
[gasp]
I'm done with you.
This isn't what I expected.
I went through a
considerable amount
of effort to gather
all of you Espadas.
I never expected your strengths
to be inferior to my own.
Now then...
Are you all ready?
Members of the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads,
and you failed mock Arrancars,
Whooa. The last Espada
has been taken out.
Aahh.
Mashiro!
Ah-!
I know, I got 'im!
Huaah!
Hm!
[Kensei]
Hey, listen up.
When you fight at this level,
you'll find that you become
exhausted quickly!
Take your mask off and put it
back on or your energy will run
out.
Wow! You think you
know everything!
So just how long do you
think I normally maintain
Hollowfication?!
15 hours! That's 15 hours!
I can go on like this past
midnight!
Mmmm.
yeah, okay.
[attack yell]
Huaaaa!
[Kensei]
Behind you!
I told you,
I can handle this!
How's this?!
Whoa!
Aaahhhh!
Hey, let go!
Rrgh. You little creep!
You just tore up my scarf!
(Springing up towards her
Efforts)
Take this!
Mashiro
Super Cero!
Ahh!
Big deal!
So you countered it!
Here goes!
Mashiroooo!!
Uh oh...
My time ran out.
Ahh!
Ahhh!!
Mm.
Aahhh!
Sorry pal, But I'm afraid
I'm just not mature enough
to hold back against a kid!
You relax. I'm gonna school
this guy a little bit.
Kensei...
I wanna ask, Are you
avenging me? Heheh.
It sounds like you're
happy. Idiot.
This is happening because you
didn't listen when I warned you.
I'd never avenge someone
who behaves like that.
Hehe.
Hnh!
That kid needs to
be taught a lesson.
I'll knock him
down a peg.
Kensei...
Are you kidding?!
Stop that!
Aagh!
Haai!
Haa!
Let me show you how
you throw a punch!
Haauuughh!
Are you ready for what's next?!
Aaaah!
Bankai!
Tekken Tachikaze!!
Aaahh!
Heeaaaa!
Sosuke. I think it's time we
settle things between us!
I really liked those old days,
Back when we were in the
Soul Society.
Soul Reapers are
always in death's way,
Because of where they exist,
and what they do.
We all know we might die
tomorrow, or even today.
We may be talking one minute
and be dead the next.
No one ever talks about it,
but we all carry that
thought in our minds.
We all knew death better
than we really wanted to.
We saw death up close.
We felt death up close.
Knowing death helped
us cherish each day.
It united us.
That's how we built such trust.
You traitor!
[gasp]
Huaaaahh!!
Sosuke...
Sosuke!
[gasps] What's
happening to me?
[Aizen]
Goodbye.
I must commend you;
You people have
provided wonderful
research material.
[anguished scream]
Graaaahhhh!
Sosuke, The reason I hate you
isn't that you gained our trust
and chose to betray us.
I hate you because you
made me hurt my friends!
You used me!
And them! You destroyed us!
You ruined what we shared!!
Aizen!
I'm seething with hate for you.
It's been boiling inside me for
a hundred years!
I can't live with this hate!
I won't go back to the old
ways until you're dead!
Don't be reckless
as you approach him.
He possesses great power.
If you approach him carelessly,
it will be the end of you.
Right, I know that.
Hold on!
Listen to me,
idiot...
You need to take a
deep breath right now--
[Aizen]
Typical!
Tch!
You always try to
give good advice,
Captain Shinji.
You do.
But it's such silly
advice to give.
It's totally worthless.
Ngh!
It doesn't matter whether
you approach me recklessly,
or carefully,
or even if you decide not to
approach me at all.
The end result for all of you,
will be the same.
I'm not talking about
things to come.
Regardless of what you choose,
your demise is inescapable.
It is an event of the past.
He's taunting us! Stay put!
Tell me, what do
you have to fear?
Remember a hundred years ago?
Every single one of you died.
Have you forgotten that night?
Hiyori!!
Haaahhh!!
[gasp]
Well at least now you í^ are
leaving us.
Hiyori!!
[Hiyori]
[labored breaths]
Hiyori...
I'm... so sorry... Shinji.
Don't speak.
I did hear you...
I just couldn't hold back.
Rgh!
Hachi!!
Use your Kido to heal her--
[gasp]
Hiyori...
Tell me what can I
do to save you?
How can I help you now?!
That's it! Orihime!
Orihime's healing powers should
be able to heal your wounds!
Ichigo. Damn it! What the
hell is taking you so long?!
Ichigo!!
[distant crash]
[Uryu]
Ichigo...
Don't worry.
Go ahead,
I'll be fine.
Down there, There are
people waiting for you.
Uryu...
Are you sure?
Get going.
But you're--
You heard me!
If there's something you
want to say, I can hear it
when this is over.
But right now, there's
something else you have to do!
All right then.
Orihime, please
take care of him.
Okay. Leave it to me.
Now!
Hoooooaaaaaaa!
Bankai!
[mechanical scream]
Hihio Zabimaru!
No matter how hard you try,
it's useless!!
Ridiculous.
Huh?!
What's this?!?
Hrrgghh!
Rukia! Chad! Now!
Right!
Dance! Sodenoshirayuki!
Tsuginomai Hakuren!
Brazo Derecho del Gigante.
You shouldn't be so confident!!
[Rukia]
Watch out!!
Huh?!!
Hmph!
How can he be
completely unharmed?
Your pathetic efforts to
hurt me will never work!
He's tough and has
plenty of power.
So what now?
There's nothing to
discuss. We have to
defeat this guy.
Yeah, you're right.
What are you
whining about now?
You look like
scared little ants!
Let's do this!
Hunh? Where did you go?
I see one.
And two!
Why do you three keep
moving around!?
Just hold still will ya!
Ahhg! How annoying!
I knew it!
He can't keep up
with our speed!
We'll throw him off
and then strike!
Where are you?
You can't hide from me!
There you are!!
Waauugh!
Hikotsu Taiho!!
I've had enough of you!
What!
Hrrngh!
Well that's one down.
Now then.
Uahh!
That's two.
Just one left.
C'mon!
It's no use!
Well?
Huh?
Ohh!
Do you think you can get
away from me by running?!
Damn it!
Nn... Ngh...
Ah! Now I've caught you!
You're the last one.
Catching you wasn't easy
'cuz you're so tiny.
Ha ha ha ha!
But now you're
all mine!
Don't struggle.
This requires a
delicate touch from me.
It's not easy to hold
you without crushing you.
Now,then, How exactly
should I kill you?
Hmm. Let me think.
Squeezing you into a
bloody pulp with my hands
just isn't that amusing.
I'm not coming up with a fun
way to kill you right now.
Hey! How do YOU
want me to do it?
I'll kill you however
you tell me to.
Hey listen, I know I look
mean and scary to you, but I'm
really generous to weaklings.
Huh??
Sokatsui!
[overselling the pain]
Ow! That stung! That hurt!
That really really hurt me!
You sure got me with that one1
[gasp] That didn't
do a thing to him!
That was so painful...
Guess it made me lose my grip!
Hah!
What incredible power!
I can't get back into my
posture because the wind
pressure's too intense!
[panicked breathing]
No!
Rukia!!
[Mashiro]
Go, Kensei!
That's it Kensei,
you go give it 'em!
[Kensei]
Hey, If you have the
energy to cheer me on,
Then give me a hand.
[Mashiro]
No way! I'm mature enough to
hold back on a kid like that!
[Kensei]
You brat!