[theme music]
-Tsubaki.
Not this time.
Koten Zanshun, I reject.
[screaming]
-Tsubaki.
-Stupid girl.
What were you thinking,
hesitating like that?
-I have never seen a
move like that before,
and yet I sense no murderous
intent behind your attack.
Although you might be able
to kill certain Hollows
with that type of
move, I assure you
it will have no effect
whatsoever on soul reapers.
This is a battleground, and
by you not fighting to kill,
you'll never succeed
in stopping anyone.
-If you want to face an
attack with an intent to kill,
then why not fight me?
I'm sure you'll find
it here in my bow.
It's a thrill I'd
love to give you.
-Ah.
Very interesting.
So I guess that
makes you a Quincy.
-You're right about that.
-Uryu's bow, it's totally
different from the one
I saw before, both in
its appearance and even
its spiritual pressure.
And that glove.
He must have been practicing
in order to use it properly.
-One uses unfamiliar skills.
The other is a Quincy, and
both employ projectile weapons.
And you have both come to this
very place at this very time
to fight against me.
So do I call this an
amazing coincidence
or a brilliant twist of fate?
Either way I must show you
the true form of my Zanpakuto.
Time to spread your
wings, Tsunzakigarasu.
So what do you think?
Time to lament.
I am the fourth
seat of Squad Seven.
I am Jirobo Ikkanzaka also known
as Jirobo the slicing wind.
My nickname, Wind Scythe, proves
that I am the most skilled when
it comes to dealing
with projectile weapons.
See how my countless
blades dance through space.
No one who has seen
my attack has lived.
So tell me, do you
like what you've
seen of my Tsunzakigarasu.
You can't even follow them
with your eyes, can you?
They are a prelude to
your glorious death?
-Interesting.
Unlike the outside world, in
here the most skilled fighter
seems unfortunately
to be the one who
ends up the most
long winded whiner.
-Absurd.
That was just a fluke.
You're too cocky
for your own good.
-You still don't understand.
If you're supposed to be
the most skilled one dealing
with flying weapons,
then I'd think
about getting a new nickname.
Because where flying
weapons are concerned,
I seem to be the better man.
Unfortunately, Uryu Wind Scythe
doesn't have as nice a ring
to it.
-What have you done to my hand?
I can't move my fingers.
-Amazing.
Uryu is so much
more powerful now
compared to that
time he was battling
Hollows alongside Ichigo.
He's become a completely
different person.
-I expect you are the
one with regrets now.
As a fellow practitioner
of flying weaponry,
you must wish you
hadn't met me today.
-How dare you insult me,
you insolent little brat.
I'll kill you.
What?
-You do realize that I missed
you intentionally this time.
And also that I won't
miss the next time.
-Incredible.
The power.
As hard as it is
for me to admit it,
the accuracy and speed
of your attack technique
far surpasses my own ability.
I never dreamed I would meet
such a skillful practitioner
only to fail.
With just a single stroke,
you have defeated me utterly.
Torture me.
Destroy me.
Do whatever you want to me.
Why do you not shoot
me and finish it?
Can it be that you
intend to let me live?
-Huh.
I am a Quincy.
Believe me I have no desire to
show mercy to any soul reaper.
But I don't make a habit out
of bullying the weak either.
Now quit your sniveling
and get out of here.
Hurry before I change my mind.
-It would seem that you
are a kind-hearted soul.
Too bad-- for you that is.
Now what?
-As I suspected.
You thought that since
you couldn't beat me,
you would attack the
girl, didn't you?
Or were you thinking you
would just take her hostage?
-No.
How'd you know that?
-As I said, I don't make a
habit of bullying the weak,
but I certainly
don't mind exposing
cowards for what they are.
From the moment we
first encountered you,
you were actually
targeting Orihime, not me.
Most warriors would
find it beneath them
to attack a girl, especially
when she wasn't looking.
No honorable person,
no one with any pride
would ever do such a thing.
You coward.
I bid you farewell
and good riddance.
You're not even worth lamenting.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN):
Thank you, Uryu.
-Ugh.
There's nothing to thank me for.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): Oh
yeah, it was nothing.
Right.
Did you kill him?
URYU (OFFSCREEN): No.
He's still alive.
I just destroyed his soul
chain and Hakusui soul sleep,
the spots that govern
spiritual powers.
He's going to live, but his
spiritual powers are no more.
When he awakens, as a
result of this battle,
he'll no longer
be a soul reaper.
And that's good enough for now.
Shall we go?
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): OK.
I remember something Yoruichi
once told me about Quincys,
that in battle they gather the
spiritual particles around them
and use them to fight.
I think that's what
Uryu uses the glove for.
The overwhelming
power it gives him
must be the reason he went
off to train on his own.
Uryu didn't want to
risk harming any of us
until he was able to master it.
And to think he mastered it to
such a degree in only ten days
all by himself.
Uryu is really incredible.
But it does make me
wonder, what did I
accomplish in those ten days?
Oh, thanks.
-Don't mention it.
-I haven't done much.
TATSUKI (OFFSCREEN): Orihime.
Hang in there, Orihime.
Remember you promised
me you would.
-I remember.
Thanks for reminding
me, Tatsuki.
-What's wrong, Orihime?
Why are you acting so strange?
Did you get hurt in
the battle somehow?
-No. no.
I'm sorry.
It's nothing, Uryu.
I'm just fine really.
My eyes just got teary-eyed
there for a second.
You know how that
happens sometimes
when you look into the sun.
It can even make you sneeze,
which is really weird.
But they're not even connected.
I mean what is that all about?
Well, we'd better
get moving, Uryu.
We've got places to go.
-Ugh.
Orihime.
-What is it?
-Are you sure you're all right?
-Of course.
Why?
-No reason.
-Ah!
Why is it that no matter
where we go I'm always the one
being chased all over the place?
-Come back here, you
sideburned clown.
-You're going to get a beating.
-For being so ugly.
-Who you calling ugly?
The soul reaper with the funky
eyelashes is a real looker,
but that's not my fault.
And you guys are no
fashion models yourselves.
-Oh, you're going to
pay for that crack.
-We're going to use your
head for a door knocker.
-A really ugly door knocker.
-Ichigo.
Just in time.
I could really use some
back-up right about now.
-Ganju.
-You got a mob chasing you too.
Fight them there, Ichigo.
I got enough problems already.
And quit waving
at me, you idiot.
You're only making them madder.
Back off, I said.
You're bringing them toward me.
-Ganju, duck.
-Huh.
[grunting]
-This is Iemura reporting.
Squad Four relief crew and
Groups One, Six, and 14
are approaching enemy position.
Captain Iemura over and out.
Come on.
Let's move out.
This is not a drill.
-(GROUP) Yes, sir.
-What are you doing swinging an
overgrown blade so close to me,
you moron?
You almost took my
freaking head off.
-Shut up.
I told you to duck, didn't I?
-What good is a
warning if it comes
at the same time as the thing
you're getting warned about?
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
If you didn't
have the reflexes
of a banana slug.
GANJU (OFFSCREEN): Just be
more careful, you idiot.
Yeah, but right now, we've got
other things to worry about.
They backed off after your
little surprise attack,
but I have a feeling that isn't
going to work a second time.
And anyway, we're
heavily outnumbered.
We're going to need a miracle.
-I'm totally late.
I'm going to be in big trouble
if I don't get there soon.
Maybe I should just
pretend that I never
got the message in the
first place and go home.
But then what do I say if
Iemura asks me where I've been?
Where is everyone anyway?
Huh.
I know.
I'll ask these guys if
they've seen my group.
Excuse me, everybody,
but by any chance
have you see Squad
Four Group-- oh!
Whoa!
-Hey!
-Ow!
[grunting and complaining]
-Ah!
That didn't work out
exactly like I planned it.
-Ichigo, I think I have an idea
how we can get ourselves out
of this place.
-Is that right?
Me too.
-So you guys are trying to find
a way to get out of this place.
But why would you be trying
to get away from here?
Unless of course, you happen
to be the Ryoka everyone
is so worried about.
-You back off and
let us out of here.
-Or else your little
friend is going
to be missing some pieces.
-Ah!
But I faint at the
sight of my own blood.
-I've been running
forever, Yachiru.
Where are you leading me?
-Don't worry.
This is definitely
the right way.
I think.
-Did you just say "you think"?
-Oh, don't be grouchy.
Hey, turn right up here.
-You better be
correct this time.
-All you do is complain.
If you don't like my
directions, then forget it.
Just go where you want to go.
-OK.
I'll turn right.
YACHIRU (OFFSCREEN):
Good for you.
This is it.
I'm almost positive.
-Almost positive?
-Back off, you punks,
and let us through.
-Or else your little
friend is going
to be missing some pieces.
-Ah!
Do what they say.
Do what they say, or
else I'll be, oh--
-Not the reaction I expected.
-Maybe they didn't understand.
Try again.
-If you say so.
-Listen, riff raff.
Stand aside and let us through.
-Or else my blade is going to
take the life of your friend
here.
Come on, you sound like
you're scared of us.
-Yes.
Please.
I think they mean it.
-Very strange.
-What the hell are
you idiots doing?
-Huh.
-What does it look like?
We took a hostage.
-I see.
And does he look like
one of us to you?
-He-- who are you?
-We're all on the same side.
But I'm Squad Four,
and they're Squad 11.
-So?
What difference does that make?
-Ha.
I guess these bumpkins
really are from the outside.
I shouldn't bother
explaining it to you,
but it's much too insulting
to have you lump us together.
So listen up.
There are 13 guard
squads assigned
to protect the Seireitei.
We of Squad 11 are led
by the strongest captain.
As such, we are the strongest
unit and always the first
into battle.
SQUAD (OFFSCREEN): Yeah!
-I just noticed these guys all
have weird hair except you.
What's your squad again?
-It's Squad Four.
-Is that a good one?
-Well, Sure.
Squad Four is a
great squad to be in.
SHINIGAMI GUARD #1 (OFFSCREEN):
Don't make me laugh.
Squad Four is just the
rear echelon service
that provides first
aid for minor injuries.
That's where all the
loser wimps who can't even
wield a sword get assigned.
SHINIGAMI GUARD #2
(OFFSCREEN): That's right.
The rest of us can't
stand the little weasels.
SHINIGAMI GUARD #1 (OFFSCREEN):
So whatever you do,
don't confuse them with us.
Because when it
comes to Squad Four--
SQUAD (OFFSCREEN): We hate them.
SHINIGAMI GUARD #2
(OFFSCREEN): And if you
want to kill this
one, go right ahead.
We don't mind.
-Wait a minute.
Don't you think it's kinda cruel
recommending death for someone
just because they have
different responsibilities?
-Hey, that almost makes sense.
Looks like we're in for a fight.
-What the hell was that?
-I don't know, and I don't care.
What counts is that it just cut
the enemy's numbers in half.
[grunting and fighting noises]
-I thought I sensed
Ichigo's spiritual pressure.
It looks like I just missed him.
-Hey, you there.
Who are you and what do you know
about all these bodies lying
here?
-And what's with that stupid
outfit you're wearing?
-Hey, are you with the
intruders we saw earlier?
-Intruders you saw earlier?
Probably, yes.
-If you think you can
answer us in riddles
and get away with it,
you're about to pay
for that with your
life, intruder.
-You're going to get cut
to shreds in five minutes.
-I am sorry, but I'm afraid I
cannot give you that much time.
-Uh, what?
-You crazy or something?
-This won't take five
minutes, only two.
[cackling]
-So you're going to
refuse to cooperate, eh?
Well, we'll see how long
that lasts, Ikkaku Madarame.
-Squad 12 Captain, I'm
sorry, but I must protest.
Interrogation of
patients is strictly
prohibited in the hospital wing.
MAYURI (OFFSCREEN):
Mind your own business.
-Master Mayuri.
-You shut your mouth too, Nemu.
Or maybe you'd like me to have
you pulled to pieces again.
-No, sir.
Please forgive me, master.
-It's not that I won't talk.
-Huh?
-It's just that I really
don't know anything.
I don't know who
the Ryoka are, and I
have no idea what
they're planning to do.
-So what you're telling me is,
even though you met and fought
against these mysterious
invaders in the street,
you were defeated in battle and
then just retreated like a dog
without learning a single
shred of useful information?
-I'm afraid so.
It may seem strange to you, but
sometimes battle is like that.
I've not seen this enemy's
face nor heard his voice.
So I'm afraid I have
no information for you.
-You lie.
And now you shall
receive punishment
appropriate to your failure.
-Interesting.
Since when, I wonder,
are you entitled
to discipline members of squads
other than your own, Mayuri?
-Zaraki.
Well, since his captain
is here, there's
no need for me to continue
this interrogation.
Good luck getting anything
out of him, Zaraki.
Don't just stand there,
Nemu, you useless dullard.
Let's go.
-Hm.
-Captain.
-Well, you certainly
got yourself beaten up.
IKKAKU (OFFSCREEN):
Nice of you to visit.
-Oh, we didn't plan to.
We just got lost.
-I see your lieutenant
is here too.
-We were trying to
find the intruders,
but Kenny here was having some
trouble following directions.
So how are you feeling, baldy?
-I asked you not to
call me that anymore.
-Oh.
Should it be Mr. Baldy?
-You little brat.
YACHIRU (OFFSCREEN): How
about Mr. Shiny Baldy then?
-Is it true that you
were defeated in battle?
-Yes, that's true.
I'm ashamed to admit it, but
I was defeated by the enemy
and then allowed to live.
-Is he strong?
-Yes.
Very strong.
He appears to be a soul reaper.
He wears a shihakusho, has
short orange colored hair,
and carries a sword as long as
his body with no guard or grip.
By now he is headed towards
the Shishinro repentance cell.
-He shouldn't be hard to find.
-I gave him your
description, and I
told him to be on the
lookout for you, captain.
My warning about you did
not seem too concern him.
Regardless of
where you meet him,
you will surely enjoy
an excellent battle.
He's strong now,
and from what I saw,
I believe his strength
is still growing, master.
By the time you
encounter him, it
seems likely that he
will be stronger still.
-Excellent.
And his name is--
-I am Hanataro Yamada.
-(BOTH) Dude, that
name is so lame.
-What are you talking about?
I like my name, and it
most certainly is not lame.
-Well, you're wrong.
Where I come from,
hana means flower,
and there's nothing
lamer than that.
You might as well
yourself Blossom.
-Hey, come on.
-Why should we bother learning
the enemy's name anyway?
-But I--
GANJU (OFFSCREEN): And why
are you being so friendly
and introducing yourself
in the first place?
-That's a good question.
I don't really know why.
-And here's another question.
What did you bring him for?
-I couldn't help it.
OK.
He was sitting there, and I just
picked him up and carried him
by accident.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): How do you
pick something up by accident?
What are you?
A garbage man?
You just pick up whatever
you see lying on the ground?
GANJU (OFFSCREEN): Shut up.
You didn't notice him until now.
So what's the big deal?
-This is useless,
you guys, please.
You've got to stop
fighting over me.
-(BOTH) We are not
fighting over you.
-OK.
But you need to keep
your voices down,
or you'll lead the
guards right to us.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
Anyone out there?
GANJU (OFFSCREEN):
All clear for now.
-We're still screwed.
Because even if that
bald guy I beat up
was telling the
truth about Rukia
being held in some white tower,
we still don't know where it is
or which road we need
to take to get there.
-Hey wait a minute.
What about this map?
This would help us avoid
running into any more captains
out there.
If only it showed us
where the enemy was.
-This is a map?
It doesn't even have any
streets marked on it.
That's just stupid.
Huh.
What's this here?
GANJU (OFFSCREEN): Please.
-You idiot, you drew
this yourself didn't you.
-It's better than nothing.
Where's your map, smart ass?
HANATARO (OFFSCREEN):
Uh, excuse me.
-Just stay out of this.
Will you?
We're doing some serious
strategizing here.
-Why don't you
just beat it, kid?
You're not going to be
any use to us anyway.
No offense.
-Good idea.
HANATARO (OFFSCREEN): It's Rukia
Kuchiki you're looking for,
isn't it?
I thought so.
It all makes sense now.
The younger sister
of the Squad Six
captain currently being
held as a capital offender.
And that means the white
tower you were talking about
must be the repentance cell.
If you'll trust
me, I can help you.
I know a hidden way
into that tower.
-Well, you sure seem
to be happy, Kenny.
-Is that so?
-Yeah, really happy.
Ever since you talked
to Ikkaku back there.
-I suppose you're right.
I am looking forward to this.
This stranger survived
against Ichimaru.
He defeated Ikkaku.
And Ikkaku said he is
strong and will probably
become stronger still.
Where are you?
I, Kenpachi Zaraki,
am waiting for you.
Come out, Ichigo Kurosaki.
[theme music]
KON NARRATING: Yo.
How you doing?
It's everyone's idol, Kon.
Why isn't it my turn yet?
I've been ready and
waiting over here.
Hey, are you listening to me?
NARRATOR: If you make
too much of a fuss,
you may never get your turn.
KON NARRATING: All right.
All right.
I'll behave.
Hey you, Squad Nine captain, are
you mocking me with that hair?