[theme music]
[shouting]
-Let her go!
-Karin!
Help me!
-You're too noisy.
And anyway, you're too
small, even for an appetizer.
Hmm?
[shout]
[scream]
[shouting]
-Karin!
-One hostage is all I need.
I've been waiting
for you, Soul Reaper.
-Karin!
-(WEAKLY) Ichigo, I--
-Whoa, now that's an ugly one.
[laughing]
[gasp]
-It's not possible.
[hollow laughing]
-It's her.
It's the girl I saw
that day six years ago,
the one down by the river.
-Six years ago?
Ichigo, do you mean--
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
That's right.
She's the one.
I tried to stop her from
jumping into the river,
but when I finally came
to, she disappeared.
And my mother-- she was dead.
HOLLOW (OFFSCREEN):
Six years ago?
That's a long time.
And there have been so many.
You can't expect me to
remember every one of the souls
I've eaten.
Now can you?
[laughing]
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN):
It's Grand Fisher.
That's the code name
we've given him.
He keeps himself invisible and
disguises the lure growing out
of his head as a human.
Anyone who sees
the lure he knows
has high spirit energy
and immediately attacks
and devours them, thus
gaining all of their power.
For over 50 years,
this Hollow has
evaded every Soul Reaper
that's gone after him.
-Ah.
-And we know his favorite
victims are women.
-So does that mean my mother
was actually killed by--
[growling]
[laughter]
-Impressive.
You have been lucky, little boy.
You saw my lure,
and yet you lived.
Perhaps it was my
intention to eat you
on the spot for
your spirit energy,
but there's something
about the women.
They're just too sweet and
lovely for me to pass up.
[laughing]
-Bastard.
-That's the most
disgusting Hollow
I've seen in a long time.
[shouting]
-Karin!
-Don't be so
reckless, you idiot!
-Huh?
[shout]
[grunting]
Ichigo!
-I knew you were ugly, but
up close, you smell worse.
-Disintegrate, you
black dog of Rondanini!
Look upon yourself with
horror, and then claw out
your own throat!
Bakudo number nine, strike!
[groaning]
-How dare you interfere?
[shouting]
-Ugh!
Oof.
-Huh?
-[laughing] Now just sit there
and watch as I devour this
little girl.
-Hang on!
-[laughing] Tasty.
-No, don't!
-If you feel so
strongly about it,
maybe I should
just eat you first.
[laughing]
[shouting]
[growling]
-Karin!
[grunting]
[gasping]
[groaning]
[shout]
-Why?
Tell me.
You sacrificed yourself.
-I'm a Soul Reaper, kid,
and we fight Hollows.
We kill them without
mercy, no matter what. .
When a Hollow attacks at random
and kills someone-- ugh--
that person's loved ones
are the real victims.
They're left with
nothing but an emptiness.
As a Soul Reaper, I
couldn't let that happen.
We must always
protect the innocent.
Do you understand, spike head?
[groan]
-Hey, get up!
Do you hear me?
Get up!
He can't die, can he?
He's a Soul Reaper.
-Ichigo, even Soul
Reapers are not immortal,
if the injuries
are severe enough.
[snoring]
-Huh?
-Wait a minute.
He's only sleeping!
Tell him to get up.
Or I'll kill him!
-Rukia.
Whoa, this dude looks
like he's leaking.
-Kon, take Ichigo's
sisters and run.
[laughing]
-Run where?
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN): Just hurry.
-All right.
-I'll go, and you back me up.
Wait!
-No way, Rukia.
You back me up.
-What did you say?
-I have to do this
for my mother.
Stay out of this.
-Have you lost your mind?
This Hollow's been
getting the best
of Soul Reapers for 50 years.
He's way too strong
for you to take on--
-That's enough!
Now please, don't interfere
or try to help me.
This fight is all mine!
[roaring]
[shouting]
[woozy groaning]
-Huh?
Oh, hey, Karin.
Whoa, are you all right?
Oh, man.
I'm trying to act like Ichigo,
but staying all serious
and scowling every minute
of the day is impossible!
How can anyone look so
mad all the time, huh?
[shouting]
[grunting]
-You're too slow human.
[gasp]
[shouting]
-That was pretty brave of
you, young Soul Reaper,
telling your friend
you didn't need
any help from her to fight me.
Pretty brave and pretty stupid.
-Shut up.
I don't really
know how long Yuzu
grieved after our mother died.
And I can only imagine
how lonely Karin
must have felt without her.
-We must always
protect the innocent.
-I've also made it my duty
to protect the innocent.
That means it's my
duty to destroy you!
[laughing]
[shouting]
-I guess you didn't listen
when your friend told you not
to be so reckless.
[grunting]
-You've been lucky so far.
How many times do you
think you can get away
with jumping into the lion's
den without any strategy?
[gasp]
-Well, today's the day your
luck finally ran out, maggot!
[cough]
[gasp]
[gasping for breath]
-That'll teach you to be so
reckless, amateur Soul Reaper.
Rejecting your
comrade's offer of help
will prove to be
your final mistake.
And now you'll endure the shame
of dying without even having
wounded the great Grand Fisher.
-Ichigo!
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Stay back!
-Huh?
-I'll do this my way,
whatever it takes.
No matter what it
costs, even if I die,
I'm going to finish this.
-Then die you will,
because you allow
your passion and your rage to
distract you from your purpose.
And that distraction
dulls your sword.
You flail wildly, but
your physical skills alone
are not enough to defeat me.
And now, I shall show you why
your mind is not strong enough
to fight me, either.
Behold!
[gasp]
-Is that your mother?
-Bastard!
GRAND FISHER (OFFSCREEN):
Even the most cold-blooded
Soul Reaper has one person
whom he can never kill.
That is a fact which
you cannot deny.
By learning who
that person is, I
have evaded every
Soul Reaper who
has come before you
for over 50 years.
And I have learned that for
you, this is that one person.
-Do you remember me, Ichigo?
-Ichigo.
-You're forgetting something.
-Huh?
-What about his honor?
You want to help.
And if you lend him
your strength now,
he will probably be saved.
But in doing so, you will have
forever destroyed his honor.
Now listen and
remember this, there
are two different
kinds of battle.
We must always be careful to
distinguish between the two.
There is the battle to
protect innocent life,
and then there is the battle
to preserve one's honor.
-I understand.
This is a better
for Ichigo's honor,
and one he must fight alone.
I cannot lend him my strength.
No matter how much
I may want to,
or how much I want him to
live, I won't help him.
I must not help him.
But don't sacrifice
yourself, Ichigo.
-Oh damn, I fell asleep again.
Oh well.
-Well, Soul Reaper,
can you draw your sword
against your own
mother? [laughing]
-Bastard.
How dare you defile her memory
by bringing her into this?
You disgusting freak!
You make me sick! [shouting]
I'll cut your heart out! [gasp]
-Ichigo, you mustn't do this.
You mustn't hurt your mother.
Please, son, you must
put your sword down.
Do it for me.
[grunt]
[groaning]
-Ah?
-Didn't I tell you?
Your rage only serves
to dull your blade.
It makes you vulnerable.
And now with my next
blow, I'll finish you off!
Now, before you die,
I want to tell you
that after having faced
so many Soul Reapers,
you were the most foolish and
by far the weakest of them all!
-Ichigo, watch out!
-What?
Why don't you die?
-What is that?
[laughing]
-Mom?
Is that you?
-That lure we see isn't
actually his mother,
but she's transmitting
her thoughts to him.
-That can only mean that the
lure recorded her thoughts
at the very moment
she was killed.
-Her dying thoughts
were recorded?
EIKICHIRO (OFFSCREEN): I
thought this might happen.
I had a vision of it earlier.
Now this battle
could go either way.
-Ichigo.
My son, I'm very proud of you.
You and your father
and Karin and Yuzu,
I am so lucky to have had
those years with all of you.
And I know that because of the
love that all of you share,
you will always keep the family
together and strong, even
without me.
Ichigo, live on, my son.
Live with strength and
kindness, and never lose
that smile, the smile you always
wore when you looked at me.
Ichigo, thank you for loving me.
[crying]
-Mother--
-Ichigo.
-Mother, now I know what
your last thoughts were.
-Hmm?
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): You
say anger dulls the blade.
You may be right about that.
But there's something else
that you haven't considered.
To kill a slimy scumbag like
you, a dull blade like this one
is all that I need.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN):
Sometimes, I
wish I could be like the rain.
If I were, then
would I have a way
to connect two hearts together,
the way the rain connects
the earth and the sky, even
though the two never touch?
With each day that
passes, Ichigo,
I think I've come to understand
you at least a little bit more.
[shouting]
-Curse you, Soul Reaper!
You haven't seen the last of me!
You'll burn for this someday!
-Coward!
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN):
Ichigo, it's over.
You did it!
You stopped him!
Put down your sword and rest.
This battle is over.
-No it isn't!
It won't be over
until I've killed him!
I have to!
-Ichigo--
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): I
will avenge my mother!
-I'm glad you didn't
die today, Ichigo.
I'm so thankful.
EIKICHIRO (OFFSCREEN): Your
friend is something else.
As you know, the power
a Soul Reaper possesses
is determined by his life force.
Heh.
This kid's potential is
a little frightening.
Well, time for me to head home.
After all, two's company.
Three's a crowd.
Isn't that what they say?
It looks like our little Rukia's
finally grown into a woman.
And, uh--
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN): Give
it a rest, will you?
-OK, have it your way.
But you know the Soul Society's
going to find out eventually.
Bye, Rukia.
Good luck.
Say goodbye to the kid for me.
-I'm so sorry, Mother.
I tried to avenge your death,
but I guess I failed you.
ISSHIN (OFFSCREEN):
Well, if your mom
can see that you're taking
good care of yourself,
then I think that'll make
her happy on the other side.
-Dad, those were
private thoughts.
You shouldn't eavesdrop.
Hey, I thought you quit smoking.
ISSHIN (OFFSCREEN):
Your mom told me once,
back when we'd only
been dating for a little
while, she thought I looked
cool holding a cigarette.
Now that I think
about it, that might
have been the first
compliment she ever gave me.
It might have been
the last one, too.
That's why I always smoke
just one when I come here
on this one day of the year.
-How can you smile
about anything here?
Why doesn't anyone blame
me for causing mom's death?
It would be so much
easier to understand
if you all blamed me.
I can't take it!
I can't!
ISSHIN (OFFSCREEN): Why
should we blame you, Ichigo?
If I were ever to blame you
for having caused your mother's
death, she'd never forgive me.
It's no one's fault
that she died.
Sometimes in life, bad things
just happen, and she knew that.
She was the woman I loved,
a woman with so much love
in her heart, she would do
anything to protect her family.
And remember this.
That woman, whom
I loved so much,
was willing to give up her
own life to protect yours.
-Wow, Dad.
-Ow!
What was that for?
ISSHIN (OFFSCREEN): Can't have
you going soft on me, boy.
Be strong, Ichigo.
Live well, grow old well,
grow bald well, and then
die long after I've died.
And if possible, die with
a smile on your face.
Otherwise, I'll never
be able to face Masaki.
Try to shake off that
gloom and depression, son.
You're way too young to carry
around such a heavy burden.
I'll be waiting at the
bottom of the hill.
-Are you listening, Rukia?
I want you to let me be a
Soul Reaper for a little while
longer.
I want to become strong
so I can continue
to protect the
innocent from Hollows.
I must become strong enough to
defeat any Hollow, especially
this Grand Fisher.
I can't face my mother
again until I've killed him.
-Ichigo.
THEME SONG: Nobody
knows who I really am.
I never felt this empty before.
And if I ever need
someone to come along,
who's going to comfort
me and keep me strong?
[singing in japanese]
-Whoa, was that one
scary Hollow or what?
I know I was pretty
pitiful in this episode,
and I didn't do much, but I
promise, in the next episode,
old Kon is gonna be rocking!
I'm gonna really show
my stuff! [inaudible]!
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
Kon, you don't
have any scenes in
the next episode.
-Gah!