[theme music]
-Guess I found one.
Who are you?
-Maki Ichinose.
-I see you're the
Soul Reaper who's
been working for the
Bounts, aren't you?
-I am no longer a Soul Reaper.
My allegiance is to the
great Master Kariya.
-So where are the Bounts, then?
-Enough of your
questions, Captain.
-If you won't answer, then I'll
have to force it out of you.
At least tell me why
you choose to fight
on the side of the Bounts
when you have this much skill.
-Because Master Kariya's
way is paved with justice.
There's no justice anymore
in the Soul Society,
but now Master Kariya
will cleanse this place
and purify it.
-You traitor.
Is that Ichigo?
-Well, it's Toshiro.
-Rangiku and Renji.
-It would appear that
most of the thugs
have already left
the forest, captain.
[screaming]
-Stop it!
I want off, I want
off, I want off.
Oh.
Uryu and Ichigo.
-What are you doing here?
-Chad and I came along
with Ganju and his friends
to try and stop all
of Kariya's thugs
from gathering in the forest.
-But for some
reason, there doesn't
seem to be as many of them as
we were told there would be.
-Hm.
I'm aware of that.
MAKI: You're all
too late anyway.
-Huh?
-Hm?
-You can't interfere.
I won't let you get
to master Kariya.
-And just how to you plan to
keep us from getting to Kariya?
Considering the fact that
you're outnumbered seven to one,
you're pretty confident.
-Go on ahead.
I'll handle this
situation myself.
-But Captain.
-I doubt that the Seireitei
is under any serious threat,
but still.
They've been steadily
increasing their powers
by absorbing reishi
ever since they arrived.
-We'll go warm the others.
Come on, Renji.
Let's go.
-I'm ready when you are.
-None of you are going anywhere.
Flash and brust.
Nijigasumi.
-What the devil just happened?
It's too early for the sun
to be shining this brightly.
-I can't see anything.
-What?
What is going on?
Ichinose!
-Captain Hitsugaya.
-Renji?
Where did you come from?
-I was about to ask
you the same thing.
I could've sworn that
Ichinose was attacking me
but it turned out to be you.
-But I don't get it.
-What the hell's going
on around here anyway?
-Don't get reckless.
We'll end up
attacking each other.
-What's he mean?
-It appears any movement
could be hazardous.
-Damn it.
This must be his
Zanpakuto's power.
-That's correct.
My Nijigasumi is a
Zanpakuto of light.
The light that
Nijigasumi releases
reflects and refracts
the air around you,
bending and altering the course
of light to create a new space.
-So the reflections
cause an illusion.
Still.
Even though he's
with the Bounts,
he is a Soul Reaper after all.
He must have spiritual pressure.
Then why can't I sense it?
-Is he shifting through
dimensions the way you do?
-No.
It's different I never
sensed him opening up space.
-He couldn't disguise
his spiritual pressure.
That would be impossible.
HITSUGAYA: That cave the
Bounts were hiding in
had a special mineral
that blocked our ability
to detect spiritual pressure.
Could he somehow be using that?
Damn.
We're wasting time.
-If we stand here
doing nothing, he'll
just pick us off one by one.
ICHINOSE: None of you
will leaving here alive.
-Everyone.
Be careful.
-(IN HEAD) It's useless.
-What was that explosion?
-What the hell?
-Well, if it isn't Ichinose.
It's been a while.
-Zaraki.
-We did it!
We found Ichi!
-Yachiru!
-Hey, jiggles!
How you doing?
I haven't seen you in a while.
ORIHIME: I'm good,
what about you?
-Ichigo.
When you visit the
Soul Society, you
should stop by and
say hello to me first.
I'll fire up the barbecue.
-I'll definitely
do that next time.
-Zaraki.
-Hey.
Looks like things have been
getting pretty entertaining
around here lately.
Hm.
-His spiritual pressure is
so immense it just blew away
Ichinose's spiritual pressure.
I can't believe it.
-Captain Zaraki.
The other Bounts have already
left to attack the Seireitei.
We would have gone as well,
but Ichinose stopped us.
-Huh?
-Kenpachi Zaraki.
-Ichinose.
They tell me you'd
rather live with Bounts
than with your own kind.
-What I do is none
of your concern.
-The head of the Bounts,
his name is Kariya, right?
-I don't have to
tell you anything.
-Ha.
You haven't changed at all.
So, what's your plan?
You were probably given
orders to stop these guys,
weren't you?
And if that's what you want,
then I won't try to stop you.
-What?
Have you completely
lost your mind?
-That is, unless you've still
got a grudge against me,
in which case maybe you'd
like to fight me instead.
-(IN HEAD) I should do
as Master Kariya asked.
I should dispatch this
group of Soul Reapers
as quickly as possible,
then move on to support him
and the others in the Seireitei.
Damn it.
-Ha.
-(IN HEAD) Master Kariya.
Forgive me.
-Your face shows
more determination
than the last time I saw
you, although that's not
saying much.
-Kenpachi Zaraki.
I will cut you down!
-Excellent.
I was beginning to get bored.
Let's get started then.
Show me what this
Bount has taught you.
Have you improved at all?
-All right Kenny and Maki.
Give it everything you've got!
-Be quiet and let
me concentrate.
Go watch some place else.
-OK.
-Kenpachi.
-Hey.
I think it's best if you
let Kenny and Maki settle
this one by themselves.
-Are you sure about that?
-Mhmm.
After all that's
happened, I think
Maki would like it that way.
-I guess I understand.
-We gotta go.
-Right.
-He's all yours.
-Now we can get
down to business.
Come on.
Hit me with your best shot.
-My pleasure.
-You've gotta be kidding.
You didn't actually
believe you could cut me
with those weak attacks?
That's all you gott?
I had expected better.
-I'm not done.
-What the--?
What an idiot.
Don't waste my time with
these foolish tactics.
Your time is up.
-Not so fast!
Flash brightly, Nijigasumi.
My Nijigasumi manipulates light
and makes all things invisible
when it shines.
When Nijigasumi is released
it dispels every shadow,
leaving nowhere to hide.
-How disappointing.
You haven't changed
one bit, have you?
-He deflected it with just
his spiritual pressure.
-Did you really believe
such a low level
attack could defeat me?
I thought you left the Soul
Society to improve your skills,
but I guess I was wrong.
You're not even a challenge.
I'm going to put an end to this.
-Maki's spiritual
pressure just transformed.
-You've been hiding something
from me, haven't you?
You should know better
than to hold back with me.
-Kenpachi Zaraki.
This is where the fight begins.
Flash brightly.
Saigyoku Nijigasume!
-Kenpachi Zaraki.
This is where the fight begins.
Flash brightly.
Saigyoku Nijigasume!
-Yeah.
Now, that's what
I'm talking about.
That's the way.
Nice, quick reflexes.
You have gotten better.
When you really try,
you're not half bad.
-Bastard.
You're as arrogant
as you ever were.
You haven't changed at all.
How could the 13
Court Guard Squads
allow someone like
you to be a captain?
It's completely ridiculous.
A captain of the 13
Court Guard Squads
is supposed to protect
those under him,
but who have you ever protected?
When you fight,
just who is it for?
How do you justify your
insane lust for blood?
-The same old song
and dance, isn't it?
You want to know the
reason why I fight?
I do it because it amuses me.
That's all the reason I need!
-You never even
earned the right to be
called a captain of a
13 Court Guard Quads.
The philosophy of
the Soul Society
has become rancid and deceitful.
Master Kariya sees
that corruption.
That's why I brought
him back here with me.
Master Kariya has
a vision, and I'm
willing to risk everything
to help him achieve it.
I gained this power
for just that reason.
-What are you going to do?
Talk me to death?
If you've got a
problem with me, why
don't you use that
power of yours?
What the--?
What the hell is this?
-You're seeing
Nijigasume's true power.
This is Saigyoku Nijigasume.
Now disappear, Kenpachi Zaraki!
Kenpachi Zaraki is dead.
Nijigasume uses my
spiritual pressure
to create limitless
beams of light.
Those beams will devour every
shadow as thy consume Kenpachi.
-He's not dead.
I can feel it.
-He is breathing, but it's
only a matter of time.
The light that has
engulfed him will soon
compress into a
high density being,
squeezing the life out of him.
There is no way to escape.
-Kenny won't lose to you.
-How pathetic.
Look, the compression
is beginning.
-Where am I?
For some reason, it's getting
harder and harder to move.
Heh.
My spirit energy.
Is there enough?
-Where are you going?
-I must assist Master Kariya.
-Don't you want to finish
your fight with Kenny?
-There's nothing left to fight.
-Kenny's not dead.
He's alive.
-He's dead.
And I'll do the same thing
to if you try to interfere.
KENPACHI: I might have
something to say about that.
Heh.
-But how?
Impossible.
What?
-Heh, heh.
-But how?
How did you--
-I released some of the
spiritual pressure which
I keep hidden inside me for
an occasion such as this.
-It can't be.
The way you could have blocked
Nijigasume's spiritual pressure
is with an even stronger
spiritual pressure.
And that's impossible!
-Your Zanpakuto derives its
power from Kido, doesn't it?
-Why?
What are you getting at?
-You haven't changed
at all, have you?
But I should congratulate
you, because even
though your
technique stinks, you
did make me use my full
powers for a second, there.
Although to believe that a
light could dispel all shadows
and engulf you-- it's idiotic.
The concept of shining
light on everything
is impossible to begin with.
It doesn't take a
scientist to tell you
that no matter how
much light you create,
there will always be a shadow.
-How does someone like
you get to this position?
A person without noble
goals or any sense of honor.
Why does someone like you
have this kind of power?
My captain based his entire
life on the principles
of justice and honor!
And then you-- How can you trust
anything the Soul Society says
when they let a barbarian
like you become a captain?
We have come to deliver justice
to the Soul Society that
is long overdue, and you
will not stand in our way.
It's because of people like
you that this is happening.
It's all your fault!
-You stupid idiot!
You talk about nobility.
Then why don't you
tell me about one
of these noble goals of yours?
And are they really
yours, or were they
just given to you
by someone else?
-Don't act like you
understand what I'm doing.
-All I'm saying is,
that's why you're a loser.
Relying on people and loyalty
are two different things.
It's no fun fighting someone
who doesn't have his own goals.
There is no passion.
-Why, then?
Why did you come all the
way out here to fight me?
Was it just to humiliate me?
-Heh.
If you had to really
been concerned
about achieving Kariya's
goals, then wouldn't you
have ignored me and stopped
Ichigo and the others first?
But you chose to ignore Kariya's
orders and face me instead.
Sounds to me like you
put your goals above his.
You believe that your power
had come through Kariya,
but that kind of power
can only be spawned
by hatred and your
desire to kill me.
If you really wanted to hurt
me, then use that hatred.
-(IN HEAD) This man--
could it be true?
-Oh, Kenny.
Oh, Maki.
-Have you made up your mind?
-(IN HEAD) Master Kariya.
I'm sorry.
When you achieve
your ultimate goal,
I may not be there
to share the glory.
Even so-- please forgive me.
-Come on.
-Kenpachi Zaraki!
My captain.
-Seems your hatred
wasn't enough.
Hm?
-Kenny, did you?
-I gave it everything I had.
Let's go home.
[theme music]
YACHIRU: Kenny, shouldn't you be
heading back to the Seireitei?
KENPACHI: There's
no need to hurry.
Ichigo will become stronger
when he fights the Bounts,
and I'll defeat
him when he does.
YACHIRU: That's so smart.
KENPACHI: So let's
wish Ichigo luck.
ICHIGO: Gah.
Why does my stomach
hurt all of a sudden?
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
guide to Soul Reapers.
-Welcome.
-Hanataro Yamada.
About this document.
-Right.
You see, it's a plan to
build a convenience store.
-Hm.
Please tell me you're not
really serious about this.
-Well, with the training I got
in the world of the living,
it'll be a piece of cake.
-It's not that I don't
think you can handle it.
It's just-- argh.
Captain, please talk
some sense into him.
-Hanataro Yamada.
-Yes?
-Make sure you carry
some cosmetics, too.
-Sure.
-Oh, Captain.