[theme music]
NARRATOR: In order
to save Orihime,
who has been kidnapped
by the Arrancars,
Ichigo, Chad, and
Uryu have snuck
into the world of the
Hollows, known as Hueco Mundo.
They crushed the Arrancars
who were trying to stop them,
headed to Sosuke Aizen's
headquarters, Las Noches.
They came across odd
Arrancars named Nel, Pesche,
and Dondochakka, and
wound up traveling
with the strange companions.
Ichigo go and his
friends hurried on,
but the Guardian of the
White Sand, Runuganga,
appeared before them
and blocked their way.
Faced with an enemy who was not
affected by physical attacks,
they were in a
perilous situation,
and could not defend themselves.
They were in grave trouble.
But at that moment--
-Why did you go off on
your own to Hueco Mundo?
Why couldn't you have
just waited for us
to come back and help you?
-Because, I had no idea if you
were actually going to come
back or not--
-Of course we were!
No matter what!
Renji and I were
planning on coming back
from the very beginning.
Why didn't you wait for us?
Why couldn't you trust us?
I thought we were supposed
to be your friends, Ichigo.
NARRATOR: Despite the fact
that Runuganga was utterly
defeated in battle, he appears
before Ichigo and his friends
once again.
He's still alive?
We're going to have some
problems with this guy.
-It can't be!
I standard him
into 1,000 pieces.
-Stop right there.
You'll go no further.
I won't let you take another
step toward Las Noches.
-Runuganga is made of sand.
So it makes sense for there
to be more than one of him.
-So this is a second body.
-Dance, Sode no Shirayuki.
Tsugi no mai, Hakuren.
[roar]
-Rukia!
-Want are you doing?
-Sorry.
I got too excited.
[scream]
-You hurt him, lady!
-Whoa!
[screaming]
-Damn.
-Huh?
What's that?
-Whoa!
-Hey, you guys, is
everybody all right?
-You could say that.
-Seems we're all right.
-Thanks a lot, Bawabawa.
[mumbling]
[scream]
-Boy, that hurts.
-Watch where you're
fallin', Nel!
PESCHE: An unfortunate
fate awaits you, evildoers!
-Look out!
Step aside!
Now, that was really close.
-Excellent reflexes, bad guys.
-Hell, yeah.
-Can you believe
that perfect landing?
-Dammit.
Whatever.
Where the hell are we?
URYU: Underground.
Right?
ICHIGO: We fell from up there.
Didn't we?
-Hm.
What's this?
-Hey, what's up?
Something wrong?
URYU: This is a tree.
ICHIGO: A tree?
-That's right.
It's the same as the ones
growing above ground.
Hm.
I see.
The trees above
ground are actually
the tops of these giant trees.
-They reach all the way up?
Right to the surface?
CHAD: Have you noticed
how huge this place is?
RENJI: Yeah.
Fact is, I can't see how we're
ever going to get out of here.
[shivering]
-Huh?
What's wrong?
-This is-- it's
the Menos Forest.
-Hold on a second.
What's that?
I've never heard of
the Menos Forest.
-It's exactly as I thought.
-What do you mean, Uryu?
Can you explain?
-Well, it was very far away,
but when we were all falling,
I could've sworn I
saw a group of Menos.
I imagine that in this world,
Arrancars and Espada both
live right on the surface.
While the Gillians and
all of the lesser Hollows
live underground.
Is that correct?
-Yeah.
You're right.
ICHIGO: Which means--
RENJI: It means that this forest
has Hollows behind every tree.
-Nel, do you know the
way back to the surface?
-Nel only hear rumors
of the Menos Forest.
It's a new place for Nel.
This is the first time
Nel has ever been here.
Nel doesn't know of
any way out of here.
D'aw!
This isn't any good!
We're all going to die for sure!
-It's really a forest of death!
-Yeah, man.
Danger!
-Hey, don't worry, Nel.
It's all right.
We found a way into this
forest, and now we're
going to find a way out.
-Ichigo.
-It's logical.
The fact that we can
see Hollows indicates
that they have a way in, which
really means there's a way out.
-Very good, evildoers.
That's a pretty
clever thing to say.
-You guys are very impressive.
-Honestly, it doesn't please
me much to be praised by you.
-Hm.
-All right.
If you guys don't mind, I'd like
to get the hell out of here.
-Hey, Ichigo.
Rukia's missing.
-Huh?
-When did she disappear?
-Probably when we were
swallowed up in the sand.
-What happened?
Where am I?
Ichigo!
Dammit.
Where are Ichigo and the others?
Damn.
Why are there so many Hollows?
I keep defeating them, but
their numbers don't diminish.
They're as many as when I began.
I have to rejoin Ichigo and
the others as soon as possible.
Ichigo!
Renji!
Where are you?
What's that?
Sode no mai!
Tsukishiro!
If I can just get there...
Menos Grande?
A Cero!
Whoa!
ICHIGO: Hey!
Rukia!
RENJI: Rukia!
Where are you?
URYU: Rukia!
-Hey, Soul Reaper!
-What's the deal?
We can't find her anywhere.
-We fell from the
same place, after all.
I don't really see how she
could've gotten that far.
-Oh-- I got it.
-What is it, Ichigo?
-Rukia's really small, and
kind of a lightweight, right?
OK.
Maybe she just got blown away.
-You're right, Ichigo!
That would explain it!
It makes perfect sense.
That's why we couldn't find her
when we searched this place.
-What do you think Rukia is?
Some kind of kite, or something?
[mumbling]
-Huh?
What?
Hold on.
What's he trying to say?
[mumbling]
-Oh.
Hey, Ichigo?
Bawabawa says that he's
going to climb a tree
and try to find her.
-Hm?
-Ah!
Bawabawa!
What a good boy!
All right.
Go!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Go and get a good look.
Look all around for
that vile Soul Reaper
with your sharp eyes, Bawabawa.
-Heh, heh.
That's a good idea, Pesche.
-Hey.
He just called her
vile, didn't he?
-And he doesn't
have eyes, either.
-You know, all of your
comments aren't helping here.
Wait a minute.
[mumble]
-I want to see what this
underground area looks
like as a whole.
Let me jump on and
look for myself.
-I'm going, too.
-Give it your best, Bawabawa!
We know you can do it!
-They don't give up.
Impressive.
-I'm very grateful
that you saved me,
but it's time to put me down.
You can let go of me.
I told you to let go.
Hey.
Are you listening to me?
See you later.
What?
Hold on.
What do you think you're doing?
-Just bear with me.
We will arrive at my
hideout momentarily.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): This man--
-Get ready.
-There are many
sounds in the forest.
-There are several odd
spiritual pressures.
-So, what should we do?
-They'll die if we
leave them alone.
-Hey.
We received a notice
from Las Noches.
-It looks like we're
going to have some fun.
Heh, heh, heh.
-Huh?
Hey.
Is that a light created by Kido?
It's true.
You're really a
Soul Reaper, right?
Where are you assigned?
What's your squad?
Tell the truth.
You left your
school, didn't you?
Well?
What do you have to say?
-My name is Ashido.
-Ashido?
-And this place is
called the Menos Forest.
-The Menos Forest?
-This is where Menos live.
It is a world that is far away
from the rules of the Soul
Society.
-What are you trying to do?
You don't want to talk, huh?
You have nothing to say?
He's strong.
I can tell that his
fighting style's random.
But still, it has
incredible strength.
Huh?
ICHIGO: Hey!
Can you see anything?
-No!
It's no good!
It's very strange.
When we were
falling, I could have
sworn that I saw a group
of Menos in this direction.
But I don't see
them anywhere now.
Where did the Menos go?
ICHIGO: What the--
-Huh?
ICHIGO: Take a look at that.
-Just listen to them.
What are they fussing about now?
ICHIGO: Renji!
Let's go!
RENJI: All right!
-Uryu!
It's Hollows.
-Hm?
[roar]
-Chad!
Uryu!
-Get outta my way!
[roaring]
-What's this?
-I have no idea.
-Now they're surrounding us.
-Here they come!
Ichigo!
-What is it, Nel?
Dammit.
Hide yourself!
-You should, too!
Hide, Ichigo!
-Don't go!
There's danger!
-Right.
The proper course is to
leave those evildoers.
-But we mustn't!
Ah!
[roar]
-Look at the size of them.
They're Menos.
-Yes, I see.
That certainly explains what
all that howling was about.
It's a Menos.
I should have
guessed that before.
[shaking]
-Bawabawa!
Please don't move
around like that.
My aim is-- ah!
-Getsuga Tensho!
Are you all right?
-Yeah.
Thanks to you.
[roar]
-Roar, Zabimaru!
-They keep coming
and coming, Pesche.
We're going to be eaten
for sure at this race.
-All right.
Our only option is
to bravely withdraw.
-But what about Ichigo?
-Listen, Nel.
You just have to make yourself
believe that those Soul
Reapers are complete strangers.
As if we never knew
them to begin with.
-Well, yeah, but we
already know them.
-That's precisely why
I'm saying to stop
knowing them immediately!
-Ah!
PESCHE: It may be
too late already.
[screaming]
-Nel!
-Ichigo!
-Dammit, we've been caught.
-They're gonna eat us!
-I'm coming!
[roar]
[screaming]
NEL: Ichigo!
Why are there so many of them?
-They're the same
ones I saw earlier.
-Aw, hell.
-Is this why you brought
me all the way here?
Was your only
purpose to kill me?
-So, that's all you've got?
In that case--
-Ah!
Huh?
[theme music]
NEL: We're going to
be eaten at this rate.
But what's the best
way to cook us?
DONDOCHAKKA: I'd probably
have a strong taste
if I were simmered
and made into a broth.
PESCHE: I should be
deep fried to savor
the sweetness of my flesh.
NEL: Nel would taste
great as a sashimi!
ICHIGO: You sure have a
lot of time on your hands.