[theme music]
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
So tomorrow, I die.
It seems strange,
but even when I
heard that my execution was
set for tomorrow, I wasn't sad.
It must because of the
dream I had last night, that
dream about the night
I can never forget.
MAN: Please, wait in
here for a moment.
The lieutenant will
be here shortly.
Make yourself comfortable.
-I, um--
-Yes, what is it?
-I'm just an ordinary
new member in the squad.
Please try to treat be the
same as everyone else here.
-Oh, yes.
Of course.
I'll try to keep it in
mind. [laugh] [sigh]
MAN: Did you hear
about this new girl?
MAN 2: Yeah, she's supposed
to be from the Kuchiki clan.
MAN 3: Great, just what we
need-- another captain's pet
getting treated better
than the rest of us.
-I heard she didn't even
have to pass the graduation
exam to get into the squad.
MAN: What a joke.
And here we've got to
bust out butts just
to stay out of trouble.
MAN 2: It's not fair,
but that's life.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): It's the
same here as everywhere else.
KAIEN: Hey!
What are you lazy bums
doing hanging around here?
Get back to your
posts, all of you.
-Hello, I'm Lieutenant
Kaien Shiba.
Welcome aboard.
-I see.
Yes, sir.
-What did you just say?
What kind of greeting
is that supposed to be?
I am your commanding officer.
You are supposed
to state your name
and say, pleased
to meet you sir.
What's your name, damn it?
-Uh, it's Rukia Kuchiki, sir.
-And?
-And-- and I'm pleased
to meet your, sir!
-All right.
You're OK, Rukia.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
A normal greeting.
A normal scolding.
A normal relationship between
officer and subordinate.
-Welcome to Squad 13, the
best squad of them all.
Unfortunately, our captain
isn't in the best of health.
So I pretty much run
things around here.
In fact, it's not a
problem if now and then you
forgot and accidentally
addressed me as Captain Kaien.
-OK, I'll try to remember.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): After
such a long, strange road,
that sense of normalcy
was exactly what I wanted.
RUKIA: Lord Byakuya,
my entrance to Squad
13 today was successful.
-What seat where you named?
-Uh, well, my deepest
apologies, brother.
But with my abilities, I wasn't
able to qualify for an officer
seed upon entry.
-I see.
You may go.
-Ah, not the long face again.
Now what?
-[gasp]
-And why is it you
practically jump out
of your skin every
time you see me?
You're hurting my feelings.
Anyway, I brought this for you.
So drink up.
-Oh.
KAIEN: Knowing you, you
probably won't tell me anything.
But I have to ask.
What's got you so depressed?
-Oh.
-Just remember this.
As long as you're a part
of this squad, Rukia,
I will stand by you even
if it costs me my life.
-Lieutenant--
-Ah, yeah!
-Smells like love.
-Oh, you're so cool, Lieutenant.
I just love a man in uniform.
-Did you hear that?
I'll stand by you? [laugh]
-You've got him wrapped
around your little finger--
-Kiyone, Sentaro,
shut up, you two!
How dare you show up
for duty drunk again?
-(SLURRING) Don't let
it get to you, Rukia.
I'm from the slums too,
so I know what it's like.
All of these snobs
telling me I'm
low class really gets annoying.
Whenever they try, just do like
I do and flick a booger at 'em.
Works every time.
-Now that's class! [laughs]
SENTARO: Right!
-All right!
That's enough out of
you two loudmouths.
Sober up and get
back t your post!
[sputtering]
-We were just having fun.
You're such a killjoy!
[laughs]
[arguing]
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
Kaien always had
a way of making me feel at ease.
-Die, Hollow!
-Well done, Lieutenant!
-Excellent!
-Make quick work of that.
-Just like you always do.
KAIEN: All right.
Mission accomplished!
[chattering]
-I hurt myself.
Huh?
Ms. Miyako.
-Are you all right?
-(NERVOUSLY) Oh, yes.
Yes, it was nothing.
Thank you.
-Oh, good.
I was worried for a second.
KAIEN: Hey!
Who's that?
Is that you, Miyako?
I wasn't expecting you.
How long have you been here.
-Oh, I've been here a
little while-- long enough
to see you take
care of the Hollow.
I just came in
case you messed it
up and needed me to save you.
-[laugh] Well, at least it's
nice to know you have my back.
-[giggle]
-Rukia, go alert the squad.
Have Sentaro and Kiyone help.
Tell them that
we're pulling out.
-Yes, sir.
And thank you for
helping me, Ms. Miyako.
-[laugh] You take
care of yourself now.
-Yes, I will.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): Miyako
was Captain Kaien's wife.
She had risen
quickly to the rank
of third seed
officer in the squad.
Not only was she
a strong warrior,
she was intelligent,
kind, and beautiful.
She was my idol.
I admired her so much.
I hoped some day I
could be like her.
Then one day, Miyako
received orders
to lead a
reconnaissance mission.
-Unfortunately, this Hollow
is an unknown entity.
And none of the Soul
Reapers it's attacked
have survived to report back.
Don't be reckless.
-You'd have to admit, that's
some pretty unusual advice
coming from someone
like you, Lieutenant.
[laughs]
KAIEN: Quit joking around.
-It's all right.
I take my mission as a
Soul Reaper very seriously.
And this Hollow's horrible
crimes cannot be allowed
to continue.
I'll do whatever I can to
put a stop to such evil.
-Ms. Miyako.
-Oh, don't worry about me.
This is just a recon mission.
We'll gather all the information
and leave all the heavy stuff
to you and the Lieutenant.
Recon team, let's move out.
-[together] Right.
[coughing]
-Do you need anything, Captain.
-No, thanks.
I'll be fine.
RUKIA: Excuse me.
-Rukia, is there any report yet
from the reconnaissance team?
I'm afraid not, sir.
They still haven't returned.
[footsteps]
-Sir, the recon team--
there's bad news!
[gasping]
-[gasps] Miyako!
-She's unconscious now, but
her life isn't in any danger.
-And the others?
-The others are all dead, sir.
-All four of them?
RUKIA: Kaien.
-We've had our share
of bad luck lately.
-Yeah, I can't believe
the whole reconnaissance
team got wiped out like that.
-Except for Ms. Miyako that is.
MAN: How is she?
Is she gonna be all right?
MAN 2: Yeah, they said
her life's not in danger.
MAN: Well, that's good.
She's one person the squad
really couldn't do without.
MAN 2: Yeah.
-Huh?
Ms. Miyako, should you
be out of bed so soon?
[shouting]
MAN: Miyako!
[shout]
-What's going on?
-[laugh]
-Ms. Miyako?
SENTARO: What happened here?
-This is horrible!
-Stop it, Miyako!
[gasping]
[splattering]
[shouting]
-Kaien, hurry.
I can't believe she did this.
RUKIA: Oh, Kaien.
KAIEN: Let me go
after her, Captain.
She couldn't have
gotten very far, sir.
-No, don't.
Think about it, Kaien.
Following her is exactly what
the enemy wants you to do.
KAIEN: That may be.
But it's still the only option.
This monster that's
controlling Miyako
used her to kill her own
men, men who trusted her.
Miyako's honor has been defiled.
You must let me go, Captain.
UKITAKE: Very well.
I shall go with you.
-What?
-Huh?
You, Captain?
-Mm.
You come too, Rukia.
-Yes, sir.
-You two-- seal off this
area and call the squad
to battle stations.
-[together] Understood, sir.
SENTARO: Let's go!
HOLLOW: I smell more
prey approaching--
more foolish meat.
RUKIA: What is that?
UKITAKE: Kaien.
-Huh?
-I'll go first, sir.
I'll scout out what
its abilities are.
Huh?
KAIEN: Captain, I beg of you.
Permission to go fight it alone.
-Go.
-[laughs] So you're
the first, eh?
You're nothing but a boy.
KAIEN: Tell me, how
many Soul Reapers
have you devoured so far?
-How many?
[laughs] Sorry, boy.
I don't keep track of
such trivial things.
-Have you ever, even once,
had any regrets about it?
-That's such a stupid question.
I have a heart, you
know, just like you.
There isn't a single night
that I don't have regrets
after eating a Soul Reaper.
Even now I'm having regrets
about that woman Soul Reaper.
I regret not eating
the rest of her!
[laughs]
-So you controlled her and
made her kill her comrades?
-Controlled her? [laughs] Oh,
not the way you're imagining.
I was actually inside her body,
then I ate my way out of her
and returned to the
form you see now.
Too bad you didn't
get to see that part.
[laughs]
Want to see what it's
like for yourself?
Come on, boy.
I'll eat you too!
[shout]
You're fast, but
not fast enough.
-Rankle the seas and
the skies, Nejibana!
What the hell?
-You fell for it, boy.
Once every night, the first
one to touch tentacles
will see his
Zanpakuto destroyed!
-[shout] Impossible.
I've never heard
of such a power.
-Kaien, get away!
Captain, Kaien
has been disarmed.
We have to help him.
-But if we were to
step in now, what
would become of Kaien's pride.
Even if by going to
his aid you are somehow
successful in saving his
life, the cost of such an act
would certainly be the
death of his pride forever.
-That doesn't make any
sense at all, Captain.
What good is pride to
a man if he's dead.
-Listen now, and
remember these words.
There are two kinds of battles.
And those of us who have
chosen to be warriors
and to fight those
battles must always
be aware of the difference
between the two.
There are battles that are
fought to protect lives,
and there are battles that
are fought to defend honor.
Right now, Kaien is fighting
with all his heart and soul
to defend honor-- that
of his men who died,
and his own honor, and above
all, his beloved wife's honor.
[growling]
-[laughs] What's the
matter Soul Reaper?
Too full of yourself to ask
your friends to help you?
-Shut up.
I don't need a sword or anything
else to handle scum like you.
We'll see about that.
Because now I'm
going to do unto you
just as I did unto your
beloved and delicious wife.
I'm going to play you like
a puppet from the inside.
And against your will,
you'll slay your comrades
with your own hand.
[laughs]
-Lieutenant Kaien?
HOLLOW: Yes, what is it, girl?
What do you want?
-[gasp]
-[slurps]
-Lieutenant Kaien?
HOLLOW: What is with you, girl?
Why do you keep repeating
my name again and again?
Are you that worried about me?
Or maybe you're in love with me!
-[gasp]
HOLLOW: [laughs] I guess if
you really love me that much,
then maybe I should
eat you first!
-Captain.
UKITAKE: Rukia, get out of here.
-Huh?
-Get out of here!
Run away, now!
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): Why, why did
this have to happen? [cries]
Kaien!
HOLLOW: Why I you
attacking me, Soul Reaper?
I think I know what
you're waiting for.
You're trying to think of a
way to rip me out of this body
so you can still
save your friend.
Isn't that right?
But this is different
from human possession.
We are both spirit beings, and
now our spirits are united.
It can never be undone.
[shout]
UKITAKE: I see.
Then you leave me no choice.
I'll kill his body
and you inside it.
HOLLOW: Are you insane?
What kind of a Soul Reaper
would slay one of his own men?
UKITAKE: Kaien no longer exists.
I won't let his body become
food for a monster like you.
Now die!
Coward!
[coughing]
Now, of all times.
Rukia!
You were supposed to get
away from here, you idiot!
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): I don't
know what made me go back.
I didn't have a plan.
HOLLOW: [laughing]
-Rukia!
HOLLOW: [growls]
KAIEN: My Captain--
RUKIA: [gasp]
KAIEN: --thank you
for understanding
and for letting me
fight to the end.
RUKIA: But Kaien,
does that mean you--
KAIEN: Rukia, I apologize to
you for getting you involved
in all of this in
the first place.
I know this was painful.
But thanks to you, I'm saved.
Now I can still
leave my heart here.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
No, I haven't done
anything deserving
of anyone's thanks.
I ran away because I
was afraid to fight.
[crying]
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
Then I ran back.
But it was only
because I couldn't
stand to see you suffer.
The only one I saved was myself.
I'm not worth
shedding blood over.
Not ever.
UKITAKE: Byakuya!
The execution-- it's been moved!
-Yes, to tomorrow.
-Well, what are you
going to do about it.
-Why should I do
anything about it?
-Huh?
Are you serious?
-The date has been set.
If that is the
decision and the order,
then there is nothing
to do but to head it.
Don't bother me again
with such petty matters.
Excuse me.
-Well, wait just a minute!
This is not some stranger.
Your sister's life
is at stake here.
If someone doesn't do
something, she's likely to die!
[coughs]
-You should be careful.
You'll only shorten
your life, Ukitake.
Having already lost
your lieutenant,
I wouldn't think losing
one more would matter.
In any case, Rukia is
a member of my house.
As such, whether she lives or
dies is none of your business.
I trust you'll refrain from
taking any reckless action.
[music - "happy people"]
SENTARO: I'm so devoted
to Captain Ukitake,
I'd follow him anywhere!
KIYONE: Give it up, Sentaro!
I'm way more devoted to
the captain than you!
SENTARO: Oh yeah?
Well-- well I stalk
the captain 24/7.
KIYONE: Well, I
check his schedule
and get where he's going
even before he does.
SENTARO: Wait a minute.
Is that even legal?