[yelling]
Hey, Ulquiorra, how's
it going?
We are going to drag her
back down from that palace!
Orihimeeee!
Goodbye.
[grunting]
I can do this...I can see
all his moves and still
react in time...
Watch!
Mm!
Uh!
[roaring]
The last time that we
battled together, I couldn't
read any of your moves at all.
So why am I able to
read your moves this time?
Actually, I think it's
because you've become
more human.
Did you say that... I've
become more human?
I see.
You must feel very proud
just being able to keep up
at this level.
Let's see how long
that will last you.
[gasping]
Uh!
Not a chance!
Hey, are you
coming or what?
I don't know, Loly.
This feels like a bad
idea.
I don't want anything
to do with her anymore.
You heard what he said,
didn't you? Lord Aizen
couldn't have been
clearer.
This is our chance. It's
the only shot we've got.
Just you wait. We are
going to find her...
... and then... we are
going to drag her back
down from that palace!
What do you think
you're doing, girl?
[gasping]
Why would you even bother
trying to save him now?
What do you mean?
Why wouldn't I?
He's your friend, is he?
And yet, you didn't protect
him from my first attack...
Why did you hesitate?
What?! You don't
understand, I--!
You actually don't know.
Then let me enlighten you.
The truth is--
Shut up.
You sure do love the
sound of your own voice.
Quit picking apart every
little thing she does or
says.
None of what you're
saying matters anyway,
all right?
Orihime, thanks
for stepping in.
Uh!
Find cover. It's gonna
get too dangerous for
you in here.
Just be careful.
You know, it's funny. I
didn't peg you for much
of a talker.
But you're a regular
chatterbox, aren't ya?
A Getsuga. You still don't
get it, do you? That won't
have any effect on me.
[yelling]
[grunting]
[yelling and grunting]
Huh?
He's wrapped a Getsuga
around his blade instead
of discharging it.
So that his sword
strike has the strength
of a Getsuga.
[yelling]
Not good enough.
I suppose you feel
that you're awfully clever.
Yet, you've learned nothing.
You forgot that even when
you had your mask on, you
were unable to defeat me
with Getsuga.
Wield it how you may,
it won't matter.
Using the Getsuga without
a mask is useless.
[grunting]
[gasping]
Uh!
Ichigo.
[gasping]
Well, well, well,
what have we here?
[grunting]
Uh! Orihime?!
Hey, what's the
matter with you?
There might not be that
many of them left, but we're
still in the middle of a
battle right now.
Yeah, but...
Orihime.
What about her?
Ichigo will take
care of her.
I don't know. He's up
against an immense amount
of Spiritual Pressure...
[grunting]
Damn it.
Better wrap it up
quick, then. We don't
wanna be too late.
Uryu!
Sorry it took me so long.
Mayuri's treatments took
longer than expected.
Well, get a load of you,
it looks like you made a
complete recovery, huh?
Uryu, we've gotta
get moving.
Yeah, I figured
as much.
Man, what the hell is
Ichigo doing up there?
Hmm.
[gasping]
[giggling]
Hey there, sweetheart.
Remember me?
Huh. I
guess not.
Aww, that's all right. I
mean, I can't say I'm
surprised, really.
I'm so ordinary, why
would the little freak
of nature trouble her
precious mind with
the likes of me?
[trembling]
That's about to change,
though. Say goodbye to your
ivory tower, hun. Your little
reign is over.
[gasping]
Orihime!
Who the hell are they?!
Stay back! Don't you
even think about it,
you hear me?!
Any closer and I'll
gouge her eyes out!
Getsuga!
Ulquiorra!
I don't want you to get
the wrong idea. I wasn't
acting out of a desire to
save you.
Out of the way!
I'm not going anywhere!
Ichigo!
Aw, that's a real shame.
Guess your knight in shining
armor, doesn't have what it
takes.
All right then! Tear this
tramp to pieces, Menoly,
and take it slow!
Menoly?
I don't want to.
There isn't any point.
No point?! What the
hell are you talking
about?!
Think about it. This
girl has the ability to
heal any wound, remember?
We'd just be
wasting our time.
And anyway, it's not like
it would make us feel any
less empty.
Oh, so what, you're
having a sudden change
of heart
all because this simpering
little idiot saved your life,
is that it?
Of course not!
[grunting]
You coward!
Forget it, then. I'll
handle her on my own.
[trembling]
Loly, wait!
Quiet!!
[whimpering]
Lord Aizen doesn't give a
damn about you. You're no
use to him now, he said it
himself. Got it?
I can do whatever
I want with you.
Without fear of
Lord Aizen's wrath.
You're a dead woman,
you just don't know
it yet.
And once I'm finally
finished with you, I'm
going to reach inside
your corpse...
... and tear out everything
you stole from me!
Orihime!
Getsuga...
... Tensho!
I said, get
out of the way!
If you want a new opponent,
you'll have to kill me first.
Finish me, if you
think you're capable.
Shut up!
And move!
[struggling]
[gasping]
[giggling]
Get away from her!
[trembling]
[yelling]
Huh?
What?!
What's that?
[growling]
[chuckling]
[grunting]
Ha!
[panting]
What's the matter?
Tell me again... what
you were saying before.
Was it that all of my
subordinates have
fallen?
Uh!
Hm. But that's all right.
Prattle on as much as you
like.
[laughing]
Oh, you should see the
look on your face.
Something's happening
with Master Ulquiorra.
Could this be...?
Another massive amount of
Spiritual Pressure has
appeared near Ichigo...
What could be happening
this time?
Hey, Ulquiorra, how's
it going!
I thought I'd come and
back you up. Need a hand?
You can't be serious. I
don't need any help and
certainly not from you.
What?
It's that guy again.
[chuckling]
Ah, don't be such a
stick in the mud.
Besides, this Soul
Reaper kid,
he's lookin' a lot
stronger than he used
to, am I right?
Let me have
a crack at him!
You're looking well.
It appears that you've
made a decent recovery.
But I'll pass. There's
nothing for you to do
here, Yammy.
Huh?
Go back and get a
little more bed rest.
Or find some other Soul
Reapers captains to play
with.
What are you
talking about?!
You're not gonna hog all
the fun for yourself now,
are ya?!
You know how you get
once you've entered that
state... You become too
greedy. The answer is no.
Ah, come on, lighten up,
Ullquiorra.
Yammy...!
Huh?!
Uh! Look, don't mind us!
We're not involved in any
of this!
We'll just get out
of your hair, okay?
Come on, Loly,
let's go!
You have got to be
joking! After we've
come this far?!
Loly!
We're in over our
heads, OK?
[screaming]
Menoly!!
Hey, Ulquiorra,
what gives, huh?
If you wanted to be alone,
then what the hell are all
these girls doing up here
with you?
Why don't
you ask them?
Huh. Yeah, I
guess you're right.
So, what's the story
with you two?
Why would a couple of
losers like you come
slithering out of your hole?
You're not
welcome here.
Here. Let me help
you find your way.
Get lost!
[grunting]
Are you kidding me?!
Don't tell me you're
done already!
Heh. Pathetic. I
didn't even break
a sweat.
Hey, Ulquiorra! These
two are a couple of duds!
I'm gonna come join you
over there!
[struggling]
Yammy, you bastard.
What are you
lookin' at?
Heh. I'm sure you're
getting a kick out
of this.
I was just about to
kill you... now look
at me.
Go ahead.
Laugh it up.
[gasping]
What are you doing?!
Get away from me! I
don't need your pity!
What's the matter with
you?! I mean, are you
out of your mind, or what?!
I was an inch away from
killing you, you little fool!
Why are you--- why are you
trying to help me?!
I don't understand.
What the hell are you?
[growling]
[screaming]
Orihime!
This is getting old. I've
already told you, you're
going to have to deal with
me first.
What? You're
still alive?!
You'd be better off dead
than to be wasting time
making friends with a human!
Ah, whatever. I think I'd
rather play with you! You
seem like you're more fun!
Leave her alone!
[chuckling]
[gasping]
Hmmm?
What the hell?
Now where were could you
have possibly been hiding
that dagger. Naughty little
thing, aren't ya?
You got a problem?
I don't give a damn about
you, okay? I just don't
wanna owe you any favors!
I'm sorry. Did you want
me to backhand your ass
again?
Shut the hell up Yammy!
Keep your filthy hands
off my catch, you hear
me?!
Poison! Escolopendra!!
I don't wanna hear one
more word out of you,
you dumb prick.
I didn't come all this way
to let a complete idiot like
you defeat me!
Ahhh!
Hmmm?
All of you are dead...!
You, Ulquiorra, everyone!
I'll cover you in so
much poison; there'll
be nothing left of you
but a reduced pile of scum!
Haaaaaa!
Hmm-hmm!
Heh.
[gasping]
[screaming]
Hmm!
[struggling]
Wait! Don't
hurt her!
Get back!
[gasping]
Nothing's changed. I
still don't care about
you.
I hate you more
than anything.
Heh.
[groaning]
Man, for such a dainty
little thing, you sure do
have an awful big mouth,
girl.
[struggling]
Damn it. Screw you. Think
I give a damn what you say?
You're pathetic. Ya know that?
Huh?! What'd
you call me?!
You heard me... you
pathetic scumbag.
[growling]
[laughing]
What were you saying?
Couldn't hear ya!
Hmmm. Well, that's no
fun, she already died
on me.
Knew this was gonna be
a waste of my time.
No!
Hmm? What, you got
something to say?!
Huh. Hey! Ulquiorra!
What's the deal with
this one?! Can I kill
her yet?
[gasping]
Don't touch her!
[grunting]
[struggling]
Orihime!!
[chuckling]
[gasping]
[laughing]
Hmmm?
[groaning]
Uryu!
Don't let yourself
get distracted.
You just focus on your
own opponent, Ichigo.
I'll deal with him.
Don't you worry. I can
handle his friend on my own.
How did Uryu get all the
way up to the Fifth
tower?
Making that kind of
entrance? I'm gonna
guess he flew.
Oh! Wait! I've heard there's
a tribe in the World of the
Living that gets around by
riding on broomsticks!
Bingo!
Uh, yeah, I'm a Quincy,
not a witch, OK?