We're here looking for the
guy named Ichigo Kurosaki!
Where is he!!
What's with that guy?
Just what era is he from?
I don't recognize
this guy at all.
So here's the
deal Kurosaki!
Until you decide to come out
here, me and my boys from
Miyasho High are sealing off
your school gate!
[Uryu]
Excuse me.
Huh?
Enough with the outdated
scare tactics. Can't you
see you're making everyone
nervous for no good reason?
Now hurry along
and go home.
Huh?!
What's that?!
Are you Kurosaki?!
What'd you say?!
Augh!
Hey! What the
hell was that?!
You asking for
trouble, ya punk??
That's exactly what I
was going to ask you.
What part of me
says "Kurosaki"?!
So what's with
this Four-Eyes guy?
I take back what I just said.
You don't have to leave.
In fact, don't any of you
think you're allowed to leave.
That idiot! Did he
just come out to
make things worse?!
You bastard!
- Get Him!
- Yeah!
- Kill Him!
- Come on!
Guh!
Ow!-Ow! Ow!-Ow!-Ow!
Ow! Ahh! Okay! Okay!
Hey! One, two, three, four...
My leg! That hurts!
Okay okay! I give! I give!
Six...
Agh!
Hey what's the
big idea?!
Why don't you tell me.
What did you jump in for?
What?! It's really
not obvious to you?!
I jumped in to get
you to back off!
That! That's the guy, Obuta!
Him? Grr!
He's the one
who jumped me!
Hm?
Hehh!
[Ichigo]
You're that thief.
Yaah!
The only reason I punched
you is 'cuz you were
rippin' someone off.
So what're you
crying about?
Ahh!
You shut up!
I've already heard enough here!
Ready for your beatdown?
Kuros--
Augh!
This is none of
your business!
they came looking for me,
so back off!
This became my
business a while ago,
so you back off!
If you get involved,
it'll turn into a huge mess!
Don't forget you're
our class president
ya dumb ass!
What?!
[in unison]
What the hell are you
two yapping about?!!
Uryu! You've been spending
way too much time hunting
Hollows lately!
You're bound to get the
attention of the Soul
Society, what then?!
"Hunting" Hollows?!
Actually, I'm
exterminating them!
And I only go when
Kisuke asks me to go.
You act like I'm
seeking them out!
I guess you've kinda forgotten
that Kisuke was a wanted man
by the Soul Society until
just recently, huh?
This isn't the time or
place to bring that up!
Text me or something!
[Ichigo]
Right! Like I know
your phone number!
Hey! When did you buy
a cell phone anyway?
I didn't buy it, Kisuke gave
it to me 'cause I've been
helping out with his shop.
Oh really? What is
that, from 1990?
[Yokochin]
Hey Kurosaki!
Hnh!?
[chuckling]
[Yokochin]
Ah! I'm glad to see
you're still doing well.
- [chuckles]
- You're in trouble now!
You do remember me,
now don't-cha kid?
No?
Why you bastard!
I'll kill--
Augh!
[Thugs]
Yokochin!
Huh?!
[rapid punching]
You seem to be having fun.
Ichigo my boy!
She knows you!
Do you know who she is?
[sputter]
My boss!
Always coming up with these
lame excuses not to work for me.
Well, this is
the last straw.
You're coming with
me right now!!
No way!
Heh!
Eghghghghgh!
Amazing. She just
hauled Ichigo off in
one sweeping move.
Who is she?
So now, what do we do?
I think I'll
just lie here.
Hey now! Take this
tape off of me!
I'll consider doing that, if
you promise me not to run off.
Y'know you're starting to
sound like a kidnapper!
Thanks for calling!
It's fast, cheap,
reliable Unagiya!
You want two double orders?!
Hey numbnuts! We're not an
unagi eel takeout place!
Huh?! I answered the phone
saying "Unagiya" because that's
our shop's name ya idiot!
[click]
[Ichigo]
Y'know...
I keep telling you this,
but why don't you change
the name of this store?
What?! just drop my family's
name from the store that was
passed down to me?!
Not gonna
happen!
Listen lady, I'm not
knocking your family name,
I'm just saying you
should change the
name of the store.
I won't do it!
And don't call me "Lady"!
Address me as Ms. Ikumi!
Now get to work!
Huh?!
Look after the Kondos' rabbit
over on Second Street!
Then organize Ms. Fukushima's
toy rat collection over on
Sixth Street!
And do yard work
for Mr. Yamashita
in South Kawase!
And there's a
lot more jobs.
While you've been slacking
off, more and more requests
have been stacking up!
Aw c'mon! You can handle
these things by yourself!
Hey Ichigo. Why do you
think that I hired you?
To slack off?
You're here, so you're
gonna work for me!
[Kaoru]
Mom, where are you?
Oh crap!
Wagh!
Mommy, I'm kinda hungry.
Oh, can I get you
something Kaoru my sweet?
Do you want some spaghetti
with meatballs? Or cheese?
I'm okay.
Oh! It's stupid
Ichigo!
What's he doing here?!
I know my Mom's pretty,
but don't try getting too
friendly with her, ya creep!
Bluuh!
Right now go wait in the
kitchen. I'll be there
in a minute, okay?
'kay!
Nyuuh!
That's enough.
I'm sorry. It's so strange
but you're the one person
he just doesn't warm up to.
I'm sure you'd like to
tell him what you think,
but try to hold back, okay?
"Tell 'im what I think"?
Like I'm not interested
in an old lady like you?
That hurt!!
[doorbell]
Huh? A customer?!
Hi! Please come in!
Uh?
Hi... Uh... Welcome.
[Ichigo]
What are you
doing here?
You two know each other?
Not quite.
Want some ramen?
No thank you.
We've got plenty
of unagi.
But we don't serve
freshwater eels.
[Orihime]
Uryu!
Hm?!
I heard that Ichigo's
been abducted!
Is it true?!
"Abducted"?
I guess it might've
looked like that to
somebody who saw it
from afar.
But in reality...
Hey, wait a sec!
[Uryu]
He's all right! It was
his boss from his job who
came by and grabbed him!
It was just his Boss?
I'm sure that's
what Ichigo said.
His pushy boss.
Hmm. It wasn't
anyone weird?
Well, I'd say that
she's a little weird.
But aren't most of
the people Ichigo
hangs out with weird?
Oh!
You're right!
You and I are both
kinda weird people!
Er, I meant that--
But you know what, for about
two days now I've been sensing
these really strange vibes
floating all around Ichigo.
Did you notice
anything, Uryu?
No...
I'm not really
feeling that.
No?
Oh! My job! Gotta go
or I'll get chewed
out by my boss too!
I'll see ya
tomorrow! Bye!
See ya.
She's right. Ichigo's Spirit
Energy is supposed to be gone,
but there was
definitely something
still there around him.
[Uryu]
And I'm sure it was
Spiritual Pressure.
[gasp]
Thank you for this food!
Hey.
[sip]
I said hey!
Why the hell did you
show up here and
start eating ramen
in front of us?!
When I asked you earlier you
said you didn't want any.
And I've gotta eat the
noodles before they
start to get all mushy.
Go eat it at your own house!
It's not like this is your
break room! It's mine!
So you don't think this
is a work space, you
think it's a break room?
But Ichigo's on the right
track with his question.
What're you here for?
You wanna hire us?
Of course I do.
I need a job done.
Let's talk.
Ya have any cold tea?
[gulping]
So, just what is it
you want me to do?
That's a strange thing to ask.
I don't want anything from you.
I've been looking for someone
who's willing to take on a
difficult errand for me.
And I happened to see
the sign for this place.
So I knocked, and you
answered the door.
It's sheer coincidence.
Sure. And you just
happened to have ramen.
Hmph.
So then, is this young
lady here the owner?
Huh?! I sure am!
Alright. Here's what I need.
[gasp]
Jinta, Home run!
Got it!
[Jinta]
Quit hitting a baseball in
front of someone's house!
Agh!
Ogh... Hey Jinta.
And the only one allowed to
hit a Jinta home run, is me!
Hrrgh!
It is not right to be
throwing a baseball that
hard at someone who
isn't wearing a mitt.
We're sorry.
Is your stomach okay?
I know that Jinta can
act so juvenile.
But would you still be willing
to play with him sometime?
Yeah...
[both]
Why we'd love to.
[Karin]
Is Mr. Urahara home?
Hm?
[Kisuke]
Yes, here I am!
Well! How unexpected.
[Kisuke]
If it isn't
Miss Kurosaki.
[Kugo]
I want you to do a background
check on someone for me.
This guy's name is...
Isshin Kurosaki.
You know him?
Is that a fact?
What are you kidding?
Isshin Kurosaki is my father!
You wanna know something
about him, then ask!
I'll answer
your questions!
You mean he's your old man?
What a crazy coincidence.
Yeah right.
You think you could answer
any question about him?
You really sure you know
your dad that well?
What's that supposed to mean?
Just exactly that,
I asked you a simple
question, and I need
some answers.
You think you know him,
But besides the obvious,
how much do you really
know about your father?
Fact is, there are probably
some really important things not
even you know about your family.
At least, not just yet.
Start by going to
Urahara's Shop.
I think you might find
something of interest there.
[Kisuke]
Are your back and shoulders
sore from the burden of
spiritual possession?!
Then you need Katakoran Alpha,
the anti-spirit rub!
For those times when you don't
want spirits following you, and
also for use in the bathroom!
Try Sekirei X, the
anti-spirit repellant spray!
Need instant escape
when a Hollow attacks?
You're good with these
electromagnetic restraining
pills- Zetaborutan!
Is there anything
else that you need?
Nope.
Well what about our
newest product,
Katakoran Theta?
How's it different?
It has Vitamin C.
Skip it thanks.
You sure I don't need
to pay you for this?
Yeah we're good. The thing is
I owe your older brother a lot.
I see.
So hey. How is your brother
anyway, same as always?
Yup.
And you're okay with
what's happened?
Yeah.
It's alright. Ichigo
doesn't need to get his
Soul Reaper powers back.
My brother's always been
fighting for us, even before
he became a Soul Reaper.
There was always something or
someone he had to protect.
And he always carried that
burden himself.
So the way it is now,
Is okay with me.
From now on, it's our
turn to protect Ichigo.
I'll see ya.
Hm!
Karin? What's she doing
at Kisuke's place?
[Kugo]
Are you worried?
You must be.
I mean, seeing your
kid sister visiting
the place of a dodgy
guy like Urahara.
Hey, there's nothing
dodgy about him.
Kisuke's the one--
That "saved all of us",
is that it? Well?
What?!
Just how much do you
know about your buddy?
And what makes you think
you understand Urahara?
Here's some advice.
Act now while you can.
That's if you want to
protect your family.
[Ichigo]
So I didn't get your name.
Just who are you?
I'm Kugo.
Kugo Ginjo.
Here's what you
need to know.
I'm not buying any of what
you're trying to sell me.
It's your call.
Wait. I wanna give you this.
Hm?
See ya!
Kurosaki.
Where'd that
old man go?
If I still had my Soul Reaper
powers right now, I could
trace his Spiritual Pressure.
[gasp]
[light sigh]
Guess I still haven't
gotten past it yet.
[Orihime]
Ichigo!
Hm?!
Hey, Ichigo!
Wanna have some tasty bread?
I've got plenty to share!
Hey why are you
fidgeting so much?
I-it's just...
Uh, I wasn't expecting
that you would invite
me up to your room.
Well it's not like this is
the first time you've been
up here, so what gives?
Here ya go.
Oh, thank you.
So hey, we can't eat
this much bread.
Oh... Are you sure?
Only four of us
live here and that's
a ton of bread.
Why don't you just take
some of it home with you?
I mean your boss was nice
enough to give you these
odds and ends, right?
They're not "odds and ends"!
They're unsold bread!
It's the same thing.
[mouth full]
Not the way you say it.
So, hey.
Yeah?
I'm wondering.
Has anything happened
to you recently?
[sip]
Not really.
Why would you ask me
something like that?
Well, I just had...
this feeling.
You did?
Yeah. It's just that,
how should I say this?
I guess I'm concerned
you might be in trouble.
Has anyone suspicious
been following you?
What's that?
Someone following me?
I guess I'm usually in
trouble of some kind.
But "being followed"?
That sounds more like
your style.
[chuckle] No one's
following me!
Oh well. I guess
that feeling I had
was all wrong.
Sorry to bother you.
Guess I was imagining
things and got concerned.
Hey, don't worry about it.
You're just looking out for your
friends, that's not a bad thing.
Oh hey! Lemme give ya back
that manga I borrowed.
Oh it's okay!
There's no
rush, really!
[Uryu]
This Spiritual Pressure
belongs to Orihime.
I guess she beat me to it.
I hope she finds the source of
those feelings she's having.
But getting an answer out
of Ichigo's not easy.
Instead of just asking
him straight out,
maybe I can get him to spit
it out if I take this step
by step.
Huh?
[gasp]
Oh no you don't!
There he is.
He's fast!
No ordinary human
can move that fast!
[Uryu]
I don't see any changes in
the reishi surrounding him.
So then how is he able to
accelerate like that?!
Huh?
What was that?
A light?!
Hm?
Ah!
It's your call.
"X-cution".
[sirens]
Huh?!
That sounds close...!
[Ichigo]
Uryu, lemme see
your cell phone.
[Uryu]
Sure. It works fine here in
the World of the Living.
[Ichigo]
Wow! The display's
in black and white.
[Uryu]
Pretty rare, right?
[Ichigo]
There's no camera,
or infrared features.
[Uryu]
That's 'cuz it's a vintage
phone that can't be found
anywhere else! Isn't it cool?
[Ichigo]
No one sells it
'cause it's so old!