This is way off the mark.
Kisuke must have made a
mistake in his calculations.
[Kagerosa]
Not really.
I summoned
you here.
Kageroza!
Don't blame your friend.
I tweaked the
Precipice World a bit.
What the hell for?
Heh heh heh heh heh!
Hyaah!
Why is Nozomi so important?!
Heh heh heh heh!
This is funny
to you huh?!
What did you hide
inside her?!
You're just full of questions,
aren't you, young man?
I'd love to answer them all,
but I don't have the time.
I'm on a tight schedule.
The more pressing question you
should be asking yourself is,
why did I summon you here?
You're here so I
can erase you.
Erase my existence?
Why am I your target?
Heh heh heh heh!
Answer me!!
Uh..?
You are a great threat to
my plan, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Eyah!
You are not human.
Nor are you a pure
Soul Reaper or a Hollow.
You're an anomaly.
I'm not even able to
create a Reigai of
you from Reishi.
Yaagh!
It's upsetting.
Really.
You're the unaccountable
variable, and frankly,
a thorn in my side.
Waagh!
I bid you farewell,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
[gasp]
What is it?
What's wrong?!
Ichigo's
Spiritual
Pressure!
It just completely
disappeared!
What?!
So just what do
you mean by that?
Exactly what
I said.
All of a sudden his
Spiritual Pressure
vanished.
That can't be!
[2 swords clashing]
Hado Number Four.
Byakurai.
[gasp]
Huh.
Hado Number Thirty Three.
Sokatsui.
Scatter...
Senbonzakura.
Huh?
You can't escape!
[gasp]
Rrgh!
Raaaghh!
Heh!
Nigeki Kessatsu!
Suzumebachi!
Haaaa!
Very impressive,
Captain Soi Fon.
Even with your rather slight
build, you were able to take
my attack straight on.
However, you lack the
destructive force to defeat
me with a single attack.
And as long as the attack
you use is Nigeki Kessatsu,
your aim gives away
your intention.
Reading your trajectory,
then redirecting it and
striking first, means
victory will be mine.
Hmph! Not if my attack
were to change.
Clones?!
Since my destructive force
isn't enough, I'll use numbers!
Tenken!
Huh?
Too slow.
Bleagh!
Not this time!
You won't get away!
[gasp]
Shunko!
[panting]
Ryujinjakka!
Bushogoma!
Shunsui!
You should be more
worried about yourself!
Very impressive,
Old Man Yama.
It's becoming more and more
obvious why you've been Head
Captain all these years.
Even with all the wounds you
have, you still stand tall.
Despite that, your
Spirit Energy is
gradually weakening.
If you had as much power as
earlier, I wouldn't be able
to heal the wounds from
your attacks so easily.
[Shunsui]
Definitely.
If we continue wearing
you down, this battle
will eventually end.
Your opinion has been
proven wrong before.
[Straining]
Haaa...
HYAAAAHHHH!
[exasperated]
Oh boy.
From the way he's
acting, he's got no
intention of giving up.
Then let us continue!
This doesn't look good.
The captains who've already
entered and are fighting
the Reigai seem to be
losing their battles.
Is there any
sign of Ichigo?
I'm afraid
there isn't.
[sigh]
Then... Does that
mean that...?
He was in the Precipice World,
but he entered as the Cleaner
was approaching.
It stands to reason he
was probably swallowed.
By the Cleaner?
But how?!
[gasp/grunt]
[Nozomi]
I don't believe it...
Huh?
Just a minute ago, he...
[Ichigo]
Hey! What's with the
sad face, Nozomi?
Nothing,
I'm okay.
Don't worry; you'll be safe.
Everyone's going to be looking
out for you while I'm gone.
Well, I better get going!
It's... all my fault.
Nozomi...
No!
Huh?
[sobbing]
Ichigo...
Heh. So.
You can still move?
If I can't hit you with
Suzumebachi's second sting,
I'll just wear down your
strength until you have
no way to stop me!
Yaagh!
Huh?
[gasp]
[Kon]
Don't worry!
Huh?
It'll take a lot more than
that to wipe out Ichigo!
[chuckles]
Mh...
Oh come on!
Are you telling me you don't
believe what I just said?!
He's right, Nozomi.
It would take more than
just that to kill Ichigo.
Yeah. And besides,
Ichigo was the one
who made the decision
to go out there.
Don't feel like you
were responsible.
Because you weren't.
What everyone's been saying
is true, so there's no
point blaming yourself.
Nozomi, that rascal Ichigo
always keeps his promise!
You gotta just
trust him and wait.
Mh...
Hey! Why are you looking at
me like that for Nozomi?!
Tell me. How can you have
so much faith in him?
The two of you are always...
at odds.
Uhh...
Uuhhh...
Don't go thinking that
I actually believe in
him or anything!
We're not even friends!
I'm his boss and he's
my servant!
And I say--
Whooaaa!
Okay.
But the situation he's
gotten himself into
must be pretty bad.
Maybe we should go
to the Soul Society
as well.
Now you're really worrying
for nothing, Chad.
Yeah, You shouldn't
underestimate our captains.
Hngh...
This is where
it ends.
Tenken!
What?!
[panting]
I let down my guard.
I didn't anticipate you
having that much strength.
I will do whatever it
takes to defeat you.
And when I
finish with you,
I'll go help Sir Genryusai,
the man who taught me how
to fight as a Soul Reaper!
That isn't going
to be possible.
Why not?
The Head Captain's fate...
is about to be sealed.
[raspy panting]
Come, Master Genryusai.
Let's put an end to this,
shall we?
It's just too bad,
Old Man Yama.
[Soi Fon]
You must've noticed it.
The Head Captain's
Spiritual Pressure
is becoming weaker.
And he's not the only
one getting weaker.
Kenpachi Zaraki,
Toshiro Hitsugaya
and Byakuya Kuchiki.
None of those real
captains will survive,
and have the opportunity
to reach Kageroza.
All you Reigai
underestimate our
Head Captain.
What?
[Komamura]
For the past thousand years,
Sir Genryusai has remained
as the most powerful
Soul Reaper that lives.
[gasps]
Huh?
Oh damn!
Feel my Ennetsu Jigoku!
Resist until you are ashes!
It appears you no
longer have your
strength or speed.
You don't appear to be
able to move, either.
True.
I don't seem to
have much Spirit
Energy left.
Captain Soi Fon,
why is it that
you fight?
Heh. Because it is
my duty to fight.
I see. That's exactly
the kind of answer
I'd expect from you.
But that can't be
the only reason.
What?!
Someone who rises to the
rank of captain can't
increase their powers
without bearing some burden.
There must be something more.
Another reason for you to fight.
Ngh.
I sense you have
another reason.
We all possess something
inside us that we
cannot compromise.
It's that inner passion
that gives us the strength
and courage to fight.
Well, let's settle this!
Bankai!
Kokujo Tengen Myo-oh!
In your weakened condition,
you no longer have any means
of avoiding my attacks.
Don't be so sure.
I too have my last
resort move ready.
We will see. For a warrior like
me, the thing I desire most of
all is a contest of strength!
Bankai!
Jakuho Raikouben!
This goes against my pride,
but I must win.
Ugh.
[crowd gasps]
Sir Genryusai. I'm on--
Ahh. Another large
Spiritual Pressure is gone.
Captain Zaraki,
Captain Komamura,
And even Head
Captain Yamamoto.
Not one of them was
able to find their way
here and reach me.
Soon the remaining captains
will be gone, like the others.
You can't fight me any
more with your wounds.
Yet you still
won't give up.
There's only one head
of the Kuchiki clan.
There can't be two.
Bankai.
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Senbonzakura
Kageyoshi.
[Nozomi]
Are the captains
that amazing?
[Rukia]
Yes, but there's nothing
to be afraid of.
His noble presence...
[Renji]
And his wealth!
[Rukia]
His unparalleled
artistic sense...
[Renji]
And his wealth!
[Rukia & Renji]
That's who our
Captain Kuchiki is!
[Nozomi]
Uh, I don't get it.