[theme music]
-Sometimes we must carry
out justice on our own.
-Such foolish talk.
You have no right to
decide for yourselves
what is right and wrong.
It is your duty to accept the
true justice of the world.
-Then what is the true
justice of the world, Master?
Who determines right and wrong?
-Did you not hear me before?
The time for words has passed!
[music playing]
All things in the
universe turn to ashes.
Ryujin Jakka!
-[singing] Oh, Captain!
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
Captain Zaraki, where have
you disappeared to, sir?
Hello?
La la la.
Ah, there you are, Captain!
I've been looking for you.
You won your battle already?
-No, they fled.
It was looking like
a good fight, too,
but that wolf-faced bastard ran
off before we even got started.
-Wolf-faced?
-He suddenly started screaming
about old man Yamamoto fighting
somewhere.
-Ah, yes.
I can feel that, too, not that
you've mentioned it. [laughing]
-What the hell?
Why are you so cheerful
all of a sud-- uh, huh?
You mean you won without
getting so much as a scratch?
-Yes!
Oh, but I should tell you, I
did get my outfit kind of dirty,
so I had to go change clothes.
That's where I just came from.
-Somehow you actually
look healthier
now than you did
before the fight.
-Do you mean it Captain?
Do you really think
I look beautiful?
That's so nice of
you to tell me.
-That's not what
I said, you moron.
Get a grip.
-Oh, I'm sorry, Captain.
I got a little carried away.
I guess it's because
it's the first time I
battled like that a long time.
And I must say, I rather
enjoyed the feeling.
-[gasping] Damn him.
How could he have
suckered me like that?
I've never seen a
Zanpakuto like that one.
YUMICHIKA (VOICE OVER): I would
imagine that by now you're
curious about the true
power of my Zanpakuto.
What I'm about to show you
is confidential, of course.
My Captain and Ikkaku will be
mad at me if they find out.
-Somehow he drained m
of all m spirit energy.
Damn it!
It's coming from
the old district.
SHUSHEI (OFFSCREEN):
That Captain Yamamoto's
spiritual pressure.
-How many years has it been
since I've seen this born?
How long since I felt
this fear like the weight
of the deep sea?
This transcendent spiritual
pressure even in its Shikai
state, this heat, scorches
the heavens and consumes
even the clouds.
That blade turns everything
before it to ash.
That most terrible Zanpakuto,
the oldest and greatest
of them all.
It is Ryujin Jakka.
-What are you waiting for?
Go on and release your swords!
You haven't much time.
Surely you don't
wish to be burned
without even challenging me?
-I guess it can't
be helped, Jushiro.
Shall we?
-Yes.
All Waves, rise now
and become my shield!
Lightening, strike now
and become my blade!
[speaking japanese]
-Flower Wind rage
and Flower God roar.
Heave Wind rage and
Heavenly Demons sneer.
[speaking japanese]
-[speaking japanese] These two
are the only true Zanpakuto,
and they are magnificent!
Just like the old
days, the two of you
have lost none of your power.
-Thank you, Master.
-Are you both ready to face me?
-Yes, any time.
[music playing]
[crash]
-Any pain, Jidanbo?
So how did that one feel?
-Yeah, we want you
to be fully healed.
-I feel great I'm as
good as new, in fact.
Many thanks to you for
helping me get better.
-No, not at all.
We're happy to help.
-It was the least that we
could do for you, Jidanbo.
-If you want to
thank someone, you
should probably thank
that Ryoka girl.
She worked for hours
on healing your wounds.
If not for her, you probably
would have lost that arm.
-Her name was Orihime.
I remember.
-Yeah, and I know
why you remember.
She was a cutie.
-It's been five
days now since she
and her friends went
into the Seireitei.
-Five days, huh?
I have to say, I don't
think much of their chances.
KUKAKU (OFFSCREEN): Are
you really that worried
about her, Jidanbo?
If you're so concerned,
why don't you come with me?
-Oh, what?
Miss Kukaku Shiba?
-Yeah, you got it.
-[together] Ah!
Greetings, Miss Kukaku.
We're at your service.
-Report.
-Jidanbo, seems fully
healed, Miss Kukaku.
You can see for yourself.
-Uh, what is it, Miss Kukaku?
You look like you want
something from me.
-You've been asleep
for five days, Jidanbo.
You and I have a few
things to talk about.
Let's go for a walk and
discuss a few things,
like some unfinished
business with Yoruichi.
[music playing]
[wind blowing]
[footsteps]
-Hah!
[music playing]
-I'm not impressed.
For someone who's spent as many
years hidden away as you have,
it doesn't seem
to me like you've
gotten any stronger, Yoruichi.
-Well you, on the
other hand, looks
like you've let your skills
get rather dull and rusty.
-I noticed there was a Shihoin
symbol on the Tentoken flying
cloak that Ryoka
kid was wearing.
You have him that, didn't you?
-That's right.
There was no way for him to
save Rukia if he couldn't fly.
-How shocking to see evidence of
corruption in the Shihoin Clan.
It's a disgrace to learn
that one of their members
has been actively
supporting a Ryoka
invasion of the Seireitei.
And it seems the Shiba Clan
has become involved, too.
What a shame to see how low the
four great houses have fallen.
-You certainly are
talkative today, Sui-Feng.
Is it because you're excited
to see your old mentor again
after so many years?
Or are you just expressing
your usual pent up anger
like the child I remember?
Well?
Which is it, Commander?
Has it been a little
too much for you
following in my footsteps?
-Don't flatter yourself.
You still act like
you're better than me,
but those days are gone.
I'm the one with
all the power now,
because I'm the one who controls
the Stealth Force, Yoruichi
Shihoin!
need Your time is passed!
[music playing]
Let me show you the difference
between you and me now.
As you already know, when the
leader of the Stealth Force
draws her sword, an
execution battle is eminent.
Any opponent must die.
And if that should happen to
include a former commander,
then that is what
will have to be.
You chose to throw away
the title that I now hold.
Just look around you.
There's no escape
for you, Yoruichi!
-I really hate being
underestimated like that.
It's true that I threw away
the Stealth Force title,
but there is one other title
that I never relinquished.
-Flash Master, Yoruichi!
[cloth tearing]
That's not a real title.
But since you
claim it, you leave
me no choice but to rip it from
you with my own bare hands.
-You still wear
the keisen uniform
of the Punishment Squad, huh?
I didn't know you
were so traditional.
-Does it make you
think about the past?
-Yes, it does a little.
-Think back some more now.
Try to remember,
and don't hold back.
Compare us.
Between you we me, which of us
shines as the better warrior?
[music playing]
It seems I've taken a hit.
One for one, then.
We're even so far, Yoruichi.
-So it seems.
Have you got some gimmick hidden
in the folds of your uniform?
Your movements have
improved, Sui-Feng.
-Some kind of gimmick?
I guess you could say that.
I'll show you.
Sting all enemies to death.
Suzumebachi.
You can't escape me!
Why can't you just accept it?
Admit that I'm
better than you now.
I may be better
than you ever were.
I was just holding back before.
I know, you didn't
think the likes
of me even had anything
to hold back, did you?
That's what you were thinking.
I told you not to
underestimate me.
I told you that I'd make
you sorry if you did.
I stayed and grew
stronger while you
ran and hid from the
battlefield for 100 years,
and now you're going to pay for
it with your life, Yoruichi!
Remember my power, Yoruichi.
The power of Suzumebachi is
in its Homonka, or Death Mark.
The Homonka is etched into
the body of the target
with my first attack,
as you can see.
The last time you were here to
see it, I hadn't perfected it.
But over the last 100
years, the Homonka
has finally become complete.
So I suggest you be careful
not to take a second hit
and then try and
run away, Yoruichi.
The Suzumebachi's killing
power is in the second strike,
so all I have to is hit you
in the same place once again,
and you die instantly.
Here comes the second
attack, Yourichi!
[music playing]
-Ha!
Showing your back to the
enemy and running away
isn't much of a strategy, is it?
I suppose you're running in
order to buy yourself time,
but it's useless.
You to know why?
Before it was
perfected, my Homonka
used to disappear after a
while, but now it lasts forever.
Those marks on you will never
come off unless I make them.
So you can run and run
all you want, Yoruichi.
Go ahead and try to
escape, but those Homonka
will stay on until I
hit one of them again!
[inaudible] Too slow.
[music playing]
Now do you understand what
I've been trying to tell you?
I'm simply better than
you are, Yoruichi.
Now that I've made my
point, I can finish you off!
-You've never seen such
a fighting technique
before, have you?
It's unique because
it combines elements
of both Hakudo and Kido.
It's something I created myself.
You should feel
privileged, actually.
This technique has only
been perfected recently,
so you're the first victim of
it in actual combat conditions.
It doesn't even have a name yet.
-Wrong.
It has a name.
-What did you just say?
-It's called Shunko.
-You don't know what
you're talking about.
-Don't you know why that
keisen uniform you're wearing
leaves the back and
shoulders exposed?
Because those parts
would be wasted.
When this move is
performed, a dense Kido
envelopes the user's
back and shoulders.
The Kido draws power first
to the arms and legs,
and then explodes it outward.
In other words, the moment
the move is activated,
any fabric on the back and
shoulders would be blown off.
[music playing]
The fact is, I
really didn't want
to have to resort to using
this technique against you.
You better be careful, Sui-Feng,
because to tell you the truth,
even I can't control
this technique very well.
[theme music]
MALE SPEAKER (VOICE OVER):
Yoruichi has gotten all
serious, so in the next
episode, I'm gonna--
FEMALE SPEAKER (VOICE OVER):
You're going to strip?
MALE SPEAKER (VOICE OVER):
No, I'm not going to strip!
I'm not like you!
FEMALE SPEAKER (VOICE
OVER): You're not?
How boring, I was kind
of looking forward to it.
MALE SPEAKER (VOICE
OVER): Then I will do it.