[theme music]
NARRATOR: One by one,
Ichigo and his friends
were defeated by Espadas.
Genryusai Yamamoto
dispatched several captains
of the 13 Guard
Guard Squads to aid
in the fight against the
Espadas in Hueco Mundo.
Byakuya Kuchiki faced Espada
number seven, Zommari Rureaux.
He arrived just as Zommari
was about to finish off
Rukia, who had been knocked
unconscious by Aaroniero.
-The reason I'm
killing you is simple.
It's because you aimed your
blade at my only pride.
Now, this is your fate.
-Lord Aizen!
I'm sorry--
NARRATOR: Meanwhile,
Mayuri Kurotsuchi
had a tough fight with
Szayelaporro Granz
and his doll.
The doll could control
Mayuri's senses.
-It's all over.
-It can't be.
[laughter]
-This is so easy,
it's become boring.
I thought there would
be more to it than this.
-I got you.
-Ah!
What's going on?
NARRATOR: Mayuri had studied
Szayelaporro's strategy.
To protect himself
against the doll,
he created replicas of
his internal organs.
Furious, Szayelaparro
quickly changed tactics.
Using his tentacles, he grabbed
Nemu Kurotsuchi and tell
held her as his hostage.
-My goodness.
Everyone keeps chattering.
It's so noisy.
Bankai.
Now, claw out.
[crying]
MAYURI: Konjiki Ashisogi Jizo!
-This gas-- some
kind of bacteria?
[scream]
-Oh, thank goodness.
You're awake.
RUKIA: Lieutenant Kotetsu?
Hanataro?
Why are you here?
-Wait, your treatment
isn't finished.
Please lie still.
-I'm sorry, but she's right.
You can't get up yet.
-Byakuya.
My brother.
-Silence.
Didn't you hear what
Lieutenant Kotetsu said?
Lie still until they're done.
-But brother-- your uniform.
-It is not important.
-You're hurt.
-I said it doesn't matter.
Right now you must rest until
you are healed completely.
You have to prepare yourself for
the real battle the awaits us.
[shout]
-You're not too bad, you know?
-Heh, heh, heh.
-For a pathetic Soul Reaer.
-You're pissin' me off.
I've about had it with
your trash talking.
Stop messing around and fight.
[shouting]
-Most people I attack would
try to avoid my blade.
-Yeah, but my way
is much more fun.
Besides, when I fight, I
expect to get a real battle.
And this cut's nothing
but a little scratch.
-Heh!
We'll see about that.
-I'm impressed.
That attack was
pretty damn good.
Argh!
-Guess your brute
strength wasn't enough.
-Nothing to do with it.
I had you dead to rights.
The sand got in the way
of my sword's trajectory.
-Is that so?
[shout]
-Ichigo!
-Orihime-- you gotta help.
-Right.
Hang on.
I'll heal you.
-No.
Not for me.
Not yet.
Heal Nel first.
-All right, Ichigo.
I'll heal her right away.
-Hm.
Ah, yes.
I can hear them.
It's those two barbarians.
They're still tearing
each other apart.
Hm?
-Uh-- are you seeing
what I'm seeing?
-As much as I wish I wasn't
seeing it, yeah, I am.
It ate him.
-I'm watching it, too.
You don't need to gross me out.
-RENJI: What?
You asked me if I saw it.
I was just answering
your dumb question.
-Yes, but you don't need
to describe it to me.
Hey, Renji, you've been
infected by the poison, too.
-I have?
Wait.
Why isn't this stuff
affecting you, too?
-Well, I've been infected
by that poison before.
I probably developed antibodies.
-No fair.
You get a free pass?
Why's it gotta be me?
-What's not fair about it?
I almost died last time.
Well, whatever.
You're going to need
that antidote fast.
Hey, Mayuri?
-Uryu, no!
-You know, you really shouldn't
make assumptions like that.
It's only common sense to
alter the formula of a poison
after every use.
-You bastard.
-Don't get worked up.
It'll only spread the poison.
MAYURI: Developed antibodies?
Hmph.
Don't you think a professional
would prevent that?
URYU: Forget that.
Just give us the
antidote, or we'll--
RENJI: What did I just say?
You've got to calm down.
-Master Mayuri?
I beg your pardon, sir?
Could you come
over here, please?
I just need some help
getting untied from this.
-Hey.
You heard her, didn't you?
Why don't you go help her out?
-Talk about irritating.
Fine, then.
Here's the antidote.
-Hang on.
Don't throw it!
Hey!
No!
The bottle broke!
[crunching]
[gasping]
[screaming]
-What's going on?
Something strange is occurring.
Hey.
Mayuri.
What are you waiting for?
Hurry up and untie her!
[gasping]
-What the hell is that?
-You really thought
you killed me?
-Wait.
That voice!
-Szayelaporro.
-Behold, La Lujuriosa's
most brilliant technique.
Gabriel.
It gives me the
ability to regenerate
using my enemy's own life force.
Gabriel invades
my opponent's body
and absorbs her
reishi from within.
Or more precisely,
replaces it altogether.
You see, I use those cells
to fuel my regeneration.
The reconstruction
process requires every bit
of reishi in my opponent's
body to be overtaken.
Obviously, the
target is killed off.
And finally, I am reborn.
Now, then, what do you say
we all reintroduce ourselves,
Mayuri Kurotsuchi?
-That guy's an animal!
-Did you get all that,
Mayuri Kurotsuchi?
By constantly
renewing my body, I
will continue to
exist for eternity.
It is said that the
Phoenix is immortal.
When it grows too old, it
hurls itself into the fire,
and from the flames
it rises again, anew.
Understand now?
That is immortality.
That is perfection.
It's not about
transcending death.
It's about incorporating
death into the cycle of life.
And a being whose existence
cannot be interrupted by death,
someone such as myself, who
thrives in the endless cycle
of demise and rebirth, that is
what you would call a perfect
being!
The concept of mortality
does not exist for me.
Even if you did
manage to smite me,
I would simply rise again
without a definitive end.
Understand this.
I cannot be killed.
Even if you tried
for all eternity,
you could not defeat
me, Mayuri Kurotsuchi.
-Huh?
-Captain Kurotsuchi?
[gasping]
-M-- Master Mayuri--
I-- I'm so-- sorry.
-What's the matter?
Can't stand watching your
dear second in command
on the precipice of death?
You're a sensitive little
fellow, aren't you?
But no matter.
She doesn't have long now.
This girl, oh, how
can I describe it?
It's as if she's
the empty cocoon
a butterfly has left behind.
-How delightful.
Really.
Such an amusing little power.
It tickles my fancy.
And-- is that all you've got?
-What?
-Come on.
You must have something else.
I mean, you called
yourself a perfect being.
Surely you must have
some other power
you just forgot to mention.
Yeah?
-What is he doing now?
MAYURI: Oh, don't be so serious.
Telling me won't make
me think less of you.
Don't be coy.
Go on, show me.
Let's see it.
[crying]
[laughter]
-Did you really think that
behemoth could eat me,
and nothing would happen to it?
When it consumed me, my
cells dissolved into it
and took over its
nervous system.
I may not know exactly
how your Zanpakuto works,
but by taking over the
nucleus of its motor controls,
I don't really have to.
Even this Bankai thing
is mine to play with.
What rotten luck.
Too bad your Bankai takes the
shape of a living creature
that I can control.
-Ah!
-My, my.
This is a tools that I created.
You think it can
defy its master?
In the event that it
is used against me,
I designed it to
simply self destruct.
Well, I suppose this means you
have no other hidden power.
In that case, why
don't we move along?
I'd like to use you as a
test subject for a new drug
I've developed.
There's no need to
put up your defenses.
-What's he doing?
-No idea.
-The drug I'm testing
is (IN SLOW MOTION)
already inside you.
-What?
His voice-- what the--
MAYURI: Yes.
I placed several drugs
inside Nemu's body,
knowing that if
Nemu were devoured,
or her body somehow
compromised, they
would be released
into her opponent.
-What drug?
What the hell did you give me?
-Well, judging by
the area of her body
through which you just passed,
it looks like this is it.
Relax.
This one isn't a poison.
Let me see.
I suppose you could call
it a superhuman potion.
-Superhuman?
MAYURI: When two
swordmasters fight,
they often describe a sensation
where their blades seem
to freeze in midair, as if
their sense of time slows down.
Such phenomena
are known to occur
when one's senses are
pushed to their limits.
Well, my drug forces
your consciousness
into that state of
heightened awareness.
In other words, it's a
drug that will allow anyone
to experience the
superhuman limits of ability
and sensation.
SZAYELAPORRO (VOICEOVER):
What is this?
He's speaking so slowly.
I can't understand him.
-Are you still
following me, Espada?
With this drug, a bullet would
look completely motionless,
even to a child.
So now in your superhuman
state, a normal person like me
must look bizarre, my movements
exceedingly slow and tedious.
(IN SLOW MOTION)
Slow and tedious.
Now, then, this sword-- does
it appear to have stopped?
Voila.
And the amazing thing
about this potion?
The master swordsman's senses
are only heightened the brief
instant his blade
crosses his enemy's.
But my superhuman potion
amplifies your senses
by a factor of thousands.
No, trillions.
The drug's normal dosage is
one drop diluted 250,000 times.
But I made your batch special.
Pure and undiluted.
With what's coursing
through your veins,
one second will feel
a hundred years.
Take this sword, for instance.
As I move it closer to you,
your superhuman alertness
makes the movement
appear agonizingly slow.
As if it will take several
centuries to reach you.
It's delightful.
But, while your senses are
sped up to superhuman levels,
your non-superhuman body
will fall painfully behind.
Your body cannot possibly keep
up with the incredible amount
of data your sharpened
senses are sending it.
Even if you manage to
block it with your hand,
it'll be hundreds
of years before you
feel the pain of the
blade piercing your flesh.
In fact, I'm talking to
you in the president,
but who knows when my words
will actually reach your mind?
Well, we're in no
hurry, I suppose.
Yes, take your time.
Enjoy the everlasting
agony of my sword
slicing through your heart.
Savor it, 'til your
blood turns to dust.
For now, I bid you adieu.
You'll be seeing my again,
in about a hundred years.
[theme music]
URYU: How did you get
inside her body, anyway?
SZAYELAPORRO: Through her pores.
Really, those pores
were way too open.
She needs to take
better care of her skin.
MAYURI: Nemu, didn't
I tell you to use
the same cosmetics as me?
I'll sew up every
one of your pores.