Let go of the girl!
Ichigo!
Scatter,
Sembonzakura!
Who is that?!
Aah, ha ha ha ha!
Go, Kenny, gooo!
So how do you
think I look?
Okay, everyone,
quiet on the set,
and action!
We're going to make movies!
Say what?... We're gonna what?
We're coming up
on blockbuster
movie season.
Now, as you all know,
these are difficult economic
times for many people.
Consumers are
tightening their belts
and spending less.
On everything, that is,
except the movies, one of
the few industries that
is actually thriving.
No matter how bleak the economic
picture, people still flock to
the multiplex
and put their money down for
an hour or two of escape.
We have to find a way to tap
into that revenue stream!
Are the Thirteen Court
Guard Squads really
that hard up for cash?
As a matter of fact,
from what I've heard,
the Seireitei's suffered a
lot of damage recently from
all the battles and calamities
that have been going on.
The repair costs have
been astronomical.
It's not like you worry about
damage to a few buildings when
you're fighting for your life.
So we have decided to hold
the First Annual Seireitei
International Film Festival,
to coincide with the
release of Bleach Movie 4.
[cheers]
"Bleach Movie 4,"
where the hell'd
that come from?
Don't think so hard.
Let's just make a
kickass film that'll
blow everyone away.
He's right, Ichigo.
Come on, let's go!
Egh, How did I
get roped in?
Cut! Not like that!
I Can't believe how
gung-ho everybody is here.
And where the hell
did all this equipment come
from?
Gangway!!
Hm?
"Seireitei International
Film Festival. co-sponsored
by Urahara's Shop..."
Man, even him? I thought that
guy was supposed to be banned
from the Seireitei for life.
[Retsu]
Ichigo.
Captain Unohana...
and Captain Komamura?
Hello there.
So are you guys
shooting a movie, too?
Mmm. Squads Four and Seven
have decided to pool our
resources. Our film is a
joint co-production.
Really?
What's it about?
It's set in a
post-apocalyptic world.
It tells the story of
how the human race is
saved by animals.
Saved by...?
Oh! You're the lead?
[chuckle]
Got a problem?
Eyahh!
What are you
looking at?
Oh, nothing! It's just that
you don't look much like a
savior of the human race.
[grunt/growl]
[gulp]
Actually, I was
thinking that myself;
there's something wrong
with that costume, though I
don't know exactly What...
You can be honest!
It's me, isn't it,
Captain?
It's because of my
acting, isn't it?
I'm not good enough!
I'm dragging down the whole
production, aren't I?
Well, the costume
isn't helping.
[Sajin]
Now that you mention it,
Tetsuzaemon, you could
use an acting lesson.
[Tetsuzaemon]
I'd be honored, sir! Woof!
Do you think maybe
we should ask Squad
Twelve to help us?
Captain Kurotsuchi did say
they're constructing full-body
costumes for the science
fiction film they're making.
A science fiction film, huh?
With full-body costumes?
Ichigo?
Huh?
Are you free
right now?
Yeah. I guess.
Well, as it happens, we find
ourselves short of actors and we
could really use your help.
Do you think you might
be available to play a
small part in our movie?
Oh, uh, I don't
think I, uh...
As I say, we're short of actors,
and we could really
use your help.
Oh. Okay.
Oh, it looks very
good on you.
Now what?
Do I have to fetch?
All right, we're shooting scene
15, the big fight between our
hero and the human,
who was turned into a
dog-man by the curse
of the dead dog.
The what who
was what?!
[distant big laugh]
Aah- ha ha!
Heh!
Ichigo? Is that
you under there?
Kenpachi?
What are you
doing here?
We're making a movie, of course!
You guys might as well pack it
in, because we in Squad Eleven
are making a blockbuster hit
with our captain as the star!
We show him going around making
mincemeat of everything,
buildings, people, even worms.
It's an action f
lick.
Yeah, and without
any special effects,
it's all for real!
Awesome, isn't it? Bam!
Yeah, but it doesn't
sound like there's
much of a story.
Aahh!
Yeah, Ichigo!
You'll be perfect!
Just the sort of worthy
opponent I can cut up
into little pieces for
the big climactic scene.
Come on and fight me!
It'll be good!
Eh, no thanks.
Huh?? What's wrong?
Are you saying you're
afraid to fight me?
No, no...
Not exactly.
[Unohana]
Captain Zaraki.
Huh?
I'm sorry, but you see,
Ichigo has already been
cast in our film.
Now, I'm afraid I'll have to ask
you and your colleagues to
please clear the set.
You what?
Captain Unohana...
Tch.
Huh?
Ichigo. This isn't over,
I'll deal with you later.
Come on. Let's beat it.
Yessir!
With pleasure, sir!
Go, Kenny, go! Ha haa!
YEEAAHHH!
Ha ha ha!
Well. Places, please,
and we'll get started.
Oh. Right.
What a relief.
That costume was itchy.
[Jushiro]
Ichigo, is that you?
Huh?
[Ichigo]
Captain Ukitake?
Captain Kyoraku!
Hey, what's the matter with you?
No offense, but you look like
something the cat dragged in.
I'm just beat, that's all.
Captain Unohana made me be
in her squad's movie and
we just finished shooting.
Ha ha ha! I imagine
that was quite rough.
Wait a minute, what
about your movie?
Aren't you guys
making one too?
Well, yeah. In fact, I came
up with what I thought was
a killer idea for a movie,
but Nanao vetoed it.
I will not be associated with
any film rated "adults only."
What the hell kind
of movie were you
guys hoping to make?
As a matter of fact,
we're filming right now.
[Jushiro]
Sentaro and Kiyone are making
a documentary about me and how
I live life to the fullest.
It's supposed to be...
inspirational.
What can I say?
Ha ha ha ha!
Ehh... Ooohh...
Jushiro, you all right?
Yes, I just felt
a little dizzy.
There you are!
I've been looking
everywhere for you.
Why did you go wandering
off? We're ready, but we
can't start filming
without you.
Oh. Sorry.
Gotta go now.
Take it easy.
Yes. Thank you, I will.
Good luck with the movie,
I can't wait to see it!
You're late, Ichigo.
Rukia? What's up
with that costume??
[chuckle] So how do
you think I look?
Rukia's playing the
starring role in our movie.
She is? Just what the
hell kind of movie
are we making anyway?
I call it "Intergalactic
Maid Cop Versus the Space
Invaders of Doom from
Another Planet! Part One!"
Whether you want world
peace or fluffy towels,
it's Intergalactic Maid
Cop, at your service!
I still don't get why
she's dressed like that.
Don't you read the trades, you
idiot? Maids are a hot trend
right now. This could be the
start of a major franchise!
Oh, and we got Rangiku to play
Maid Cop's arch-nemesis, the
beautiful busty evil alien
criminal mastermind.
That's me! Like the scar?
Cute, huh?
And Ichigo, you get to
play the part of the high
school Soul Reaper who
comes to Rukia's rescue.
Sounds like
real life.
And here we have
the rest of our
cast and crew.
Ichigo, what exactly are we
doing? I was just told to show
up here if I wasn't busy.
Mmm.
Orihime, you play
a human victim of
Rangiku's evil
mind control.
And Chad, you'll be
our trusted production
assistant and gofer.
And I've been put in
charge of designing the
costumes, of course.
Sure, it figures. No wonder the
maid and the alien are wearing
dorky little capes.
[Renji] Uryu, you're also
going to be my cameraman.
Oh, and last but
by no means least,
Captain Kuchiki.
[Ichigo]
Byakuya??
Yeah, the captain's in
charge of supplying visual
effects using his kido.
As the honor of the Seireitei
depends on the success of
this film festival,
it is the duty of every
captain to play his part
in achieving that end.
Right.
Okay now, let's
get started, we're
losing the light!
Scene 62! Ichigo, you're going
to rescue Rukia from Chad and
Orihime who are under Rangiku's
evil mind control, got it?
Places, everyone!
Whoa, I didn't know I'd
be in the first scene!
Wait, wasn't I supposed
to be the gofer, Renji?
Just let me worry
about the details.
Wait, How did you get
to be the director?
Listen up.
Here's how the
scene plays.
Okay. Rukia's been captured
and is about to be executed
by Chad and Orihime.
But Ichigo, your hands
are tied, because even
though they're
under Rangiku's mind
control, they're
innocent people.
So, you find yourself in a
hopeless situation, got it?!
And?
Well, and then you rescue
Rukia, of course, what do
you think happens?
Okay, how?
It's up to you to
figure that part out!
I need an agent.
All right,
places, everyone!
Okay now, I'm counting
on you for any visual
effects, Captain.
But whatever you do,
try and make 'em
really dramatic.
Understood.
Action!!
You'll never get
away with this,
you evil alien
mastermind!
No? Don't make me laugh,
who's going to stop me?
You, Maid Cop? You look a
little tied up at the moment.
Ha ha ha ha!
You can laugh and mock me all
you want, I will not lose heart.
I know my friends will be here
to rescue me any minute now.
Too bad you won't
still be alive to
welcome them.
You! Execute her!
Okey-doke!
Sorry about this Rukia.
But remember, we're under
her mind control and we
aren't responsible for
our actions.
Orihime, I don't think
somebody whose mind is
being controlled would
really say that.
Oh no, time is running out!
Great Cosmic Gollygosh,
this is a desperate pickle!
What will happen?
Could this be the end of
Intergalactic Maid Cop??
Hold it right there!
Who is that?!
Let go of the girl!
Or else prepare to feel the
righteous blade of Ichigo,
High School Soul Reaper!
Look at you. You didn't even
want to do this and now you're
chewing up the scenery.
Shut up!
Ha ha ha! I think
you're forgetting the
situation you're in.
I have these hostages,
remember? Make one false move
and your fellow humans will
perish. Is that what you want?
Sorry we can't help out.
But she's got us under
mind control.
Rgh.
Gah! You evil fiend!
Don't flatter me.
Now, my mind slaves,
kill him!
We never rehearsed
this, what are we
supposed to do now?
I don't know,
just attack him!
Ichigo, you dodge 'em.
Isn't the director
supposed to direct?
Hrrm. Whatever.
El Directo!
Nice try. But you'll
have to do a lot better
than that to beat me!
Uh!
I don't know,
it's missing
something.
Captain, I think it's
time to show your stuff.
Very well.
Orihime! Stick your hands out
and go into your stance!
Me? Why?
Just strike a pose!
Oh. Okay.
Hado Number 33. Sokatsui!
Huh?
Hey, that was close!
Hado Number 4. Byakurai!
I get it that you're trying to
make it look good, but come on,
do you have to make
it look this good?!
You're not even the guy
I'm supposed to be fighting!
Hello?! Why are you
just standing there?
Keep attacking!
El Directo!
Scatter Sembonzakura!
Eyyahhhhh!!!
Oh, poor Ichigo!
How could you do that to
him? That does it!
I don't care if you are
helpless mind slaves, you're
going to pay for this!
Take that and that
and that and--!
All right, mind slaves!
Drop to the ground now!
Arrgh! She got me!
[oversold grunts of pain]
You little brat!
However, luckily for you,
I'm gonna let you off easy.
Farewell!
Ichigo. Thanks to your
noble sacrifice, I'm alive
to fight another day.
Farewell. Farewell forever,
my dear and loyal friend.
[Ichigo]
Don't go killing me off!
Huh?
Do my eyes deceive me?
You're still alive, really?!
Of course I am!
Point!
Then together we will
continue the never-ending
fight for galactic peace
and universal brotherhood!
[Renji]
And cut! Print it!
Beautiful!
Auggh.
Ichigo, are
you all right?
No, I'm not, in fact.
You almost killed
me for real!
[Uryu]
Oh no.. Oh, no!!!
What is it?
What's the matter?
What was I thinking?
I forgot to sew this
on to Rukia's costume!
[sigh] Who cares?
Nobody will notice.
[Renji]
Rrgh, we have
no choice.
Huh?
We'll have to do another take.
Once more from the top and do
it exactly the same way!
WhaaAAAA-A-A-A??!?!
[Renji]
So this is our next location.
What do you think?
[Rukia]
Sokyoku Hill?
[Renji]
That's right. No one's ever
filmed in this sacred place
before. We're the first.
It'll be a real selling
point for the movie.
You got official approval
for this, right?
And all the proper
permits and everything?
'Course. Whattaya think,
Ichigo? Pretty cool, huh?
Rrgh.
Uh, is there
a problem?
Yeah, there is.
With this whole
damn movie.
What do you mean?
For one thing, why am I the
only one who keeps getting
the crap kicked out of me?!
I keep being blown up,
Blasted with
precision attacks,
sent flying and thrown down
holes without any warning!
Yeah, but your acting
was great in every
one of those scenes.
I wasn't acting!
And besides, I don't even
have a clue what the damn
story's about! Do you?
Story, shmory, who cares?
We're going to rearrange
everything in the
editing stage anyway.
We can always erase
the soundtrack and
dub in new dialogue.
Cover up any rough
spots with CGI and music...
I knew it, you're
just making it all
up as you go along!
Maybe, but that's
fine with me.
You can't spend too
much time worrying
about the story.
[Rangiku]
Look at Shuhei's group.
They're still working on
their script, they haven't
even started shooting.
They're way
behind schedule.
Momo is about to
blow a fuse.
We don't want to end
up like them, do we?
Oh, wow, those
poor guys.
When the script's late, the
whole cast and crew suffers.
Hmm.
Whatever!
The main
thing is,
why does your
aim have to be
so accurate,
Byakuya?
You got a grudge
against me or
something?
No, not at all.
But,
It's simply that I believe
that true art requires me to
be truthful in my performance.
Nobly said,
my brother!
If the name of the
Kuchiki Clan is to
appear in the credits,
I cannot allow
mistakes to be made.
Well, I'm glad
you're happy.
Cause I quit.
What? No, you can't!
When we're so close to
finally finishing the movie?
Sorry, I just can't
take it any more.
Auggh!
Hey! What the hell
was that for?!
What are you
so afraid of?
Mmph!
So you got a little
beat up during filming.
You're going to get discouraged
over something like that?
It happens all the time!
Are you afraid you're not
going to look good on camera?
Is that it?
Or maybe you're afraid you're
not a good enough actor to make
it look truthful and real?
[gasp]
If you don't have confidence
in your acting, make up for
it with passion.
If you're afraid you
won't be able to make it
real, then find a way to
fake it so it looks real.
If you find that the work is too
hard and the schedule too long,
then try nailing all your scenes
in one take!
Stand tall, speak clearly,
and stop worrying what
other people think!
Now come on, get on your feet
and be the man I've always
known you to be, Ichigo!
Hm! You talk too much,
you know that?
Okay, now that we're all on
the same page, you ready?
Let's get back to work!
Yeah!
What are you people
doing here?!
Huh??
Crap! They
found us!
Intruders! Sound the alert!
Hey, what's going
on here, Renji?
Never mind,
just get moving!
Wait, I thought you
said you got permission
to shoot here.
Yeah, I kinda
lied about that.
[appalled gasp]
It's called guerilla
filmmaking, everybody does it.
Beats having to deal with
all that stupid paperwork.
Intruders!
Seal the area!
Get them!
[Ichigo]
Great, we're surrounded!
[Orihime]
Oh, no!
Now roar! Zabimaru!
Follow me! Hurry!
Wait! Renji,
where you going?
Never mind, just run! Run!
Don't let them
get away!
[Ichigo]
Where are we?
[Renji]
Hell if I know.
[Ichigo]
Look, a dead end!
[Renji]
Well, I guess I've
got no choice.
Bankai! Hihio!
Zabimaru!
[Renji]
There, y'see?
Just like I planned it.
[Ichigo]
Yeah, right.
Damn! How did they
get here so fast?
Is this still
"just how you
planned it?"
[gasp] They're
behind us, too!
Hmm.
Captain?
I will not jeopardize my
clan's honor by allowing
myself to be captured here.
I think your clan's honor
went in the dumpster when
you signed on to this movie.
Hey! Wait, Byakuya,
don't do anything crazy!
Bankai Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Yeah! He did it!
YAHHH!
[Rukia]
And so, evil is defeated
and peace is restored to
the Soul Society,
thanks to the noble sacrifice
of young Ichigo Kurosaki.
We would like to add that no
actual sacred sites
were trespassed upon or
destroyed in the making of
this motion picture.
We hope you enjoyed it and
thank you for your support.
How could you not enjoy it?
it's got everything!
Thrills, laughs, action!
I think the grand prize
for the best film is as
good as mine!
YAAAHHH!! I knew I
should've quit when I
had the chaaaance!
[Rukia]
The End!
[Ichigo]
So does the festival's grand
prize come with any money?
[Byakuya]
It's been withdrawn.
[Ichigo]
What? Why?
[Byakuya]
The prize money is going to
be used for repairs instead.
It seems the Seireitei
was nearly destroyed
during filming.
[Ichigo]
But that was all your fault!