[theme music]
NARRATOR: Rurichiyo
Kasumioji, the princess
of a high-ranking noble family
within the Soul Society,
was supposed to remain in her
palace as head of the family
after a period of internal
strife had been resolved.
Instead, she suddenly
returned once again
to the World of the Living.
Rurichiyo had argued
with her guardian
Kenryu over her priorities.
He felt she should
mend relations
with the other noble families.
Rurichiyo wanted to hold a
Kemari tournament to cheer up
for subjects.
In a fit of anger, she
ran away from home.
In despair and feeling
responsible for his inability
to persuade Rurichiyo, Kenryu
decided to commit suicide.
When Rurichiyo became
aware of Kenryu's plans,
she realized how
important he was to her,
and raced to stop him
from taking his own life.
RURICHIYO: You fool!
KENRYU: Lady Rurichiyo.
-How could you be so brainless?
Did you really
think going through
with that was going
to make me happy?
I am responsible
for my guardians,
and that means I
cannot let you die.
Got that?
-You mean, Lady Rurichiyo--
-They certainly are a
handful, no doubt about it.
-You're telling me.
RURICHIYO (VOICEOVER): Oh well.
I suppose I will have to
concede just this once.
-I am so happy that you
understand, my lady.
I won't have to lose my
life, not for something
as dumb as Kemari.
-What did you say?
-Uh.
-Did you just
called Kemari dumb?
So, you believe your
princess has dumb ideas.
-No!
I, uh, just meant, well, silly
hobbies, like Kemari, are--
-What do you mean,
silly hobbies?
-No.
It-- that came out wrong.
Well, if the cat
is out of the bag.
-You do not understand because
you have never played it.
-Oh, I have played it plenty.
Why, in fact, I would wager
I'm better at Kemari than you,
my lady.
-Then I challenge you
to a Kemari contest!
That will settle this argument.
The loser must concede the issue
and never bring it up again.
-Fine.
You have a deal.
-How the hell did things
wind up like this?
[whistle]
-Why are we being
forced to participate
in settling this issue?
-Stop complaining, Ichigo.
It's an opportunity.
Think of it as an honor to
play in a noble family's Kemari
competition.
-Oh, so demanding we play
now becomes an honor.
And how in the world did you
come up with these teams,
anyway?
-I'm sorry about this.
I couldn't refuse his request
since I'm part of a noble clan.
-In my case, I've been your
enemy from the beginning.
-And, of course,
you know how I feel.
I go wherever Rukia goes.
-There.
Are any more questions?
-Good grief.
-Kenryu, our team appears
to be short a player.
What are we supposed to do?
-I'm glad you
noticed that, Uryu.
There's someone
here whose duty is
to help guide Lady Rurichiyo.
He appears to have betrayed us.
-I don't think of it
as a betrayal at all.
Unlike you, Enryu is
always on my side.
-The truth of the
matter is I wanted
to be on Lady
Rurichiyo's team as well.
Enryu is always her favorite.
At any rate, I suspected
this might happen.
So I arranged for a
qualified substitute.
ICHIGO: Yoruichi?
-Leave it to me.
This competition
is as good as over.
-I admire your conference.
That's why I asked Kisuke to
help me find a good player.
-The Kasumioji clan is a
major customer of mine.
That's why I had to
come through for them.
Thanks, Yoruichi.
I know your participation will
catapult your team to a win.
-Kisuke?
What the hell are
you doing here?
Oh my.
Did I forget to mention
my store happens
to be the main sponsor
of this competition.
[cheering]
-We've arranged for
the referees as well.
-I'm going to be
watching very closely.
Obey the rules.
-Are you kidding?
-Speaking of the rules, we
will now explain them to you.
Begin, Ms. Kuchiki.
-Kemari is an ancient
Japanese sport
which is played by two
opposing team using a ball.
Players kick the ball in
the air to a set height,
and then pass it to the
other members of their team
without letting it
fall to the ground.
-By the way, those are
horrible drawings, as usual.
-[growl]
-The playing field is an open
space marked at each corner
by trees called kekari.
All you do is keep kicking the
ball within the open space.
The rules are very simple.
-So it's a game where keeping
the ball up and assisting
your team members
is very important?
But you haven't explained how
someone is supposed to win.
-Good point.
And that's why for
this competition
we're using a special
Kasumioji rule.
--[clears throat] I believe
you'll find this to be quite
simple.
Whichever team drops
a pass is deemed
to have lost the contest.
The final decision will
be made by the referees.
Lady Rurichiyo, are these
rules acceptable to you?
-Yes, of course.
If your team should somehow win,
Kenryu, I will then obediently
return to the Soul Society
and do whatever you say.
But we're going to hold a
Kemari tournament if I win.
Do you accept that?
-That will be fine.
-Believe me, though, there's
no doubt that my team will win.
-You sure about that?
I wouldn't start
celebrating just yet.
-For this competition,
we've marked
all corners of Karakura
Town as kekari.
There's a 90-minute time limit.
And for the duration
of the game,
we've set up conditions
identical to an area
freeze and Konpaku protection.
So please stay
within the kekari.
-How did you determine
the time limit?
-It was the most we
felt we could do.
If we keep it
frozen for too long,
the Soul Society
will reprimand us.
-You're sure it's
all right to do this?
-Ichigo, you shouldn't worry
so much about the details.
-She's right.
You'll be more motivated
to put your effort
in if there's a time limit,
rather than facing something
that can drag on endlessly
without a resolution.
-He's telling the truth.
URURU: Excuse me?
If everyone's ready, we
should begin the competition.
[whistle]
[grunting]
-And kick off.
-Oh, great.
The ball's gone into orbit.
-[grunt]
-Oh, yeah!
My lady, how'd you
like that move?
-That was nothing.
-Oh, wow!
Both team captains are
challenging each other
from the very start.
-Right.
Let's win this thing, Ichigo.
-I'm with you.
-We'll see about that.
Damn it, I missed.
-Hey, that was dangerous!
-I forgot to mention that it's
OK for those without the ball
to try and block moves
by the opposing team.
-That's some oversight.
-What are you doing, Ichigo.
Game on.
-Just a minute.
KURODO: Uh-oh.
There's a problem.
The ball's about to
go outside the kekari.
-Don't worry, guys.
I'm all over it.
I'm uniquely suited
for this situation.
After all, I'm a Mod-Soul,
reinforced leg strength model.
Check out the action.
Kon kick!
How was that?
[grunt]
JINTA: I believe I distinctly
said no going out of bounds!
-[shout]
-Referee Jinta just administered
a penalty kick to player Kon
for going out of bounds.
-If the Soul Society
finds out the barrier is
being used as kekari,
there'll be trouble.
Because of that, I
understand the severity
of the penalty kick.
-That's right.
It's the player's fault for
going out of bounds on his own,
the idiot.
-What kind of trouble
are we talking about?
And why are we taking
so many risks here?
-Got it!
Rukia, I'm passing it to you.
-It's time for a block.
Are you ready for
this, Enryu? [shout]
-What the--?
-A [inaudible].
Nice move by Enryu.
-Daichimaru is a
defense-type Zanpakuto
that can create an
instant barricade.
It can block an opponents
attack by building
a set of walls from the ground
directly underneath them.
It is quite effective.
-What a brilliant move!
-Why all the shouting?
You're about to make
my eardrums pop.
I'm covering for Enryu.
It turns out he's
embarrassed to have
other people hear his voice.
-Fine.
But please don't
scare your teammates.
ORIHIME: Ichigo, we
have to get the ball!
-Hey, Chad!
Pass it over when you get it.
-[grunt]
ICHIGO: Can't you kick lightly?
-Ichigo, go after
it with Flash Step.
-Guess I'll have to.
What's going on here?
-I'm going to get that ball.
I figure I can
beat you in a race.
-Heh.
I think you figured wrong.
-Ah!
I've got to do something.
I'm pretty limited in this form.
-Good.
I made it time to spare.
-You thought you could beat
me to the ball with such
a slow Flash Step?
What a joke, Ichigo.
-Will you put something on?
-In a surprise move, Yoruichi
transforms and catches
Ichigo off guard.
-He'll be all right in a minute.
-It's his own fault.
He should have expected it.
-Lady Yoruichi, pass
the ball down here.
-I guess I'd better.
Here, take care of the ball
while I put on my clothes,
Rukia.
-It exploded!
What are you doing?
-Sorry.
I guess I just don't
know my own strength.
-Soten Kisshun.
-Great job, Orihime.
Did you see that, Kenryu?
Now that's pulling
together as a team.
-We'll see.
From here on, the real
contest is about to begin.
-[sigh] Look at all this.
The way this is going, I'll
be an old man by the time
I'm finished.
Rurichiyo and Kenryu went
to the World of the Living
and they haven't come back.
I want to go to.
Maybe I can take a little break.
Huh?
-Lord Shu, I've
brought more documents.
-I can't handle what
I've already got!
-These are different, my lord.
-What?
-[shout]
-Ichigo.
-Gotcha.
I'm on it.
-Oh, no you don't!
-Santen Kesshun.
-Hey, is that fair?
-All right, he's blocked.
Go for it!
-Good move, Orihime!
-Oh, no you don't!
Come on, Kon!
Dance, Sode no Shirayuki!
-Huh?
What are you planning
to do, Rukia?
-You'll find out.
Sorry.
You better brace yourself.
-Huh?
-Tsugi no mai, Hakuren!
-[shout]
-Damn it!
-That was brilliant,
Ms. Kuchiki.
-I think my nose is bleeding.
-No one is allowed to
go outside the kekari.
Bakudo Number 99,
[inaudible] Kin!
-Ah!
[groan]
-Hey, that's my body!
-Unavoidable.
You seem to forget
we're trying to do this
without telling
the Soul Society.
-I haven't forgotten!
Why are we doing something
we have to keep secret?
IKKAKU: What's all this about
keeping a secret from the Soul
Society?
So, is there something you
want to tell me, Ichigo?
-Uh, Ikkaku.
Uh, well-- uh, let me think.
-We've been facing some
strong adversaries lately,
so I'm in the process
of retraining Ichigo.
-Special training--
that's what's going on?
-Yeah, and you came along
at just the right time.
I'm afraid someone got
injured a moment ago.
I'm wondering if you'd be
willing to give us a hand.
-I don't know precisely
what's going on.
But it seems very interesting.
-Substitution.
Mr. Madarame will be taking
the place of Mr. Kon.
ICHIGO: Hey, wait a minute.
We don't agree to that!
-We need a ruling.
Substitution is approved.
-What?
-The treat you're enjoying
comes from the candy maker
to Kasumioji clan.
I had a feeling you'd
find it most enjoyable.
--[laughs] You are a
sneaky one, Kenryu.
-I am a student, one who bows
to the master, Mr. Urahara.
-It's been a while
since I've taken you on.
Are you ready for me, Ichigo?
-You serious?
Hold on.
-Don't hold back, or
you're gonna get hacked!
-Well, fine, if that's the
way you want it. [shout]
-This is when the
real fight starts.
Extend, Hozukimaru!
[shouting]
-Heh.
[fighting noises]
-What's Ichigo doing up there?
He's not even kicking the ball.
-Don't know.
-Hang in there.
You're doing great, Ichigo!
-What's happening?
It appears that
everyone's forgotten
the original point
of this competition.
-I have to agree.
-Looking at the overall picture,
does it even really matter?
-I have to say, you're
very persistent.
The same goes for
you, Lady Rurichiyo.
Let's say we put an end
to this contest already.
What do you say?
-Sure.
It's no big deal to me.
-All you have to do is admit
your team lost the competition.
-The important
thing in all of this
is restoring the clan
as soon as possible.
I've told you over and over
that recreational activities
can still be provided afterward.
That's still my position.
Are you prepared to accept it?
-Not yet!
-Lady Rurichiyo, why
are you so obstinate?
-Isn't it obvious?
Because I want to see
smiles on everyone's faces.
Ever since I came
back to lead the clan,
everybody has been
working very hard in order
to keep things together for me.
But in spite of that,
there's still many things
that I just have
not mastered yet.
And as a result, I end up
putting a terrible burden
on you and all the others.
-[gasp] But, my lady!
-Do not bother saying it.
I know the situation
is unavoidable,
because I am still just a child.
But regardless, I
still felt guilty.
And I tried to think if there
was something I could do,
some way that I could
make my subjects,
and the staff at the mansion,
and even you feel happy.
And the Kemari tournament
is what I came up with.
[cries]
-I didn't know, my lady.
[gasping]
[screech]
-A hollow?
-Guess we exerted too
much spirit energy.
-This is trouble!
-Everyone, run for it!
-[scream]
-Lady Rurichiyo.
-[inaudible]!
[scream]
-Hold tight, my lady.
Lady Rurichiyo, you
have to go with Enryu.
-No way.
I'm not doing it.
I'm not leaving
you behind, Kenryu.
-[cries] Lady Rurichiyo!
[cries]
-What?
[shouting]
-Getsuga Tensho!
-Lady Rurichiyo, were
you hurt in the attack?
-I'm fine.
Really, Kenryu.
-What happened to
the Kemari ball?
-I am not sure.
I lost track of it when
the Hollow attacked,
and it disappeared.
I guess that means
it fell to the ground
on my turn, which also
means this contest is--
[gasping]
-Is that the Senkaimon?
-Oh, there you are!
-Shu?
-Why did you come her to
the World of the Living?
-Because I wanted to
show you something.
-My lady, these are
letters from your subjects.
SHU: Remember you once
mentioned publicly
that you wanted to hold
a Kemari tournament?
Well, since no details have
been released since then,
people decided to
send in letters
of encouragement and support.
They're really excited about it.
You see?
There's a lot.
I don't know where you
came up with the idea,
but it turns out
to be a good one.
You captured
everybody's imagination.
They can hardly wait to
hear the details of how
the tournament is going to work.
-That is great.
But the arrangements might
be kind of complicated.
KENRYU: Lady Rurichiyo?
-Huh?
-There could be no
more definitive outcome
to our competition.
It's clear to everyone that
I lost, and I hereby concede.
As a result, Enryu
and I will do whatever
it takes to help
with your tournament.
-Kenryu, Enryu!
[laughter]
-Well, got to be going.
There is quite a
bit of preparation
to do before the
Kemari tournament,
so I have to leave at once.
Sorry for causing
such a commotion!
KENRYU: We put
you through a lot,
and we appreciate all your help.
RURICHIYO: See you soon!
Bye now!
ICHIGO: But-- hey, wait!
Would someone mind explaining
to me what all that was about?
[theme music]
URAHARA: In the next episode,
we're going back in time
110 years.
It'll feature me when
I was very young,
which should be
very embarrassing.
ICHIGO: Hey, what
about my scenes?
URAHARA: Don't worry.
You're still in the episode.
They gave you two lines
in the illustrated Guide
to Soul Reaper segment.
ICHIGO: I see what's going on.