[theme music]
NARRATOR: Shusuke Amagai, former
leader of an expedition unit,
was named the new
captain of squad three.
Despite his incredible power,
Amagai was also quite humble.
The morale of squad three
grew as their new captain
fought alongside them.
Meanwhile, Lieutenant Izuru Kira
had discovered a darker side
to Amagi's right hand man,
the mild-mannered third seat
Kibune.
The more time he spent with
him, the more Kira's suspicions
grew.
-I heard of this place, but I
never actually set foot in it.
-Me neither.
Nobody uses fighting
arenas like this anymore.
Seeing how we have access
to it, third seat Kibune
thought we might as well
use it for training drills.
-All right, fall in.
-But sir, where
is Captain Amagai?
-Right, about the Captain.
AMAGAI: Permission
to speak, sir?
-Well, what is it, Amagai?
-I realize I'm the newest
member of the captain's counsel
and I'm speaking
out of turn, but I'd
like to share an opinion.
-Very well, speak.
-Sir.
The incident in
question occurred
just after I was appointed
captain of squad three.
When we battled the Menos
in the Precipice World,
I requested that the Department
of Research and Development
shut down the
restrictive current,
but it was reactivated
while we were inside.
My squad could have been
wiped out by that current.
Luckily, they made it out.
-What is the meaning
of this outburst?
-What?
-If you're here to whine,
you came to the wrong place.
This council has neither
the time nor the inclination
to listen to every squad's
petty little complaints.
-I know.
As a matter of fact, that's
what I want to discuss.
-Is it?
-The 13 Court Guard Squads are
comprised of independent units,
each with their own
unique skill set.
I understand that.
But from an
organizational standpoint,
there's no cooperation between
us, no strength in unity.
This Precipice World
blunder perfectly
illustrates the 13 Court Guard
Squad's most basic weakness.
-What do you suggest,
that all of us hold hands
and get friendly
around a campfire?
-No, I wouldn't
go that far, but I
do think we should at least
conduct joint training.
-Not on your life.
I'm not wasting my
men's time with games.
Laughable.
-Actually, Kenpachi, there's
nothing humorous about it.
-That so?
-Think about Aizen,
Ichimaru, Tousen-- three
dangerous rebels, who each
took advantage of gaps
in our communication.
Unifying our squads would
make us all stronger.
To me, Captain Amagai's
suggestion makes sense.
[quiet crying]
-Come on, now, don't get
discouraged, Shusuke.
You made some very
good points back there.
-Who cares?
I didn't get a commitment
for joint training sessions,
so the whole thing
was a failure.
I can't feel any lower
than I do at this moment.
[sobbing]
-He hasn't had a lot
to drink, has he?
-Nope, he's hardly had anything.
-Then why's he like this?
-Apparently, the smell's
enough to get him drunk.
[sobbing]
-Don't give up on your
idea so soon, Shusuke.
It has a lot of potential.
-You really think so?
-Sure.
I know it looks like your
proposal was rejected out
of hand, but you have the
council a lot to think about.
-And it helps that
Jushiro got involved
explaining what
you have in mind.
-Captain Ukitake,
I owe you big time.
-Hey, easy!
-What the heck?
-Shusuke, you OK?
-I'm great!
Thanks to you, that is.
Now I'm even more
motivated than before!
I should get back to
strategizing right away.
Bottoms up!
-Look at that.
[snoring]
-What do you think?
-About him?
-Yes, him.
-Well, he certainly doesn't
hold back, but I like him.
-Yes, I agree.
-It is tough, though.
-What is it?
-I just hope his
enthusiasm doesn't
alienate the other captains.
[snoring]
-Joint exercises?
No way.
-Yes, the new captain of
squad three suggested them.
-Huh.
Well if you ask me, they'd
be a massive waste of time.
-Joint training sessions, huh?
-It's a pleasure
to work with you.
-I bet it would be a lot
of fun to train together.
-I don't know, I doubt it.
-Oh come on now, you can't be
sure unless you give it a try.
-I'm already sure.
-I think it sounds delightful.
-Seems like Jushiro and Shunsui
are throwing a lot of support
behind Shusuke's plan.
I hope it doesn't
cause any problems
with the members in opposition.
-Unfortunately, I'm told the
proposal for joint training
was scrapped.
-So squad three is all alone.
We're the only ones doing
coordinated training drills.
-This was going to
be our big chance
to show the other
squads what we can do.
-Well, it looks like
we're going back
to all those meaningless
chores again.
Like the other day, when I had
to clean squad seven's toilets.
-That's nothing.
I've becomes squad 11's gofer.
It's awful.
They chew me out even if
I'm just 30 seconds late.
-Could be worse, at least
not as bad off as squad four.
-Absolutely.
It's like squad four
exists to do chores.
[grunting]
-Wait, don't tell me.
-Squad four made me
do their laundry.
-What?
[grumbling]
-There's no reason
to be so glum.
It turns out, the captains
of both squad eight and 13
have agreed to support Captain
Amagai's reorganization
strategy.
Who knows?
The initial rejection
by the Captain's Council
might soon be reversed.
-Really?
-That's tremendous news.
-I got my fingers crossed.
-About time already, too.
-And from the looks of it, you
have no discipline, either.
-Lieutenant Kira?
Is something wrong?
You're looking at me funny.
Is that something on my face?
-Oh, uh, no.
Actually, well,
third seat Kibune,
it's just that I spotted you
entering the Kasumioji house.
-I beg your pardon?
-Whoa, third seed
Kibune, is this true?
-Not at all.
I'm afraid I do
not have the status
to visit a place as
exclusive as that.
Must've been someone else.
-But I could have sworn.
-Be reasonable.
I'm just a common soul
reaper, I couldn't
begin to impose myself on
such an aristocratic clan.
-Yeah, that's a good point.
-You had us confused
there for a second.
-Was I mistaken?
No, I'm sure it was him.
-Urgent message, urgent message!
Menos have been detected
entering the Seireitei!
All squads, proceed to guard
posts and prepare to intercept!
-Menos are here?
-Really?
But how?
-What the heck's going on?
-What do we do?
-I-- I don't know.
Isn't it obvious, sir?
We've got to attack, and
fast before the other squads
beat us to it!
-But how?
The captain didn't--
-This is our chance to
show the others just how
strong our squad can be,
right third seat Kibune?
-Right, then let's roll out.
-Yeah!
-No, stop.
We must wait for the Captain.
-But sir--
-Without his orders, there
is nothing we can do.
We should stand by until
the Captain returns.
-No, Izuru, if we've
trained properly,
the squad will remember
how to maneuver even
without the Captain by our side.
Wouldn't you agree?
Your fellow squad members are
confident that they can fight,
but you seem determined
to undermine them.
That's not what I call
leadership, Lieutenant Kira.
-No, that's not what I'm saying.
The fact is, it's
reckless to launch
an assault without knowing
more about the circumstances
we're facing.
-Is that so?
Because it sounds like you
don't think we can handle it.
-Third seat Kibune's
absolutely right.
Our squad's strong
enough to do this.
-Let's mount an attack!
-Well, Lieutenant Kira?
-He can't even make a decision.
Third seat Kibune,
you take over.
-What?
-That's right.
I will follow your
commands, sir.
-Me too.
-I'm in as well.
-Your men have decided
to take action.
Will you support them, or not?
-I--
-It appears that you are
unable to make up your mind.
You leave me no choice but
to lead this mission myself.
Everyone, let's move.
-Sir!
-Listen up, men.
Don't let anyone get by us.
Squad 11 is the one that's
going to catch this prey.
How the hell did you
and your men get here?
-Funny, I was going to
ask you the same thing.
-My squad doesn't
have time to waste.
-And neither does mine!
[growling]
-Quit following us!
-Same to you, pal!
Can't you see my
squad's got a job to do?
-We're the ones
with the job to do!
-For now, get to
your guard positions.
And don't wear yourselves out.
It's odd that we haven't
received any eyewitness
information about the enemy.
-What about you?
-I'm leaving you in
charge of this area.
-Captain!
-Lieutenant.
-Wait, what's the
meaning of this sign?
-It's highly unusual for Menos
to set foot in the Seireitei.
I advise you to stay out of our
way and let us take care of it.
-Huh?
-Squad alert!
Menos detected in the northeast
sector of the Seireitei!
Proceed in that direction!
I repeat-- Menos
detected in the--
-Did you hear that, men?
Head northeast!
-Hurry up now!
No falling behind!
-I don't get it.
-According to the messenger,
they should be right here.
-It sure doesn't feel like
there are any Menos nearby.
-Third seat Kibune.
I really think the squad
should pull back at once.
We don't have visual
confirmation of a target,
and on top of
that, we don't know
what powers they may possess.
-Lieutenant Kira, you want us
to turn back after all this?
-No way.
If we take them
down, squad three
will finally get
some recognition!
-Listen--
-Lieutenant Kira,
if I were you, I
would refrain from
confusing the squad
with any more of these
contradictory orders.
Besides, I thought
you were vehemently
opposed to this assault.
So why did you
bother showing up?
-Why you--
-Sir, there are now
several conflicts
between squads
deployed in the field.
-Thanks for the report.
-Captain.
-Hmm.
Well, Nanao, what do you think?
-Sir, clearly something
is going wrong.
There's no enemy in sight, yet
there's tension in the air.
-Yeah, you're right.
Well, wanna head home?
-Wait, what are
you talking about?
Menos are inside the perimeter.
-Menos?
I don't know about that.
-Huh?
-You have doubts, too?
-What?
-What are you saying, this
has all just been some ruse?
-In all likelihood, yes.
-What makes you say that?
-Thus far, we only have
rather vague reports,
but no actual sightings, and I'm
only sensing spiritual pressure
from the squads.
If I were to venture
a guess, I would
say someone has
played a trick on us.
-Oh.
That's our Captain for you!
-Hey Sentaro, that
was totally my line!
Stop stealing my thunder!
-Oh cram it, pipsqueak.
You're the one who
was copying me!
[growling]
-No way I would ever
copy you, you moron!
-What did you just call me?
-In any case, someone
sounded the alarm.
Someone provided false
information that led to this.
Everyone, from captains
and lieutenants
down to the average
soul reaper believed it.
They all took the
bait, proving how easy
it is to trick
the 13 Court Guard
Squads into chasing an
enemy that does not exist.
Though now the real question
becomes who's responsible?
-It was I.
-Huh?
-Head Captain.
KIBUNE: Well
Lieutenant, what exactly
are you suggesting we do?
-Call off this attack.
However, if my men insist
on pressing forward--
-I just don't get you.
Very well then.
Let's get to it.
AMAGAI: Not so fast.
-I'm sorry everybody.
I didn't mean to
abandon my duties.
-Captain!
Where were you?
-Heh heh heh.
Too much alcohol.
I passed out.
-Again?
What a lush.
-Oh, and Makoto.
-Sir?
-The squad doesn't
vote on decisions.
When I'm not here, Izuru
will give the orders.
Remember your rank.
-I apologize, sir.
-Captain Amagai.
-Sorry about that, Izuru.
If only I could
handle my liquor.
Next time, though, you
should take control.
-Sir--
-What's the matter?
-There it is!
-Charge!
-Let's hurry it up, men.
Squad 11 will be the
first ones on the scene.
-I don't think so.
We're more ready
than you'll ever be.
-Move it.
Victory is ours.
We can't let some
other squad swoop in
and take what rightfully
belongs to us!
-I have no idea what's
going on, but hurry!
-What the hell?
A dead end?
-What do we do?
-The five Menos
you see, the truth
is, I created em myself
using the Tenshintai.
I wanted to study how each squad
would react to my false alarm.
Alas, it has gone as I expected.
All that's left is to see
how the new captain deals
with the chaos.
-Don't panic.
Just do as you were
trained, and there's
nothing that can stop us.
-Uh, right.
-Go to the other squads and tell
them how we usually maneuver.
I'll give the order.
-Understood, sir.
-Sorry to do this, everyone,
but from here on out,
you'll have to do what
squad three asks of you.
-All right, squad seven.
Let's fall back.
-You serious?
-Ikkaku, squad seven
is pulling out,
and I suggest you do the same.
-Why should I?
-Just listen to me.
-Fine, whatever.
All right, squad 11,
we're falling back.
-OK Aida, have squad
six move to the right!
-Sir!
-Please flank right!
-Got it.
-Kano, heads up!
Move squad ten over to the left!
-Sir!
-Now, Izuru!
Take squad eleven
right down the middle!
-Yes, sir!
-Do it now!
-Yeah, I got it!
[shouts]
-OK, Inose, lead squad
seven to the back right!
-And so it appears the
five Menos were destroyed
by fast-moving,
coordinated formations,
each following orders
from squad three.
-I see.
The proposed joint
exercises will
be carried out with my approval.
-Man, that felt great.
-Sure did.
And the best part of it is,
the other squads can't turn up
their noses at squad
three ever again.
-Yeah, with Captain
Amagai at the helm,
squad three is in good hands.
-You know it.
Ain't that right, Captain?
-I'm relieved.
But maybe that's
the liquor talking!
[snoring]
[theme music]
-Kenryu, I have not been
attending school lately.
Is is not necessary
to go there every day?
-Do not fret, m'lady, Ichigo
Kurosaki and the others have
been with us this whole
time, so it must be fine.
-Actually, it's not fine.