[music playing]
[theme music]
NARRATOR: In order
to save Orihime,
who was kidnapped by Sosuke
Aizen, Ichigo and his friends
snuck into Hueco Mundo,
the realm of the Hollows,
and infiltrated Aizen's
fortress, Las Noches.
While battling the Privaron
Espada, Gantenbaine Mosqueda,
Chad found he had
awakened a new power that
had been sleeping within him.
After defeating
Gantenbaine, Chad
was confronted by
Nnoitra, a full Espada,
and discovered he was
powerless against him.
-I knew it.
You're as weak as a newborn.
-Chad couldn't
have been defeated.
We made a vow.
We vowed we'd all come back,
and we'd all return alive.
-Obviously you're
aware of what happened.
If I were you, I'd be angry that
they were all foolish enough
to sneak into Hueco
Mundo in the first place.
NARRATOR: Meanwhile, Rukia, who
has been fighting the Espada
Aaroniero, finds
herself in grave danger.
-My true ability is
called Glotoneria.
It's quite simple, I
devour dead Hollows
and absorb both their
spirit energy and abilities.
Understand?
When Metastacia came back
in Kaien Shiba's body,
I devoured him and was able to
absorb both their abilities.
Because this body really
did belong to Kaien Shiba.
The muscles retain
all his experience,
and the mind retains
all of his memories.
They're accessible for my use.
It's an elegantly
effective system,
when you think about it.
I simply accessed
all of his memories,
and acted accordingly.
It's the end game.
Allow me to demonstrate for you.
I'll show you what an Espada
sword release actually
looks like.
Devour here!
Glotoneria!
[music playing]
-It's there on your face.
You're terrified.
That fear is well-founded.
The form you see before you
is the result of combining
the strengths of every
Hollow I've ever devoured.
Don't imagine that the
release of a regular Arrancar
compares in any way with
the power of an Espada.
For your information,
my Glotoneria
can simultaneously display the
abilities of all the Hollows
that I've ever eaten.
The last time I
did an estimate, I
had devoured 33,650
Hollows, more or less.
In case you can't do the math,
that means that this moment,
as you stand there alone
and consider fighting me,
you're facing off an army
of over 30,000 Hollows.
-Kaien.
[laughter]
-I'm very sorry,
Lieutenant Kaien.
But it looks like this
is as far as I can go.
It is because I killed
you that your body fell
into the hands of the Hollows.
If I'm honest with
myself, I killed you
in order to save my own life.
But even so--
I know this was painful.
But thanks to you, I'm saved.
Now I can still
leave my heart here.
-In the end, I got your
body back from the enemy.
And I kept telling myself that,
no matter how I felt initially,
my actions had actually
saved your life.
I can see now that I was wrong.
Here, in these last
moments of confrontation,
I accept the reality
of my defeat.
I no longer have the
strength to raise my sword
to defend myself.
I no longer have the will to
use this sword against you.
[music playing]
[gasping]
[laughter]
-Farewell, Lieutenant Kaien.
I'm truly sorry.
-Rukia.
Rukia.
Rukia!
-Oh!
-What's going on?
Why are you slapping me around?
-Because you wouldn't respond.
Yelling and shaking
you wasn't working.
-Are you crazy?
I could have broken my neck!
-What do you mean, broken neck?
It's not like I hit you
all that hard, idiot.
Quit daydreaming.
Get a grip, will ya?
We're almost there.
-Where are we?
-Move it.
Or I'm going to
leave you behind.
-Sorry!
Coming!
The wind whispers
against my face.
The forest path
opens up before me.
The rustling of the
leaves in the trees,
the smell of the grass.
The warmth of the sun's rays.
The chirping of the birds.
-Hey!
Where in the world
are you going?
-I remember everything
about this place.
I remember each tree.
I remember my feelings,
constantly shifting
between anxiety,
excitement, and warm.
This is Mount Koifushi.
On the northern edge of
West Rukon's 3rd district.
This is where I
trained with Kaien
Shiba for the very first time.
-So you're the new recruit?
My name is Lieutenant
Kaien Shiba.
Welcome aboard.
-I see.
Yes, sir.
-What did you just say?
What kind of greeting
is that supposed to be?
I am your commanding officer.
You are supposed to
state your name and say,
pleased to meet you, sir.
What's your name, dammit?
-It's Rukia Kuchiki, sir.
-Hm.
And?
-And, and I'm pleased
to meet you, sir!
-All right.
You're OK, Rukia.
-A normal greeting.
A normal scolding.
A normal relationship between
officer and subordinate.
-Welcome to Squad 13, the
best squad of them all.
Unfortunately, our Captain
isn't in the best of health.
So I pretty much run
things around here.
In fact, it's not
a problem if now
and then you forget and actually
address me as Captain Kaien.
-Uh, OK.
I'll try to remember.
Yes, an ordinary relationship.
But this sense of
ordinary was exactly what
I'd been looking for.
-We're not finished yet.
Let's go.
-Right.
Are you ready?
In the middle of my
attack, a bird flew by,
and I was distracted
for a moment.
So as I made my second strike,
Kaien deflected it from below.
I remember every last detail.
I was supposed to
be concentrating
so hard that I would lose
sight of anything else.
Hm.
-So you're hungry, are ya?
Well all right then, fine.
If you're going to be
that insistent about it.
-I beg your pardon, Lieutenant.
That's not it at all.
It was just that--
-Whatever, it's no big deal.
-What are you doing, Lieutenant?
You're not supposed to
toss a sword at someone
when it's unsheathed.
It's dangerous!
-What are you getting
so upset about?
Are you embarrassed, just
because you're hungry?
-I'm not hungry.
I was upset back then,
but not over being hungry.
It was something else.
Lord Byakuya.
My entrance to Squad 13
today was successful.
-What seat were you named?
-Well, my deepest
apologies, brother.
But with my abilities, I wasn't
able to qualify for an officer
seat upon entry.
-I see.
You may go.
-I soon discovered I didn't have
the gift for sword fighting.
Dig your claws into the
wall of sinless dreams.
Hado #33.
Sokatsui!
While I was at the Spirit
Technique Soul Reaper Academy,
my Kido received high marks.
But when I joined
the 13th Squad,
my abilities were just average.
I'm obviously not as good as
the rest of these recruits.
Why am I even here?
What is my purpose?
-I don't really measure up to
the others, so why am I here?
-What are you talking about?
Isn't your role obvious?
You're here so you
can fight and defend.
-I'm not clear.
What am I defending?
-You don't know what
you're defending?
A bunch of things, all
sorts of things, everything.
-That's a really lame answer.
That's like, nothing at all.
Can't you give me something that
paints a more specific picture?
-Hm?
You want something
more specific, huh?
Rukia.
Have you ever heard our
Captain's view on life?
-Not really, no.
-In his opinion, there are two
types of battles in this world.
He's thought about
this quite a bit.
He says there are battles
to defend your life,
and battles to
defend your pride.
That makes sense, right?
Seems like a fairly
clear separation.
But personally, Rukia, I don't
believe that's quite accurate.
Because in the
final analysis, you
end up defending the
exact same thing.
-The same thing?
What would that be?
-Your heart, of course.
-Please.
Get real.
-Do what?
I'm being serious here.
Show some respect.
Rukia, let me ask you something.
From your experience, where
do you think your heart is?
-Well, if I had to guess, I
think somewhere around here.
Isn't that right?
-Ha.
If you want to be
literal about it.
But in my opinion, it's
more a state of mind.
I believe it's right here.
Not inside our bodies at all.
I think a heart is
created between people
when they meet for
the first time.
A bond that's brought to
life between individuals.
It's an emotional connection.
When you think about something,
or care about someone,
that's where your heart is born.
If you were the only person
who existed in this world,
your heart would have
no way of forming,
so it just wouldn't be anywhere.
-I remember clearly,
those were the exact words
Kaien said to me.
-There's nothing to
worry about, Rukia.
If you believe, with all of your
heart, that you belong here,
then this is where you'll stay.
-He also said, if your
heart is here, then
that's all the reason in the
world you need to be here.
You must never doubt that.
-But listen, Rukia.
In the fights to come,
there's something
I must warn you about.
Something you must promise
me you will never, ever do.
I mean this.
You must never die alone.
Our souls are our bodies.
And when we die, our bodies
turn to dust and become
the reishi that go on to
form the Soul Society.
But where do our hearts go?
We entrust our hearts
to our friends.
-I'm not sure I
completely understand.
If you entrust your
heart to your friends,
it will continue to
live on inside them.
That's the most important thing
you'll learn from my training.
Don't you dare die alone, Rukia.
[music playing]
[laughter]
-Rukia.
We entrust our hearts
to our friends.
[laughter]
-Huh?
I see you're still
conscious, somehow.
That's admirable.
Or perhaps, I should
say, it's pitiful.
You can struggle all you want,
but the fact still remains,
this fight is over.
And you're about to die.
It's amusing that you
still have the strength
to grasp your sword.
I finally remembered.
-Remembered what?
Whatever you're doing,
it's a useless gesture.
Are you going to take me on
with that stub of a sword?
You're pathetic!
Accept defeat!
-Sa-- San no mai.
Shira-- Shirafune.
-Impossible.
-I finally remembered
where his heart resides.
You may have Kaien
Shiba's body inside you
after you devoured him.
You may have his memories,
and his techniques.
But Kaien lives within me.
You see, I was entrusted
with his heart.
[groaning]
-Farewell, Espada!
[explosion]
[screaming]
-Save me, Lord Aizen!
Save me!
It hurts so much, it hurts!
You promised me,
if I went with you,
I'd be free from
all my suffering.
You promised, didn't you?
So why am I in so much pain?
It's more than I can bear.
I'm telling you, it hurts!
Help me, help me, help me, help
me, help me, help me, help me,
help me, help me,
help me, help me.
Everything's gone black.
No way.
This can't be happening.
I refuse to accept it.
[gasp]
-Don't die.
Don't die, Rukia.
Promise me this, you
will never die alone.
[music playing]
-I've known loneliness.
The loneliness of one
who's been locked away.
And I've known happiness.
The happiness felt when your
friends come to rescue you.
-Hey.
-And I've known something else.
I've known terror.
The terror of seeing those very
friends injured and defeated.
Don't worry, Orihime.
I'm coming to save you.
[gasping]
[theme music]
-Master Nnoitra,
what were you doing
when you placed your finger
in the ground the other day?
-If you must know,
that's how I search
for different spiritual
pressures within Las Noches.
-You can do that?
I'm going to try it, too!
-Let's go, Tesla.
-Yes, sir.
-Hey, don't you even want
to see if I can pull it off?