[Aizen]
The truth is,
Ichigo Kurosaki,
All of the battles you
fought up to now,
were simply a
part of my plan.
I'm not done yet!
Hyaahh!
[exhausted panting]
I have to thank you,
Genryusai Yamamoto.
By your heroic actions,
you have protected my world.
Damn you.
Genryusai Yamamoto.
Unfortunately, I cannot
spare your life.
You are the embodiment of
the Soul Society's history.
Out of respect, I have decided
I will finish you off quickly.
[gasp]
Don't make me explain it
again, Sosuke Aizen.
His charred arm is
starting to crack!
That means he's using the
forbidden technique,
which can only be
activated by using one's
burned body as a catalyst!
Sacrificial Hado
Number Ninety-Six!
Ittokaso!
I underestimated him.
He sacrificed his own burned
body as a weapon, without a
moment's hesitation!
Getsuga...tensho!
I'm not done yet!
Damn!
Ssyaahhh!
Heh.
What's so funny?
You missed your
chance kill me,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
What?
Too bad for you.
You won't get that
opening again.
Don't be so sure.
I was able to
injure you.
Injured?
You call this an injury?
High-speed regeneration?!
It's not high-speed
regeneration.
Do you really think I'd
undergo Hollowfication?
This is merely a compulsion
to protect its master.
What are you talking about?
[Ichigo]
But that's...
[Aizen]
Yes, it's the Hogyoku.
Your Spirit Energy
works very well.
I'm very pleased.
You've matured
splendidly.
Just the way I wanted you to.
Eh? What?!
Months ago, you
met Rukia Kuchiki.
And following your
battle with Uryu Ishida,
you awakened to your
own Soul Reaper powers.
Eh?!
During your battle with Renji
Abarai, you learned about the
power of your Zanpakuto.
During your battle with
Kanpachi Zaraki, you became
aware of your Bankai.
During your battle with
Byakuya Kuchiki, you began
your Hollowfication.
During your battle with
Grimmjow, you mastered
your Hollowfication.
And during your
subsequent battle
with Ulquiorra,
it appears you gained
an even greater power.
The truth is, Ichigo Kurosaki,
All of the battles you've
fought up to now,
were simply a
part of my plan.
Rauughh!
I'm too injured to fight.
Do you want to save
your family?
Of course I do!
If there's a way
then tell me how!
It will only be temporary.
But, you must become a
Soul Reaper yourself.
Then give me that blade,
Soul Reaper.
My name is Rukia.
Rukia Kuchiki.
[monster roars]
Rrrauugghr!!
And my name is,
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Heh.
What the... They just
keep on coming!
Something's wrong here.
There are far too many
Hollows coming for that
small amount of bait I placed.
It's as if they're being drawn
by an even greater force.
But what?
Sensei!
[Ichigo]
Uryu!
Huh?
You say we're at opposite poles,
but I say when two warriors are
heavily outnumbered the trick is
to fight back to back!
Sounds like a plan!
What the? Ichigo!
Look at the sky!
What's that?!
Unff!
What's he doing?!
Nnnghh...
I'm feeling extraordinary
Spiritual Pressure!
Ichigo's power is
actually increasing!
RAAAAGGHHH!!
I-iiii win!!
Hee he he he he he he!
Ehhe! hehe!! he he he!
[Akon]
Hey, Hiyosu!
Eh?
I thought you should know,
the Stealth Force has
turned in their report.
Mmmhee he he he he!
So, what does it say?
It's exactly as you suspected.
Your instincts are spot-on.
It's the missing criminal.
Yep. Knew I was right.
We shouldn't waste any time,
we need to get on this.
We have to catch her and
retrieve the Gigai she's using.
I agree, but I have to say,
I'm surprised you were able
to find her.
Yeee hee he he he he!
It was kind of a
lucky turn of events.
I can't tell you why, but I felt
like watching some broadcasts
from the World of the Living.
When I turned on the monitor,
I saw this playing. Just good
timing, I guess!
You can say that again. It's
amazing but your hobby does come
in handy, every once in a while.
Admit it, you're jealous.
So, any indication as to
when they're going to
send us her Gigai?
Well, yeah, regarding that,
It looks to me like it's
going to be a while.
There are formal
procedures to go through.
In the meantime,
to cover themselves,
they sent a retrieval team.
Well! You don't say.
Who's on that team,
if I'm not being too nosy?
Mmmf.
I shouldn't say.
Roar, Zabimaru!
Now open your eyes!
See what lies before you!
And fall upon your prey!
It's all over you little runt.
You've lost to Renji Abarai, and
will die where you stand!!!
[gasp]
[shaky breaths]
Not enough time!
Ah! What!?
What just happened?
You're slow.
Brother, don't do it!
Rgh! Why you!
See, I'm gonna keep pushing
you and pushing you.
so you can
always remember that attack!
Am I making
myself clear?
When you counter,
you don't let
them cut you.
If you protect someone,
you don't let them die.
When you attack, you kill!
Understand? Can't you see?
My sheer resolve to kill you
is reflected in my sword.
Huh?
When you counter,
don't let them cut you.
Why you--!
When you protect someone,
...don't let them die.
When you attack, you... kill!
Wait for me Chad!
I'll beat this guy!
And then I'll save you!
I promise!!
Sorry to say, but I don't
feel like dying just yet.
Because if I die, then
everyone who is counting on
me will be destroyed, too!
What is this? You're thinking
you can beat me now, aren't you?
Heh heh heh.
Ichigo, do you have complete
and utter trust in me?
It goes without saying.
I'm putting all of my power
in your hands, Zangetsu.
Do with me what you will
and lend me all your power
in order to win this fight!
[charge growl]
Huuaaa!
Hrrrghh!
Huaaahh!
Ban...kai!
Tensa Zangetsu.
There could never be a Bankai
as small and fragile as that.
And a lowly ryoka could
never attain Bankai.
It's inconceivable.
I've got him!
Impossible! He sliced
through all of them!
[Byakuya]
Senkei, Senbonzakura
Kageyoshi.
This senkei is the form I show
to only those special few
enemies,
who are truly deserving
of my vow to kill them
with my own hands.
Byakurai.
[shocked gasps]
It's over for you,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Ngh, what'd you say?!
My body...
I can't move!!
You're only a human.
Though your spirit
has not been broken,
there is a limit to
what you can endure.
You have reached that limit.
This is the end,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
It's all for nothing
if I don't win!
I want to win!
I...need to win!
[White Ichigo]
Tsk!
I thought I told you already,
It's a big problem for me if
you get yourself killed.
That's impossible!
Who or what are you?!
[White Ichigo]
You wanna know who I am?
Hee he he he he!
I have...
No name!!
Hyaa! Hee-hee ha ha ha!
Ichigo, what a complete
amateur you are!
Ungh!! You fool!
Damn you!
What's this? Has he already
undergone Hollowfication?
Hello, Gin.
Oh, my. Don't tell
me it's all over.
Hmf.
Believe me, there's
no need to worry.
It's all going
according to plan.
And everything
begins now.
[Gin]
So why did you review all
those past battles today?
[Aizen]
I didn't want our viewers
to forget what had
happened up to this point.
Believe me, it wasn't because
I had forgotten about it.
[Gin]
Is that right?
Well I certainly had.
[Aizen]
Not me. I never forget anything.
[Gin]
Oh please.
You so did.
Admit it.