THEME SONG: (SINGING
IN JAPANESE)
-Damn it.
How many freaking steps
does this stupid stairway
have, anyway?
-What difference does it
make how many there are?
-Finally, we made it to the top.
-Nobody up here, either.
Security seems pretty lax.
All right then, guys, let's just
head straight for the tower.
-(TEARFULLY) Oh, Captain.
[footsteps]
-You look terrible.
MOMO: Rangiku, I--
-So have you finally
calmed down yet?
-Uh, oh, yes, I have.
I'm sorry I lost
control out there.
I made trouble for
you too, Rangiku.
-Huh?
Oh, listen, it's no problem.
Never mind about me.
You're the one who's in
big trouble right now.
-Yeah, I know.
What's going on out there?
-Hmm?
It's a complete disaster.
Something like this
happening right here
in the midst of all the
squads, it's unheard of.
And with this Ryoka
situation, everyone
is disorganized, acting on
their own without any focus.
-But what about-- what about
Captain Aizen's murderer?
-They're still gathering
evidence from the crime scene.
We just have to wait
for the head captain
to announce his findings.
-Evidence?
But I already know
who killed him!
It was--
-Don't say it, Momo.
That is an accusation
that you can't make.
I understand.
I know you want to see
that justice is done,
but you should be more concerned
about your own Squad Five.
Think about it.
All in one day,
your squad has lost
both its captain and lieutenant.
I appreciate that you're
hurt and you're angry.
Nevertheless, when
this happened,
the actions you took upon
discovering Captain Aizen's
body, confronting
Captain Ichimaru,
and releasing the energy
of your Zanpakuto,
was there no other choice?
Nothing else you might have
done in that situation?
If you think about
it, I'm sure you'll
realize that you did have some
other options at that point.
The title of lieutenant
demands that it should never
be taken so lightly,
no matter what.
-You're right.
I'm sorry.
I just-- I thought if I could--
-Here.
This was in Captain
Aizen's room.
It's addressed to you.
-These are from the captain?
They're for me?
-You're lucky it was my
captain who found it.
But you need to know, if
it had been anyone else,
they probably would
have seized it
as evidence for
the investigation.
And it never would
have reached you.
I haven't read any of it, and
I don't know what it says.
But it seems to me that
as a loyal lieutenant,
you should be very honored
to know that your captain's
last words were for you.
I hope you appreciate it.
-Oh, I do.
Thanks so much, Rangiku.
AIZEN (VOICEOVER): Momo, if
you're reading this letter,
then it means I
didn't make it back.
MOMO (VOICEOVER): He knew.
He knew someone
was targeting him.
Then last night,
after I fell asleep,
he wrote this letter knowing
he might not see me again.
Oh, Captain.
AIZEN (VOICEOVER): I
know my actions lately
have been the source
of great worry to you.
And for that, I am truly sorry.
Until now, I've
never spoken to you
about the feelings of
apprehension I've been having.
But you must understand, Momo,
that whatever I kept from you,
it was only because I
wanted, if at all possible,
to keep you from becoming
involved in all this.
Sadly, I have now done just
that, and you are involved.
I hope that somehow you can find
it in your heart to forgive me.
The chain of events
was unavoidable.
As for me, I am probably
no longer among the living.
Therefore, to you, who I
trust more than any other,
I leave this record of the
truths I have uncovered.
-Oh, no.
-This spiritual pressure,
it's incredible.
-Crap.
We gotta run.
I don't know what's
going on here,
but I'll tell you for
sure there's someone close
by we don't want
to meet up with.
We have got to move
and get the tower
before the enemy finds us.
-Right.
-I'll try.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Come on.
KENPACHI (VOICEOVER):
He's finally here.
I was getting tired of waiting.
Well now, let's see.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
Something's wrong here.
What's going on?
We've been running for a while
now, but I can still feel him.
We haven't put any distance at
all between us and the enemy.
My legs feel heavy,
like I'm running
in quicksand or something.
But I'm running fast.
I know I am.
And the spiritual pressure,
it's like someone's
got a blade pressed right
up against my throat.
-What the hell are you doing?
This is no time for a break.
-I can't keep running.
I've got no strength left.
-You sure can be a
pain in the ass, kid.
-Are you two all
right back there?
-Never mind us.
Get moving, Ichigo.
KENPACHI (VOICEOVER):
Three of them, huh?
Which is the one?
Not that one.
Are you the one?
What's the matter with you?
How long are you going to
keep looking over there?
-Huh?
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
What-- what the hell?
KENPACHI (VOICEOVER):
What's the matter with you?
How long are you going to
keep looking over there?
-Huh?
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): What
the hell just happened?
I could swear I
just got stabbed.
But murderous intent.
Could just the intent to kill
actually have such power?
-Are you Ichigo Kurosaki?
-How do you know my name?
And who are you anyway?
-Come on.
I'm sure Ikkaku told you that.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Ikkaku?
Wait.
IKKAKU: Just a minute.
Can I ask you question?
Who's the strongest
member of your group?
-That's me, I guess.
-If so, then I suggest
you keep an eye out
for my captain, Ichigo.
The captain has no
interest in fighting
against weak opponents.
If it's true that you are
the strongest, then it's you
he'll come after.
-Is that good?
-You'll find out when you meet.
That is, if you can somehow
manage to stay alive
long enough after he finds
you to take his measure.
-Tell me what his name is.
-I'm captain of Squad
11, Kenpachi Zaraki.
I'm here to fight
you to the death.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER): I felt that
same spiritual pressure again,
pressure strong enough to reach
through the sekkiseki rock
walls of this tower.
What is going on out there?
-I want to leave you with
some unconfirmed information.
They say that a
group of intruders
attempted to enter the
Soul Society yesterday,
five of them.
Now my sources say one of
them carried a sword as long
as his body, a Soul Reaper
with orange colored hair.
RUKIA (VOICEOVER):
Ichigo, is it really you?
I've prayed you would
be able to stay alive.
You must give up on me
and get away from here!
In this world, Ichigo,
there are forces
you can never
understand, forces which
defy the logic in the
world of the living.
Please, forget about me.
Run.
Run away from this
place so you can live!
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
So this is him.
Kenpachi Zaraki, the
famous captain of Squad 11.
-If you should encounter any
captains, don't fight them.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
The spiritual pressure
I've bee sensing all
this time was his.
I already know there's
no running away from it.
-What's wrong?
Is something the matter
with your hearing?
I've just challenged you
to a fight to the death.
I assume, since you won't answer
me, it's all right with you
if I start.
-Ganju, Hanataro.
Hana-- Hey, are you OK?
GANJU (VOICEOVER):
Ichigo, you idiot.
ICHIGO: But, Ganju.
-We just got the
wind knocked out
of us by this
spiritual pressure.
But that's not what you should
be thinking about right now.
Worry about the issue at hand.
Face your enemy, or
he'll take you out
before you know what hit you.
-Whoa, just look
at all that drool.
-Huh?
-You must've scared that
little guy pretty bad,
Kenny, to make him do that.
Uh-oh.
I think I made him mad.
-Well, what did you expect?
That was just stupid.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
What the hell?
Where'd she come from?
And how could she be unaffected
by his spiritual pressure?
-And stupid is as
stupid does, right?
-Well, you said it, not me.
ICHIGO: Hey, twerp
with the pink hair.
-Huh?
-Who are you?
Or maybe I should
ask, what are you?
-My name is Yachiru Kusajishi.
I'm also known as the
lieutenant of the 11th Squad.
It's nice of you to ask.
Thanks.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
A lieutenant?
The same rank as Renji?
But I didn't even
sense her presence.
I didn't noticed her at
all until she landed right
on my shoulder.
Obviously, she's no
ordinary opponent either.
-Hey, Ganju.
-Right here.
-Get Hanataro up
and go on ahead.
You save Rukia.
I'll deal with
these two somehow.
-No way.
You're going to need--
-Ganju!
---help with-- huh?
-Please.
-Oh, wow.
Now you're all alone.
-I'm sorry, but I can't
let you follow them.
KENPACHI: You really
don't understand, do you?
-What?
-Don't make me repeat myself.
I've been waiting for you
to get here for some time
now, in the hopes
of a decent fight.
I'm not the least bit
interested in your two friends,
nor, for that matter, your
mission to free that Rukia.
-Oh yeah, is that so?
-Not bad.
Though your stance is too
rigid and you leave gaps
in your defence, I must say your
spiritual pressure is something
else, way too much for
even some lieutenants.
No wonder Ikkaku lost to you.
But even with that, you're
still nowhere near my level.
I'll tell you what,
Ichigo Kurosaki,
I'll give you an advantage.
-Give me a what?
-I'll let you go ahead
and have the first strike.
I'll stand here and you can
cut me anywhere you want.
-Wow, Kenny.
You're the most
generous captain ever.
-Aren't I?
I'm just a walking bleeding
heart of generosity.
-Quit playing around with me!
-Huh?
-Hmm?
-Is this some kind
of a joke to you?
You think I can attack
someone who hasn't even
drawn his sword?
Don't mock me.
-I'm not mocking you at all.
I'm giving you a free shot.
Not wanting to attack someone
who hasn't drawn his weapon
is certainly admirable.
But I think you might want to
save that sort of gallantry
for another occasion.
Come on.
Lighten up.
Let's have a little fun.
It's a question of
kill or be killed.
Really, what better way can you
think of to spend one's days?
You could go from my
throat or for my gut.
Take out my eyeball if you want.
Or if you're lucky, you might
kill me with a single strike.
Just quit your
quivering and attack!
-No, Ichigo.
Ichigo, don't do it!
Run!
-Hold still.
-What do think you're
doing, squirming
around when I'm
trying to carry you?
-But we can't leave
Ichigo behind.
We can't.
-Now that you mention it,
you're probably right.
But still, he-- he said
he could handle them.
-Handle them?
Are you crazy?
By himself?
He can't.
He's got--
-Hey, settle down.
---to get away.
It's the only way he'll survive.
-Settle down, Hanataro.
-But you don't understand.
There's no way Ichigo can
win, even with all his skill.
It's impossible.
He'll be killed.
-Do you know him, Hanataro, that
spiky-headed guy back there?
What's the Story
-He is-- he's the captain
of the infamous Squad
11, Kenpachi Zaraki.
The name Kenpachi is passed
down through the generations
to the one among
the 13 squads who
most savors fighting
and killing.
That name means that
the one who carries it
will never go down, no matter
how many times he's wounded.
It goes way beyond any question
of power or weakness or skill
or strength.
He can't die.
He's invincible.
And if Ichigo
fights, then Ichigo
is certain to die at his hands.
-In that case, we
definitely can't go back.
We'll keep going forward
and try to reach Rukia.
-But, Ganju, we--
-Hey, shut your mouth.
Listen up.
Ichigo gave us a job to do.
He told us to save Rukia, right?
You felt that incredible
spiritual pressure back there.
We all did.
So you can be sure Ichigo knows
that wired-headed freak isn't
normal.
I'm sure that's why he stayed
behind to fight him alone
and ordered us to go on ahead.
He knew exactly what
he was doing, Hanataro.
That's because, for Ichigo,
the main priority is the same
as it's always been, and that's
to save this Rukia Kuchiki
person no matter what happens.
Do you understand, Hanataro?
We've been entrusted by
Ichigo to carry out its order.
He's counting on us.
-I see, Ganju.
-If you see, then you know
we haven't a second to lose.
Let's get moving.
-Oh, yes, right.
GANJU (VOICEOVER):
Ichigo, after we've
saved Rukia, I swear
we'll come back for you.
When this is all over, we'll
come back to the Rukon District
together.
We still have a lot of things
I want to talk to you about.
So until then, Ichigo,
don't you dare die.
[hums]
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
This can't be happening.
I know I swung with full force.
And I know I didn't miss.
How can there not even
be a scratch on him?
And how can it be that my
hand is bleeding instead?
Impossible.
KENPACHI: Is that it?
Is that really all you have?
I'm disappointed.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
What the hell?
What did he just do?
He touched the Zangetsu's
blade with his bare hand.
That's crazy.
-You're kind of a slow
learner, aren't you, Ichi.
You can never cut
Kenny, certainly
not with that, because
to Kenny it's almost
like your sword has
no blade at all.
-Shall I tell you?
You'd probably like to know why
your sword can never cut me.
It's simple, really.
Whenever two spiritual
pressures collide,
the weaker one gets pushed down.
It's forced to submit.
It gets hurt.
While your spiritual
pressure may
have been enough to
hone that sword of yours
for the purpose of
slaying your enemies,
it's nowhere near as strong
as the spiritual pressure
that oozes from me.
That's all there is to it.
What a joke, when I
think of all the time
I spent looking for
someone as unworthy as you.
Though even as a joke,
it's not very funny.
Now it's my turn, Ichigo.
Try to live long
enough to at least let
me get the rust off this thing.
I am counting on you, Ryoka.
CLOSING THEME:
(SINGING IN JAPANESE)
-All right. [chuckles] Finally
it's my turn to do battle.
So let's hurry up and
get things started.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Chad,
are you really going
to fight that old man?
TATSUFUSA: Hey, where are you?
Are you going to come
out and play, or what?
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Are you
sure he's all right in the head?
TATSUFUSA: I'm waiting.