Rrraaggh!
Can't be!
You're mine!
Hyaaahh!
Getsuga... tensho!
Yaahh!
What's wrong?
You seem to
have missed me.
Is his Zanpakuto that strong?!
Just so you know...
I haven't been using my
Kyokasuigetsu's powers
in our fight so far.
What you're seeing
is just my basic
strength.
What?!
Concentrate, Ichigo!
Don't let him get
into your head!
Captain Komamura?
Keep your mind clear.
I know why the captains
who went to Hueco Mundo
sent you here first.
You haven't fallen victim
to Aizen's Shikai.
Ichigo, we will all
fight to protect you.
You're gonna fight
to protect me?
What are you saying?
It's just crazy! Look at you,
You're all in terrible shape!
That's a matter of perspective.
We think letting you fight
alone would be even crazier.
Besides, we allowed that,
we wouldn't be able to
settle our own personal
grudges with Sosuke.
It would be selfish of you to
take him on by yourself.
This... is a battle...
for all of us.
That's right.
I have to believe in them.
They're committed to
this battle. They'll be
there if I need them!
Focus on their fighting! Wait
until they give me an opening!
Good thing you
moved when you did.
I almost had you.
You seem quite confident,
Captain Kyoraku.
If that's how it appears,
I must be doing pretty
well. Thank you.
For someone who's launching
sneak attacks...you are.
Aizen...
Swinging a sword out of
hatred is nothing more
than mindless violence.
There is no honor
in such behavior.
Aizen...
Your words and actions
prove that you were never
worthy of being a captain.
Hm. How interesting.
You hate me more than any
other Captain in the
Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
I never expected you to
make such a statement.
Or perhaps, when Momo recovered
from her injuries and came to
the World of the Living,
...all your anger evaporated
and disappeared?
Bankai...
Daiguren Hyorinmaru!
I guess what you said
earlier was right.
This sword IS
filled with hatred.
Hatred of you!
I realize now I didn't
come here to fight you.
I came here to destroy
you and end your terror!
[ramping up yell]
Yaaaa-aaaaaa!
Heh hm hm.
Such Spirit Energy!
It's strong!
And it's not
just Captain
Hitsugaya.
[Izuru]
Captain Komamura,
Captain Kyoraku,
everybody here,
They're all raising their
Spirit Energies to the limit.
This might be too much.
Being exposed to this
much Spirit Energy
could hurt Rangiku
and Momo even more!
[shallow breaths]
You're right.
But even with all
this power,
You think it will be
enough to stop Aizen?
[Toshiro]
If my sword is
filled with hatred,
I'm also unfit to be a Captain.
You want to hear that, right?
Hm!
It's true. As long as I end
up killing you, I don't
care if I lose my rank as
Captain in the process!
I'll do everything
I can to crush you.
You won't even have a chance
to use your Kyokasuigetsu.
Oh? You think you can stop me
from using my power? Well...
I will!
Are you ready, Aizen?
You don't look like you
want to fight me. Too bad.
Even if you don't,
I'll show no mercy!
Attacking before Captain Aizen
can use Kyokasuigetsu?
How naive...
You have completely
misunderstood Captain
Aizen's abilities, and
the power he possesses.
Hyoryusenbi!
Hyoryusenbi...Zekku!
Tenken!
Tengumaru!
I'm sorry Captain Hitsugaya!
But I'm stepping in!
This might not be what you
wanted, but we can discuss that
after we've wrapped this up!
Do what you like. I never
expected to fight him by myself.
[Aizen]
That's a good
attitude to have.
Huh?!
What the?!
How'd he get there?!
It's like he's moving
too fast to track him.
A group offensive, distractions,
sneak attacks, decoys...
To battle me you'll need to
use all of those fighting
strategies and more.
Your chance of capturing me is
very slim...
How interesting!
With so many of us attacking,
you think you can stay calm?!
Nice move, Rose!
Keep him tethered
like that, so he
can't get away!
Don't worry.
I've got him!
Eeyyahhh!!!
Now!
Yaaaagh!
Aizen!
He's not
even fazed!
Quite impressive!
And he didn't even get
a single scratch...
You really thought because
you had me outnumbered,
you could crush me?!
Think again.
You see, my understanding of
what the word power means,
is undoubtedly radically
different than what that
word means to you.
I'll teach you.
Here's what power is.
Huh?!
I'll give you an example.
Kokujo Tenken Myo-oh!
[gurgle]
Yahhh!
Hm.
(Seriously Wounded Exhaled
React)
(Ready to Rumble Growl)
Kinshara!
Now you see, Others don't fear
Captain Aizen just because he
can use his Kyokasuigetsu to
destroy them.
Yes, Kyokasuigetsu's
power is terrifying,
but fearing it alone
wouldn't have been enough
to subjugate all those who
would rather die than obey.
There was only one reason why
those powerful Espadas were
able to function as a group,
in spite of their wildly
different personalities and
uniquely individual motives.
It's because Captain Aizen...
is strength itself.
His power, speed, and precision
all exceed that of a normal Soul
Reaper. He has no equal.
You can attempt to safeguard
against his Kyokasuigetsu
all you want, but you could
never prepare enough.
Even if you put your heads
together, he will outthink you.
Take all the precautions you'd
like against unfortunate
happenings like the sky falling
or the earth splitting,
but I can assure you,
there's really no use in trying.
Create all the elaborate plans
you want,
but his superior powers will
undo any of your schemes.
[Aizen]
A Hollowfication?
I told you, you're all
just failed experiments.
Have you forgotten that I
rule over the Arrancars?
Mock Arrancars like you
should never try to attack me.
It can't be!
Is it your turn now?
Very interesting.
I never expected
the Stealth Force's
Commander to show up here.
[Aizen]
"One must not expect beauty out
of a battle. Or virtue in death.
"It's not merely your
life at stake here.
"If you truly wish to
protect your comrades,
attack the enemy from behind."
Every Soul Reaper should've
learned this at the Academy.
Especially a member
of the Stealth Force.
Hmph.
I never expected to hear
a traitor talk about how
Soul Reapers's should act.
How ironic...
At one time-I was a teacher to
them.
Central Forty-Six must've been
stupid if they were letting
someone like you teach.
That surely helps explain
why a two-faced traitor
like you could fool them.
It's not good to talk
ill of the dead.
Let's face the facts.
You were fooled as well,
weren't you?
Really? Do you think
I was fooled by you?
Of all people, Me?!
Cloning, huh? This is quite
an impressive performance.
I feel so honored
by you praising me.
Never before has the
Stealth Force been praised
for our slick flashiness,
So to thank you,
I'm going to finish you off
with this performance!
Nigeki Kessatsu.
"Nigeki Kessatsu", huh?
[gasp]
What an amusing
technique.
But it's not good enough.
What?!
A Soul Reaper battle
involves Spirit Energy.
I can easily overwhelm your
silly power by accessing my
own Spirit Energy.
[gasp]
(CT Shocked Suddenly Being
Run-Through Grunt Noticing
react)
[Shunsui]
How careless
of you.
Your form made a shadow on the
ice.
Kyoraku...You bastard...
Hm.
It's all over, Aizen.
Gh!
Tch.
You really are naive...
You recklessly charge in when
you see a chance at victory.
You act on impulse.
That is your biggest
deficiency, Captain Hitsugaya.
No...
[Aizen]
It's the other way around!
They did it...
They sure did!
The Captains,
they finally did it!
They defeated Aizen!
Hey, Izuru!
Now we've got something
to celebrate!
We won! so you might try
putting a smile on your face!
Uh, right...
Oh wow! I'm surprised
you're able to sit up!
I'm amazed!
Momo...?
Hey wait...
Where exactly are
you going, Momo?
Hey! Wait a second!
Yeah-Slow down!
How 'bout that.
We finally turned
this thing around.
Didn't we, Gin?
Hey guys...
Hold on...
What the hell are you guys
doing?!
Momo...!??
But how..??!
When did you do it?
A good question.
So when did I do it?
My Kyokasuigetsu's power
is complete hypnosis,
so I have the ability to
alter your perception of
what's real.
It's so overpowering it can
control all five of your senses
and lead people to hallucinate
all sorts of strange things.
Shut up, I know that!!
I'm asking you when you
used your Kyokasuigetsu!
So here's a
question for you.
Now consider this.
At what time did you think that
I wasn't using my Kyokasuigetsu?
[gasp]
Shiro...Why...?
Why?
[anguished scream]
Auuugggghh!!
Captain! Control yourself!!
You've left yourself...
wide open...
Damn it...
Heh heh heh.
[Ichigo]
Aizen and Gin are
the only ones left.
The rest is up to me!
[Aizen]
Do you really believe that we
are the only one's left?
[Ichigo]
We're not?
[Aizen]
Aren't you
forgetting someone?
[Ichigo]
No, I don't think so.
[Aizen]
Are you sure?
[Ichigo]
I won't fall for
your deception!
[Aizen]
But I'm not
deceiving you.