[theme music]
NARRATOR: Ichigo and the
Soul Society's advance troops
were ambushed by the Arrancars.
During the battle,
Ichigo was injured
and Orihime was coerced
into going to Hueco Mundo.
The Soul Society alerts
Ichigo and the others
of Orihime's disappearance,
and Ichigo vows to save her.
But he is forbidden
from taking action
by Head Captain Yamamoto.
The head captain determined
that the Arrancars had
had sufficient time to prepare
and that a battle was imminent.
He ordered Captain Hitsugaya,
Rukia, and the advance troops
to return to the Soul
Society immediately.
Left alone in the
world of the living,
Ichigo decided to ignore Head
Captain Yamamoto's orders
and made plans to go to
Hueco Mundo on his own.
Not knowing how to
break into Hueco Mundo,
Ichigo went to Urahara's shop to
get the information he needed.
When he arrived, he found that
Uryu and Chad had been waiting
there for him, and
were determined
to travel to Hueco
Mundo as well.
-Believe in us.
-It looks like
everybody's ready.
Finally.
-Let's go.
ORIHIME: I can't help but
wonder if it was really
a good idea for me to come here.
I wonder if the battle got worse
because I healed those people.
No.
But right now, I
have to make them
think that I'm of use
to them, no matter what.
At least-- At least
until everyone
is prepared for battle.
-You know.
Somehow, I never expected
the buildings here
to look as solid as this.
It's weird, huh.
I mean, when you consider all
the crazy things that come out
of this place, I figured
it would look like a dump.
-Ichigo, keep your voice down.
If they don't already
know we're here,
we don't wanna go around
advertising the fact.
-Is this place
really Hueco Mundo?
-Did you hear what I just said?
-I heard you.
Think I'm deaf?
You were making more
noise than I was.
-Oh, yeah, sorry.
-Hey.
I figure this'll go a lot faster
if we let them know we're here.
We just grab the first
guy who shows up,
then we make him tell
us where Orihime is.
Hey!
Is anyone here?
Come on out!
-Ichigo.
-Well, are you just
gonna stand there,
or are you gonna
help me find someone?
Hello?
-He's right.
-No.
Not you too.
Hey wait for me!
[alarm sounding]
-All right.
Looks like the coast is clear.
-Hey!
Where is everyone?
-Ichigo.
-What's wrong?
You already said
the coast was clear,
so there's nothing
to worry about.
-Of course you need to worry.
You can't just walk in here
without any sense of caution.
Just shut up, will you?
-Uryu, calm down.
-I'm the calmest one here!
-Huh?
-We better get out of here.
-Look what you've done.
Is that what you
call being careful?
-If you'd kept your mouth shut,
we wouldn't be in this mess!
-Hey!
Don't try to blame
this one on me.
-Now may not be the best
time to settle this argument.
-Tell him that!
URYU: A hallway.
Should we take it?
-Anything's gotta
be better than this.
-Chad!
-Uryu.
-Hang on!
-Thanks guys.
That was close.
-What idiots.
Who uses old fashioned
traps like that?
-I wouldn't talk if
I were you, 'cause
you're the one who fell for
that old fashioned trap.
-Bu-- I-- sorry, I guess I
just wasn't paying attention.
-Well, as long as we
know whose fault it was.
-I think we should keep moving.
-Well, anyway, at least
this path looks safe enough.
-Hm.
-Well, that's fine, but
where does it lead to?
Where the hell are we going?
-How am I supposed to know?
-We've been walking
quite a while.
We'll have to run into
something sooner or later.
-I'm not so sure about that.
We haven't come across
a single sign of life.
Knowing our luck,
this'll end up being
a one way road to nowhere.
-Just keep your guard up.
You never know.
-Don't worry about me.
I'm ready for anything.
Uh oh.
Bummer.
-It looks like
it's the same kind
of trigger as the last one.
[rumbling]
-Wait a minute.
That sound.
What the hell is it?
-I hope it's not
what I think it is.
We're screwed.
-Amazing.
All the traps they've
set are so simplistic.
-I'm glad you find
them so impressive.
I never said I was impressed.
-Where are you going?
Just leave this to me.
-Chad!
Nice work, Chad.
-Nice, huh?
I told you to keep your guard
up, but you wouldn't listen!
-Yeah, yeah, whatever.
It was all my fault.
Are you happy?
-Hey.
Don't ignore me.
I'm not just gonna
let it go this time.
-Who are you?
-Oh, you finally showed up.
Wait!
What are we running away for?
We've been trying to flush
one out and we finally did.
We need to get back there
and beat some answers out
of that guy.
-Are you insane?
What do we do if we're fighting
in a small space like that
and the walls
collapse around us?
-Who cares if the
walls collapse.
It's not gonna make
any damn difference.
-You must work really
hard to be this dumb.
Didn't you notice anything
while we were walking around?
We haven't passed a single
window this entire time.
So, think.
Why aren't there any windows?
Because this corridor is
underground, you dummy.
-Who cares if we're underground.
-Fighting in this space
is not a good idea.
We've gotta find an area
with more open space.
-Uryu, look.
It's some kind of hall.
-All right.
You don't have any problems
with this place, do you?
-Hm?
A staircase.
If we're lucky, it will
connect to the outside.
I'll go check.
-Hey!
-Where do you think
you're going, intruder?
URYU (VOICEOVER): Another one.
I guess I shouldn't be
surprised that we stirred up
more than one in
a place this big.
It's another trap.
Looks like they've
got us sandwiched.
-Hey.
Just shut up, will you?
URYU: Are these
things Arrancars too?
-They sure look a lot more
like Hollows than the ones
we were dealing with back
in the world of the living.
Eh, it doesn't matter
to me what they are.
You guys just stand
back and watch.
I'll handle these two--
What the hell are you doing?
-You're the one who needs to
just stand back and watch.
-This time--
-We're going to handle it.
-What's with you guys?
URYU: Take it easy.
You're gonna want to save
your strength for when
we find Orihime.
Besides.
I've spent some
time with Kisuke,
and he's been informing
me about the Arrancars.
Apparently, the group that
Grimmjow brought with him
was a mixture of Gillians
and Adjuchas class Arrancars.
When a Menos Grande
becomes an Arrancar,
it doesn't always take
on a humanoid form.
But only the most powerful
class, the Vasto Lordes,
take on a human shape
100% of the time.
And as for the
other two classes,
even if they do become
Arrancars, many of them
won't take on a humanoid form.
Also, the lower their
intelligence, the more likely
they'll resemble
an ordinary Hollow.
-Uryu!
-That is unforgivable.
Demoura is one thing,
but you're implying
that I, Aisslinger,
have low intelligence.
Absolutely unforgivable.
-Aisslinger, shut your face.
Stop acting like
you're all high,
and mighty, and smarter than me.
Huh?
Gotcha!
-What would we want
with human forms?
We abandoned our human
forms long ago so
that we could become
even more powerful.
Hmph.
Don't underestimate me, human.
[shout]
-This is crazy!
Let me help!
-Stay right there.
Chad And I have
got this handled.
-Bastard!
I'm the one you
have to fight now!
Argh!
Ah!
Uryu, what was that for?
-I told you to stay
out of the way.
-Huh?
-What the hell's with you guys?
-Just stay out of the way.
Got it?
-I wouldn't waste time
worrying about your friends
if I were you.
-Hey Chad, look out!
-Stay back, Ichigo!
-We'll handle this ourselves.
-What the hell?
-Damn.
I thought this guy was just
using an ordinary attack.
But he's summoning all the
spirit energy around him
into the palm of his hand.
That attack's a lot more
dangerous than it looks.
I can't construct
my weapon when he's
disrupting the spiritual
pressure like this.
If I could get a little
distance between us-- Chad!
-Huh?
AISSLINGER (VOICEOVER):
His attack is too slow.
He could never keep
up with my Sonido.
Their fighting ability
is easy to measure.
The one has power, but
lacks speed and agility.
The other is fast, but lacks
the power to do any real damage.
I'll finish this!
-Now!
-Huh?
What's he doing?
Why is he just standing there?
-So you've finally
given up, human fool!
Argh!
-Demoura, wait!
[crying out]
-My, my.
Compatibility is
always so important.
I became so absorbed
in the challenge
of fighting the same
opponent all this time
that I completely forgot
one of the basics.
You see, I forgot we
were fighting two on two.
If either one of us is having
difficulty fighting with one,
we could simply
trade with the other
for a more compatible enemy.
Pit power against power.
And of course,
speed against speed.
Now then...
time to step up this battle.
-What the hell is that?
Uryu-- is that a bow?
-You have to ask?
Interesting.
What else would it be?
Have you ever know
me to go into battle
with any other
weapon than a bow?
This is my new weapon.
Ginrei Kojaku.
[screaming]
CHAD: It's a good thing I
didn't destroy your entire mask.
Half of your face is bad enough.
I'd hate to see the rest.
[shout]
-That's all you've got?
Too bad.
I was hoping you'd be stronger.
[shout]
-Dammit.
Disgusting human.
URYU: So that's a Sonido, is it?
You were right.
You are fast.
Impossible.
He's just a human.
There's no way he could keep
up with the speed of my Sonido.
-Oh, that's right.
I guess I forgot to tell you
that I'm not an ordinary human.
I am a Quincy.
This is Hirenkyaku, a Quincy
high speed maneuvering
technique.
I happen to think it's better
than the Soul Reaper's Flash
Step, but that's my opinion.
-A Quincy?
You mean you're some kind
of higher level human?
I never knew anything
like that existed.
-You didn't know?
That's too bad.
I guess you really are ignorant.
-Even if you can keep
up with my Sonida,
that's not going
to change anything.
The only weapon you've
got is that bow,
and there's no way it can defend
you against my Una Tirotear.
Oh, what?
You really think you'll
be able to shoot down
all of my Tirotear?
What a childish tactic.
You'll have to think of
something better than that.
Go ahead.
Give it your best shot, Quincy.
But I think there's
something you should know.
My Una Tirotear is able to
fire a continuous stream of 108
shots at once.
Let's see how long you
can stand up against that.
URYU: Oh, I see.
108 shots all at once
is very impressive.
The only thing is my Ginrei
Kojaku fires slightly more.
Like 1,200.
[screaming]
-Huh?
Dammit.
You'll pay for that.
I won't lose to a
weakling like you.
You hear me?
I won't lose!
No!
He couldn't!
No way!
-Are you done?
Since you waited until
now to use that attack,
I'm guessing it was
your last resort,
and you've got nothing left.
So I think it's time I
show you my final attack.
I'd rather not.
You see, I don't
enjoy finishing off
an enemy who's lose
his will to fight.
It just doesn't
sit right with me.
But in this situation,
I just can't
allow myself to feel
any pity for your kind.
El Directo.
[theme music]
CHAD: It looks
like we'll finally
get to see all of the Espada.
ICHIGO: More new characters?
We've already got Soul Reaper
captains, Visoreds, and now
Espada?
It's getting so
crowded around here.
Someone's going to
have to disappear soon.
URYU: Better stay on
your toes, Ichigo.
You can't afford to
let your guard down.
ICHIGO: Again?