Welcome to my castle, Los
Noches.
[roaring]
Shatter...
Kyokasuigetsu!
I am the emperor...
Barragan Ruizenban!
Now then...
The preparations for our
invasion are finally
complete.
We will now mobilize our
forces into the World of
the Living.
I will wipe out Karakura
Town, create the Ouken,
and bring down the Soul
Society.
The door to a new world
will be opened.
Stark. Barragan.
Halibel. I'm counting
on you to pull off this
attack.
Everything is in place,
and we're ready to begin
on your command. We shall
not fail you, Lord Aizen.
Whatever you say, sir.
Hm?
You... bastards!
Jakuho Raikouben!
[growling]
See ya.
[screaming]
Oh, dear...
It looks like another one
of your friends has gone
down in flames.
[panting]
Captain Soi Fon!
Man.. That was close,
Captain? Are you all
right?
I've felt better, but...
at least I'm still
alive.
There's a large crack in
the Shiju Saimon barrier...
... made by the Jakuho
Raikoben.
I've never seen such a
thing---Its power is
incredible.
Are you two all right
down there?
What kind of a question
is that, fatso?! Of course
not! She could've died!
Under normal
circumstances, I can only
use the Jakuho Raikoben
once every three days.
Now I've used it twice in
one day.
Just so we're clear, I
expect to be compensated
for this.
Oh yes, of course.
I'll pay you back,
as promised.
I'll trap Kiskuke Urahara in
my strongest barrier for a
full month. Huh?!
The barrier's crumbling!
Impossible!
[gasping]
Unforgivable!
What?! Is
this for real?
[gasping]
Unforgivable!
This can't be!
You will pay for this!
Oh, damn it! How can he
still be alive after
getting hit by my Jakuho
Raikoben?!
Is he invincible?!
I'm going to kill you
all! And I'm going to do
it with my own hands!
I am the king of Hueco
Mundo! I am a god! I can
never die!
[grunting]
You will regret your
insolence toward me!
I will turn you
all to dust!
I don't understand what's
driving him so hard to
defeat us! Do you think
it's his loyalty to Aizen?
You don't really think
that will save you from
my wrath, do you?!
There is no escape from
me!
I will disintegrate your
bones!
You think mimicking a
Hollow will protect you?!
Know your place!
I am the emperor...
...Barragan Ruizenban!
I am the god of Hueco
Mundo!
Watch yourself, Hachigen!
[laughing]
Puny beings! You pale in
comparison to my powers!
Your petty concerns are
of little importance!
Soul Reapers, humans,
Hollows, Arrancars...
as well as free will,
animals, plants, the sun,
the moon, and the stars...
In reality, they
mean nothing.
As you are about to
discover, the only thing
that is absolute in this
world is my power!
Other than that,
everything else is a
trifling matter!
The fact is, I am
supremely powerful. And
as such, the world should
be under my control.
There can be no equality
between opposing powers.
Your lives hold no real
value. To me, you are no
To me, you are no
more than ants.
[laughing]
I commend you! I'm
surprised that an ant
like you has even been
able to injure me!
I imagine you will feel
quite proud of yourself
in hell!
[laughing]
What? What's happening
here?
You're the one who gave
me the idea.
That is your own power,
the only thing that is
absolute in this world.
Hmm?
Something about all this
seemed strange to me. As
we've witnessed,
everything your power
touches, grows old, rots,
and crumbles to dust. But
that doesn't explain why
it prevents you from
turning into dust as
well.
That paradox led me to
come up with a theory.
If you weren't suffering
the effects of exposure
to this power, it stood
to reason that you must
have surrounded your body
with something that could
hold it at bay.
I had to breach that
barrier, so I forced your
power back inside of you,
to a place where that
protection would normally
never reach.
That is impossible! How
could you do that without
my being aware of it!
You bastard! What have
you done with your right
arm?!
What game are you
playing?!
It's no game---My arm's
inside you!
He severed his own arm
with a barrier, and
transported the rotting
flesh inside Barragan!
How did he come up
with that?! That
man's a genius!
If your power is
absolute, as you say,
then it only makes sense
that you, yourself,
should not be able to
withstand that power.
I had no proof of this
when I took the chance to
infect you. But now that
I see the results,
I'm glad I made the right
call.
Curse you, you ant! How
dare you defy a god in
this way?!
Your insolence will
doom you to destruction!
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid
the word 'god' is not
very familiar to those of
us who are inhabitants of
the Soul Society.
As a result, we
apologize---We are not
able to understand the
implications of your words.
We must ask you to
forgive our lack of
faith, god of Hueco
Mundo. Now, farewell.
[screaming]
Wow! Amazing!
He pulled it off! He
actually defeated that
guy!
[groaning]
I'm amazed you're still
able to move!
I will not die! I refuse
to die.
I have sworn revenge! I
promised I would kill you
for your disrespect, and
I will! You will pay for
your arrogance! And I'll
exact that penalty with
my own hands!
I am a king! I am a god!
I shall not die... unless
I take you with me!
Hachigen, look out!
We will die together!!
[bell ringing]
[sighing]
I have had enough.
How boring. Nothing is
more meaningless than a
trained army without a
single enemy to conquer.
Am I wrong?
Not sure why I bother to
ask. No one here is going
to disagree with me.
[roaring]
What happened?!
Gagamel's been killed!
Identify yourselves!
[growling]
Stand down.
This is just the thing I
need to pass the time.
Why have you come here,
strangers?
Very pleased to meet you.
My name is Aizen...
...I'm Sosuke Aizen.
You must be Barragan,
king of Hueco Mundo.
Indeed. And what exactly
are you? Since none of
you are wearing masks,
I have to presume
you are not Hollows.
Are you humans? Or are
you Soul Reapers?
Well, it doesn't matter
what you are. Truthfully,
I am growing weary.
If you had not shown up,
I would have had to
improvise some
entertainment. I would
have split my army into
two, and forced them to
kill each other.
Be that as it may, I
suppose I should greet
you. Welcome to my
castle, Los Noches.
Heh.
How amusing. This place,
with no roof or walls, is
a castle?
I have no need for a
roof. as king, that all
of Hueco Mundo's skies
form the roof of my castle.
I see---Well, I suppose
that would be one way of
looking at it.
That's quite enough,
Kaname. There's no
point in baiting him.
Right.
Your majesty, I was
hoping we might have a...
...little chat.
Could you take a look at
my sword...?
It's called...
Kyokasuigetsu.
And why should I care?
I wish to ask you a
simple question.
What is it?
Tell me... Are you
satisfied with your
existence as it stands
in this moment?
What?
Have you ever looked
around and felt your
world was not the way it
should be? Do you ever
find yourself wishing you
could achieve a higher
greatness?
Hmm...
I can help you. You just
have to obey me.
If you were to do so,
I could give you even
greater power.
Greater power, you say?
That's right. My research
will soon be complete.
I'm perfecting a way to
turn Soul Reapers into
Hollows, and Hollows into
Soul Reapers.
By removing the
boundaries between these
two opposing states of
being, you could achieve
higher greatness.
You could truly lead the
way to stepping forth
into a new world.
[laughing]
What an amusing proposal!
You actually have the
nerve to suggest I can
achieve greater power and
discover a new world?
Don't make me laugh! I am
the king of Hueco Mundo,
the king of all I survey!
No one can surpass my
power, least of all you
foolish mortals! No world
exists, other than the
one I already control!
How unfortunate...
Attack them now, my
minions! Crush these
arrogant ants!
What an unfriendly bunch.
[roaring]
I shall take you on
myself.
You are about to be
killed by the king of
Hueco Mundo. Consider it
an honor.
It seems awfully
ironic... for the
king of Hueco Mundo.
Think about it, my
friend. Even though
you're a Hollow, the way
you wield your weapon,
and your giant black
form...
...remind me very much of
a Soul Reaper.
Silence!
Hmpf! What a fool! In the
end, you weren't even
able to put up a proper
fight.
How pathetic. It was
hardly worth my effort.
What is this?
You! How can you still be
alive?!
My Zanpakuto,
Kyokasuigetsu, has the
power of complete
hypnosis.
What are you talking
about?
In other words, the
people you defeated
before, were nothing more
than illusions.
Shatter... Kyokasuigetsu!
What is happening?!
This is your world...
stripped of all mirage.
You bastard!
Don't do anything rash.
It's pointless. You won't
be able to kill me.
Yes. On that day, I made
a vow...
A vow that I would take
my revenge on you...
That I would take back my
throne, no matter what
the cost.
That day is here! We will
die together!
I have been waiting for
this opportunity for a
long time, Sosuke
Aizen...!
The moment of retribution
is finally at hand. you
will regret ever giving
me power.
That power is
your undoing!
I am a king, a god! I
will never die! I will
hunt you forever, Sosuke
Aizen!
Farewell, King of Hueco
Mundo. In the end, it
turned out you shared the
same concerns as most mortals.
...A desire to avoid
aging, coupled with a
great fear of death.
My goodness, it appears
the Soul Reapers have
actually defeated him---
You should pay attention,
or those may be your last
words.
There's always time to
die. Why are you in such
a hurry? I'm not going
anywhere.
I can't waste a lot of
time dealing with
underlings. Once I've
taken care of you, I'm
gonna go kill that
bastard, Sosuke.
One thing at a time, my
friend.
[grunting]
Our Number Two just
died... and he doesn't
give a damn.
Shameful.
What's wrong?
Don't talk to me,
Lilinette.
Are you crying? Ow!
What's going on?
Are you okay, Stark?
Revenge isn't my thing,
but I'll make an exception.
Gin, you and I are both
from the same region---We
should get to know each
other better!
I doubt you know anything
about where I'm from.
We're not even in the
same league.
That's kind of
closed-minded.
You're obviously coarse
and lack elegance.
That's it! I swear on my
homeland, I'm taking you
down!