Gunchotsurara!
You're about to find out
that each Espada signifies
an aspect of death.
Damn it all! Ryusenka!
Hunt...
...Tiburon!
[gasping]
You are powerless.
Your ice dragon is
drowned by a single
strike from a shark...
You are next...
I will avenge those three
you burned...
You will suffer!
How can you still be
alive?
After your sword release,
I didn't think that your
speed and range would
increase so quickly.
But I took a
few precautions.
An illusion made of
ice...
I can only use a move
like this once, so I held
off using it until I knew
it would have the maximum
effect on our battle.
Our strength is not...
to be underestimated.
It's clear to me now...
As I might have expected
from a captain level Soul
Reaper, you have an ability
proportionate to your rank.
It helps you avoid
danger, but I hope you
don't think that's
enough to save you.
I don't need saving.
Ahhh! That's a lot of
destructive power!
[trembling]
Huh?
You fool...
Keep your guard up! It's
bad enough I'm stuck here
with a big dumbass like you!
Oh, sorry about that.
Wait a minute! That's a
pretty harsh statement,
Captain!
That crack about my
ass wasn't very nice.
Getting nervous about
this fight? Halibel puts
on quite a show.
At this point, the enemy
must experience the pain
of her sacrifice.
Sacrifice?
That's right...
You're about to find out
that each Espada signifies
an aspect of death.
A mortal's death always
results from one of these
aspects.
The presence of these
aspects is the basis
behind each Espada's
abilities, beliefs, and
reason for existing.
Solitude...
Nothingness...
Despair...
Destruction...
Ecstasy...
Madness...
Greed...
Rage...
And Halibel signifies
the aspect of death
known as sacrifice.
Her lethal power
is unstoppable.
It will eventually
consume her opponent,
leading to his death.
[grunting]
Too weak.
[gasping]
I'm already familiar with
that technique!
You've
misjudged me.
My Zanpakuto is extremely
powerful. In case you
didn't notice, its ice
and snow capability has
the strength to turn any
kind of water into a
lethal weapon...
Even if the water in
question happens to be
your weapon.
The truth is, if all you
can do is manipulate
water...
... then your attacks
will never be able to
reach me.
They can... and
they will.
If you want to see the
proof, then I'll show
you.
Come on.
What makes you think I'm
going to fall for your
taunts and close the
distance between us?
I told you that
you misjudged me.
That was your
first mistake!
Actually, you're the one
who misjudged me...
Hirviendo.
[gasping]
Yes, you realized that my
water could become your
weapon. But you ignored
the possibility that the
opposite could also be
true.
Your ice could become
my weapon.
Cascada.
Hmm?
Captain Komamura!
Don't worry, Izuru.
It was quite loud,
but that shockwave was
nowhere near us.
Please hurry, and finish
treating everyone's
injuries.
Yes, sir.
The only problem is...
there are so many of them.
And they're hurt so badly.
There's no way I can get
this done in time on my
own.
This force field isn't
impenetrable, either.
If we're attacked, there's
only one thing standing
between us and them...
...And that's Captain
Komamura!
Come on out.
Do you really think that
I'm a big enough fool to
be taken in by another
one of your tricks?
That was close.
I was able to avoid it by
quickly putting up a wall
of ice.
But if I had gotten
caught by that force, I
wouldn't have lasted a
second.
I'm not gonna stand a
chance against her with
an ordinary defense.
What are you doing?
Are you taking a break?
Or did you come to your
senses...
... and decide it's
time to surrender.
So if the enemy's weapon
can be taken over and
become your own...
... then the opposite
is also true.
You must not think
I'm very bright.
Let me tell you, I was
well aware of that concept
before you decided to
lecture me.
Gunchotsurara!
We're about to see if
your technique is
effective or not.
Hirviendo.
Uh!
[yelling]
Thank you for the lecture,
Tier Halibel. Now allow me
to teach you something.
Your greatest vulnerability
is exposed when you use your
strongest tactic.
For me, that's always
been an ironclad rule.
Very amusing.
Hm!
Well. It's about time.
I was beginning to think
you weren't going to take
this fight seriously.
Believe me, I'm serious.
And I seriously don't
intend to sit by and get
pounded.
Oh really? It seemed
like you were barely
putting any effort into it.
Hm?
[gasping]
Hm...
Hey, that was close!
If you had attacked me
like you really meant it,
I'd probably be dead by
now.
You had no intention of
cutting me from the start.
So why have you gone through
all this trouble?
We won't get anywhere if
all we do is guess each
other's intentions.
Things will only change
if one of us takes the
first step forward.
But that's where the
problem lies, doesn't it?
Neither one wants to give
away his strategy.
Both of us are waiting
for the other guy to make
the first move.
It's an interesting
situation when you
think about it,
because it all comes
down to a contest of
will.
Someone's going to have
to go first.
Getting impatient yet?
I'd love to see your Cero
about now.
All right, already.
Let's get this over with.
I'll take you up on
your invitation.
[gasping]
La Gota.
What is she planning
to do?
It doesn't look like she's
blindly launching a barrage
of attacks.
On the other hand, she
must be aware that her
technique is not strong
enough to finish me.
She doesn't appear to be
aiming right directly at
me.
Shouldn't you look where
you're going?
[gasping]
Dammit!
You seem to be most
confident when you're
running away.
Cero.
[gasping]
[panting]
No more running away
for you.
You fight such a timid
battle. Can't say I really
blame you, though.
You and I are both
waiting for the same
thing, aren't we...?
...Waiting for this
battleground to be
filled with water...
...so we can strike a
final blow.
So, what's
your point?
It just means one of us
will have to make a
decision.
We'll go in circles if
she and I continue like
this.
I've never attempted this
with Bankai before... but
I'll have to take the chance.
Have you come up with
some sort of strategy?
To tell you the truth,
it's not really necessary
for me to wait for water
to gather.
I'm ready.
[gasping]
This Spiritual
Pressure...!
[gasping]
They're too
close to us!
What's the matter?
Did you hesitate because
you might injure your
allies?
None of your business!
You should try worrying
about yourself!
You're right.
Either your allies get
sacrificed in this fight...
Or you yourself will
become the sacrifice.
Please, feel free
to pick an option.
What about this
option?
Sennen Hyoro!
Hm.
He trapped her!
[gasping]
Spare me. Is this
the best you can do?
What?!
Are you through? If you
don't have anything more,
then I guess it's my turn.
Dammit.
Cascada...
If I dodge her attack...
Uh!
...She'll hit the people
below!
All right.
Ryusenka!
Ahhhh!
Do you think you can stop
me, using a weak response
like that?
Check the volume of
the water in this
battleground.
It has already reached a
level that is more than
enough to finish you.
And believe me, this
Cascada won't compare to
anything you've seen before.
Ahhhhhh!
Captain
Hitsuguya...
Come on, Captain.
You can do it.
[grunting]
Ahhhhhhh!
Impossible! Captain
Hitsugaya!
To..
...shiro.
So, you were able to
shatter that Cascada. But
you've accomplished
nothing.
When we sacrifice
ourselves, it's to
further our tactical
advance.
You, on the other
hand, are willing
to fall in battle,
simply to protect the
other members of your
squad.
My subordinates were not
simply defeated. Each one
left behind a marker for
me, a guideline telling
me how to carry on the
fight.
If I lose this battle...
The sacrifices of my
predecessors will have
all been for nothing.
I hold within me the
resolve of those who
have fallen before me.
I'm resolved as well.
Resolved to stop you.
I suffered a great deal
of damage, but I can
still fight.
Yes, but it's a waste of
time. You won't be able
to operate at full strength.
I'll trust that what
strength I have left,
will be enough to keep
you from victory.
Such wasted effort.
Hmm!
What's going on?
My Hyorinmaru is the
strongest ice and snow
type Zanpakuto.
It allows me to weaponize
all kinds of water, from
any source.
The entire sky
is always...
... under my control.
Hyoten Hyakkaso...!
That Barragan dude guy
sure is sure able to
memorize a lot of stuff,
isn't he?
He didn't memorize it. He
was looking at his hands
the whole time he was
talking. He probably
wrote down all his lines
on his palms.
Really?---In that case,
the guy's pretty stupid!
Just like you.
What?!!!