ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Ever since
the powers of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me, my
whole world is changed.
Now, I'm Ichigo Kurosaki,
substitute Soul Reaper.
And I'm combining my
powerful spirit energy
with this blade in order
to protect my friends!
[theme music]
ICHIGO: So now what, guys?
What do we do now?
What do we do?
What?
-I know.
How about you stop repeating
the same thing over and over?
It sucks.
ICHIGO: What did you say?
-I said, quit your yammering.
Say something meaningful,
or else shut up!
-I'll say whatever I
want to say, you freak.
Unless you think
you could stop me.
-Yeah, I'll stop you.
-I'd like to see you try.
-Oh, please.
Stop it, you two.
-You're acting like a
couple of five-year-olds.
[grunting]
-Hmph.
-Orihime, do you remember
anything about your kidnappers?
We need a clue,
something to go on.
-Hm.
Hey, there is one thing
I just remembered.
-[together] Hm?
-We had some tea.
-They gave you tea?
-And that's not all.
There were muffins, too.
-Orihime, that isn't gonna help.
-Mm, sorry.
-How can we rescue
Chad if we don't
know who these people are.
-We know they're
Mod-Souls, just like me.
They make us look stupid.
And they're driving me
up the frickin' wall.
-It worries me that we
still haven't heard back
from Urahara.
And what got Yoruichi
in such a panic?
What the hell's
going on around here?
-Hey, are you listening to me?
Nobody ignores me.
You should be listening
to everything I-- [squeak]
-Shut up, you.
-What gets me are
these games of theirs.
Why don't they get
to the point, instead
of making us waste our
time running around?
ICHIGO: There's a
lot we don't know.
HITSUGAYA: What about Sui-Feng?
-She went off somewhere
alone, apparently right
before the gate was sealed shut.
-She didn't take
anyone with her?
No one from the
Punishment Force?
-That's right.
That's what Omaeda just told me.
What exactly is
going on, Captain?
-It's all part of a plan that
Yoruichi Shihoin and Ukitake
put together.
It's nothing you need to
concern yourself with.
Oh, and by the way,
what were you doing out
talking to Omaeda
the first place?
I seem to recall you had a whole
day's worth of paperwork to do.
-Uh, I did.
But I got it all finished
much faster than I expected.
-Interesting, Rangiku.
Then I suppose that mountain
of files hidden over there
behind the sofa is
just my imagination.
Rangiku!
-Where do you
think you're going?
-There's no point in
hanging around here.
I'm going to head back to
Urahara's shop and wait.
-But what about Chad and all
the kids from our school?
-Actually, they're probably
not in any real danger.
Whatever these guys
are up to, they
do seem to follow
the game's rules.
I think it's safe to assume
that the worst they'll
do to Chad and the others is
to give them some challenges.
-Hey, what's going on?
-What is it?
ICHIGO: It says,
"You have 30 minutes
to destroy the gate-- Ririn."
What gate?
-Something's coming!
-Whoa, look at that.
It's huge!
-Yeah, it's too freaking
huge to even be real.
It's got to be
another hallucination.
URYU: It's opening.
[gasping]
-Damn it.
-Ichigo, what about your body?
-We'll to get it later.
Let's go.
YORUICHI: Hurry!
SUI-FENG: Right.
YORUICHI: Look at this.
-Hm.
It looks like--
YORUICHI: --reishi residue.
Obviously, the
intruder's a lot faster
than I expected him to be.
-I'll send this data to the
Soul Society right away.
YORUICHI: Good.
Ukitake should be standing by.
HITSUGAYA: I thought I might
find you here, Shunsui.
-Hey, look.
It's the boy genius.
Care for a drink?
-I think I'll pass.
Am I interrupting?
-Welcome, captain.
HITSUGAYA: What are you
two old men up to anyway?
-It's a bit of an investigation.
We're receiving some data
right now from Sui-Feng
in the World of the Living.
-Then that must
be the reason you
needed to have the gates sealed.
KYORAKU: Exactly.
It's much easier to isolate
intruders and collect accurate
data on them when we don't
have other souls passing
back and forth.
-Intruders?
-Right.
We're trying, but so far
we haven't identified them.
-Is all this related in some
way to the Aizen incident?
-It is possible.
So far, it's too soon to tell.
ANALYST: I have the data.
What Sui-Feng sent us
was a reishi sample,
so I ran it through
the analyzer.
-Something's wrong!
There's no way to
identify this reishi.
It's blank.
You must have entered it wrong.
Try again.
ANALYST: Yes, sir.
-What do you think?
-I think it's strange.
KYORAKU: You got that right.
It's going to take
another bottle of sake
for me to get through this.
RENJI: It looks pretty
damn solid to be
just a hallucination.
[giggling]
-Over there!
GIRL: Well, what do you think?
Pretty impressive, isn't it?
-Cut out the stupid small
talk and tell us what's up.
I want to know right now why
the hell you're doing this.
-Aw, it wouldn't be any
fun if I told you that.
We haven't even gotten started
with the final battle yet.
I'll tell you everything
once it's all over.
[grunting]
URYU: Everyone,
hold onto something!
-So strong.
This is no illusion.
Get 'em!
--[shout] You didn't sew
me together very well!
--[giggle] I guess this part of
the game is mostly over now,
isn't it?
But what else can they do?
They should give up.
-Of course you're right.
Well, how about it down there?
Are you ready to
admit your defeat yet?
-Hell, no.
We'll fight, and
we'll beat you, too.
-Yeah?
Do you recognize this?
-I don't believe it.
It's Urahara's hat?
-Oh, well.
You should have surrendered.
-No, Uryu!
-Ichigo, help!
Please, help!
[scream]
-Orihime!
[shouting]
-Ichigo!
[grunting]
-It's too strong!
-Renji, take care of Orihime!
There's only one way
out of this freak show.
-What do you think
you're doing, idiot?
-[grunt]
-You can't use your Bankai
here, or the whole town
will be destroyed, Ichigo!
-If I don't, the town will
get sucked in along with us!
[grunt] Ban-- huh?
-What's the matter, Ichigo?
-No, Ichigo!
-[gasp]
[shouting]
ORIHIME: What-- what happened?
-[grunt] Huh?
How did I--?
Oh, Orihime, can it be
that you came to save me?
ORIHIME: Uryu!
-Where are we?
-Who knows?
We went through the gate.
That's all I can remember.
-Yeah, me too.
Orihime!
Uryu!
URYU: Over here!
ORIHIME: Oh, Ichigo, Renji.
I'm so glad you
two are all right.
-Yeah.
It looks like all
four of us are.
-You mean all five!
Thanks a lot.
-Yeah, but where
have we ended up?
-Is this the alternate dimension
you were talking about?
-I don't know.
[giggling]
-What a surprise to see
all of you still alive.
-Come on down.
You won't laughing for long.
-Better be nice.
Look who we have.
-They've got Chad!
GIRL: Since you've all
managed to survive this long,
I'll give you a bonus round.
Welcome to the Challenge Stage!
-What is this?
-And to make it even
more fun, Noba and Kurodo
will join in, too.
-A grand idea.
That will give us a
chance to finally show
our new friends our true powers.
Right, Noba?
-Huh?
I suppose.
-Oh, come on.
Would it kill you to
show a little enthusiasm?
You're so boring!
-That's enough, Kurodo.
It isn't important.
What is important is that
they only have five minutes.
-[gasp]
-That's right, ha!
Find a way to save your friend
within that time, or else--
well, you can probably figure
out what will happen. [giggle]
-[gasp] An hourglass?
-[giggle] Of death.
All right.
Let the Challenge Stage begin!
Now the Challenge
Stage has begun!
-[laughs]
-Uryu, stay here
and protect Orihime.
-OK, will do.
-Hey, you can ask me
to help too, you know.
KURODO: [laughs] Now
the real fun's starting,
-[gasp]
[fighting noises]
-That guy's turned himself
into a perfect copy of Ichigo.
-Which one is the real one?
-You've got some
nerve copying me.
-Yeah, right.
Look who's talking, you phony.
-Roar, Zabimaru!
Oh, no you don't!
Huh?
-What just happened there?
-It looks like he
sucked up Renji's attack
and then used it against him.
-That's a sneaky power to have.
-Uh, uh, uh.
-Why you-- [grunt]
-You better find a way to beat
me, or that friend of yours
is gonna be breathing sand!
-Chad!
-[giggle]
-You bastard!
Damn it!
-We're close now.
-Right.
-Be careful.
[hypnotic singing]
-What is that?
-I'll find out.
Send the data.
-Hm?
-We're receiving a
video transmission.
-That looks like--
-You shouldn't interrupt
two consenting adults.
-Did he consent to you
sucking out his soul?
Who the hell are you, anyway?
--[laugh] You'll
know soon enough.
SUI-FENG: Shall I chase her?
YORUICHI: No.
She looks skilled
at running away.
Did you send the data?
-Yes.
Do you know that person?
YORUICHI: Yes, but
it's the first time
I've seen her in that form.
Sui-Feng, I want you to
go back now and report
the details of this to Ukitake.
-Right.
-Sentaro, are you there?
-Yes, sir.
-The investigation's done.
I want you remove the seal
from the gate right away.
-Right.
Consider it done, sir.
KYORAKU: There goes another
perfectly good evening wasted.
Goodnight.
-Goodnight, Shunsui.
Captain Hitsugaya, can you
assist me with something?
-If I can, sure.
What is it?
-Yes, well.
[fighting noises]
-It's no use.
-How about this?
-[gasp]
-Sorry, Ichigo.
Are you all right?
-I'm fine.
RIRIN: [giggle] Did you
forget there's a time limit?
It's almost up.
-Chad, no!
-I thought you were
kidding at first,
but I see that you're
seriously trying to defeat us
with these slow-motion
attacks! [laughs]
-And now, for the
final stage. [shout]
[shouting]
-Ichigo!
-Use your Bankai, Ichigo!
It's our only chance!
-All right.
[shout]
-Not again.
It broke!
-Huh?
What happened to it?
-[squeak] Who knows?
-Chad!
Chad!
Chad, are you all right.
-Think so.
-I'll get those ropes off.
-It's OK.
They came lose somehow.
-Huh?
ORIHIME: Chad!
It looks like you're all right.
-Yes.
-Chad, do you
remember anything that
happened while
you were captured?
-Hm.
There was tea.
-You see?
I told you.
You laughed, but
there really was tea.
-Hm.
Heh.
-What is it?
-Ichigo?
-Now I get it.
It all makes sense.
All right, Urahara.
I know you're here somewhere.
-[together] Huh?
ICHIGO: This is all
your doing, isn't it?
Come out and show yourself.
-[gasp]
-That didn't take you
long to figure out.
What was it that tipped you off?
-It was your hat.
When I saw it on the
ground just now, I knew.
-You see?
I told Ririn here
the whole hat thing
was laying it on too thick.
-He's smarter than I gave
him credit for. [giggle]
-Hm.
I should have figured it out,
because you never finished us
off or hurt us when
you had the chance.
You kept pushing us into
tighter and tighter situations,
but you always let us slip away.
We should have noticed that.
Chad was never in any
real danger, was he?
-Uh-uh.
In fact, most of the time
we spent playing checkers.
-She beat me every single game.
-I still don't understand
why you did this.
-If you give me back my hat,
I'll explain everything.
I have found that
certain games can
be very useful for
training purposes.
They can improve a
number of disciplines,
including stamina,
intellect, teamwork, making
quick judgments, and
coping with adversity.
They even strengthen the
bond between friends.
Perhaps most important of all,
they provide a chance for you
to each take a good
look at yourself.
-Do you really
think we need that?
-Yeah.
For instance, your Bankai
doesn't work, does it?
[gasping]
-No way.
Is that true?
-Ichigo.
URAHARA: Remember, you are a
substitute Soul Reaper, not
quite a Soul Reaper.
You may have been able
to use your Bankai freely
while you were in
the Soul Society,
but things are not
quite the same now
that you've returned home.
You mustn't start thinking that
every time things get tough,
all you have to do
is use your Bankai.
Try to remember
it's not that easy.
Hm.
That aside, did you know
that Yoruichi was here
conducting an investigation?
-Yeah?
I was wondering what
had her so concerned.
URAHARA: I don't
know all the details.
But an unexplained phenomenon
has everyone concerned.
-What sort of phenomenon?
-So far, all I know is
that it was serious enough
to justify the Soul
Society closing
the passage to the
World of the Living.
-I know.
I bet it's got something to
do with the Aizen incident,
doesn't it?
-Doubt it Aizen got
away with the Hogyoku,
but he's still going
to need a lot of time
before he can mature it enough
to utilize its full power.
He probably won't surface
or make a move for awhile.
Which is good,
because right now,
you're too weak to counter him.
But Ichigo?
-What is it?
-Soon enough, the issue of
the Hogyoku will return,
and we will not be able to deal
with it without your Bankai.
Will you try to learn
to use it again?
I'm asking you to
do this for me.
-All right.
I'll do it, but--
-An excellent decision!
Thanks so much.
ICHIGO: Huh?
-That guy could sell a
refrigerator to an Eskimo.
-All right, then.
Ichigo, why don't
we get right to it
and start cultivating
your situational analysis
and critical judgment skills?
-Uh--
-Ichigo, you really need
to use your head more.
You let your opponents
take advantage of your
far too often.
-Uh.
-Ironically, the
member of your group
who's best at that kind
of critical thinking
is actually Uryu, the
one who doesn't even
have any powers anymore.
-Huh?
-It's true.
Right, Uryu?
URYU: Yes, I lost
my Quincy powers
while fighting in
the Soul Society.
-Why the hell
didn't you tell us?
-All those times you didn't use
your powers were because you
couldn't?
-Is this really true, Uryu?
-Huh?
-You freakin' idiot.
-What'd you say?
-By doing that, you put
every one of us in danger.
I'm not trying to say
that you endangered us
by not having any powers.
Fighting as a team, we all have
different things we contribute.
And you were a huge help
there in the Soul Society.
But if you lost
your powers, that
isn't something you
should have kept secret
from the rest of us.
We would have been a stronger
team if we had known.
Hey, you have to
trust you friends
enough to tell them the truth.
You know that.
-Ichigo.
--[clap] Well, that concludes
the lesson for today.
Let's go up and have
something to eat?
-Hm?
-I'm guessing by now, Tessai has
whipped us up something tasty.
-But an entire town
just got destroyed.
What are you going
to do about that?
--[giggle] You should know we
would never do something like
that.
That was just a big hologram.
-Well, then, where did all those
kids from our school end up?
-They're probably waking up now?
-[groan] Where are we?
-How did we get here?
-What just happened?
-Well, it's about time
everybody woke up.
-Ms. Ochi?
How did we end up way out
here in the mountains?
-Who knows?
But as long as we're here,
it's a perfect time for us
to learn something.
[groaning]
-Big dipper.
Little dipper.
How fun!
-No kidding.
-Can we go home?
-You're annoying!
YORUICHI: Kisuke!
-Huh?
-What-- Yoruichi!
-I have something to tell you.
-Yeah, what is it?
-The intruder is a Bount.
[theme music]
KON: What do you mean,
a new type Mod-Soul?
And supposedly, they've got
all sorts of bizarre powers.
Well, I don't care.
There's no way they can
match my popularity.
URAHARA: I wouldn't
be so sure about that.
Something incredible is going
to happen in the next episode.
ICHIGO: What?
Kon disappears?
KON: Huh?
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers.
YORUICHI: Golden.
Wearing clothes
is so comfortable.
Hm?
Sui-Feng!
What are you still doing here?
I thought I told
you to go on home.
-It's just now that we're in
the World of the Living, I--
-What's wrong?
- --wanted to do
something nice for you.
So, um, I, uh-- take this!
-Chocolate?
No thanks.
-[cries]