[theme song] [foreign language]
NARRATOR: Ichigo
and his friends were
on the brink of being defeated
by the formidable Espadas when
the captains of the
13 court guard squads
arrived in Hueco Mundo.
Under the orders of
head captain Yamamoto,
the captains quickly challenged
the Espadas to battle.
Byakuya and Mayuri won
their respective fights,
but Kenpachi was still locked in
fierce combat against Nnoitra.
Nnoitra's Hierro
skin was considered
the hardest of all the
Espadas, and Kenpachi
struggled to cut through it.
However, after watching
Nnoitra dodge an attack,
Kenpachi noticed a
weakness in his defense
and fought with renewed vigor.
Nnoitra, fuming with
anger, attacked Kenpachi
with all his strength and
cut off his eye patch.
-[sigh] You fool.
You never should have
ripped off my eye patch.
After that, I can't hold back.
You look alive.
Or is it just that
you haven't died yet?
-You jackass.
Can't you see?
There's no chance I'm
going to die here.
I am strong.
I am not going to die here!
Now, bray!
Santa Teresa!
-[grunt]
[grunt]
[shout]
[grunting]
-What?
Is that really all you've got?
[grunt]
[gasp]
[cry]
-[grunt]
-[scream]
-[gasp]
-What's the matter?
Shouldn't I be dead by now?
-[grunting]
Yes.
-[groan]
-Damn it.
-This guy has six arms?
-[laughter]
It's all over, soul reaper.
-Kenpachi!
-Don't get involved!
Remember what he said.
This is Kenny's fight,
and Kenny's alone.
Sorry, Ichi, but you heard him.
No one interferes.
ORIHIME: Ichigo.
-[grunt]
-[moaning]
-Heh.
-[grunt]
-[laughter]
Now we're talking!
This is great!
We're having some fun now!
-[gasp]
-You think this fight is over?
How can it be over when I just
got this nice hole in my gut?
Hell, now it's an
even fight again!
So, where did we leave off?
Espada.
-[shout]
[shout]
-[grunt]
-[grunting]
-[gasp]
-[grunt]
-[grunting]
-[moaning]
-[scream]
Ha.
-[grunt]
-[cry]
-[grimace]
-[grunting]
-[laughter]
-[gasp]
NNOITRA (VOICEOVER):
What the hell?
[scream]
-[laughter]
NNOITRA (VOICEOVER): But
I'm the one cutting him.
He's the one who's bleeding!
-[laughter]
-[grunt]
NNOITRA (VOICEOVER):
And yet nothing
works, no matter
how much I hurt him.
-Ha ha ha!
NNOITRA (VOICEOVER): How
does he keep coming back?
I am the strongest.
The strongest!
This has gone on too long.
Hurry up and die!
-Kenpachi!
-[gasp]
-[sniggering]
-Huh.
If we keep this
up, I think there
is a chance that I'll die.
-Oh, Kenny.
No!
-I'd hate to die.
-[moan]
-Oh well, then.
Guess I have no choice.
It's been a while
since I've tried this.
But it's time for some kendo.
-Hold on. what did you say?
-Back when I joined the
13 court guard squads,
the old man made me learn kendo.
Said it might come
in handy some day.
[panting]
-No good! again!
KENPACHI (VOICEOVER):
It wasn't my cup of tea.
Kendo.
The way of the sword.
Sounded so pretentious.
I never used it.
But let me tell you.
There was one thing
I took away from it.
An important
lesson-- that a sword
becomes much more
powerful when it's
swung with both hands
instead of just one.
Heh.
-Huh?
What the hell are
you talking about?
You idiot.
Of course it does.
That should be
perfectly obvious!
KENPACHI (VOICEOVER: But you
don't know the half of it.
-Attack!
KENPACHI (VOICEOVER):
You have no idea
just how much stronger
it can make a man.
-Ha ha.
NNOITRA (VOICEOVER):
Is he giving up?
He's just standing there.
I am the strongest.
I am the strongest!
Is he giving up?
He's just standing there.
I am the strongest.
I am the strongest!
[grunting]
-[scream]
-[grunt]
-[panting]
KENPACHI: Are you still alive?
[snickering]
Well, look at you.
You're a lot tougher
than I thought.
-Damn you.
-See you around.
-What the?
Hold on!
-What do you want?
Quit bugging me.
-Where do you
think you're going?
This thing is nowhere near over.
-Are you dumb?
I believe it just ended.
And I'm not about to
finish off somebody
who can't even fight back.
-Oh, is that so?
Then I'll say it again.
This thing isn't over yet.
Because in case you
haven't noticed,
I can still fight you back.
What's wrong?
Come on.
Say something.
Or are you just too damn scared?
Answer me.
Are you scared of
me, soul reaper?
-Puh.
What a pain in the ass.
Fine, then.
Bring it on.
-[scream]
-Yeah.
NELLIEL: Why?
The annihilation of this colony
was not part of your orders.
Why did you massacre them?
-Why don't you shut up?
After all, nobody told
me not to kill them.
-Lord Aizen exact orders were
to find the Vasto Lordes.
He never authorized you
to do any mass killings.
-You know, not everyone
agrees with every order
Lord Aizen dishes out.
Those that defy us
are renegade elements.
Eliminating benefits
Lord Aizen, doesn't it?
NELLIEL: You honestly
did this for Lord Aizen?
-[snickering]
Doesn't it look that way to you?
[screaming]
[maniacal laughter]
Heh.
Besides, if I could kill
them off that easily,
they couldn't have been
ranked Vasto Lordes.
I think I was within my orders.
You're just getting
all teary-eyed
because 100 or 200 hollows
were killed, aren't you?
You're just soft.
-I suggest you think
before you speak, Nnoitra.
The only difference between
us and those hollows
is that we were lucky enough
to evolve beyond that stage.
-Oh, you disapprove?
Then come at me-- if you think
you've got a chance, that is.
-You amaze me.
Even after becoming an Espada,
you're still just a child.
-What was that?
Hey!
Get back here!
I will not lose!
There is no way I can lose!
I am-- I am--
What-- why?
Why did you save me?
-I didn't save you.
I merely stopped
your suicidal actions
so we wouldn't lose an Espada.
-Nelliel.
I truly do hate you.
But surely you must
already know that by now.
So answer me why.
Why do you keep
following me around?
-That's simple.
It's because you are
much weaker than I am.
NNOITRA (VOICEOVER):
Don't be ridiculous.
Everybody always feels
so much pity for me.
Don't they realize they're
only rubbing salt in my wounds?
I will show them no mercy.
Whether they're strong
or whether they're weak,
whether they're only a child
or some monstrous beast,
I will kill them with one
blow so that they'll never
have the strength
to pity me again.
I am--
-Nnoitra?
[theme music] [foreign language]
NNOITRA (VOICEOVER):
I was born to fight.
Being pitied by others
is a sign of weakness.
Nelliel, I'll show you that I am
stronger than you in every way.