[music playing]
NARRATOR: In order to seize
power of the Kasumioji Clan,
Gyokaku Kumoi secretly
sent assassins
to kill the clan's
princess, Rurichiyo.
Ichigo agreed to become
the princess's bodyguard
and fought to protect her.
After a fierce battle,
Ichigo defeated Hanza Nukui,
the leader of the assassins.
But Uryu and Chad
sustained serious injuries.
Princess Rurichiyo was
overwhelmed by guilt
at the suffering she had caused.
So she returned to
the Soul Society,
hoping to stop the fighting.
Rurichiyo was already aware
that Kumoi was the one targeting
her, but she returned
home to go through
with her arranged
marriage anyway.
Ichigo and the others
followed Rurichiyo
and interrupted the ceremony.
-Rurichiyo!
Let's go.
MALE VOICE: Stop right there.
MALE VOICE: Intruders!
MALE VOICE: Circle around them!
-Hey, Rurichiyo!
Rurichiyo, listen to me.
-Huh?
What?
-Rurichiyo, we've come for you.
It's me, Ichigo.
-They fell for it.
-Ru--
SUI-FENG: Don't move,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
-Captain Sui-Feng.
-What's going on?
ICHIGO: Rurichiyo!
-Stop panicking.
Calm down!
-Rurichiyo!
-Stop right there.
-Ichigo Kurosaki, what could
you possibly be thinking?
To intrude upon a ceremony
for nobles is forbidden.
-Captain Sui-Feng,
please hear me out.
There's a good reason for this.
This marriage and the
naming of the new clan lord
would not be valid if
allowed to proceed.
-Sorry.
Can you give me just a second?
-Go ahead.
-Rurichiyo, I'm
sorry-- sorry that we
made you feel alone
instead of protecting you.
We drove you into a corner.
We all know how much
you've been through,
and we came here to tell you
there's no reason that you
should have to shoulder
the entire burden yourself.
But if you've made up your
mind, then we'll support you.
-Rurichiyo.
ICHIGO: You don't have
to listen to Kumoi.
You're the true leader
of the Kasumioji Clan.
If there's anything
you can't do alone,
we'll help you-- myself, Kenryu,
Rukia, Orihime, Uryu, and Chad.
You won't be alone again.
It's up to you.
Only you can make the right
decision for yourself.
[music playing]
-I don't know what
you are talking about.
-Lady Rurichiyo?
-Lady Rurichiyo.
-You have shown
insolence towards me
and towards this ceremony.
ICHIGO: I don't understand.
You can't be serious.
-What are you waiting for?
Arrest these intruders now.
-Yes, sir.
-No further disturbances
will be tolerated
from you or from your friends.
-Hey, tie all the prisoners up.
-Yes, sir.
-Good job, Enryu.
Are you going to do it now?
-Hey, you guys, help me out.
Ah!
-I can't believe Sir
Enryu's destructive power.
All this time he was
holding back that Zanpakuto.
Just what was he waiting for?
ICHIGO: Rurichiyo!
-Ichigo.
-Rukia, where's Rurichiyo?
-I don't know.
-There you are.
Ichigo, you can't get away.
Move, Kuchiki.
-I'm not going anywhere.
-Thanks, Rukia.
-Wait.
-Rurichiyo.
There you are.
What's the matter with you?
-Unhand me.
I do not know who you are.
-Of course you know me.
Snap out of this.
Come on!
-Let go of her!
Stop hurting Rurichiyo.
-Hey, kid listen.
If you're her fiance, you should
know that she's obviously not
acting like herself.
-Huh?
-Kumoi must have done something
to make her behave like this.
-Well, I don't-- I don't
know anything about it.
-You fell for it,
lowly substitute.
-Impostor.
-Rurichiyo?
No way.
-Impostor-- what are
you talking about?
-You fool.
Do you have any idea what
you're doing, Kuchiki?
-Captain, forgive me.
I promise to explain
myself in time.
Please just let me go this once.
-I cannot.
-Damn you.
SUI-FENG: That's
far enough, Ichigo.
Hurry and go.
KUMOI: I will leave
him to you, then.
Come, it is dangerous.
-Hold it!
-You disappoint me.
I thought you were supposed
to be a lot smarter than what
you've shown me today.
I've misjudged you.
-Wait, please.
You have to listen to me.
-We've had enough talk.
-Ichigo, I'm on my way.
-You.
-Lieutenant Omaeda.
-How dare you all
treat me this way?
-There-- there's a reason.
-I don't care.
I'm gonna make you pay!
-Sir Kenryu.
-Lady Kuchiki,
now's your chance.
-Thanks.
-So, taking her place?
-Nice job.
Don't let him go, Enryu.
-Let go!
Don't you realize who I am?
-Over there.
-Hurry!
The lieutenant's in trouble.
We've got to help him!
-Bloom in glory, Benishidare.
-Listen, Sui-Feng.
That Rurichiyo was an impostor.
-What proof do you have?
-I just know.
You have to trust me, Sui-Feng.
-I've had enough
of your nonsense.
Obviously, you're not used
to fighting with hakuda.
By getting up, I assume
you want to feel more pain.
Well, then-- sting all
enemies to death, Suzumebachi.
I wanted to finish this
without releasing my zanpakuto,
but-- guess I can't.
[speaking japanese]
What now?
-Ichigo, we should
get out of here.
-Damn it.
I guess we have no choice.
-Not that way!
It's too dangerous.
This way is safer.
Hurry up.
The soul reaper's
will come soon.
-There's no sign that
Ichigo Kurosaki or Rukia
Kuchiki have left.
We think they're probably
hiding inside the palace.
-All right, then.
Gather the available men
and reorganize the squad.
Go after them.
-Right away.
-Captain, what do we
do with these two?
-We'll deal with them later.
Right now, concentrate on
finding Kurosaki and Kuchiki.
-Captain Sui-Feng,
I am going to ask
you to refrain from
pursuing them in the palace.
-How else will we find them?
-Leave that part to us.
The intruders will be forced to
flee the palace on their own.
Then all you have to do
is simply capture them
as they run outside.
-It won't work.
-Please, Captain Sui-Feng.
Surely you will
honor the request
of a high-ranking noble family.
-Hmm.
-You should be all right here.
This place is pretty safe.
Everyone has been in a panic
since you crashed the wedding
ceremony.
-So, you're Shu Kannogi, the
fiance of Lady Rurichiyo.
Why are you helping us?
-Well, it's-- because I
wanted to help Rurichiyo.
Please tell me where the
real Rurichiyo is being held.
Did anything bad happen to her?
-I know you have
questions, but calm down.
-How could I possibly calm down?
I am Rurichiyo's fiance.
I'm supposed to be the
one protecting her.
-I see.
-I heard what you said
after the ceremony.
It made me think-- just what
is my purpose for being here?
Both our families arbitrarily
agreed on our engagement.
But then I saw her.
And from the first moment I
caught a glimpse of Rurichiyo,
I've been in love with her.
-No need to bow.
You must be Shu Kannogi.
SHU KANNOGI: Even then,
I knew that Rurichiyo
was in a difficult position--
having to keep everyone happy
while trying to preside
at the same time.
Yet even though I was
right by her side,
I knew she always felt alone.
And I-- I couldn't help her.
-Don't worry.
It's still not too late.
We can protect
Rurichiyo together.
But before we do, we
have to get out of here.
-Careful.
Sui-Feng and the
others have probably
surrounded the palace
looking for us.
-You're right.
What do we do?
-Um--
-What is it?
-Just that I kind
of have an idea.
-Has there been any
word from Kumoi yet?
-No.
-Look at this place.
I mean, they may be high
and mighty aristocrats,
but their palace is obscene.
What do they need so
much land for, anyway?
-Omaeda, mind your
disrespectful tongue.
-OK.
-Now tell me what
happened to the two men
you captured earlier.
OMAEDA: They're
under strict guard.
SUI-FENG: Make sure of it.
Ichigo Kurosaki and the
others may come for them.
-What?
No way.
Not a chance with
all this security.
-Reporting.
-Hmm?
-Ichigo Kurosaki
and Rukia Kuchiki
have appeared near
the back gate.
-What?
Seize them, immediately!
-But they're holding Lord
Kannogi as a hostage.
SUI-FENG: They're what?
Stop right there, Ichigo.
You weren't satisfied with
merely crashing the wedding
ceremony, so now you're
taking a hostage, too?
-Captain Sui-Feng, this is not--
-Rukia.
I'm sorry, Sui-Feng.
Please move out of our way.
Now.
Let's go.
-Right.
-And don't try to follow us.
-Impossible.
Not Rukia and Ichigo.
-Excuse me.
Who is Ichigo Kurosaki?
-I forgot.
You've never met him,
have you Captain Amagai?
He's a human
substitute soul reaper
who we're beholden to for
helping us in the past.
-Substitute soul reaper?
I didn't realize there
was such a position.
-Kurosaki and Kuchiki
took Shu Kannogi,
son of the Kannogi clan.
Together, they escaped
to the Seireitei grounds,
where we picked up their trail.
They're good, but Squad Two
has been successfully tracking
them.
Still, considering
Ichigo Kurosaki's power,
I believe we need
reinforcements.
-In that case, it makes
sense for me to go.
Since you're all obviously
quite close to them,
it may prove difficult
for you to bring them in.
-I approve of Captain
Amagai's plan.
Deploy your men immediately
to the Sereitei.
Squads Two and
Three-- I order you
to capture the substitute
soul reaper, Ichigo Kurosaki,
and Rukia Kuchiki of Squad 13.
-Yes, sir.
-Excuse me, Head Captain.
There's one more thing.
-Yes?
-Gyokaku Kumoi, the Kasumioji
Clan's senior retainer.
He requested our
help, yet he refused
to allow us onto
the palace grounds.
He is a bit cautious when
dealing with soul reapers.
And there's another
unusual circumstance
involving Ichigo Kurosaki--
-Very well, I shall keep
all of this in mind.
-But, sir--
-That is all.
-Captain.
-Izuru, did you get word?
-Yes, sir.
Everything is ready
as you ordered.
-Substitute soul
reaper-- it may be
an uncomfortable
mission for you.
But it is all for the
Order of the Soul Society.
You understand what I'm saying?
-Yes, sir.
-All right.
Get ready to leave.
-Uh, one thing, Captain.
-Go ahead.
-About the substitute soul
reaper, Ichigo Kurosaki.
Did he really break in
on the Kasumioji Clan?
-Of course.
Didn't you get the report?
-Yes.
-Well then, what's the matter?
Go ahead, speak your mind.
-Well, you see, I'm torn, going
back and forth over what to do.
But in this case, I
believe it's my duty
to let you know what
I think, Captain.
Recently, I saw third
seat Makoto Kibune
entering and leaving
the Kasumioji grounds.
-Makoto?
-Yes, sir.
I confronted him about it.
But strangely enough, he denied
ever visiting such a place.
-What else?
-I had hesitated to tell
you any of this earlier,
but this isn't the
first time third seat
Kibune has acted suspiciously.
Once before, he tried to
kill one of his comrades.
And he's also been spotted
recording secret information
during a battle.
He seems quite sincere
on the outside,
but there's a different
side of him he rarely shows.
-I find that hard to
believe about Makoto.
I've never heard any
rumors like that before.
-It's true, Captain!
And this time there
was a disturbance right
after he visited
the Kasumioji Clan.
And All the while, he denies any
connection to the clan at all.
There must be something--
-It's too soon to
jump to conclusions.
Even if Makoto is somehow
connected to the Kasumioji
Clan, it would be
unfair to convict him
on hearsay and speculation.
-Yes, sir.
-Then again, with all
that's happened and now this
on top of it, he
can't complain if we
suspect him of wrongdoing.
-Captain--
-Izuru, did you discuss
this with anyone else?
-No, sir, not a single person.
-My gut is telling me something.
I'm afraid there may be
much more to this incident
than we think.
-And what would that be?
-I don't know yet.
In any case, just keep an
eye on Makoto's actions.
If anything happens,
let me know immediately.
Understand?
-Yes, sir.
AMAGAI: First, we
capture Ichigo Kurosaki.
Then we'll deal with
everything else.
[music playing]
-Isn't there an easy way to
capture the substitute soul
reaper and the others?
-Why not put a
bounty on their heads
as well as a reward
for information?
-Good idea.
I'll make arrangements
right away.
By the way, what's the
reward going to be?
-Whatever you can afford.
-Huh?