[Kon]
I said wait up! Hey!
Come on, where are
you going, anyway?!
In case you didn't notice,
I'm talking to you!
Will you wait up a sec--
Ow!
That hurt, lady!
Why did you stop
so suddenly?!
I don't know.
Huh?
Where am I supposed to go?
What are you
talking about?!
You mean you've been
walking around without any
idea where you're going?!
Aah!
(Small effort as she hits Kon
with a rock)
You're not supposed to throw
rocks at people!
Oof!
Leave me alone. pervert.
I keep telling you, lady,
I am not a pervert!
I do have...
a place to go.
Huh?
I just can't remember...
where it is.
Wh--? Wha?!
But... Wait!
[choked]
I can see now that I was right.
There's a certain majestic
quality to your skin.
I wanted to try it
before this, but I
didn't want to damage my
own body in the process.
I'm so glad you
became available for
the experiment.
Looks like their battle's
about over as well.
Hah. What a bust.
I thought you'd put up
more of a fight.
Egh... Damn you!
What do you think?
Should we finish
them off?
Might as well,
they're done anyway.
[gasping breath]
Who was that?!
Are you people... Reigai?
Oh! So you know
about us, do ya?
Don't move!
Like hell!
Rgh!
Forget about it, Ikkaku.
There's no point wasting
our time, fighting these
weaklings anymore.
We need to start looking
for Nozomi Kujo.
Heh! I guess you're right.
Hey!
[gasp]
Orihime, what is it?
The battles seem
to have ended.
Can you tell
what happened?
I'm not sure. The Spiritual
Pressures remaining are
the weak ones.
And I think
Uryu's there too.
Are you saying that the real
Ikakku and the other Soul
Reapers have been defeated?
[Chad]
If they were, I'm sure
Uryu is probably attending
to them right now.
Once I return and I
have retrieved Nozomi,
not only the Soul Society,
but also the World of the
Living, will be forced to
exist under my control.
Someday quite soon,
we will meet again.
There's no way I'll ever
allow his plan to succeed!
To start with, we
have to find Nozomi,
and fast!
Mm.
[gasp]
What is that?
Something wrong?
There's another
Spiritual Pressure.
More of them?
Oh, great,
who is it now?
I see. So, it's you, Izuru.
I assume you're here to
fight me?
I don't really want to,
but given the situation,
I don't have much choice.
Huh! Don't you remember,
you've lost to me once already.
I remember it very well,
but this will be different.
Uh?
You see, I'm not the same person
you fought back then.
Literally.
Don't expect the same
results this go-around.
Just as I remembered.
You're very good.
You don't seem any different
than you were before.
Hm. Now naise your head.
Wabisuke!
[gasp]
I assume you're familiar,
of course, with the power
of my Zanpakuto, Wabisuke?
As I recall, it doubles the
weight of whatever it strikes.
That is correct. Eventually,
the opponent, unable to bear
the weight, ends up
collapsing on the ground.
With his head bowed down,
as if in penitence.
That's why it's called
'Wabisuke'. I get it.
[gasp]
I think you've forgotten
something. My Zanpakuto isn't
affected by yours.
No matter how many times
you strike it, the weight
stays the same!
Now growl... Hainek--
Egh...
[clang!]
How were you able to do that?
Easy.
How many times did you block me?
Three times! There's no
way it could become that
heavy from three strikes!
Heh.
When Kageroza created us,
he improved our powers.
The original Zanpakuto doubled
the opponent's weight.
But with Kageroza's technical
expertise, he was able to
vastly increase its capacity.
This Zanpakuto can
increase the weight...
... by as much as tenfold.
By... tenfold?
In other words, if you took
three strikes, your weapon
now weighs one thousand
times its original weight.
Which makes it essentially
useless, as you now know!
There's no escape!
Waagh!
Hado Number Thirty One!
[breath] For Izuru's
impostor, you're strong.
An impostor, you said?
You heard me!
That's interesting.
We possess the same memories as
the originals, and what's more,
our powers are much greater.
Since we 'impostors' are
superior to the originals,
is it really fair,
... to dismiss us as nothing
more than 'phonies'?
I think we should be
considered the embodiment
of these characters, not
the so-called 'originals'.
I don't know how you feel,
and I don't really care.
I know this.
In the final assessment,
only the superior will survive.
[gasp]
Game over. This will be
a fitting end for you.
Oh really? I'm not sure you have
the strength to pull this off.
Ugh! Say your goodbyes,
Lieutenant Matsumoto!
Huh? What the hell... ?!
Hmpf. You're a dummy.
A rod?!
Mm-hm!
Oh no!
[CLANG]
Dammit!
Now growl... Haineko!
Huh? Ah!
Auggh!
[wet cough]
Damn you...
[wooden clattering]
The Spiritual Pressure from
that direction disappeared!
But now, one has
shown up even closer.
Hm? Who's there?!
Are you... my Reigai?!
You really do look like me!
It's like looking straight
into a mirror. Very creepy.
Oh yeah? Tell me about it!
It's not a fun feeling,
that's for sure.
Yeah, you're right
about that!
One Rukia Kuchiki is
more than enough!
I have to take you out!
You're welcome to try!
Prepare to die!
Hyaa!
Yaaaah!
[Shunsui]
[humming]
[Jushiro]
What do you mean,
Shunsui is a material witness?
There has to be some mistake!
Release him immediately!
[Central 46]
Not gonna happen!
Give me a reason!
Squad Eight Captain Shunsui
Kyoraku was caught red-handed,
altering Precipice World
traffic records.
That is a Class
One felony!
It is also sufficient evidence
to regard him as a suspect in
other acts of sabotage!
By being able to control the
Precipice World, he can cut
the Soul Society off from
the World of the Living!
If that were to happen,
the consequences would
be disastrous!
But Shunsui has no motive
to do such a thing!
We don't know what
his motive might be.
That's why we've
detained him.
But I don't---
Captain Ukitake!
Let me remind you that
decisions of the Central
Forty-Six are absolute!
Once a determination
has been made in a
particular inquiry,
you should be aware
that even captains are not
allowed to dispute it.
You will now leave
this chamber.
Tch!
The Central Forty-Six are a
bunch of pig-headed idiots!
[Unohana]
You can't blame them,
you know.
Huh?
The evidence is there,
in plain sight.
As a result, there's no
reason for the Central
Forty-Six to listen to you.
Captain Unohana, I'm positive
this incident is a conspiracy,
arranged by someone.
Yes. And on the surface at
least, it appears to be a very
well-conceived operation.
Any idea who might
be behind it?
Not yet. We've just
begun to look.
It appears to me,
that we're up against
someone of great cunning,
who won't give himself
away very easily.
But be assured, we will
find him, eventually.
I understand. However, I may
conduct my own investigation.
If you do so, captain,
I urge you to be very
careful.
[Unohana]
We must trust no one
but ourselves.
And even taking precautions,
it may already be too late.
She's not here.
Where could she
have possibly gone?
I don't understand.
Why does Nozomi keep
trying to run away?
Do you think it's because she
feels she can't rely on us?
Or is it something else?
Maybe she doesn't want to
cause us trouble.
Maybe it's just to escape...
you know, from the enemy.
Uh!
That's what I
think, anyway.
What other reason would she
have to come all the way to
the World of the Living?
She knows a
place to hide.
Maybe, but where?
Hmm.
[Kon]
Come on, Nozomi!
Enough is enough!
What's gonna happen if you
get caught again by the
guys who are after you?!
If you stay with Ichigo and
the others, at least you know
you'll be protected! Hey!
Why would they protect me?
What do you mean?
What kind of
question is that?
Would they be doing it
for the Soul Society?
Or the World of the Living?
None of that!
You don't understand anything,
and on top of that, you're in a
big load of trouble!
Yeah, walk away!
I don't care what
happens to you anymore!
That's it! I'm
completely through
with you! Hmpf!
Aren't you even the
least bit upset?!
[gasp]
What are you doing?!
We're going back!
Even if I have to
drag you there!
Get off me!
No way!
I'm dragging you back!
You forced me into this!
Do you give up yet?!
You're nuts! Quit
sneaking a peek up my
skirt! And let go!
You have to go back to Ichigo!
He's the only one who can
protect you!
That won't be necessary.
Huh?
I'll fix things so he
doesn't need to protect me.
What are you talking about?
That's why I came here,
to Karakura Town...
Nice move. You're not too bad,
for an impostor.
I must say, it's an honor to
be praised by the original.
But I think you'll find,
I'm even better than you think!
This is crazy!
She does seem to have greater
fighting ability than I do!
How am I going to be able
to overcome her advantage?
Lieutenant Kurotsuchi?
Rukia Kuchki.
You're a Reigai, too?!
Augh!
They're teaming up
to finish me off!
Lieutenant Kurotsuchi
has the speed.
I don't have a chance against
the two of them together!
[Reigai Rukia]
You're not getting
away from us!
That's fine! I wasn't
planning on running off!
Her reactions are so fast!
I'm in trouble if I don't
find some way to distract her!
(Effort as she lands, followed
by startled breath as she turns)
(Pain reax as she gets kicked by
the real Nemu, followed by
efforts as she flips and lands)
Huh?
Time to end this!
Dance! Sodenoshirayuki!
Somenomai! Tsukishiro!
Somenomai--
Too slow!
Haugh!
Master... Mayuri.
[clatter]
Hm?
This must be their essence.
Huh?
Let that be a lesson
to you, Reigai!
Are you all right?
Lieutenant Kurotsuchi!
Rukia!
Lieutenant
Matsumoto!
So, you were able
to destroy her?
Yes.
Mm.
[Kon]
Hey, give it up already!
I'm not letting go!
Hope you have a strong grip.
Ow!
Gaaah! My eye is hanging by
a thread! I have to get to
a sewing machine! Huh?
What's that look about?
I know now,
where I have to go.
Really?! Is it
someplace close by?
I hope we can get there
by walking! I don't have
a driver's license!
And once you've visited the
place, we can both hurry
back to Ichigo! Right?
Eagh!
Easy with that ear!
I have no way to replace
it if you tear it off!
I must find the gate.
Which gate? The shrine
gate right here?
No, it's not this one.
Is there a place somewhere
in town that has a lot of
these gates, all in a row?
Somewhere that has a
lot of... these gates...
Ah - haaa!
There is such a place!
It's a shrine in
the mountains!
I've been there before!
Show me how to get there.
Ah ha ha ha! You
finally decided you
need me, right?!
If you were smart, you
would have accepted my
help from the beginning,
instead of--!
Ow!
Stop doing that! It hurts!
Let's get moving!
I don't have to take
orders from you!
It's this way.
[humming]
[man gets punched]
Huhh?
About time you showed up.
You here to bust me out?
We're going to see
Master Genryusai.
We need to report what's
going on and get his input.
I guess. They certainly
don't make these cells very
comfortable for sleeping.
This place was literally
a pain in my butt.
This is no time for jokes.
We have to get you out of
here, right now.
Here's your sword.
Ah yes. Just the
thing I needed.
[Rukia]
I'm not sensing any more
enemies in the vicinity.
We'd better go back and join
the search for Nozomi Kujo.
That's a good idea.
Mm.
I still can't sense the
girl's Spiritual Pressure.
Any ideas on where
we should start?
No, sorry.
You're not going anywhere.
[gasp]
Shunsui...?
Sorry about this.
Augh!
Can't believe you fooled us.
What's the
matter?!
That was so easy.
Almost too easy.
Stop, Shunsui.
Huh?
That's not the job
we're here for.
We have to go. We have other
matters to attend to.
[Orihime]
Ichigo! I've come up with a
plan to get Nozomi's attention!
[Ichigo]
What is it?!
[Orihime]
First we get a cat. Then we
place it here, and then...
[Chad]
[chuckles] Kitty, aww!
Kitty! He he he he!
That's odd. I thought
for sure Nozomi would
go for the cat.
[Ichigo]
Okay, that's it.
I'm going home!