The Zanpakuto. Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined by
its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper and
dies with its Soul
Reaper.
That is the existence of
a Zanpakuto.
So the only defense left
for you is running away?!
You run away and hide...
Then attack me from the
shadows? You fight just
as dirty as you look!
You think I care how you
fight!?
I am a Zanpakuto whose
sole aim is to harvest
as many lives as I can.
I have no interest
in how my Master fights!
I just realized something.
I don't like you.
That's fine with me...
I feel the same...
Using flash step to avoid
a direct hit.
What a complete idiot.
You wouldn't be in pain
if you'd just died.
All the same to me
because it's over!
Who the hell are you?
A Zanpakuto slaying his
own master. I
didn't think you could
have such poor taste.
Izuru?
You continue to amuse
me, Ichigo Kurosaki.
When I began this
mission, I never expected
to become so invested in
a single Soul Reaper.
Well for a Zanpakuto you
sure talk an awful lot.
Is there ever a point to
your speeches?
You know what, I've had
enough of this small talk!
It's time to settle this!
Still workin' for
him, huh, Zangetsu?
I'm going to fight to get
you back. Even if it means
I have to fight you.
I've made my decision.
So what are you going to
do, Zangetsu?
I have to find out...
Between the two of us,
which one is truly the
strongest?
If it means I get my
answer, I am more than
willing to cross blades
with you.
Without Zangetsu's power
fueling your Zanpakuto,
you won't be able to
fight as hard as you
normally can.
So I guess I will lend
you mine for the time
being.
However, in exchange,
you won't be able to
use my power to its
fullest extent either.
Bankai!
Snake. Be careful.
Yeah I know.
Did something about him
change?
Sure seems so.
I have had enough of this!
Zanpakuto are supposed to
be used by their masters!
That's the way it is!
What did you just say?!
What kind of arrogant
garbage is that?
Wait. That's a pretty
bold thing to say.
I suppose that means you've
finally found the will to
take us on!
Oh I have more than will.
I am going to destroy you
with everything I've got!
Hm! Don't get ahead
of yourself, Renji.
That's right! You better
watch your mouth!
Huh?
If you think you can beat
us with just the will to
fight, you've got another
thing coming.
Yeah! No matter what you
try, we're still
stronger!
Care for a taste of it?
Of what?
Your own blade, of
course.
Izuru. What now?
Shuhei. Stay still and
try not to talk too much.
Those injuries look pretty
bad.
Not gonna happen.
I can't just sit here
and let you take care of
my problem.
Believe me, I wouldn't
have planned it this way
either.
But allowing a lieutenant
to die before we can figure
out how to resolve this
problem would be far worse.
I'm not just here to help
you.
Remember, we have a
mission to put down the
Zanpakuto rebellion, at
any cost!
Izuru.
Another idiot to kill?
Well, that's just
fine by me. I don't
really give a damn which
one of you wants to die first.
After all, my desire is
to reap as many lives as
possible.
Really aiming high,
aren't you?
I might as well take full
advantage of my freedom!
Too slow!
Just waiting on you.
Bakudo Number
Thirty-Seven,
Tsuriboshi!
What the hell is this?!
Here I come, Ichigo.
Getsuga tensho!
Dammit!
So much strength. That
was too close.
Have I been able to exert
that much power?
Get up, Ichigo. I am
not finished.
All right then. If
that's what you want!
Bankai!
I am sorry, Ichigo.
Without my power, you
will not be able to use
your Bankai.
I can see that.
Getsuga tensho.
How am I gonna stand a
chance against him
without using my Bankai?
I can lend you my power.
But you won't be able
to use your mask.
Getsuga tensho!
Not bad!
You've got more fight
in you than I thought.
What are you, dense or
something? I've been
training my entire life!
We have no choice.
Let's do it.
Bankai!
Renji, you look
surprised. We are
Zanpakuto, after all.
Surely, you must have
known we were capable of
this.
Hikotsu Taiho!
Hey Old Man. You said
you wanted to find out
which one of us was
stronger.
Is it really that
important to you?
Why do you ask?
Because if it is, then
severing our bond is not
your main goal.
My only goal was to make
you more powerful. You
have surpassed my
expectations.
There is nothing left
for me to teach.
Whether or not you have the
strength to defeat me in
combat is up to you.
And the cold truth is,
even if you were to fall
to my blade, I would be
content with the outcome.
Is that so?
It is.
Okay then.
So in order to regain
your power, I have to give
this fight everything I have
inside me
and prove my strength.
With or without you.
It is as you say. Do
not hold back, hit me
with all you've got,
Ichigo!
I'm much more difficult
to handle than you might
think!
Fine. Let's go!
Our Bankai is nothing
like the one you know.
Ours has no blind spots!
The game is over. No
matter what you do, your
Shikai cannot match my
Bankai!
Now do you understand?
You will never defeat us.
Shut your mouth!
Damn it. She's right.
My Shikai can't hold up
against their Bankai.
They're reading every
one of my moves before I
make them.
I guess it makes sense.
After all, more than
anyone, they know my
usual pattern of attack.
What the hell am I going
to do?
Heh!
Don't bother trying to
think your way out of this.
Of all your weaknesses, Renji,
your lack of intelligence
might just be the most
pitiful one of all.
My weakness?
It's worth a shot.
What now, Monkey?
He probably realizes that
it's pointless to continue
fighting like this.
Bakudo Number Four!
Hainawa!
Hm?
It's not over yet!
Ugh, he never learns.
This is pathetic, Renji.
I'm awful at Kido...
which is why they'd never
expect me to use it.
Hado Number Thirty-One!
Shakkaho!
Someone's getting
creative. So this is
what you were planning.
Too bad your level of
Kido is so weak.
Not quite.
And here comes some
more!!
What're you doing?!
Your Kido is dangerous to
everyone, including you!
So you're trying out a
new technique, huh? There's
no way you can beat us with
that sad Kido of yours!
Got it! Ha-ha!
What?!
It looks like that sword
is really worthless now!
Goodbye!!
Not just yet!
Shakkaho!
Oh please!
What?!
What happened?!
Higa zekko!
He blocked me again?
I've told you before,
Ichigo.
You have to strike at me
with everything you've got!
Because otherwise, you have
no prayer against me!
Don't you think I know
that?
You know what? I'm
getting the hang of
it now!
I've grown quite tired
of this little skirmish.
Let's settle this, Ichigo.
Ready when you are.
Very well. Getsuga!
Tensho!
Getsuga tensho!
Well! It's not like I
can let my host die, now
can I?
Impossible! He isn't even
using his Bankai. Yet
this power.
You're next, Muramasa!
Hmph.
Ichigo Kurosaki, didn't
you have any misgivings about
destroying your own Zanpakuto?
Not one.
What?
I know Zangetsu better
than anyone.
I knew he wouldn't run away
from me. That he would take
my attack head on. And that's
why...
There was no way I could
run from a battle and
turn my back on him!
Our bond is our strength!
I see.
What's happening?
Your bond is the source
of your strength.
Fascinating.
It seems I've toyed with
you for too long. It is
best that I move on.
Hey, what are
you doing?!
Til we meet again,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
You all right Zangetsu?
Yes.
I will be all right now.
His mind control is broken.
Mind control?
It's true. I may have some
weaknesses, but as long as I
continue to strive for
greatness,
I think I'll
become stronger.
No. I know I will!
Well, isn't he full of
himself!?
That last hit kinda
stung, didn't it snake?
You're actually pretty
good, Renji!
You guys...
We came to our senses.
It's time we ended this
ridiculous rebellion.
Hm? Wait, what do you
mean?
Muramasa. It appears
he was able to control the
Zanpakuto by somehow awakening
our darkest instincts
and bringing them to
the surface of our minds.
Hold on, are you saying
that all the other Zanpakuto
are under his control?
I can't be sure, but
it's very likely.
Ichigo. This time it was
you who saved me.
I can't take all the
credit.
Well, what will you do
now?
Isn't it obvious?
I'll find Muramasa.
And stop him.
I see.
Ichigo Kurosaki. He
might be the one.
Hey, it's thanks to me
you won this battle! So
you at least have to hear
out my request!
What do you want?
I demand a house with a
garden and a garage built
inside your inner world!
I wouldn't mind having
a dog or a cat.
And it better be a
purebred!