I'll have you out of
there in no time!
So far, so good...
Just a little
bit more...
Kon!
Huh?!
Ahhh!
[gasping]
Kon? Kon!
Kon!
What are you doing?!
[gasping]
No, stop it! Stop!
[grunting]
Kon...
[growling]
Hado Number Thirty-One!
Shakkaho!
[growling]
Get back!
[gasping]
[growling]
[roaring]
What a pitiful creature.
Hmmm...
[gasping]
Tessai, have you heard
anything from Kisuke, yet?
No-No word from him yet.
The fact that we
haven't heard from
them isn't good.
Hmm.
If you're all so
worried-why not go
check it out?
Ikkaku! Have you
completely recovered?!
Ha! An injury as minor as
this doesn't even phase
me!
So c'mon, how about it,
Renji?
I don't know, man.
I say just go for it!
[gasping]
When we were
investigating earlier, we
were able to confirm
several captain-level
Spiritual Pressures
inside the Seireitei.
So my Brother and
the others are alive?
[gasping]
The Boss knew the
situation might change
and left us instructions
to be flexible in our
response. From what I
know-I'd say now is the
best time to attack.
Renji.
Right! Guess we're
going to the Soul
Society!
[growling]
The only thing that's
left for you, is
self-destruction.
Well at least I won't
have to do it myself this
time.
[snarling]
[gasping]
Who is this guy? Is
he Nozomi? No, is this
Kageroza?
[struggling]
[screaming]
[roaring]
[grunting]
Just between you and me,
fighting with brute force
really isn't my style.
Oh, I know. That's why
it makes even more sense
to engage you in a battle
that relies on brute force.
[grunting]
Unlike you who slacked
off during his training,
I didn't.
In fact, I used my time
here to make my skills
even sharper.
[yelling]
[gasping]
Bankai! Kokujo Tengen
Myo-oh!!
[yelling]
Huh!
Ahhhhhhhh!
What do you think?
I'd say we have a
serious problem.
They act like they're
fighting us one-on-one,
but whenever they see an
opening, they're
attacking whoever they
can...
I know. That gives them
a strategic and numerical
advantage.
Yeah. We'd better start
changing that by taking
'em out one by one.
Huh?!
[yelling]
[grunting]
Both of them are such
barbarians.
I'd like to see those
future guinea pigs left
in as pristine condition
as possible.
Well, well!... And
you're going to just
watch it all from your
lofty perch? How can a
person that's like you
be a captain of the
Thirteen Court Guard
Squads?
How amusing. A mod soul
with a sense of humor, just
like its original. I guess
you'd be perfect.
Oh? Perfect for
what, now?
I've decided that it would
be quite a pleasure to dissect
the Reigai of the irritating
Squad Four Captain.
Claw out!
Ashisogijizo!!
Minazuki.
[gasping]
Bakudo Number
Sixty-Three. Sajosabaku!
[grunting]
Heh.
That will never work on
me. Huh?!
What the hell?!
[laughing]
[grunting]
Impossible!...
[groaning]
[laughing]
Captain Kurotsuchi!
Bankai.
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
[gasping]
[chuckling]
It won't be long.
[gasping]
[snickering]
Even if your hollowfied
state, you continue to
pursue me.
[growling and roaring]
Bakudo Number
Thirty! Shitotsusansen.
[roaring]
I don't have any more
time to waste dealing
with the likes of you.
[growling]
[roaring]
Hado Number
Fifty-Eight! Tenran!!
Bakudo Number
Nintey-Nine, Kin!!
[growling]
As I said... I am done
with wasting any more
time or energy by
spending it with you!
That Spiritual Pressure!
It appears that Kageroza
has at last achieved full
strength.
Well, finally. That's a
game-changing turn in
this battle.
Yes, victory is ours
now...
Bakudo Number Four,
Hainawa!!
Whoa! Gotta say, that's
a pretty sneaky move for
you.
Catching you off-guard
isn't going to be easy
if you can see it
coming.
In that case, I guess
I'll have to block your
view!
Bakudo Number
Thirty-Seven, Tsuriboshi.
You think that's
gonna stop me?
Bakudo Number
Sixty-Three, Sajosabaku!
Gochu Tekkan!!
[gasping]
Ya missed me!
Firing bursts of
techniques ends up
leaving you wide open.
Hado Number
Eighty-Eight. Hiryu
Gekizoku Shinten Raiho!!
Bakudo Number Eighty-One,
Danku!
Didn't I tell you I'd
block your view?
[gasping]
You really thought I
wouldn't anticipate
what you'd try for your
next attack?
Hado Number
Thirty-Two. Oukasen!
[lightly growling]
I pity you.
Unable to return to being
a Soul Reaper, but also
unable to become a full
Hollow.
You're now the polar
opposite of the complete
being that I have
become.
Raiku.
[weakly breathing]
Now, farewell, Substitute
Soul Reaper.
[gasping]
What's this?
Ichigo!
[yelling]
[grunting]
Roar! Zabimaru!!
Wait a sec, is that guy
supposed to be Kageroza?
Yeah, it looks like it.
Where's Nozomi?
Damn it, guess we
got here too late!
Heh. So it's you
pests again.
You must know by now that
with my advanced powers,
even all of you combined
are no match for me.
So... why
are you here?
Why do you think?
We've come here to
rescue our friends.
Friends?
[laughing]
Loneliness is
not a sin.
No matter the
circumstances...
Yessir!
I do not need
help from others.
Other people only get in
the way.
To help... is
merely to pity.
It is an act of jealousy
towards the strong. An
insult to a noble spirit.
To be alone is to be a
selected one. A privilege
reserved for a superior
soul.
Friends, you
say?....
Huh!
[laughing]
If your lives are of so little
value to you, that you'd
sacrifice yourself for someone
else without hesitation...
Then you will die here!
[gasping]
[grunting]
This ends now!!
What?!
Rangiku!
We've come here to
help you out, Captain.
No one here asked for
your help. Buuuuttt...
All these small fry are
making it too hard for me
to concentrate on my fight.
You guys handle
the cleanup.
Yes, sir!...With
pleasure!
[gasping]
[grunting]
Uryu!
His Zanpakuto takes
slices of space and
recreates them.
The last time we fought I
thought he was manipulating
time, but that's not what
he does.
He uses his Zanpakuto to
recreate a space that
didn't exist before.
Then he shifts his
location to that space in
an instant. Isn't that
right?
Oh? It seems I've
underestimated your
deductive skills,
Quincy.
As a reward, allow me to
show you my true power!
Oh, no you won't!
Roar! Zabimaru!
Seethe, Sumitsukigasa!
[screaming]
What was that?
You should be paying
attention!
Cry, Benihime!
[grunting]
This will end it!
Renji!!
[coughing]
[grunting]
I've got him!
What the--?!
Heh. Sumitsukigasa!
[yelling]
[screaming]
[groaning]
W-What just happened?
You just experienced the
true power of my
Zanpakuto, Sumitsukigasa.
True power?
Duplicating an
adversary's attack and
reproducing it exactly,
is the power of Raiku.
And Nozomi's
Arazomeshigure allowed
her to absorb an
adversary's Spirit
Energy and convert it
into her own power.
But Sumitsukigasa
possesses the power of
both of them.
Raiku came with the risk
of being vulnerable when
reproducing an
adversary's attack, as
well as consuming a great
deal of my Spirit
Energy.
But now that I possess
the power of
Arazomeshigure, my
problem is solved. Now I
am able to absorb any
attack and continue to
counterattack
indefinitely.
That's absurd. Can
that even be done?
I assure you it can be
done. In my present fused
state, I am both Kageroza
Inaba and Nozomi Kujo.
It's only natural that
I have access to her
Zanpakuto power.
Nozomi.
I don't care what you
possess-I'll crush that
power of yours right now!
Renji, don't do it!
Bankai! Hihio
Zabimaru!!
What a fool.
[yelling]
Sumitsukigasa.
Renji!!
If we attack him like
Renji did, the force will
be absorbed and directed
back at us. So what can we do?
Okay, since that's the
case... We have to mount
an attack that he can't
absorb.
[grunting]
Huh?
Tetsuzaemon! Don't get
distracted by other opponents.
Concentrate only on the
opponent that you are fighting!
I'll do that sir!
Those damn Reigai.
They've turned this
into a brawl, attacking
at random and effectively
exploiting our unguarded
positions.
The pride of the
Originals, who prefer
fighting one-on-one, isn't
working to our advantage.
I'd say at this
rate--
Heh.
Damn it!
Licht Regen!
Tsuginomai, Hakuren!
Hihio Zabimaru!!
Your efforts are in vain!
I will eliminate you one
by one so that you won't
be able to coordinate
your attacks.
[grunting]
Now Rukia, do it!!
Hakuren!!
Don't mess with me!
What?!
Ahh!
[grunting]
Too slow!
[yelling]
[screaming]
Now that I am one with
Nozomi, my power is far
beyond all of yours.
Your clumsy attempts at
trickery will have no
effect.
Hm!?
I see So you were after
Nozomi just to get this
power.
Yes. This is the full,
original power that my
Zanpakuto possessed.
But my original frail
body was too weak to
wield it at its full
strength.
That was always my true
objective for becoming a
Reigai.
It was the only
way to be able to fully
control this Zanpakuto.
I expect you're now
planning to use your
newly acquired power to
rule the Soul Society.
Rule? Heh. How could you
possibly think that's what
I really want?
[gasping]
It's not?!
My objective is to
destroy the Soul Society.
Iro Oni. White!
That is why... Time is of
the essence...
[grunting]
Now die.
[gasping]
Ichigo!!!!
Captain! If you keep on
using your Bankai, our
squad's repair budget
will run out!
Don't let it bother
you, Tetsuzaemon.
But your Bankai draws the
most attention! That's the
reason the other squads are
going to blame everything on us!
You mean, all of this?!
Yes, sir.