[theme music playing]
URYU (OFFSCREEN):
When are you going
to stop and get
some sleep, Orihime?
You need to rest.
-I will.
Just a little while longer.
-So is Tsubaki recovering?
-Not yet.
I'm afraid it's
worse than I thought.
Tsubaki!
Not this time!
Koten Zanshun, I reject!
Tsubaki!
-You stupid girl!
What were you thinking,
hesitating like that?
-Tsubaki, no!
I guess my will
wasn't strong enough.
-It's OK.
Don't worry, Orihime.
It just requires a certain
knack to heal one of our own.
But it'll be all right.
-I'm sorry.
-Don't look so sad, Orihime.
You still have your
shielding and healing powers.
Don't forget that.
-That's correct.
And not only that.
You need to stay strong,
because any doubt that
resides in your heart has
a direct negative influence
on our powers as well.
-Oh, but I--
-We just need to practice
more, and pretty soon you'll
be able to skip saying the
whole kotodama spirit chant
and just summon each of us
by using the attack names.
-If you can learn
to do that, we'll
all be better able to protect
you by reacting much quicker.
-Oh-- OK.
What is it?
-Just you wait.
I'll be well again in no time.
-OK.
URYU (OFFSCREEN): Are
you ready, Orihime?
ORIHIME (VOICEOVER): Yes.
Let's go.
[music playing]
URYU (VOICEOVER):
Orihime loosing
her attack powers may actually
turn out to be a good thing.
Having spent these
last few days with her,
I've learned that she's
really not suited for combat.
He just doesn't have it
in her to hurt anybody,
even if it's the enemy.
People like her shouldn't fight.
Battles aren't good for
her or her little friends,
and her allies, too.
MAKIZO (OFFSCREEN): Hey!
Hold it there, you two!
Just let me get a look at you.
What are you doing in this area?
What squad are you with, anyway?
-Well, we're--
-We're with Squad 11.
-Hmm?
Well, what do you know?
I'm in Squad 11, too.
But here all this time,
I never had any idea
that in a squad that
specializes in combat,
we had moron's stupid
enough to walk around
without carrying Zanpakuto!
URYU (VOICEOVER): That's
what I was afraid of.
Each squad has distinct
characteristics.
-Hmm?
Hey, this is Squad 12's emblem.
You're not one of ours.
You don't even know
this stuff, do you?
No more lies.
Who are you two?
URYU (VOICEOVER): Damn.
I wanted to avoid fight, but
this guy leaves me no choice.
-Ooooh!
Huhhhhh!
-Well, it looks like we
came along just in time.
MAN (OFFSCREEN): Are you two OK?
Uh-huh.
-Some nerve this guy has,
questioning his own comrades,
huh?
-Not to mention
the jerk is drunk.
-Thank you very
much for helping us.
-Stop.
What did you expect?
It's the least we could do for
our fellow Squad 12 members.
-And these Squad 11
bullies are always
looking for any excuse they can
find to give us a hard time.
Idiots!
Forgetting your sword
when you're in a rush
is no big deal.
Come on, let's go.
MAN (OFFSCREEN): Yeah, we'll
walk you back to the barracks.
URYU (VOICEOVER): Wait a second.
Something's not right here.
Why would these guys go out
of their way to help us?
Even though the big guy was
drunk, his suspicions about us
were perfectly logical.
Our clothes don't
match our story,
yet these four weren't
suspicious at all.
Orihime, get away
from those guys now!
[explosion]
[screams]
-Captain, this isn't what
you said was going to happen!
You said-- you said we were
just supposed to talk to them!
You told us to bring them
back to the barracks!
-Oh, no, no.
Once the bombs
have been released,
they are not ever
supposed to return.
[explosion and screams]
A shield?
-Thank you, Uryu.
I didn't see that coming at all.
If you hadn't warned me--
-Don't thank me.
We survived because you
were able to summon them
without calling
their names, Orihime.
-What about the
four that helped us?
-I'm sorry, but
they didn't make it.
But that's not something
you should feel any guilt
or responsibility for, Orihime.
The one who bears that
responsibility is right there!
-Oh, I have not seen
this technique before.
This shield of yours, it's the
work of the girl behind you,
I assume.
-I've not about to answer that.
-How interesting.
There may be something
I can learn from you.
I'll make you an offer, woman.
Why don't you come work for
me as my research subject?
-That's ridiculous.
I told you already we
have nothing to say you!
-You needn't worry.
Rest assured, I take
good care of my subjects,
and I'm always very
"gentle" with the ladies.
[crying]
MAKIZO (VOICEOVER):
Girl's crying.
But why?
Could she be crying out of fear?
No.
ORIHIME (VOICEOVER): Look out!
MAKIZO (VOICEOVER):
If it was fear,
then she wouldn't
have risked her life
to save me from the explosion.
What is it, then?
Is she crying for the
four who just died?
And why did she save
me in the first place?
I'm the enemy, after all.
Why show me any mercy?
I don't get it.
I just don't get it.
-So, then, how about
if I guarantee you
my best working
conditions, woman?
I'll limit experimental drug
therapies to eight times a day
and mechanical experimentations
to five hours a day.
I'll even do my
utmost to refrain
from performing surgeries
which may be life-threatening.
How about it?
Rather generous terms for a
mere experimental subject,
wouldn't you agree?
[quincy bow sound]
-Hmm?
KUROTSUCHI (VOICEOVER):
He's first.
Well, a Quincy, eh?
Such a rarity these days.
In fact, it's been years since
I've seen a live specimen.
But I'm sorry to disappoint you.
I long ago finished researching
your pathetic species.
I'm no longer interested
in dealing with your kind,
so just get out of my way.
-Finished researching?
What do you mean by that?
Just who the hell are you?
-You don't know?
What do you Ryoka do, just
storm into the enemy's base
without doing any research into
who it is you're attacking?
How very careless of you.
I would think you would
at least commit to memory
the names of the 13 Captains!
I'm the Captain of Squad 12, as
well as the second generation
Chief of Research and
Development, Mayuri Kurotsuchi!
You don't need to remember
that, though, because soon
you will no longer
know anything.
-[inaudible] Orihime!
Run, get out of here.
-No!
I'm staying!
I want to fight, too!
That
-That's out of the question.
Hey, you Squad 11 guy.
Take the girl with you and go!
-I don't take orders from you.
I'm getting out of here!
URYU (OFFSCREEN): Not
without the girl, you're not.
Not unless you want
an arrow in the back.
And if you don't hurry
up and take her now,
you'll die here, caught
in the crossfire.
-But I--
-Do it!
-Damn it.
Let's go, missy.
You're coming with me.
-Did I give you
permission to run away?
[music playing]
-Did I give you permission
to try and stop them?
-My, my.
I've already told you I
have no interest in you.
-Put me down!
-Get your hand out of
my face, you crazy girl!
-No!
-Can't you you see that I'm
trying to rescue you here?
I'd think you'd be a little
more thankful that I,
Makizo Aramaki of Squad 11
am the kind of chivalrous man
that would go to
such great lengths
to avoid leaving behind
a delicate woman!
Ahhhh!
Why you!
Take this!
Sorry about that, but
I had to do something.
I have no intention
of getting mixed up
with that freak
Kurotsuchi, or of getting
an arrow in the back from
your four-eyed friend.
So I really had no choice but
to get a little rough with you
just now-- oh, no, maybe
I got a little too rough.
I'll be sure to apologize
to her when she wakes up.
-My, my.
This Cases the first
time in a long time
that I've been faced
with this problem.
URYU (VOICEOVER): He
took his own arm off.
-[sarcastically] It hurts.
It hurts, it hurts.
My, my, how this hurts.
Almost enough to make me
lose my mind, it hurts.
And I see that the
girl has gotten away.
But as long as she has
left behind even so
much as a single
hair, I will still
be able to track her down.
Ah, I can't wait to
capture her and experiment
until I turn her too much.
Sadly, I must deal
with you first.
URYU (VOICEOVER):
What a monster.
And there's a second
enemy as well.
If Kurotsuchi is the Captain,
then the woman behind him
must be his Lieutenant.
So far she hasn't moved
an inch even though her
superior a bow
pointed right at him.
Does that mean her
combat abilities are low?
If so, then I should
start with the Captain.
-Where'd he go!
Not bad.
You do seem to have
some good moves.
This attack and the time before,
you used Hirenkyaku, right?
It's an advanced
Quincy technique
to achieve high speed by
gathering spirit energy
into a current beneath the feet.
I am surprised to
find someone as young
as you has been
able to master it.
It would appear that you are
a talented specimen indeed.
URYU (VOICEOVER): I
couldn't outrun him.
And how does he know all this?
-However, chasing you
around this way really
is a bit of a bother.
I'm much more interested
in capturing the girl
and getting started
with my research,
so I'm rather pressed for time.
I'm a busy man, you
see, so I've decided
to use the method that requires
the least amount of energy
and effort in order to kill you.
Claw out.
[music playing]
Ashisogi Jizo.
[shouts]
URYU (VOICEOVER): He's
released his weapon.
What are its abilities?
Will it absorb my attack?
I can't just fire recklessly!
Damn it!
What's she doing?
Let go!
Oh, no!
I can't believe it.
He deliberately slashed
his own Lieutenant.
Isn't she his partner?
How can he do
something like that?
-You idiot.
I gave you a direct
order to hang onto him
even if your arms
were ripped off.
-My deepest apologies.
-Hmm!
Oh, well, it isn't as if I was
expecting very much from you
in the first place.
At least she served her purpose.
Killing you now will be as
easy as strangling a baby.
URYU (VOICEOVER): He
sacrificed his own Lieutenant
just to make sure his
sword connected with me.
-Look how you're sweating.
I can tell you're
in pain, and yet you
take it without crying out.
Not so much as a whimper.
That is some iron will you have.
Perhaps this is
not the first time
you've been cut by a blade.
-It's the second time.
-Oh.
How nice that you
have some experience.
However--
[nemu struggling]
Do you have to make so
much noise over there?
-My deepest apologies, sir.
My Captain, sir, please.
My I have some of
the medicine as well?
The wounds seem to have
penetrated to my lungs,
and I-- I'm not sure I
can sustain my life force
much longer.
[coughing]
-Yaa!
[screaming]
-You insect!
Are you deliberately
insulting me?
Is that it?
Are you suggesting there's
something wrong with your body
that an insignificant
slash could cause--
URYU (OFFSCREEN): Stop it!
Why are you doing that?
How can you treat your
very own people that way?
If you don't treat
here soon, she'll die!
-So now even you feel
free to begin insulting me
by suggesting she'll die
from a wound like this?
A body which I created?
Surely you're not
saying it could
cease to function from an
injury as minor as this one?
You'd better be careful
whom you insult.
-You created this girl?
-That's right.
Would you like to know
what the brat's name is?
I melded the essence
of my Gigai technique
with my Gikon technique and
named her Nemu Kurotsuchi.
An appropriate name for such a
masterpiece, don't you think?
So you can forget about parading
your misguided sense of justice
around here.
I'll use this thing
however I see fit,
and what I do is no concern
to a stranger like you.
-Uhh!
-Stop it!
URYU (VOICEOVER): My arm.
It won't move.
-My, my.
It would seem a bit
dense of you to only now
be noticing such a thing.
This robs the mobility from
all four limbs of whomever
is cut by it.
My Zanpakuto immobilizes
the body of whoever it cuts.
-A tranquilizer.
-Don't be ridiculous.
I never use such
primitive technologies.
This process looks at all
the countless signals fired
from your brain and
selectively severs
only the signals controlling the
neural impulses for movement.
That's how
sophisticated this is.
It takes away the
ability to move,
but unlike
tranquilizers, it leaves
intact the pain receptors
and nerve endings.
In other words--
-Ahhhhhh!
Uhhhh!
-Not and ounce of
your pain is lost.
Hey, you, Nemu.
Get up.
I want you to administer
the killing blow.
Nemu!
Oh, that's right.
You were cut by my sword, too,
so you can't move your limbs
any more than he can.
Damn it!
You're so useless!
URYU (OFFSCREEN):
Leave her alone!
-What's that?
-I said, leave her alone.
-My, my.
You are persistent.
Or is this an example of that
annoying Quincy honor you
people are always
mumbling about,
and that leads you to
show mercy to your enemies
just because they happen
to be wounded women?
-What?
-Oh, you know what
I'm talking about.
That stupid line
that all you Quincies
keep saying right up
until the moment you die.
By the honor of the
Quincy, I cannot do this.
Quincy, I won't allow that.
Quincy this, Quincy that.
Every last one of you!
It's so annoying!
But no words you say
will make any difference,
because soon with one
thrust of this blade,
I will forever silence you.
-You monster.
-Your disrespect is disturbing.
Don't you know what
hardships I had to endure?
When I became Chief of
Research and Development,
the Quincy was already a
rare and vanishing breed,
so it was difficult to
get subjects to study.
The few survivors were under
Soul Reaper surveillance.
The trick was to
bribe them so they
would be too late
coming to the rescue.
Then I could collect the souls.
Such hard work it was,
opening up living skulls,
electric shocks, sawing off
limbs, grinding bodies to much.
It was made even harder with the
poor quality of the specimens.
The last one was
a grubby old man
who kept screaming out
the name of his student.
It was all so pathetic.
Do you want to see
a picture of him?
It was taken after
the experiments,
so the body isn't
exactly intact anymore.
[music playing]
What was that student's name?
My, my.
I can't believe I've
forgotten it now.
It just seems like
after the experiment,
I lose all interest in--
[explosion]
What's this?
-Do you want me to tell you
the name you can't remember?
That student's name was Ishida.
Uryu Ishida.
This man is Soken Ishida.
He was my teacher, as
well as my grandfather!
-And?
-It's a So thing
Orihime's not here.
I wouldn't want her to see
what I'm going to do to you.
A girl like her
should never have
witnessed a battle like this.
Now I swear by the honor of the
Quincy, I'm going to kill you,
you monster!
-Oh?
[music playing]
[theme music]
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): It feels
like I'm not in the show
very much lately.
YORUICHI (VOICEOVER):
Don't worry about it.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
But Yoruichi!
YORUICHI (VOICEOVER): You aren't
in the next episode, either.
Uryu's handling
things all by himself.
URYU (VOICEOVER):
Just leave it to me.
YORUICHI (VOICEOVER): And if
you don't master Bankai soon,
Ichigo, you may never
get another chance.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): I'm
doing the best I can!