[theme music]
-What is it that makes
you so unreasonable?
What's your purpose?
Why did you come here
in the first place?
-I've come to save the
life of Rukia Kuchiki.
-Oh, come on.
Hm, you mean Rukia
the soul reaper
who went missing in the world
of the living a few months ago?
That's not enough time
for a true friendship.
A relationship like
that can't be worth
risking your life over.
-I can't deny.
I don't know very
much about Rukia.
That's not the point.
I might not risk my
life for her but Ichigo
wants to save her life.
And that's all I need to know.
What may seem like an
unworthy cause to you
is more than enough
reason for me.
-Well, I tried.
But if you're that determined
it would be insulting
for me to ask you to back down.
I guess it can't be avoided.
Unfortunately, it
means now I'm going
to have to take your life.
[grunts] [labored breathing]
[gasp]
-I'm sorry.
[gasping]
-Why would the stealth
force have sent you here
if they had orders to deliver,
they would have just sent
the hell butterfly.
-In ordinary circumstances
yes, but this one is different.
This order is signed by both
Head Captain Yamamoto and Squad
10 Captain Hitsugaya.
-Signed by both captains?
Is the order top secret?
[footsteps]
[labored breathing]
[gasp]
[sword slash]
[groaning]
-Is running away the only
thing you know how to do?
-(IN HEAD) Calm down.
Go to calm down.
I can cut him!
I have to!
-I'll let you go ahead
and have the first strike.
I'll stand here and you can
cut me anywhere you want.
You can go for my
throat, or for my gut.
Take out my eyeball if you want.
Or if you're lucky you might
kill me with single strike.
Just quit your quivering!
[roars]
-(IN HEAD) This
can't be happening.
I know I swung
with my full force.
And I know I didn't miss.
How can there not even
be a scratch on him?
And how can it be that my
hand is bleeding instead?
Impossible.
-Is that it?
-Is that really all you have?
-Damnit!
I'm not scared of him!
[crash]
-That's enough of
this running around.
Stop embarrassing yourself.
I'm not very fond
of chasing rabbits.
[grunts]
-Hm.
-Pff.
[labored breathing]
[gasps]
-(IN HEAD) Damn.
How can that be?
I hit him.
I hit him straight on.
But I couldn't cut him.
What does it mean?
Are his powers really that
much greater than mine?
Damn it!
No, calm down.
Got to calm down.
The only reason I
couldn't cut him
is that I'm overwhelmed
by his spiritual pressure.
That's the problem.
If I calm down and sharpen
my spiritual pressure,
then I should be
able to cut him.
Remember what Zangetsu
said-- rid yourself of fear.
Focus only on the task ahead.
Retreat and you will die.
Hesitate and you will die.
[gasp] I can win!
Chad's spiritual pressure.
It's gone!
[clink]
-(IN HEAD) No, it can't be.
Chad's been defeated?
He can't be dead.
No way.
It can't be possible.
Chad's too strong to lose.
He's invincible.
-I must admit, it surprises
me that his final attack
was that powerful.
If I had taken a
direct hit, I might
have had a real problem here.
It's amazing enough
that a human could even
get into the Seireitei
to begin with,
but to think that he
could fight this hard.
[labored breathing]
NANAO (OFFSCREEN):
Captain Kyoraku!
I have urgent news!
-What is it now?
It must be important
to make you run.
Come to think of it,
stealth force sent someone,
didn't they?
What's it about?
-It's about Captain Aizen.
He was found dead this morning.
-Hm?
-The cause of death was the
removal of his soul chain
and soul sleep and destruction
of his heart by Zanpakuto.
So far, there are no suspects.
It's being investigated
as a murder.
The news was classified as top
priority for officers' eyes
only.
And it's signed by both Head
Captain Yamamoto and Captain
Hitsugaya.
I believe the
information is accurate.
-That's bad news.
Sosuke was-- very well.
I suppose we should go
and pay our respects.
-Yes sir.
-(IN HEAD) Chad.
Chad.
Chad!
-Wait, one moment, Captain.
I just noticed something.
This Ryoka-- it isn't dead yet.
Shall I administer
the killing blow?
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Chad!
-Shall I administer
the killing blow?
-Leave him be, Nanao.
That is my responsibility.
It's no job for you.
-But Captain!
One of these same
Ryoka was probably
responsible for the
murder of Captain Aizen!
-Hm, perhaps.
But then again,
maybe they weren't.
-Huh?
-I'm just saying.
We don't really know for sure.
Anything is possible.
Anyway, there's no need
to kill so unnecessarily.
Let's call the
rescue squad and have
him put in a cell somewhere.
If he or one of his friends is
the killer, all the more reason
to keep him alive to find out.
Understand?
-Yes, Captain.
I understand.
I'll make the arrangements
with Squad Four at once.
My apologies, sir,
for trying to meddle.
-Hm.
Things seem to be getting
rather complicated.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Chad!
He's alive!
It's faint but I can still
feel his spiritual pressure.
So then.
What am I waiting for?
I have to win this fight.
Because if I lose now then Chad
and Orihime and Uryu and Ganju
and Hanatoro and
Yoruichi-- all the people
who've lent me their
strength-- they'll all die!
I can't be afraid!
I don't have the time!
[jingling]
-So I see you decided to
stand your ground at last.
Does this mean that you are
prepared to die like a warrior,
or does it just mean
you've given up?
-The answer is neither one!
[yells]
-(IN HEAD) Wait for me Chad.
I'll beat this guy.
And then I'll save you!
[slash] Promise!
-Sorry to say, but I don't
feel like dying just yet.
Because if I die, then
everyone who is counting on me
will be destroyed too.
-(IN HEAD) I can cut him.
And if I can cut him,
then I can beat him.
I know it now.
I know I can win!
-What is this?
You're thinking you can
beat me now, aren't you?
Don't let your guard down yet.
Stay like that, razor sharp.
You see, this is
where the fun begins.
Now, Ichigo Kurosaki!
[giggles]
-Kenny looks so happy!
[laughing]
[grunts]
[yells]
-Sosuke Aizen, Captain of
Squad Five, has passed away.
When he was taken
down from the wall,
his breathing had
already stopped
and nothing more could be done.
No Gigai?
Are you certain one wasn't used?
-Yes.
I investigated every
conceivable angle,
including the
possibility that someone
might have used a
substitution body to deceive
other eyes at the
scene of the crime.
But in the end, all
of that only served
to confirm the reality
of Captain Aizen's death.
Of course once all of
this chaos and fighting
is finally resolved, a
new Squad Five Captain
will be selected by the Central
46 and the other squad leaders.
Squad Seven Captain Komamura,
Squad Nine Captain Tosen,
thank you for coming.
Now please return
to your commands
and rest assured I will soon
pay a visit to the front lines
myself.
-It was good of you could
come Captain Tosen and Captain
Komamura.
How is Captain Aizen?
I see.
What did Captain Unohana
say, if I may ask?
-Only that Captain
Aizen had passed away.
It seems to me that
if we want to get
to the truth behind
Captain Aizen's death,
the quickest way will be
first to put an end to all
this fighting and confusion.
-And by that do you mean--
-Ah, unfortunately yes.
I'm going to have to enter this
fight whether I like it or not.
Abstaining from
battle is always best,
but it seems things aren't
going to be so easy this time.
Ah, if it weren't
for fighting we
could avoid so many
misunderstandings,
so many ugly emotions
brought to the surface,
so many ugly tragedies.
-(IN HEAD) Finally the
time has come for Captain
Tozen's Suzumushi
to be released.
-I loathe fighting
with all my heart.
[screams]
[gasps]
[jingling]
-That's good.
Good reaction.
Your concentration is improving.
Unlike earlier, you can actually
hear my bells ringing now.
I only wear the bells
and this eye patch
to make things harder so
I get more enjoyment out
of my battles.
I'm glad you're taking
advantage of them.
Because otherwise they
don't serve any purpose.
-Damnit.
You take me for a fool?
I suppose that's
also the reason you
won't call on your Zanpakuto.
-Hm?
-Ha!
You see?
Because we both know my
sword can cut you now,
so if you let your guard down--
-My Zanpakuto
doesn't have a name.
My sword is completely
out in the open.
It has never had a sealed form.
What you see here is the
true form of my Zanpakuto.
-Is that so?
Well you probably shouldn't
have revealed that.
Because that tells
me your sword isn't
going to get any more
powerful than it is right now.
And in that case!
-In that case what?
In that case you were
going to be able to win?
Is that what you were thinking?
Now you're the one who's
taking me for a fool.
You should have
thought to ask me
why I don't seal my Zanpakuto.
It's my spiritual pressure.
It's so huge that even
if I use all of my might,
I can't seal it.
So when I fight, I
make sure to hold back.
I never swing my sword
with my full strength.
Do you see why?
If I didn't do that,
my enemies are so weak,
the battle wouldn't last long
enough for me to enjoy it.
[gasp]
-Didn't I tell you not to let
up on your spiritual pressure?
Relaxing just because you
found a glimmer or two of hope
for victory?
[gasping for breath]
-What a boring way
for this to end.
[crash]
-Tah.
And I had been waiting
such a long time for this,
to come up against someone
who could have killed me,
someone who at least heard
my bells during battle.
[gasping for breath]
-No more, huh?
That was no fun at all.
-(IN HEAD) Damnit!
[gasp] Damn!
Damn!
I don't want to die.
I can't die!
Not here.
Not in a place like this.
I can't.
I can't afford to die yet!
Move!
Move, body!
Got to stop the bleeding.
You have to let me
fight one more time!
[gasp] I have to save Rukia!
[theme music]
-Did you see that Ichigo?
That's the strength
of our Captain.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
It isn't over yet.
I'm going to turn this whole
thing around right now.
-Oh really?
How?
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Well
I'm gonna, um-- I mean--
KENPACHI (OFFSCREEN):
I'm looking forward
to hearing this too.
YACHIRU (OFFSCREEN):
Kenny looks so happy!
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
Well I'll do my best!