[MUSIC - BEAT CRUSADERS,
"TONIGHT, TONIGHT, TONIGHT"]
-You freeloaders!
Get of off my bed.
The bed is reserved
for the team mascot.
And the mascot is me!
-If I want to be on the
bed, I'll be on the bed.
Got it?
So just go be a
mascot somewhere else.
There's only so much I
can put up with, you know.
-What did you say?
This house was crowded enough
without the three of you.
And now we've got a full-blown
population density crisis,
leaving no room for
your annoying bodies!
-If you would just
calm down for a moment,
you'd realize that your
argument has no merit at all.
Because in our current
stuffed-animal form,
we take up very little space.
So in terms of the
area-to-occupancy ratio,
our presence is actually
quite insignificant.
-Why, you!
I oughta--
-What did I say?
You guys have got to
get along and be quiet.
-Don't look at me.
It's not my fault.
We tried to be nice, but that
older model keeps attacking us.
-Old model?
-What did I do?
Why does this stuff always
have to happen to me?
[bell tolling]
-Where's Ururu?
-He's in the back room, resting.
But he prefers to
be alone for awhile.
And we should respect that.
-I understand.
-What about those
Bounts who disappeared?
-Nothing.
I don't sense them.
-Yes.
Well, we're not
sure whether it's
an atmospheric
phenomenon, or perhaps
an entirely different
condition, which
is for some reason blocking
all of our sensors.
-But--
-We detect nothing.
-Yes.
-Those weird things that
came out back there--
what were they?
-This is just a theory.
But my guess is
that the Bounts are
able to gather chi
and spirit energy that
exists in the World of the
Living, and by manipulating it,
transform it into these dolls.
If my theory is correct,
these things that Ichigo saw
were probably dolls, too.
These new dolls must be
very important to them,
because the Bounts were willing
to sacrifice one of their own
in order to create them.
-It keeps getting
more complicated.
-Before we can do
anything else, I
think we should try to
gather some more information.
And I'd like Renji to
help me out with that.
-Hm?
-We should go investigate
Kariya's mansion
to see what we can find there.
-Sounds good.
-Chad, Orihime, I
think you'd both be
safer if you moved in
here for a little while.
-You think we're in danger?
-Hm?
-Since we can't sense our
enemies' spiritual pressure,
we never know when
they'll strike.
I think you'll be
safe enough at school.
But you both live alone,
and that worries me.
So at night, I'd feel
better if you stayed here
where there's a barrier.
-Sure.
-Good idea.
-You should probably get home
as soon as possible, Ichigo.
You haven't been
there in a while,
and I would imagine
your family is
wondering if you're all right.
Also, I want you to
think of a strategy
that we can use against the
Bounts when they strike again.
-A strategy?
-Ririn and the
others will go along
to help you with your plan,
while at the same time
keeping a lookout for
any Bount movement.
-With our three brains, we'll
come up with a plan in no time.
-And you can count on us
to watch your back, Ichigo.
-No a problem.
-This is a joke, right?
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): I did what
Urahara said and brought them
home.
But I don't know.
-You're just a
rookie, but you strut
around liking you're all that.
-And you're just an old model.
KON: I dare you
to say that again.
-Old model!
Old model!
-You are so unbelievably cruel!
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Bad idea.
RIRIN: Aw, did I hurt
the old model's feelings?
-How am I supposed to
read with all this noise?
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Right.
She's here, too.
-And I had just got to the
best part of the story.
It's the climax,
where Caitlin, who's
been bullied and
tortured by Rodriguez,
finally snaps and seeks
revenge, clutching
her newborn baby and a rifle
-Why do you always have to
hide in the closet like that?
-Because I decided this is
the best place to sleep.
So I'm gonna sleep here!
-Rukia, they're being mean.
Can I come up and-- whoa!
-For crying out loud.
When will you learn?
-Not even death
can cure stupidity.
-But Kon's stupidity
runs through all aspects
of his personality.
It's actually quite impressive.
-You called me
stupid, didn't you?
RIRIN: Oh, yeah?
I'll show you.
KON: You take that
back right now.
NOBA: Stop.
-[groan] Stop it!
The two of you are driving me
crazy with all this fighting!
If I have to hear any
more, I'm gonna go nuts.
[door opening]
-Did you hear what I said?
I'm going to go completely nuts!
YUZU: Ichigo!
Who are you talking to?
-Oh, no.
This is-- this is
for a class project.
-I thought for dinner
I'd make sukiyaki.
I know it's your favorite,
so hopefully that
will make you feel better.
-Oh, no.
I'm not really--
-It's OK.
Don't worry about it.
Just know that if you ever
need someone to talk to,
Dad and I will always
be there for you.
Because that's what
families are for!
Well, I'll see you later!
-Uh, hey.
But I wasn't--
-Your sister completely
misunderstood.
-She has every reason to worry.
-I don't blame her at all.
A grown man having an
argument with a roomful
of stuffed animals?
She must think you are
completely off your rocker.
-Yeah?
And whose fault is that?
[alarm]
-Hey, Ichigo!
-What perfect timing.
For once, I'm actually glad to
hear that stupid alarm go off.
I feel like I'm about
to go nuts around here.
KON: Ah!
Wait!
Don't leave me!
-Now then.
This is the perfect
opportunity to do our own work.
-Well, if they're off
to fight a Hollow,
I don't see how we're
going to be of much help.
NOBA: Mm.
-Ichigo, Rukia, how could you
run away and leave me alone
without any protection?
You're horrible!
-Would you stop crying?
[squeak]
-Ugh.
What do you think you're doing?
-I don't think you
fully understand
what's going on here.
-Why so serious all of a sudden?
-The Bounts are targeting
strong spiritual energy.
-What's that have
to do with anything?
-Do we have to spell
everything out for you?
Everyone in Ichigo's family
has strong spirit energy.
-Now that Ichigo
and Rukia are gone,
we have to come up with
a plan to protect them.
-Now you're talking.
[roaring]
-You've gotten
pretty good at this.
-Yeah, I guess.
We should probably get back.
-Huh?
Hey.
-What?
-Something doesn't feel right.
-Like what?
-Well, I'm not exactly
sure what it is.
But I feel a strange energy
coming from your house.
-A Bount or something?
-No.
It's familiar, but I
can't quite place it.
-Ah, that ought to do the trick.
[squeak]
-Ah!
What are you doing?
-I was gonna ask
you the same thing.
What the hell is
all this nonsense?
RIRIN: It's all right, Kon.
I'll explain.
-Huh?
-It's a booby trap,
designed to ensnare Bounts.
-You mean this is
a Bount booby trap?
-Right.
So no matter when
the enemy attacks,
we'll be safe and sound.
-Urahara supplied us
with the materials
we needed to build a
trap powerful enough
to stop a Bount.
I dare say you'll be amazed when
you see what we came up with.
Look!
This trap uses a bait
specifically designed
to grab the Bount's attention
and draw them in close.
Then, pull the string-- voila!
A proverbial rat in a trap, to
be disposed of at our leisure.
ICHIGO: [sigh]
KURODO: This basket is made of
a special bamboo that seals away
spirit energy to ensure that
those buggers don't get out.
-Fascinating.
-You've got to be kidding me!
KURODO: And the
piece de resistance.
Feast your eyes on this!
-What exactly is it?
-It's a Bount repellent.
The balloons at both ends
gather minute particles
of spirit energy
that are in the air.
And then the CD-shaped
reflector panels
release a bright light,
which the Bounts hate.
-We're not trying
to scare birds here.
-Not to worry, because I also
set up my ground-based Bount
repellent that has
exactly the same effect.
I call it Kon's Special
Bount repellent.
-Oh.
-Great.
They can wash their hands.
-And if a Bount somehow gets
passed the outdoor traps,
we have indoor
traps set as well.
If a Bount comes strolling
down the hall and steps
over this mark, he'll
trigger the sensor,
releasing the rice
grinder that's
been suspended from the ceiling.
-Yes.
And this particular
rice grinder is
made of seki seki, which
seals away spirit energy,
rendering the enemy
utterly defenseless
and completely at our mercy.
-I don't suppose that trap
you were working on earlier
has any special
powers, does it, Kon?
-Of course!
The ropes are treated with a
special liquid that seals away
the spirit energy of
anyone's feet touch it.
-And you're saying that Urahara
supplied you with all of this?
-That's right.
-[sigh]
-As long as you're
in this house,
you're completely secure.
-And who do you think is
going to fall for these traps?
HANATARO: Ah!
Help me!
[crash]
-What's that?
-[groaning]
-It looks like Hanataro.
-Rukia, is that really you?
-My trap's a success!
It does more than
just trap the victim.
You see?
It also makes them fall
face first into a pie!
ICHIGO: What are you doing here?
-Well, I was looking
for the house
that I'm supposed to
deliver this pie to.
Oh, in case you need
it, the convenience
store I work for has
delivery service now.
-OK.
And that's when you got
caught by the Bount trap?
-Bount trap?
-So the Soul Society
didn't send you
to the World of the Living
to help deal with the Bounts?
-Ever since I got here, I've
been so busy with everyday life
that I don't know
what I'm doing.
-But now that you
bring it up, I can't
remember why I came to
the World of Living.
-Come on.
-[laughs] I guess we've answered
your question about whether
these traps will work or not.
-Whatever.
Just get rid of this
crap, all right?
[gasping]
-What did you say?
-I don't believe it.
We just explained
how these traps
will protect us from the Bounts.
-You've had enough
fun for one day.
Now clean it up.
You can come inside and
wash your face, Hanataro.
HANATARO: Thank you,
I appreciate it.
-Boy, you sure did fall
for that trap, didn't you?
-Hey, Rukia!
Wait for me!
-That's the thanks
we get for helping?
-They all underestimate just
how powerful the Bounts are.
And the only thing that
will open their eyes
to the seriousness of the
situation is a good scare.
-Unforgivable.
-[laughs evilly]
Just wait and see.
-[laugh]
-Yeah!
-These special suits
that Urahara mad for us
to amplify our powers will
be absolutely perfect.
Though I never thought that we'd
have to use them in a situation
like this.
-Yes, you're right.
And it's convenient
that these suits
look similar to the Bounts
dolls we saw hatch earlier.
-[laughs] We'll show Ichigo
and the others a thing or two.
When we show up
looking like this,
Ichigo and Rukia will see us
and think that Bounts have come.
Then they'll attack us.
When they do that, I'll amplify
my illusion power with the suit
and dodge the attack!
-Excellent.
And while you're
doing that, I'll
use my suit's power to enhance
my transformation energy
and completely overwhelm them.
-When Ichigo begins
to panic, Noba,
who's been hiding all this
time, will release the traps.
We'll fall into the traps on
purpose and barely escape!
He'll have no choice bu
to admit the traps work.
By risking ourselves, we'll let
them see with their own eyes
how foolish they were to
laugh at our anti-Bount plan.
-They're coming.
-All right!
Let's do this.
-Ready, willing, and able.
RIRIN: Noba, make sure all
the traps are set properly.
-Mm.
HANATARO: I'm sorry I have
to borrow all this stuff.
-Don't worry about it.
-Huh?
Ichigo?
-What's wrong with you now?
-It-- that is!
-Huh?
[gasping]
-Hado 33, Sokatsui!
[shouting]
-So, did I do it?
-I think that you overdid it.
RIRIN: I didn't expect that.
KURODO: Thank you, Noba.
If you hadn't saved
us with your power.
we'd have been a
couple of dead ducks.
-Noba, can't you hear us?
ICHIGO: What's that?
Look out, Noba!
Get away from there!
RIRIN: Hado 31, Shakkaho!
[shouting]
-Sorry, Noba.
Are you all right.
-I'm fine.
[panting]
-Rukia wasn't surprised one bit.
-I would assume
that's because of all
of her training
as a Soul Reaper.
She's used to
life-threatening situations.
That's why when she
saw us, her reflexes
allowed her to react
instantaneously.
-Why don't we forget this?
It's too dangerous.
-There's Ichigo,
KURODO: Listen, Ichigo, there's
a perfect good explanation--
-Ichigo, Ririn and Kurodo have
been eaten by those bug things.
-Huh?
[shouting]
-Rukia!
-Hado Four, Byakurai!
[screaming]
-Where did they go?
-Kon.
-What is it?
-Get in my body, will ya?
KON: Ugh, what the hell?
-Rukia, did you see which
way the Bounts went?
-I've lost sight of them.
But they can't be far.
So if we hurry,
we can catch them.
-All right.
I'm all ready to do this.
-I was just able
to contact Renji.
-Uh--
-I know it couldn't
have been easy watching
as your friends got
eaten like that.
-No.
-Noba, you he stay right
here and keep watch.
Contact us immediately
if something happens.
-Hey, wait for me.
-Ririn, Kurodo, even
though we've only
known each other a little
while, as a fellow Mod-Soul,
you have my word that I
will avenge your death.
[scream]
-What happened?
Kon, are you all right?
-I can't go on.
The rest is up to you.
-Did you find them?
-No, I didn't see anything.
I'll go look down that way.
-All right.
RIRIN: Are they gone?
KURODO: Yes.
What ferocious savages.
Our wonderful is
completely ruined.
NOBA: At any rate, we
have to clear this up.
-Agreed, but let's get
out of these suits first.
RIRIN: Good idea. [grunt] Ah!
KURODO: I think it must
have short-circuited.
[sighing]
Why can I still hear your voice?
-The external speakers
seem to be broken.
But it looks like the
suit-to-suit radio
is working perfectly.
-That's it!
I'm sure that Noba has a
receiver for this radio, too!
-Of course.
So all we have to do is
go back and tell Noba,
and then we'll be saved.
-Because once we
talk with Noba, he
can explain to them
exactly what's going on.
And they won't
attack us anymore.
KURODO: However, judging from
Rukia's attitude earlier,
I don't think he's had the
chance to explain it just yet.
RIRIN: At any rate, we
should get back there.
KURODO: I agree!
RIRIN: Someone's coming!
[whimpering]
-Why does my big
sister always have
to be such a pain in the neck?
Return your own damn CDs.
What do I look like, a slave?
KURODO: Is he gone?
RIRIN: He spotted us!
-Hey, afro dude, how
come you're up there?
If you're playing some
kind of game, can I watch?
-Be quiet!
This is not a game I'm playing.
And you can't watch!
-What's your problem?
You know, I don't think it
would kill you to stop and talk
to me for a minute.
-Would you please stop talking?
I just don't understand why
so many people in this town
can see me.
RIRIN: What's going on?
KURODO: He seems to be the Soul
Reaper in charge of this town.
RIRIN: Huh?
Then what are Rukia
and the others?
KURODO: Well, I don't think that
Rukia, Renji, and Ichigo are
involved in the day-to-day
protection of the town.
They have more specific tasks.
But his duties seem to
encompass a broader scope.
-Freeze, you dolls!
KURODO: [gasp]
RIRIN: Oh, no!
KURODO: Run away!
RUKIA: Hado 33, Sokatsui!
-Hey, what's going on?
-Get back here!
-Oh, Lady Kuchiki.
What an unexpected
surprise to see.
-Shakkaho!
-Doh!
Ah!
-That looks like Rukia
up there playing war.
I had no idea she
was into that stuff.
How come I'm always left out?
No one tells me anything!
I can't stand it anymore!
-[sigh] Finally finished.
RIRIN: Almost there!
-Huh?
KURODO: Ah, Hanataro.
-[screams] Oh, god!
Oh, god!
Oh!
[cries] Ouch.
RIRIN: Kurodo, I
just thought of a way
to kill two birds
with one stone.
KURODO: I know exactly
what you're thinking.
-What?
I hope they're not
who I think they are.
RIRIN: All right.
Prepare yourself!
KURODO: You are now our hostage!
[screaming]
-Not so fast.
KURODO: This isn't good!
-Roar, Zabimaru!
[screaming]
-Renji, looks like you
got here just in time.
-I'd say so.
-Don't let your guard down.
They may be small, but
there with the Bounts,
so we can't underestimate them.
RIRIN: Nothing we do
seems to work out.
KURODO: You can say that again.
-Looks like we have
no other choice.
So you know what this means.
-Well, if we must, we must.
RIRIN: Let's go!
KURODO: Right Energy release!
RIRIN: Combine!
Go!
-Full demon!
ICHIGO: What is that?
-I don't know.
That's the dumbest looking
thing I've ever seen.
You're history!
Roar!
Huh?
What the heck is this?
-Renji, over there!
-How'd that goofy looking
thing get my Zabimaru?
-Roar, Zabimaru!
-[shout]
-Save me!
Save me!
Please don't let
it hurt me, Ichigo.
-Damn.
How did it do that?
-Unbelievable!
-Huh?
What the--?
Stop it!
That tickles! [laughs]
-Rukia!
-Ha!
Now to finish you off.
-Ichigo, Renji,
something's weird!
RIRIN: [laughs] It's too late.
Even if you were smart
enough to figure it out,
there's no way to escape.
-Whoa!
[groaning]
RIRIN: Oh, that hurt!
KURODO: How could I make a
stupid mistake like that?
-Pitiful Your whole attack
was nothing but an illusion.
[whimpering]
-It's the end of the line!
-Where'd they go?
-Huh?
-Noba?
[groaning]
ICHIGO: Ririn!
Kurodo!
RUKIA: What's the
meaning of this?
-Well, these are--
-Their suits are made by
that perverted store owner
to give these two idiots
more fighting power when
they're in stuffed animal form.
What you've been
seeing is Ririn's power
to show illusions and
Kurodo's power to transform.
-Seriously?
URAHARA: Sorry, I had no idea.
We probably shouldn't
use these suits anymore.
It wouldn't be good if you were
mistaken for the enemy again.
-Yeah, you got that
right, because I might not
be around to save
them the next time.
Noba didn't say a word.
So if I hadn't spoken up,
you'd have been goners.
You'd probably be pushing up
daisies right now! [laughs]
Am I right?
What's wrong?
You know, you had
any manners at all,
you'd show a little less
attitude and a little more
gratitude.
Because after all, I am the
one who saved your-- [shout]
-You are the rudest,
most obnoxious man
that I've ever met in my life.
-What did you say?
RIRIN: Don't bite me!
I'm gonna teach you a lesson.
-It might be a good idea to
disable all the traps for now.
We still have to work out a
few of the kinks before they
they can do as much good.
-That's for sure.
Which reminds me,
did you guys clean up
all the ones planted
around the house?
-Uh-uh.
KARIN: Yuzu, I'm home!
[gasp]
[grunting]
-I get it.
Yeah, this is a
new game, isn't it?
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers!
GROUP: Golden!
So Hitsugaya's called
everyone together.
-Yes, he wants to
dispatch several people
to the World of the Living.
Who do you think we should send?
-What about Yachiru?
ARAMAKI: She's in
the sweets room.
-What's Ikkaku doing?
ARAMAKI: He's sleeping.
-How about Yumichika?
ARAMAKI: He's
organizing his files.
-All right, then.
We'll send Yumichika.
-Huh?
But he's the only one
who's doing any work.
KENPACHI: You idiot!
Play is more
important than work.
You can work whenever you want.