Hello there..
[growling]
How impressive! In such a very short
time, you increased your power ten fold.
I did it to defeat you!
[yelling]
Mm.
Now, Orihime, do it!
Tsubaki!
[gasping]
I don't know why this
is happening to me.
Well, I suppose it's about
time for you to wake up.
So now-who am I?
[gasping]
[screaming]
Damn you...!
You bastard! Just what
did you do to her?!
What did I do? The
same thing I did to you.
[gasping]
[panting]
Damn it, I'm too late.
Orihime and Chad's
Spiritual Pressures...
It doesn't appear they've
been injured, but...
[exhaling sharply]
I sense another Spiritual
Pressure!
Okay. Break time's over.
Right.
Yukio.
I'm on it.
Loading 'Invaders
Must Die'.
We're almost there, guys.
After this, we can
finally get rid of our
cursed powers and become
human again. Count on it.
Good. I'm beside myself
with excitement.
... and then the squirrel ran down my pant
leg and it was gone. Hey, look, it's Uryu.
Are you coming back?
Not yet, but I had some paperwork
I had to take care of.
I heard you got hurt
pretty bad from falling
out of a tree while
trying to save a cat, of
all things.
I couldn't believe it!
I got hurt trying to save a cat?
Great. What
kind of story did
Ryuken tell these guys?
[gasping]
That Spiritual
Pressure.
Uh--
By the way, Keigo... While I was gone,
did you come across anyone suspicious?
Uh...
Oh. Those punks stopped
coming around.
They were after Ichigo and he hasn't
been here for the past couple of days.
He's probably off doing one
of his part-time jobs.
Hey, what do you say
we go bug him at work?
Think I'll pass.
The other Spiritual Pressure
that I felt where I
last sensed Orihime's
and Chad's presences...
It definitely belongs to the
guy I was following. And
just now, I felt it coming
from Keigo and Mizuiro, too.
But it doesn't add up.
Why did he approach
them? They don't possess
any special powers.
And what was that odd
sensation I picked up,
that was mixed in with
each of their Spiritual
Pressures? What is he plotting?
I have to find out.
No. Ichigo didn't come
home yesterday, either.
I see.
This will sound kinda
strange...
...but has anything really
unusual happened to
him, or to anyone else in
your family, recently?
Huh?
For example, have any of you experienced
anything you can't explain?
Huh, that kinda stuff
happens to us all the time.
But Ichigo's been kinda numb when
it comes to things like that.
I swear, there could be a
ghost or monster in front
of his face and he probably
wouldn't notice it.
[chuckling]
Really...
Uh--
Do you know where his
part-time job is?
I'll get you the address.
Here you go!
Unagiya...?
If you find Ichigo
there...
...tell him everything's fine here at the
house. He doesn't need to rush home.
[gasping]
What's wrong?
Sorry, it's nothing.
Thanks for the address.
[lightly grunting]
Who was that? Was it
Ichigo's friend?
Yeah. It was Uryu.
That's the first time I ever spoke to him,
but he's exactly like Ichigo described him.
Oh, yeah?
Huh?
[grunting]
Okay, you've been hitting it pretty
hard for an hour. You can stop now.
[grunting and exhaling]
[panting]
What's the matter? You
aren't talking...
I expected you to
complain.
So, how 'bout starting up
another set, then?
Mm?!
I'm messing with you. I presume you've
built up some stamina after all that.
Stamina?
That's right...
Fullbring puts a lot of pressure
on your flesh and blood.
To fully control it, you need to
have a crazy amount of stamina.
I see. That's why you've had me
jumping through all these hoops.
Mm-hm.
And I see you recover
fast. That's important.
Tell me... When your Fullbring was finally
complete, you saw something, right?
Mm!
I knew it. You should
have seen me glowing as a
Spiritual Being, even with
your vision destroyed.
That's why, to make sure I
was on the right track,
I forced you to fight
me without your sight.
It was a way to prove to you that your Soul
Reaper powers were starting to come back.
Uh!
You look confused so let
me explain a little
better. After you lost
the bulk of your Spirit
Energy, the remnants inside of you lay
dormant in one location for a long time.
We believed that, through
Fullbring, we could use
the Spirit Energy that
flowed inside of you from
your Combat Pass, to stimulate
your remaining Spirit Energy.
Once you build up your
stamina and learn to fully
control Fullbring, your
Soul Reaper powers
will merge with it on
their own...
...and you will then gain powers
beyond that of a Soul Reaper.
Take this.
Mm!
Give it a try...
Let's see what you can do. Your Fullbring
should be fully functional already.
[inhaling]
Yukio!
Yeah, I'm on it.
Uh!
[roaring]
How's that?
Very impressive. Not bad,
kid.
Now you're going to need a name...
for your Fullbring.
Don't see their car. Must
be out.
Welcome back. You managed
to master your Fullbring.
I had to plug my system in.
You were taking so long, I
was worried the battery in
this thing would run out.
Yeah. Sorry for all the
trouble.
Mmm.
Apart from all that...
...You should go home for
today and see your family.
I assume they must be worried...
after not hearing from you.
Right! I haven't called
since I started training!
How many days has it been
since I began all of this?
Just about 24 hours, in
total.
Huh?
You didn't know, but I
fast-forwarded time while
you were inside. You
should be thanking me.
So you should head on home now. I'm sure
your family is anxiously awaiting you.
Now, I'll be able to
protect them...
My friends...
...my family... everyone.
It's strange. I can sense
that odd Spiritual
Pressure hanging around.
But none of the people I
met today seemed to be aware of it.
And I couldn't
ask them if they remembered
meeting that guy.
Orihime said she was attacked by the
same guy who attacked me. I wonder
if it's possible that all of this
is happening because of his powers.
If that's the
case, then...
[laughing]
Now that was really impressive!
The kid was
actually able to complete
his Fullbring training.
With that completed, we can all finally
say goodbye to our cursed powers!
The question, though... is how
Tsukishima will act. We'll see.
[gasping]
What's wrong with you guys?
Aren't you happy about this?
It's just that we finally
remembered...
About what?
About exactly what we're
supposed to do.
[gasping]
Damn it!
Dirty Boots!
Looks like they're still
up...
They must have been
worried about me.
I'm home!
Huh?
Welcome home!
Thank goodness you're
finally back, Ichigo!
Yeah, I'm sorry I'm so
late...
We were all waiting for
you!
Whose shoes are these?
You won't believe who
came by to visit us!
Hey, don't pull! Who is
it?
[giggling]
You have to guess!
You have to at least give
me a hint!
All right, fine. Here's the hint.
He's one of our cousins.
A cousin?
Right! Now you have to
guess his name!
That's going to be hard. What cousin
would drop by here unexpectedly?
He finally came home!
Uh!
Hi Ichigo...
It's been a while.
See? I told you you'd be surprised, Ichigo!
It's cousin Shu!
We haven't seen or heard
from him since Grandpa Rin's
memorial service, and how
long has that been?!
He came by earlier this evening, and
we all had a nice dinner together! It
was so nice to catch up with
him after all these years!
Yeah, but it would've been nicer if you
actually told us you were stopping by.
I have to say, Shu, that part
of you hasn't changed much.
I'm sorry.
Was I too much trouble?
[gasping]
No, of course not.
[struggling]
What are you waiting for,
Ichigo? Come and say hi!
Tsukishima!
You bastard! What are you
doing in my house?!
Ichigo?!
What's wrong with you?
Stop it Ichigo! What's
gotten into you?!
Yuzu's right! Have you gone crazy?!
Let go of his collar!
You're hurting him!
Are you mad that he dropped
by without calling?!
Hey, it's not that big a
deal!
What have you
done... to my sisters?!
Stop it, Ichigo!
It's all right, girls.
I understand.
Ichigo's always so
serious.
I figure... He's just angry
at me for staying so late.
Answer me!
[doorbell ringing]
[gasping]
Um, Yuzu... would
you mind?
Okay...
[breathing hard]
I bet our friends
are here.
[gasping]
Hi Yuzu! Long time, no
see!
Hi! Here, go ahead and
use these slippers.
Thanks a lot!
You have enough for
everybody?
Shu, we're here!
Huh? Oh, I see Ichigo's
here, as well!
Oh, yeah.
Hey, Ichigo! We hear you've been
staying out late for a few days!
You should be more sensitive
to your sisters! You've been
leaving them here all
alone each night!
It's okay. We all right
without him.
Come on, Karin--
I asked everybody to
come.
I wanted to see the whole gang,
since it's been such a long time.
Don't give me that scary
look.
I'm sorry about inviting
everyone so late,
but tomorrow's Sunday,
so, it's okay, right?
You know what...?
Maybe I'll call Chad and
Orihime, as well...
Hi Orihime, it's me.
That's right, Tsukishima.
Huh? What are you talking
about?
I just ran into you the
other day...
Actually, I'm at Ichigo's
place right now...
[roaring]
[grunting]
What the hell?!
Tsukishima!
All right, Tsukishima...
Tell me what in the hell
did you do to everyone?!
Tsukishima, are
you hurt?
No, I'll be fine.
You're not fine! You're
bleeding!
Tsukishima!
Ichigo! What's
wrong with you!?
[gasping]
I have no idea why you're
acting like this, but that's
no way to treat a relative
you haven't seen in years!
What relative?! No! This
guy is---
I don't wanna hear your excuses!
Just apologize to him!
Wait a minute! You don't
understand---
You need to say you're
sorry right now!
[grunting]
What's the matter?
Ichigo...!
What's gotten into you?
You're not acting like
yourself at all! It's
like you've gone nuts!
I've never seen you like
this!
Ichigo...!
Why are you so upset? What
did he ever do to you?
You're being so mean!
Just apologize!
Come on, Ichigo!
Why are you so angry?
Talk to me! What's going
on?!
What's wrong?!
This is all your fault!
Yuzu's right!
Apologize!
Ichigo?
[panting]
What's happening?! I don't understand!
Is this Tsukishima's power?!
Is that you, Ichigo?
What's the matter?
[panting]
Look at you, you're all drenched in sweat.
Did something happen?
Here, drink this.
It'll help calm you down.
If you feel like talking,
I'm here to listen.
Thanks so much... I
appreciate it.
Mm.
What are you
doing?
Just relax and be quiet!
[doorbell ringing]
Who could that be at this
hour?
Coming!
How am I supposed to
tell her what happened?
There's no way she
would understand.
She doesn't know about Soul Reapers,
or Hollows, or Fullbring. Telling her
about that stuff out of the
blue would just frighten her.
Ichigo!
[gasping]
It's your lucky day, Ichigo! Your friend
Tsukishima's here to pick you up!
[gasping]
What is this?! What the
hell's going on?!
Somebody!
Anybody!
Isn't there anybody left...
who's still sane?!
Ichigo!
[grunting]
Ginjo!
He got them! Riruka...
Kutsuzawa...
Yukio... and Jackie!
All of them. Tsukishima
got them all!
[gasping]
Ichigo, don't forget to give that
Fullbring a name by the next episode.
What?! I don't even know
where to begin!
If you don't have anything, we can
name it, but it'll be embarrassing.
Wait, I have something!
[whispering]
That's a good one!
Huh?! Wait, I couldn't
hear that!