[panicked fleeing]
-Yaahh!
-Whoaa!
Give back my sword,
you fools!!!
[beastly yell]
Aaaaaghhhh!!
Huaaaa!
Wauugh!
But you don't deserve to
learn anything with that
half-hearted resolve!
Haaah!
Since you won't
teach me willingly,
Guess I'll just have to
force it out of you!
Haaaaa!
Finally, I can
ask you directly.
Tell me. Why did you choose
to go to work for Aizen?
Hm?
Is that really what
you want to know?
Huh?
That's a shame.
You really should've
stayed where you were.
Oh, Rangiku.
You're a pain.
What's this?!
It's his sword.
Something's different!
Now allow me to
test you out!
I'm ready!!
Haaaaa!
Hyaaaaa!
[drained panting]
[Isshin]
Hurry...
Ichigo...!
Captain Aizen, what is this?
[Aizen]
He's torturing those poor
kids by letting them
think they'll get away.
Boy, he sure is cruel.
Chizuru!
Mizuiro!
Huh?
Hm?!
Whoa! Wait! So you
two have been awake?!
Get this, he was busy
charging up his phone.
Sorry!...
But I think I'm good to go now.
I borrowed a charger
from the corner store.
"Borrowed"!?
Ya mean you stole it?
Hey, don't get
so technical.
It was an emergency and
the clerk was asleep so
I couldn't pay him.
Well, I see your point,
but go pay him later.
I also grabbed us some
food to tide us over!
Huh!?
See?
Wow!
I got some beef jerky, too.
If you want something salty,
you could eat that.
So I take it this is what
you eat most of the time?
It figures you'd like
really processed stuff.
Huh?
No way. Ever since middle
school, I've only been
eating home-cooked meals.
What? But I thought
your family was...
I made it work.
There are plenty of girls
out in the world who are
really good at cooking.
You just gotta know
how to find them,
and then they'll feed you.
Augh!
That's right. You're one of
those kinda guys aren't you?
Isn't that annoying!?
I hate that he treats
women like that!
Makes you wish you hadn't
come looking for him right?!
I mean really! Right?! Right?!
Stop touching me!
I agree.
[Tatsuki]
So, have you heard
what's going on?
Keigo kinda filled me in.
He said the situation's
pretty serious.
That there's some dangerous
guy who's coming to kill us.
So I got these.
Huh?
Stun guns
for everyone!
Where'd you get
those from?
[Tatsuki]
Forget I asked!
Stuns guns aren't
gonna stop him.
This guy can put us
out of action just
by coming near us.
He turned Don Kanonji's
staff from wood into dust
just by touching it.
Call it a "cane".
Not a staff!
He's really that powerful?
And he's not human?
Oh well, forget these things.
Huh?
[Tatsuki]
Chizuru, what's wrong?
You look like you're in shock.
Ah!
Well of course I'm in
shock! I feel numb!!
I don't know what's
going on here!
How can you all be so
cool and calm right now?
I feel like you guys are still
not telling me everything.
Tell me what you know!
Uh...
Well you see...
It's...!
No...
Huh?! What is?!
What's happening?!
I don't know enough about
it to explain it to you.
This is no time for chit chat!
Let's get movin, boys and girls!
Get up Mizuiro!
Grab her!
We have to get away!!
Fine! But you're gonna
tell me what you do
know about this later!
Hey! We gotta move!!
We need to stick
to the alleys!
If we stay out of sight,
we'll get to the
outskirts of town
without being attacked!
[gasp]
Who's that?!
Is he the one
after us?
You're wondering...
"How'd he find us"?
[Aizen]
I didn't.
I just decided to
stop pretending I
was looking for you.
Wow, It really
does turn to dust.
Hey! What do ya think
you're doing, boy?!
You can't throw things
like that at people!
Well then, how 'bout this?
Hunh?!
Hm?
[all] [panicking]
Yaahhahh!!!
[Don Kanonji]
Whoa! Has this
young man totally
lost it or what?!
Just shut up,
will you!?
I don't wanna sound
like Don Kanonji, but
that was a crazy stunt
you just pulled.
Hunh?!
Hnh?!
Yaaahh!!
Damn!
Keigo!!
This sword belonged to a guy who
was dressed just like Ichigo!
It just might get
through to this guy!
You idiot!! Even if that
sword does work, you'll
probably be killed!!
[Mizuiro]
Keigo!!
[Don Kanonji]
Boy!
I had to come back. Couldn't
run off and see you take such
a big risk all by yourself.
Heh. Thanks Kanonji.
Let's go, young man.
Give back my sword, you fools!!!
Ow-Ow! My back! Oww!
I give! Get off of me please!
Whoa hey that's my kidney!
Hold up now, son!
You're new!
Are you a friend?
[Keigo]
He's Afro-dude!!
Say what!!? "Afro-dude"??
That's a pretty silly name!
Look who's talking about
having a silly name!
[shouting]
And quit being so loud!
It's really annoying!
[big shuddering]
A-ahh-oo-aa...
Are you okay, Afro-dude?!
Don't get too freaked out!
Looks like you're shaking!
Quiet! I'm not shaking!
I'm just pissed because
you took my Zanpakuto!
[Kurumadani]
good morning!
Tsuchinamazu!!
Whoa!
Ooh!
All right!
Now run!!!
Hunh...?!
Huh...?
[gasp]
Ah!
Well, helo,
Captain Aizen.
I've returned.
[Chizuru]
What's going on now?!
Do you think that guy's
come to save us? Is that
the reason he's here?
[Mizuiro]
From the looks of things,
I wouldn't bet on it.
The last thing he's
going do is help us.
[Keigo]
This is really bad.
So you're back.
[Aizen]
What happened to the woman?
I killed her.
[Aizen]
Indeed. Her spirit
energy has disappeared.
I'm surprised.
Because you knew her so
well, I got the feeling
that you might show her
mercy and let her live.
Me? Show mercy?
I don't have
any of that.
I let you know that the
very first time I met you.
I'm a snake.
My skin and blood are cold.
I have no heart
I slither, looking for prey
with the tip of my tongue.
I swallow everything whole.
That's the sort of
creature I am.
[Don Kanonji]
Hey!
Quit with the gawking,
ya goofballs!
You kids can't
be standing here
flat-footed!
This is our
chance to move!
Yeah, he's right!
Let's get the
hell outta here!!
[Aizen]
Oh my.
I'm tired of them.
Catching mice is
so boring.
What will you do with them
after you kill them?
I'll hang their corpses on
the outskirts of town,
where they'll be easily seen.
Then I'll get to work
on creating the Ouken.
Sounds good to me.
Since that's the case,
I'll take care of killing them.
It'll be so much fun.
Gin...
Sounds good to me.
Since that's the case,
I'll take care of killing them.
It'll be so much fun.
[Aizen]
Gin...
(Surprised Gasping for Breath
reax as he is mortally Wounded)
[Gin]
There is only one way to avoid
the power of your Kyokasuigetsu.
And that's to touch its blade.
But it must be done before
its powerful influence puts
one into complete hypnosis.
It took me decades of gaining
your trust, just to get that
single fact out of you.
Tch!
[Gin]
In all 13 Court Guard Squads,
not a single person was aware
of that.
But it seems all of them were
quite confident they'd be
able to kill you, Captain.
Watching them made
me very nervous.
[gasp]
The only one who can kill you,
Captain Aizen, is me.
I knew that.
I brought you here with
me knowing exactly what
your objective was.
Because I was interested
in what technique you'd
use in trying to kill me.
But I'm disappointed in
you, Gin. Did you honestly
think you could kill me
with something like this?
No, I didn't.
You see this?
There's a tiny piece missing.
Just now, I left a bit of my
blade inside you, Captain.
What?!
As for my Bankai's power,
I know I explained it to
you before, right?
Well sorry,
but I lied about it.
It doesn't extend
as long as I said.
Nor does it extend as
fast as I told you.
However...
When it extends and
contracts, It turns to
dust for just an instant.
Also,
Inside the blade, there is a
powerful poison that dissolves
and destroys cells rapidly.
Tch!
From the look on your face,
I see you understand.
When I was pulling my sword
back out of your chest,
I left a fragment of my blade
inside of your heart.
You see, that tiny chunk of
metal didn't turn to dust.
Gin!
If you want to say something,
I suggest you say it quickly.
But no matter what you say,
you're going to die very soon.
Kill'em,
Kamishininoyari.
Gin! Damn you!
You'll die with a hole
through your heart.
Isn't that what you wanted?
Huh?
Gin...
Gin!
[panting]
It's over... It's over now.
[explosion]
Yaahhh!!
Whoa! What is that?!
I have no idea!
It's really hopeless!
We're all going to die!!
Hold on!
Keep it together!
What could it be!!?
Heck if I know!
All I do know is it's
something really bad!!
I always win, Gin.
Even without it being
inside me, that Hogyoku
that you took from me,
Still belongs to me.
What the hell's happening?!
He's the one!
[Gin]
He's in charge,
he's the boss.
So... I'll kill him!
[Gin]
If tomorrow, you were to
turn into a snake and you
began devouring humans,
If with the same mouth,
you told me you loved me,
Would I still be able
to say "I love you" the
same way I do today?