[theme music]
[police siren]
-A cockatiel that's cursed?
-Uh huh.
All of the people that
have owned this bird
have got into these really
terrible situations and died.
-Wow.
Are you serious?
That's not a good sign.
-Hey, [? shegale, ?]
you want to take him?
-So please, tell me.
Just how stupid
do I look to you?
Here's an idea.
Why don't you set him free
or dump him someplace?
-Well, that would be too cruel.
-Well, how about you,
Chad, what do you say?
Isn't he cute?
-Hey, knock it off.
You know Chad's got a
weakness for cute things.
[screech]
-Ah!
-Whoa!
-We shall continue it.
We shall continue
our quest to devour.
In order to fill the
emptiness of our existence,
we must continue our neverending
quest to hunt them down.
And above all, it is the
spirit of a soul reaper
that is most delicious.
Once you have tasted it,
you will never forget it.
You will crave it always.
[groaning]
-Ah!
-We-- Ch, Ch, Chad?
-Yeah, are you all right, buddy?
-Yeah, I think I'm OK.
-You're OK?
Then how come you're
bleeding, bro?
-Thank you so much
for saving me.
-Hm?
-Hello there, my name
is Yuichi Shibata.
So what's your name, mister?
-What?
Did you hear that?
That, that bird is talking
just like a real person.
-Yeah, I heard it.
It is cursed.
-I'd really like to
know your name, mister.
-Sado Yasutora.
I'm 15 years old.
-Check it out.
Chad's interested in the bird.
-Jeez, there's not even a
trace of that burn left.
It's nearly healed
in just one day.
-Don't be so surprised.
I got the best grades
in my Kido class,
and I have a talent for it.
Healing your wound was easy.
-You got graded?
So what then?
There's a school
for soul reapers?
-Huh?
You could call it that.
Tell me, how do I
drink from this thing?
-Uh, you got to
poke a hole in it.
You just use the sharp
end of your straw.
-What straw?
-So, you're together again.
-Huh?
-Uh huh, you two
seem pretty chummy.
-Mizuiro, shut up.
Come on, does it really look
to you like we're chummy?
-Maybe.
Well, to be honest, you two
do appear to be pretty close.
But people are going to talk,
and if they talk enough,
everyone will think
that you're an item.
-Whatever.
If I really cared about
what people think,
then I guess I would have dyed
my hair black a long time ago.
-Yeah, that's true.
-So this is the straw.
It's short.
But now I have to know,
where do I poke it?
-Hi there.
How you doing?
-Why, hello there.
You're, um, Mizuiro?
-That's me.
I guess we haven't been
properly introduced.
I'm Mizuiro Kojima
I really like--
-Picking up chicks.
-Huh?
Ichigo, that's not cool.
-Watch it-- he may look like a
dork, but he's a real player.
Seriously.
-Cut it out!
You'll permanently
damage my reputation.
Besides, Ichigo, you know older
women are really more my style.
-Like I said Rukia,
watch this one.
-Huh?
[grunting]
-Eh, just forget it.
-What's this, Rukia Kuchiki,
the hot transfer student,
is here with you guys?
How did that happen?
-Ichigo picked her up.
He's the one who
brought her here.
-Huh?
I did not.
-Ichigo did?
Ha, ha, what a guy.
Good job.
-Well, I guess.
It's really no big deal.
-Huh?
Greetings.
I'm Keigo Asano.
Welcome, lovely lady, to
this garden of manliness.
-Uh, hello.
-Yeah!
Lunch party, right
here, right now!
-So party noodles and juice?
-Shut up!
It's the feeling that counts.
-So, Rukia, if you find
yourself needing anything,
you just call on me.
I'm here for you.
-Oh?
Great!
Open this.
-No prob.
Your wish is my command.
Huh?
-Hey, Chad.
-Hm.
-So Chad, what's
with the bandages?
-Whoa, you got hurt.
How?
What happened to you?
-I had a mishap.
A steel beam fell on my head.
-A steel beam, for real?
-My hand got hurt when a
motorcycle ran into me.
The rider that hit me
got banged up pretty bad.
The force of the collision threw
him off and he was knocked out,
so I picked the guy up and
carried him to the hospital.
-Well no wonder you
were late to school.
-The only thing
I wonder about is
what exactly is
your body made of?
-Hey, so where did
you get that bird?
-My name's Yuichi Shibata.
It's nice to meet you.
What's your name?
-That is amazing!
I mean, the way this bird
can talk is phenomenal.
My name's Keigo Asano.
Keigo Asano, can you say that?
-So Chad, just where
did you get this bird?
-Someone gave me him.
-Hold it, there you
go again, getting lazy
and cutting your story short.
Come on!
That's a bad habit
you have, Chad.
Now explain.
Spill it.
-That was the whole story.
-There you go, just
like you usually do.
You never share the details--
-Don't worry.
You're right, there is
something in that bird,
but I don't think it's evil.
It's probably just
a lonely soul,
you know, one that
didn't have many friends.
But we can't leave it or
it might become a hollow.
Tonight we need to
perform a Konso.
-Oh, great.
That's just what I need,
another sleepless night.
-It doesn't help to complain.
-Yeah, I know.
RUKIA (THOUGHTS): How odd.
Ichigo was concerned
about the safety of others
and sensed the soul's process.
Maybe he's beginning
to understand
what it means to
be a soul reaper.
-Here you go.
-Oh, thank you.
-I got to tell you, back
in eighth grade, that
was when I first met Chad.
The color of my hair always
got people's attention,
but not in a good way, and
I'd end up in these fights.
Actually, the day I
met Chad, his timing
couldn't have been better.
I was in the middle
of this little scrap.
PUNCHING
These guys really
meant business.
-Hyah!
-Ah!
Ugh.
-Hey!
Who the hell?
Huh?
Ah!
Uh!
Hold on to him!
-Go ahead, [? Ashiba,
?] let him have it!
-Die!
[punching]
-And that was the
day I met Chad.
And Chad never fights
back, no matter
how much people egg him on.
-He's an odd one.
-Yeah.
-This juice tastes good.
-Enjoy.
I'm home.
Move, Ichigo!
Out of the way!
-Hey, what's your hurry?
Where's the fire, Karin?
Hey.
-Welcome home, Ichigo.
-So what's got you
both so worked up?
-An accident.
There was a big car
wreck down at the corner.
-The big car wreck?
-I just told you, four cars!
So you can't take that many?
Well, here's a news flash,
they got to go somewhere.
We can't treat them all
here, we're a small clinic.
Listen, tell your boss this is
a request from Isshin Kurosaki.
He'll find me some hospital
beds that are open, no problem.
Just do it!
-Uh, hey dad.
-Damn stupid idiots, they
wouldn't know a stethoscope
from a cellphone.
-So is there anything I can Do
-No.
Just assume that fetal position
and stay out of the way.
-Dad, we've got this one last
patient that needs treatment.
-Right.
[groans]
-Man, this guy's as
big as they come.
[grunting]
-Ichigo, come here
and get to work.
-You bet.
Uh, Chad.
-Hm?
-Whoa, what a horrible wound.
-So, what happened
to you out there?
This looks like a
pretty nasty burn,
but I think I can help you out.
-I've got this feeling.
-With this wound,
you're going to have
to take it easy for a while.
-That's good.
-Huh?
-I'm fine now.
Thanks for helping.
-What!
You are crazy!
Do you have any idea how
much blood you've lost, son?
[groans]
-I told you.
-Yuzu, Karin, get a
bed ready for him.
-Right.
Time to go to bed, Mr. Giant.
-Did you feel it?
-Of course.
I felt it all the way
in here, and yet I
sense no evil in Chad's bird.
But I sense that Chad's wound--
it really reeks of a hollow.
[groans]
-Uh!
Uh.
-Morning, Ichigo.
Breakfast is ready.
-So, hey, is Karin up yet?
-She didn't want to eat.
She said she's not
feeling so good.
I'm worried.
-Really?
Karin's sick?
That's not like her.
-Ichigo!
-Huh?
-Bad news!
Chad's disappeared
from his room.
He's gone.
[breathing heavily]
-Ichigo!
-Huh?
Rukia.
-So you got any idea
about where he might be?
-No.
You got any info?
-Not yet.
There's no news from the
Soul Society about a hollow,
and I'm not sensing
anything either.
When hollows aren't
chasing souls,
they can hide themselves
between this world and the Soul
Society.
When a hollow is between
those two worlds,
like the one on the left,
it can't be detected.
What that means is that we won't
be able to locate that hollow
and deal with it until it
shows up to attack Chad.
You understand?
You got it?
-I think I can understand those
kindergarten drawings of yours.
-Uh!
-Ugh!
I think I got it.
A hollow's targeting Chad
to gobble up his soul.
But if we wait for it to
show up and attack him,
it'll be too late.
I've got to think.
I got an idea.
We'll use Chad's bird friend.
Can we use that bird
to help us detect
the presence of a hollow?
-No, that's impossible.
[sigh] Hm.
-Ich- igo, what's this
sensation I'm feeling?
-You sure are nice, mister.
-Hm.
-But I need to apologize
to you and help
you understand something.
Please listen?
Everyone who has ever owned
me ends up with bad luck.
-Yeah, I know.
-I'm sorry.
I should have told you.
It's not--
-Don't worry about it.
-So please, mister, forgive me?
And abandon me-- just
leave me here and go.
-Hm.
-Go ahead, mister.
-I can't do that to you.
[chills]
[coughing]
-I- chi- go.
[struggling]
-I have got to tell him.
-He's trying to feel
the soul in that bird.
Even I can't sense such a
weak soul at this distance.
And that human soul is partially
eclipsed by the bird's soul.
To hone in on it
from so far away.
He's done it.
-Oh yeah, I got you!
-Ah, wow.
[grunts]
-He saw it.
Spirit ribbons, rays
of spirit energy.
But only a high level
soul reaper can see those.
Can it be?
Is he really developing into
a soul reaper that quickly?
-I think we somehow ditched him.
-Listen, mister,
you're in danger here.
-Don't worry, I'll be fine.
If nothing else, I should be
sturdy enough to handle this.
Huh?
[creaking]
-Huh?
[crash]
It's found us.
Let's get out of here.
-Oh, mister!
-Don't worry, we're
going to make it.
[shattering glass]
[breathing heavily]
-There!
It's Chad!
Hey, Chad, stop running away!
You need my help, hold up!
-Ichigo!
-Karin?
What are you doing Here
You look really sick.
[thud]
-Uh.
-Karin?
-Ichigo, you need to
get Karin home now
so we know she'll be safe.
I'll handle them.
-Hm?
What, are you kidding me?
I can't just leave you.
-Just do as I say.
I know what would happen
if we leave her here.
You'd be worrying about her
when you fight the hollow,
and that cannot happen
here, no matter what.
Go on, get moving.
Get her home, and
get back here quick.
-Rukia, I hope
you know right now
you don't have the strength
to fight a hollow by yourself.
Please, don't risk
yourself for my sake.
-Don't be stupid.
A veteran soul reaper never
takes any unnecessary chances
with a hollow.
Now, go.
-Right.
[breathing heavily]
-You're going to be
all right, Karin.
You just hold on and
hang in there, OK?
-Ichigo, I came to
tell you, I saw it.
I saw the memories of the
spirit possessing that bird.
Maybe it was because
I'm the closest in age
to that human soul.
His strongest memory flowed
into my mind, and I saw it all.
I saw exactly what he
saw-- his mother's murder.
[screams]
-It happened right
in front of him.
You must tell him that if
he goes to the other side,
she'll be there.
You've got to help
that poor boy!
Please do it!
Don't let him be alone anymore.
All the terrible pain
he's had, it needs to end.
[breathing heavily]
-Damn!
I can't even catch up with him!
This Gigai I have is
worthless, I can't even fly!
Next time I get
a temporary body,
I'll make those R&D imbeciles
give me one stronger than this!
This Gigai's legs
can barely run,
and its heart and lungs
are slowing me down.
This is bad.
[breathing heavily]
[grunt]
-You smell good.
You smell wonderful, delicious.
Time to eat your soul!
-Uh!
Uh.
-So you're still alive.
You're tougher than
I thought, and you
can see me quite clearly.
That makes me curious.
Just who are you?
-Uh!
-Ah!
-Heh, uh!
Ruler, the mask of
blood and flesh,
all things of the
universe that fly.
That which takes-- ah!
In the name of truth
and temperance,
dig your claws into the
wall of [inaudible] dreams!
[inaudible] 33, kale fire crash!
[explosion]
-I did it.
I got my powers back.
Huh?
Ah!
[explosion]
-What's going on?
Hear that?
-It's attacking her.
-Hm?
-It's that young lady who
was chasing us before.
The monster is
attacking her right now.
It's going to hurt
her really bad.
-You, just stay here.
I got to do.
-What are you going to do?
-I'm going to help her.
-Wait!
Please!
Don't go, it's
just too dangerous.
-Hm.
-No, don't.
Don't do it!
Don't go!
You don't understand.
Wait.
It's not me I'm worried
about, it's you.
I really don't care what happens
to me, but you're nice, mister.
It's just that I
don't want to see
you get hurt like
all the others!
He's a monster, and you won't
even be able to see him!
He will kill you!
Don't do it!
No, please, stop!
He'll get you, too!
Don't go!
-Oh, no.
My spell, it didn't
even hurt him!
-Heh, heh, heh, I see.
So that's what you are.
I know that spell, it's
a soul reaper's spell.
But yours was so weak it
had no bite to it-- too bad.
-Uh!
It's just as I thought.
My Kido hasn't
recovered its force.
My spell has no effect.
-My, my, a tender little
soul who's lost her power.
Mm, and you do
smell so delicious.
This is bringing back
such wonderful memories.
You see, I've already
had the pleasure
of devouring two
other soul reapers who
tried to help this boy pass
on to the Soul Society.
And I assure you, they
were mighty good eating.
-The boy?
You mean the human soul
that's in that bird?
-That's right.
-What's your problem?
Why is it you've pursued this
poor kid so relentlessly?
Tell me why!
-I might be more inclined
to give you an answer
if you were to let me
have a little nibble.
-You hollow scum.
[evil laughter]
[crying]
-Don't worry, Karin.
-You've got to tell that
boy, if he passes on
he'll be able to see his mother!
You just have to let
that poor boy know.
Don't let that boy
be alone anymore.
Please don't let that happen.
He deserves to be at peace.
[crying]
THEME SONG: Nobody
knows who I really am.
I never felt this empty before.
And if I ever need
someone, I'd come along.
Who's going to comfort
me and keep me strong?
[singing in japanese]
-Ichigo's really learning how
to win friends and influence
hollows.
And Rukia's still test
driving her new Gigai,
so she's mixing it up, too.
But how are they going to hand
this hollow hooligan his hat
and give him a big show?
-Hey, bucket head, you
better get back to your store
and make sure that licorice
root shipment came in.
We're out of here.