[theme music]
NARRATOR: Soul Reapers,
the spiritual guardians
to the world of the living.
Their job is to maintain the
balance between the myriad
of good and evil souls
that fill this world.
Sosuke Aizen, who
betrayed the Soul Society
and left the Seireitei in chaos,
has set his plan into motion.
Arrancars have arrived
in Karakura Town.
Using the Hogyoku, Aizen
has created these Arrancars
by shattering the boundary
between Soul Reapers
and Hollows.
The life and death struggle
between the Arrancer Edrad
and Ikkaku Madarame,
third seat of Squad 11,
was particularly fierce.
-Awaken Volcanica.
-Now, watch carefully,
my block-headed friend.
Don't tell anybody
you saw me doing this.
Bankai.
NARRATOR: In order to fight
Edrad's powerful Zanpakuto,
Volcanica, Ikkaku was forced
to use his hidden Bankai,
the massive blade
Ryumon Hozukimaru.
-An impressive display.
-You can decide
if it's effective
or not after I use it to
cut off your ugly head.
Hozukimaru is finally awaken.
He's such a slow starter.
He's usually asleep
when I use my Bankai,
and he takes his own
sweet time getting up.
I can monitor his progress
by watching the dragon slowly
light up on the blade.
When it's completely red, his
power will be at full strength.
And when that happens, I
can start cutting you up
like a turkey on a platter.
NARRATOR: At the end of
a titanic clash of power,
Ikkaku, though badly
injured, finally managed
to defeat Edrad.
-Rukia.
[panting]
-Toshiro.
He's in trouble.
-Rangiku.
-Hm.
-Damn.
-So is that all that a
captain's Bankai can do?
What a disappointment.
You're really quite pathetic.
-I'm not done.
-Got to admit that
thing's pretty fast,
considering how
big it is, brother.
Not very effective.
-Shut up, will you?
[groaning]
[laugh]
-Damn it.
--[laughing] Don't tell
me that's all you've got.
That's the best
you Bankai can do?
How did a loser like you
ever get to be lieutenant?
Guess the 13 Court Guards
squads aren't that great.
-This fight's not over.
-It's not going very well, sir.
Hitsugaya and his squad are all
facing very powerful opponents.
-Damn it.
Those Arrancars are a
lot more of a problem
than we thought they'd be.
-At this rate, they'll--
-I'm aware.
We need that authorization.
[whimpering]
URURU: Danger.
Danger.
-Oh no.
Renji's in trouble up there.
-Looks like he's
having a tough time.
-Not good.
-What do we do?
-I have absolutely no idea.
-What's going on up there?
It looks like he's
getting his butt kicked.
-So what's your
plan now, brother?
Well, if you don't want to make
a move, how about I go first?
KURODO: What's the
matter, brother?
-Think you're smart, huh.
-What the?
What is that?
RIRIN: Now's your chance.
-Huh?
-I used my powers
to make an illusion.
Then Kurodo transformed
to look like you.
And now, Noba's teleporting him
around to attack the Arrancar.
-Hey, I'm over here.
-Stop it now.
There's no way those
attacks will work on him.
You're in danger.
-Don't worry.
We'll handle this.
Noba.
Kurodo.
-Kurodo, ready.
-You think you can take me on?
You brat, got you.
[scream]
-Ririn!
-Oh no.
Kurodo!
Ririn!
Noba!
-Did you really think
that you could defeat me
with tricks like that?
-Everyone's getting the
snot kicked out of them.
Come on.
Huh?
Ururu?
Why are you awake?
I thought I told
you to go to bed.
Huh?
Wait a minute, the Arrancar's
strange spiritual pressure
is affecting her.
What are you-- no!
Ururu!
-If you're done
playing games, what
do you say we finish our
business here, brother?
-What the hell?
Where did that kid come from?
-Danger.
You are a threat,
a danger to us.
You are an enemy, and
enemies must be eliminated.
-I don't believe this.
-Damn.
You passed!
You dare put your hands on me.
Now, you'll pay.
No one attacks me and
lives to tell about it.
Impale Del Toro.
You want to test me?
Well, this is what happens
when an Arrancar releases
his Zanpakuto, brother.
-You bastard.
-No!
-Run for it.
Get out of here.
-OK.
Got it.
You honestly think you
can stop me, brother?
We'll see.
-Save yourself, moocher.
[laughing]
-Before I finish you off,
allow me to tell you my name.
I'm Arrancar number
15, Yylfordt Granz.
[thunder]
KOUFANG (VOICEOVER): So
Yylfordt has released his power.
Well, that means
one of two things.
Either he lost interest and
decided to wrap things up,
or he was injured from an
unexpected counterattack
and had no choice.
Hm, I doubt that happened.
Pathetic.
-It's not over yet.
-Hm.
Whipping your tail at me.
Such a desperate move, really.
Is that the best you
can come up with?
This is so disappointing.
I can see your ice flower
starting to come apart.
-Yeah.
What about it?
-Temper, young man.
I know something
about your powers.
As that flower behind
you disintegrates,
it serves as a countdown to when
your Bankai's power runs out.
I'm correct.
Aren't I?
You're still young.
Your Bankai has yet
to fully developed.
Bankai requires enormous
amounts of spirit energy.
And even though
you're a captain,
it must be difficult to
remain in Bankai mode
for long periods of time.
So it's remarkable that you've
maintain it even this long.
But now, your original
12 petals have
been reduced to just three.
And when they have
all withered away,
your Bankai will have
completely disappeared.
At that point, you will
be powerless against me.
It would be easier for
me to wait and defeat you
when you're weak and
your Bankai is gone.
But it would be
disrespectful of me
to treat a captain
in that manner.
So I'll crush you now
while we are still
able to fully engage each other.
That is the sporting
thing to do.
Awaken Snip Tijereta.
[gasp]
-Huh.
[groaning]
-Since you're going
to die, I suppose
I should tell you my full name.
I'm known as Arrancar
11, Shawlong Koufang.
Please accept my final
respects, little captain.
-Hm.
Exactly the kind of response
I'd expect from a captain.
I admire your
courage in facing me,
despite the obvious
difference in our powers.
Honorable.
-You say your name
is Shawlong Koufang.
I want to ask you something.
I understand you're also
known as Arrancar number 11,
and every Arrancar has his
own numerical designation.
I'm confused about the
significance of those numbers.
Does it mean that you're
the 11th strongest
Arrancar to be created,
or is it some kind of rank
as in the military?
-Nothing of the sort.
Our numbers refer to the
order in which we were born.
It has nothing to do
with our strength,
but that only goes for any
of the numbers above 10.
You're confused.
Let me explain.
The system Lord Aizen
set up works like this.
When we Hollows are reborn as
Arrancar through the Hogyuko,
we're given a number
from 11 on according
to the order of our birth.
The ranks one through
10 are reserved.
Those of us who turn out to be
exceptionally skilled killers
are assigned a
number from one to 10
by order of their abilities,
strongest to weakest.
Those select 10 are the
Espadas, and their given numbers
are inscribed on their bodies.
They have the authority
to command the rest of us.
Truth is, our powers
don't even register
compared to those
of the Espadas.
So you know the importance
of this offensive, one
of the Espadas has
come here with us.
He has remarkable powers,
a ruthless killer.
Without question, if one
of you has the misfortune
to confront him, that
person's fate is sealed.
You might as well
prepare their grave,
for they have no
hope of survival.
The sixth Espada is
Grimmjow Jaegerjaquez.
-What the hell?
-Hey, are you even
trying, soul reaper.
I don't want to waste
the effort of killing you
when you're not at
maximum strength.
I'm giving you a break, kid.
I'm willing to wait until
you summon your Bankai.
You better do it, or I'll
punch you full of holes
like I did to that
soul reaper over there.
What's the matter?
Too scared to fight.
-You bastard.
Bankai.
-That's more like it.
-Come on.
I can't keep this
up much longer.
RANGIKU (VOICEOVER): Come on.
Hurry.
-So you're still
breathing, are you?
AKON (ON RADIO): Squad 10.
Come in, Lieutenant Matsumoto.
The restriction removal
has been authorized.
Gentei Kaijo is a go.
-Message received.
Captain, Renji, Gentei
Kaijo has been approved.
Go full power.
-It's finally come.
-About damn time.
-What's this?
-Activating Gentei Kaijo.
[theme music]
RIRIN: These Arrancar
are too strong.
KURODO: It's all right.
They can use Gentei Kaijo now.
It's a technique that triggers
a kido bomb containing
huge amounts of compressed
spiritual pressure.
The explosion kills
anything, even Arrancars.
RIRIN: Really?
NOBA: Liar.
RIRIN: I'll believe
anything about now.
[theme music]
HANATARO: Illustrated
guide to soul reapers.
Golden.
-Ahh.
What in the world
did Hanataro do now?
These guys are
seriously pissed off.
Wait a minute.
What am I running for?
Hanataro's a soul reaper.
I've got a real weapon.
Oh yeah?
Well, prepare to experience
Hanataro Yamada's Zanpakuto.
-Kon had a reasonably good plan.
But what he didn't know is
my Zanpakuto, Hisagomaru,
heals the wounds of
anyone it touches.
[screaming]