[theme song]
NARRATOR: In their quest to
rescue Princess Rurichiyo,
Ichigo and Rukia entered
the Soul Society,
where they met fierce
opposition interrupting
Rurichiyo's wedding
to Shu Kannogi.
Captain Amagai joined
Ichigo's group,
and they all searched
for Rurichiyo.
Meanwhile, Lieutenant Izuru Kira
saw Rurichiyo on the Kasumioji
grounds, but he
had his hands full
fighting Third
Seat Makoto Kibune.
Makoto admitted his selfish
and reckless actions
had gotten him ostracized by
the 13 Court Guard Squads.
Angry about his rejection,
he had reached out
to the Kasumioji clan and
became a brutal guardian
of their interests
at a high cost.
And now, he possesses a
supremely powerful bakoto
crafted by the Kasumioji clan.
-I will have more!
I now hold here the
key to great power!
Possessing such absolute power
will force every Soul Reaper
to respect me and
bow down to me!
Look at you, Izuru.
People like you who
have no real ability
yet still get promoted
to Lieutenant.
It's your kind I
exterminate from this world.
Your weakness is a crime.
A sniveling toad
like you doesn't
deserve to have
what you possess.
When the last
captain went berserk,
you couldn't even stop him.
Powerless people like you don't
deserve to stand above me!
Your life's done!
Here's the killing blow!
-Damn it.
You're through!
Nice move, but I'm not done!
You are pathetic.
You don't stand a chance
against my strength.
-What was your motivation
in coming to Squad 3?
Did you think it was the best
way to become more powerful?
You must've known there
were better ways to do that.
-To truly have one's
power recognized,
one must be at a level
where it may be displayed.
-Really?
But that strategy won't work.
Captain Amagai is well aware
of the destructive actions
you've taken.
Even if you kill me
now, you have no future.
-Who needs a future here?
-What?
The Kasumioji clan's
strategy is to use the bakoto
to create a new order.
It's simple.
This bakoto is filled
with enough raw power
to allow me to annihilate
all of Squad 3,
and that's just the beginning.
-That's your goal?
You and the Kasumioji clan?
-Why do you insist
on questioning me?
Truth won't help you
when you're dead.
-[screaming]
-Just give up.
-I can't do that.
How shameless.
When Squad 3 trusted you.
-I can't wait to
kill all of you!
Like I told you before, all of
you are filled with weakness.
I never considered anyone
on Squad 3 to be my equal.
-Really?
Very well then.
You are not worthy
of forgiveness.
Your heart's filled
with nothing but venom.
You will not change.
I can see that.
We are all just
enemies in your way.
Is that it?
-Do you have a point?
-You've deceived
everyone who trusted you.
You say you hate
weakness, yet it's
you who's lost his
sense of honor.
The way you used others
proves you're the weak one.
-Let's see about that.
-[gasp]
-[yelling]
-You sound exhausted.
Better catch your breath.
I must say, I'm surprised
you're still standing.
I'll see to it you never become
the strongest Soul Reaper.
-That's where you're wrong.
-Down here!
-Hado Number 31, Shakkaho!
-But how?
-You've lost all perspective.
Instead of you controlling
the power of the sword,
its power has now taken
complete control of you.
-No.
You're wrong!
-You think you
possess power, but you
don't have true strength.
You were right.
I couldn't stop
Captain Ichimaru.
I was not strong enough.
But I feel responsible
for my squad,
and that gives me
inner strength.
I will risk my own
life to defend them!
[growling]
I'd lose my life before
letting them down!
-Your resolve can't
defeat my power.
I earned this power!
I've sacrificed more
than you ever could!
-Force alone isn't enough!
I'm fighting for a cause!
[yelling]
[grunting]
-What's that?
-The bakoto!
-Oh, I see.
That stuff moving
around covering
your zanpakuto--
that's your bakoto.
And so--
-That was it.
That's what negated the effects
of my Wabisuke's ability.
It appears your
so-called strength
was as big a fraud as you.
-[growling]
-I must admit, my
Wabisuke's attacking force
may not be as strong as yours.
But that's only part of
what makes up one's power.
Zan Ken So Ki, right
action, and a heart
filled with good
intention form true power.
-I will not let this happen!
-Huh?
-[growling]
-What the--
-Makoto!
-You can't win!
Never!
I will win!
-I don't believe
what I'm seeing.
His sword has consumed him.
-Wha-- what the hell?
Hey, wake up!
-Huh?
-[roaring]
-Damn.
-Lieutenant!
-Third Seat Kibune!
-What is this?
-Makoto.
As the lieutenant of
Squad 3, I will stop you.
-[growling]
-Lieutenant Kira, you survived!
-Sir, are you all right?
-I suppose so.
Makoto.
-Lieutenant Kira.
Lieutenant!
-Tell Captain Amagai
what happened here.
-Coordination between all
the squads is going smoothly.
-Very well.
Now, return to your post.
-Yes, ma'am.
SOI FON (VOICEOVER):
Captain Amagai.
His defecting could still
prove to be troublesome.
And as for that
substitute Soul Reaper--
-Sorry.
Move aside.
-Just what are they
trying to achieve?
-You really haven't
changed, Soi Fon.
-Lady Yoruichi.
-You seem confused
by what's happened.
-You're right.
-I have some information
that might help you out.
-Huh?
-Hold it!
Damn you, stop!
-I've got them.
-Huh?
-Forget it.
You're done!
Let Rurichiyo go.
-[groaning]
-Is she all right?
-It's a doll.
-Ichigo!
-How's Rurichiyo?
-It was a fake.
-Not again!
-So where is she?
-Who knows.
But by now, they must have
moved her to another location.
Huh?
What's that?
They're at the arena?
-I see.
Thanks.
-So this Makoto
really was involved
with the Kasumioji clan.
-All this time.
It's just hard to believe.
-It is.
I never thought their clan's
influence extended this far.
-As for him, you three take
Lieutenant Kira to Squad 4.
-Yes sir.
You can count on us.
-So what's your next move?
-Tough call.
This means this isn't just
a matter of the succession
rights anymore.
The bakoto's power overtook
and killed one of my own men.
That's a problem.
-What's that?
What's a problem?
-Huh?
RUKIA (OFFSCREEN): Renji!
-What was t that
brought you here?
-I got this feeling.
I sensed the spiritual
pressure of Izuru fighting,
and I was right to come here.
Now explain this.
Why'd you take so
long to contact me?
Huh?
-I'm surprised you
found us, Lieutenant.
I will fight you if you
plan to arrest them.
-Captain Amagai, wait a minute.
Ichigo and Rukia are
close friends of mine.
[sigh] So you
spoke of a problem.
Was Izuru getting
injured part of it?
-The Third Seat
from Squad 3 became
linked with the Kasumioji clan.
Izuru discovered this fact
and was forced to stop him.
-There's not enough time to sit
here and explain everything,
but a lot of bad
stuff's going on here.
-Huh.
Sounds like you're in the middle
of a real sticky situation.
-Lieutenant Abarai.
Since you consider
yourself a close friend,
would you be willing
to help us out?
-Huh?
-This weapon is evidence
of the Kasumioji clan's
treasonous deeds.
This must be delivered
to Head Captain Yamamoto.
And tell him what
you've just heard.
-I would like to help,
but I don't know.
You'd do a much better job
explaining what's going on.
-That's true, but I think
it's important to get
to the Kasumioji palace
just as soon as possible.
I believe that's going
to be where they're
holding the princess,
and time is running out.
-What makes you think
they've taken her there?
-A few reasons
immediately come to mind.
First, it's their fortified
stronghold, and well defended.
The second reason is that we
already found her there once
before, so they may assume
we crossed it off our list--
that the palace is the last
place we'd think to look.
Another thought.
If Makoto was really
their big trump card--
-Then when they hear
Makoto's been defeated,
they're sure to kill Rurichiyo.
-I see what you mean.
So of course I'll help.
I'll make sure this gets
to the head captain.
-We're counting on you, Renji.
-No worries.
I won't let you down.
-Captain, sir!
We're fully prepared to deploy!
-Wait a little longer.
-But captain, didn't we
already receive orders
to deploy quite
a while ago, sir?
We shouldn't wait.
-You speak the truth.
However-- Yoruichi Shihouin.
-Still full of questions?
Well, I have something
that might help you.
Come on, just hear me out.
-Once the Head Captain gives
the order to not be disturbed,
he means it!
-I know that!
Of course!
And I'm not asking you to
reinvent the wheel here!
-Then what do you expect of me?
-It's just I've
got something here
that he needs to take a look
at, and I need to talk with him!
-In that case,
give me some time.
-Time is something I don't have.
-What is all this commotion?
-Damn.
Getting around them
is going to be hard.
-Now what?
-I thought you
had the plan here.
-Ichigo Kurosaki!
-Huh?
-I'm aware that
you are out there.
Now come out.
-Toshiro.
-I knew that you'd
show up again.
-Please wait, Captain.
I'm asking you to listen
to what we have to say.
-All right.
Maybe all of you should
explain yourselves
in front of the Head Captain.
-Huh?
-Shusuke?
Why you?
-Go!
Out!
Just leave this place to me!
-Are you sure about that?
-Right, thanks.
Let's go, Shu.
[guards yelling]
-I can't just let you pass.
-Lieutenant Matsumoto!
-We don't have time
to explain now.
Just let us get by, please!
-I can't defy my orders.
I wish that I could.
-Go on.
Move it.
I'll handle her.
-Rukia, wait.
-Go, Ichigo!
-All right.
-[growling]
-Stand down, Shusuke.
-I'm sorry, but I can't
do that right now.
-Since that's your
answer, you've
left me no other choice here.
I warn you.
Rain over the frosted
heavens, Hyorinmaru!
-Sever, Raika!
-Now the real battle will start.
-Notice to all.
It has been brought
to my attention
that possible acts
of treason have
been committed by
the Kasumioji clan.
All 13 Court Guard
Squads are hereby
commanded to occupy
the Kasumioji
grounds to search for
and seize any evidence.
-Ho!
-Won't get by me!
Ha!
Oof!
-[groaning]
-Sorry, guys.
Shu, any idea
where Rurichiyo is?
-Uh, there are many
places where she could be,
but I think they might have
taken her to the back tower.
That was one part of the palace
we were never allowed to visit.
-So which way?
-That way.
SHU (VOICEOVER): Rurichiyo.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
Where are you?
[theme song]
RENJI (VOICEOVER): Hey, Izuru.
Are you all right?
IZURU (VOICEOVER): Renji?
What are you doing here?
RENJI (VOICEOVER): When a
buddy like you gets hurt,
I always take the time
to pay him a visit.
[MALE SPEAKER (VOICEOVER):
The real reason you're here
is because you missed deployment
with the rest of your squad.
IZURU (VOICEOVER): Wow.
You're a real pal.
RENJI (VOICEOVER): Shh.