Takaoni!
Ah!
We will finish this now.
Ryusenka!
Kubikiri Orochi!
Ready? Get em' Stark.
He's coming!
I can see that!
Slam! Tengumaru!
Play... Kinshara!
Wha!?
These things are like flames!
There's no end to them!
Ah!
Agh, move around
all you want. I'll
still crush you!
What-?!
[coughs]
Damn it!
Hey Rose!
Can you hear me?
What is it?
I figured it out!
They're not flames!
They're a Cero!
And they're dangerous
when they explode at
close range!
[gasp]
Damn it!
They're not Ceros.
Regular Ceros don't have
enough power to mortally
wound Hollows with the kind
of strength that you possess.
I took my own soul and
tore it into pieces and
I have made those pieces
obey me like partners,
so that now I may
use them as weapons
to destroy you...
These wolf-shaped warheads
are a deadly combination
of both of us...
You see, that is our
Ressureccion, the true power of
Espada Number 1, Coyote Stark
and Lilinette Gingerback...
[howl]
[Coyote & Lilinette]
Let's go.
[panting]
This game's over.
Run, and I'll let
you live.
[spits]
We don't run.
I see.
There's no choice.
I don't like the term
'finishing blow'...
But that's exactly
what this is.
[sharp exhale]
[gasps]
[pained breaths]
[Lilinette]
Stark!
What...
the hell...
is this?
Check it out...
(Small CT pain gasp)
[Lilinette]
Stark, are you all right?!
I'll be fine,
don't worry.
What are you talking about?!
He caught you from behind
and ran you through!
Do us both a favor,
keep quiet.
[Lilinette]
Don't act so tough!
You just took a
major blow!
Don't you think it's about
time we got serious?
Just turn me loose,
I'll show 'em!
The problem is,
we can't overdo it.
You're aware of that, right?
Of course! Stop
being so paranoid!
And you stop being
so reckless!
What sort of move
was that, Captain?
Hiding in the shadows like
a coward doesn't suit you.
I'm surprised that you'd resort
to such a slimy technique.
Kageoni.
[Shunsui]
But I wasn't
hiding anything.
Up until now, Katenkyokotsu
here just wasn't in the
mood to fight seriously.
That's why I get tired
of playing with her.
You see, Katenkyokotsu
is quite mischievous.
She has the power
to turn children's
games into reality.
And the worst part of
the whole thing is She
decides on the rules,
and everyone who enters
the domain of her Spirit
Energy is forced to abide
by those rules...
...Including myself, as well.
In Takaoni, whoever's
on higher ground, wins.
In Kageoni, the person whose
shadow gets stepped on, loses.
Win and you get to live...
Lose, and you end up dead...
It's just as simple as that.
Can't argue with her;
she's too self-centered.
But always doing what she
wants can be exhausting.
Impressive!
You catch on
very quickly!
He's so fast! I'm not sure I
can defeat him, one on one!
[Shunsui]
Takaoni!
I explained this, didn't I?
In Takaoni, the
person on higher
ground always wins!
Whoa!
You'll have to excuse me;
I forgot...
Those wolves are there
to protect you, aren't they?
[Lilinette]
Are you all right, Stark?
Your reaction time could
be a lot faster, you know!
Zip it, kid.
[Lilinette]
Oh yeah? My advice is the
only thing keeping you alive!
I don't need this now!
Hm? Hey, are you talking
to that girl who's always
hanging around you?
Very interesting, that
means she still exists.
Why is that
so important?
If I recall correctly...
You split your soul into pieces.
Those pieces now follow and
obey you, and you use them
as weapons. Is that right?
All of those wolves, then,
are just an extension of you.
It appears you've
been following along.
So let me ask
you something.
If I take out those
wolves, what happens?
Would it damage
you directly?
Let's not find out.
Or more likely... Does it mean
that girl will disappear?
Who knows?
Come on, play along.
I gave you enough clues
to how my powers work.
I never asked you for
that information.
If I touch the ground,
he'll use his Kageoni on me.
And if I confront him
in the sky, he'll fight
using his Takaoni.
It's a no-win
situation!
[Lilinette]
Listen to me, Stark.
What is it?
I have an idea.
Take his bait.
What are you saying?
You'll see. Don't think about
it, just take my advice.
[frustrated]
Hnh.
So then, What sort of game
should we play next?
You think two men fighting to
the death is just a game?
You're crazy!
You deserve to lose!
Takaoni!
Here he comes!
Guess I win!
Not quite!
Kageoni!
Ready for another round?
Ah!
[Lilinette]
We've got him , Stark!
Lilinette!
Calm down.
I'm still here.
[relieved exhale]
What kind of reaction is that?
You were worried about me,
weren't you?
I told you before, quiet down!
Takaoni!
Damn it!
[Lilinette]
Stark!
Ah!
Bushogoma!
Lilinette, speak up!
[Stark]
Where are you?!
Talk to me!
Lilinette...
I have to admit, that
was extremely close...
I didn't expect your
wolves to be the ones
coming after my shadow.
And for a moment there,
I thought I was about
to be defeated.
But the explosion that wiped
out your partner helped me
understand your powers.
Your wolves could only drag the
things they had bitten, into
their circle of destruction.
As long as there were
objects surrounding me
and offering protection
from their attack,
the wolves would detonate and
disappear before reaching me.
My Bushogoma turned out to
be perfect for providing
that protection.
So.. It's finally just the two
of us facing off.
[Stark]
I'm alone.
Iro... Oni, 'Gray'.
[gasp]
Why do I have to fight
someone this strong?
I always envied the weak.
The souls of all my
friends diminished just
by being in my presence.
I was left alone
and isolated.
In the depths of my loneliness,
we divided our soul into two.
I can't recall what
our original form was.
Maybe it wasn't
like either of us.
In the end, I finally
realized it didn't matter.
It was the only way I could
escape the solitude.
That's why I
envied the weak.
You can stay with the
pack if you're weak.
But since it wasn't possible for
me to be weak, at least I had a
comrade who matched my strength.
[panting]
Thanks to Lilinette's
last attack, he's
moving a lot slower.
My wounds are not as severe,
compared to his. But I can feel
it. Something's not right.
Iro... Oni, 'Gray'.
When he cut me, it felt as if he
went deep enough to slice off my
arm... So why...?
My arm is gray...
He has no gray on
his body.
What's wrong?
Time for you to
make a move.
You have to say the
color you want to cut.
But you won't be
able to cut any other color,
except the one you announce.
Lilinette...
I can still fight!
White!
Ah!
Well I'll be...
You guessed correctly.
In Iro Oni, you can very easily
take damage from the color you
announce. The way it works is...
...The more risky the color is
to you, the more damage you're
able to deal to your opponent.
As it turns out, white is the
color that would cause the
most damage to both of us.
I was planning to let you in
on the secret, bit by bit.
I didn't expect you
to figure out the
rules so quickly.
You really are quite a
difficult opponent.
I can't believe this!
Why do I have to fight
someone this strong?
Black!
[pain]
Eyaaaahhhh...
[Aizen]
Impressive... Are the two
of you responsible for
those piles of Hollows?
[Stark]
No... They just died
on their own.
[Aizen]
I see.
You're new here.
You seem strong.
This is fortunate.
I'm looking
for comrades.
What a coincidence.
So are we.
Do you have other comrades
as strong as you?
Come with me,
if you want
to find out.
We accept
your offer.
It appears you won't
die, just from being
in our presence.
Sorry...
...Lord Aizen.
[Stark]
It appears I won't be able
to repay my debt to you.
I'm not alone...
I'm... not alone anymore.
Tell me something...
Do you have a name?
I'm Lilinette.
And what about you,
do you have a name?
You were once me.
I'm Stark.
Stark, you say.
What do we do now?
We can do
anything.
Well then,
where should
we go?
Anywhere.
We're both together now...
...forever...
Good work,
Captain Kyoraku.
Mm. I'm glad
you're both safe.
You haven't changed at all.
Hm?
You still tend to ignore
the basic code of honor...
...like interfering
with an ally's battle.
Heh.
Only amateurs would give
up a victory for the
sake of a code of honor.
As a Captain, I can't
afford such luxury.
There's rarely a
clear-cut determination
of a good side and a bad
side in these battles.
It's hard to pinpoint who
caused what, exactly.
Once war breaks out...
...both sides
become evil.
Smash! Hagurotonbo!
Butcher Them!
Kubikiriororchi!
Did we
get her?
Not yet.
She's not gonna
give up.
[Toshiro]
Bankai!
Daiguren
Hyorinmaru!
La Gota!
Ah!
Cascada!
Ryusenka!
Tch.
Huuahh!
Heeahh!
Stop, that's enough...
...Gin.
We will finish this now.
Excuse me?
Uh!
[gasps]
Lord Aizen...
What is it?
[gasp]
I'm done with you.
Based on your performance...
It appears you're not strong
enough to fight for me.
Gin. Kaname. Time to go.
No world is without sacrifices.
Doesn't he realize this?
The sea of blood covered in ashes.
We refer to this hell as the world.