[theme music]
NARRATOR: In order
to save Orihime,
who was kidnapped by Sosuke
Aizen, Ichigo and his friends
snuck into Hueco Mundo,
the realm of the Hollows,
and infiltrated Aizen's
fortress, Las Noches.
Upon entering the fortress,
they are engaged in battle
by some of the Aizen's
most powerful Arrancars.
[gasp]
-Well, well.
At the head of
the pack, are you?
-Devour her, Glotoneria!
[gasp]
[chuckling]
[shout]
-I was simply toying
with you, seeing
how long you would be
fooled by my little charade.
-I'll kick your ass!
Now roar, Zabimaru!
NARRATOR:
Unexpectedly, Ulquiorra
appears before Ichigo, who is
on his way to help his friends.
Ichigo attempts to avoid an
altercation with Ulquiorra
in order to rush to Rukia's aid,
but the fight is inevitable.
-You kidnapped her
and brought her here!
I suspected that she
didn't come to Hueco
Mundo of her own free will.
I'm going at this guy
with everything I've got!
Bankai!
-A Bankai, is it?
[growl]
[gasp]
[shout]
[grunt]
[shouting]
ULQUIORRA (VOICEOVER):
What is that form?
And how can he possess
such spirit energy?
It's as if he's one of us.
[gasp]
[shouting]
-It's over.
Getsuga Tensho!
[shout]
ULQUIORRA (VOICEOVER):
Impossible.
[panting]
NEL: Ichigo!
-Nel?
-Ichigo!
[crying]
[grunt]
I thought you were going to die!
Don't die!
-Who knows?
I still might.
-Look at you, a
complete physical wreck.
But you still used your
powers to fight with!
Stop that!
That's nutty crazy!
I was really worried about you.
Yeah, that's the thing,
because you were fighting,
and I was scared.
So don't-- don't
do that anymore.
Don't do it!
And stop--
-Sorry, Nel.
I guess that you
got pretty scared.
-Oh, Ichigo!
-Easy.
Gah!
Your snot, make it stop!
It's touching me!
-Huh?
-Come on, now, that's gross.
-Back it goes.
-Ugh.
How nice.
All right.
Let's go.
-Are you all right, Ichigo?
-Yeah, I'm OK.
We can't waste any more
time hanging around here.
[gasp]
What?
How?
-Impressive.
Even using both my hands,
I couldn't stop it.
I'm quite surprised.
Was that it?
Finished, Ichigo?
-[gasp] I can't--
-Hmph.
Yes, it would
appear that it was.
[gasp]
How unfortunate.
ICHIGO: Nel!
Are you all right?
Nel!
Try to hold on.
I'm gonna find you
somewhere that's safe.
You can rest.
[shout]
[groaning]
-I'm impressed by
your reaction time.
You used your mask
to block my Cero.
But this time, it
shattered instantaneously.
I am afraid that you won't be
able to bring it out again.
You've nothing left
to hold me off.
It's time to give up.
[thump]
[gasp]
-I'll never surrender.
You're the leader of
the Espada, aren't you?
So it's very simple.
What I have to do is
defeat you in battle.
Then this war is
as good as over.
-I see.
It looks as if you
have been misinformed.
[gasp]
-You're the fourth.
-Correct.
Espada number four,
Ulquiorra Cifer.
Of all the Espada, my
power is ranked fourth.
[gasp]
Ichigo Kurosaki, it's pointless.
You cannot defeat me.
Even if you were lucky
enough to succeed,
there are three
Espada ranked above me
who are much stronger than I.
Try as many times as you like.
[groaning]
The results will
always be the same.
It appears that I have
grossly overestimated you.
Your development didn't
meet my expectations.
This is the end, then.
If you can still move
in that condition,
leave Hueco Mundo immediately.
If you can't move,
then die there.
No matter what, your path
ends here, Soul Reaper.
[gasp]
-Ichigo?
It can't be true.
First Rukia, and
now it's Ichigo.
It can't be.
[rattling]
-Ulquio--
LOLY: Look at that.
The princess is all by herself.
[laughter]
(SING-SONG) Oh, Orihime.
Let's play a little game.
SZAYELAPPORO: I knew
you'd react that way.
I must say, you
really are amusing.
But I've told you
several times now,
you can't damage an Espada
with just your Shikai.
Try to get that
through your head.
[gasp]
RENJI: Shut your damn mouth!
You make me sick.
Outta the way!
[laugh]
[shout]
-Just as I expected.
Simple technique.
-But I got you to move.
[gasp]
-You mean you hadn't
noticed it yet?
I suppose you were
expecting that too.
Hah.
It doesn't matter If
I can't use my Bankai.
It doesn't matter
what information
you've gathered on it.
Zabimaru is an extension
of my arms and legs.
Just 'cause you
can read my moves
doesn't mean I'm done,
not by a long shot.
In fact, this battle
has barely begun!
You're not getting away.
Huh?
[shout]
-How unfortunate that you
lack the basic elements
of intelligence.
I've already told
you that I received
all of your data and statistics.
Now what else?
Your attack speed's obviously
a basic part of your technique
and is extremely predictable.
[gasp]
[shouting]
-Ah.
Hmph.
Let's consider all
the facts, shall we?
You no longer have a
way to win or to escape.
-What are you saying?
-Simple, really.
Once you've played your best
hand, then what's left to play?
[shouting]
-Lumina, Lumina, give it to me!
Not fair, not fair!
Give it to me.
I want--
[shouting]
SZAYELAPPORO: I'm tired of this.
-What was that?
-I told you, I've
grown tired of this.
Perhaps you'd like me to speak
slower, so you can understand?
Your Zanpakuto is a power type.
There's absolutely nothing
special about it, is there?
In fact, the manner in
which it changes forms
is extremely rudimentary.
I know it's rude of
me to point this out,
but whatever interest it
once held has long faded.
Hmph.
Why don't we finish this?
[wailing]
-[gasp] What the?
-They're the Fracciones.
Espadas are given Arrancars that
have the rank of 11th and lower
to be our direct
subordinates, and they
serve as living testaments
to our ultimate supremacy
as Espadas.
Those are Fracciones.
Some of the Espadas
have only one,
while there are
others who have many.
Not to brag, but my eight
Fracciones are a bit unique.
They were originally
Hollows that I modified.
Lord Aizen was kind
enough to use his power
to turn them into Arrancars.
-So what?
[shout]
[growling]
-Wouldn't you agree that the
time for all this chit-chat
is over?
Why don't we be
realistic about this?
Your incompetence
is definitive proof
that you are not worthy
to fight me directly.
[growling]
Say goodbye.
The show is over.
[shout]
-You bastard!
Get your hands off me!
[laughter]
-I want no one to interfere.
Of course, I'm not going
to interfere, either.
Do try your best to make our
epilogue exciting, won't you?
[laughing]
[gasp]
-(SING-SONG) Huh.
-Well, look at this.
You live in a fancy
room, don'tcha?
-Yeah.
-Nice.
-Yeah, it's a very nice room.
I guess Lord Aizen must
really like you a lot.
-Isn't that the truth, princess?
You're the girl of the hour.
Everybody is talking about you.
You must be important.
It's amazing that five people
came to save their princess.
-(VOICE TREMBLING) No!
-Tell me, Princess
Orihime, do you
think that everybody should
kneel down to worship you?
-Hah, loser.
-Think you're special?
Think you deserve
all this attention?
Huh?
ORIHIME: I don't think that.
LOLY: I'm sorry, what was that?
You'll have to
speak up, princess.
I couldn't hear what you said.
-I don't think that!
-[laughing] You hear that?
You hear what she's saying?
She says she doesn't think that.
-How shocking.
[gasp]
-Let me give you a
little piece of advice.
Miss Orihime, princess.
Don't start thinking
you're so special.
You're nothing but a human.
You don't deserve the honor
of being at Lord Aizen's side.
What?
Nothing to say?
-What a pain in the ass.
-Want to beat her up?
-Sounds good to me.
We'll stop when the
baby starts crying.
-[laughing] An excellent idea.
Show us how ugly you
are when you cry.
Show us your ugly face!
[grunting]
[quizzical grunting]
[pained shouting]
-Oh?
I may have spoken too soon.
You're just full of
surprises, aren't you?
I didn't think you'd
last this long.
[pained shouting]
SZAYELAPPORO: You've created
a troublesome situation
for yourself.
Once he's gotten into
a state like this,
it's not easy stopping him.
[shouting]
How unfortunate.
It appears I may not
be able to collect
your body in its pristine form.
A shame.
-Huh?
[shouting]
[gasping]
URYU: It's unfortunate
for you that when
you had this
building constructed,
you didn't consider having
it made of sekkiseki.
I could sense your spiritual
pressure through three walls.
What's wrong?
You look like you've taken
quite a beating, Renji Abarai.
-Is that you?
Uryu!
[theme music]
SZAYELAPPORO: Occasionally,
your spiritual pressure
increases momentarily.
How does that work, Soul Reaper?
RENJI: It's pure willpower!
SZAYELAPPORO: [sigh] The kind
of response unintelligent people
always give.
RENJI: What was that?
URYU: I hate to admit it,
Renji, but the guy's right.
RENJI: Back me up!