So...
Is this Karakura
Town?
Pretty cool, huh?
Heh.
I figured why not choose an environment
that you're used to fighting in.
Aren't you happy? Now you
can fight me one-on-one.
Sorry guys. Make that
two-against-one.
Uryu, you really
ready to fight?
Rukia treated me. I'm not fully
recovered, but I'll be fine.
Listen, I- I think I might
owe you an apology, Ichigo.
Huh?
Remember right after we returned from
saving Rukia in the Soul Society?
That was when you first told
us about the Combat Pass.
It's also when I started thinking
that another Substitute Soul Reaper
must have existed before you. And
that he had probably gone missing.
If that other Soul Reaper was alive,
they should have told you that he was,
and if he was dead, they should
have told you why he died.
But the fact is, they told you nothing.
Which probably means even
the Soul Society didn't
know what happened to him.
I should've told you this
when I thought of it.
You're right.
You should've!
Ahh!
C'mon! What the hell?!
That's ancient history.
You need to stop dwelling on all the stuff
that happened way back in the past.
It's idiotic!
(Sigh) Yeah, like you don't
dwell on things forever.
You say something?
Forget it...
Then let's do this! And
don't get in my way!
I'm just concerned. What
if there is a reason that
the Soul Society withheld
this information from us.
(Chuckle)
That's...
...Impossible!
Aw man...
Looks like nobody else
is out yet.
They must all be taking
their sweet time.
How boring. Guess I'm
gonna head back home.
Oh no you're not!
We made a promise that we would come
together and we would leave together!
If you leave early, the Head Captain will
be angry with you again, you got it?
Hey! Don't pull my ear!
That hurts!
I don't know how he pulled
this off, but he's found
a way to use his power to
trap me in this place.
(Chuckle) What are
you swinging at?
Is that your best attempt to locate me?
I'd say you're just unwilling to power up
to your full strength
unless I say something
drastic like "Too bad your
friend's about to die."
(Sigh)
Looks like I'm the one who got
stuck with the annoying guy.
Hm?
All right!
Show yourself! Where
are you?!
Oh no! Stop!
Hey! Don't!
Don't think you can-
Tempt me with these
plushie dolls of yours!
This is way too easy. Maybe
I should just shoot her.
You know...
I'm not sure this is the best time
for you to be gazing at the moon.
I was thinking to myself that it's
a good thing I'm fighting you.
Why's that?
Because Ichigo
Kurosaki's too soft.
Right now he is fueled with anger
for you people. But knowing him
as well as I do, it's doubtful
that he would have the will to
kill you when the
time comes.
Oh? So I get the feeling you're implying
you're the right man for the job?
I truly despise the way
that you fight.
You toy with your opponent's heart by
robbing the bonds they share, and use them
to do your dirty work.
It's too despicable
to allow.
You and your
cowardice.
Your punishment is death.
I shall cut you down
before you even have the
chance to touch me.
Ahh!
Hey you! Quit runnin'
ya bastard!
What was that?! No matter
how I figure it, that
single punch of his
shouldn't have been able to
knock down a tree
that large?
It didn't even look like it had
enough force to break a wooden sword!
But he's smashing everything
with just one punch!
How's a kid like
him doing that?
(Jumping Grunt)
Ahh!
(Painful Scream)
(Painful Sigh)
Ha! I busted your shoulder, didn't I?
Too bad for you, huh?
Huh?
(Painful Moan)
(Gasp)
Ahh!
(Painful Moan)
What the hell was that? That bastard just
popped his shoulder back into place by just
flexing his muscles! What
kind of freak is this guy?!
Hey! What's the matter, kid?
Something got you a little worried?
I'm not scared of
you, ya jackass!
You gonna attack?
Making the first attack against
a woman isn't my style.
So you're a
gentleman?
Or maybe you're
just narrow-minded.
So have you ever fought a
woman stronger than you?
It's never mattered to me if women are
stronger or not. I won't attack first.
Oh. So you're not just narrow-minded
about women, you're inflexible as well.
What's with that motorcycle
pipe on your chest?
Do you get more powerful
when you rev it up?
Oh this?
I'm surprised. A Soul Reaper
that knows about bikes?
Yeah, kind of.
So you're not going to make
the first attack, huh?
Then you better shut up and get ready. But
I'd draw your sword now if I were you.
I wouldn't be stubborn, or
it might really cost you.
(Engine Revs Up)
(Gasp)
You're about to find out, the dirtier my
"Dirty Boots" get the stronger they become!
And it doesn't just
work on my boots.
Any dirt or mud that happens
to get on the Fullbring
surrounding my body makes
me stronger as well!
This is your last
warning...
Draw your sword!
(Grunt)
Pretty darn quick.
See if you can
keep it up!
I got him!
You're done!
(Gasp)
What?!
I hit him hard! How come he
wasn't knocked completely flat!
Right, I get it.
So where's the
next one? C'mon.
I told you!
I'm about to make you regret
that you ever said that to me!
(Gasp)
(Painful Moan)
I've been training for
over a year to be
prepared to fight someone
the level of Aizen.
It doesn't matter if
you're a man or a woman.
None of you can stand
up to me!
Damn! Guess I figured wrong. I thought
if I defeated her, I'd be able
to get out of this
place.
What else have I got to do? I mean
there's gotta be someway out of here.
You probably can't leave here,
because I'm still alive.
Well now, you've already come to.
You're certainly a tough one.
I may be conscious, but I don't think
I'm going anywhere any time soon.
Now's your chance
to finish me off.
Can that crap,
all right?
Huh?
What's that? It looks
like the sky is folding!
Damn! That means
Yukio was watching us!
He's thinking that since
I haven't defeated you,
he might as well wipe out
this whole dimension
with us in it!
Go on! Hurry up and
kill me!
If one of our Spiritual
Pressures were to disappear,
then this dimension should
open right up instantly!
Quick! Kill me!
I can't do that.
Why not?!
A man who lays a hand on a woman is scum.
I'd rather
die then go through life
such a pathetic man.
(Gasp)
You're coming with me.
We'll force our way out.
That sounds like the
logic of a child.
I thought I was
cynical enough now,
that that kind of talk
wouldn't effect me anymore.
I just wish that someone like
you had been around to save me.
When I needed it
the most...
What are you-
Huh?
Jackie's gone.
How noble, she died
trying to save her enemy.
But, I'm not too sure that her opponent
could've actually survived that.
(Explosion)
Hm?
Oh, hey, good job.
So you finally made it. I was starting
to think you might never find me.
You must've located me by leveling up
from all those traps I put in your way.
You don't seem the least bit tired.
I'm surprised you're not.
You sure talk a lot.
You're pretty violent.
What do you think would've
happened if I'd left a
bomb in the next room.
You could've just
blown yourself up.
Weren't you just
watching?
My Hyorinmaru is a sword that is able
to control ice. I would've frozen any
blast before it
reached me.
A sword of ice, huh?
That's so cool.
I didn't come all this way
to have a chat with you.
Well in that way we have
something in common, don't we.
So you can reset the broken walls and rooms
I destroyed, huh? That's awfully useful.
Didn't you see all I've done? My ability
is this whole dimension that you're in.
So in here, I'm
basically God.
Ah, I see...
You don't understand. As God of
this dimension I can do anything.
For example...
How about that?
You truly are a
god. How impressive...
Why is it...
That you insist on making
fun of my ability?!
You jerk!
So why did you dodge that?!
'Cause you're afraid?
Don't let me dodge it then.
You're holding back.
Of course I am! Shall I show
you what happens if I don't?!
Time for your worst
nightmare!
There's no way for you to escape this room!
Because the next room and the next, all the
walls, the ceiling, and the floors
are all part of my ability!
I've just set all of those
beasts to follow you
wherever you go, forever,
until the life's
crushed out of you!
That's it! Come right at
me so I can kill you!
You Captains are elite snobs who were
raised with a silver spoon in a happy home!
A coddled spoiled elitist
like you will never beat me!
Now I see, you were
abandoned...
You're wrong!
I left them! I was the one who
abandoned my stupid parents!
I was the one who chose to get out!
Don't you
dare talk like you know
anything about me!
I transferred all of my
dad's bank accounts over
to me and destroyed his
life by bankrupting him!
They left me alone all
the time, so I'm self-
taught. And that's what
they get for always
being so busy, and never
taking their child seriously!
It felt great when I'd heard
they'd committed suicide!
Sorry to interrupt your sad
story, but you're wide open.
(pushed grunt)
Damn it!
Uh-oh. You've programmed them to
pursue me until they crush me.
Do you want to shut them down
before they destroy us both?
Ahhh!
(Gasp)
(laughter)
How's that?! You decided
to save me anyway!
Of course, I knew that you would!
You pitied me!
Do not think I
took pity on you...
I have no interest in
your past, but if I were
to kill you now, there's
really no guarantee
that as a result, this dimension and the
other dimensions would disappear...
Since that's the case, how
about I make you a deal?!
(scared gasp)
H-hey! Wait a
second! Hold it!
The deal is, I won't freeze
your arms and your head...
If you shut off your power in the
next five minutes, I won't kill you.
Damn it! No... Never!
I'm not scared!
Ya wimp! You are!
See?! There's enough power in
my punch to pulverize you ass!
That's why your the one
who's scared to death here!
Damn you Soul Reaper! Get
down here and fight!
You flyin' up in the air
like that is cheating!
I'm not flying. I'm
just standing here.
Oh, same difference!
(annoyed sigh)
Without knowing exactly
what your power is,
it's really not that
satisfying to beat you.
So I thought I'd try to
understand your ability first...
But I'm done with that.
So I ask you, do you want
me to slap you like a
brat or to destroy you
like a man. You choose.
That's an easy choice! I've decided
I want to destroy you like a man!
Glad to hear it!
Then let's go!
Mm-Ahh!
(gasp)
Ahh!
(painful grunt)
Damn! The tendons in my
two fingers are torn!
What's even worse is
he smashed Hozukimaru!
Hah! That was a good block!
If I'd hit your
head, it would've split
it open and this fight
would have been
all done!
You're right there,
I'm damn lucky!
That's stupid talk! You're not lucky! I
broke your spear with a single punch!
I'm the lucky
one here!
But if you wanna push
your luck, why don't you
try charging at me again?
You do that and
you'll windup with
a busted skull!
It looks like that punch of yours breaks
any weapon that gets close to you...
I guess that means I'll have
to do this job by hand!
So you're going to take me on with
just your fists?! Bring it on!
You've got it!
Ahh!
(fighting grunts)
What the hell is it with this guy?!
This is impossible!
I know I'm really connected with
my punches. He's gotta feel 'em!
But how is it my hits aren't having
any affect on him at all? Damn!
I may not be breaking bones with each
punch, but he doesn't even look hurt!
(punch grunt)
Huh?!
What was that just now?
I didn't feel anything!
(punching grunt)
(punch grunt)
Oh no! My chances of hitting
the jackpot are going down!
My "Jackpot Knuckle" always allowed me to
make one lucky hit! I've never used it this
many times in a row, so I had
no idea this could even happen!
The odds of hitting the jackpot
go down when it's used too often!
What's wrong?!
Looks like your big punch stopped working.
You worn out already?!
Shut the hell up!
I'm not worn out!
Dammit!
(quivering in pain)
All right! Jackpot!
(powerful grunt)
How'd he?!
I really have to hand it to ya. Your
punches were pretty damn powerful.
But luckily, when you did hit a vital
spot, you didn't do much damage...
Sorry, kid. I'll admit
you may be a lucky guy...
But I'm the luckiest guy in the
Thirteen Court Guard Squads!
What's wrong?
From this distance you
won't be able to cut me.
The fact that you're
waiting where you are,
means you understand
coming any closer would
put you well within
my range.
I must formulate
another plan...
I see you're
quite cautious...
Did that move seem
meaningful to you?
How about this?
I don't believe I should
view either of them
as meaningless acts while
in this situation...
Oh?
Scatter Senbonzakura!
Rukia, how are
things with you?
Well, several animals
ambushed me, but
everything's fine! And
they are all so cute,
and soft, and cuddly!
Uh, what I mean to say
is, all of them are
beautiful works of art!
Rukia...
Y-Yes...
Bring a pink one
back for me.