-Good evening, everyone!
This week's episode
of Spirit Hunter
is brought to you
live from an abandoned
hospital in the
town of Karakura,
where the tortured
screams of the dead
can be heard echoing
through the hall.
-Who knows what
horrifying sights
we'll witness here this evening.
-And now, folks, let's
get in a warm welcome.
This century's premier
spiritualist and messenger
from hell, Mr. Don Kanonji.
[applause]
-The spirits are
always with you.
-Bwahahahaha.
-Huh?
Ichigo, you barely
reacted at all.
Don't you even know
where it's from?
-Uh, Spirit Hunter?
-Yeah, isn't that
show just the best?
Come on then, Ichigo.
Join in with me.
-Banzai!
-Oh hey, Tatski,
what's the matter?
-Let's go already, you
can bwahaha with me.
Now move!
-Yo, Ichigo.
Keigo here.
-And Mizuiro!
-Bwahahaha.
-Meh.
-What do you mean,
you're not going?
It's the best TV show in Japan.
And it's going to
be broadcasting live
from Karakura.
You live in this town, dude.
You'd have to be
dead to miss it.
-Guess that makes me a zombie.
Get lost.
-But I already went to the
trouble of asking Rukia to go.
-Hi, Ichigo.
-Come on, Rukia.
Muahahaha.
-No.
I'd be too embarrassed to do it.
-Oh please, Rukia?
Do it.
Muahaha.
-Geez.
She's becoming quite the
little actress, isn't she?
[crowd chanting]
-And how is everyone tonight?
Hold on to your
seats, my babies.
It's time again to
hear the spirits cry.
[applause]
-So tell us, what do
you think of this place?
Well?
-The stench of the spirit world
hangs in the air around us.
I'd have to say that.
[crowd chanting]
-Bwahahaha!
-And we're cutting
to commercial.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Man, I hate
stupid shows about spirits.
-This way, everyone.
We're about to get started.
Make your way to the spirit
purification location.
-Ichigo?
-I'm sorry for the other day.
-What do you mean?
-It's just that
Tatsuki was telling me
you really can't stand
TV shows like this one.
And I had no idea.
-That's cool.
It's really no big deal.
-Bwahahaha.
-Look at those two.
They know it drives me
nuts, but they do it anyway.
-But you still showed up.
Why is that?
-Oh.
Yeah, well my dad
and my little sister
go out of their minds
for Spirit Hunter.
-And that's why you're here?
-Guess so.
I couldn't just let them
come alone, you know.
-Wow, you've got such
a good heart, Ichigo.
-Why, isn't that normal?
-Uh, oh.
Yeah.
That's normal.
Mmhmm.
Very normal.
-Hey, Orihime, I we're going
to head on without you.
-Oh hey!
Hold on, Tatsuki, wait up!
See you.
-Yeah, sure.
I'm normal.
But what about the
rest of these weirdos?
What's their excuse?
-Ichigo, what's wrong?
-Bwahahaha.
-You, too!
-Hey, what's with
the serious look?
As long as you're here, you
might as well try and have fun.
-Shut up.
I'm always like this.
-Between all of your school
work and your duties as a soul
reaper, you must be exhausted.
And there will be hard
battles on the road ahead.
Use tonight to enjoy
yourself a little.
-What?
Are you--
-By the way, tell me.
What is this festival all about?
-You mean you showed up
here without even knowing?
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
Seriously, you
think there'd really be spirits
in an old deserted hospital
like this one?
-What are you getting at?
-I mean, if they
had been here, you
soul reapers would have helped
them cross over already, right?
-Well, not necessarily.
Jibaku spirits are often
tied to places like this.
Jibaku spirits are ghosts
that dwell within the Earth,
so it's very rare
that soul reapers are
able to pinpoint their location.
There's only one reason a
Jibaku would reveal itself--
when it notices humans are
invading its territory.
[eerie noise]
-What's the matter, Chad?
-Do you guys hear anything?
-Huh?
Come on, Chad, cut it out.
You're giving me the creeps.
-It's just your imagination.
[eerie noise]
-Yeah, right.
My imagination.
-Oh, boy.
I never should have come
out here with you guys.
-Hey, why the long face?
-Nothing.
[eerie noise]
-That's the cry of a Jibaku.
So there is one here.
-Wait a sec, how do you know
that sound's not a hollow?
-There are certain paths along
which hollows come into being.
One path is when
a jibaku spirit,
with its fierce attachment
to the world, is left alone
and becomes a hollow, much
like this spirit here.
-So then he's a--
-A hole on the verge
of becoming a hollow.
A demi-hollow.
[screaming in pain]
-Yeah, well he sure feels
like a hollow to me.
Except that he's not wearing
one of those white masks.
And the hole in his chest
hasn't opened all the way.
-The hole in a
hollow's chest shows
that the heart has
been lost, leaving
nothing but raw instinct.
The white skull-shaped
mask is all that shields
those bared instincts
from the outside world.
Neither are necessary if
the heart is still intact.
Upon death the chain of fate
is severed from the body.
Usually, the spirit waits
for a soul reaper's guidance.
But if they have
regrets in this world,
they become bound to the
source of their pain.
So that means this
demi-hollow's heart
is chained to the hospital.
-This hospital belongs to me!
I'm not giving it up for anyone!
Don't even think about
trying to come in here!
I'm going to be filthy
rich in this place--
-Yeah, well, whatever he is,
he sure sounds like a dumbass.
(ON TV): Coming back
from commercial--
-Oh!
I think the show is
about to get started.
-The spirits are
always with you.
Wahahaha!
(CROWD): Wahahaha!
-Hey, knock it off!
-Don't worry.
It takes months for a spirit
to transform into a hollow.
-Now then, the time has come
once again for Don Kanonji
to take the stage.
-You can feel the excitement
in the air tonight.
TATSUKI (OFFSCREEN): We
don't want the spirit
to become agitated with
this many people around.
We'll do the konso
after the show.
-Yeah, but--
-Spirits go through
so much pain when
they transform into hollows.
They fill the night
with terrible screaming.
I mean, does it look
like that demi-hollow
is suffering to you?
-Huh?
And who the hell are you?
You think you can come in
here and defile my hospital?
You've got some nerve, buddy.
And what's with the
crazy frigging hat?
-My guess is no.
-There, you see.
Unless someone
deliberately messes
with that opening
in his chest, he's
still got another six months
before he becomes a hollow.
[screaming in pain]
-All right, let's send you
over to the other side, baby.
-There it is, folks,
the super spirit
gained an unusual [inaudible]
this early in the game.
-What the hell does
he think he's doing?
-The fool.
All he's doing is speeding
up the creation of a hollow.
-Oh yeah!
[speaking gibberish]
-Get gone!
-Come on, knock it off!
-Hey, who's that guy?
-Security, do your job!
-Over here, we've got to
get you out of your bodies.
-Kill her!
-Let go of me.
[screaming in pain]
-No!
-Get your hands off of me!
Who did that?
-Hello.
-Mr. Hat and Clogs?
-Don't just stand
there like a lump.
Get to work already.
-Right.
-Hey, what's wrong?
-What the hell are
you doing here?
-What?
-Out of the way.
I'll take care of this.
-Hey, stop it!
-Holy moly, Don Kanonji was
just thrown through the air.
-What's wrong with you, kid?
-Well, then, I guess
you can see me, too.
-Of course I can.
I'm the century's
premier spiritualist.
Oh wait, I get it.
You're dead, but you're
a fan, aren't you?
-Don't make me kill you.
[screaming in pain]
-Don't tell me, am I too late?
-He's gone.
-Yeah!
Mission accomplished, baby!
ANNOUNCER: Another
successful soul purification!
-Are you kidding?
-No.
The moment a demi-hollow
becomes a hollow,
it disperses and reforms
as a hollow elsewhere.
But if its heart was
bound to something here
in this hospital--
[crowd chanting]
-Yeah, thank you!
-Look out, Ichigo!
Above you!
[screams]
-What is it?
-A hollow.
I hope you're ready.
-Oh, I feel it.
I feel something that
reeks with the scent
of a super dangerous spirit.
Now I understand, you're that
other spirit's evil lord,
and you've come here
seeking vengeance.
-Nice try, jackass.
-Oh, the pain.
Must devour!
-Hold on.
-Run, boy.
-Huh?
-To wah.
Come on, you bad spirit.
Don Kanonji, the premiere
spiritualist of the century,
is ready!
-How are you?
-What are you doing?
-Kid, why didn't you run?
-Look, you're the one
who should be running.
-Huh?
Me, run?
What are you saying?
[roars]
-Oh, Jesus.
-Just as I thought.
Wonderful.
But he's got his
work cut out for him.
Let's see how he does.
-A golden chance.
ANNOUNCER (OFFSCREEN): What
could this mean, ladies
and gentlemen?
Don Kanonji--
-Oh, I see, so that's how you
plan on fighting this one, huh?
ANNOUNCER (OFFSCREEN): The
glass of the entrance has
been shattered and whole
walls have been destroyed.
Folks, it appears
that Don Kanonji
must be battling against
some unknown force.
-Don't worry about it.
A hollow of that level won't
be a problem for Ichigo.
-But I, uh--
-Best not to make too much
of a fuss at the moment.
Besides, seems as Don Kanonji
has a bit of power himself.
Why don't we let them handle it?
-Wait, why are we
running away, kid?
-Because I heard some
idiot say we should run.
-I know, but I was talking
about you, kid, not me.
Kanonji runs from no one.
-All right.
Can you explain this one to me?
Why should I run away and
you stay behind to fight?
-Well I-- I have to stay,
because-- because after all,
I'm the hero.
-Huh?
-Listen, little man.
Do you have any idea
the ratings my show
pulls in for the network?
-What the hell do I care?
-I'll tell you why you should.
I've got 25%.
One in every four households
is watching my show.
And many of those
views are children.
Those children
watch my adventures
and their hearts are inspired.
They see me stand
up to evil spirits
and learn what true courage is.
So don't you get it?
With all those kids out there
watching my show, running
isn't an option, understand?
-Don Kanonji, you're right.
-You bet I am.
Now let's get out there
and crush that monster.
-Think, you idiot.
You can't do that.
What if the audience
gets mixed up in it?
That thing is going after people
with high levels of spirit
energy like you and me.
There's no question it's
going to come after us,
but we need to fight it in
here so no one in the audience
will get hurt.
-Kid, I am amazed.
For you to have thought
things through like that
in the heat of battle.
Kid.
-He's here.
-I'll devour you!
-Let's do this!
-Not enough room.
Dammit, it's too cramped
to use the [inaudible].
What the hell is this?
I can't frickin' get it off.
I can't get him.
Ah, hold on a second!
-Hey, kid.
Are you all right here?
-You again?
Move it, Kanonji, run!
Dammit.
Hold on!
Kanonji!
-Are you hurt, kid?
-You can't handle them!
Get the hell out of here!
-No.
I know my own strength
and I know the difference
between my enemy's
powers and my own.
I must say, you've made
quite an impression
on me today, putting the
safety of others first.
That's great.
You and I are two of a kind.
What's say we be friends?
-Oh, uh, that's
all right, really.
-Whooooa, Kanonji!
Ultimate attack!
Cannonball.
-Kanonji!
-Even if this body
is obliterated,
so long as I can
serve as a shield
to the children of tomorrow,
I shall carry no regrets
for the life that I've lived.
Good luck.
-Sorry, pal, but
this is the end.
-Well done.
That was great.
Magnificent.
Just magnificent.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Kananji.
Don't get too excited.
-Huh?
Why not, kid?
You just defeated this monster.
This is a time to rejoice.
Huh?
What the?
it can't be.
He's the one who-- What?
-He was a hollow.
With the chain linked
to his soul broken,
the hole in his chest opened.
He became a monster devoid
of conscience, a hollow.
-That-- who?
So then-- no.
So if that's the
case, what is it
I've been doing all this time?
Oh, no.
I'm so ashamed of myself.
[cries]
-Hey, come on.
Quit your crying,
hero, let's go.
Everybody's waiting.
[crowd cheering]
-What's wrong?
You'd better answer them.
It's part of a hero's
duties, isn't it?
-Kid.
ANNOUNCER (OFFSCREEN):
All right,
Don Kananji's soul
purification seems to be over.
-Mission accomplished!
Bwahahahaha.
-Bwahahaha!
[cheering]
-Kid, that was a
magnificent battle.
I stand in awe of your courage,
and I'm amazed by your power.
I hope you'll lend me that
strength in the future.
-Uh-- yeah, sure,
once in awhile.
-Thank you.
From now on, you will
be my number one pupil.
-That's a demotion!
Rukia and I set out to
exterminate some hollows.
-Bwahahahaha... It is I, Don
Kanonji.
But somebody beats us to it.
-Come on repeat after me.
A mysterious figure watches
from the shadows.
-I can't hear
you! One more time. Muahahaha.
Shut up... will ya? I am begging
you, please go home!