[music playing]
[theme music]
NARRATOR: An investigation
was triggered
when the Rukon district
residents started vanishing,
leaving only their
clothing behind.
Squad Nine's Captain, Kensei
Muguruma, and his Lieutenant
Mashiro Kuna, were put in
charge of the operation.
But when their spiritual
pressure disappeared,
it became a major case involving
the 13 Court Guard Squads.
When Shinji Hirako and his
allies arrived on the scene,
they were met by
Kensei and Mashiro.
Shockingly, the two
had somehow transformed
into powerful
Hollow-like beings.
A much different Kensei
launched an attack.
Shinji and the others
fought against him.
But then, all of a sudden,
Hiyori also transformed.
[music playing]
-Hold on a minute.
Kaname.
Tell me.
Why did you do that?
You betrayed him.
Your own captain.
AIZEN: He didn't betray him.
He's actually quite loyal.
As a matter of fact,
Kaname was just
loyally following my orders.
You, of all people,
can understand that.
So please don't hold it
against him Captain Hirako.
-Sosuke.
Sosuke!
What's happening to me?
AIZEN: In the end, I hope
you'll remember one thing.
Any betrayal you
can see is trivial.
What is truly frightening,
and much more lethal,
is the betrayal you cannot see.
Good bye.
I must commend you.
You people have provided
wonderful research material.
Well, unexpected guests.
How very interesting.
-To what do I owe the
honor, Captain Urahara.
Commander Tsukabishi.
-Whoopsie.
Well I guess they found us.
-I'll kill them.
-No, don't.
-But sir.
-Kaname.
I think I made myself clear.
-Yes sir.
Please forgive me insolence.
-Kisuke.
Why'd you come here?
You're such an idiot.
Shinji, what is up
with that hideous mask?
-You don't know the half of it.
-Hm.
-So, Lieutenant Aizen.
-Yes.
-What have you done?
-Nothing.
As you can see, I
happened upon the members
of the Soul Investigation Unit.
They seem to have been
injured in battle.
I was merely trying
to save their lives.
-You bastard.
They'll never buy that.
-Tell me, why are
you lying to us?
-Lying?
Is there a problem with a
lieutenant helping his captain?
-No, but that's
not what I meant.
Injured in battle?
You call these injuries?
You're dancing around the truth.
This is Hollowfication.
-Hm.
First it's the vanishing souls.
Squad members disappearing
like they've been erased.
And now, what you see here,
it can only be one thing.
Hollowfication experiments.
Someone's doing research.
Actually, let's not beat
around the bush, shall we?
We both know who's responsible.
-I see.
Your reputation
surely precedes you.
To tell the truth, I'm
glad you came tonight.
Gin, Kaname, we
fulfilled our objective.
Let's go.
-Stop, Sosuke!
We are not done!
-Clear out of the
way, Captain Urahara!
Hado #88.
Hiryu Gekizoku Shinten Raiho!
[explosions]
-Bakudo #81.
Danku.
[explosions]
-Hm.
It can't be.
My kido, stopped
by a lieutenant.
Using a Danku with
no incantation.
Forgive me.
It seems I let him escape.
-Tessai.
Who is that guy?
[gasping]
-Shinji!
-We must deal with
Sosuke and the others.
But later.
First we need to treat
Captain Hirako and his group.
-Perhaps.
But with the Hollowfication
so far along,
we can't treat him here.
-Captain Urahara, forgive me.
But it appears you know
more about this situation
than I thought.
I can tell by your familiarity
with the term Hollowfication.
If that is the
case, then I assume
you may also know how
to undo all of this.
-Yes, I know.
But the technique is risky.
-I see.
Even so, it is
better than nothing.
We'll have to transport
all eight of them
in their current condition.
We can take them to
Squad Twelve's barracks.
-Huh?
-With the facilities
at the barracks,
we'll have a chance
to save their lives.
-But in their current condition?
They can't move.
How can we?
-We will use time stop and
teleportation techniques.
-But wait.
Those are--
-Yes, I am well aware.
Both of the techniques
are strictly forbidden.
Which is why I suggest
that you close your eyes
and stop listening for
the next few moments.
[music playing]
-Hm.
Huh?
-Uh.
-Hollowfication is
one of the discoveries
I made while I was studying how
to strengthen a Soul Reaper's
soul.
In the process, I created
a peculiar substance
they can break down the boundary
between Hollows and Soul
Reapers.
That's what I'll use to
treat Shinji and the others.
-What is this
substance of yours?
-I call it Hyogoku.
-Hyogoku.
What is the sensation?
Spiritual pressure?
No.
It's different.
It's a presence.
The presence this
stone possesses
is somehow trying to
push me away from it.
What is this thing?
What has Captain
Urahara created?
And Captain Hirako and the rest.
This substance will
save their lives?
-Who knows.
-Huh?
-Like I told you, this
option is the ultimate risk.
The odds that Hyogoku
will return them to normal
is, even by the most optimistic
guess, only about 20%.
-That's all?
-If Lieutenant Aizen was really
behind the vanishing souls
incident, I doubt he even
considered the possibility
that a treatment for
Hollowfication might exist.
This is our only option.
There's no other way.
[music playing]
[nature sounds]
-Huh?
[music playing]
-Captain Urahara.
-Tessai.
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid it didn't work.
I need to step outside
and get some fresh air.
[music playing]
-What's the meaning of this?
-Squad 12 Captain
Kisuke Urahara,
and Kido Corps Commander
Tessai Tsukabishi.
I am here to inform
you that Central 46 has
issued warrants for your arrest.
Come with us, now.
-Will someone tell us
what's going on here?
-No one granted you
permission to speak.
You have been summoned
here for an inquest.
You will only speak in
response to questioning.
Is that understood,
Squad 12 Captain?
-Inquest?
Am I being accused of something?
Pardon me.
-Can you tell us your
whereabouts last night,
shortly after midnight?
-The District Six
forest, in West Fugai.
-Conducting Hollowfication
experiments?
-Now you hold on a minute!
-Who told you such a thing?
-As part of your evil research,
you tested Hollowfication
on the Captain of Squad 5.
As well as seven others in the
Fugai district, isn't that so?
You don't deny it?
-Your reputation
surely proceeds you.
[gasping]
-Who told you that?
-You have no right
to ask questions.
-It was Lieutenant Aizen, right?
-This is your second
warning, Captain.
Speak again and we will
add to your charges.
-He's the one behind
this entire mess.
Listen to me!
We only want out there to
rescue Shinji and the other men.
-When you push your lies that
far, they become comical.
And besides, the
Lieutenant of Squad 5
never left the
seireitei last night.
-But he was--
-We have this sworn statements
of over 124 squad members,
and one captain class member.
That leaves very
little room for doubt.
-Impossible.
-I have new information.
-We searched through the
research wing of Squad 12's
barracks, and
found much evidence
of Hollowfication experiments.
-I have heard enough.
It is time to pass judgment.
Commander Tessai
Tsukabishi, for the crime
of using forbidden
technique, you
will be imprisoned in
Underground Penitentiary 2.
Shugo.
Kisuke Urahara,
Captain of Squad 12,
for conducting research
on banned phenomenon,
and using such to cause injury
to follow squad members,
you are sentenced to
eternal banishment
to the world of the
living, and will
be stripped of
all spirit energy.
Further, the Captain of Squad
5, as well as the other seven
Captain class members,
who were the victims
of your cruel experiments,
will be disposed of as Hollows.
-You can't.
Wait a minute!
Huh?
-Who are you?
You do not have permission
to enter the conference room
while proceedings
are in progress.
Leave immediately,
you impudent fool!
[overlapping side conversations]
-Seize them!
Get the intruder!
-You heard the judge!
-Where are you?
-Is anyone there?
[nature sounds]
-Oh, what a relief.
Thank you, Yoruichi.
-I don't need your thanks.
I'll even hold off
on the ass-kicking
I owe you for not asking
for my help last night.
-Huh?
-I went ahead and brought
all eight of them here.
Oh, and the new gigai prototype
you were working on, too.
Well, go on.
Have at it.
If I know you, from the very
first moment Shinji told you
about this incident, you
imagined the worst case
scenario.
And I bet you also came
up with the best solution
to overcome it.
-Huh?
So you saw right
through me, huh?
So conniving.
-Look who's talking.
-Tessai.
I'm going to need
you to put a time
stop on Shinji and the others.
Then I think you'd
better set up a double,
or even a triple,
barrier around this area.
Over the next 24 hours
we will construct
a total of 10 stealth gigai.
Two for us, and the
rest of them will
be for Shinji and the others.
-And you, Yoruichi?
-Oh, don't you worry about me.
I always stay out of trouble.
-For now we have to lay low, and
work on solving this problem.
I promise we will find a way
to undo the Hollowfication.
[clock ticking]
[music playing]
-Kisuke did say there
were no miscalculations.
That was the biggest
miscalculation of all.
As expected, everything turned
out the worst possible way.
Kisuke got us all to this point.
We owe him big.
Oh, and Sisuke Aizen, too.
[music playing]
-Let's do this.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: Society is awash with
evil, but a warrior for hope
arrives to save the day.
His cape in the wind
is a symbol of justice!
Fly into action, Konso
Cop Karakura-Raizer!
Next time, I may not
want to, but I'll
fight for Karakura town.
Stay tuned!