[theme song]
-(IN HEAD) What's this?
Her spiritual pressure
is out of control.
Ran'Tao.
Hang on.
I think I can use the artifact
to remove the unstable spirit
energy inside you.
I-- I've reached my limit.
We're not safe here.
We'd better go.
KARIYA: You think you
can just walk away?
Now it's your life that's about
to come to an end instead.
-Having problems Uryu?
-Ichigo.
-You again.
-Uryu, are you all right?
-Yeah.
Don't worry about me.
I can take care of myself.
-And Ran'Tao.
You OK?
-Yes, I think I'm all right.
-Both of you, get to
some place safe now.
I'm gonna take care of
Kariya once and for all.
-Given my condition, I suppose
that's out only option.
-Yeah.
Bankai!
Come back here!
Getsuga Tensho!
-Let me help you.
-Thank you.
-Oh.
There you are Uryu.
-Hm?
Orihime?
-I'm so glad you're safe.
I have to admit, I was
worried about you, Uryu.
-Hey, wait.
Where's your artifact, Uryu?
-I'm afraid it disintegrated.
-It disintegrated?
But I thought you said if
anything went wrong with it,
it would mean a huge explosion.
-That's true, but
then I figured out
that my best chance
was to only use
the artifact to amplify reishi.
So as a result, there
was no explosion
when I reached my limit
because it was already empty.
-Yes, that makes sense.
-You understand that?
-Not a word of it.
-Stop it.
The only thing that matter
is that Uryu is safe.
But listen, Uryu, please!
You have to stop going off
on your own all the time.
How can we possibly help
you when you do that?
-I suppose you're right.
-Is everyone all right?
-Yes, we're OK.
-Where is Ichigo?
-He's fighting Kariya.
-Wha?
-Captain, sir.
-Yes.
I know, Lieutenant.
I am not about to let Ichigo
fight this battle on his own.
We're going too.
-Captain.
Wait.
Hm?
And who are you?
URYU: Uh, this is
Ran'Tao, Captain.
-You're Ran'Tao?
The engineer who was exiled?
-You're the one who
originally created the Bounts.
-That's right.
And you're the caption
of Squad 10, aren't you?
-Why do you ask?
-It's not my place, but
if you don't act now,
I fear the Seireitei is doomed.
-What are you talking about?
-I assume you already know that
Kariya has absorbed the Jokai
Crest into his body.
-Yes.
And we're aware of how
powerful the Jokai Crest is.
But our research also
revealed that Kariya's still
going to need more time before
he can use its full power.
In other words, we believe
that he is most likely
trying to buy himself
some more time.
-Yes.
I'm sure you're right.
Unfortunately, the
Jokai Crest power he has
isn't the main problem now.
There's a much
greater danger here.
-Greater than the Jokai Crest?
-Jokai is the general term for
giant reishi-generating devices
that were once used
in the Soul Society.
At one time, there were
probably several dozen
of these devices
in the Seireitei.
One day during a
series of experiments,
one of the Jokai Crests
suddenly went out of control.
When it exploded, the blast
annihilated almost 1/10
of the Seireitei.
Central 46 was so
alarmed by the accident
that they took immediate
steps to seal away
the rest of the
Jokai Crests forever.
-One Jokai Crest was
bad enough, but this?
-If I'm right, then we cannot
allow Kariya to detonate
the Jokai Crest that he's
already absorbed into his body,
because that explosion will
surely set off the other Jokai
Crests, and I'm certain that's
what Kariya is planning.
If all of the Jokai Crests
were to explode at once,
their destructive force
would be unfathomable.
[screaming]
-Why does the Soul Society keep
such horrible and frightening
things around?
-That's because horrible
and frightening things
are always less horrible
and frightening when
they're kept out in the open.
-I think I get it.
Like hiding your dirty
clothes under your bed.
-Uh, not exactly.
-So, what should we do?
-At this point,
our only option is
to use Kido to seal away
all the Jokai Crests.
The original seals
will be weakened now
after so many years.
They'll be vulnerable
to Kariya's explosion.
-Captain.
-Let's do it.
We'll begin resealing
them immediately.
Do you know where the other
Jokai Crests are located?
-In here.
I'll be all right.
It's just like I told you.
I've been fighting with my
spiritual pressure sealed
inside and overextended myself.
Now I've reached the
limit of my endurance.
I'm afraid that I must
leave the rest to you.
-Lieutenant.
Let's go.
-Yes sir.
-What about the rest of you?
-We're going to help Ichigo.
That's the least we can do.
He's out there
fighting somewhere,
and we can't just
let him do it alone.
There's a possibility
that he's been injured,
and I have to be there
to help heal his wounds.
-Easy, Orihime.
-Uryu, let me carry Ran'Tao.
We'll take her to a safe place,
and then we'll find Ichigo.
-All right.
Thanks, Chad.
-All right!
Now that that's finally
decided, let's get going!
-I can't wait until this
whole nightmare's over.
-Right.
Thank goodness.
-All right, everyone.
Let's get going.
Ichigo needs us.
-I must commend you for
being able to keep up with me
as long as you have.
-It's like I said, I intend
to settle this thing now.
-Tell me, do you know what
kind of a place this is?
-Yeah.
You could say that.
I'm very familiar
with this place.
-It's just perfect, isn't it?
For settling
something like this.
-I agree.
-Flash and burst.
Nijigasume!
-Aren't you--
UKITAKE: What?
-Ron'Ta gave me this map to
lead us to all the Jokai Crests.
-My, my.
Who would've thought
that such things still
existed here in the Seireitei?
Well, it looks like we stayed
up all night for nothing.
-Captain, please.
You must take this
situation seriously.
-Hm.
-Does the Head Captain know?
-I sent Rangiku to inform him.
We should be receiving
his orders shortly.
-One thing's for certain.
To re-seal so many Jokai
Crests all at once,
we're going to need every
captain, lieutenant, as well
as every able seated
officer we can mobilize.
-What do we do about Kariya?
-Ichigo Kurosaki has
gone off to engage him.
RANGIKU: The following is an
urgent message to all captains,
lieutenants, and squad members
of the 13 Court Guard Squads.
The Bounts' plan is to detonate
ancient generators known
as Jokai.
We have confirmed the existence
of a large number of them.
They must be sealed
away immediately.
A level one precautionary
warning is hereby in effect.
Everyone is to proceed
to a Jokai Crest.
The hell butterflies
will lead you there.
-You must go too, lieutenant.
Find a Jokai Crest and
assist with sealing it.
-Yes, sir.
-Given the grave
nature of this threat,
I too must get involved and
direct the sealing process.
Captain Komamura,
you will assist me.
-Yes, Head Captain.
-If you'll excuse me.
MAN: What's going on
up on the Sogyoku hill?
MAN: A big fight's
about to start.
I hear every Soul Reaper in the
Seireitei has been mobilized.
MAN: Yeah.
And that Ichigo
Kurosaki is taking
on the leader of of the Bounts.
MAN: I guess that means we
should probably clear out.
Let's ask Captain
Kuchiki for instructions.
MAN: Good idea.
-Ichigo.
-Well, well.
You're still alive.
-Master Kariya.
Before I proceed, there's
something I need to ask you.
-What is that?
-What happened to
Koga and the others?
-They died.
-All of them?
-Yes.
They all died.
-Oh.
Is that so?
-Hey!
Why are you doing this?
Stop this!
I said stop it!
-I can't stop.
-Why are you even here?
You're not in any
shape to fight.
-What do you think
you're doing, Ichinose?
-Before, if you told me
to destroy the Seireitei,
I would have had no
choice but to obey you.
I abandoned this place
long ago, and I would not
mind seeing it all disappear.
At least that's what I thought.
When I looked at
you, I thought I
was reminded of the captain
I once revered and respected.
That's the reason why
I fought by your side
in the first place.
But--
Why do you insist on
standing in our way
when we've come here to see that
justice is finally delivered?
-Are you an idiot?
Are you sure that justice
is your goal, Ichinose?
Or is it just revenge
that you're after?
-You don't understand!
-Come on, then!
-Kenpachi Zaraki!
[shout] It was during
my battle with Kenpachi
that I remembered
something I had forgotten.
Back then, I wanted
to change things.
I wanted to make the 13 Court
Guard Squads into something
better.
That was my desire.
My captain and I had
the same beliefs.
That's why I worked
so hard by his side,
and why I felt my ideals
would never change,
even if he wasn't there anymore.
But when he was killed, the
sheer emptiness of his death
changed my ideals into
a desire for revenge.
So tell me, you
have the power now
to change the Soul
Society, Kariya.
If you will use that power
to rebuild the Seireitei,
to make it the way it should be.
If you promise this, I shall
kneel before you once more.
But, if not, if you choose
to use your power only
for destruction and revenge,
then I will stop you.
Nothing can be
born of vengeance.
Now that Koga and all
the others are dead,
the only one left who
can stop you is me.
So what's it gonna be?
-Ichinose, I'm afraid
that's impossible.
-Don't try it!
-You don't have sufficient
power to stop me.
[gasping]
-But I do appreciate your help.
Thanks to your
interference, I've
had just enough time for
the Jokai Crest's full power
to spread throughout
my entire body.
-Kariya!
[scream]
-Hey, Kariya!
What the hell have you done,
you backstabbing monster?
-What are you talking about?
-That man was your comrade.
He served faithfully
by your side,
and that's the
way you repay him?
-What difference does that make?
-What difference?
-Ichinose was your enemy.
It makes no sense to me
that you should pity him.
-Well, I don't pity him.
But I can never forgive
you for ruthlessly
murdering one of
your own comrades.
-To tell you the truth, I
never thought of any of them
as my actual comrades.
They were all just
pawns for me to use
until my goals were achieved.
-Bastard!
-In any case, it's time
to settle this with you
once and for all.
Zeige deke!
Now, Messer!
-What the hell's this?
-What's happening?
-I've never felt wind like that.
And I can sense Kariya's
spiritual pressure
starting to rise rapidly, too.
-Let's hurry up!
-I didn't think I would
need to show you my Doll,
but it seems I'm
almost out of time.
Allow me to introduce
you to my Doll, Messer.
Now you'll find you can no
longer come anywhere near me.
-Arrogant to the very end.
-Yah!
-Hey.
Where are you going?
-Renji.
Why are you here?
-I hadn't heard
from the captain,
so I decided to come
here and look for him.
What's going on, Rukia?
-Renji.
I need a favor.
-Yeah?
What's that?
-I need you to take me--
take me to the Sogyoku.
-Why, Rukia?
[theme music]
KIRAYA: Soon.
Soon I'll be filled with the
power of the Jokai Crest,
and I will wipe the
Seireitei from this world.
There's nothing anyone
can do to stop me anymore.
ICHIGO: Kariya, I'm
going to stop you.
I won't let you destroy
the Soul Society!
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers.
MAN: Golden.
Is?
This the place?
-Yeah.
We were told that Ichigo and the
others would be resting here.
-Wow, those other guys
sure do have it rough.
I think I'll use
my soothing powers.
-Urgent message.
The Substitute Soul Real--
-No, you stop that.
- --has begun fighting
against the Bount,
and you're to return
to your command post.
-Understood.
-I'm here, everyone!
Huh?
Oh, not again!