[music playing]
[THEME MUSIC - AQUA TIMEZ,
"VELONICA"]
NARRATOR: Ichigo
and his friends were
on the brink of being defeated
by the powerful Espadas when
the captains of the
13 court guard squads
finally arrived in Hueco Mundo.
Under orders from head
captain Genryusai Yamamoto,
the captains came to Hueco
Mundo with the intention
of engaging the Espadas
in battle as they bravely
attempted to rescue
Ichigo and the others.
Kenpachi Zaraki
arrived on the scene
and found a weakened Ichigo.
A fiercely-fought battle
with Espada Number Five,
Nnoitra Gilga, ensued.
Both of them took great
pleasure in the challenge
of fighting a strong opponent,
and their battle's intensity
increased as they fought.
Yet despite Kenpachi's
powerful attacks,
he could not cut through
Nnoitra's Hierro, which
is reputed to be the
hardest skin of all Espadas.
Under the withering pressure
of Nnoitra's intense attacks,
Kenpachi continued to
search for a way to cut him.
-No matter what you do,
your sword cannot cut me.
That's why you are doomed
to lose this battle!
KENPACHI: There are many
different personalities
within the Soul Society.
I've come across
annoying guys like you
before who say they
can't be cut by my sword.
But guess what?
In all this time, I
haven't met a single person
whose eyes and throat
can't be speared.
-How many times
are you gonna make
me say it until you believe me?
No matter how much you
try, I cannot be cut!
Ha.
I guess you can't
understand it, can you?
How can someone still
be alive after you just
ran a sword through their head?
Isn't that what's going
through your head?
Ha, ha, ha.
Well, here's your answer.
-Bastard.
I can't believe this.
-It simply passed
through my head.
Now do you understand?
You can't defeat
me, Soul Reaper.
You don't have the power.
You might as well give up.
-Ha.
-You simple-minded fool.
What the hell's so funny?
-Sorry about that.
I'm feeling happy, so I
couldn't help but laugh.
-Happy, you say?
Why?
-Well, there was no joy
thinking that even if I cut you,
it wouldn't affect the
outcome of our match.
But now I feel happy because
I know that if I do cut you,
you'll die.
I like that.
I'm looking forward to
cutting you in half.
It'll make my day.
-Good luck.
I told you, you can't cut me.
Idiot!
Yah!
Damn it.
It seems you still have
quite a bit of power left.
-Yah!
[chuckling]
-Huh?
-Ha, ha, ha.
Yah!
-Kenpachi's taking it to him.
-Yep, now it's getting good.
[grunting]
-Ha.
How many times do
I have to say it?
You can't cut me, moron.
-Yah!
-Kenpachi finally cut him.
-Captain Zaraki!
[giggling]
-What is it, fool?
You are surprised that you
were actually able to cut me?
[slurping]
-If I were you, I wouldn't
let one lucky slice give you
the wrong idea.
[gasp]
[giggling]
-Kenny's finally
his old self again.
Here he goes.
Do it.
-What's that spiritual pressure?
[grunting]
-Hey, are you OK?
-Come on, one more round.
Bring it on.
-This fight is over!
-Yah!
-Heh.
-What's he doing?
[gasp]
-Ha, ha.
-Damn.
-Guess what?
It took me longer than
I thought it would,
but now I'm used
to your tough skin.
-"Used to"?
(VOICEOVER) Did
I hear him right?
Could he really be getting
used to all of this?
-Guess you could say I've been
kind of out of practice lately.
My muscles got out of shape.
It's like I forgot how
to really use them.
So you have my thanks.
You gave me the wake-up
call that I've needed.
Let me return the
favor with this!
[grunting]
-You.
Yah!
-Kenpachi!
-Watch out.
[gasp]
-Yah!
[grunting]
-Hmm.
-No way.
Damn it.
Uh.
[trembling]
-Yah!
Ha-yah!
[groaning]
-Ha.
[power crackling]
[whimpering]
[panting for breath]
-Tsk.
[panting]
-You fool.
You never should have
ripped off my eye patch.
After that, I can't hold back.
-What is it?
Your eye patch?
Is that how your power works?
-It was a seal.
-A seal?
KENPACHI: I use it to
control my spirit energy
so I can savor
fighting my enemies.
[panting]
-You're still standing.
-You look alive.
Or is it just that
you haven't died yet?
[panting]
[grunting]
NNOITRA: You jackass.
Can't you see?
There's no chance I'm
going to die here.
No, not by the likes
of your damn sword.
[wind howling]
-The wind.
-A massive amount of
spirit energy is gathering.
-Can he--
NNOITRA: Feel that?
I feel it.
I am strong.
I am not going to die here!
Now pray.
Santa Teresa!
[gasping]
[music playing]
-His arms.
Somehow he's doubled them.
It just isn't fair, damn it.
[whimpering]
[gasping]
ICHIGO: And his wounds.
They've closed.
What's with that?
Those wounds were
inflicted on him
after Kenpachi's
eye patch came off.
Kenpachi.
-Ha.
So tell me.
What's it like to see an
Espada's sword released
for the first time?
Aren't you going to say
something, Soul Reaper?
-Nice spiritual pressure.
-Huh?
-It's been a while
since I've had
that feeling that an opponent's
spiritual pressure is
sharpening my blade.
-Oh, is that so?
Then let's see you cut me.
Attack me with your
so-called sharpened blade!
-Yeah.
-Yah!
-He-yah!
-Huh?
What?
Is that really all you've got?
Ha!
-Oh, no!
-Kenpachi.
[gasp]
-Can't he--
-That sword of yours, it had
nothing behind it, Soul Reaper.
Ha.
Looks like he's out cold.
Is it over?
Since he's done, guess I'll
clean up the leftovers.
-Yachiru!
-Orihime, wait!
What was that?
Was I just repelled?
That capability, is that part
of Orihime's Shun Shun Rikka?
-Santen Kesshun!
-Ha!
That's nothing.
[gasping]
-You think so?
You should look behind you.
-Huh?
-Huh.
[grunting]
-Kenpachi!
-Three arms left to go.
-Damn it.
-I warn you.
If you attack me, Kenny's
gonna get awfully angry.
-I'm not getting angry.
Now, quiet.
-You were playing dead?
That was a cheap trick, pal.
-It wasn't a trick.
I needed time to think.
You had four arms
at the time, which
made attacking you
much more involved.
So I was thinking,
trying to figure out
how to keep you
from blocking me.
But the more I thought
about it, the more
I couldn't come up
with any good ideas.
And so I think I'll cut off
your arms one at a time.
-That's really smart, because
if you cut them all off,
then he can't fight.
-What's that?
You're right.
I misspoke.
I'll leave you one arm.
-Mm-hmm, right.
You'll leave me one arm?
This is getting really stupid.
Enough of this.
That arm of mine
you just cut off
is the last one
you'll ever touch.
In fact, this will
help you understand.
[gasping]
-You talked about how you're
going to defeat me and leave me
with only one arm.
That was a bit
premature for someone
who will be dead in a moment.
I am about to prove
something to you.
You're weaker than
me, Soul Reaper.
Yah!
Ha-yah!
-Ugh.
-Ha.
What a lightweight,
getting blown around
like a leaf in the wind.
That makes it hard to
slash you with my attacks.
Could it be you're afraid
and simply running to hide?
Huh?
Ugh.
Oof.
Ah!
[grunting]
-What the hell?
[groaning]
-What's the matter?
Shouldn't I be dead by now?
-(STRAINING) Yes.
-Oof!
[gasping]
-You idiot.
You are so delusional.
You can't cut off my arms.
It's not that simple.
Here's the reality
that is your fate.
You're about to be
slashed to pieces
by all six of my deadly arms.
-Ugh.
-Kenpachi!
[gasping]
-Kenny.
[laughter]
[MUSIC - STEREOPONY, "HITOHIRA
NO HANABIRA"]
ORIHIME: Yachiru, I
think it's amazing
that you two didn't
get lost in Garganta.
YACHIRU: That's because
the yaki smell very sweet,
so we just followed our noses,
and that led us to this place.
ORIHIME: That must be--
ICHIGO: Yeah.
It was his Ambassador
Seaweed bean paste cake.