[theme music]
NARRATOR: Soul Reapers,
the spiritual guardians
to the world of the living.
Their job is to maintain the
balance between the myriad
of good and evil souls
that fill this world.
Sosuke Aizen, who
betrayed the Soul Society
and left the Seireitei in chaos,
has set his plan into motion.
Arrancars have arrived
in Karakura Town.
Using the Hogyoku, Aizen
has created these Arrancars
by shattering the boundary
between Soul Reapers
and Hollows.
Meanwhile, Visoreds,
Soul Reapers
who have awakened the
powers of their Inner Hollow
have appeared and
confronted Ichigo.
Aware that Ichigo
is one of them,
the Visored named Shinji Hirako
invites Ichigo to join them.
Despite the fear
and the anxiety he
feels from awakening
the Hollow within him,
Ichigo, nonetheless,
found the strength
to confront the two powerful
Arrancars, Ulquiorra and Yammy,
who were sent by Aizen.
-What do you want to
do with her, Ulquiorra?
Maybe we should take
her back to Aizen
to show him this weird
healing power she possesses.
-Wait, Aizen?
-No, that won't be necessary.
Just kill her, Yammy.
-Gotcha.
-Uhh.
-[chuckles]
Hrrh!
-[whimpers]
-Ugh.
-Uh!
-Sorry, Ichigo.
-It's all right.
I'm sorry I couldn't
get here sooner.
-No, I mean, all
this is my fault.
If I-- if I was stronger,
I could have stopped this.
-There's no need for
you to apologize.
You did everything you could.
Now, I'm going to deal with
these two and end this!
-Hm.
-Bankai!
-[shrieks]
-Tensa Zangetsu.
ORIHIME (VOICEOVER):
That's Ichigo's Bankai.
Wow!
I've never seen it
this close up before.
It's amazing!
I know it must be the
same, but somehow it
feels different from the
time at Sokyoku Hill.
Uh.
His spiritual pressure
is so wild and fierce.
It's so heavy.
I feel like it's smothering me.
This doesn't feel
like Ichigo at all.
-Orihime, stay back.
-All right.
-You got a Bankai, huh?
Hey, Ulquiorra, this the guy?
-Yes.
Considering how clumsily you've
dealt with the situation,
I'm surprised we were able
to flush him out at all.
The orange hair,
the black Bankai.
No doubt about it.
This is our target, Yammy.
He is the one.
-So he saved us the trouble
of searching for him.
Hah!
Que suerte!
[grunts]
-I'm guessing you're
the reason Chad's
lying on the ground over there.
-Hm, you're going to
do something about it?
-Huh?
Hhrghah!
ULQUIORRA (VOICEOVER): Idiot.
That's what you get for
charging into a fight
before evaluating
your enemy's strength.
You should have mastered the
Pesquisa, like I told you.
Even so, he sliced
through Yammy's Cero
and lopped off his arm
like it was nothing.
Not what I would have
expected from someone
who had just learned Bankai.
His spiritual
pressure is strong.
Still, at this
level of power, he
couldn't possibly pose
a threat to Lord Aizen.
-[heaving]
Damn!
You little runt!
-Surprised you can stand
there and call me names.
I guess you're as
tough as you are ugly.
-It seems you're
having a hard time.
Shall I take over?
-Stay back!
[grunts]
-I can't believe you
need your Zanpakuto
to deal with a runt like this.
YAMMY: Shut up and stay back!
-That's a Zanpakuto.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
I should have known.
His sword is a Zanpakuto.
The cracked Hollow mask,
the hole in his chest,
and the Zanpakuto.
I know I felt something odd
about their spiritual pressure.
Who are these guys?
Are they Visoreds,
like Shinji and me?
HOLLOW ICHIGO
(VOICEOVER): Do it!
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Damn it!
He's here.
-Huh?
HOLLOW ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
Just switch with me, will you?
I'll take care of this guy.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Go away.
Go away!
I don't need you.
-Hah.
-Ugh!
-[gasps]
Ichigo!
-Stay where you are!
-No!
-Orihime, no!
-Shut up!
[growls]
Rrrh!
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER): Damn it.
I can't move my body.
I rejected you.
So now, you want to get
in my way and sabotage me?
Damn it.
YAMMY: Hah!
He stopped moving.
Looks like this flea has
lost all of his fight.
-Uhh, uhh.
ULQUIORRA (VOICEOVER):
Something strange is going on.
His spiritual pressure,
it keeps fluctuating.
One second it's none, and
then it suddenly spikes.
When it's low, it's
inconsequential.
But when it's high,
it's stronger than mine.
What the hell is going on?
-I'm done messing around!
Time for you to disappear!
Huh?
-Hey, there.
Sorry, I couldn't get here
a little sooner, Ichigo.
You know how it is.
-What the--
-[snickers]
-All these bugs keep popping
up and getting in the way.
But stepping to the
front of the line just
means you're going
to get killed first.
Sucker!
-[grunts]
-Whoa, waah, whoa, ungh!
YORUICHI: I've got this.
-He's all yours.
-[growls]
Huh?
Ugh!
[grunts]
[heaves]
-Hah!
-Arrgh!
Ugh.
-Humph.
-Yo-- Yoruichi, is it you?
-Yeah?
-Is Ichigo all right?
Where is he?
-He's fine.
Don't worry.
Can you swallow?
-Yes.
-You just don't know
when to quit, do you?
-[growls]
-Uh!
A Cero.
-[laughing]
You mess with me, little
girl, you got blown to bits.
No one could escape the blast
of my Cero at this range.
Huh!
Who are you?
And how did you survive my Cero?
You should all be dead!
-You need to pay
closer attention.
I knew if I tried to block
it, the others might get hurt.
So I simply took the
offensive and responded
with a similar attack.
-That's impossible!
-If you don't believe me, I'd be
happy to demonstrate it again.
-[grunts]
-Now, scream.
Benihime!
-Uh.
-Ulquiorra.
Ugh!
Why did you do that?
-Idiot.
If you had a brain in your head,
you would have figured it out.
That's Kisuke Urahara and
she's Yoruichi Shihoin.
At your current level, you
wouldn't last five minutes
against the two of them.
Let's go.
-Are you running away?
-Why?
Are you trying to
goad me into a fight?
You know very well
what would happen
if you tried to fight
me while protecting
those pieces of trash.
Even you must realize the
odds are stacked against you.
Normally, I'd be
happy to oblige.
But we've completed
our mission here.
It's time we deliver our
report to Lord Aizen.
I'll tell him the Soul
Reaper he's interested
in has no value whatsoever.
He's not even worth killing.
-I'm home.
I picked up the juice
you asked me to get.
Ururu, Jinta, what's up?
Is Yoruichi doing all right?
[gulps]
-Aah!
[exhales loudly]
-I was going to ask you
how your arm is doing,
but I can see it's fine.
-Yeah, well, being able
to handle everyday tasks,
like eating and
drinking, is one thing.
-What about combat?
-[sighs]
It was my own fault
for not getting off
and attack while I
was ready for it.
The Arrancar's exterior had
stronger spiritual pressure
than I had anticipated.
They're strong, Kisuke.
They're very strong.
I hate to admit
it, but I think we
may have misjudged the full
extent of their powers.
-[groans]
-Bore!
Bore!
Boring!
Grrr.
Urgh!
Rrrgh!
What are you doing,
moping around?
On a day like this, we should
be out there picking up chicks!
I'm out of here, Ichigo!
Agh!
[crash]
[pattering rain]
-Ngh!
Aargh!
Just because the
guy owns me, I have
to be a slave to his moods!
Ugh!
I cut myself to shreds for
you, and you can't even
get out of bed!
Hey, you!
I'm talking to you, you slug!
Well, I'm going to find
a cute young hottie.
And when I do, I'm not going
to introduce her to you!
She'll be like, oh,
Kon, you're so sweet!
We're going to have more
fun than you've ever had.
And you'll be like, oh,
man, why didn't I go?
But don't come crying to me!
Hey!
Are you listening to me?
Say something!
Hm, I wish I could
figure out what
the heck is wrong with that guy.
GIRL: Dad, hurry!
It sounded like glass breaking!
And then I heard someone--
-Oh, no, not her!
GIRL: --shouting
outside the house!
Oh, look!
It's bust up.
What are you doing out here?
Poor thing.
How'd you get so dirty?
-If it keeps up
like this-- damn it!
ORIHIME: No, no, no, no!
Getting depressed like
this won't solve anything.
Uh.
[moans]
-Hm.
GIRL: No!
What on earth happened?
Tell me right now?
-Uh, he-he, I tripped
and fell down the stairs.
-You expect me to believe you
got those injuries falling down
the stairs!
-[chuckles]
-This is no laughing matter!
You've been absent
for five days now.
And just look at you.
You're a mess.
Why do you always
make me worry so much?
-Eeh, you're not going to get
all mushy and hug me, are you?
CHIZURU: No way.
Just look at you.
How could I?
ICHIGO: Orihime.
-Uh, oh, what is it, Ichigo?
I, uh, well, don't
worry about it.
It's not important.
-What's up with Ichigo?
-Sorry, Chizzy.
I have to use the restroom.
-What?
Orihime, wait up!
ORIHIME (VOICEOVER):
Please don't feel bad.
I wasn't thinking,
and I just jumped in.
I have no one else
to blame but myself
for getting hurt like this.
It looks a lot worse
than it really is.
So please don't look
like that or act
like you're the one
who's responsible.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
Who else can I blame?
Chad was injured, too.
Tatsuki nearly died.
It's all because I'm weak.
I don't know what I can
do other than feel guilty.
MAN: So where the heck is it?
WOMAN: How should I know?
MAN: Wait a minute.
I thought you wrote it down
before we left the Seireitei?
WOMAN: I lost it.
MAN: Oh, that's just great.
WOMAN: I think that Renji
would lead us, right?
You've been here before.
You should know
where you're going.
RENJI: What are
you talking about?
You've been here, too.
WOMAN: I know.
But it was such a short time.
RENJI: Enough already.
Just search for his
spiritual pressure.
MAN: Man, I can't believe
the weird clothes they all
wear here in the
world of the living.
-It's called a
uniform, brainiac.
The students are
required to wear them.
WOMAN: Oh, well, listen
to you, Mr. Smarty-Pants.
-Give me a break.
Besides, I don't think
that's the standard uniform.
-How are you supposed to
move in these clothes?
They're so tight!
-Yeah, well, maybe you should
try untucking your shirt,
like the rest of us.
-What?
Are you crazy?
If I did that, I
wouldn't be able to fit
my sword to my belt!
-A wooden sword really
isn't part of the uniform.
-For crying out loud!
You're the ones who said I
couldn't bring a real sword,
so I brought a wooden one!
-We are not the ones
who make the rules.
It's a law here in the
world of the living.
-Well, it's ridiculous!
What kind of stupid law says
you can carry a real sword?
-What's the big deal?
I actually kind of
like these clothes.
-That's easy for you to say.
You only like them because
they show off your--
-Shut up, you guys!
We don't need to draw
attention to ourselves.
So just walk quietly
and try to blend in.
GROUP: Yes, sir.
MAN: This is the room.
Go on, open the door.
-[gasps]
-Yo, what's going on, Ichigo?
-Uhh.
[gasps]
-Ruh-- Renji?
Toshiro?
Wait a minute.
What are you guys doing here?
-That's Capt. Hitsugaya to you.
-Yeah, fine.
But I don't understand
why you're here.
-Orders from above.
Looks like there's a major storm
brewing with the Arrancars.
We were sent here to join forces
with the Substitute Soul Reaper
and prepare for the battle.
-Uh, Arrancar.
What the hell is that?
-What?
You're not serious, are you?
You mean you've been
fighting these guys without--
-[sighs]
---any idea who you
were dealing with?
-Hm, what are you talking about?
WOMAN: You dummy!
-Huh?
WOMAN: He's talking about
those guys who beat you up
the other day.
-Rukia.
-It's been a while,
Ichigo, hasn't it?
[theme music]
-Why are you dressed like that?
-What do you mean?
Everyone likes costumes.
I've also got a nurse's
uniform and a maid's outfit.
YUMICHIKA: Yeah, well,
about the maid thing, I
don't know if that--
RANGIKU: I tried to get
the captain to try some on,
but he said he wasn't into it.
YUMICHIKA: (EXCITEDLY) Really?
[theme music]
-"Illustrated Guide
to Soul Reapers."
-Wow, I got to
tell you, I really
appreciate you're inviting
me over to dinner like this.
-I think I got
everything you asked for.
UNOHANA: Oh, there doesn't
seem to be any meat in there.
GANJU: Yeah, you're right.
-Nyah.
-I guess you must
have forgotten.
[chuckles]
Not to worry.
I prepared something,
just in case.
GANJU: [gnawing]
This is excellent!
[gnawing]
-This meat is
delicious, Captain.
Where did you get it?
-I caught it wandering
around by the front door.
-Oh!
Bonnie!
No!