[grunting]
Shorty! Shorty! Shorty!
Let's go.
[yelling]
[grunting]
[growling]
Come on, Sosuke...
Let's settle this now.
Looks like I missed.
What are you talking
about? You obviously
hit me.
Komamura.
I'm sorry to interfere,
Captain Komamura.
I beg you, sir... Please
let me join you in this
battle.
Shuhei!
Mashiro... Super Kick!
Oh, my...
That girl defeated Fura
with little effort. You
know, I feel somewhat
sorry for Wonderweiss.
He really cared for that
thing.
Ahhhh...
Mashiro...!
Ahhhh!!!!
...Drop kick!
Ahhhh!!!
Well... so
much for him.
Yeah! Victory!
Hmph!
Hey...
I need to talk to you.
How 'bout later? I'm
kinda tied up now.
And if you're still
harping about who we are
and where we came from,
forget it!
Don't worry. I don't
care about that anymore.
The fact of the matter
is, I need to ask if
you'll do me a favor.
Can I leave her to you?
I would help, but...
I want to... go and
confront Sosuke.
Um... Is that all right?
All right? What are
you, stupid? We came
here to take Sosuke's
ass out, and instead we
saw you guys getting
slaughtered, so we
decided to step in and
help you, even though
some of us thought it
was a bad idea! So why
should we let you fight
Sosuke first?
You're right. I
shouldn't have asked.
Forget what I just said.
I was being too impatient.
Forget it? That's all
you have to say? How
'bout 'I'm sorry'?
I'd like to hear an
apology from that big
mouth of yours!
Sorry.
Huh! What was that? I
can't hear you?!
Sorry.
A little louder?!
What kind of an apology
is that? There's no
feeling in it!
That's all you're
getting, so live with it!
Hmpf! Apart from that,
what's a kid like you
doing in a captain's
uniform?
Are you really a
Captain?!
From the way you fight,
it's hard to believe anyone
would promote you to that rank!
I said I was
sorry. Let it go.
You think you're hot
stuff because you were
able to become a
Captain? Well, you
don't impress me at all!
I've seen newbies who
fight better than you!
You're too height
challenged to wear
the uniform!
Shorty! Shorty! Shorty!
What do you mean,
'shorty'?! You're
short!
What?
You're shorter than me,
so shut up, you shrimp!
Who you calling a shrimp,
you hair-ball?! You want
to fight? If you want a
fight, I'll give it to ya!
You're the one who's
trying to pick a fight!
I just wanted to apologize
to you,
but you insist on
not letting it go!
Oh! Now you're touching
me!
Is that what this has all
been about from the beginning?
Are you just a pervert?!
A pervert?! I can't
belie---? What did you
just call me?!
Pervert! Pervert! Pervert!
Shut up! How dare you
say that, you little
brat!
Oh, you can't keep your
hands off me, can you,
you pervert?!
That's enough from both
of you!
Huh?
Don't over-react It's
okay to be interested
in a girl's body.
That's not what happened!
I'll give you some
privacy...
What?! Don't leave me
alone with him!
You're taking me on by
yourself?
I was under the
impression I was going to
fight three against one.
That's interesting. You
see, I was thinking...
...the same thing!
Damn! We'll settle this
later.
Let's go!
Fine.
[gasping]
It's finally three
against one.
I like those odds.
He looks strong---I'll
give him that.
Are you both sure...
you want to remove your
masks?
We can only wear them for
three minutes. It's a
hero's handicap.
So if you're ready...
Let's begin.
Damn! That gun he's
carrying can fire Ceros.
Stop dodging! Stand
still and take it like
a man!
Ouch! Now why did you go
and do that, Stark?
I can't hit the things
I'm shooting at, when
you're blabbering like
that.
Well if you weren't so
busy holding onto my
butt, maybe you could aim
better!
I told you before, I
can't tell where your
butt is on this thing!
Yeah, like I'm supposed
to believe that! Hey,
quit squeezing so hard!
Are we interrupting?
And who might you be?
That's what I want to
know! Who is this guy?!
He's absolutely huge!!
Not to mention the fact
that he's super strong!
It's been a while, hasn't
it...
...Miss Soi Fon?
What?! Wait a minute,
Captain, you know this guy?
Why didn't you say something
to me earlier?!
You should have told
me! I thought he was
just some stranger who
butted into our fight--
I don't know him. I've
never seen him before.
I should have expected
you wouldn't acknowledge
our acquaintanceship.
I'm aware that you've
never thought very highly
of any of us. I suppose
it's only natural.
Huh?
You are wasting time.
It doesn't matter who you
are, or what powers you
have. All those things
are meaningless to me.
You are all equally
helpless against my
power.
Now then... Turn to bones
and perish.
Respira!
Kido.
I know you have the
lethal power... to
rapidly age anything
you can touch.
That is the reason I have
come to confront you.
Your powers are
ineffective unless they
can make contact.
I have nothing to
fear from anything
you posses.
Yeah! Amazing! This
guy refuses to be
intimidated!
I see....
Don't bother, you
cannot escape.
[gasping]
We're all screwed!
Shut up, Marechiyo!
What?! That barrier
can't be breached!
Shuhei...
He's in no condition to
return to the battlefield
yet.
It's obvious he's
pushing himself.
It's been a while, hasn't
it... Captain Tosen.
I'm here... to thank
you.
Interesting choice of
words...
Are you being sarcastic?
Not at all. I came here
today to thank you for
everything you've taught
me.
I'm truly grateful. I've
learned so much from you.
And now, I'm going to use
every skill you've ever
taught me in the past...
...to open your eyes, to
appeal to your sense of
honor...
...and bring you back
into the Soul Society.
You're going to make
me... come back... to
my senses?
You haven't changed...
...Suzumushi.
Shuhei... I thought I
told you... Those who
do not know fear, have
no right to fight.
Like I said before,
you haven't changed
at all.
Even as you stand there
to confront me, your
words don't have a shred
of fear in them.
He's right behind you,
Shuhei!
[struggling]
You do not understand the
true meaning of fear.
You can't defeat me.
[grunting]
Listen, you shorty,
stop gettin' in my way!
You should be glad I was
in your way! You can't
even thank me for saving
you!
Who told you to save
me?! I certainly didn't!
You messed up my attack!
Are you crazy?!
Halibel's not holding
anything back while
fighting those three...
Wouldn't you agree?
And here I thought I
could ambush you...
You see everything. No
matter. I guess...
...we'll just have to
fight head-on.
You ready, Sosuke?
Foolish pests! Did
you think that your
Kido would not age?
Your minds work in such
limited, pathetic ways.
Humans die, animals die,
plants die---
even Soul Reapers die!
It's the arc of the
universe. Everything that
comes to life, eventually
ceases to exist.
And if men's creations
grow old. The the Kido
of the Soul Reapers do
as well.
There may be a Kido that
can last for a thousand
years, but there is no Kido
that can exist for eternity.
And it is no surprise,
because the concept of
eternity is an absurd notion
born out of the fear of aging.
We've got to get out of
here right now, Captain!
We're just no match for
this guy!
Let's swallow our pride
and get help from the
others before this guy
reduces us to--
Would you shut
up, Marechiyo?!
I'm starting to become
bored with your timidity
and lack of strength.
Let's end this now.
Now then... Perish!
[screaming]
This won't stop me!
The head, unable to
retreat, falls slowly and
surely into the depths of
the bottomless ocean, and
atones for its sins in
bolts of blue, white,
black, and red.
I see what you're
attempting. You're adding
chants to your Kido,
strengthening the barrier
originally created
without incantation. A
very clever maneuver,
but you're not going
to make it in time!
Gate of the Dragon Tail!
Last one! This
completes it!
Hmm... a very
impressive trick.
Help me, Soi Fon! Please
lend me your strength!
Huh? The Captain's
strength?
That is correct. I need
to borrow the power of
her Bankai!
[gasping]
The only way you could
know about my Bankai is
through Kisuke Urahara.
That man... never
ceases to annoy me.
Believe me, I can
understand your not
wanting to work with
anybody associated with
Mr. Urahara...
But this is an emergency
situation!
And it's vital that you
find a way to get over
your bitterness!
[groaning]
Very well, then.
Listen. I'm prepared to
offer you a deal.
Yeah? What kind
of deal?
What a waste of energy!
Even something as
elaborate as this, is only
going to buy you a little
time.
Now rot!
Gate of the Tiger Fang!
Gate of the Turtle Armor!
Gate of the Phoenix
Wing!
Shiju Saimon!
[breathing hard]
[laughing]
How absurd!
You think this structure
can contain me?! You're
deluded!
It will barely slow me
down!
[laughing]
Buying time against me,
the master of aging... is
like spitting on a god.
Though, perhaps I
should praise you for
doing your best.
You're missing the point.
That barrier is not actually
meant to contain you.
Hm?! What?
Do you remember? You
avoided Captain Soi Fon's
Bankai by releasing your
aging powers, which
caused it to detonate
before it struck. At the
same time, you directed
the blast away from you.
I asked myself a simple
question.
If you were in a place
where you couldn't escape
the force of a blast...
...and if you were also
at a distance where your
aging powers could not
reach us...
Hm?!
...then what would happen
to you?
You... bastards!!
Repeat your promise.
Tomorrow, you'll trap
Kisuke Urahara in one
of your barriers for
a full month.
Oh, I promise.
Good.
You'll pay for this, you
Worms!
Jakuho Raikouben!
See ya.
[screaming]
Oh, dear...
It looks like another one
of your friends has gone
down in flames.
I salute you, king of
Hueco Mundo...
...and offer my deepest
condolences.
Decay is my companion.
The world is my servant.
We have an appointment,
you and I. As crows pick
away at this body,
I'll be waiting for
you at the elm mansion!