Welcome back.
[gasping]
Orihime.
What's the matter?
I thought you'd be happy
to see us now that you're
back again, but you look
so troubled.
You should try
to smile...
Everyone gets so
depressed when the
sun doesn't shine.
[trembling]
Smile and wait here a
while. That's all you
need to do. Just until...
...Just until my men
and I finish destroying
Karakura Town.
You're going to
destroy...
...Karakura Town?
That's right.
[gasping]
I need to destroy
Karakura Town, to create
the Ouken.
Sosuke Aizen and his forces
set out to invade Karakura
Town to create the Ouken.
A key to unlocking the
Soul King's dimension.
Leaving Las Noches
under the care of
Espada Ulquiorra.
Meanwhile, Ichigo, Uryu,
Chad, Rukia and Renji
had entered Hueco Mundo
to rescue Orihime, who was
being held captive by Aizen.
But the group soon found
themselves imprisoned
within Hueco Mundo
alongside Captains Byakuya
Kuchiki, Kenpachi Zaraki,
Mayuri Kurotsuchi
and Retsu Unohana,
while Karakura Town
was left defenseless.
By then, however, the Soul
Society, using Tenkaiecchu,
had switched Karakura
Town with an exact
replica,
evacuated the populace,
and turned the area into
a battlefield.
Now, under the command
of Head Captain Yamamoto,
the captains and lieutenants
of the Thirteen Court Guard
Squads
stand ready to confront
Aizen and his army.
Excellent...
It seems we made
it here in time.
Made it in time?
Now why would you think
to say something like
that?
I'm well aware that what
lies beneath you is not
Karakura Town.
This may come as a
surprise, but that means
nothing to me.
Stark, Barragan, Halibel.
Come here.
If Karakura Town is now
inside the Soul Society...
...we'll just kill you
right here...
...and create the Ouken
within the Soul Society.
It is that simple.
Mm!
All things in the
universe turn to ashes.
Ryujinjakka!
Jokakuenjo.
We are safe. This wall of
flames ought to keep
Sosuke and his cohorts at
bay for quite some time.
Now then...
We shall show them no
mercy. End them at once!
Woo, sure is
toasty in here!
The Head Captain went a
little overboard, don't
you think?
Well, Captain Aizen?
What's gonna be our
next move?
We wait.
This battle... will come
to an end... without us
having to lift a finger.
You'll see.
I implore you! You must
put all your spirit into
this to defeat them here!
Even if your flesh is
torn from your body, use
your bones to form an
impenetrable wall!
No matter what the cost,
we must never let them
step even one foot into
the Soul Society!
Attack now!!
[grunting]
Take that! And that!
Heh.
[grunting]
Nice try!
You don't have what it
takes to handle me, let
alone the three of us!!
Uh! What?
[gasping]
It's you!
Momo!
Mmm...
Thrust! Cierva!!
Eat your fill! Leona!!
Strangle to Death!
Anaconda.
Quimera Parca.
Haliebel's Fracciones,
Apache, SunSun and Mila
Rose,
used Quimera Parca to
create the monster Ayon,
who defeated Ragiku
Matsumoto and Momo
Hinamori with ease.
Shuhei Hisagi, who had
come to help, was quickly
incapacitated,
as he fell prey to Ayon's
massive strength and power.
Continuing his rampage,
Tetsuzaemon Iba was soon
leveled by Ayon as well.
Izuru Kira, who was
administering first-aid
to the others,
then found himself with
the demonic destroyer
closing in on him.
[gasping]
Inexcusable...
...making your Head
Captain come out here
to the front lines...
You squad members are
quite a disappointment.
It's Head Captain
Yamamoto.
[grunting]
Captain, what
was that?
Calm down, you fool.
It's just the Head
Captain.
What?!
The Head Captain himself
came out and took part in
the fight?
Omaeda...
Come here, please.
Huh...?
What is it?
[grunting]
Nice try, Captain, but I
won't fall for the same
trick twice---
[grunting]
We've all come
here to fight.
And that means even the
Head Captain is no
exception.
Now, quit acting
like such an idiot.
That's mean of you!
[roaring]
Hmm, well, it appears
you have not learned
your lesson.
[roaring]
[growling]
When you are ready, I
will be right here.
What!
It is obvious to me that
you are a simple beast that
only lives for killing...
How pitiful.
Ryujinjakka,
Hitotsume...!
Nadegiri...!
No way!
[grunting]
[screaming]
I admire your bravery in
challenging me with only
one arm.
[screaming]
[struggling]
As a show of respect,
I'll let you off with
just burns.
[gasping]
What!?
What's that?
Apache... Sun-Sun... Mila
Rose... You have all
fought well.
As powerful as you are,
you're still just the
third strongest?
As powerful as
I am, you say...
I don't recall showing
you the full extent of
my power just yet.
Uh!
Bankai!
Daiguren Hyorimaru!
You're strong...
you Soul Reapers.
Thank you for the
compliment.
I wanted to dodge any
confrontations and wait
until the battle had
ended...
... but I see now,
that's not going to
be possible.
I'm happy to hear it...
At this point in the
battle, there's only
three of you left to
challenge us.
I'm guessing that
girl is number three.
Am I right?
On a personal note, I'm
hoping that old man is
Number One.
I'd be much more
comfortable if you
were number two...
Hmm... I see.
Sorry, but
I'm number one.
[sighing]
I was afraid of that.
Too bad for me. If you're
the strongest, it makes
my battle more difficult.
...especially because we
are so much alike.
[screaming]
Are you afraid?
You are useless to Lord
Aizen now.
There is no one here
to protect you. You
are alone.
It's over.
You will die here. You
will die, all by yourself
with no one to witness it.
So I want to know, how
frightened are you?
I am not. At all.
You see, now I know that
my friends came to rescue
me. So right now, my
heart...
My heart is with them.
Ridiculous.
No matter what you think,
the fate of you and your
friends is already
decided.
Even if they do manage
to find you, it will not
change the fact that you
are going to die.
There's no turning back
from that now.
Sharing your feelings
with someone, when
you're on the verge of
death, brings some sort
of comfort to you humans.
It's an instinct to help
minimize your fear and
sorrow.
But in reality, it is
impossible to know
another's emotions.
Empathy is simply a
meaningless human
delusion.
That may be true...
It might be impossible to
feel exactly what someone
else is feeling.
But when people truly
care about each other...
their hearts grow so
close, you can't tell the
difference between them.
Please don't die!
Uh!
Don't die, Ichigo!!
You don't have to win,
and you don't have to
fight for me.
Just don't get hurt.
I couldn't bear it.
That's what it must
mean when they say...
two people are of one
heart.
Tell me, what
is a heart?
If I tore a hole in your
chest... would I see it?
If I split open your
skull... would it
be there?
[trembling]
Uh!
Ichigo.
Step away from her.
I was just about to.
My responsibilities
are clear.
My duty is to protect Las
Noches until Lord Aizen
returns.
I haven't received
orders to take the
life of this woman.
Until those orders come,
I will allow her to live.
However...
You are a different
matter.
Killing you would be
absolutely within my
duties of protecting
Las Noches.
You shall die...
by my sword.
What a surprise... it's
funny.. I never figured
you would be the first
one to draw your sword.
On the way here, I was
thinking that you wouldn't
take me seriously enough
to draw right away.
So tell me. Is it
reasonable to say you
consider me an opponent
that's equal to you?
You might say that.
I consider you an enemy
worth destroying.
That's good enough.
Ichigo.
Now I remember what
happened in the story
up 'til now.
So you're saying
you'd forgotten?
Huh? Oh, you're the guy
I was fighting against!
Ichigo Kurosaki.
What is it, guy I
was fighting against?
Don't you know my name?
Aw, come on now, I
know you, guy I was
fighting against!