-Ever since the powers
of the Soul Reaper
were thrust upon me, my
whole world has changed.
Now I'm Ichigo Kurosaki,
Substitute Soul Reaper,
and I'm combining my
powerful spirit energy
with this blade in order
to protect my friends!
[theme music]
[laughter]
-Hi there, boys!
My name is Ririn.
Nice to meet you, too.
-What do you want?
Why are you doing this?
-Hah!
Do you like my game?
-Uryu, you go after the kid.
-Aw, such silly boys.
I'll see ya later, boys.
-Dammit.
-What the hell is going on here?
-Ah.
[crash]
BOY (OFFSCREEN): Hey,
hold on a second!
MAN (OFFSCREEN): Let's go!
-Hey!
What did you have to
go and do that for?
-Hey.
I need a favor.
Do you mind if I leave my
body with you for awhile?
-Sure.
No problem.
But what's going on?
-Now Chad's been kidnapped, too.
-Hm.
-It looks like they're trying
to pick us off one by one.
It's not safe to
just leave my body
laying around while
it's unoccupied.
-Fine.
Then what am I supposed to do?
-You're going to stick with me.
-Oh, so you've finally
acknowledged my abilities?
Well, now I don't know if I
feel like helping you or not.
-Don't worry, your body
will be safe with me.
But we'd better deal
with this situation
before someone
else gets grabbed.
-Damn.
How in the hell are we
supposed to get at those guys?
All my attacks were
totally useless.
-Just charging at
them didn't work,
so we'll have to try
a different strategy.
-You think Aizen could
be involved in this?
That would explain a lot.
-It's hard to tell.
-Urahara, were you
able to find out
anything about the
telephone conversation?
-I was hoping that I
could get a reimon, which
is the spirit equivalent
of a fingerprint.
But I didn't come
up with anything.
-So what does that mean?
-Who knows?
Hard to tell.
But my guess is that
we're not dealing
with humans or
Soul Reapers here.
-I definitely felt
something strange
about the spiritual
presence of those three.
-You could feel that?
-You've never been
known for your ability
to sense spiritual
pressure, Ichigo.
-Shut your big mouth.
-It looks like the enemy's
powers are derived from Kido.
If I'm right about that, then a
direct attack with a zanpakuto
is going to have little
or no effect on them.
-What about Zangetsu's
Getsuga Tensho?
Could I cause some
damage with that?
-In theory, yes.
That is, if you're
able to control
the power of that technique.
-Only Captain
Kuchiki's Senbon Zakura
has that kind of raw power.
It could just wipe out the
enemy, and us along with it.
-Well, it's not like
yours is any better.
When you use bankai, you can't
do Kido style attacks, either.
-No, I'm not confident that I
can control Zabimaru in bankai.
And Soul Reapers at my rank
are only allowed limited powers
while in the world
of the living.
-So what's that leaves us with?
Uryu, it's up to you now.
You're going to take those guys
out with your Quincy powers.
-I kind of figured you'd
come up with that conclusion.
-They targeted Chad
and Orihime first,
knowing they'd be the
easiest to take out.
So we know we're facing
an intelligent enemy.
-So far, everything's going
just the way they want it to.
[phone ringing]
-Hm?
-Thanks for calling
Urahara's shop.
Now, what can I do for you?
[laughter]
RIRIN (OVER PHONE): Let
me speak to the redhead.
-What do you want?
RIRIN (OVER PHONE): It
was so much fun before.
I want to continue our game
at the Karakura Museum.
Bring all your friends.
ICHIGO (OVER PHONE):
Fine, whatever.
Just tell me what happened
to Chad and Orihime.
Are they safe?
Hey!
They want us to
come to the museum.
-What?
Again?
-All right!
Things are going to be
different now that I'm along.
You don't have to
worry about a thing.
Just follow me.
Huh?
Hey!
What is the meaning of this?
-Shut your mouth
before I sew it shut.
I already explained
that we don't
know where this enemy
will attack us from,
so we need you to
watch our backs for us.
-But did you have to turn
me into a cutesy backpack
like the ones little kids wear?
-Would you quite
thrashing around so much?
It's hurting.
-I wouldn't mind riding around
on Orihime's back for a while,
but why do I have to
get stuck with this guy?
-If I'd know that I was going
to get stuck carrying you,
I would have made a few
extra modifications.
-It can't be helped.
Renji and I have become Soul
Reaper, so we can't be seen.
-If I was riding around
on Orihime's back,
I'd never complain.
-If we should get
into trouble, just
drop him in the
nearest gutter and run.
-I heard that!
-Nothing would make me happier.
But unfortunately, I've packed
some important tools inside
of him.
-Huh?
What tools?
Ah.
Wha?
Huh?
What is this?
-I removed some stuffing
from your stomach
and made a pocket so
I could bring along
a few things I needed.
-Wow.
I've never even
thought of that before.
-I bet something like this
would sell like hot cakes.
-Damn you.
I should report you to
the stuffed animal rights
organization.
-Should someone stay outside
and keep watch, just in case?
-If they didn't
have any hostages,
it might be different.
But we're going to need
every man we've got.
[laughter]
RIRIN (OVER INTERCOM): Welcome!
We've done everything
you've asked us to do!
Now show yourself!
RIRIN (OVER INTERCOM):
First we play hide and seek!
You guys are it!
-What the hell?
We didn't come to play games!
RIRIN (OVER INTERCOM):
Don't be such spoil sports!
If you find us, I promise
we'll return your friends.
-All right.
I guess we'll find you, then.
RIRIN (OVER INTERCOM): Oh!
One other thing.
Take off your weapons
and leave them there.
-What?
RIRIN (OVER INTERCOM):
You never know
what might happen to your
friends if you don't play.
-I hate that brat.
RIRIN (OVER INTERCOM): you
can put them in those cases.
-They even spelled it wrong.
-That little
circle's really cute.
-Shut up!
-That's not funny!
-You two are playing
right into their hands
when you react that way.
-Just shut up!
-What can you do?
You might as well
reason with a brick.
Huh?
-What's wrong?
-I take it you don't
feel that, then?
-Nothing just now.
But I have felt a strange
spiritual pressure
since we got here.
-Interesting.
-Kon!
You need to tell us if anything
unusual happens behind us.
-I got your back!
-What's with this place, anyhow?
-Huh?
-Hm?
-It seems like the same room,
just over and over again.
-When I came here before, it
was definitely not this big.
[laughter]
RIRIN (OVER INTERCOM):
We're over here.
Over here.
-Which way?
-The best way out
of a labyrinth is
to advance with your hand
against the same wall.
And I suggest we
start over there.
-Doesn't seem like there's
anything out of the ordinary.
-I just noticed something.
We've been moving
steadily to our right,
so the room directly
to our right
should be the room
that we started in.
But instead, there's
another room to the right.
-It's the same room.
What's going on?
-I say we head back
the way we came.
-What's wrong?
-The entrance isn't
there anymore!
-That's impossible.
-Kon!
This is your fault.
I told you to keep
your eyes open.
-I've been watching
the entire time,
but there was nothing
out of the ordinary.
[laughter]
RIRIN (OVER INTERCOM):
You're not doing so hot.
At this rate, you'll
never solve the puzzle.
-Dammit.
-I'm about ready to start
kicking these walls down.
-No, wait.
I don't think you'll
accomplish much by doing that.
This is obviously
some sort of game
they've cooked up in
order to make fun of us,
and now it's our job to figure
out how to solve this puzzle.
-Puzzle?
-Yes.
They must have given
us some sort of hint.
[laughter]
RIRIN (OVER INTERCOM):
The boy with the glasses
is getting warm.
-They're making fun of us now.
-All they're trying to
do is get into your head.
Once you're thinking
about them, you're
not focused on
solving the problem.
-Yeah.
But they're so
freaking obnoxious.
-They're using a strategy
which strips away our abilities
to defend ourselves
while at the same time
strengthening their position.
If we don't think calmly,
we haven't got a chance.
-I'll give it a try.
-Wait.
I've got an idea.
[laughter]
KON (OFFSCREEN): That tickles!
-We'll base the
investigation from here.
-And I'm stuck holding
this thing, huh?
-Not at all.
This is an important job
that only you can do.
We're depending on you here.
-Oh.
Well, then, since
you put it that way,
I suppose I could help you out.
But you two better show
a little gratitude!
-He'll believe anything.
-We should start off by
moving straight ahead.
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): We
haven't seen that room yet.
URYU (OFFSCREEN):
Let's check it out.
-There's something here.
-They look like display cases.
-What the--
RENJI (OFFSCREEN):
Over here, too.
-Uryu--
-Look!
-What?
-Orihime!
-Ichigo!
-Chad!
Renji!
-What's going on?
-Hey, guys.
I'm not liking this!
[laughter]
-I can't raise my arm.
My body-- this is bad.
-Hey!
Wake up!
Ichigo!
-That hurts!
-My stuffing is coming out!
My stuffing!
-Uryu!
Renji!
Wake up!
-This place is dangerous!
-Come on.
We gotta get out of this room.
-You got that right.
Follow me, you guys!
-Dammit.
-All I know is the
three of you passed out
and went down like
sacks of potatoes.
Show the man some love
for saving you jerks.
-The mist in there
must have contained
a hallucinogen, or something.
[laughter]
RIRIN (OVER INTERCOM):
You sould be careful.
-I really hate that laugh.
-This room appears
to be safe enough.
-Renji!
Wait!
That was close.
-The floor just
suddenly disappeared.
[laughter]
-Too bad.
-Damn her.
-This doesn't make any sense.
It's like an infinite
loop, but that's impossible
considering the size
of this building.
-Well, impossible or not--
-You guys had better
take a look at this.
-That's the pole we tied
that line of yarn to earlier.
That can't be.
-Uryu, take Kon off
your back, will ya?
-Uh, sure.
-OK.
Hold on tight.
-Huh?
Whatcha doin'?
Ah!
Oh, that-- ah!
-Hm?
[groaning]
-It's like a Mobius strip.
They've somehow
twisted this building
into an unending labyrinth.
-And that's why we always
end up at the same place?
-But wait.
That's physically
impossible for them to do.
-It's the only answer
I can come up with.
And if we're going
to win this game,
we've got to figure out
how they've done it.
I'm drawing the path
we've taken so far.
It's like this.
We ran into traps in this
room, and this room here.
-So according to this, if we
go into the room ahead of us,
there's going to be a trap.
-But if we move
in an L formation,
we shouldn't hit any traps.
-You've solved the puzzle.
Good work, Uryu.
Now we can find those guys
and end this stupid game.
-Yeah!
-If only it were that easy.
-This sucks!
-We'll find it.
The answer must
be here someplace.
-Man, Uryu.
How many things did you
stuff inside me, anyway?
-I can't take it anymore.
We're going in circles, and
even those voices have stopped.
-Stop running your
mouth and start
using your head to
figure this out.
It's hard to believe that you're
a lieutenant of the 13 Court
Guard Squads.
-What did you say?
-Stop it, both of you.
-Not to mention
that you're supposed
to be in charge of
this little town,
and if you'd done your
job right, none of this
would have happened.
Idiot!
-Well, you should be thankful
that a lieutenant even
set foot in this
stinky little town!
[laughter]
-Huh?
RIRIN (OVER INTERCOM):
They're fighting.
-I've had enough!
Stop playing these stupid
games and show yourselves!
-When are you going to
see that this is pointless
unless we can solve this puzzle?
-If you're so smart, why
haven't you solved it?
-Why don't you shut up?
-Stop it, you two.
We're all just tired and
frustrated right now.
We need to calm down.
-Stay out of this!
I'm done.
From here on out, I
can handle this myself.
-Yeah?
Well, good riddance.
Because I'm tired of picking up
after your dumb ass mistakes.
-Hmph!
-Oh, give me a break.
[laughter]
RIRIN (OVER INTERCOM):
A split among friends!
-I wouldn't be his friend if
he was the last guy on Earth!
-Whatever.
What's happening?
The space is twisting.
-Is he crazy?
According to your drawing, there
should be a trap in that room.
-Advancing in an L shaped route.
Mobius strip.
Traps that block our way.
The spiritual pressure
when that gate appeared.
When Chad and
Orihime disappeared.
And ever since the moment
we entered this building--
it feels like-- I've got it!
Ichigo!
Renji!
-Hm?
-I figured out the secret.
-Are you sure?
-Really?
-Listen closely.
-Wait.
Could it really
as simple as that?
-You're sure you want
to take that chance?
-I'm willing to take
that risk, but I'm
going to need one thing.
Can I borrow your
substitute combat pass?
-What do you want to do with it?
-It's just in case.
Here I go.
-Uryu!
-I knew it!
[laughter]
RIRIN (OFFSCREEN): Very good!
-What is this?
[laughter]
-How'd you figure out
the secret to my puzzle?
-We pieced together the hints.
Once I wrote it down,
I figured it out.
It's like a game
that children play.
There are nine rooms
placed in a 3x3 format.
You just made them
loop infinitely.
If we were to go three spaces
either forward or horizontally,
we would win.
So, whenever you felt
like we were getting
too close to that
third room, you'd
create a diversion with a trap.
Your traps were
all hallucinations.
It would've been far too
difficult to set up real traps
to match our movements.
But you knew you
could lead us where
you wanted using hallucinations.
We discovered the traps
and avoided them unharmed,
but that's what you had intended
because you'd only set them up
as a psychological trick.
You counted on the fact
that since our friends had
been kidnapped when
they were alone,
we'd be extra cautious, and
would stay together as a group.
It took you by surprise when we
suddenly split apart and took
up three spaces simultaneously.
You probably started to
worry, because you never
expected their
pig-headed stubbornness
to outweigh their desire
for self preservation.
And you knew the illusion
was not infinite,
because when Renji and Ichigo
were nine spaces apart,
that's when the twist
in space appeared.
So finding that clue was
actually just a lucky break.
Then all we had to do
was get through the rooms
with imaginary traps,
and connect three spaces.
-That's right.
However--
-Uryu!
-Solving that puzzle was
only a part of the game,
because the game's not
over until you catch us.
-Now, that's where you're wrong.
[groaning]
-I thought so.
You really are Mod-Souls.
-How did you know?
-When I entered the
museum, I thought
I recognized the traces of
your spiritual pressure.
Then I realized that
they're the same
as Ichigo's stuffed animal.
Despite the embarrassment of
carrying this backpack around,
I learned about
the characteristics
of a Mod-Soul's
spiritual pressure.
-Are you calling me
an embarrassment?
-Renji, did you pick up on that?
-Naw.
-The one who appeared
out of nowhere
used his power to
manipulate space.
And I assume the
one who showed us
those hallucination
traps is you?
[whimpering]
-I think it's about time you
tell us exactly what you want.
Huh?
[laughter]
-Wait!
Orihime!
Chad!
-What's going on?
-How did you--
-I don't know.
We just found ourselves
standing there.
-Huh?
-Look out.
They're going to
use that gate again.
-No.
Not this time.
-We played hide and seek,
and you won fair and square.
So we're giving you your
friends back, like we said.
-You can have these back, too.
-Where are you going?
[laughter]
-I have to go get ready
for the next game!
[laughter] School
is about to begin.
All good students should
be in their classes.
-What's she mean?
RIRIN (OFFSCREEN): I'd
go quickly if I were you,
or your friends may
start to disappear.
-Wait!
Come back here!
[laughter]
[theme music]
URYU (OFFSCREEN): Now that we
know our enemies are Mod-Souls,
it'll be easier for us to
formulate a plan of attack.
RIRIN (OFFSCREEN): You'd
be foolish to think
that we're the same
as a certain idiot.
KON (OFFSCREEN): Who are
you calling an idiot?
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN):
Apparently you,
because you responded to her.
KON (OFFSCREEN): Uh, yeah.
[theme music]
KON (OFFSCREEN): Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers.
FEMALE VOICE: Golden.
NARRATOR: The Female
Soul Reaper Association.
An officially
sanctioned association
of the Soul Society,
created to elevate
the status of the society
of female Soul Reapers.
It serves as a
shadow organization,
influential in the
management of Central 46.
-Everyone.
Thank you for waiting.
Our chairman is
ready to address you.
Madam Chairman?
-OK!
Is everybody ready to play?