The Zanpakuto... Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined by
its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper and
dies with its Soul Reaper.
That is the existence
of a Zanpakuto.
He's here.
Yes, I'm quite sure you
know him very well. Head
Captain Genryusai
Yamamoto.
I do, but who are the
others?
They are Zanpakuto and
they are working together
to seal away Genryusai
Yamamoto's power.
Things have remained in
this state for quite some
time now.
Working together?
Hey, get away from there!
You're going to force
him to use his Spirit
Energy.
Don't blame us if his
Spirit Energy burns you
to ash.
Yeah!
As you could imagine, he
has been very difficult
to reason with.
The Head Captain has
become quite troublesome
for us.
Byakuya!
It's you!
Damn.
What the-?!
W--wait!
You said you know where
the Old Man is. So let's
hear it.
Well, I can tell you this...
Not only is it the most likely
place he would be...
...But I also sensed the
Head Captain's Spiritual
Pressure near there.
Hmm...
What should we do?
There's not much point
in waiting for them to
come to us.
It's never been our
nature to wait, anyway.
Come on, Kenny!--We
really should get going!
Our turn to find the old
fella! All right?!
You can relax. We're not
playing hide and seek.
Hey!
The guy that I want to
fight is probably there,
right?
Yeah, I'm
pretty sure.
You just be sure that
you don't take on the
Head Captain by mistake.
I'm pretty sure I can
tell the Old Man apart
from that traitor.
How about it? Will you
two be coming with us?
I'm completely bored out
of my mind!
Your idea of what
constitutes fun and
excitement on a daily
basis
is enough to give
anybody else a heart
attack.
That sounds just a bit
cruel.
Yeah, but it's true.
When I became free I
was hoping it would be
the beginning of a much
more interesting life
with my master not
bugging me anymore.
Instead, you've gone and
let your master easily
overpower you.
What?! That's because
you got in my way!
I'm quite aware of that.
And I think I was more
easily overpowered.
What's wrong? You're
not even trying to put
up a fight.
Well, I have to agree with
you, I'm just exhausted from
all this overwhelming boredom.
[sighing]
Who's there!?
Kazeshini?
You really shouldn't
scare us like that!
Kazeshini!
What happened?!
Oh, no. His
wounds are bad.
You're right. I'm
surprised he made
it back here.
What are you doing?
Glad you could make it
back, Kazeshini.
Now rest up so your
wounds can heal.
[struggling]
Muramasa--
What is it,
Kazeshini?
There's something I've
been wanting to ask you.
Go ahead.
You said to use my
intuition, that I must
always follow my instinct.
Of course I
remember that.
Well, I'm certain my true
instinct is to reap the
lives of Soul Reapers.
I'm well aware of that.
And my mission is to
release all Zanpakuto from
their Soul Reaper masters.
Then...
Tell me why the hell a
Soul Reaper is standing
right there?!
That Soul Reaper is Byakuya
Kuchiki, and he plays a
crucial role in achieving
our greater objective.
I am very thankful that,
with all your help,
Byakuya was able to make
it here safely.
Okay, fine. Then explain
why any of us should have
to suffer just to have this
Soul Reaper around.
Even though we have
a greater objective
to consider,
it saddens me that
Zanpakuto have been hurt.
But there's no need to
worry...
...As long as we have
Genryusai Yamamoto, the
Soul Reapers will not do
anything too drastic.
We are very close to
achieving our goal.
They should be getting
desperate by now.
Sorry to ask this of
you, but you'll have to be
patient for a bit longer.
This certainly is
the Head Captain's
Spiritual Pressure.
But I'm also sensing some
kind of powerful barrier
around it.
Ryujinjakka was probably
too much for Muramasa to
manage.
He must have placed
Old Man Yama in a special
containment field.
We would be very
fortunate if it's true we
don't have to take on the
power of Ryujinjakka.
You seem to be pretty
positive that the Old Man
is down there somewhere.
Correct. There's no
mistake. He's here.
The only problem is that
this cave meanders through
the ground like a maze.
Ooooh.
[sniffing]
Also...
There is another entrance
on the other side but I'm
sure that it's guarded as
well.
If they are all in there,
we must proceed with
extreme caution.
What a pain in the ass.
How about we cut the chatter
and start moving?
You show them, Kenny! Way
to go, Kenny! Go! Go! Do it!
Go! Go, Kenny!
Brother! I guess there's
no reason to plan a surprise
attack at this point.
Yeah. And no sense in waiting
around to see what they're
going to do. Let's go.
Good idea.
Ichigo... We'll use the
other entrance and meet
them inside.
Right.
The Soul Reapers are
coming.
Yeah...
Damn. This sucks.
I came in here ready and
rarin' for a fight.
But how am I supposed
to find a fight if I can't
even see where I'm goin'?
Hey, Yachiru. Which way
do you think we should go?
Let's see... That way!
That's no help. I can't
see which way you're
pointing.
No, not this
way! That way!
Hey! Stop that, you
idiot! Quit messing
around!
Yoruichi...
Yes? What
is it?
There's something
I need to know.
All right.
Do you think Byakuya is
here as well?
He's a popular subject
today. Are you worried
about him, too?
Yeah...
Byakuya joined the
Zanpakuto and turned
his sword on Renji. He
even threatened Rukia.
I don't understand what
his motivation would be
for all of this.
It is really quite simple.
My desire...
... Is to uphold
my self respect.
That is all.
But I thought...
maybe you would
have more insight.
I don't have a clue.
Ichigo!
Huh?
Relax, my friend. You
need to calm down and
stay focused if you plan
to confront Byakuya.
I'm sure that boy has his
reasons, although what they
are is beyond me. But I--
What is this?
That's odd..
I had heard that you used
to be the commander of
the Stealth Force.
You're not presenting
us with much of a
challenge today.
Stealth Hoho--Shiho
Number Three...
Utsusemi!
Having a little trouble?
Girls these days are all
talk and no muscle.
Go on, don't wait for me,
Ichigo! Right now, saving
the Head Captain takes
top priority!
When you're done with
that.. You'll be free
to go off and do whatever
you like.
I'm on it.
What a charming array of
steps --My feet tingle
with excitement!
That's very positive of
you. Do you mean that?
I was being sarcastic!
Look at 'em...
You and I are gonna have
to climb all the way up
those steps to make it
through this cave!
What shall we play?
Want to play?
Who's there?
He wants to
know who we are.
He does?
Do you really not know
who we are?
Really!?
Come on, let's play!
Oh brother... I guess
you'll have to deal with
them. If you don't, we
won't be able to move on.
Yeah, but I'm just not
comfortable fighting with
kids, even if they're
Zanpakuto.
Well, good luck. What
else can I say? Do
your best.
So now then... How
about you two tell me
who you are?
Who could we be?
Yeah, who?
I'm guessing
Sogyonokotowari, right?
That's correct!
Aw, he figured
it out right away.
How boring!
Sorry, I couldn't help
myself. I spoiled your
game, huh?
It's okay. Let's
begin the next game!
Yeah, let's do it!
What do you want to play?
How about throwing fans?
That sounds great!
All right!
One..!
Two...!
Three!
Ready... go!
Well, now. What kind of
game can I expect to play
with you, Miss?
Well, unfortunately...
Game-time for you is
over, I'm afraid.
Oh, don't say that. We've
known each other for a long
time.
I'm sure there must be
some way we can reconcile
our differences.
I refuse. Your arrogance
is unbearable.
To be perfectly frank,
we've run out of patience
with you.
Did you say 'we' ?
That would explain the
other Spiritual Pressure
I've been sensing.
It's nice to know I
haven't just been
imagining it.
Ah, you finally decided
to show up.
Oh...
That saves me time,
looking for you.
I'm glad you could come,
Soul Reaper. Now I'll
get my revenge from our
last encounter!
The Head Captain must be
down this way.
He's not alone.
Hey, wait!
The Head Captain's
Spiritual Pressure.
He's here!
Wha...?!
What?!
Die! Soul Reaper.
You bastard!
I won't let you go!
It's time for me to reap
your life!
Bankai!
No!
Getsuga tensho!
Damn it!
Shuhei. I'm sorry.
That was intense.
Well...
I guess it's up to me.
Let's do this!
Well, I never would have
imagined that my swords
could be so beautiful.
And I never expected mine
to be children.
I wonder if there's some
way I could get on their
good side and not have to
fight them.
Yeah, I want to play with
them for a while.
Please fight them.