The Zanpakuto. Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined
by its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper and
dies with its Soul
Reaper.
That is the existence of
a Zanpakuto.
[laughing]
So the only defense left
for you is running away?!
So, You run away and hide,
then attack me from the
shadows? You fight just
as dirty as you look!
Fight Dirty?!
What's wrong with that?
Does it really matter in
a life or death situation?
I prefer to look my
opponent in the eye.
You think I care how you
fight!?
I am a Zanpakuto whose
sole aim is to harvest as
many lives as I can.
I have no interest in
how my master fights.
I was under the
impression that you and I
had a mutual understanding.
Through communication.
We formed a relationship
where we were a synergistic
unit.
I can't say I know
about other Zanpakuto!
But I know who I am. I
exist to reap lives!
That was the only thing
I was responsible for in
this relationship.
Is that so? Then you
have left me no choice.
If killing you means losing
my Zanpakuto, then so be it.
I just realized something.
I don't like you.
That's fine with me.
I feel the same...
So Sword Beasts are
attacking the Rukon
District?
Yeah. They've teamed up
and are on a rampage!
We better hope we're
not too late!
Enough talk!
Keep running!
What was that?!
Well, speak of the devil!
Looks like we found one!
You're wrong.
That's not a
Sword Beast.
Could that be--?
Shuhei... isn't
that your Zanpak---
Just go on without me,
guys. I'm the on he's after.
Hey!
Come on, you guys. We've
got to keep moving. Let's go!
Hold on!
Not too bad.
Again with your surprise
attacks. You don't quit.
That's right. I'm sorry,
but until we settle our
fight, I'll do whatever
it takes to get you.
I'll pursue you to the
ends of the earth, to
the death!
Reap Kazeshini.
Haah!
Izuru, what was
that all about?!
That was Shuhei's
Zanpakuto Kazeshini,
wasn't it?
Has it joined up with the
Sword Beasts?
No. It's not
like that!
Shuhei's Zanpakuto,
Kazeshini, is unlike
any other Zanpakuto.
Even after the Muramasa
incident was resolved, he's
continued to act independently
of Shuhei.
Kazeshini is a Zanpakuto
that reaps lives.
Shuhei says that once it
targets someone, it will
keep pursuing that person
until the fight is settled,
Even if that target
is his own master.
So, he's willing to take
his own life to kill?
Really? Then Shuhei sure
is stuck with a difficult
Zanpakuto to deal with.
Yeah.
So! As usual, you keep
running and hiding from
my blade!
And as usual you refuse
to stand where I can see
you and fight.
Always trying to pull a
surprise attack on people.
I don't like the way you do
battle.
I don't care! The only
goal that I have is to
reap your life!
It's meaningless to
debate our methods for
achieving that goal!
Haah!
Bakudo Number Sixty-two!
Hyapporankan!
Ahhh!
Bastard.
Now, you've finally got
what you want!
Well, it's a start.
Just know this, until you
agree to attack me head-on,
I have no intention of
settling our fight.
You're always pushing to
have us fight your way.
I just hate it!
We agree then. We see
this the same. We both hate
the way each of us chooses
to fight.
[grunting]
Hey, sorry I'm late.
What's up, Shuhei? How'd
things turn out?
Okay for now. What's
the situation here?
We were too late. By the
time we got here, all the
Sword Beasts had already done
their damage and disappeared.
We have got to go and
hunt them down before
they go and do this again!
I heard that you attacked
your master again...
Give us a break, will ya?
Because of you and your
thirst for blood,
the Soul Reapers are
worried that all of us
are going to start acting
as crazy as you and cause
a bunch of
trouble for them.
Why do you keep on trying
to take the life of your
master?
Still under Muramasa's
mind control?
That's none of your
damn business!
It's not our business!?
I don't really care what it
is that you do, but just stop
stirring up trouble of all of
us in the process.
We are all
Zanpakuto.
If you want to isolate
yourself, we won't stop you,
but we won't help you, either.
That sounds fine to me!
Because I have no intention
of asking you guys for help,
so good luck out there!
He's so gloomy.
And look who's talking!
[yelling]
Stop!
Well! Fancy meeting you
here!
[grunting]
You're mine!
Huh?!
I'm done wasting
time with you.
Come back here!
Hey!
Why is it so important to
you to protect people you
don't even know?
[breathing hard]
Dammit, I lost him.
[screaming]
What the-?
Help me.
Huh? You again?
You're not him.
Wait!
Huh?
Who are you?
What?
You're definitely not one
of my kind. Are you one of
the Soul Reaper's dogs?!
You call me a Soul
Reaper's dog? You've
got some nerve.
[baby sounds]
[struggling]
You're not one of them,
are you? You're different.
Don't lump me in with
those Sword Beasts.
I beg of you. Please
look after my baby.
Say what?
[cooing]
No way, kid.
I'm not a Sword Beast
or a nanny. I'm a Zanpakuto.
I have no interest in
anything, except for
reaping lives.
[cooing]
Damn. This kid's blood would
probably rust my blade...
Huh?
[cooing]
Let go.
Move!
[choking back tears]
Uh-uh!
[sobbing]
Knock it off!
I hear a baby!
It's coming from
over there!
Come on! Stop it! Don't
cry! Shut up, please?!
You leave me no choice!
Listen, kid. The fact that
you're still alive is a miracle.
Be grateful for that, now, go
disappear somewhere.
Man, you need to
learn to take a hint.
[cooing]
Ahhhh, stop following me,
you pesky runt! I've had it!
Time to lose you, you rugrat!
[giggling]
Oh, so you like hangin'
around like that. Well then
just hang in there, they'll
find ya. So long!
[struggling and crying]
Ha-ha ha-ha ha hah!
What the hell? What have
you got on your back?
Kazeshini, he looks
so good with you!
Dammit, woman,
I'll kill you.
Hey, kid. Laugh.
I said laugh.
What a gloomy kid.
Well, you're not exactly
Mister Sunshine, yourself.
So you and this baby have
become buddies?
You should've just left
the kid somewhere. Like
the middle of a lake.
Shut up!
I don't know how, but
it just turned out this
way.
I kinda got stuck with
him. Anyways, how about one
of you take this kid. Huh?
Uh, guys?
Are you whining? Earlier
you made a big point of
saying you had no intention
of asking us for help...
Oh, but that's
not what I meant!
Well we wish you good
luck raising a kid!
Bye-bye!
Hey, wait! I--
Ah!
What the hell's
going on?
Something just doesn't
feel right. Why is this
happening to me?
That Spiritual Pressure.
That means those Lieutenants
are on the move again. That's
my cue.
Hey, don't touch that!
You wanna die?! Stop it,
you're gonna cut yourself!
I said no,
that's final!
[crying]
[grunting]
Okay, okay, enough!
Quit your wailing!
Man, this brat is really
getting under my skin.
Huh? What now? What?!
Oh, no! You're kidding,
right?! Not that!
[screaming]
[giggling]
Dammit. This really
messes things up.
There they are!
And what was that for?!
[yawning]
Hey. Now, don't you start
falling asleep here!
[grunting]
So Shuhei, have you
heard the latest?
About what?
Some of the Zanpakuto
have told me, there's this
interesting rumor that's
been going around.
A rumor about your
Zanpakuto.
Hm?
There you are.
Oh.
You stay right here.
[sighing]
All right, then.
Whaa!?? Ahhhh!
There. Just stay here and
be quiet for a while.
[screaming]
Help! Another Sword
Beast!
Hey! Stop! Damn! You're
not getting away!
This is taking too much
of my time.
Hey, you stubborn
bastards!
[baby crying]
What now?! You've gotta
be kidding me!
Now is my best
opportunity yet!
[baby crying]
[grunting]
Aaah!!
[baby crying]
There, there, baby.
You're fine...
Don't cry! Huh?
Please don't hurt
us! Leave us alone!
No, don't go to him!
Listen...
Y-Yes?
Did you try to take this
baby with you?
Yes. He was here all
alone, just crying.
Do me a big favor. Take
this kid and--
[screaming]
Looks like I caught
a Soul Reaper's dog!
We kill our enemies!
[laughing]
Now, you're done!
Ahhhhhh!
[heavy breathing]
Well! Fancy meeting you
here!
[screaming]
Uh!
[cooing]
Huh?
Take him and get far away
from here.
Huh?
Please, just
get out of here.
Uh-right!
[crying]
[heavy breathing]
Hmmm?
Hey.
I'm here for you.
This is what you wanted.
You said until I agree to
attack you head-on, you had
no intention of settling our
fight. That right?
Yeah.
Well, that's why
I'm here.
Right.
Now, Reap.
♪Sleep my baby. Sleep
my lovely...♪
♪Close your eyes,
my sweet.♪
♪
[grunting]
I've got one question.
What did you do with
that kid?
Huh? Heh! I don't know
what you're talking about!
Heh!
Hey, why don't we end
this once and for all?
Yeah, good idea.
I guess we can
get along.
You think so?
[crying]
Don't... cry.
Hey...
Hm?
Am I going to change
back? Will I become a
normal Zanpakuto?
Yes, you will.
When I'm a Zanpakuto
again...
You and I... what is
it that we will be
fighting for?
We will fight to
protect something.
[grunting]
I see.
Do I sound like a
hypocrite to you?
Yeah, I'd say you do,
but then again...
It doesn't sound like
a bad idea.
Well, that's that,
huh?
Hey Wabisuke, what's
the story with that baby
Kazeshini was carrying
around?
He's caring for this
baby and keeping it
a secret.
So there's only one
conclusion we can draw
from those two things.
Are you saying...?!
It was his love child.
I knew it!