[attack yell]
What?!
[attack growl]
[panting breaths]
(Renji)
Where are they?
Did we get them!?
(all)
[gasping]
Looks like
you did it.
Mhm.
Way to go,
Nozomi! That
was awesome!
I guess...
[gasp]
[angry breath]
[heavy breathing]
[gasp]
Brother!
Did you think... that
I'd be defeated so
easily by a technique
like that?!
Hado Number
Seventy-Three...
Soren Sokatsui!
[screams]
Time to finish
you off.
[gasp]
What?!
Damn you!
[dying shout]
(Ichigo)
Head Captain!
Why are
you here?
Hm.
[gasp]
Is she the one
you mentioned
to me in your
report?
(Rukia)
Yes. She's
Nozomi Kujo.
[gasp]
The name does
not matter. She
is nothing more
than a Mod Soul.
[sad sigh]
Wait a minute!
Where are your
manners?!
You can't just waltz
in here and dismiss
this girl like she
was nothing!
With all due
respect, Sir...!
This girl can help
us defeat Kageroza!
Her Zanpakto
can absorb an
enemy's Spirit
Energy!
Trust me, the
last thing we
need is help
from a Mod Soul.
Look here, you old
geezer! She may be
a Mod Soul, but she's
still a young girl!
And there's
no reason to
insult her--!
Keep quiet,
big mouth!
Hm..?
[frightened whimper]
Wait! You've
gotta hear me
out!
Yes, Nozomi is a
Mod Soul, but what
difference does
that make?!
You will find
out soon enough...
Let's talk now!
She's on our
side! She's one
of us!
(Genryusai Yamamoto)
End of discussion!
There's more
of them..!?
Uryu! Chad! Do
what you can for
the others. Take
them to Orihime!
All right.
[grunt]
OK, let's take
care of business.
[painful groans]
Renji!
Don't try to
act so tough!
You need to stay
back here with Rukia.
Shut up..!
I can still
fight...
Enough! In your
condition you won't
help. You will only
get in the way.
[grunt]
...Yes, Sir.
[gasp]
I see. You
two again.
Master Genryusai...
Oh brother... This
kinda sucks for us.
We have to fight
Old Man Yama.
Too bad.
There's no
way around
it.
You got
that right.
All waves rise
now and become
my shield!
Lightning strike
now and become my
blade!
Sogyonokotowani!
Flower wind rage...
and Flower god roar!
Heavenly wind
rage! And Heavenly
deamon sneer!
Katenkyokotsu!
Impressive. I must say
you both look very
convincing, considering
you're imposters.
Why thank you.
Your words of
praise do us
honor.
Nevertheless, the
two of you are
still brats,..
...and you need
to be taught a
painful lesson.
All things in
the universe
turn to ashes!
Ryujinjakka!
Ichigo Kurosaki!
Yeah?
You need to
stay back
as well!
I'm fighting
with you!
That is an order!
I cannot guarantee
you will be safe
in the cross fire!
Oh!
What the hell!?
Whaaaa?!
I will put
an end to
this myself!
The young lady
says she is
going to take
us on.
That's fine, but
we better make
sure we capture her
without hurting her.
You're right I
presume you are
aware of what her
Zanpakto can do.
Very much so.
And we both have
to be careful
when we cross
swords with her...
(Shunsui Reigai)
...or she'll suck
away our Spirit
Energy.
Hiyaaahh!
[gasp]
[leaping grunt]
[battle grunts]
Nozomi! Stay
back!
[attack grunts]
No I won't!
You're a
feisty one!
[battle grunts]
Those damned
children. What do
they think they
are doing!?
Bakudo Number
Sixty-One!
Rikujokoro!
Bakudo
Sixty-Two!
Hyapporankan!
Bakudo Sizty-
Three!
Sajosabaku!
[grunt]
Bakudo
Seventy-Five!
Gochutekkan!
Seems as if
the fight has
distracted you.
You were wide open.
That's not
like you at
all.
[small chuckle]
[battle grunts]
What's wrong, Ichigo?
Your Spirit Energy
seems to be fading
fast,,,
Shut the
hell up!
Hiya!
Come on,
Ichigo...
He's not
doing so
well!
[panting breaths]
He's in
trouble.
What can
we do?
[grunt]
Where is
he!?
[gasp]
Hiya!
You're in
my shadow?
Sorry... Did
I surprise you?
It's called,
"Kageoni."
[leaping grunt]
Well I'll be
damned! You
figured it out
already!
(Shunsui)
You're right. I can't
use Kageoni unless
there's a shadow.
(Shunsui)
However...
Katenkyokotsu is
very versitile. It
knows a lot of other
fun games. For example...
[gasp]
...This one! Where
the one who's higher
up is stronger, known
as Takaoni!
[grunt]
[gasp]
I know how
your Zanpakto
works...
If our swords
touch, my Spirit
Energy will be
absorbed/
[sigh]
[kicking grunt]
[scream]
I beg your
pardon, I over
did it a little.
[groan]
Heh. Well that's
a relief!
If I had injured
you I'd be in big
trouble with my
boss.
[attack yell]
[fighting grunts]
(Thinking)
What should I do?
Bankai, then
Getsugatensho?
I bet you're
trying to decide
whether or not
to use Bankai.
[gasp]
I sense even if
you did use Bankai,
you couldn't maintain
it for long.
And I'm guessing you aren't
able to unleash Getsugatensho
more than two or three more
times at the most.
We'll see!
(Nozomi)
Screams
Iro Oni...
Black!
[scream]
Nozomi!
(Thinking)
I've gotta
make a move!
[fighting grunts]
Bankai!
Hm?
Getsugatensho!
If you're going to
attack someone, you
need to understand
you're opponent's power.
Otherwise, you're
just going to waste
a perfectly good
offensive.
Huh?
[heavy breating]
Looks like your
spirit energy has
dropped again.
[grunt]
Oh no! This
is bad! Real
bad!
Will you
calm down!?
How can I stay
calm!? Both Nozomi
and Ichigo are
in big trouble!
The worst part
is, I can't do
a darn thing to
help out...
I'll go
help him.
I'll go,,,
with you...
You can't do this!
Neither one of you
can do anything in
your condition!
You need to
stand down!
Shut your mouth.
[gasp in pain]
[choking] Your
attack technique is
just as effective
as ever, Rukia.
But you still
can't go! You
heard the old
geezer!
In your
condition
you'll just
get in the way!
Even so, sometimes
you have to put
yourself out there.
Rukia's right
about that.
If we could get
a single hit...
[gasp]
What's the
matter!?
That spiritual
pressure...
[gasp]
(Retsu Reigai)
This can't be..!
(Retsu Unohana)
Why the surprised
look? You should
already know...
[gasp]
(Retsu Unohana)
A Bakudo like
that isn't strong
enough...
(Retsu Unohana)
It would do nothing
more than slow him
down for a moment.
What are you
talking about?
I have a
feeling you
made a critcal
error...
You misjudged the
power of Genryusai
Yamamoto. After
all...
...it isn't by accident
that he's been the Head
Captain of the Thirteen Court
Guard Squads for a millenium.
Everyone get down!
[screaming]
[angry grunt]
Ichigo! Nozomi!
[gasp]
(Kon)
Ichigo! Nozomi!
[nervous gasps]
[gasp]
[grunt]
[grunting]
Hey you old
Geezer! What
the hell!?
You almost
turned us
into ashes!
Where's Ichigo?
Did he get
caught up in
that blast?!
Look! Over there!
[gasp] That was
close. Too close
as far as I'm
concerned.
[gasp]
Say something,
damn it!
Kon, stop it.
Yeah but
Rukia!!!
The existance of Mod
Souls is a bitter
legacy in the Soul
Society's past.
His intention
may have been to
eliminate Nozomi
along with Kageroza.
You mean he's
just gonna wipe
out everybody!?
(Ichigo)
It can't
be..!
(Nozomi)
While I'm alive, both
worlds will continue
to be targeted.
Perhaps eliminating
me is the way to
stop Kageroza.
Don't be
ridiculous!
It's true. I
understand it...
...but I'm
not gonna die.
Yeah, you
got that right!
By the way,
you're holding
me too tight. You
can let go now.
Oh! Sorry!
That was
close...
He had us
there...
You may be
nothing but
imposters...
But from what I've
observed, you use
the powers of my
students well.
I didn't think
you'd still be
standing.
[grunt]
(Kageroza)
That will be
enough!
(Kageroza)
Thank you for
your hard work
everyone...
(Kageroza)
Now please,
step back!
I will
take care
of the
rest...
[gasps]
Hey it's
him! Look!
(Genryusai)
Kageroza Inaba!
(Kageroza)
You're everything I
expected, Head
Captain Yamamoto,
(Genryusai)
Even the power of the
captains working together
could not hold you down.
Despite all that,
everything is
going as planned.
I will take
Nozomi now,
if you don't
mind.
I'm afraid I
still need her
to fulfill my
plans...
[grunt]
[attack grunt]
[panting]
Old man! Listen,
you can't just
undisciminately
attack that bastard!
Silence! Who
do you think you
are talking to,
boy?!
(Genryusai)
I am no idiot! Do you
not think I know what
his abilities are?
Well, if you know,
then all the more
reason for you to
be careful!
Yes, indeed. It
would certaily be a
problem if he were
to copy my techniques.
Then what are
you going to
do?
I suppose I will
have to attack him in
a way that will not
allow him to do that.
Ok...
but how?!
I'll be
your decoy.
Hm?
[gasp]
Are you out
of your mind!?
It's ok. Really,
it's the least
I can do.
It's too
dangerous!
I don't care.
Please understand.
Nozomi...
Help me out
here, Old
Man!
You have
one chance...
[gasp]
Nozomi...
(Thinking)
What's she
up to?
(Thinking)
I doubt she'd allow
herself to be
captured so easily.
Hiya!
So you are trying
to cross swords so that
you can absorb my
Spirit Energy.
Sorry, my dear,
but I won't
fall for that.
[attack grunts]
It's futile!
[attack yell]
When did you
charge that?!
Ha! But it's
still not enough!
Are you ready
to give up?
Hm?
[attack yell]
Negate!
[gasp]
I'll stop you...
using every ounce
of my Spirit Energy!
The Substitute
Soul Reaper!?
Getsugatensho!
[gasp]
Ichigo!!!
They did it.
Did I
get him?
Well...
Ichigo!
[gasp]
(Thinking)
He nearly...
destroyed me...
[grunt]
[gasp]
Ichigo!
This is proof of
my power. My
judgement paid off!
(Kageroza)
Ryujinjakka is certainly
a frightening power...
(Kageroza)
But at the very moment of
his attack, I copied
Nozomi's Zanpakto power...
(Kageroza)
In that instant I
was able to absorb
all of your attacks.
Now my Raiku is
even stronger than
before!
It has the powers
of both Head Captain
Yamamoto's Ryujinjakka--
--and the Substitute
Soul Reaper's
Getsugatensho!
(Kageroza)
As strong as
you are, Head
Captain...
You won't be able
to remain unscathed
after an attack of
such immense power!
[evil laughter]
The time has
come! This ends
right now!
Get out, Head
Captain!
Oh mo!
[gasp]
Out of my
way, girl!
[grunt]
No! What are
you doing!?
Nozomi!
(Rukia)
That Kageroza
really scares me..
(Rukia)
I never know
what to expect
from him.
(Kon)
Hey Rukia! They say
ineracting with something
soft is a great therapy--
(Kon)
--for helping to ease
your worries! Something
like me, for example.
(Kon)
What do you say!?
[gettick smacked shout]
(Rukia)
You're right! That
feels much better.