The Zanpakuto. Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined by
its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper and
dies with its Soul
Reaper.
That is the existence of
a Zanpakuto.
What the hell is this?!
Don't move!
We are here to take you
into custody.
Bankai!
Getsugatensho!
We don't wanna give you
the impression that we
have nothing left.
Hado number thirty-one!
Shakkaho!
I am the Third Seat of
Zaraki's Squad!
Ikkaku Madarame!
Lieutenant Iba!
Oh, Lieutenant Kotetsu.
What's the situation?
Captain Soi Fon and the
others are fighting at
the Squad Six barracks.
We've gotten reports
that the Stealth Force
has the enemy surrounded
and is preventing them
from escaping.
I see. Then I suppose
we should hurry to their
position and give them
some backup.
I agree. Apparently,
there are many fighters
who have been wounded already.
What the--? What's wrong?
Over there!
What the hell is that?
My guess is it's
Ashisogijizo.
How can you tell?
Look at it.
I've never seen
anything like it.
Hey, is it
talking to us?
Well, no matter how weird
it looks, we've got a
Zanpakuto here.
Let's capture it!
Not just yet!
I think that's
poison!
What?! Come on! You
gotta get outta here!
Hado Number One!...Sho!
We better go inform
Captain Kurosuchi
immediately!
Right!
I'm not letting
you do that!
Who are you!?
Great, now it's
raining.
Thunder and lightning are my
allies. It is in this rain that
I can display the special powers
that make me truly great!
What is so funny?!
Correct me if I'm
wrong, but your friend
there. Isn't that Tenken?
I wouldn't think it's
a good thing to let him
get wet.
Well don't worry!...
Even a torrential rain
would have no chance of
extinguishing Tenken's
flames of hell.
I'm not convinced.
The way you just said that
makes me think you're not
too confident either.
What?!
What Tenken? I see.
You're saying that
these rain clouds are
nothing more than a means
to reinforce my technique.
And that even if this
rain itself appears to be
weak, I have nothing to
worry about, right?
I, Gonryomaru, feel
unworthy Tenken, I
allowed myself to be
tricked by her flawed
logic. I am
ashamed.
So how do you communicate
with that fire breather? Do you
have some sort of code like
maybe smoke signals?
Silence!
Tenken usually keeps to
himself and can be shy
and reserved!
You are very weak...
Are you sure you're a
captain-level Zanpakuto?
Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up! You will
not belittle us!
Feel my wrath!
So then, is that the
extent of your power?
You want power!??
You're done!
How'd she..?!
So. Looks like you do
have some power.
This isn't going to be
easy.
Gotcha!
Aw that was close!
I was sure I would get
the second strike in!
So tell me, was that the
first time you were struck
by your own technique!
Yay!
Are you... Suzumebachi?!
Ding ding ding! Right!
You are correct!
So how do you like my
look? I didn't like your
lame style, so I really
went for it!
I've always said to myself if
I ever got free, I would create
my own fashion statement to look
awesomely sharp!
I'm really glad I was
able to manifest myself
the way I wanted to.
What? Do you have a
problem with that?
You always waste your
free time doing something I'd
never do! You worship Yoruichi!
That's so dumb!
You should use that time to pay
more attention to yourself! You
need a change! Go find yourself
a real man!
What the hell? You're
really my Zanpakuto?
So you don't
believe that?!
Maybe another strike
with this will convince
you.
You sure talk a big
game...
You're kind of a
weakling, you know?
You're so irritating!
Damn you!
You look awful mad.
You.
I will... never
forgive you!
Oh well, I didn't
expect you to.
Come on. Why don't you
go ahead and give up?
At least if you gave up
now, I'd still be
willing to let you
live.
I'm never giving up to
you!
Listen.
Notice that Spiritual
Pressure?
Earlier, Ikkaku's
Spiritual Pressure just
disappeared, didn't it?
Ikkaku.
You people have no chance
to win against us with
the level of your
abilities.
Ikkaku did not lose!
Hozukimaru's Spiritual
Pressure disappeared as
well!
Hmph! I suspect that
Hozukimaru tailored his
power to match Ikkaku's
fighting level. As you
know, those two are quite
alike...
But you and I are
different.
You always try to hide my
true nature. I'm proud
to display my power
anywhere.
No! Don't!
I will!
Tear in Frenzy.
Well?
How does it feel to be
struck by the power that
you loathe?
I don't want everyone
to know about this power.
I wouldn't be able to
stay in Squad Eleven.
Are you still saying
that? Why're you so
stubborn?
Must stay in Squad
Eleven.
Again with that!?
Shut up, Fujikujaku!
I see.
[screaming]
Sorry!
And what was that about?!
That woman down there is
your target! It's your
job to keep her in check!
Well I don't see why
I'm the one who has to
back you up!
'Cause that's how it works!
We lost last time because you
didn't hold up your end!
Oh, is that right?
As I recall---
What are those
two doing?
Weird.
Whatever. Let's
move out while we can.
Hey!-Stop!
You are not getting away!
And you over there! Show
yourself!
Oh-no!
Hado 31. Shakkaho!
Damn!
Isane-Are you okay?
No you don't!
My legs! I
can't move!
I see. Don't tell me
you don't know about
the power of Ashisogijizo?
Ashisogijizo deprives its
victims of the ability to
move their limbs.
You were struck by its
attack and now you've
lost the use of your legs.
You're like a little
bird who has had its
wings clipped.
Uh! Where--? It's you!
You shouldn't strain
yourself.
You need to get some more
rest. The ordeal you went
through to get me back
almost killed you.
So what happens now?
Muramasa and the rebels
staged an all-out attack.
The Soul Reapers are out
there battling them now.
I see. Then I can't stay
here in bed any longer.
Have faith.
Your friends are strong.
They will not go down
so easily.
You showed me that
strength when you
reclaimed me, Master.
Stand aside!
It's no use, guy!
Lieutenant Hinamori!
Are you okay,
Isane?
What are you
doing up there?!
Hi!
Not you again!
You're both in trouble!
You two should talk
This time we're not
letting you get away!
Hmph! That's what I was
going to say. Last time you
just got lucky! You caught
us with our guard down!
You old lady!
I'll knock that rudeness
right out of you!
Behind you!
Let's get
out of here!
Who's on the run now,
old lady?
Renji!
Byakuya!
Please make all this
stop!
Damn it!
Ikkaku's Spiritual
Pressure disappeared.
Yumichika's in danger
as well.
Getsugatensho!
Bakudo Thirty Nine!
Enkosen!
Damn! You've got
good reflexes!
But no matter how hard
you can fight, you
yourself can't change
where this battle's
taking place. And I
know you can feel the
Spiritual Pressure
that's all around you!
You sense we're
overwhelming you.
I'm getting sick of
looking at that glare of
yours! I think I'll need
to gauge your eyes out!
Here's a thought...
You think its good to
keep making so many
direct attacks?
What? What do you mean?
Well... If anyone should
know the power of my
Zanpakuto, that someone
should be you, right?
What about it?
Wait-You're not saying
you regained your Shikai,
are you?!
Answer me! Right now, you
coward!
You can't really expect
me to answer that question.
Something must be wrong
with you.
Now that I think of it,
when we were fighting,
this guy did nothing but
fend off my attacks. He
hasn't tried to attack
me once.
But... Why would he go
through all that tedious
stuff when he could've
just used his Shikai?
He's bluffing!
What's the matter?
Shut up!
He dodged it again!
What?!
Over here.
You can't use your
Shikai!
Even if he somehow
miraculously did regain
his powers, I will
shred him to pieces
before he's able to use
that Shikai!
Hado Fifty Eight!
Tenran!
Allow me to put your mind
at ease.
I have not regained my
Shikai yet.
But you were destined to
lose the moment you let
yourself get caught in
your maze of self-doubt.
I knew it!
Bakudo Sixty
Three. Sajosabaku.
All right. I'd better
get going to help out the
others.
Your back is wide open to
attack.
Wabisuke!
Damn it!
You're finished.
Izuru!
What are you looking at?
Out of my way!
Outta my way!
Aren't Shunsui and
Jushiro joining us in
battle?
Uh, actually,
they're--
I see! They're
commanding things from
the barracks! So this pinch
we're in is part of the plan!
Uh, yes, you're right!
I forgot to tell them.