The Zanpakuto... Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined
by its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper...
And dies with its Soul
Reaper.
That is the existence
of a Zanpakuto.
Byakuya!
Brother! Be careful!
A silvery-white
windflower silk scarf
and a Kenseikan...
You're from the Kuchiki
Clan, aren't you?
I'm Byakuya Kuchiki,
the head of the Clan.
Twenty-eighth generation.
The leader of the
twenty-eighth generation.
Well, well...
Obviously, a great deal
of time has passed since
I was sealed away.
So, I assume by now
Ginrei finally died.
How dare you refer to my
ancestor's passing so
flippantly.
You personally ruined the
reputation of the Kuchiki Clan.
Because of that, you will
never have the right to
utter the name of my
Grandfather.
You bastard!
Byakuya, I don't
understand...
What's going on here? I
thought you were on their
side!
You must observe quietly.
This fight is his alone.
He's upholding the Kuchiki
Clan's honor.
I'm confused...
This makes no sense! I
thought your mind was
controlled by Muramasa!
No. There was a time when
Muramasa did try to influence
me. However...
Master...
So you have returned to
your senses, Senbonzakura.
Can you tell me what happened?
I don't know. I suddenly
heard a voice coming from
within my mind.
It told me to release my
soul and follow my instincts.
I see. As I feared.
Byakuya was aware of the
Zanpakuto, Muramasa, and
its master, Koga. His
Grandfather, Ginrei,
told him that Koga had
been sealed away.
You need to know this, my
boy. If by chance the
seal is broken and that
man escapes,
it will be your duty, as
head of the Kuchiki Clan,
to hunt him down and slay
him.
I pass this responsibility
to you.
The world must never be
exposed to his warped,
evil power again.
On my sacred honor as
head of the Kuchiki Clan,
I swear to do this.
Byakuya went to the
archives to search for
any clues as to where Koga
had been sealed away. But--
As he feared, there was
no record of Koga's
whereabouts. All he came
away with was the further
realization that it was
best to keep this to
himself.
So you're saying that
the Soul Reaper over
there, was connected
to the Kuchiki Clan?
So tell us then! For
what reason was this
whole thing hidden
from us?!
It was all for the sake
of learned where Koga had
been sealed away!
Destroying Muramasa
alone would be meaningless.
The one who had to be
defeated was Koga!
In order to continue our
investigation, I acted as
though I was still brainwashed.
But it wasn't easy to
discover where Koga had
been sealed away.
That's why Byakuya stayed
by Muramasa's side.
Even if it meant that his
friends would think that
he betrayed them.
He was willing to risk
his own death?
He had to stay true to
his duty as head of the
Kuchiki Clan.
Byakuya...
Tell me this, head of the
Kuchiki Clan... Do you intend
to seal me away as well?
I do not. I cannot allow
you to remain alive any
longer.
All your actions have been
a disgrace to the Kuchiki Clan.
Now, I will kill
you for that.
How predictable. Spoken
with all the arrogance I
would expect from the
Kuchiki Clan.
So be it.
If you're truly the head
of the Kuchiki Clan...
That's ample reason to
fight you. With or without
your threats.
Koga. Use me. I will
still fight for you.
Hmph.
Your power and mine are
one. My power belongs
to you.
But, w-why?!
You've become nothing
more than a hindrance to
me. I don't need to use a
pathetic, unstable sword
like you. My power
alone's enough.
Damn you! Have you no
loyalty and or respect
for your own Zanpakuto?!
A Zanpakuto is merely a
tool. There are countless
replacements.
Muramasa!
Is his despair so
powerful that it's
impossible for him to
control his Spirit Energy?!
Koga--
What!?
I can't believe what I'm
seeing. He collected Menos
inside of him!
I'm wasting time.
Ichigo...
Byakuya, I get it. You've
only been pretending to
betray us.
Your first duty is to
preserve your Clan's
honor.
That being said... Why not
let us take care of this,
and you focus on defeating
Koga.
He's right.
Ichigo, let's do it!
Right!
Getsugatensho!
Soren Sokatsui!
Senbonzakura...
Let's go.
Yes.
What is that supposed to
be?
You mean this?
Don't you remember? I
said I could find a
replacement weapon.
So, are you ready,
Kuchiki Clan leader?
I must admit, you do seem
to possess the skill of a
Kuchiki Clan leader.
Let's see how you do now
with Kido!
Kongo baku!
Hado Number Thirty-Three
Sokatsui!
Gakirek-ko!
Hado Number Four
Byakurai!
Hyogaseiran!
Hado Number Eighty-One.
Danku.
Byakuya!
Your Kido's no match for
my Senbonzakura. It's
mere child's play.
You'll have to do
better than that.
Watch your mouth,
youngster--Don't be
so smug!
I've captured your shadow.
You are no longer able to
move. Not even a single
finger.
Scatter! Senbonzakura.
It ends here.
You left yourself wide
open... Kuchiki-Clan
leader.
You're not getting away!
What have you done?
How did this happen?
Muramasa was able to
control the Zanpakuto's
minds...
...He got inside them.
His ability to do that
came from my power.
By sending Spirit Energy
into my adversary, I am
able to confuse all of
his five senses.
Your body's senses are
already right in the palm
of my hand.
You can't even tell for
sure if this is actually
me standing here before
you.
An illusion?
Hardly. That's far
too simplistic!
In your present state,
your perception is off.
Your eyes can't tell when
something's coming at
you, nor when to swing
your sword. Nothing
matches up, so you can no
longer fight effectively.
You made it easy...
If you had attacked while
closing off your mind to me,
the way like Ginrei
Genryusai did, I wouldn't
have been able to use this
skill.
When I snapped Muramasa,
I surprised you---You let
your guard down for a
moment.
You're wrong.
What?!
Actually, I challenged you
with my mind completely
wide open, in order to
kill you.
If I had closed my heart, I
might have been able to seal
you away, but I wouldn't have
been able to destroy you.
Considering your
situation, you've got a
lot of nerve to speak to
me like that.
Oh, no you don't!
What?!
Hyogaseiran!
Danku.
Hey, aren't you all
turned around?!
[chuckling]
What a pathetic sight!
Without your Zanpakuto,
it looks like you're
powerless, youngster.
My enemy's skills are so
irrelevant. Everyone falls
to their knees before me!
Yes! And it's all
because of my own power!
I don't need anything
from a Zanpakuto.
I'm the most powerful Soul
Reaper to ever live!
Let's make this your last
day as the Kuchiki Clan
leader!
What the hell?!
Impossible!
It did Shikai by itself?!
Senbonzakura...
Yes, Master. I know your
senses and body have been
shut down...
I will fight as your eyes
and limbs. Instruct me
to do as you wish.
I'm going to control the
senses of both that sword
and you together!
I don't think so.
Bankai.
Senkei. Senbonzakura
Kageyoshi.
This is the true form
of my Senbonzakura...
...A space that focuses
offensive energy for the
sole purpose of defeating
an enemy.
There is no need here
for defensive power. And
confused senses will
not help you.
...For without fail, this
blade will be able to find
you, wherever you are.
Ha-ha. Wherever I
am, you say.
Then let's test the
precision of its guidance.
Damn you! How is it that
you possess so much power?
Because we fight together.
That's what gives us power.
A Soul Reaper and a
Zanpakuto combine to
make one.
We are only able to
display our true powers
when our souls are in
harmony with one another.
Your pride caused you to
abandon the one you need
right now.
Alone, you cannot
defeat us.
Shut up! You don't know
enough about me to judge
me like that!
No one acknowledged what
I did, despite all my
successes.
Instead, they branded me
a traitor and tried to seal
me away! If that was going
to be the case,
I had to create a place
for myself somewhere!
Order is created by
power!
With my power, I am going
to become king of a new
world!
Such foolishness...
What was that?!
The real tragedy is that
you fail to recognize the
true nature of power.
The power you need is to
be able to relate...
... to others. And also,
to connect to your Zanpakuto
in a synergistic way.
You sound like such
a complete idiot!
That has never been the
kind of power I've needed!
My power is like no
other!
Absolute power that has
equal. Not here or anywhere
else in the universe!
It seems there is no use
discussing this.
Blame your own immaturity
for not being able to
recognize that your confidence
is nothing but arrogance.
Koga...
I will now complete my
duty, as head of the
Kuchiki Clan, as I have
foresworn to do...
...Honoring my the wishes
of my predecessors.
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Shukei Hakuteiken.
You are more than I
expected. In a long line
of Kuchiki-Clan leaders,
few, if any, were as
powerful as you.
Because you were once a
member of the Kuchiki
Clan,
I will pay my final
respects by using this
ultimate technique.
I will defeat you. And in
doing so, end this curse of
ever having been part of the
Kuchiki Clan once
and for all!
I was strict with Koga,
but that backfired. I let
Byakuya have his own way,
but he grew up to be
obstinate. I must say,
raising children is
difficult.
The World Of the Living
has lots of how-to books.
Do not give him
any ideas.