Are you Ouko Yushima?
He's not responding so
far.
Hey, you there! Get up!
Wakie wakie! Hey, anybody
in there?!
It's no use.
Huh?
I hate to say this, but
it doesn't look to me
like he'll ever regain
consciousness.
Are you serious?
[straining]
[roaring]
Hey! Snap out of it! Come
on!
It won't do any good.
But if he won't talk to
us, we'll never be able
to get him to reveal the
location of Kageroza's
secret lab.
Here we finally
discovered where the
developer of Mod Souls
was hiding and he's no help.
Actually, I was sort of
expecting this.
Huh?
The Soul Society wanted
to hide the existence of
Project Spearhead...
Knowing he'd be locked
away, Ouko likely---
Uh!
What's going on?
I believe this is
a clue to finding
the lab.
Are you serious?
What is it?
It's blood.
Blood? Whose?
I don't know yet, but it
seems to still be fresh.
It doesn't appear to be
his blood... Which
means... Someone else
came to see him recently.
Kageroza!
Yes.
But how's that blood
going to help us find the
location of the lab?
Well, my friend, we need to
thank Mayuri for that bit
of fortune.
Huh? Wait, isn't that
device for finding
Reishi?
Yes, indeed. Right now
I'm using it to scan
this blood sample so we
can track down Kageroza.
Track him down? But I
thought you said his
Spiritual Pressure
couldn't be detected.
If it was just his blood
alone, we'd be out of
luck...
However, Mayuri was able
to inject Kageroza with a
certain drug.
Can you tell? It's very
powerful. It stops all
thought processes.
[chuckling]
That drug's still in
his system. So if we can
trace the signature matching
this blood, then...
...That's where Kageroza
will be! And we'll find
his lab!
Exactly my thought!
[roaring]
[panting and gasping]
It's a Hollow!
What's it doing here?!
What squad are you men
with?
[gasping]
Lieutenant Ise!
Listen to me carefully.
All squads are to stand
by at their barracks.
But... Where did this
Hollow come from, ma'am?!
And we also sense
Captain-level Spiritual
Pressures clashing
everywhere!
What's going
on here?!
It's very confusing and
upsetting!
Everyone calm down!
[roaring]
[gasping]
That Hollow needs to be
dealt with, immediately.
Take him down.
Yes ma'am!
Hmph.
[grunting]
Give it up. I am the true
head of the Kuchiki Clan.
Hey Byakuya! Looks like
you're having trouble
there, my friend-- Do you
need some help?
No thanks. Do not
interfere.
However, if you need any
help, feel free to ask.
Heh!
[growling]
I don't need help. I'm
havin' way too much fun!
By the way... Let me make
this clear...!
This one's mine, so
don't butt in!
Well now.. Looks to me
like they have the edge
on us.
I see that the
capabilities of the
Reigai have improved.
Damn that Kageroza.
He sure knows how to make
the party exciting.
Say... You think they
brought some drinks?
Don't joke about this.
Here they come.
Bushogoma!
Hey, that's a pretty good
imitation of me!
Bushogoma!
Sogyonokotowari!
Uh!
Huh!
Sogyonokotowari!
Great move!
That was really
nice return fire.
Stop fooling around,
Shunsui! What's the
matter with you?
I guess you're right. It
does seem inappropriate
to the circumstances.
I suggest we make a
strategic retreat.
Right! You heard her,
everyone!
All Captains, cease
your attacks against the
Reigai! We're pulling
back!
I won't give in to these
frauds!
That's an order, Captain!
It's no use trying to
run. You will die here.
Gokei...! Senbonzakura,
Kagayoshi!
Bushogoma!
Guncho Tsurara!
[yelling]
Hado Number Eighty-eight!
Hiryu Gekizoku Shinten
Raiho!
This is the place!
It's humongous! What is
this structure?
It's the Senkaimon, a
gateway to the World of
the Living. It's the main
gate used by all Soul
Reapers in the Soul
Society.
Why exactly are
we here?
I'm not sure myself.
I gotta tell you, you
don't inspire too much
confidence.
[gasping]
Hold it.
Is that a Reigai?
It looks to me like this
is definitely the right
place!
And on top of that, it
looks as though I'll
have to battle it out
with my Reigai, as well.
Listen carefully. While I
distract him, use the
opportunity to find a way
inside.
Wait a minute, why me?!
I'm no good with technology
and computer programs and I
have no idea what to do!
It's really not that
hard. It's just the same
as what I did at the Department
of Research and Development.
I'll try and catch up
as soon as I can. Until
then, it's up to you to
carry out this mission.
Listen, I hear what
you're saying, but I'm
not sure that I can
really...
Remember, Nozomi
could be there.
Is that right?! I'm on
it, then!
That must be the
entrance. Well, here
goes.
[grunting]
You caught me off guard,
friend. I see you came
dressed ready for the
occasion.
You knew it was me all
along? Should have
expected that.
I have to tell you, it
feels kind of awkward..
Crossing swords with
myself like this.
You really think so?
That's funny, it doesn't
bother me at all.
I'm just sorry you insist
on getting in the way!
This is my chance!
[panting]
This way!
Nozomi! Where are you
being held?!
[panting]
No... This way!
Come on, Nozomi!
I'm coming, Nozomi!
[gasping]
Nozomi!
Nozomi! Hey, Nozomi!
It's me, Kon! Can you
hear me? Wake up,
willya?!
[groaning]
Come on, Nozomi! You've
gotta wake up! I'm here
to rescue you! Nozomi!
[gasping]
Will you shut up... you
pervert.
[choking up]
Nozomi...!
I'm gonna get you right
outta there!
But how do I
get you out?
You need to go.
Huh?
Hurry. Get out of here.
I'm not leaving! Why do
you think I came all this
way to find you?!
So just relax! I'm gonna
rescue you and restore
Ichigo's Spirit Energy!
Two birds one stone!
Listen to me! Get out
while you can!
I said I'm not leaving,
so save your breath! I'm
not going to ignore a
friend in trouble!
[grunting]
I'm your friend?
All right. How do I do
this?
Let's see... First, I'll
restore Ichigo's Spirit
Energy...
What did Clog-Dude say?
It's really not that hard.
It's just the same as what I
did at the Department of
Research and Development.
Yeah. Except I can't
remember what he did!
This happens all the
time! I'm such an idiot!
That sounded to me like
Kon screaming. I'd better
hurry!
You're not going
anywhere.
A portable Gigai?!
That's correct.
[grunting]
I even impressed myself!
Damn, I'm good.
Yes, I am. Thanks.
Uhhh... Hmm...?!
Come on, think, of
something, Kon! If I don't
hurry, Nozomi will end up
being fused with Kageroza!
And if that happens,
Ichigo and the other Soul
Reapers will all be
toast!
I'm not going to let
that happen! But damn it,
how are you supposed to
work this thing?!
I'm not kidding! You've
got to get out of here!
I said forget it!
Once the fusion is
complete.. There's no
telling what will happen.
Hold on a minute! Are you
saying you don't even
know what's next? I can't
believe this!
So once you're fused...
Will you no longer be
you?
I don't know. But I know
about Ouko Yushima...
He swore an oath of
vengeance against the
Soul Society.
After all the brilliant
work he did in the
creation of Mod Souls,
they refused to recognize
his accomplishments. To
get revenge, he split
himself into two Mod
Souls...
In the process, his
original body became a
mere shell.
[grunting]
Don't move!
Hey! What happened?!
Damn it! Call Squad Four,
quickly!
Hide... Lose yourself
among those incompetent
Soul Reapers and hide
your existence. And one
day, my legacy shall be
fulfilled... You two will
carry on my will and complete
my research...
[stunned]
By splitting himself in
two, his Spirit Energy
also changed so he
could go unnoticed.
In the split, Kageroza
inherited Ouko's
vengeance and ambition.
And you, Nozomi?
I inherited his
self-control.
Kageroza and I... are
just like darkness and
light.
Like the light? Then there's
a good chance you'll
still remain, after the
fusion!
I can't be sure. In the
end, I could be swallowed
up by the darkness.
What?!!
That is what I've been
trying to tell you all
this time, Kon. The
vengefulness Kageroza
inherited from Ouko
has gotten stronger.
...to the point where
even the light might be
swallowed.
That's why you need to
get away quickly. While
I still have my
consciousness!
Nozomi...
Nozomi!
Nozomi-Wait!!
[struggling]
Nozomi!!!
I told you I'm not
leaving!
[gasping]
How could I leave you?
You said you were the
light.
I was all alone until I
met you.
The truth is, you're my
light, as well.
You and Ichigo changed
that for me.
And I won't let that
light be extinguished!
For the first time in my
life... I see I'm not
alone.
I promise I'll protect
you!
You and I, we're--
We're bound by...
... friendship!
Hado Number Thirty-Two...
Oukasen!
Hado Number Fifty-Four...
Haien!
Another portable Gigai?!
Man, give me a break!
[grunting]
[panting]
Oh, come on! How many
Gigai do you have?!
Why, I oughta--!
[yelling]
Kon...
[groaning]
Damnit. This isn't
working at all.
Mmm.
Listen to me!
Huh?
From this point on, do as
I tell you.
Really? You know what to
do?
From Kageroza... I read
his memory.
What did you see?
I'll tell you, but first,
we're going to need
Ichigo's Reishi.
I brought it with me!
Hey, watch it!
Out of portable Gigai? At
least, that's what it
looks like to me.
You're right, I've used
them all up.
Well, if you have any last
words, go right ahead.
How polite. But I'm
afraid I have some bad
news for you.
Despite what you
think, it isn't over
yet.
Is that so? Well, then...
Hado Number
Eighty-Eight... Hiryu
Gekizoku Shinten Raiho!
A Number Eighty-level
Hado, without an
incantation?!
Hey! It started up!
Nozomi, am I doing this
right?
Think so. Next, flip the
switch on the far right.
Got it!
Oh, yeah! That's the
ticket! It's working!
You can relax now,
Nozomi!
I'll have you out of
there in no time!
So far, so good...
Come on, folks, let's
move it along!
This is sure taking
forever!
Come on, come on! Come
on, already!
I don't want to worry
you, but we seem to be at
a disadvantage here.
Regardless.. We can't
afford to lose this
fight.
You guys don't know when
to give up. Can't you
admit that you can't win
against us?
It's time for the Reigai
to become the real thing.
You might as well
surrender.
I refuse!
I don't understand. Why
do you continue to oppose
us? For what?
Don't make me repeat
myself.
We protect what must be
protected. That's all
there is to it.
We understand. But the
same is true for us, as
well.
Oh please. How can you
say such a thing?
He's right. We're not
really the same as you.
And you're about to see
why. In a few moments,
we'll show you what sets
us apart.
Mm.
I swore an oath to
protect. And that's
what I'll do!
Just a little bit more...
[gasping]
Kon!
Huh?
Ah!
[gasping]
Kon! Kon!
Kon!
What are you doing?!
[trembling]
No, stop it! Stop!
[grunting]
Kon...!
[growling]
[grunting]
Hado Number Thirty-One!
Shakkaho!
Get back!
[gasping]
[growling]
[roaring]
What a pitiful creature.
I'm so proud of myself!
I'm strong, even as a
Reigai!
Come on, did you expect
anything less? There is
one small thing that
bothers, me, though.
What a coincidence! I
have a concern, as well!
The stubble has to go!
Wow, we think alike!