[music -- aqua timez, "alones"]
-There you are, Orihime.
ORIHIME: Miss Yoruichi.
-I've been looking for
you for some time now.
Kisuke asked me to find you.
-Mister Urahara?
YORUICHI: Yes, that's right.
He wants me to bring you to his
subterranean training ground
right away.
-No way!
That's so cute.
That girl has got the most
unbelievable taste in-- ack!
-Can it.
And stop squealing.
[rangiku laughs]
-Rangiku!
Wait, how the hell
did you get in here?
-Through the front door.
It was unlocked, so I came in.
It seems you're
saying at a place
where security isn't
their main concern.
That aside, just
what has this world
done to your fashion sense?
-If you mean this shirt,
the owner of the house
gave it to me.
-You mean you wear whatever the
owner of the house gives you?
How weird.
-[annoyed] was a gift.
I get up a bed and
meals for free.
It would be rude
to turn down a gift
when I'm living off
their good graces.
-Really?
I complain about the food
and clothes all the time.
I never realized it was rude.
-Boy, I sure feel bad for the
sucker she's staying with.
-I know what you mean.
The poor girl, Orihime.
She may be a human, but I'm
starting to feel sorry for her.
-Hey there.
I hope everybody didn't
miss me too much.
So how have you guys
been doing without--
[keigo gasps]
-No way!
Somebody hurry up
and pinch me so
that I know I'm not dreaming.
I said pinch, not kick!
You've underestimated me.
I happen to be Keigo
Asano, and I never
fall for the same attack twi--
-Easy now.
He was only coming
over to say hi
because he was
excited to see you.
-Oh, sorry.
I guess I got carried away.
-I'm home, darling.
Were you a good boy
while I was away?
Huh.
Sorry about that.
I must have the wrong house.
Wait a minute!
This is the right
house all right,
but the wrong woman
is in my kitchen!
Who are you?
-Is the entire house
like these two?
-Well, It's only
going to get worse.
So finish up your business
and get out of here
as soon as possible.
So, what did you come here for?
-Well hello.
Longtime no see, Orihime, Yeah.
I tell you, I've been surrounded
by these two filthy men
for so long now that it just
brightens everything right up
to have a woman in
the workplace again.
I'm glad you're here.
-Oh, so that's how it is, huh?
I guess you don't see me
as a woman anymore then.
YORUICHI: Oh come now, Yoruichi.
I was talking about down
here in the training ground.
Because of your
feminine charms, it's
always bright and cheery
upstairs in the shop.
-Yeah right.
Whatever, Kisuke.
-Please, Orihime.
Sit down right over here.
-Uh, OK.
[crash]
-Oh, it's Chad.
And Renji, too.
-And they're being
just as loud as usual.
-Urahara, I'm pretty
sure he's done,
I'm going to go ahead
and finish up for today.
-Oh no!
Chad!
-Tessai, Ururu, Ririn.
Kindly wake Chad up, please.
-Just leave it to me.
He'll recover fine once I give
him some of this magic tea.
-Yes, hang in there Chad.
You only slightly injured.
And soon, you'll
be as good as new.
So try to stay conscious,
because help is on the way.
-We've got your back.
-Wait.
We're not done yet.
-Don't get carried away.
That tough guy act
won't work with me.
-I'm fine.
-No, Chad!
You need to be healed first.
-Mmhm.
Listen Chad, it
sounds like your mouth
is trying to write a check
that the rest of your body
can't cash.
So remember, even if you
think you can still fight,
it could lead to a disaster.
So you really need to
let us treat your body.
What's going on?
How come nobody seems
to be listening to me?
-Because you talk too much.
-You'll never learn.
-I bet that's going
to leave a mark.
-Wow.
I'm surprised he's still alive.
-Go, Chad.
-Mister Urahara, um,
what was it that you
wanted to talk to me about?
-Well, a little while
ago, Rangiku Matsumoto
came here for a visit.
-Huh?
-So you know about the Oken,
and the danger that lies ahead?
This new situation is sudden
and a little unexpected.
But whatever the case
may be, all of us,
including the Soul Society,
will have to focus and prepare
for the upcoming battle this
winter from here on out.
It's going to be all out war.
More blood will be
spilled than ever before.
Both we and the Soul Society
will need more offensive power
than we already have.
-I see.
-It'll be OK.
I'll stop Aizen, I promise.
I know I can still get stronger.
I can really feel it now.
-I-- I want to
become strong, too.
[chad grunts]
-What's the matter?
Do you want to stop now?
-Not yet.
No way.
-Is that so?
In that case, I'll say this.
Orihime, when war
breaks out, I want
you to stay out of the battle.
Tsubaki, since he was
destroyed in the skirmish
with the arrancar
the other day, you've
been unable to restore him.
Correct?
-Yes, you're right.
Tsubaki was so badly broken
that I was unable to fix him.
I don't even know how I would
begin to heal him if I could.
-Tsubaki is your
only means of attack.
So without him,
I'm afraid I can't
allow you to
participate in combat.
It's only reasonable.
-Wait, hold on, Kisuke.
That's not fair.
Orihime's our friend.
Don't forget that she
fought successfully
in the Soul Society, and battled
against the Bounts as well.
-Chad.
-If she says that she wants
to work on getting stronger,
then you can't just cast
her aside so easily.
-You should think
about this, Chad.
Do you want to get her killed?
-No.
She has defensive
and healing powers,
which are more important
than attacking abilities.
The defensive power of Santen
Kesshun is quite limited.
Most likely, they will be of
no use in the upcoming battle.
As for healing abilities,
we have squad four.
This time, captain Unohana
and Lieutenant Kotetsu's squad
members will be at
the front lines.
They will compensate many times
over for Orihime's absence.
-But I don't understand!
-No.
That's enough.
A warrior who has
lost her strength
will only end up
getting in our way.
-But Urahara.
ORIHIME: It's OK.
-Orihime.
-Thank you, Chad.
But really, it's OK.
And thank you, Mister Urahara.
I appreciate it.
I'm really glad that you've
been so honest with me.
Guess I'll be going, now.
-Orihime, wait!
Hey, what are you doing?
-Take it easy.
Kisuke is absolutely
right, you know.
While squad four does
specialize in healing,
they're also in
the 13 Court Guard,
which means they're
trained in combat.
And although Orihime has some
powers, you have to remember,
she's still just a human being.
Also, I got to say.
Her personality just
isn't suited for battle.
Right now may have been
the best time to tell her.
-I just hope you're right.
-Wow, she's gone.
-Poor little kid.
-Orihime, I-- what's wrong?
Why are you in such a rush?
-[sobbing] Oh, Rukia.
-Hey, what's the matter?
Orihime, what's wrong?
[orhime sobs]
-What?
Kisuke, I can't believe
he said that to you.
He won't get away with it.
-No, it's OK.
But you know what?
I've kind of calmed down since
you and I've been talking.
I think it's better this way.
I'm sure.
I mean, it's true that really
don't have enough power
to help us win against--
-It's not OK!
Haven't you fought by our
side all along up until now?
Aren't you furious at
him for casting you aside
so easily like that?
-No, I-- I'm not mad.
-Stop lying to me like that.
-I'm not lying, really.
I feel lonely, but not mad.
But being lonely isn't nearly
as bad as being in the way.
[orhime whimpers]
-I feel lonely.
I guess while everyone else is
fighting, I'll be all alone.
But if I'm only going
to be a burden to Mister
Urahara and everyone
else, then maybe it's
better to just be
lonely instead.
-Orihime, listen.
In a battle, the ones
who get in the way
are not the ones
that lack power.
They're the ones
that lack resolve.
During our fight in
the Soul Society,
there wasn't a
single person that
became a burden to any of us.
Not Ichigo, not Chad, not Uryu.
And not you either, Orihime.
If any single one of
you weren't there,
then I wouldn't be here
today talking to you either.
I bet you we can find
something for you
to do that will help
us in this fight.
Let's work on it
together, Orihime.
-Thanks, Rukia.
[rukia and orihime gasp]
ORIHIME: Hiyori.
-You're coming with me.
Hachi wants to talk
to you right now.
-OK, but who's Hachi?
[orihime shrieks]
-Huh?
Who in the world was that girl?
-Ow, that hurts.
-Hey, Hachi.
I brought you the
one you wanted.
-Orihime?
-All right, that's it, Ichigo.
Your break is over.
-Hey, wait.
Hold on a second.
What do you want with--
-I said that your break is over.
-All right, that's it.
-Hachi is just a nickname.
My real name is Hachigen Ushoda.
Nice to meet you.
-It's nice to meet you.
Um, so.
What was it that you
wanted to see me about?
Huh?
Ow, wait a minute!
What are you doing?
Please stop it, you're going
to pull my head right off
like that!
-Just as I thought.
These hairpins are the
real form of your power.
They're like a zanpakuto.
This is truly rare.
But this one is chipped.
I've been quite curious
about it ever since you
came here earlier to
speak with Ichigo.
-Yes.
But I'm afraid I can't fix
it, because a part of it
was shattered.
-Well, would you like
me to fix it for you?
-What?
Can you really do that?
-Why, of course.
-Oh, goodie!
Thank you, thank you so much!
-It's nothing, really.
-All right, you can
let go of her head now.
-I don't get it!
This makes no sense.
Why is Hachi so willing to go
and fix that girl's weapon?
And why'd he bring her
here all of a sudden?
She's annoying!
-Will you quit your yapping?
-This is so not fair.
-Well, I bet he's happy.
Yes, because we hardly
ever meet anyone
with powers similar to his own.
It's sort of makes me feel
like, well, it sort of makes
me feel like our
family is growing.
I bet Hachi feels that
way, and some others.
-Still not good enough.
-I see.
He was broken so that not even
a single splinter remained.
And you were unable to fix him?
And as a result
of that, you were
asked to stay out of
the upcoming battle.
Do I have the
situation correctly?
-Um, not quite.
But since I've already
explained it like, five times?
Let's go with that.
-However, this is still strange.
From just looking at
your spiritual pressure,
you should have powers
very similar to mine.
But if that were the
case, you would still
be able to return him
to his original form,
even without a
shattered fragment.
[poof]
-Huh?
What do you want, woman?
What's with that
look on your face?
-Tsubaki!
I'm so glad you're finally
back, I missed you so much!
I can't thank you
enough for this, Hachi.
-Hmm.
ORIHIME: Oh, Tsubaki.
I just want to hug and squeeze
you and never let you go.
-Orihime.
I have now fixed
Tsubaki for you.
And with this, you will be able
to return to the front lines.
However, I have to
agree with the others.
I cannot recommend that you
be allowed to fight alongside
them.
If your powers are
anything like mine,
then you are
definitely not suited
for fighting-- especially when
your opponents are arrancars.
In spite of all that I've
told you, are you sure
you still wish to fight?
-Yes.
Yes, I still want to fight.
-Hmm.
Well, you'll just have
to get stronger, then.
You have not yet mastered
your own abilities, Orihime.
But surely there is a
means for you to fight.
Always keep this
thought in mind.
What's important is
not how you should be,
but rather how you want to be.
-Got it.
Rukia.
Listen, Rukia, the truth
is, inside this place--
-Don't say anything.
I don't need to know.
I came here.
And I felt a little bit of
Ichigo's spiritual pressure.
If he didn't say
anything, then he probably
knows what he's doing.
It's enough just
knowing that he's safe.
Let's get going.
ORIHIME: Ichigo.
I'm weak.
And it always seems like I'm
looking back towards you.
But now, I'm going to go
forward and not look back,
so that the next
time I see you, I'll
be able to fight without
looking back at all.
All right, Rukia.
Let's go.
[footsteps echoing]
[door creaks]
-Ulquiorra.
What do you want?
-You've healed.
It's a good thing that I decided
to bring your severed arm back
here, just in case.
-Bah.
This took too long.
My arm felt like it
was going to rot away.
You know, it would be nice if
our bodies healed on their own,
just like your eyeballs do.
-Stop complaining.
You're lucky to
have an arm at all.
If it were completely
destroyed like Grimmjow's, you
would've been kicked
out of the Espada too.
-I guess you're right.
-I have completed the treatment.
-Oh?
-How is it?
Is the movement and
the responsiveness
the same as before
it was severed?
-Not good enough.
If it was in its
usual condition,
I would've split
her right in half.
-Idiot.
-Nevertheless, I know it'll
get better sooner or later.
Then when it does, I'll get my
revenge on that Soul Reaper.
-You have an interesting
ability, young lady.
[MUSIC -- ORESKABAND,
"TSUMESAKI"]
-Captain, Rukia
Kuchiki called and said
she was going to return
temporarily to the Soul Society
with a friend.
-All right.
Let's prepare for their arrival.
-I've already mentioned
it to the squad
and suggested preparing
for a welcome back party.
-Don't forget to cook the rice.
-Yes, sir!
-Don't you guys have
anything better to do?