(Struggling Grunts)
(Gasp)
No way! Impossible!
[Renji]
Listen carefully!
We put all of our Spirit
Energy into that sword!
[cont'd]
That's more than enough
to restore Ichigo's
Soul Reaper powers!
Ichigo!
[Rukia cont'd]
Show them, Ichigo! Show
them that despair, no
matter how deep,
[cont'd]
will never be
enough to stop you!
Right!
(Attacking Grunt)
Ha! Your Getsugatensho
is much more powerful, but
is that all you've got?
Because the bottom line
is, that isn't going to be
enough to kill me, Kurosaki!
[Ichigo]
You've got it all
wrong.
That wasn't a
Getsugatensho at all.
Just a strike.
Ahh!
What's happening?
What the hell is
this Spirit Energy!
Getsuga...
...tensho!
Sorry, I missed.
But next time,
I won't.
(Nervous Gasp)
I've got to get some
distance between us
so I can regroup!
[Ichigo]
You're not going
anywhere.
Where does he get
that type of force!
(Attack Grunts)
Ahh!
(Fighting Grunts)
(Swing Grunt)
Ahh!
(Grunt)
He's become even more
physically powerful!
[Ginjo Cont'd]
This goes against
everything I expected!
I wonder if the Fullbring
[cont'd]
he learned increases
his innate powers?!
(Gasp)
(Swing Grunt)
(Growl)
(Attack Grunt)
Ahh!
(Stunned Gasp)
Getsuga...
...tensho!
(Stunned Breath)
(Strained Breathing)
Damn it!
But it'll take more
than this to kill me!
You hear me, Kurosaki!
But it'll take more
than this to kill me!
You hear me, Kurosaki!
(Gasp)
[Renji]
You can feel it
within you, right?
Huh?
[Ichigo]
Rukia...
[cont'd]
Renji...
Byakuya...
[cont'd]
Kenpachi...
Ikkaku...
[cont'd]
Toshiro...
And more, a whole
lot more.
[Ichigo]
Shinji...
[cont'd]
Rangiku...
Ms. Unohana...
[cont'd]
Hanatoro...
Dad...
[cont'd]
Kisuke...
Yoruichi...
[cont'd]
And even the old
Head Captain...
You now have all our
powers, Ichigo.
What's up? I thought
it was a serious crime
to transfer your powers
over to a human.
We really didn't have
a choice in the matter.
The orders came directly
from the Head Captain.
I completely understand
the situation.
Very well then, Kisuke
Urahara. Bring the
sword to me.
But Head Captain!
You're sure about this?
Despite what people may
think, it remains that
Ichigo Kurosaki has saved
us all. We cannot ignore
a debt like that. Now
it is time for us to
repay him.
[cont'd]
We must do this even if
it means breaking tradition.
It would bring perpetual
[cont'd]
shame to the Thirteen
Court Guard Squads, to
ignore what we owe him.
This is a direct order
from your Head Captain!
Hear me, all Captains
and Lieutenants of the
Thirteen Court Guard
Squads! You are hereby
ordered to place your
Spirit Energy into this
sword! We will help Ichigo
Kurosaki regain his
[cont'd]
Soul Reaper Powers!
[Renji]
That's what happened.
Nice move on the part
of the Head Captain,
don't ya think?
[Toshiro]
Don't be ridiculous!
It wasn't the rational
idea you'd expect
of a leader.
[Toshiro cont'd]
I can tell you, the Head
Captain would have never
made a decision like that
[cont'd]
in the past.
The truth is, you're
the one who brought
this on, Ichigo.
All these powers are
a gift to you.
[Toshiro cont'd]
You're receiving them as
a result of the changes
you made to the Soul
[cont'd]
Society in all of your
battles. Accept them
with honor.
(Proud Breath)
(Explosion)
[Ichigo]
What is that?!
You're kidding me.
There are two reasons
why the Head Captain
decided to restore your
Soul Reaper powers.
The first one is
just as we told you.
[Toshiro cont'd]
And the second has to
do with him.
[cont'd]
Long before you ever
appeared, there was another
man in the World of the Living
[cont'd]
who was issued a Combat
Pass as a Substitute Soul
Reaper. Only to later
[cont'd]
relinquish that position
and disappear.
[cont'd]
And that is him! The
first Substitute Soul
Reaper, Kugo Ginjo!
The first Substitute
Soul Reaper?
How is that possible?
But I thought-!
When Jushiro handed you
the Combat Pass, he must
have told you about this.
The Soul Society has a
law. It covers the
emergence of a Substitute
Soul Reaper.
[cont'd]
According to that rule,
if the Substitute Soul
Reapers are deemed
[cont'd]
beneficial to the Soul
Society, they are given
this Combat Pass as proof
[cont'd]
of their status.
[Toshiro]
The law governing
Substitute Soul Reapers was
created for Ginjo himself.
(Gasp)
Captain Hitsugaya...
Hm?
[Toshiro]
Yes, I know. I'll save
the details for later.
For now, concentrate
[cont'd]
your attention on
him.
Ha! Now that's a good
idea! You guys are gonna
have a very big problem
if he's not focused on me!
[Ginjo cont'd]
Oh by the way, thanks
Kurosaki...
If I hadn't borrowed
your powers, your last
attack probably would've
killed me,
(Heavy Breathing
from Running)
[Orihime]
Ichigo, he was
crying.
[cont'd]
I don't understand.
Ichigo and Mr.
Tsukishima are best
friends.
[cont'd]
So why did things
turn out like this?
[cont'd]
Mr. Tsukishima is the
one I love.
[cont'd]
Way, way before I even met
Ichigo, he was there in my
life, watching over me.
[cont'd]
He always protected me
and treated me with
kindness.
[cont'd]
For as long as I can
remember, I've always
looked up to him. He means
[cont'd]
everything to me. And
I would sacrifice anything
for Mr. Tsukishima.
[cont'd]
That's how I've
always felt.
[cont'd]
So then why?
Why does it hurt me
more to see Ichigo
cry like that!
[Orihime cont'd]
I don't know why, but
I can't stand it.
It's so painful, it
[cont'd]
hurts in my mind,
my heart, and even in
the pit of my stomach!
Please don't cry,
Ichigo!
[cont'd]
It's tearing me
apart!
Please don't cry!
Ichigo, thank
goodness you're
not crying!
(Gasp)
[Orihime]
Rukia! Renji!
Toshiro!
Do you see that, Chad?
They all came here to
stop Ichigo!
[Chad]
Something's not right.
Why is everyone up
there standing
behind Ichigo?
[Chad]
I thought they all came
to stop him. But now,
instead, it looks like
[cont'd]
they've come to
defeat Ginjo!
(Scared Gasps)
(Chuckle)
[Tsukishima]
What's the matter,
you two?
[Tsukishima]
Could it be you're
having doubts about
your past.
Mr. Tsukishima?
[Tsukishima]
Why are you looking
at me like that?
Don't tell me you've
already forgotten all
the memories we've shared.
(Nervous Breath)
[Tsukishima]
Think about it. Who
was it who protected
you from you parents,
[cont'd]
and raised you,
Orihime?
(Scared Breathing)
(Chuckle)
[Tsukishima]
And who was it that
gave you that pendant
when you were just
[cont'd]
a young boy, Chad?
Something's not
right with me!
I'm alive right now
because of Mr. Tsukishima,
so why am I having doubts?
I believe in...
I believe in..
I believe in Mr.
Tsukishima!
He's my true friend!
He's always been!
Tsukishima! Stop
drilling more memories
into them! You'll make
them useless to us!
[Ginjo cont'd]
You realize how many
people you've broken
like that?!
(Painful Grunt)
Well, that was easier
than I thought it'd
be!
Really? I'm the one
with all the dead
weight on my shoulders!
(Nervous Breath)
Thanks to you careless
efforts to unsettle them,
Mr. Tsukishima, we were
easily able to come up
behind and knock
them unconscious.
In the end, you
did us a great favor.
[Kisuke cont'd]
Now that they've both
been temporarily taken
out of action, we won't
[cont'd]
have to worry about
accidentally injuring them in
the event of a confrontation.
[cont'd]
And you don't have to
worry, Ichigo! We've
already moved the others
[cont'd]
to a safe place. So
now, you'll be able to
fight without holding back!
[Jackie]
Kugo!
Huh?
[Giriko]
What?! I knew
this would happen!
(Gasp)
This is really quite
unfair! We had an
agreement! How could you
take Ichigo's power
all for yourself?!
Hold on, Giriko!
He's right! You promised
to split his powers
with all of us!
Everybody just chill out
here! I, for one, don't
really care about having
Ichigo's powers!
[Ginjo]
All of you, shut up!
I don't need to be
reminded of what I said.
There. I just shared a
portion of Ichigo's
powers. Happy?
Ah!
Ah! This feels great!
(Happy sigh)
Wait a minute!
Stop!
(Angry grunt)
It's wonderful!
Amazing! Ichigo's
Fullbring is truly an
awesome power!
[Giriko cont'd]
It feels like my entire
body is being rejuvenated!
I feel as I did in my youth!
I'm not surprised at
you reaction, it's what
I'd expect, for an old guy.
(Amused Grunt)
[Tsukishima]
Aren't you going to
share this with
Shishigawara?
It's not nice of you
to leave him out.
The truth is, I thought
it would be risky
to increase his power.
When this fight's
finally over. I want
you to kill him.
(Sigh)
That's too bad, I
thought he had an
interesting ability.
All right! Here we
come, Ichigo!
[Giriko]
In a few minutes, you
will be able to fully
feel the wonderful power
[cont'd]
you've given us!
Oh, listen to him,
all in your face.
Stay back, Ikkaku. It's
my fault their powers
have been allowed to
increase.
Let me handle this.
[Giriko]
What?
Wait, what in the
world do you think
you're doing?
Don't tell me you're
going to try to take
on all of us at once!
(Stunned Gasps)
(Explosion)
(Painful Grunts)
Ah!
(Painful Grunt)
I went easy on you.
That's why you're
all still alive.
[Yukio]
Oh, really?
[cont'd]
I suppose you're
proud of yourself for
that! You think you're so
[cont'd]
cool, but you're just
a joke to us. You don't
get it do you? You think
[cont'd]
the tag here should be
'You have defeated the
enemy.' But in fact,
[cont'd]
the tag reads 'The
enemy has evaded your
attack.'
Thanks to my Digital
Radial Invaders.
Pretty cool, isn't it?
It's one of the new
upgrades I just got.
Something that came
with taking away
your Fullbring.
That's right. We can
all now wear and emit
our Fullbring just like
you did.
Before, my Invaders
Must Die would only
work inside video games.
But thanks to you, I
can now extend its
powers to the real world
too.
[Ikkaku]
You're way too soft
on them, Ichigo!
(Painful Grunt)
Ikkaku!
There's no point trying
to end this fight by
striking your enemies with
the flat of your blade.
You have to crush
them quickly!
[Ikkaku]
They started the fight.
They have to live with
the consequences.
(Gasp)
Stay sharp, Ikkaku.
Sorry, Captain.
Not bad. What do
you think? Should I
award bonus points?
No, don't bother.
Ahh!
[Ikkaku]
Who in the hell
are you?
Hm?
Ugh.
Looks like we're all
properly positioned
for the battles that
are about to come.
[Yukio]
Let me assign spaces
for each pairing.
Huh?
Hold on there,
Byakuya. That one
looks stronger.
[Kenpachi]
Switch with me!
[Giriko]
Excuse me, you wanted to
switch because another
opponent looked stronger
[cont'd]
to you?
I must say that's
quite insulting,
my friend.
I couldn't care less
if you're insulted.
It's boring to cut down
weaklings like you.
You seem to be a
muscle-bound idiot
as far as I can tell.
Let's see if you have the
same attitude after
I smash my way
right through you.
same attitude after
I smash my way
right through you.
same attitude after
I smash my way
right through you.
Still think I'm just
a weakling? Or am I more
suitable, now that my
Time Tells No Lies has
transformed me?
[Giriko]
I've discovered that
the simpler the terms
of my contract with the
[cont'd]
Gods of Time, the
more powerfully it's
manifested!
[Giriko]
Are you impressed
so far!
My contract right now
is an increase in
power!
As you can plainly
see, I am more
powerful than anyo-
What happened?
Impossible!
(Chuckle)
What a waste of
my time.
[Ichigo]
You guys have
changed, Toshiro.
[Toshiro]
We've trained to become
stronger in both mind
and body. Our appearance
[cont'd]
reflects those
changes.
[Ichigo]
Well, I wouldn't
say you've changed
that much.
[Toshiro]
What do you mean?!
Look at me!
I'm a lot taller now!
[Ichigo]
I guess that depends
on your perspective,
shorty.