ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
I'm Ichigo Kurosaki.
And other than having the
ability to see spirits,
I used to be an ordinary
high school student.
But the day I met
Rukia Kuchiki, I
was given the powers
of a Soul Reaper
in order to protect the
world of the living.
As I began my work as a
substitute Soul Reaper,
I found myself thrown into
a never-ending battle.
In the midst of everything,
my best friend Orihime Inoue
was abducted by ex-Soul
Reaper captain Sosuke Aizen.
My friends Chad and Uryu join
me as I race to rescue Orihime.
Once we arrived in Hueco
Mundo, we entered a fight
with powerful enemies
known as Arrancars.
We were too late to
keep Aizen from entering
the world of the living.
But luckily, the 13
Court Guard Squads
were already there to stop him.
An all-out war was
about to begin.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: In order to prevent
Sosuke Aizen from destroying
Karakura Town, the Soul
Reapers used four pillars
to create a massive
Senkaimon to relocate
the entire town to
the Soul Society.
Izuru, Yumichika,
and Shuhei, who
were defending three
of the pillars,
faced attacks from
Barragan's Fracciones.
They emerged victorious
from their various battles.
However, the final
pillar was destroyed
in a fight between
Ikkaku Madarame
and the Fraccion named Poww.
Tetsuzaemon managed to prevent
the return of Karakura town
by using emergency stakes.
Captain Komamura, who
had rushed to the scene,
eventually defeated Poww,
putting an end to the assault.
-Very well.
Shall we at last get
on with the real fight?
BARRAGAN: Don't let even
a single ant escape alive.
There is no place for you
to return to as losers.
Don't you dare disappoint me.
Kill them all.
-I implore you, you must put
all your spirit into this
to defeat them here.
Even if your flesh is
torn from your body,
use your bones to form
an impenetrable wall.
No matter what the
cost, we must never
let them step even one
foot into the Soul Society.
Attack now!
-[chuckling]
[groaning]
-Fighting you is a joke!
-Aaah!
-[laughing]
-You worried?
Your second in command is
getting his ass kicked.
-So what?
He's a fool.
And the only
thoughts he ever has
are about money, food,
and his family's business.
-Say that's pretty cold.
Is that how things
work with you?
-I don't like a cozy
atmosphere in my squad.
-Really?
-Ha!
-Damn!
-Bakudo #30, Shitotsu Sansen.
It's all over, Arrancar.
I didn't have the time
to learn your name.
-[grunting]
-Sting all enemies to
death, Suzumebachi.
Nigeki Kessatsu.
That is the power
of my Suzumebachi.
-What are you talking about?
Are you saying if that thing
stings me twice, I'm history?
-You're about to find out.
-Cero.
[explosion]
SUI-FENG (VOICEOVER): Sonido.
-You're not too efficient
for an assassin.
Maybe you do have a weapon that
kills an enemy in two strikes.
Why announce it?
Why not just use it?
With flash step, this
battle would be over by now.
That's what I would have done.
-He's fast.
-Haa!
Ready for another?
Ha ha, how does it feel
to be on the defensive?
-[gasp]
-Haa!
What's the matter?
No opening to attack me?
-Hah.
You sure run your mouth a lot.
-Aaaugh!
[grunting]
[panting]
-What's up?
You tired or something?
-What?
-I'll be able to finish
you off in one strike.
You better do something.
There's no point
in holding back,
you should use your best
move before you're killed.
-(ANGRILY) What?
Huh.
You've got a big mouth.
Now watch and learn.
I'm going to take
you down, my friend,
without the use of my
Shikai or my killer move.
[grunting]
[panting]
-[yawning] Time's up.
-Uhh!
[groaning]
-You still alive down there?
-[groaning]
-Oh, great.
That's too bad.
To be honest with
you, I really wanted
to fight that blonde chick.
See, I had no interest
in battling you.
You're just a fat-ass.
-I'm a what?
What are you talking about?
Are you blind or something?
Man, wait a minute.
Of course.
You're just jealous.
That's it.
What a dummy, I should
have figured it out
from the beginning.
I can't help it if you look
bad and have a terrible odor
as well.
Could be worse.
But it's not my fault
you're fat and ugly!
Don't blame me.
-Excuse me?
-Don't play dumb.
It couldn't be any more obvious.
You are suffering from a
classic inferiority complex.
It's why someone
who looks bad tries
to put down someone
who looks good.
Or why someone with
no money puts down
someone who's wealthy.
-Is that right?
So where is this guy who looks
good and has a pile of money?
I'd really like to meet him.
-Tell me something.
Are you also an idiot on
top of being fat and ugly?
-An idiot?
-Come on.
All you have to do
is open your eyes.
Just think about it.
Look, are you so damn dense that
I have to spell it out for you?
All right, fine.
I am a man of
considerable wealth.
I happen to have a
great sense of style.
And my looks obviously
leave nothing to be desired.
I've been talking about
myself, of course.
-Eugh.
-You have an issue
with my speech?
-Oh, yeah.
Do all Arrancars
talk this much when
they're right in the middle
of fighting for their lives?
-I suppose I do become
a little chatty when
victory is so easily
within my reach.
-Interesting.
So it appears to
me the only way I
can make you talk less is to
make this battle much more
difficult for you.
And believe me when I say this
is something I'm willing to do.
My second in command talks
enough for the both of you.
-So what's your point?
-Just I prefer the quiet, since
I have all the talk I need.
-Maybe I'll just fix your
mouth so you can't talk either!
-Don't be so sure!
-Huh?
-Haa!
-Augh!
-Huh?!
-Haa!
(VOICEOVER) I've got him!
[gasp]
-If you think I can't
keep up with your speed,
you've underestimated me!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Am I still talking
too much for you?
[grunting]
-[gasp]
-Haa!
Disappointing.
I expected more.
You're the captain
of Squad 2, the unit
that's known as
the Stealth Force.
I heard that that squad
was comprised of assassins,
the most lethal fighters
in all of the Soul Society.
So far I'm not impressed
with your technique.
Or is this the best that the
Soul Society has to offer?
Oh, by the way,
when we met earlier
you said you didn't have
time to learn my name.
Well, guess what.
You have time now.
And I'm going to tell you.
His Majesty Barragan's
Fraccion, Ggio Vega.
And while I'm on
the subject, there's
another name you
should hear as well.
Bite off, Tigre Estoque!
-Let me explain
something to you.
A good-looking man is bred from
a good lineage and environment.
He's incredibly polished.
Truth is, to a poor man like
you it's much too confusing.
You couldn't comprehend the
lure of a hot man like me.
[laughs]
-Thank you, I got your message.
Would you shut up
already, fatso?
-I refuse to be called
fatso by someone
who looks like a tub of lard!
And anyway, I'm not
fat, I'm full bodied.
It's a reflection of abundance.
It's much different from
how a knuckle-dragger like
yourself bloats up for no
apparent reason at all.
How about that?
-You are the biggest
pain I have ever met.
-Right back at you.
Anything you call me
bounces off and lands
right on your fat
head, so there.
-Are you four years old?
I'm going to have to
shut you up permanently.
-Say what?
That's big talk for someone
who doesn't have a clue.
You lack a sense of style and
your clothes are really shabby.
You should think about getting
a makeover before you-- huh?
-Stomp down.
-[trumpets] Mamut!
[trumpets] Mamut!
-Whoaah!
Damn it!
These guys are always using
sneaky transformations!
How did he become
so huge like that?
All I've got to fight
him with is this sword.
[groaning] That's
going to leave a mark.
Huh?
--[laughing] With
my Resurreccion,
my movements get
slower as I get bigger.
But I should still
be fast enough
to take out a pest like you!
Right, fatso?
That's it, run for
your life, you turkey!
[laughing] Haa!
How about another one?
[grunt] You're pretty slow.
If you lost a few
pounds, maybe you
could put on a little speed.
Quit dragging that lard-ass!
-Who you calling lard-ass?
I told you before!
Listen, I'm just full-bodied!
And maybe you hadn't
noticed, but you're
no greyhound either, wise guy.
-That might be, but
I'm doing the chasing
and you're doing the fleeing.
Maybe those pockets full of
money are holding you back.
Did you ever think about that?
-Waahh!
This guy is completely
out of control.
I'm not going to fight him
head on, that's for sure.
-What the?
-See ya!
In a street fight, you
need more than just speed.
You may be good
in a race, but I'm
guessing you're not so good
at climbing up tall buildings,
are you?
Enjoy the view from down
there, elephant breath!
Aaahh!
-What were you saying?
[jingling]
-OK.
Here I come!
Hyaaah!
Uwaaahh!
SUI-FENG (VOICEOVER):
His attacks are sharper.
-You plan to fight, or just
stand there analyzing my moves?
-Who's to say it isn't
part of my technique?
-Ha ha, fine.
Keep it up, if that's the
way you want to play it.
But I'm running out of patience.
So take this!
-[grunts]
SUI-FENG (VOICEOVER):
He's also increased
his destructive power.
-Get ready, because
there's no time to rest!
Hyaah!
Urgh!
Well, not bad.
The cat finally
showed its claws.
SUI-FENG (VOICEOVER):
I see, his Resurreccion
has increased his attack
capacity by several levels.
-Now die!
SUI-FENG (VOICEOVER): His
speed has also increased.
However--
-Haahh!
-Nice try, but you're
just not good enough.
--[chuckles] Now
that's more like it.
-No fair, hold on.
Wait!
No way!
You can't be able to jump that
high with your size and weight.
You're not supposed
to be here, you
should be stuck on the ground!
-Maybe that's a good lesson.
You should be more careful
about judging people, especially
based on their appearance!
Hey, running away isn't
going to accomplish anything.
Besides, how far
do you think you
could get with
all weight on you?
Maybe you should've
spent some of your money
to get rid of that
hundred pounds of blubber
you're carrying around.
Now you're mine!
-Aaahh!
-[gasps]
-I'm not running
away any more, am I?
-How did you do that?
-Huh, who do you suppose
you've been dealing with?
-What?
-I'm the lieutenant of Squad 2
and the head of Stealth Force
Second Unit, known
as Patrol Troops.
My name is Marechiyo Omaeda!
If you knew about
the Stealth Force,
you'd know I'd
never be that slow.
-You were playing me?
Damn you!
[groans]
-Now smash them, Gegetsuburi!
-[grunts]
-Maybe that's a good
lesson, you should
be more careful
about judging people
based on their appearance.
-Huhh!
Hyah!
Huhh!
-That same technique again!
-Haahh!
-Well, looks like my
attacks are starting
to have an effect on you.
I understand why you didn't
fight back all that time.
You were analyzing
my moves, looking
for some kind of weakness.
I knew you were doing
that because deep inside,
you were convinced
you could come up
with some kind of method
to neutralize my attacks.
But unfortunately
for you, I haven't
shown you everything I possess.
So I wouldn't get
too comfortable
thinking you have
me all figured out.
I still have a few
tricks up my sleeve.
-Guess we'll find out.
-All right, I won!
Hey, look at you now.
You got exactly
what you deserve!
Talk smack to me, will you?
You see what
happens, butterball?
You thought you were
pretty damn smart, right?
You've got no substance,
oh, sure, big man.
You and your tricky
body, hopping around.
So who's in charge now, you with
your weird nose like a vacuum
cleaner?
Maybe I should tear that
thing off your face,
what do you think?
Oh, ooh.
-[growls]
-I, you see-- sorry,
that came out wrong.
I'm actually obsessed
with this nose.
The truth of the matter
is, I've always admired
long, handsome noses.
I wish I had one myself.
-Is that so?
How about I extend your
nose so it looks like mine?
-No, no, that's all right!
I was just kidding, I'm
happy with the way it is.
If you don't let go,
you're going to stretch it!
NIRGGE: Like this?
-Ahh!
Come on, give me
a break, will you?
You're going to mess
up my beautiful face!
-Ugh!
-My nose is still here, right?
That pachyderm
didn't pull it off?
Huh?
Wait a minute, what happened?
Captain!
-[chuckles]
[theme music]
SUI-FENG (VOICEOVER): The names
of the Arrancar Resurrecion
forms are quite
hard to pronounce.
That's Tigre--
GGIO (VOICEOVER):
Tigre Estoque, that's
written with Chinese characters
for tiger, fang, swift
and wind.
SUI-FENG (VOICEOVER):
Save that stuff
for the Arrancar encyclopedia.
GGIO (VOICEOVER):
Will you shut up?
I'm trying to tell you, the
higher ups won't let me.