[theme music]
NARRATOR: At the palace
of Szayelaporro Granz,
deep inside of Las
Noches, Uryu and Renji
battled against
clones of themselves,
created by the Espada.
-Look what you did to my palace.
How will I ever explain
this to Lord Aizen?
I am very displeased.
-Uryu!
-Such a delicious meal.
NARRATOR: Szayelaporro
used his La Lajuriosa
to create a powerful doll
that could control Uryu's five
senses.
Though the doll appeared
to be a simple toy,
any damage it suffered
would directly affect Uryu
and was used as a
cruel torture device.
Uryu was incapacitated
by the use of the doll,
and when Renji
attempted to intervene,
a doll was crafted for
the lieutenant as well.
-I'll get you for that!
-Don't make a fuss.
All I did was destroy
a vital internal organ.
-Huh?
-My, my, my.
Some people act just
little children.
Humans, Soul
Reapers, Quincys too.
It's actually quite vulgar.
NARRATOR: Meanwhile,
Ichigo won a deadly battle
against Grimmjow,
and rescued Orihime.
However, a fight between Espada
number five, Nnoitra Gigle
Nelliel tu Odelschwank
quickly followed.
-Why'd you stop your sword?
-Why'd you stop yours?
-You're annoying.
You're so annoying.
When I'm fighting you, I
can't help but think back.
Except for those ridiculous
rag tag clothes you're wearing,
you haven't changed
one single bit.
-Finally, wriggles
my way out of there.
Huh?
Pesche!
Hey!
Are you all right down where?
Hold on.
I'm gonna get you out, brother.
PESCHE: Thanks, Dondochakka.
Come on!
Heave ho!
Don't give up now.
-It's too heavy.
I need to take a
load of for a sec.
PESCHE: Hey.
Why the heck did you stop?
I could almost see
the outside world.
-Yeah, well, it don't matter
if you can see outside,
because the only thing
in sight is going
to be Renji and Uryu getting
beaten up by Szayelaporro.
You know what?
I just noticed something.
PESCHE: Hey.
I can see out now.
-When Szayelaporro does that
lethal sword release of his,
it kinda looks
like udon noodles.
PESCHE: Huh.
It does.
Now that you
mention it, maybe we
should call his attack
the Szayelaporro noodles.
-Nah, that sounds like a
pretty lame attack to me.
PESCHE: Then why'd
you even bring it up?
You're the one who said
it looked like noodles.
Quit babbles and get me out.
-OK, OK.
Geez.
You're the one who keeps
on babbling, Pesche.
-Look.
I'm free.
Wait a sec.
What are we doing?
we can't waste our time here.
Master Nel.
-Nel.
-Ichigo, wait.
You're not--
-Nel's in a lot of trouble,
and I-- I have to go help her.
-Ichi--
-Don't move.
You will not get in
Master Nnoitra's way.
That woman, Nelliel tu
Odelschwanck, she is a boulder.
And any boulder that obstructs
Master Nnoitra's blade
must be destroyed by
Master Nnoitra himself.
-Ah!
-There.
All done.
I'm happy that's over
in time for lunch.
If I were late, the others
might have gotten worried.
-Hold it.
I thought I said this was
a fight to the finish.
We're not done yet.
-Are you implying
that you'd like
this to be a battle
to the death?
-Do you even have to ask?
-I refuse.
You don't deserve to
have such an honor.
-What was that?
-When we became Hollows,
we transformed from humans
to beasts.
And then, Arrancars, we
regained our sense of reason.
Those with the ability to reason
must have a purpose to fight.
You lack a purpose.
I'm under no obligation
to keep fighting you,
and there is no reason
whatsoever to kill you.
-Well, I have a good reason.
I loathe and despise you.
-Sorry.
That's not a reason.
It's instinct.
You are still a beast.
I cannot acknowledge
you as a true warrior,
so you are not worthy
to be my opponent.
I won't have the
life of someone who
isn't a warrior
on my conscience.
-Damn you.
-Nnoitra.
Are you all right, sir?
Can you--
-Don't get friendly with me.
Just because I couldn't
defeat that girl,
Tesra, don't start acting
like you're my equal.
You're not.
-But why Master Nelliel?
Why not any other Espada?
-Because I hate her.
I can't stand seeing a woman
defeating a man in battle.
it turns my stomach.
Hey, Nelliel?
Remember how you called
me a beast before?
You told me back then that
I'm not a worthy opponent.
Well then, how does it feel
to be killed by a lowly beast?
NEL: Pesche, Dondochakka.
Pesche, Dondochakka.
Where are you?
It's time for dinner.
Hm.
Pesche.
Dondochakka.
Come out.
Where are you hiding?
In here?
Hm.
Pesche.
Dondochakka.
Where could those
two guys have gone?
It's strange.
[gurgling]
-Huh.
And I'm so hungry.
-Hey.
-Not you again.
-Are you looking for someone?
-Why don't you mind
your own business?
And carrying your weapon
around is an empty threat.
If you really want to appear
dangerous, you'd put it away.
-Pesche.
Dondochakka.
-I'm so sorry, Master
Nel, we failed you.
-You-- You ripped
off their masks.
How dare you?
-Yeah, I did.
So what?
They were too weak.
That's the bottom line.
Now then.
I think I've given you a fine
enough reason to fight me,
haven't I?
-Not quite.
This isn't a reason for
a fight to the death.
-You're serious?
-But you have done wrong.
You've injured two of
my closest friends,
and for that, I promise
I will make you pay.
-Damn it.
I can't stand her.
-Too slow.
-Heh.
You'd probably
tell me I'm acting
like some mindless
primal beast again.
As if I care.
The whole point of battle
is to win at all costs.
It doesn't require
a good reason.
Fighting isn't logical.
Never has been.
You looked for some lofty
rationale and paid the price.
You make me sick.
What do you want?
Your work is already
finished here, Szayelaporro.
-Why the sudden cold shoulder?
I thought you and I were
allies, joining forces
to meet our goals.
Can't I at least witness
the outcome of this?
-I don't remember us
ever joining forces.
I took advantage of you.
That's all there was to it.
You wanted to fight
Nelliel, and I
wished to test my
new device in action.
Thus our partnership was born.
Cooperation is forged
out of common interests,
because it has benefits
for both parties.
-So philosophical.
Makes me want to puke.
Nelliel.
It was never power
that divided us.
It was experience.
Pure and simple.
Before your wound has healed and
you've returned to Las Noches,
I will have surpassed you.
My powers will be so great
that your sword will not
be able to touch me.
Let's go.
-I don't think you
can give me orders.
-Is that so?
You're not even an Espada.
Perhaps.
But it was my device alone that
allowed you to beat Nelliel,
and I believe that
affords me some respect.
Am I wrong?
See what I mean by
common interests?
-Spirit energy?
Did she just turn into a child?
-Fascinating.
I've never seen
such a phenomenon.
Spirit energy is escaping
from the crack in her mask,
and her soul is shrinking.
-Ha.
Who cares how it's happening?
Look at you now, Nelliel.
In a body that
suits you perfectly.
But on the other hand, I
suppose that's the last time
our swords will ever cross.
That really is a shame.
-This place.
Wh-- where am I?
And you?
Who are you?
-My goodness.
She's lost her memory.
-Huh?
My head feels so funny.
-Pesche--
-Be quiet, Dondochakka.
This can only mean one thing.
Master Nel-- Master Nelliel
tu Odelschwanck has died.
Her mask destroyed,
all her power lost.
Her memory erased.
The girl who lies before
us is not Master Nel.
However, we must protect her.
From Nnoitra Szayelaporro.
From suffering and hardship.
From all dangers and adversity.
If our master has
become defenseless,
we must shield her
with our lives.
We have sworn to serve
Master Nel in any situation,
and this is our one final duty.
-You are too persistent.
I've taken you down
countless times.
Why can't you just take the
hint and stay down for once?
-Argh!
-Like I said, you're
too persistent.
-Urk!
-I just severed your
left Achilles tendon.
Now then, what part of
you shall I break next?
Of course, if I play
with too many organs,
your body might quit altogether.
-Damn you.
-Ah, ah.
Don't you move a muscle.
What did I just say to you?
We don't want to end our
playtime too early, do we?
Be a good boy and sit still.
What is going on?
-I got it!
I got it!
Now, Dondochakka!
Bring out Bawabawa!
-Yah!
Comin' to get ya!
Yah!
-Uwah!
-What the-- why's
that thing coming out
of Dondochakka's mouth?
-Bawabaa's one of the combat
spirit bugs Dondochakka
houses inside his body.
But we didn't dare tell
Master Nel about it.
We were worried that
any information about us
would trigger her
memories to return.
You see, Master Nel
always hated fighting.
And now she's free from
the horrors of violence.
But if her memory
came back, so would
those painful, sad thoughts.
And our duty was to protect
her from pain, no matter what.
However, she certainly
has the will to fight now!
And if Master Nel says
she wants to fight,
our job is to be at her side!
We will not be intimidated by
the likes of you, Szayelaporro!
Here we come.
-Rawr!
-Heh.
You honestly think
you've got a chance?
If you had half a brain,
you'd just surrender.
-It's unfortunate.
-Huh?
-I knew it would be rough on
me so soon after transforming
back.
I didn't want me to use
this unless I had to.
Praise.
[theme music]
PESCHE: Dondochakka, we did it!
DONDOCHAKKA: Oh, yeah!
What did we do?
PESCHE: When your face is
partially obscured onscreen,
it means you're mysterious,
strong, and handsome.
I'm sure plenty
of ladies noticed.
DONDOCHAKKA: Wait!
My face only
appeared in shadows?
Does that mean I'm ugly?
I want a second opinion.