The Zanpakuto... Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined
by its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper...
And dies with its Soul
Reaper.
That is the existence
of a Zanpakuto.
Scatter!
[grunting]
[fighting grunts]
Reign over the
Frosted...Heavens!
[screaming]
Roaaaarrr!
Uh...huh?
Above you!
Damn it!
[grunting]
He went that way!
We've got him!
There he is!
[growling]
[gasping]
Hey, those are nice
weapons you got there.
How 'bout we compare
whose is stronger...
Yours or mine?
Kazeshini...
Alright, I get it. You
want me to stop playing
around!
[fighting and growling]
Get back here!
What in the--?
Damn you!
Huh?
[choking]
[screaming]
What the hell?
[gasping]
Well done, Kazeshini.
You're getting good at
cleaning up these messes.
Hmmm...
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Everything's fine.
What? Is the fight over
already?
Renji...
Sorry we're late,
Shuhei.
It happens all the time,
Monkey's big butt always
slows us down
she needs to stop
eating so much!
What are you
talking about?!
Don't worry about it...
The Sword Beast didn't
put up much of a fight.
Judging by their recent
activity, Sword Beasts
appearances seem to be
dwindling down.
Yeah, you're right.
Looks like we've been
effective. Perhaps there
are only a few of them
remaining.
Now that the reconstruction
of the Seireitei is coming
along, things are finally
getting back to normal.
Yeah.
You've been eating
nothing but sweets lately.
Look around, I don't
think that it's my butt
that's getting bigger.
Hey, I'm a growing boy,
so that makes it all
right.
Don't forget, you and
I together are one.
So the bottom line is,
if you're still growing,
so am I.
Hey...
Hm?
That Sword Beast
we caught...
... it returned to back to
Sword Form even though I
never struck a fatal blow.
Huh?!
Are you sure?
Hmmm.
[breathing heavily]
[screaming]
[growling]
Nice moon tonight,
wouldn't you say?
Huh? No, it's too
bright in my opinion.
Hey!
Hm?
Now there's something
new under the moon.
So, I guess you guys
are buddies now?
It's only unusual in your
eyes. Our masters hang out
together quite often.
Heh, yeah, whatever.
So what brings you here
tonight? Or did you
just come by to kiss
your master's ass?
What?! You'd better
watch your mouth, you big
slug! You're asking for a
beating!
Okay, okay. Don't
get so excited.
Hey! I thought we came
here to discuss
something.
[groaning]
The Sword Beast we
worried about has
appeared.
[grunting]
You're sure about that?
Absolutely.
An incident happened
right in front of me.
Before I could attack, a
Sword Beast was sucked
dry of its Spirit
Energy and returned
to Sword Form.
It has to be his doing.
As we know, Sword Beasts
were originally Zanpakuto
that lost their masters
and became wild.
They each have a finite
amount of Spirit Energy.
They eventually lose
their power and disappear.
Huh. Looks like they're one
step away from extinction.
That's right.
Except this guy is able to
take Spirit Energy from other
Zanpakuto and make it his own.
So what? I'm able to
do that as well.
Yes, but what makes him
both unique and troublesome
is that he's one of those
rare Zanpakuto
who's able to surpass
his master's powers.
Why is that so
troublesome?
To him, his master was a
nuisance from the very
beginning. And now that
his master has died,
there's no-one around to
control the way he uses
his power.
[heavily breathing]
[screaming]
This isn't good.
He's dangerous.
Everything he comes in
contact with will be stripped
of its Spirit Energy and used
to make him stronger.
With that ability, it's too
big a risk for us to let Soul
Reapers face him.
We're going to have to
take action.
And if we're successful,
we'll be able to put an end
to the Sword Beast hunt.
And destroying him means
a grand finale for us.
Huh?
Waitress, let's have
another couple of bottles
of this sake!
Coming right up!
Rangiku, too much alcohol
is poison to the body.
Yes, but too little
poisons the spirit!
That's right. What are
you worried about? It's
not like she's a child who
doesn't know when to stop.
Haineko, you know
me so well!
The two of them never
change. Hm?
Katenkyokotsu,
want some?
Well, don't hold back.
You can have some. We're
sharing the order.
Here you go.
Huh.
So, tell me something,
Nanao. Why did you bring
Captain Kyoraku's Zanpakuto
with you?
Why wouldn't I bring her
with me? We're part of the
same squad.
Where's her
partner?
She's back at the
barracks, drinking with
the Captain.
Oh? And you're all
right leaving the
two of them alone
together?
Come on, she's a
Zanpakuto. What is
there to worry about?
I'm so happy! It's so nice to
have a meal with everybody
once in a while.
I must admit you're
right. Even the food
tastes better.
Hey, Momo! What's
the problem?
You haven't had a drop
of sake this whole time!
I came here today to
enjoy the food, I wasn't
even planning to drink.
What?!
Are you telling me you
won't accept my sake?
Stop giving Momo a hard
time, Rangiku!
You don't have to defend
me, Tobiume.
Hold on, girls. Let's
all calm down.
I'll accept your sake,
how would that be?
What in the world is up
with you, Haineko, you're
behaving awfully level-
headed today.
Yes! Because I happen
to be a mature woman!
Ha! That's my Zanpakuto!
Very well said!
Maybe you could learn
something from her,
Rangiku.
What?!
[giggling]
Thank you very much!
[groaning]
Can you try and walk a
little? We're carrying
you.
Can't feel my feet!
She ends up like this,
just about every time we
go out drinking.
Huh?
Aren't you
girls coming?
We wanna enjoy the
night air a little bit
before we turn in...
Is it okay if I leave
Rangiku with you guys
for now?
Um.. Sure, that's fine.
We apologize, Momo. Is it
really all right for us
to go off on our own?
Don't worry about it.
It's nice to be able to
spend time with your
friends.
I think I'm gonna barf!
Come on, Rangiku! Try
to hold it together!
At least until we can
get you back home to
the barracks!
Oh, brother!
[groaning]
We're not far,
just hold on.
I told you we should have
cut her off!
Thank you, Rangiku.
It was fun.
Hm?
How sentimental are you,
staring at the moon!
We finally found him.
Let's get
to work.
[panting]
[growling]
[screaming]
[panting]
[grunting]
[panicking]
[screaming]
[roaring]
There you are.
I have to say, I never
figured you'd get this
big.
[growling]
I knew you were the one
behind this, Kirikaze!
You were the one out of
all of us that was the most
dissatisfied with your master!
You've mis-used your
ability to transform!
You've entered the bodies
of other Zanpakuto, and
leached away all of their
Spirit Energy.
That's disgusting!
His size comes from all
the energy he's consumed.
He's cannibalized many
Sword Beasts.
That's all about
to end right now!
[grunting]
He turned himself
into mist!
What?
Scatter!
That was uncalled for!
Something had to be done,
or we all would have been
in peril. So quit
complaining.
Less talk, more action!
[yelling]
Watch it!
He's vulnerable
from the rear.
[roaring]
[grunting and roaring]
That's as far as you go!
As you're about to find out,
you don't have a monopoly on
leaching Spirit Energy.
I can do it
as well.
[roaring]
How 'bout it? Now that
the tables have been
turned...
...you'll find it's not
such a pleasant
experience!
[struggling]
What is it?!
This... can't be!
[struggling]
[growling]
Break the
connection!
Bastard!
[screaming]
I'm running
out of time!
[screaming]
[squealing]
I've got you!
[growling]
[roaring]
[grunting]
[struggling]
Gonryomaru, are you all
right?!
Roar!
Uh... huh?
Above you!
[roaring]
Damn it!
[grunting]
Renji!
Bakudo Number
Sixty three! Sajosabaku!
[roaring]
He'll transform
into mist.
I've put a
stop to that.
[roaring]
Lady Rukia!
Don't get distracted.
You're right in the
middle of a battle.
Keep your guard up.
Come on Haineko. Let's
get you on your feet.
You know you're not
allowed to sleep on
the job.
Rangiku... Why
are you here?
Give us some credit. Did
you really think we didn't
know what was going on?
Uh!
Sorry, Momo.
You idiots! What were
you all thinking
coming out here?
Who's the idiot? What
did you think you could
do in your condition?
It's obvious you're all
reaching your limits.
[gasping]
All of you knew?
Right now, all you
need is to concentrate
on your enemy.
That's what we were
trying to do! This Sword
Beast's abilities are too
dangerous for Soul Reapers.
Way dangerous! You
wouldn't be able to
defeat him, that's why we
came without telling you!
That's enough!
After all this time, you
don't get it, do you?
Swords alone and Soul
Reapers alone will never
be enough!
The only way this works
is when we're paired
together, and operate as
a team! That's when our
true strength reveals
itself! Didn't you learn
that lesson from what
happened to Muramasa?
We're only vulnerable
when we split our
energies in half.
Hm! Renji...
I hear you. We were
wrong to come here
by ourselves.
[roaring]
He broke free!
Kazeshini...
I'm with you. Let's wrap
this up once and for all.
Are you ready?
Yeah!
[growling]
Renji! He's goin'
after your friend!
Sodenoshirayuki!
Scatter!
Pierce!
Reign over the Frosted...
Heavens!
[growling]
My energy...
Sir Hyorinmaru! I can't do
anymore with the Spirit
Energy I have remaining.
You can't give up!
Remember what we told
you! You're not in this
fight alone!
Lady Rukia!
It'll be all right.
They can't separate us,
we're always together!
Yes.
Come, Sodenoshirayuki!
[growling]
Now dance,
Sodenoshirayuki!
Tsuginomai! Hakuren!
[growling]
Wabisuke!
Tobiume!
Kazeshini!
Haineko!
Raise your head...
...Wabisuke!
Now snap...
...Tobiume!
[growling]
Reap...
...Kazeshini!
[growling]
Now growl...
...Haineko!
[growling]
[weaker growling]
He can't turn into mist!
He's weakened considerably.
Renji!
Hm?
You ready to do this?
Yeah.
We'll give you our
remaining Spirit Energy
as well!
Renji, this has been an
experience we will never
forget.
And you've been there
for us every step of
the journey.
Zabimaru...
We couldn't have dreamt
of anything more...
Not to mention, it
was a lot of fun.
You said it.
Bankai...! Hihio,
Zabimaru!
[grunting]
Ahhhhhh!!!
Hikotsu! Taihooooo!
[struggling]
They've all disappeared,
just as we expected.
By the time the Sword
Beast reached the limits
of its Spirit Energy,
all of our Zanpakuto
were so weak, that it was
completely impossible
for them to maintain
their manifested forms.
You mustn't feel
too bad for them.
Their appearance was
temporary and only happened
because of Muramasa's powers.
They knew they'd return
to sword form,
eventually.
That's right.
There's no need to feel
too upset...
They've just gone back to
where they originally
came from.
They'll always be
there for us.
Right? Don't you feel
their presence?
Yes...
It's a very comforting
feeling.
Even though they no
longer appear in those
other bodies...
It's okay, because they'll
be with us wherever we are.
Uh...
Renji?
Huh? What is
it, Rukia?
Uhh...
Nothing. It can wait.
[chuckling]
Kind of a relief,
it's finally over.
Yes. Let's all go back
to the Seireitei.
The producers are finally
done, messing around with
the plot. Thank you for
waiting, Master Ulquiorra!
Understood. Can I have a
cup of tea before we
begin?
Absolutely! Ichigo's not
even here yet, so take
your time and enjoy
yourself!
I am here!
Whaat?!