[theme music]
[alarm clock ringing]
-What time is it now?
-It's 9:00 already, boss man.
This is going to be bad.
-What?
Nine o'clock?
Come on.
We gotta go, Bonnie. [whistling]
[trampling hooves]
-Whoa!
[grunting] Ha, that's
the way, Bonnie.
I can't play with you
right now, though.
Come on and give me
a ride out of here.
Whoa!
-What?
Hey.
Come back here.
-Oh, I'm not running away.
Just wait.
I'll be back here
again tomorrow.
We'll settle this
thing once and for all.
You just wait for
me, dandelion head.
And try not to turn to
fluff, and blow away.
Let's go, everyone.
-You stupid coward!
How dare you--
[trampling hooves]
-[coughing]
-That was weird.
-If you ask me,
that was a disaster.
-I'm going to kill that guy as
soon as I find out who he is!
[rooster crowing]
-It looks like Jidanbo's
wound has closed up.
I hope he'll be OK
when he comes to again.
-[snoring]
CHAD (OFFSCREEN): Big
bodied men like him
have plenty of
stamina and strength.
I'm sure he'll be
fine before long.
-Yeah, you're right.
It would take a lot to
permanently harm someone
as big and powerful as Jidanbo.
-The question now is who
exactly is this Kukaku
Shiba we're supposed
to be looking for.
As usual, Yoruichi left
out a lot of the details.
It would have to be
someone Yoruichi thinks
can help us get
into the Seireitei
without going through the gates.
-Which would probably mean
someone with great skill.
-Wow.
I wonder if that means it's
a really smart purebred cat
with pedigree papers.
I hope so!
Or an American
shorthair type cat.
Or even a dalmatian.
CHAD (OFFSCREEN): Orihime.
-Huh?
-Just because it's
someone Yoruichi knows
doesn't mean it'll be a cat.
And by the way, a
dalmatian is a dog.
-Are you sure?
-Judging from the
name Kukaku, I'd
say we're going to be dealing
with a well-built man, probably
a powerful samurai warrior.
CHAD (OFFSCREEN): No,
I think he'll be more
of a hermit type master.
-Aha!
Like this.
And he'll have this.
Ta da.
A hermit type samurai
warrior master
with the ears and
tails of a cat.
-If he looks anything like
that, we're in trouble.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): Aw.
How about if I draw him with
dalmatian spots instead?
URYU (OFFSCREEN):
Not bad, Orihime.
Except you forgot
to give him a cape.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN): Oh,
I always forget something.
-What's the holdup
with Ichigo, anyway?
-He's inside.
Should I call him?
-That's OK.
I'll go get him.
ORIHIME (OFFSCREEN):
Now I have to think up
another version of Kukaku,
maybe with a bigger head.
-Orihime, maybe you're
thinking too hard.
-Huh?
What do you mean, not going?
-That's what I said.
You three can just go
on ahead without me.
I'm staying to
finish my battle what
that pinhead from yesterday.
-That's not an option!
You're coming with us if
I have to drag you myself!
Argh.
-If I don't show up,
he'll think I'm a chicken!
-Who cares what he thinks?
-Hey.
What's up?
Aren't you two ready to go yet?
URYU (OFFSCREEN):
Get in here, Orihime.
Help me get him out of here.
-Leave me alone.
I'll beat that
boar-riding punk quick,
and catch up to you guys
before you know-- [screaming]
-What's wrong with you?
Have you forgotten why we
came here in the first place?
Lives are at stake.
Rukia's life in particular
is in your hands.
Surely you haven't
forgotten about that.
You don't have time to waste
on foolish grudge matches
with strangers.
Are you ready for
the task at hand?
[music playing]
-What is it now, Renji?
Have they moved up
my execution date?
RENJI (OFFSCREEN): Yes.
It's less than 14 days from now.
The use of the Sokyoku
has been approved.
As a result of that,
we're here to transfer you
to the repentance cell.
-Ah, looks to me like
we're heading out
towards the empty countryside.
Are you sure this
the right way, Uryu?
Hey.
I'm talking to you!
-Just be quiet.
I'm following the elders' map.
And according to this,
we're almost there now.
If you don't like the
way I'm guiding us,
then why don't you take
over, great leader.
-Don't get your
panties in a wad.
I was just wondering.
-Kukaku Shiba is probably
the type of master
who likes to keep his
identity secret by hiding
away out in the wilderness.
-That would make sense.
But it's not the case here.
Living in these
types of surroundings
is just Kukaku's
personal preference.
The fact is, Kukaku
moves frequently.
But the houses themselves
always look much the same.
I guarantee you'll know it's
the house when you see it.
-What's that supposed to mean?
-You'll see soon enough.
Just wait.
Ah.
It looks like we've arrived.
-Wha--
-No way.
-Oh!
It's fantastic.
-Hmm?
-Like I said, you'll know it
when you see it. [chuckling]
-What kind of person would want
to live in a house like that?
-I don't know.
But whoever he is,
he sure doesn't
care about keeping
his identity a secret.
And building houses
like this one,
it's no wonder he doesn't
live in town anymore.
-I bet he's not allowed
to live in town anymore.
-Hm.
So this time the banner is
held up by giant human arms.
It's actually quite
clever, don't you think?
-That is one word
for it, I guess.
-But not the word
I was thinking of.
-Come on.
Let's go.
-Yeah!
[giggling]
-(THINKING) I can't believe he
would actually take me to such
an embarrassing destination.
-(THINKING) I can't let anyone
see me walking into a house
that ridiculous.
-What's the matter with you two?
Hurry up.
-All right.
Oh, and Uryu, you
better not tell
anyone I went int this
place, or you'll pay for it.
-Don't worry about that.
(THINKING) Hmm, strange.
That's an awfully big chimney
for such a small house.
Huh?
And the top is sealed shut.
I wonder why.
MALE SPEAKERS (OFFSCREEN):
Halt, strangers.
-Huh?
-Who dares trespass here?
-Foreigners, from
the looks of them.
And one of them
is a soul reaper.
-Very suspicious.
I, Koganehiko--
-And I, Shiroganehiko--
-Can not allow you passage
inside this building.
-Be gone!
-Or advance, and be killed
now for your insolence.
-Crap, more gatekeepers.
This soul society is just
one annoyance after another.
-Master Yoruichi!
-A descending staircase
right from the front door?
Now that's just weird.
-It kind of makes you wonder how
they get to the upstairs, huh?
-A thousand apologies,
Master Yoruichi,
for not recognizing right
away that it was you.
We had no idea these
trespassers were your servants.
-(THINKING) Now I'm a servant?
-It's my fault.
I should have sent word ahead
that my companions and I were
on our way here.
-[laughing] You're too kind.
Such generous words
from such a person.
Please wait here while
I announce your arrival.
Master, we have visitors.
Now, please enter.
-Well, it's been a long
time, hasn't it Yoruichi?
-Ku-Kukaku's a--
-A woman?
-You assumed it was a man.
But I never told you that.
-Hmm?
What's this?
You seem to have brought a
bunch of brats along with you.
-I shall explain that.
First, though, I have a
favor to ask of you, Kukaku.
-That is usually the case
when you look me up, Yoruichi.
Is it dangerous?
-Probably.
-Heh.
It's been a long time
since we talked like this.
Well, well my friend.
Lucky for you, I enjoy danger.
[music playing]
Right
-Can you see it, Rukia, there
at the edge of the cliff--
the instruments
of your execution.
Sokyoku.
MALE SPEAKER
(OFFSCREEN): A person
who is held here can stand
at the tower's window,
and gaze out at the Sokyoku
and perhaps repent his sins.
That is why this place is
called the repentance cell.
Now your hands I release.
Thank you for escorting the
prisoner here, lieutenant.
We must go now.
-Fine.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
We must lock the tower, sir.
-Huh?
-Lieutenant Abarai,
this is not permitted.
-I want to leave you with
some unconfirmed information.
They say that a
group of intruders
attempted to enter
the soul society
yesterday-- five of them.
Now my sources say one of
them carried a sword as long
as his body, a soul reaper
with orange colored hair.
-All right.
I think I get the picture.
Aw, what the hell.
I'll take the job.
-Excellent.
-I have some reservations.
But with Urahara involved,
how can I say no?
However, while I trust
you completely, Yoruichi,
I do not trust these
kids accompanying you.
So I'm going to
send and overseer
with you, just to keep
an eye on them for me.
-Overseer?
-Yeah.
Well, I call him that.
But he's actually
my kid brother.
He's still kind of a doofus,
and not all that useful.
But he'll have to do.
Hey, in there.
Are you ready?
GANJU (OFFSCREEN): Yeah, sis.
I'm ready.
-All right.
I'm opening the door.
So behavior self.
GANJU (OFFSCREEN):
OK, I promise.
It's an honor to meet you.
My name is Ganju Shiba.
And I'm pleased
to be of service.
[gasps]
-Oh!
[shouting]
-You two already
know each other?
-(THINKING) How many days
has it been since I last saw
Rukia's face look so alive?
Unfortunately, it
was Gin Ichimaru
who met them at the gate.
So the substitute soul reaper
is probably dead already.
It's probably a good thing
I didn't tell her that.
ISSHIN (OFFSCREEN): Hey there.
-Huh?
-I haven't seen you
for a while, Renji.
-Captain Isshin?
-Do you happen to have
a minute to spare?
Well, it's been a long
time since you and I
had a talk, Renji.
-True.
-I haven't seen
you since you were
sent to Captain Zaraki's place.
Quite a few years
ago, wasn't it?
And now you're with
Squad Six, I hear.
-So what did you
want to talk about?
-Renji, would it
be accurate to say
that you are fairly close to
the prisoner, Rukia Kuchiki?
-Huh?
-You can tell me the truth.
Weren't the two of you good
friends in your younger days,
back in the Rukon district?
-Yes.
-In that case, I'll
get right to the point.
In your personal opinion,
does Rukia deserve to die?
-How, how can you
ask such a thing?
ISSHIN (OFFSCREEN): Doesn't
it it seem a little strange?
Her crime was the unauthorized
transfer, and subsequent loss
of her spiritual powers,
and then refusing to return.
Serious offenses, to be sure.
But does this punishment
fit the crime?
The order for immediate return
and disposal of her Gigai,
the lessening of the grace
period from 35 to 25 days,
and the use of the
Sokyuku on a soul reaper
ranked lower than captain--
all these measures are
outside the norm.
I have a strong suspicion that
these things are happening
as the result of the
will of a single person.
-What are you
suggesting, captain?
You're not saying that--
ISSHIN (OFFSCREEN):
I'm suggesting
only that you keep
your eyes open.
Be careful.
There's something not
right in all this.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Attention all captains.
Attention.
Please assemble and report
for an emergency meeting
immediately.
I repeat, all captains
are to report immediately.
[roaring]
[roaring and grunting]
-Die.
[giggling]
-[screaming and laughing]
Take a hike, fat boy!
-Why you orange headed moron!
[grunting] You suck at fighting.
-You ought to know.
How do you like
these, pig straddler?
[shouting, grunting, squealing]
ICHIGO (OFFSCREEN): Going
to rearrange your ugly face
for you!
GANJU (OFFSCREEN):
Take that, dandelion.
-[gasping] Why, you
little-- [shouting]
[screaming]
[explosion and screams]
-Did she have to wreck the
place just to stop them.
-At least now we
know why this lady
has to change houses so often.
-Extreme makeover.
KUKAKU (OFFSCREEN): What's
the matter, you idiots?
I ought to rip you a new one
for being so damned stupid.
At this rate, you two
are going to screw up
this entire mission,
not to mention
you've already
destroyed my house!
I don't want to
hear any excuses.
You got something to say?
-Uh, no, nothing at all.
-(THINKING) What it
is with these two?
Brother and sister, and both
of them nutty as a fruit cake.
[gasp]
-Listen, you idiot.
You're in my house now.
If you don't like the
way I do things here,
then get the hell out.
Any questions?
-Nope.
Nope.
I'm just fine with it.
-OK, then.
I'm glad you understand.
-Your sister's a
real piece of work.
-I know.
-All right.
Everyone on your feet.
-Yes, sir.
-Koganehiko, you
and Shiroganehiko
begin preparations outside.
-Understood.
-The rest of you,
gather up your crap.
And follow me.
-How can it be so
bright down here?
I didn't notice any
generators anywhere.
-Lots of firefly creeper vines.
I keep them growing along the
walls, and on the ceiling.
I
-Don't think I've
ever heard of that.
Is that some sort of
plant that only grows here
in the soul society?
-All right, then.
Here we are.
-Hey.
-Open the door, Ganju.
-Yes, sir.
-I said-- [muffled shouting]
Get your hands off of me.
-Just keep cool, OK?
-[roaring]
-Oh!
-What is that thing?
-It's huge.
-You can quit worrying about
getting through the wall.
With this launcher, I'll get
you all into the Seireitei
through the air.
-The air?
-Or my name's not Kukaku
Shiba, fireworks expert
of the Rukon district.
[music playing]
GANJU (OFFSCREEN): This is the
special little flower crane
cannon my sister,
Kukaku, invented
to break through the
barrier surrounding
the entire Seireitei, which
is made from the Sekkiseki,
a lethal and rare stone that
breaks down spiritual energy
completely.
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN): Uh.
Could you repeat that?
GANJU (OFFSCREEN):
Ugh, forget it.