[theme song]
NARRATOR: Ichigo defeated
Grimmjow, Espada Number
Six, in a deadly battle, and
successfully rescued Orihime.
But shortly afterwards,
Nnoitra, Espada Number Five,
appeared, and challenged him.
Ichigo was forced into
yet another battle
without having time to
recover from his injuries.
His mobility was
greatly affected,
putting him in a
clear disadvantage.
-Well, I have news for you.
So now you know.
That's my rank.
That careless piece
of garbage you barely
managed to defeat back there?
I rank higher than he does.
You're as good as dead.
Look at that.
I forgot your name.
--[panting] Why are we
running away again?
Why?
-Meanwhile, Uryu, Renji,
Pesche, and Dondochakka
escaped from
Szayelaporro's palace
and were heading
deep into Las Noches.
-You want to wait around
for that guy in a room
where we can't use our powers?
-No way.
And besides, now
it looks like we're
going to have to save Rukia
and Chad as well as Orihime.
-It certainly does.
-What?
It can't be.
Is this--
-Welcome back.
-Huh?
-Now then, shall show we
raise the curtain on Act 2?
[interposing voices]
-I said move!
I can't see!
Why are you crying like that?
What is it?
I wanna be upset
too, but I can't
see what I'm supposed
to be upset about.
Now move!
-Whoa!
-Finally.
Oh, no!
I didn't wanna see that!
-[laughing] Well?
How was it?
Did you have a nice little
stroll through my palace?
I don't think I owe
you any explanations,
but let me tell you anyway.
The palace and myself are one.
Being inside of it is like
being inside of my own body,
where I will it
to do what I want.
Must bring back fond
memories, Soul Reaper.
Do you remember the first time
you stepped inside this place?
-Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
-[growls]
-Huh?
-There's something
you should know.
You can't use your Bankai here.
I have complete information
about your Bankai.
Its structure, abilities,
and spiritual pressure,
how it explosively
increases its attack power,
not to mention its
Reishi composition.
I've used all that
information and devised a trap
within the palace to
seal away your Bankai.
Naturally, I looked into
your spiritual pressure
as well, Quincy.
-[gasp]
-What the--
-[laughing] You ignorant fool.
Did you think your
measly little arrow
was actually going
to take me down?
What did you think occurred?
That you'd pierced my
body and ran me through?
Is that it?
[laughing]
I am invincible
inside this palace.
However, under
the circumstances,
I do give you credit for what
you were able to accomplish.
You actually managed
to tatter my clothes.
-But I think nonetheless
that even if the difference
in our powers is great,
and there is no comparison
in our strength--
-[gasp]
-Hado 31, Shakkaho!
-[gasping]
[coughing]
-Damn you!
You lousy Soul Reaper!
Do you know who
you're dealing with?
Huh?
-Exactly as planned.
-[gasp]
-Esta terminado.
It's over, Szayelaporro Granz.
-[gasping]
-[screaming]
-Huh?
-[panting]
-That bastard.
-[growling]
-[gnawing]
-[laughing]
-Hold on!
Where are you going?
-Where am I going?
SZAYELAPORRO (VOICEOVER):
I had no choice
but to change my clothes.
However, even during that
time, I kept watch on you all.
There are hidden cameras in
every wall of this palace.
And I can rearrange the
corridors any way I desire.
If I leave you behind in a
room, it's only natural for you
to try and escape.
Sort of like a tiny
little fly trying
to escape from the
mouth of a giant dragon.
All I did was trick you into
running around in circles,
moving from corridor
to corridor, only
to return to the
exact same place.
Pretty good joke,
wouldn't you say?
Then again, maybe you
wouldn't say that.
You probably think making
you run around long corridors
and then up and down
extremely tall stairways,
only to end up back
in the original room,
is one of the worst
jokes you've ever heard.
But I've got a much worse joke.
The fact that such
lowly worms as you
dare to irritate
me to this extent
and force me to release my
full power to destroy you?
Well, that, to me,
is a much worse joke.
Sip.
La Lujuriosa.
-[whimpering]
-[groaning]
-[gasp]
-No!
-Impossible!
-Unbelievable!
-What is this?
-Mm.
-[groaning]
-Sorry to keep you all waiting.
Now, the curtain shall rise
on the long awaited Act Two.
Oh, that's not right.
I'm sorry.
I take that back.
To be more precise, it's
not how Act Two begins.
Its how it ends.
-[whimpering]
-What is it?
-I have no idea.
-Watch out!
I don't know what it
is, but don't touch it.
-Easier said than done!
-Oh boy!
Whoa, I think I'm
coming out of my head.
-Huh?
Damn it!
-What the hell are you doing?
-Hey, no fair!
You said don't touch it, but
now you all have doubles and I
don't!
-Pesche!
-Yahoo!
More of me to go around!
-What is the matter with you?
-We weren't trying to get hit!
-Now you tell me!
I thought you guys were
leaving me out on purpose!
-I'd like to leave
you out of everything!
-Please allow me my
last shred of dignity.
-Hey, will you two
just cut the crap?
-[laughing]
Now then, all the characters
are assembled on stage.
Let's not make the
audience wait anymore.
As you might presume,
your doppelgangers
possess the same powers
and abilities as you.
Fighting haphazardly
only invites death.
-[growling]
-[whimper]
-However, you
should all be happy.
I have one piece of
deliciously good news for you.
I decided to lift the
trap that seals off
your powers in this room.
Just consider it a gift.
-Huh?
-And so you can fight
to your heart's content
against your alter egos
and kill yourselves off.
[laughing]
-Damn it!
-So before we can
fight our enemy,
we must fight ourselves first.
It's kind of like a
zen riddle, in a way.
He's right about one thing.
This is a bad joke.
-Your moves are
quite impressive.
First time fighting against
a long range weapon?
-Second time, actually.
-Is that so?
-Ichigo, no!
Please stop this!
I'm begging you!
Can't you see that
Ichigo is hurt?
-Shut up, you
ignorant little fool!
Who cares if he's
injured or not?
This is a battle.
It's not supposed
to be a fair fight.
A battle is a monster from
which inequality and intolerance
are born.
A battle forms in stages.
First, hatred develops.
Then hell is unleashed.
For various reasons,
one makes an enemy.
And at that moment, everything
pulses towards a battle.
You think you can come wandering
into your enemy's backyard,
cause a ruckus with
all that fighting,
and expect to sneak out
without being noticed?
Bring it on.
Obviously, I watched you
fight against Grimmjow
from the beginning, so I
already know your every move
even before you make it.
-[whimpering]
-This is bad!
This is bad, Uryu!
-It's a little late to panic.
-You don't understand
what's going on.
With another handsome
guy like that around,
all the girls are gonna go for
him and I'll wind up alone!
-That's what you're
worried about?
-Don't pay any
attention to that idiot!
-Roar!
Zabimaru!
-[wailing]
-Will you two quit
talking nonsense already
and start fighting?
Let's go!
Roar!
Zabimaru!
-Well, I guess we
have no choice.
What do you say we
get down to business?
-Yeah!
Let's get it on!
-[screaming]
-Uh-oh!
-Why avoid it?
I thought I'd give you
a chance to increase
your handsome numbers even more.
-Oh, thanks anyway!
-Oh, no!
Now a bunch more appeared!
-What are you doing?
-But I'm not cut out for this!
-Hm.
-[laughing]
-[panting]
-Oh, Ichigo.
-[laughing]
-Too slow.
Huh?
Such a nice sword.
But it's a real shame
that it only looks sharp.
I shouldn't have
bothered dodging it.
-Ichigo!
-Please don't even
think about it.
With your level of power,
you cannot hope to win.
It may be true that your
power is tremendous,
but the Reishi called
Rikka that configures
your power is extremely fragile.
Even I could easily
destroy them.
The only reason I don't do
so is because your power
belongs to Lord Aizen.
Lord Aizen has
strictly ordered us
not to destroy your
Rikka unless attacked.
If you do attack,
I shall destroy it.
So don't force my hand.
ORIHIME (VOICEOVER): Ichigo.
Wait a minute.
I don't see Nell.
-Is something wrong?
ORIHIME (VOICEOVER): Oh no!
-No, it's-- it's nothing.
-Hm?
I see why you're worried.
I don't see the little Arrancar
who was with you earlier.
There she is.
-[scream]
-Leave her alone!
-[whimpering]
-Ichi!
Huh?
-Are you Nell?
-Huh?
-Uh-huh.
-I thought it was you.
That scar gives you away.
Boy, you've really let yourself
become all shabby, huh?
Tell me, does your mask throb
after it's been cracked?
-[whimpering]
-What's going on
here, you bastard?
-Huh?
-How the hell do you
know who Nell is?
--[wailing] I'm being
chased by myself!
Help me, please!
-Whoa!
-Oh, why'd you move?
I was counting on
you to break my fall.
Don't you want to help out a
scared friend who's in trouble?
All I really want
is to be accepted.
-Stop your nonsense!
This isn't some self-help
group therapy session!
It's a battle for our lives!
-[wail]
-Damn you two!
You managed to dodge our
Dondochakka Press Attack!
-Starting to get the
picture now, crybaby?
-Why am I always being
attacked by everyone?
I have no time for this!
Someone's out there
waiting for me!
-Waiting?
-Who knows what's
happening to poor Nell?
We have to look
for her right away!
-I know we have
to look for Nell,
but we can't do that until
we get out of here first!
-No, please!
Right away!
We have to find her
as soon as possible.
-Hm?
-I've been sensing
it for a while.
She's frightened!
Something terrible is
out there threatening her
and scaring her!
We have to get out
of here now, please!
We can't let Nell get any
deeper into Las Noches!
-I wonder, what possible
reason would you
have for coming back here again?
Did you bring her
here, Soul Reaper?
Don't bother.
I can tell from your
expression that's a yes.
Funny you've been
dragging her around
without ever knowing who she is.
-What?
What do you mean?
--[laughing] Well, if you
don't know, I'll tell you.
You only know her as
Nell, but her full name
is Nelliel Tu Odelschwanck.
She's a former Espada.
-[whimpering]
[theme song]
ORIHIME (VOICEOVER):
Nelliel Tu Odelschwanck
can't be Nell's real name.
I mean, the Nell
I know can't even
pronounce a name like that.
ICHIGO (VOICEOVER):
Come on, Orihime.
Even Nell can say her own name.
Um, right, Hell?
NELL (VOICEOVER):
[nervous laughter]
Can't say for sure!