Seethe, Sumitsukigasa!
Yaah!
Huaah!
[Rukia]
I expect you're now planning to
use your newly acquired power
to rule the Soul Society.
Rule?! Psh!
How could you
possibly think that's
what I really want?
My objective is to
destroy the Soul Society.
[gasp] Destroy?!
Time is of the essence.
Now die.
[gasp]
[Rukia]
Ichigo!!
[gasp]
[small gasp]
Ichigo!
His Hollowfication!
It's been reversed!
[Rukia]
Ichigo! Are you all right?
[Ichigo]
Rukia?
Ah! Impossible!
What just happened?!
Rrgh!
[Orihime]
Ichigo!
Orihime! You need to
take Ichigo and get him
away from here now.
No, Rukia, I can't
leave you guys alone.
[Rukia]
What are you talking about?
Nozomi's still
inside of him.
Right at that moment,
my consciousness seemed
to go completely blank.
Ugh!
[beep]
It's me.
What is it, sir?
I need more fusion stabilizer.
Prepare it immediately.
I'll get on it right away.
Hmf.
Fusion stabilizer?
Did you hear that, Ichigo?
It looks like his
fusion might not
be permanent yet.
I think you're right.
Substitute Soul Reaper.
I can see that ignoring
you before was a mistake.
Although your Spirit Energy
has left you, I can no
longer allow you to live.
[gasp]
Renji! Uryu! Chad!
All of you, step aside, at once!
Sorry pal.
In case you haven't
noticed, we don't take
orders from an enemy,
So go ahead and take
your best shot.
If you want to kill Ichigo,
you're going to have to go
through us.
He's been our friend
for a long time,
and we're not going to hand him
over to you without a fight.
A friend, you say?
Ridiculous.
[Ouko]
You're fools if you're
willing to spill your own
blood for the sake of others.
If friends are defined
by the commission of a
worthless sacrifice,
Then you all will
have to pay the price!
Byakuya!
Close, but no cigar!
Are you okay?
Hyaah!
[Shunsui]
Hado Number Sixty-Three!
Raikoho!
[Toshiro]
Yaaahhh!
They're certainly
keeping the pressure on.
Byakuya! Why did
you take such a
risk to protect me?
Heh.
[Toshiro]
Damn! They have
us surrounded!
This is bad!
There's no way out!
You need to go heal
Captain Kuchiki!
[Yumichika]
You're going nowhere!
They're taking advantage of
every opportunity to hit us
while we're down!
Their strategy is to keep us
off-balance while they swoop
in and out at will.
If one of us is injured and
not reacting quickly,
that's the one they attack.
We're completely surrounded.
We have no advantage!
[Kenpachi]
Are you all just
gonna stand there?
What's the big deal?
All we need to do is
kill off these guys,
one by one!
That's what the Reigai
are trying to do to us!
Kill us off, one by one!
Details, details!
I'm gonna do them
before they do me!
I agree!
Ha ha ha ha!
Rwwaah!
Hyaa!
Auggh!
[Yoruichi]
What should we do?
We're outnumbered, and if
we lose even one member,
they're going to use that
opportunity to take us all out.
[Shunsui]
I have to agree.
This looks pretty bad.
Even one small mistake could
get us completely annihilated.
It's useless!
Seethe, Sumitsukigasa!
El Directo!
Tsuginomai!
Hakuren!
[gasps]
Haa!
Hihio!
Zabimaru!
[snicker]
[gasp]
Eagh!
That was careless of me.
I should have taken
better precautions to
avoid getting injured
by your weapon.
[Ouko]
As I recall, it weakens
the bonds between Reishi.
Exactly. This may surprise
you, but you're not the only
one who can absorb Reishi.
How interesting. So you plan
to challenge me by attempting
to absorb my Reishi?
We plan to do more
than challenge you.
[Uryu]
You obviously underestimate
the power of my friends, which
will become your downfall.
What's your play, Quincy?
You'll see soon enough.
Yah!
[Chad]
Rrraagh!
Pathetic!
Huh?
Haaaa!
What the hell?!
Bakudo Number Four!
Hainawa!
Aah!
Agh!
Uryu, do it now!
That's it. You can
no longer escape.
Let's see which one
of us will be left
standing, my friend!
Heh!
What the--?!
[Renji, Chad and Rukia]
Augh! Argh! Uugh!
I had anticipated this attack.
You're able to create a
containment field by placing
your weapons in five corners.
To activate the technique,
it must consume the Reishi
stored within its hilt.
You created the containment
as you attacked me.
But you were so intent
on your maneuver as you
were pulling it off,
that you failed to notice that
I used Sumitsukigasa to absorb
the Reishi you had stored.
That's how I neutralized
your attack.
Not knowing that, you
ended up sacrificing
your own allies.
Before the awesome power that
I possess, your so-called
friendship holds no meaning!
[Uryu]
I figured you'd
think that way.
Huh?
I knew that you'd see through
my Sprenger attack, and that
you'd absorb the Reishi from my
Seeleschneider. However...
[gasp]
Huh?
Kageroza! It's over!
Huaaah!
Wuaaaahhh!
Stop--- No!
[Uryu]
Don't worry, Ichigo.
We're going to imprison
him like this without
triggering the explosion.
If we can continue to drain
the Spirit Energy from the
wound on his back where the
Reishi bond was weakened,
we should be able to undo
his fusion with Nozomi.
Don't underestimate me!
Hajokuri!
Wha--? What the
hell is that?!
It's swallowing
Sprenger's Reishi!
How is that even possible?!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
My Hajokuri technique
turns everything around
it into Reishi and
proceeds to absorb it!
And then...!
Yah!
Now die!
Substitute Soul Reaper!
Damnit!
Dgh!
EYAAAHHH!
The Reigai cannot
attack us right now.
Really? And why is that?
Because we're all keeping
a tight formation.
They can't use a strategy
of switching off on
opponents to disrupt us.
Huh?
After watching them operate,
I don't think any of them will
risk sacrificing themselves
to break our formation.
Rgh.
Huh.
I see. Earlier you threw
yourself at them so you
could test your theory.
[Kenpachi]
Yaaah!
Huh?
Raagh!
Heh heh!
Hm.
[Toshiro]
You sure you want to do that?
If one or more of
you leave here,
What do you think
will happen, once our
side outnumbers yours?
[gasp]
Now this is interesting.
Whaddya say we have
a test of wills?
Dammit!
Agh!
Yaaaaagh!
What happened?
[in pain]
Urgh...Agh!
What's going on?
He's acting very strange.
Get out of there! Stop it!
[both]
Get out of my head!
Nozomi!
What is it? Is the fusion
starting to break down?
[Rukia]
Stop it! Stop what
you're doing!
Nozomi!
[gasp]
Ichigo!
I'm right here!
I'll get you
out of there!
Don't let that bastard
Kageroza swallow you!
Ichigo... Please...
You have to kill me!
Wha?? What are you
talking about?
The Zanpakuto he's using
is able to kill him!
But you have to do it
quickly, while I hold
him at bay! Hurry!
I can't do that!
I won't let you die!
Please! I'm begging you!
[gasp]
You all risked your
lives to protect me.
But now, It's my turn
to protect all of you!
[conflicted gasp]
No, I won't!
We're friends, Nozomi!
We'll find a way to save you!
I swear!
Heh!
[gasp]
Hah!
Renji!
[straining]
Ichigo!
I need you to get back!
Out of my way, you fools!
Yaah!
Ungh!
Urgh...
Oof!
Rukia! Renji!
Friends, you say?
Tell me something,
Substitute Soul Reaper...
Because I don't understand.
Why do you people keep
using that word?
Why do you always cling to
that one word when your
backs are against the wall?
Answer me!
[Byakuya]
Why have you chosen
this particular way to fight?
What?
Why do you choose
to separate us?
And then attack the one you've
separated from the others?
I understand it as a tactic,
but it doesn't seem like a
choice you would make,
since you should possess
the same pride that we do.
To distrust others, loathe
the fellow allies around you,
and consider isolation a virtue.
That has to be the true
nature of Kageroza.
[Ouko]
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
What's wrong?
Cat got your tongue?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Ichigo! Ngh!
Ichigo!
See? Friends are meaningless!
A solitary life is the only
true validation of existence!
I organized my invading army
without help from anyone.
I empowered that force, and it
is now about to annihilate the
Thirteen Court Guard Squads.
The same group that
refused to give me my due.
And by resurrecting
myself as a Mod Soul,
I was able to harness the
true power of my Zanpakuto,
a power that I could not
control in my original form.
This is truly the ideal
existence of solitude
that I have strived for!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
You're so pathetic!
Huh?
Didn't you realize something
when you were doing this?
The essence of a Mod Soul is
based on a Soul Reaper's Reishi.
And that means you were unable
to create them all by yourself.
And besides, you wouldn't
have been able to wield
your true powerwithout Nozomi,
from whom you cut yourself off!
You just proved your
assumption was wrong!
The fact of the matter is,
you couldn't have done
a thing without drawing
from those around you!
[gasp]
Here's a lesson
for you!
No matter how hard we try,
we can't do everything all
on our own!
And refusing to
acknowledge that fact,
makes you nothing
but a damn fool!
Rrr... [gasp]
You're saying that
Kageroza's personality
is affecting our style
of fighting?
You're not going to
break our solidarity.
Certainly not by
employing the tactics
you've apparently chosen.
Shut up!
Ungh!
[shaken] Rrrrnnh!
Rrgh!
[gasp]
[seething]
Nemu! Damn it!
Agh!
I'll put off eliminating you
for just a moment.
You can watch as Nozomi
completely becomes mine.
Then you can die in agony.
[gasp]
Uhn!
[Ouko]
You! What is the
meaning of this?!
Hmpf!
[Kon]
It means you've
been punked!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
That voice
sounds like Kon!
You stupid dummy!
You fell for it,
didn't you?!
What do you say
to that, genius?
Why don't you just
kiss my ass and scram!
Get back in there!
You're creeping us out!
Mmmf!
That...feels...
good...Really.
You little rat!
How were you
able to do that?
So, You really want to know?
Okay, how did it go again?
[Kisuke]
Well it all started with
Mayuri liquefying his body
to fake his own death so he
could seek out Kageroza's lab,
where he ended up helping
me defeat my imposter.
Then we decided to remove
the Soul Candy from
Lieutenant Nemu's Reigai
and replace it with Kon's,
and voila! The rest is history!
Got it? That's what
Clog-Dude said!
So you have me to
thank for everything!
Thank you
for what?!
You didn't
really do
anything!
What?! Oh yes, I did!
You see this?
This is a Mod Soul!
With your Spirit Energy!
Swallow it!
[gulp]
[gasp]
I kept my promise to you,
Ichigo! Now get out there
and save Nozomi!
Heh! Yeah, you got it, Kon!
Rrrgh! You sorry
excuse for a Mod Soul!
Oh yeah? I'm better than
the ones you created!
Yours are just slaves,
doing your bidding!
At least I have
some free will!
Don't give them an
opening to move in.
Yeah, I'm well aware.
We're wise to any
moves that they make!
What is it with you guys?
I told you to keep
out of this!
Sorry about
that, Captain.
This could well be
our last battle!
We'd be privileged
to die with you.
He's right, it would
be a great honor.
If you don't mind.
What? Hah! Fine, whatever!
In fact, I guess it wouldn't
be such a bad thing, to have
someone covering my back!
[Toshiro]
Hmf, You guys, working
together in battle?
Now that is really
out of character!
You're wrong. When it comes
to protecting what we must,
we'll use any means necessary!
Protecting what you must?
Are you referring to your pride?
No. We have but one
thing we protect.
And that is the Soul Society.
Hang on, Nozomi. I promise you,
you're not alone now, and
you'll never be alone again.
And this time, we're not
going to let anyone stop
us from saving you!
We'll teach this bastard a
lesson he'll never forget!
The power of friendship!
Go get him, Ichigo!
Ban kai!
[Rukia]
Good job, Kon.
[Orihime]
But weren't you scared?
[Kon]
It didn't even occur to me!
All I could think about was
saving the two of you!
[Orihime]
That's amazing!
[Rukia]
Truthfully, though,
you had to have been
a little scared.
[Kon]
I don't know the meaning
of the word! Hey, what is
the meaning of the word?