[theme music]
‐[whimpering]
‐OK.
Now who the hell's this?
‐Captain of Squad
Three, Gin Ichimaru.
‐Oh, not good.
‐[moaning]
‐Jitambo!
No!
‐[moaning]
‐Unacceptable.
Being a guardian
of the gate doesn't
mean you're supposed
to open the gate.
‐[grunting]
YORUICHI (OFFSCREEN):
(THINKING) How careless of me.
I didn't think someone of
his caliber would show up.
Even if these kids
have gotten stronger,
the strength of a captain
is beyond their imagination.
They cannot fight him.
We must avoid that potentially
disastrous scenario
at all costs.
‐[grunting] I defended
the gate, and lost.
Once I lost, I had
to open the gate.
There was nothing
else I could do.
‐What you're saying
makes no sense.
A gatekeeper who loses isn't
supposed to open the gate.
When a gatekeeper
loses, it means death.
‐[grunting]
[roaring and clashing of blades]
‐[gasp] Ichigo!
‐You want to tell me
just what the hell you
think you're doing?
‐Yes, Ichigo.
What are you doing?
‐What's the big idea showing
up now, and trying to butt in?
You stupid fricking‐ass clown.
Anyone who's pathetic enough
to make an appearance in order
to attack an unarmed man
deserves to be killed.
‐You're sure a funny kid.
And you're not scared of me.
‐Hell no.
‐Careful, boy.
You must stop, Ichigo.
It is best we retreat for now.
‐(THINKING) Ichigo?
‐Huh?
Why?
I'm only just
getting started here.
GIN (OFFSCREEN):
(THINKING) It's him.
‐There's no way I'm going
to submit to this guy.
Look, I'll be fine.
So just let me
finish this guy off.
GIN (OFFSCREEN): You
must be Ichigo Kurosaki.
‐You know about me?
But how could you?
‐Just as I thought.
How very predictable.
‐What?
Hey, where are you going?
Hey, wait!
‐All the more reason why
I can't let you pass.
‐So then why are you
standing so far back?
Unless you're planning
on throwing that dagger.
‐It's not a dagger.
In fact, this is my zanpakuto.
Impale him.
Shinzo.
‐Ichigo!
‐No!
The gate!
‐Bye bye now.
‐Ichigo, are you all right?
‐What happened?
‐[growling] Look at the gate.
That bastard.
‐Well, it seems that
you are all right.
‐I'm sorry, guys.
It's all my fault
that the gate closed.
‐No, don't start
blaming yourself.
Your opponent was Gin Ichimaru.
It couldn't be helped.
You should just be glad
that you were not hurt.
‐Would you do me a favor?
Go over there, and try to
help Jitambo if you can.
‐Mhmm.
FEMALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
That's strange.
‐Lookie what we've got here.
‐They must've been
hiding until now.
‐But why?
‐Well, obviously we were
frightening to them.
Souls who come to
the soul society
illegally, without a soul
reaper escort are called rioka,
and are said to be the root
cause of all kinds of trouble.
‐They must think that
we're their enemies.
‐Please stop.
Allow me to introduce myself.
‐Huh?
‐I am the elder of
this area, which
is known as the Rukon district.
All of us witnessed the
events that occurred just now.
And we would all like to welcome
you as Jidanbo's true saviors.
This place is full
of many soul reapers
that are rotten
and incorrigible.
But Jitanbo, a native of Rukon
district, is not one of them.
He's always been so kind to us.
‐We all witnessed how you
fought against Gin Ichimaru
in order to save Jitanbo.
You must surely
be a good person.
We can see that.
But still, what
a terrible wound.
‐Right.
There's no need to worry.
I should be able to
heal Jitanbo's wounds.
[gasping and cries of happiness]
‐Huh?
You're kidding me.
You really can heal that wound?
‐Sure.
Just leave it to me.
Shuno. Ayame.
‐Hi.
Do you need some help?
‐Hello.
‐Could you lend me your powers?
‐Of course we will.
As your power, we are here
awaiting your command.
All you have to do is recite
the spirit chant, remember?
‐Mhmm.
All right.
Here we go.
Sotenkishun. I reject.
[gasps]
‐That's truly amazing.
So when exactly did
you get that power?
YUICHI (OFFSCREEN): Excuse me.
Please let me through.
Ugh.
Move it!
Ugh!
Hey, over here.
It's me.
It's Yuichi.
Don't you remember?
‐Yuichi Shibata?
‐Right, Yuichi the cockatiel.
You remember now, don't you?
‐Uh, it's really you.
‐I can tell you've
put on some weight.
‐I have not.
People who have never
been here before
always make that mistake.
You only think that because
you knew me as a parakeet.
Here, you don't change at all.
You stay the same as
when you first get here.
‐I see.
Tell me, Yuichi, it's‐‐ uh,
what happened with your mother?
‐Oh.
Here's where I live.
I know it looks
kind of run down.
But that makes it really
cool in the summer.
And my family, they're
all really nice.
‐What do you mean, your family?
‐Yuichi,, so you're back.
You know that mom and dad
were really worried about you.
‐[gasp] I, uh‐‐
‐Did he say your mom and dad.
‐Uh, it's just, you see, uh,
this is, uh, Hironari Horiuchi.
And I guess he's
like my big brother.
‐It's nice to meet you.
‐So he's like your big brother?
‐It is often the case
in the soul society‐‐
or rather in the
Rukon district‐‐
that people who aren't actually
related to one another by birth
form their own families,
and live together.
People who have died in
different times and places
come to form special bonds.
It's rare for someone to
meet up with a real family
member who died earlier.
‐Hmm.
But don't the soul
reapers do what
they can to reunite
you with your family?
‐Well, no, not really.
You see, I died in 1947.
It happened in
Yamanashi prefecture,
long before Yuichi died.
You can see by our age and
location that were far apart.
‐So that means you really
haven't seen your mother yet?
‐No.
But I haven't stopped
looking for her.
‐Hey, don't worry about it, kid.
And remember that no matter
what, we're all here for you.
Listen to me.
You mustn't worry.
We were all just like him
when we first got here.
But eventually, we
all change with time.
‐(SADLY) I won't
see my mom again.
[crying]
‐Uh, excuse me.
Would be all right if I stay
with Yuichi a little longer?
‐That should be just fine.
In that case, I'll
have to go and let
the family know what's going on.
‐I've been meaning to ask what
you're doing here, mister.
You're not dead, or
something, are you?
‐Uh, no.
I'm not dead.
‐OK.
Then why are you here.
‐I'm beginning to
wonder, myself.
‐Hey, look over there
up on that roof.
Isn't that your
soul reaper friend?
You know, even if he
goes up higher than that,
he won't be able to
see beyond the gate.
‐But that won't stop
him from looking.
Because he just never gives up.
That's the kind of guy he is.
You know what I mean?
I guess I must have been
right about your age
when I first started to
realize the fact that I was
a lot different
than everyone else.
I was right.
Somehow I possessed
this amazing strength.
And that strength was
what made me different.
But I don't understand
this power that I have.
I want to understand.
I have a feeling that coming
here will give me some clues.
I guess that's
part of why I came.
But in searching
for these answers,
I have had to risk everything.
‐You must really believe the
risk is worth the reward.
‐I believe that, Yuichi.
And that's why you
must never give up.
If you never give up,
and keep searching,
you will find your mother.
You believe that,
don't you, Yuichi?
‐Yeah, I do now, mister.
‐That's great.
So let's both make a promise.
‐OK.
‐Oh, uh, Chad.
‐Yeah, Ichigo?
‐What were you thinking, man.
You gotta at least
let me know when
you're behind me like that.
‐Ichigo, you should know I'm
always going to have your back.
‐Are you serious?
You really want us to give up
trying to get past the gate?
YORUICHI (OFFSCREEN): No.
I don't mean give up completely.
Once the gate has been
opened, it's only logical
that the security on the other
side becomes that much tighter.
Which means that continuing
with the same strategy
is not necessarily
the best approach.
‐I have to agree
with you on that.
‐So then what about
the other gates?
‐There won't be much
different from what
we faced with this one.
‐Well in that case, then what
the hell are we gonna do?
‐Well, isn't it obvious?
If we cannot use the gate, then
naturally we must enter another
way.
Elder, do you know the
whereabouts of Kukaku Shiba?
‐What?
You can't be serious.
‐As you may know,
she is someone who
likes to change her
place of residence.
I haven't been able to find
out where she currently lives.
‐Kukaku Shiba!
[trampling hooves]
‐Are you sure?
Don't tell me you're planning to
go through the wall like that.
‐Uh, like what?
[trampling hooves]
‐Huh?
What's that noise?
‐Sounds like a stampede.
‐Whoa!
‐[screaming]
‐What's happening?
‐[moaning]
MALE SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
Anyone know who this guy is?
‐[oink]
‐Huh?
Are you kidding?
What in the‐‐ what's
a boar doing here?
‐Well, well, well.
What do you know?
Thrown again by old Bonnie.
There's got to be a
better way to travel.
Hey.
It's been a long time, old man.
‐Konju, no.
What are you doing here?
I think you should go home.
‐What gives?
Look, I know it's been a while.
But is that any way to
greet an old friend?
I mean, what are your
guests here going to think?
Huh?
What do we have here?
Would someone explain to me why
there's a stinking soul reaper
here?
‐What did you just say?
‐What's the matter,
your ears not working?
What I said was, would
someone explain to me
why there's a stinking
soul reaper here.
‐Huh?
Well, then say something,
you snivelling dandelion.
[grunting] Hey!
Just what are you trying to do?
Are you picking a fight with me?
‐You started it pig straddler.
You walked in, and picked
on me for no reason.
What kind of a moron are you?
GANJU (OFFSCREEN): Moron?
‐What should we do about this?
We've got to stop those two.
‐Quite a mess.
This is just as I expected.
‐Come on!
This is not time to
sit there drinking tea.
Just tell us who the guy is.
‐Are you kidding me?
You really don't know who I am?
‐No, I don't.
‐Me neither.
‐No.
‐I don't want to know.
‐Heh.
Then that settles it.
Let me introduce myself.
My given name is Ganju, the
self proclaimed Deep‐Red Bullet
of West Rukon, and self
proclaimed but universally
acknowledged boss
man of West Rukon.
And finally, the self proclaimed
number one soul reaper hater
of West Rukon.
‐Self proclaimed.
‐Hah.
You forgot to add
self proclaimed fool.
‐Say what?
‐You heard me.
‐[roaring]
‐Ichigo!
‐No, Ichigo!
‐Hold it right there.
We won't let you get
in the boss man's way.
‐But look, if you really
want to fight someone‐‐
‐We will be happy to oblige you.
‐Ganju's henchmen.
‐What do we do now?
‐See that?
ICHIGO'S FRIENDS (OFFSCREEN):
They're all riding on boars.
‐Get out of here
while you still can.
Now listen.
As long as I'm
alive, no soul reaper
will ever be allowed to step
one stinking foot inside West‐‐
‐Boss man!
‐Shut up.
Give it a rest, why don't you?
Look, if you want to
fight, then I'll fight you.
‐Why you!
You punched my ruggedly handsome
face‐‐ not once, but twice.
‐Actually, the second time
around, it was a kick,
you idiot.
‐That's enough fighting, Ichigo.
You should not be
using up your strength
in a meaningless brawl.
‐Hey, don't forget
he started the fight.
So if you want this to
stop, then tell him.
‐[sighing in annoyance]
(THINKING) Getting all worked
up over such a silly
thing, the fool!
‐The way I see things, you
and me are destined to fight.
We don't have a
choice in the matter.
‐Stop this fighting, Ganju!
Can't you see this man
is a good soul reaper?
‐That's enough.
Look, soul reapers
are soul reapers.
To me, there is no good or bad.
‐You're wrong, Ganju.
‐Now get ready.
‐Not good.
How does Ichigo expect to handle
him without his zanpakuto?
‐[gasp]
‐I got it.
Thanks, Chad!
‐Very impressive.
I was wondering when
you'd use your zanpakuto.
However, don't think
that you can win this,
just because you
wield a bigger weapon.
[chuckling]
Sink!
‐The ground is gone.
‐It's like quicksand.
‐Just hang in there, Ichigo.
‐Using weird tricks
won't help you win.
‐[roaring]
‐All I can say is, if
that didn't drop you,
then you are one tough warrior.
‐[gruntng]
[grunts and impacts]
‐What's the matter?
It's not over yet.
‐[roaring]
[alarm clock ringing]
‐What time is it now?
‐It's 9:00 already, boss man!
This is going to be bad.
‐What?
Nine o'clock?
Come on.
We gotta go, Bonnie.
[whistling]
[trampling hooves]
‐Bonnie?
[music playing]
‐In the next episode, we go to
Kukaku Shiba's unique house,
located somewhere in West Rukon.
So what's the secret to this
gorgeous wooden structure
surrounded by open lands?
Well, I guess you'll just have
to wait and see. [giggling]
‐So these are natural
wood pillars, huh?