[theme music]
NARRATOR: Sosuke
Aizen's true objective
was to wipe out the enriched
spirit zone of Karakura Town.
This would allow him
to create the Oken,
and eventually take over
the entire Soul Society.
In a bold attempt to keep
Aizen's plan from succeeding,
the Soul Reapers built a
replica of Karakura Town
in the World of the Living and
readied themselves for battle.
With the opposing Espadas and
Soul Reapers fully prepared,
the furious battle between
them finally commenced.
-All right.
You should stand back.
All things in the
universe turn to ashes.
Ryujin Jakka!
Jokaku Enjo.
We are safe.
This wall of flames ought to
keep Sosuke and his cohorts
at bay for quite some time.
No then, we shall
show them no mercy.
End them at once.
NARRATOR: Meanwhile,
in Hueco Mundo,
Ichigo was determined to get to
Tower Five to rescue Orihime.
But an army of Exequias
intercepted him.
The Exequias sheer numbers
gradually overwhelmed Ichigo.
By all accounts,
it appeared the end
was near for Ichigo
and his quest.
Then suddenly--
[shouting]
-[laughs] Yeah, want some more?
-What?
Renji!
-Heh.
-El Directo!
[shouting]
-Hey, Chad!
-Tsugi no mai, Hakuren!
-Rukia!
-Idiot.
Save the heartwarming
reunion for later.
Now get going, Ichigo!
-I'm on it!
-Oh, that guy.
He still needs a babysitter.
NARRATOR: In the
meantime, Orihime
found himself alone
in the tower, face
to face with Ulquiorra.
Orihime told Ulquiorra
that because she
had shared her heart
with her friends,
she was not afraid of dying.
But Ulquiorra had his doubts
about Orihime's declaration.
-Your heart, you say.
You humans always
toss around that word
so casually, as
if it's something
you can hold in the
palm of your hand.
Tell me, what is a heart?
If I tore a whole in your
chest, would I see it?
If I split open your
skull, would it be there?
-[gasp]
[rumbling]
-Ichigo!
-Hm.
Step away from her.
-I was just about to.
My responsibilities are clear.
My duty is to protect Las
Noches until Lord Aizen returns.
I haven't received orders to
take the life of this woman.
Until those orders come,
I will allow her to live.
However, you are a
different matter.
Killing you would be
absolutely within my duties
of protecting Las Noches.
You shall die by my sword.
-What a surprise.
It's funny, I never figured
you would be the first one
to draw your sword.
On the way here, I was thinking
that you wouldn't take me
seriously enough
to draw right away.
So tell me, is it reasonable
to say you consider me
an opponent that's equal to you?
-You might say that.
I consider you an
enemy worth destroying.
-That's good enough.
-[gasp] Ichigo.
-So, all right.
What should we do here now?
Stuck with our enemies while
our boss is in that mess.
-You should be more careful with
what you say about Lord Aizen.
-And you should
mind the words you
speak to me as well, Harribel.
Seeing as how the
boss is caught up,
I will be the one
giving orders here.
And no one will complain.
-Hold on.
-Mila Rose, be quiet.
-You know, I'm good with that.
Ah!
What was that for, Lilynette?
Stop it!
LILLYNETTE: You good with that?
What are you kissing ass for?
You always kiss up to
everyone everywhere.
It never ends with you!
There they go again.
LILLYNETTE: You want to
make yourself for a change.
-The enriched spirit zone
lives down there beneath us.
Aizen said it's a fake.
He said they replaced
the real world
with a replica built
by the Soul Society.
Before the fire surrounded
him, he said all we have to do
is invade the Soul Society
and obtain the enriched spirit
zone.
But is it really
necessary for us
to go through all that trouble?
I figure from what was said
earlier, it works like this.
He said they
erected four pillars
on each side of the town and
used the power of the pillars
to swap out the entire place.
So what would happen if we
destroyed those pillars?
Now, Findorr.
-Sir.
[high-pitched noise]
BARAGGAN: I know where
those pillars are located.
There's a method to
placing things like that.
I'm certain that
their position's
at the four cardinal points.
-[shout] This is terrible!
They know!
[cries] They know!
[roaring]
-[gasp]
This is bad.
If they end up
destroying those pillars,
the real Karakura Town that
we sent to the Soul Society
will come back here.
And you know what
that would mean!
The real Karakura
Town will become
nothing but a battlefield!
[shout]
If they destroy those
pillars...
Karakura Town
will return and be destroyed!
-Quiet down, you fool
-Huh?
How naive do you think I am.
I would never allow any of
these pillars to be unprotected.
-Hm?
-Huh?
What?
IKKAKU: Extend, Hozukimaru!
YUMICHIKA: Bloom, Fuji Kujaku!
IZURU: Raise your
head, Wabisuke!
-I have stationed
capable fighters
to defend these pillars.
-Hm?
-Huh?
-You did?
-What?
Ikkaku, Yumichika,
Izuru, Shuhei!
I thought they were holding
down the fort back home.
I should have known
when they weren't
there when you had us assembled.
I felt good thinking
the soul society
was counting on me
instead of them.
Ha, ha, serves them
right, I thought.
Wait, hold on.
All of you knew about this?
-Sure did.
-Huh?
-It's an insult to
think we're like you.
-What?
SUI-FENG: I did
tell you about it.
I think you were munching
on fried crackers
and missed when I said it.
And you did look kind of
dazed from eating so much.
MARECHIYO: Me?
-That's the only explanation.
Munching Marechiyo.
-Come on.
RANGIKU: You were
the one in a daze
as you had a fried
cracker feeding frenzy.
-Hey, now!
Chowing down on fried
crackers and being in a daze--
-Maybe I didn't tell him.
-Hm.
Four new soldiers.
They can't stop us now.
It's as though four ants
guard those pillars.
Since that's the case, we will
squash them with four dragons.
Poww, Chuhlhourne, Abirama,
Findorr, go crush them.
-[together] Sir!
As you have commanded,
your majesty.
-Here we go.
Someone's coming.
[grunt]
Huh.
Well, well.
Aren't you a big fella?
I pray you're as
imposing as you look.
-You pray?
To what?
Explain that.
Are you saying that you
Soul Reapers have a god?
-Huh?
Explain?
Uh, now that you mention
it, we don't really
pray to anything specifically.
All right.
Let's do this!
If it'll make you
fight me any better,
than I'll even pray to
your god if you like.
-I see.
Then we do not have a problem.
Our god, the king, knows one
thing better than anyone.
In his divine wisdom,
he understands
that you are no match for me.
-Oh?
FINDORR: Before
we begin, I'd like
to ask, what rank do you hold?
-Shuhei Hisagi.
I'm a Squad Nine lieutenant.
-Very well.
In that case, I too will
fight with the strength
of a lieutenant-class
Soul Reaper as well.
-Hm?
-Huh?
CHUHLHOURNE: Here, here, here.
Look, I am here!
[giggle] His majesty, King
Barragan's First Fraccion,
Charlotte Chuhlhourne
has arrived.
[giggle] Huh?
My, my, my, my, my, my, my.
-[groan]
-Mhm.
-I've got this rule.
I don't look at ugly things.
-Oh, dear.
-Hey, just what the hell
did you do that for,
you stupid bastard!
-Well, that's exactly
what I want to ask you!
What's the idea of
calling someone you just
met for the first
time ugly, sourpuss?
See here, I'll
tell you something
that's really ugly-- judging
someone based on appearances.
That's right.
I'm talking about what lives in
your heart and can't be seen.
What a nice line,
if I do say so.
I mean, someone
with a heart as pure
as mine, someone who possesses
the sweet beauty of never
judging others-- it's
an absolute beauty that
defies all else.
Can you understand such things?
-[groan]
-When I say something,
you can at least
look at me, you ugly freak.
-I don't need to look at you,
because nothing you're saying
makes any sense, you
flipped out hairball!
-Oh, come on.
Just take a look.
-No way!
-I said look!
Look here.
I said look!
-[groan] Stop it!
Don't bring your
ugliness near me.
-How dare you!
You said it again!
You called me ugly!
-I'll say it all I want.
Ugly, ugly, ugly!
-I'll punch you!
ABIMARA: [shout] Gonna do it!
Gonna do it!
Who is the bravest of his
majesty King Baraggan's
Fracciones, I ask you.
I am the one!
Who is it that is the most
trusted of his majesty King
Baraggan's
Fracciones, I ask you.
I am that guy!
Who happens to be the strongest
of his majesty King Baraggan's
Fracciones, I ask you.
I am that one guy!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, huh.
Gonna do it.
I gotta do it.
Gonna do it Gonna do it.
Gonna do it, do it, do it!
Hey.
Hey, you there!
Why is it you're not
saying this along with me.
You're kind of depressing.
-What the hell do you mean?
You want me to do
that song and dance?
-Did you just call what
I do a song and dance?
There's no such thing!
Don't mock what I do!
This is a ritual,
a glorious ritual
where we shout to each other our
intent to kick each other's ass
and then psych one another
to utter his call to battle.
Let's go.
Let's do it!
Are you ready?
Gonna do it!
I gotta do it!
Gotta do it!
Come on, do it.
-No way.
I will not yell about
wanting to kick your ass.
There's no point in
joining in on an energy
wasting, negative ritual.
ABIMARA: The only
one who's negative is
you, Mr. Bump on a Log
That's About to Die!
How great.
I get stuck a gutless one.
Oh, well.
I'm King Baraggan's
Fraccion Abirama Redder.
What's your name, Soul Reaper.
-I am Squad Three
lieutenant Izuru Kira.
-You said Squad Three?
Ha.
-Huh?
-Now I get it.
You were under Gin Ichimaru.
Yeah, I heard about how
he abandoned you back
in the Soul Society.
But now I can see
it all makes sense.
I'd say he had no other
choice but to leave
a gutless guy like-- huh?
-I'm warning you.
Don't mention his name so
casually in my presence.
I mean, if you're
going to die anyway,
wouldn't it be preferable
to die in one piece?
-Now I see.
So you do have some guts.
I like that look on your face.
[theme music]
SHUHEI: It's been awhile
since I've made an appearance.
IZURU: Shuhei, don't
go getting giddy.
SHUHEI: Who's giddy?
I don't expect that
I'll get to show off
my winning smile, impressive
strength, and universally
appealing nature
to all the viewers.
IZURU: No one said
anything about that.