Where did you go, Gin?
I'm going to become
a Soul Reaper.
[gasp]
[Gin]
Since that's the case,
I'll take care of killing them.
It'll be so much fun.
[Aizen]
Gin...
[gasps]
Kill'em,
Kamishininoyari.
Gin! Damn you...
Gin...
It's over... It's over now.
[explosion]
Aaahhhhhh!!!
Whoa! What is that?!
I have no idea!
I always win, Gin.
Even without it being
inside me, that Hogyoku
that you took from me,
Still belongs to me.
What the hell's happening?!
[Gin]
If tomorrow, you were
to turn into a snake,
And you began
devouring humans,
If with that same mouth,
you told me you loved me,
Would I still be able to say,
"I love you",
The same way I do today?
[panting]
I know this feeling,
its... Hakufuku.
Augh! Gin!
Yes.
I had already discovered
the answer known as the
Hogyoku, even before
Kisuke Urahara had found it.
However, it failed.
I tried to find a way to
make the Hogyoku work.
I gouged out the souls of
hundreds of Soul Reapers
and hundreds of residents
of the Rukon District.
I chose those who possessed
latent Soul Reaper powers
and gave their energy to
the Hogyoku.
But even all those lives
weren't enough to satisfy it.
In looking at the results of
Kisuke Urahara's experiments,
I knew his Hogyoku wasn't
completed, either.
That's when I decided to
steal his Hogyoku, and
give it over to mine.
By doing that,
I gained something.
[Gin]
Evolution requires fear.
The fear that in one's
present state, one can die
and disappear at any moment.
Thank you, Gin.
Thanks to you, I have
finally evolved into a
being that transcends both
Hollows and Soul Reapers.
So what do you think
they're doing?!
Maybe the two of them
had a big falling out
and they killed each
other or something.
Yaaahh!!!
Hey! Who is that?!
Is it...?
Urk!
Hey Tatsuki?!
What's going on?!
[Rangiku]
Gin...!!
Gin!
Where did
you go, Gin?
Hey! Is that a Soul
Reaper uniform?
Where did you get that?
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to become
a Soul Reaper.
Huh?!
I'm going to become a Soul
Reaper, to change things.
[gasp]
I'll fix everything.
So you won't be crying anymore.
Gin!!
[Gin]
But in the end,
I failed.
I couldn't regain what was
taken from you, Rangiku.
[dying gasp]
I'm glad...
So long,
Rangiku.
Sorry 'bout that.
I'm glad I
apologized to you.
[anguished crying]
Thanks a lot, Dad.
Is that Ichigo?!
It really is him.
It's him!
Why does his hair
look so long?!
He looks different.
His hair's grown out.
And I swear, he looks
like he's taller!
That's good.
Yuzu and Karin seem okay.
Tatsuki. Keigo.
[Ichigo]
Mizuiro.
Chizuru.
Don Kanonji.
Heh heeh!
Imoyama.
Uh, no!
I'm Kurumadani Zennosuke!
Kurumadani-that's me!
If you can't remember
people's names,
at least be up
front with it!
Don't go naming
people based on who
you think they are!!!
[Ichigo]
Everyone just stay
where you are.
Stay still and don't move.
Huh?! What do you
mean by that?
What's up?
[tense gasp]
[Tatsuki]
I'm not feeling anything...
This isn't right...
[Tatsuki]
From this other guy, I can
feel his overwhelming power.
But from Ichigo,
I don't feel anything.
[Aizen]
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Are you really
Ichigo Kurosaki?
What exactly do you mean?
Well if you really are him,
I'd say you're disappointing.
I don't feel a thing.
You have no Spirit Energy.
Even if you're suppressing
your energy, I would still
be able to sense it.
You have failed to evolve.
You let the final chance
that I gave you slip away.
What a waste
of time.
For your own good,
You should go.
Huh?
[Gin]
I'm not interested
in you anymore.
[Gin]
Ahh!
I can see your eyes have
more power in them.
That's good.
You are at a level now...
[Gin]
Where I can die and
leave the rest to you.
Regrettable, for you.
Aizen.
Let's not do this here.
I'd rather we fought
somewhere else.
An impertinent
suggestion.
Only someone who has the
power to give me a real
challenge has the right
to make such a request.
There's no need to worry.
I will not destroy
Karakura Town.
You will--
Mmph!
What??!
How did he...! Impossible!
No one could've done this to me!
Now let's do this, Aizen.
I'll end this,
in an instant.
Now let's do this, Aizen.
I'll end this,
in an instant.
"End this in an instant?"!?
Now I see.
It's all become
quite clear to me.
I now know why I didn't
sense your energy.
You didn't lose your Spirit
energy. You discarded it.
I don't know how you did it, but
it seems you took all of your
Spirit energy and converted into
your body's physical strength.
Arm strength, leg strength,
your strong grip. The power
in your running and throwing.
So in exchange for this drastic
improvement of every one of
your physical abilities,
you chose to discard your
remaining Spirit energy.
You've given up fighting
against my Spirit energy
with your energy.
But, that won't help.
You will learn.
That new physical strength
you're counting on is
inferior compared to the
reaches of my own power.
You done?
You parried that well.
But you still must
be rather shocked.
The landscape changes with
a single slash of my sword.
My power is growing.
Honestly, I didn't actually
realize my abilities had
improved so much until you
decided to show up.
Thanks to you, I'm quite
happy right now. You see,
With you here, I can test my
powers that transcend those
of Hollows and Soul Reapers
to my heart's content.
Heh heh heh.
Wait! I'm not finished!
[Aizen]
Did you really think I wouldn't
be able to predict your moves?
Hah!
What an odd coincidence,
it seems we have both
reached a similar evolution,
which I see as the truest
form of the Zanpakuto.
Through introspection,
our right arms have
almost completely fused
with our Zanpakuto.
Heh.
What's so funny?
You know, I just realized
something while we clashed.
It's clear your evolution
and mine are at very
different levels.
If I so decide to, I have
the power to shatter your
Zanpakuto with one swing!
Impossible!
He caught it!?
I could understand
moving out of the way,
Although, with my sword
coming at him at such a
speed, he shouldn't even
be able to do that.
By just dodging my slash,
he would've eliminated the
risk of getting hurt.
But he chose to
do this instead!?
He caught it with
his bare hand!!
You look surprised.
Was it really such a
mind-blowing thing to you?
Yes, I did catch your sword.
Rrgh!
Does that scare you?
That something you can't
comprehend, happened
right before your eyes?
And you couldn't stop it?
He he he he he.
Hm?!
Very funny,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Something I can't
comprehend or stop,
you say?
Don't talk as though
you've already won
this fight.
What just happened was
simply a moment where your
physical strength
temporarily exceeded mine.
Miracles like that
do happen from
time to time.
But I'm a being
who surpasses even
the miraculous.
I will make sure that an anomaly
like that never happens again,
by crushing your
bones with Kido!
The oozing crest
of corruption!
The arrogant
vessel of madness!
Deny the seething urge to
let things Stun and Flicker!
Disrupt the sleep!
The crawling princess of iron!
The eternally self-destructing
doll of mud!
Unite! Repulse!
Fill the earth,
and know your own
powerlessness!!
Hado Number 90:
Kurohitsugi!
A full incantation Kurohitsugi
performed by one who transcends
both Hollow and Soul Reaper!
Its power unleashes enough
gravity to warp time and space!
The likes of which you could
never even comprehend!
Perish! Ichigo Kurosaki!!
You still haven't
realized it, have you?
The power I have is greater
than the power you possess,
even right now.
That huge force
that erased that
entire mountain,
That was my sword.
[big gasp]
Now its my turn, Aizen.
[Aizen]
All Humans are an
imitation of apes.
All Gods are an
imitation of Humans.