Ah!
The person who
attacked Ishida,
would be me.
[gasp]
Ichigo!
Hnh?
What's the matter, Chad?
It's Orihime!
She's in danger!
[gasp]
[Shukuro]
Relax.
I have no intention of
doing anything to you yet.
I'll be heading home for today, right
after I punish this disobedient boy.
Gahh!
I see. It's true. You're as
kind-hearted as I heard you were.
You can't even bear to see
an enemy get hurt, can you?
That's not what I'm doing.
If you're really the
one who attacked Uryu,
Then I'm not going
to let you get away!
Interesting.
Who're you calling?
Who d'ya think?
Orihime!
I don't think
that's a good idea!
Huh?!
If your call distracts
her, even for a second,
it might leave her
open for an attack!
You think it's
that bad?!
I'm not
sure.
I know her spiritual
pressure is being strained!
So are we closing
in on them?
My Spiritual pressure perception
says we're on the right track.
But I'm not having any luck pinning
down their exact location.
Okay! If you've got the direction
right, I think I know where she is.
[Ichigo]
If we keep heading this way,
We'll be right at
her apartment!
Hmm.
So if I'm the one who attacked Ishida,
you won't allow me to get away, huh?
So predictable.
And quite overused.
That will never make
it into any book.
Whoa! Hey!
What do you think
you're doing?!
Mr. Tsukishima is
gonna kill you!
I mean it!
He's super serious!
You won't get off with a spanking
from him or just a beating! He'll---!
Please be quiet.
I know what I'm doing,
but I'm not protecting you.
Sushi-gawara.
It's Shishi-gawara.
I have to focus. There's no telling
what his next move will be.
He's already
drawn his sword.
So maybe I should
use Santenkesshun.
But that might appear like
I'm provoking him to attack.
At this point, is there some
other way I can stop him?
Hey stop!
Santenkesshun!
[gasp]
What's her
apartment number?
It's four-oh-three!
This way!
[Ichigo]
Orihime!
What happened?!
Are you okay?!
[Ichigo]
Orihime!
[stunned breath]
I'm not cut or bleeding!?
That can't be!
I definitely felt that blade
cutting deep into my body!
[Ichigo]
Orihime!
Wha!?
Ichigo?!
And Chad too?
Why are you guys here?
Uh, we were worried!
Chad thought, there was something
wrong with your Spiritual Pressure.
Yeah. You okay?
There was a dip in your
Spiritual Pressure.
Can you tell us exactly
what happened to you?
Me?! Nothing much really.
[chuckle] Just school
and some homework.
I did have this tummy ache. That's why
I was bent over. That must've been it.
That couldn't
have been it.
There was another Spiritual
Pressure here until a minute ago.
Whose was it?
Oh you're right.
My friend was here.
I forgot, I met this
friend of mine here.
"A friend"?
That's right.
Tsukishima.
After my friend left, my stomach began
aching for some reason. That's all it was.
Wait a minute.
Why am I calling him my friend?
Sorry If I had
you two worried!
That can't be. He said he's
the one who attacked Uryu.
Well, I'll be sure to tell
you if anything happens!
And you guys be sure to let me know
if anything happens to you, okay?
Uh... Sure.
[chuckle]
I can't let Ichigo
know the truth!
[Ichigo]
Well then, we'll see ya later.
[Orihime]
Okay! See you tomorrow!
[chuckle]
That was strange.
For a moment there,
I thought he was my friend.
Why did I think that?
What was it in me,
that he cut?
So, what do you
think of her story?
Well.
I'm not sure.
Orihime has no idea that Ichigo's
getting his powers back.
She probably worried about
him getting dragged into a fight because of her.
One thing's for sure, she doesn't want
Ichigo to know the danger she's in.
She said there was nothing wrong, so I
guess we should believe her, right?
[Chad] I do agree with her that
having Ichigo get into a fight
in his present condition,
would be way
too risky.
I need to get in touch
with her again later.
I must've just perceived her
Spiritual Pressure wrong.
Sorry about that.
Sure, no worries.
Another.
Not for you.
Mmm?
And why the hell not?
You've had enough.
Please control yourself.
Just what're you saying?
I realize you're happy that things are
going well with Mr. Ichigo, but...
What? It's not like that. C'mon.
Huh?
Hey Riruka!
Come on wake up!
Why don't you go
home already?!
Hey!Don'tignore
me,damnit!
Psh.
Mh.
Oh I forgot! Hey this thing's empty!
One more! C'mon buddy!
You are done.
I am not done! What's one more?
I'm still thirsty here!
[Giriko]
You are beyond thirsty.
[Kugo]
YOU'RE beyond thirsty!
Oh come on. I am sotally tober!
One more won't kill me!
[Giriko]
That's enough.
Kugo. the phone.
It's your line.
Hmm?
Who is this?
Hm?! All right.
I'll open up now.
Chad and Orihime aren't
telling me anything,
but something
definitely happened.
It was probably the same
guy who attacked Uryu.
Kugo. You think it's?
Tsukishima.
It's most likely him.
So then you do
know this guy?
Tsukishima is a
Fullbringer, just like us.
You see...
He used to be one
of our members.
[gasp]
[doorbell]
[Ikumi]
I'm coming!
Who's there?
It's late ya know.
Gaagh!
Hunh?
Damn that hurt!
I've warned you before that your
door opens towards the stairs!
Open it slowly or
you'll kill someone!
How many times do--
Ichigo!
Where have you
been for so long?!
Were you taking time off
again without calling me!?
Hrmf.
Come on in!
I'll hear your
excuse over tea!
No thanks.
Don't want any.
Huh?
But why not?
[Ikumi]
Say what?!
You want more time off?!
Have you lost your mind?!
Come on! You've already taken
all this time off already!
So just how much work are you
thinking of skipping out on?!
Are you even listening?!
I'm sorry.
Hnh?
But, I thought
you should know.
Wait! We're not
done here yet!
Hold on!
Listen to me. I don't know
what's going on with you,
But stop worrying
about me, okay?
Huh?
I'm not one of
your classmates!
I'm an adult!
I'm all grown up.
So I'm old enough to
take care of myself.
There's no need for a kid
like you to feel worried.
So if something's bothering you,
just spit it out and tell me!
Ya got that? Know if you need
to talk I'm here for you.
[Ichigo]
Thank you, Ms. Ikumi.
Tsukishima,
was the original
founder of our group.
We all came together
under a common goal:
To discard our Fullbring powers
and become normal humans.
Tsukishima was the one who discovered a way to
transfer our powers to a Substitute Soul Reaper.
Naturally, he
became our leader.
Things were going well.
After years of searching, we finally
found a Substitute Soul Reaper
who agreed to absorb the powers of
several of our members. But then,
Tsukishima suddenly
had a change of heart.
He killed the Substitute
Soul Reaper and every on ewho
had given him their powers.
After that, he disappeared
without a trace.
It seemed,
He'd gone mad.
But perhaps he'd been planning
his murderous exit all along.
I need to show you something.
Hm?
[gasp]
This was that Substitute
Soul Reaper's Combat Pass.
I don't know what Tsukishima's
real intentions are.
He's always been quite good at
keeping his thoughts to himself.
And like I said, we haven't
seen him since that incident.
But for right now, I'm betting
there's one thing we can count on.
Based on the past, Tsukishima
will do anything to keep
us from succeeding with another
Substitute Soul Reaper.
[gasp]
All of his latest actions
support this theory.
He attacked Uryu Ishida, Then
made contact with Orihime Inoue.
He knows what he's doing.
He's managed to get your attention now,
by threatening your friends and family.
[beginning to seethe]
Ginjo.
I have to do something.
Stay calm,
we can't rush in.
We know he's definitely making some
serious moves. So we'll speed things up.
Your next training session
will happen very soon.
We'll contact you
when we're ready.
So go home for now,
try to get some rest.
Huh?
Dad?
Hm?!
[Kisuke]
Something wrong?
No. it's nothing.
But let's go.
Go somewhere else?
Yeah, just in case.
Hm.
I gotcha.
Let's do that.
[Ichigo]
Wait.
[Ichigo] So many things happened all at
once, that I had forgotten what he said.
Just how much do you
know about your buddy?
What makes you think
you understand Urahara?
Should I go after him
right now and ask him?
No, now's not good. What if
Kisuke really is my enemy?
I don't have enough power
to do anything against him.
I gotta get my powers back
as soon as possible!
[Orihime]
Whoaaa!
[clattering]
Eeyah... he he he he...
What was that noise?
Oh...
It's nothing, really.
I'm fine.
I just dropped some dishes.
I see.
Anyway, that's what happened?
Uh-huh.
I'm sure I got cut.
But then when I came to,
There wasn't any blood
or any kind of wound.
And both of the guys who were
there with me had disappeared.
And when I saw that both you and Ichigo
had showed up to see if I was okay,
I don't know why,
but for a second there,
I thought of that
person as a "friend".
Hm? What do you
mean by that?
Sorry. I don't understand what
I'm trying to say either.
But I was overcome with this feeling
that this stranger was my friend.
It's not like I mistook him for someone
else, I mean after all, he attacked me.
But how should I put it?
It felt like when I
thought about the past,
It suddenly seemed like I knew
who he was, it was weird.
Be careful, Chad.
I have a feeling his powers are
more terrifying than they seem.
Thanks. I will.
You said there were
two guys there, right?
Huh? Right.
Do you remember their names?
Either one of them?
Yeah, I think it was
Tsukishima, and Sushigawara.
Aahh-choo!
O-oh...
May I continue with our
topic, Shishigawara?
Uhh yes, sir!
Good.
As far as this matter is concerned, you
do not need to do anything further.
But sir! As your apprentice, don't you
feel that I should be taking every--?
Will you please stop calling
yourself my apprentice?
Oh! Sorry sir!
But as your super
loyal apprentice!
I don't think it's proper for
someone who should be helping,
to just watch quietly as
you do all the work, sir.
[frustrated]
By "this matter," I specifically
meant Orihime Inoue.
Huh?
Oh.
I've left a mark on her.
No further contact will
be necessary. Understood?
Uh! Right.
Hm.
Now, who should
I go after next?
Yasutora Sado?
Or Ichigo Kurosaki?
Think I'll go after
Ichigo immediately.
I wonder what Ginjo
will think of that.
[Orihime] So Chad, about
that Sushigawara.
[Chad] Yes, tell me about
this Sushi-gawara guy...
[stomach growl]
[Orihime] Sorry! Talking about Sushigawara
has got me wanting to go eat some sushi.
[stomach growl]
[Chad]
Yeah, me too!
[Moeh]
[Sneeze]