Forcing a girl down
to the ground...
I wouldn't call that
move "good manners".
Oh?
Uryu!
You never learn, do you?
Always getting yourself
into trouble.
Your master's not
going to be happy.
Shut up uryu!
Ichigo is not
my mast--!
[Inaba]
Hado Number Four: Byakura!
A Hirenkyaku...
Well then, you
must be a Quincy.
You seem to be quite
interested in us.
Actually, I have no
interest in you.
But I don't want you
bringing trouble into
this town, either.
Leave, now.
Then I won't have
to take action.
[Inaba]
I don't want this skirmish
turning into an incident either,
young Quincy.
But if you choose to
stand in our way,
you will leave me no other
choice but to consider you
an "enemy" that needs
to be eliminated.
I didn't come here
to get in your way.
But you see,
It's becoming obvious,
from where I stand,
you are the enemy.
As you wish.
I'll deal with you personally.
[Rukia]
So what now, Ichigo?
[Ichigo]
Isn't it obvious?
We have to return to the
World of the Living.
Be serious! This isn't the
Seireitei as we know it!
As far as you and
I are concerned,
we're surrounded
by the enemy!
[Rukia]
You really think we can just
slip right though the Senkaimon?
By now, the Reigai must
have blockaded it to
prevent our escape.
It's too risky.
Egh. Okay, so what
do you suggest?
I don't know...
[Yoruichi]
I have a plan.
[gasps]
Yoruichi!
You made it!
Do you really think that
those half-brained soldiers
could keep up with me?
I bet that they're still
trying to figure out how
they lost track of me!
Glad to see
you're okay.
Me too, but I still think
they're gonna keep a tight
guard on the Senkaimon.
I agree.
Which is why we'll bust
through the gate head on.
[Ichigo]
Do what?!
[Rukia]
Breaking through will
be nearly impossible!
They may be fakes, but you
said those Reigai possess
powers equal to or greater
than the captains!
We're going to break through
BECAUSE they're fakes!
Uhh?
Huh?
Ah! Now I see.
This attack of yours
weakens the bonds of
my Reishi,
allowing them to be converted
into your own energy.
You're very astute.
And your appearance
reminds me of someone.
Your demeanor is quite
similar to that of a
scientist I despise.
Are you referring to
Captain Kurotsuchi?
He is my superior
officer actually.
I thought so.
That must be why
you knew about my
Seeleschneider.
No, this is the first
time I've seen it.
The first time!?
I am quite capable of
analyzing my opponents'
skill and strength
on the spot.
You see unlike Mayuri,
I consider myself a true
"dispassionate scientist".
Unfortunately, that
technique of yours doesn't
have nearly enough speed
to have even the remotest
possibility of getting me.
Oddly enough,
I'm aware of that.
[gasp]
Hyaagh!
It's really simple.
It's obvious that the speed
of Ginreikojaku wouldn't
be able to catch you.
But it turns out all I needed
to do was to increase the
speed of my Hirenkyaku.
It sounded like you're not
very fond of that scientist
we were discussing.
What a shame.
If we weren't enemies,
we might've gotten along.
[Inaba] [Echoed]
I think not!
What?! Where'd he go?!
[gasp]
Me, despise Captain Kurotsuchi?
Nothing could be further
from the truth.
But... your wound?!
He is a wonderful
superior officer.
The Captain does have
"sharp elbows" in his
dealings with others,
but I respect him.
And yet, I know I
am superior to him
in all respects.
Really, that's all
there is to it.
Wha?! So what are
you getting at?!
Go mad...Raiku.
That's really
not necessary.
I have no intention of
giving you the time to
figure out my power.
Can't be. Not from
that distance.
I never even
saw you coming.
We're here.
So they've come!
Hey! Now there's even
more of them down there!
Hm. This won't be
so easy after all.
They can only hold the
Precipice World boundary wall
for a short period of time.
So just focus
on running.
We've gotta get past
them to make it through
to the Precipice World.
Let's go!
Looks like they're charging in!
All we need to do is
keep them from making it
through the Senkaimon.
But first, let's
slow them down!
What's the
matter Rukia!?
Rukia!
Eeeyah!
You need ta stop
looking around!
Damn!
Damn it!
Raaagh!
Hyoryusenbi!
What the hell?!
They just exploded!
What just
happened!?
[Ichigo]
Getsugatensho!
Ichigo, you idiot!
Why'd you let your
decoy pop so early?!
Remember our plan?
We were supposed to do
it at the same time!
Hey I couldn't help it, okay?!
That device wasn't exactly
easy to activate!
Damn that Kisuke.
Why can't he ever
invent something that's
easy to operate?
Keep going right
through the Senkaimon!
Agh!
Yoruichi!
[Rukia]
Brother!
Did you really think I'd
be oblivious to what you
were thinking of doing?
Heh heh.
H'augh!
Did you really think I'd
be oblivious to what you
were thinking of doing?
You mean to
sacrifice yourself?!
If I do, what of it?!!
[Ichigo]
Yoruichi! Whaddya
think you're doing?!
Go! I'm not going to
get killed by the
likes of these losers!
But what about--?
Get going Ichigo!
Go protect the World
of the Living.
[little gasp]
All right.
Stop them!
None of you are
getting past me!
Shunko!
Uugh!
Uaah!
Looks like our
plan worked out.
All of you Reigai were
originally created as
an experiment for the
purpose of doing battle.
Your personalities and strength
levels might be near perfect
copies of the real Soul Reapers,
but you are a bit
more aggressive.
And since that's your natural
tendency, you won't hesitate
to attack Ichigo, Rukia or me,
whenever you can.
That's why those decoys
gave us the diversion we
needed to get past you.
If those had been your real
counterparts attacking us,
they may have noticed the
difference and our plan
probably wouldn't have been
nearly as effective.
But it's too late.
And I won't let you
go after Ichigo either.
Is that so? Then we'll just
have to do away with you first.
Impressive. You may be a fake,
but you have real power.
[Inaba]
Lieutenant Kira,
Lieutenant Ise.
Thank you for being
so patient with me.
We shall go after I
eliminate this Mod Soul.
[gasp]
[struggling]
Dgh! Grrh!
Allow me to put you
out of your misery.
Ah. I'm surprised that
you're still alive.
His movements. It's not just
an issue of him simply being
able to move fast.
It was as though when he made
a move, that movement was
somehow "cut out" of time.
It seems I've been
toying with you and for
that I'm deeply sorry.
So then, let's end this.
Hado Number Four:
Byakurai.
Oh?
Hyaaah!
Uryu!
Orihime quick,
heal Uryu's wounds!
But!
I'll do what I can to give
you a little more time.
You, "give her time"?
Oh no.
Augh!
From the way you talk, it
sounds like you believe you
can somehow control time.
Oh no!
Now then, shall we
put an end to them?
I've wasted too much time.
Let's finish this.
[Orihime]
Ichigo!
You all right, Orihime?
Rukia!
[Orihime]
I'm fine, but Uryu and
Chad are pretty beat up.
Ichigo Kurosaki.
[Yoruichi]
You may only be Reigai,
but you're supposed to
be Squad Captains.
Is that really the best you
can do against just me?
How pathetic!
Do you truly understand
the situation you're in?
If you don't,
then I'll show you.
Scatter, Senbonzakura.
Your refusal to accept defeat
is exactly like a real captain!
[Inaba]
So you actually made
it back through.
That was quite
unexpected.
Who are you?
Oh I see. So it was
Yoriuchi Shihoin,
wasn't it?
Hey! Didn't you hear me?!
Why of course!
If you had her helping,
it makes it much easier
to comprehend how you
could escape.
After all she probably gave up
her life, just to save you.
I said who the
hell are you?!
Now now, just calm down.
I am Kageroza Inaba.
I study the Precipice World
in the Department of
Research and Development.
You study the
Precipice World?!
Then you must be the
one responsible for
the disappearances!
And the one controlling
those Reigai!
[Inaba]
Ohh!
You even know
about my Reigai?
How intriguing!
What's intriguing!?
I've been immersed in
my research for years.
As a result of my solitary
existence, I haven't paid
much attention to the
affairs of others.
So I'm quite surprised
at this turn of events.
Enough of your
long-winded explanation!
Oh?
I really couldn't care less
about your stupid reasons
for everything you've done.
You got that?
But since you've
decided to hurt my friends,
I'm gonna take you out!
Not very patient, are you?
No matter, it saves
me time if we want to
get this over with!
What's with his
Spirit Energy?!
Hyaaaaaaah!
Because I respect your strength
and how it allowed you to
defeat Aizen, I will not use
any cheap tricks against you.
But honestly, is this
all the power you
possess right now?
[Ichigo]
What...?!
Don't hold back. You still
have a last resort, don't you?
Substitute Soul Reaper.
Heh! Listen to you
sounding all high
and mighty!
I would've used it even
without you asking!
[Rukia]
Hold it! Ichigo!
Here goes.
Hyyyah!
Damn it! My Spirit
Energy is unstable.
I've got to finish this fast!
[Ichigo]
Getsuga!
Tensho!
Haaaaaa!!
What??!
So, was that your best?
Hmm heh heh heh heh.
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
Ichigo's definitely holding back
his strength as much as he can,
because he's afraid of
losing his Spirit Energy.
But even so, Kageroza was
able to snuff out Ichigo's
Getsugatensho so easily.
These Reigai still possess
the fierce pride of their
original counterparts.
So the fact that this man can
command those proud warriors,
shows that his powers are even
greater than we imagined!
Substitute Soul Reaper,
it certainly appears that
I have overestimated
your power level.
Or is it, that your Spirit
Energy has diminished more
than I predicted it would?
Shut up!
Sadly, in your
present state,
As a scientist, I no longer
have any interest in you!
Huaarghh!
Ichigo!
[Inaba]
This is perfect.
You two may prove
to be an obstacle
in my future plans.
Therefore, I'll eliminate
you right here!
Hey Ichigo! Kinda looks
like you two could
really use a hand here!
[Ichigo]
Renji?!
Rgh!
[Nanao]
[shriek]
Huh?
Huh??
Let that girl go!
Rrgh!
That girl is mine!
This is not what
I expected!
Brother, it's you!
Byakuya!
Looks like he really
worked you over,
didn't he Ichigo?
Shut up!
So I'm guessing you guys
are the real deal, huh?
Yer damn right we are!
But so how did
you two...?
Oh it's not just us.
Hey! It's them!
The originals.
For a petty underling, this
was some stunt you pulled.
It actually
surprised me.
Why Captain Kurotsuchi!
I honestly wasn't
expecting to see you
to arrive so soon.
You were tardy in your
report to me of the problems
in the Precipice World.
And because of your
laziness, I ended up
having to go and help
all these people I really
never had any intention
of wanting to help.
For this thankless job,
I will make you pay!
A million times over!
Surely you jest. You seem to
think you've won but I assure
you, you are mistaken.
But for tonight,
I will retreat.
Damn you! Wait!
[Renji]
Ichigo! Don't.
Why not?!
The Precipice World
has now become his
personal domain.
To enter there without a plan,
you'd have to be more of a fool
than I can imagine.
Go ahead. If you wish to
die by committing such an
irrational act, I won't
be the one to stop you.
It would be quite a fitting
death for someone like you.
Bite me.
Once I return and I
have retrieved Nozomi,
Then I will be able to
completely show all of
you my true power.
Your true power?
[Inaba]
Yes. When that occurs, not
only the Soul Society but also
the World of the Living,
will be forced to exist
under my control.
So keep in mind, all you
Originals and you too,
Substitute Soul Reaper.
Someday quite soon,
we will meet again.
That will not happen!
You will never control us!
[Nanao]
We weren't expecting that
much interference.
[Inaba]
That really couldn't be helped.
Not everything has the
outcome that one expects.
That is science.
Besides, I assumed that it
would be nearly impossible to
confine Captain Kurotsuchi
in the Precipice World for
an extended period of time.
[Izuru]
Everyone is here, sir.
We will get Nozomi back.
With our invading army!
[Renji]
Captain Kuchiki, is there
anything you need during our
stay in the World of the Living?
[Kuchiki]
I will need a place to reside.
[Renji]
Yes, sir!
[Kuchiki]
A formal garden by a lake,
with seven rooms is the
minimum I'll accept.
[Renji]
Uh... Captain!?
[Kuchiki]
And about five
or six servants.
[Renji]
How am I supposed to
make that happen?!