The Zanpakuto. Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined
by its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper and
dies with its Soul
Reaper.
That is the existence of
a Zanpakuto.
How about Ichigo? Can
we save him?!
I don't know. The fact
is, we can't take the
chance of getting near
that thing,
so we're stuck leaving
it up to Ichigo to save
himself.
That's awful!
Ichigo!
Ichigo.
Please be okay.
Where am I?
Ichigo Kurosaki...
I'm surprised
to see you.
How did you get here?!
I don't know. Where
the hell are we?
Can't you tell?
Just as your precious
Zanpakuto has a home in
the world that is your
mind,
I also had a place
to call my own.
Then... this is...
But Koga's dead!
I don't understand
it myself.
How did I end
up in this place?
Did my reunion with Koga
somehow summon me here?
Or is this whole thing a
figment of imagination?
In either case, this
place will soon fall
apart.
But no matter what, I am
eternally grateful to the
destiny that connects you
and I.
For that destiny will
allow me to finish our
battle!
But why?!
There's no longer any
reason for us to keep
fighting each other!
Don't you see? The
power you possess will
nourish me, Ichigo.
And until I obtain that
power, I will never stop
fighting you. Understand?
Not gonna happen!
Nice try.
Not gonna let
you use that!
Not this time!
What?!
It's useless.
Flailing your sword around
like an idiot won't be
enough to protect you
from my onslaught.
No... damn it...
can't move.
Goodbye, Ichigo.
[laughing]
Huh?
What?! I can move!
Getsugatensho!
I figured it out! Your
technique isn't invisible.
You make your enemies
think there's some kind
of invisible force at work.
But I saw the image of
your attack reflected
in the water.
And...
That was the answer. It
turns out the real power's
contained in the reflected
image.
Which means--
If it can't reflect on
the water, then you can't
use your technique!
You're mine now!
Indeed, I cannot utilize
my technique to its fullest
extent right now...
But you should know
that's not the only
ability I possess.
I had you placed under my
spell the moment we faced
each other in battle.
How do I...
beat him?
Ichigo.
Feel it.
Zangetsu!
His power of suggestion
does not work on me. I
will become your eyes.
But, it is impossible for
this to work unless you
and I...
Zanpakuto and master...
are truly connected to
one another.
Okay, Zangetsu.
You're going to try
again?
Get ready.
How did he see me!?
Getsuga...
... tensho!
I see. So you have your
Zangetsu by your side
once again.
Now I understand what he
was trying to say.
What?!
Recognizing and accepting
each other's existence...
That's the foundation of
the relationship between
a Zanpakuto and a Soul
Reaper.
But I bet you already
knew that.
What do you know about
anything!?
Why won't you just
accept it!?
Ichigo. We must
leave this place.
There is a maelstrom of
deep-seated anger here.
Driven by the Hollows
that Muramasa consumed
for all those years.
And at any moment, they
will rise up and destroy
him.
We don't have much
time, Ichigo!
I know.
His voice never
reached me.
Muramasa!
Ichigo, get out of here!
If you stay, you will be
trapped forever.
Muramasa! Why can't
you just let this go?
It's none of
your business!
Come on, he told you that
he didn't need you anymore.
So just give up, already!
Koga's abilities were
so immense that he could
rule over the entire Soul
Society.
I was always
so proud of that.
He possessed amazing
power!!
That's why I
will never stop!
What the hell is
wrong with you?!
What about your whole
mission to free the
Zanpakuto from captivity?!
You'll believe almost
anything, won't you?
That was all just a phony
ploy to trick you idiots!
Is that the truth!?
You even told us you
killed your master!
But when it comes right
down to it, your master
never saw you as anything
but his weapon!
You knew that. But you
still struggled to exist,
all for the sake of
freeing Koga from
his seal!
Face it. You did all that
because you wanted Koga to
appreciate you just once!
It was a lofty goal.
It wouldn't have
lasted long.
Hey!
Ichigo. Time
is running out.
If he becomes a Hollow,
the pockets of Reishi in
the World of the Living
would become dangerously
unbalanced. And Karakura
Town could be destroyed.
Don't worry, he won't
become a Hollow.
Muramasa!
My Zanpakuto and I...
we're gonna be together
to the end!
And not only me. All my
friends, and even the
captains.
To Soul Reaper and
Zanpakuto alike, they're
each special and irreplaceable
to one another!
You knew that better than
anyone else.
So how could you betray
the honor you once fought
for?!
You have no right to
stand there and judge me!
I knew what I was doing
all along!
Taking what you want
when you want it isn't the
way to treat a Zanpakuto.
The Zanpakuto should have
free will, just like the
Soul Reaper!!
Well, it appears my
time has finally come.
Ichigo...
I know. Let's
end this!
Hyorinmaru!
Captain!
That was the last of
them!
Yes.
What's going on?
What now?!
Muramasa... Muramasa!
Muramasa!!!
How ironic. After all
this, it's your voice
that reaches me.
What happened?
I don't know why, but
the Hollows' Spiritual
Pressure is all gone.
Then Karakura Town is
safe now?
Ichigo...
What?
That's definitely his
Spiritual Pressure!
This feeling... is this
what you've been trying to
explain to me all along?
Yeah.
I see. I wound up making
quite a mess of Koga,
didn't I?
Everyone makes mistakes.
That means that someday
you'll fix it.
I hope... someday.
Ichigo.
Is everyone all right?
Yes, we're safe.
Is Muramasa really gone
for good?
Yeah.
And he kept his pride as
a Zanpakuto until the
very end.
Byakuya?
You okay?
Rain?
What is this?
I dunno. It
feels strange.
Let's go home.
Good to have you.
Welcome home.
Let's go.
Wha?
What? Hold on!
They're gone.
Yes. Well, it's
about time.
Ichigo Kurosaki.
This is the second time I
am thanking you.
I appreciate your help.
Sure.
Uh-oh, I better get back
to Las Noches fast!
Huh? Sure is quiet around
here.
What's going on?
Ichigo Kurosaki.
Looks like no one updated
you on what happens next.
Ulquiorra?!
Oh no, not this again!