[MUSIC - BEAT CRUSADERS,
"TONIGHT, TONIGHT, TONIGHT"]
-Try to hang on.
-[groans]
-[gasp]
-[gasp] Noba.
[gasping]
-You've all been
very entertaining,
but I'm afraid you're
about 100 years too early.
I won't be sealed away yet.
[gasping]
-I think it's time
we brought this fight
to its natural conclusion.
[laughs]
-[laughs]
-[gasp]
-Come, Baura.
BAURA: Understood.
-We've got to hurry!
NOBA: It's no good.
-Noba.
-Over here!
-Damn it.
-He's not planning
on letting us go.
I could try Shunpo,
but my spiritual
is limited here in
World of the Living.
I doubt we'd make it very far.
Flying's out of the question.
It would be too difficult
carrying the two of them.
I've got to think of something.
-Rangiku, there's no
need for you to die, too.
Leave us, and get out
here while you still can.
We'll act as decoys
and draw his attention.
You shouldn't have any
problem getting away from here
on your own.
-I could never do
something like that.
Stop talking nonsense, and
start thinking of a way
to get all of us
out of this mess.
-[gasp]
-We'll have to wait for
him to attack, and then
use my Shunpo to run as
far away as possible.
-You got it.
-[gasp]
-Fooled you! [laughs]
-It didn't work!
-[together] Noba!
-I can't believe
you pulled that off.
NOBA: No problem.
-It looks like we bought
ourselves a few minutes.
But it's only a matter of time
before he catches up to us.
I sense clashes and spiritual
pressure somewhere across town.
It's probably Shuhei
and the others.
It seems like we keep moving
further and further away
from them.
They've been successful in
separating us from each other.
Noba's too weak now.
e could never neutralize
the doll's power
like he did before.
-I'm going to immobilize that
doll and capture it myself.
And then I'm going to
make it cough up Ururu.
-It's not as simple as that.
Without Noba, we
wouldn't have any idea
when or where it
was going to attack.
Even then, we barely
have time to dodge it.
It's impossible to
mount a counterattack
in that brief instant.
We won't be able to
do any real damage
by just attacking
with sheer force.
-If I knew when and
where it was coming from,
then I would be
able to concentrate
my attack on his belly.
That's where the
scales look thinner.
-It's possible, but it would
mean using a decoy again.
And we should pick the
battleground, not him.
At any rate, it's dangerous
for us to stay here.
We need to get moving.
-Right.
Noba, I think we should
leave your Gigai here.
-His Gigai?
-Yes.
Noba is a Mod-Soul
created to assist us
in fighting the Bounts.
The body he's using is a
Gigai created by Uruhara.
-So that's the
reason why he could
tell where the Bounts
were going to appear.
-Rangiku, I want you to
take out Noba's Soul Candy.
As a Soul Reaper, you
can do that, right?
-Chad, that's not necessary.
As long as a Mod-Soul's capsule
remains intact, he cannot die.
Mine is still fine.
-But still.
-We don't have to
leave my Gigai.
I still have enough
strength to teleport
between dimensions
with this body.
-Noba.
RANGIKU: It might work.
We might just be able to
pull this off after all.
What if we tried
to combine my Kido
with Noba's
Bount-tracking power?
We might just be able
to hook that big fish.
-Is that possible?
RANGIKU: Yes, but
it would probably
use up the rest of
our spiritual power.
If we fail, then we're done.
-What do I do?
-Noba.
-Uruhara created us
for the sole purpose
of defeating the Bounts.
Far too many innocent
souls have already
fallen victim to their greed.
I'll do whatever it takes.
-All right.
-We've got one chance.
Noba and I will have to
use Kido to draw him out.
We won't be able to
move during that time,
so you'll have to attack him.
You can take him out
with that same attack
you used to surprise
Captain Kyoraku that time.
-They've lived far too long.
Though I'm sure they're
planning something right now.
[laughs] They should be
planning their funeral.
Go, Baura.
RANGIKU: This should do.
CHAD: Yeah.
-Are you ready?
-Mm.
-[grunt]
-Noba.
-You must link your
spiritual pressure with mine.
All right.
Here we go.
-Noba, Rangiku.
[grunting]
CHAD: What's happening?
Do you think it's going to work?
Are you--
--[gasp] Hearts of the south
and eyes of the north.
Fingertips of the
West, heel of the east.
Gather together the wind
and scatter the rain.
Bakudo 58, Kakushitsuijaku!
57, 89, 85, 103, 122,
136, 184, 190, 202.
-Rangiku.
-Why can't I found him?
Is Bount spiritual pressure
different from ours?
[grunting]
-I see him.
It's working!
I don't think he knows
we're tracking him.
-He's coming.
-Which way?
Where is he coming from?
CHAD (VOICEOVER):
They've done their part.
Now it's time for me to do mine.
-[gasp] Above us!
-[gasp]
-They won't be expecting
an attack from here.
[gasp] How did they
know where I was.
-Heh.
-[shout]
[groaning]
-It's Ururu.
-Oh, it looks like
I'm back, aren't I?
-Ururu!
-[laughs] Snot-nosed brats.
I've had enough of this
foolishness for one day.
We'll finish this another time.
[laughs]
-Good.
I've had enough of
your crap anyway.
SAWATARI: Baura.
BAURA: Yes.
-[gasp]
We let them escape.
You had the perfect
shot back there,
but you chose not
to finish him off.
If you had used your
full power, there's
no way he would have survived.
-But then Ururu would
have died as well.
RANGIKU: I figured that's
what you were doing.
Looks like you made
the right decision.
-[groan]
-[gasp]
-Chad.
MAYURI: Yes!
I've done it!
I've finally recovered
the Bount data.
Whoever it was thought
they could hide it from me.
But they had no idea who
they were dealing with.
This material in these files
is absolutely fascinating.
I never knew the Bounts had
concealed such a secret.
I wonder if I can get
my hands on a Bount
to conduct a little research.
It would be simplest to go
to the World of the Living
and deal with this myself.
But I don't have
time for that now.
And I would imagine
the Soul Reapers
who've gone to the
World of the Living
to watch the Bounts
are too busy to help.
There must be a solution
to this problem.
Huh?
What's this?
[laugh] Well now, I'm
beginning understand
why the Bounts are
so anxious to get
their hands on a Quincy,
someone with the ability
to isolate Reishi
and disburse them,
converting that spirit
energy into power.
There's only one
who can do that.
Nemu?
-Yes, Master Mayuri?
-Go fetch Research
Material Q141 and take it
to the World of the
Living right now.
-Yes, Master Mayuri.
That's Q141, correct?
-I'll be anxious to see
what he does with it.
[laughs]
-Damn it.
Why do I have to get stuck
out here in the boondocks
guarding this godforsaken hole?
-Uh, because Captain
Zaraki ordered you to?
Shut up, you idiot.
I know that.
[murmuring]
MAN: What was that?
MAN: What happened to the gate?
-Someone's there.
Quit sneaking around
like some kind of coward!
Come out and show your face!
MEN: Where is he?
Over there!
I think he's behind the bricks.
-Go report this to the captain!
MAN (ON PA):
Attention, attention.
There is an intruder
in the Seireitei.
All companies report to
their defensive posts.
Repeat, this is an emergency.
There is an intruder
in the Seireitei.
IKKAKU (VOICEOVER): He's here.
I can feel it.
Someone is definitely
running in front of me.
So why can't I feel
any spiritual pressure?
-I got you!
Extend, Hozukimaru!
You only want to attack me
when you're invisible, huh?
Well, bring it on!
IKKAKU (VOICEOVER): He's
completely masked his presence.
Move.
Move, damn it!
Because as soon as you
do, I'm going to nail you.
-Gotcha!
[panting]
RIKICHI: Captain Kuchiki!
I'm sorry to disturb you.
-What's all the commotion about?
Is there an intruder?
-Well, we haven't received
all the details yet.
But, sir--
-What is it?
-A Stealth Force officer just
delivered this secret letter
from Head Captain
Genryusai Yamamoto.
And it's addressed to you.
-From Head Captain Yamamoto?
And the moon was so
beautiful tonight.
Such a pity.
-I'm sorry, Captain.
I let him get away.
-Don't worry about it.
-What?
-I don't know who it was,
but he's not much of a man
if he has to hide his spiritual
pressure while pulling crap
like this.
It's been a little boring
around here lately, though.
This could turn out to be
an interesting diversion.
[laughs]
-It's just I can't
see the Hollows.
[cries] And-- and the
ones that they attack.
Sensei.
-Hm?
URYU: I want to become strong.
I'm want to become strong.
I want to be a powerful
Quincy and protect everyone
from the Hollows.
SENSEI: Release the
tension in your shoulders.
Trust your body to
show you the fog.
-Yes, sir.
-Now maintain it and draw
the arrow straight back.
It must be a straight line.
And you release your hand.
You don't shoot the
arrow, simply release.
These are the building
blocks to all of your powers.
Perfect them with practice.
-But it's so difficult.
-A Quincy's arrow
is only released
for those you want to protect.
-Those I want to protect?
-In time, you will
understand what I mean.
URYU (VOICEOVER): Those
I want to protect.
SENSEI: Uryu, watch closely.
Once you master the basics
I've just taught you,
the rest is simple.
Everything beyond that
will depend on your heart.
URYU (VOICEOVER): My heart.
-Quincies release
arrows from their hearts
to protect the
ones they cherish.
-Ah.
[cries]
[theme music]
YUMICHIKA: Hey, Rangiku.
While all of you
were busy fighting,
I found the Bounts hideout.
RANGIKU: How'd you
do that, Yumichika?
YUMICHIKA: When you're blessed
with my brains and beauty,
it's child's play.
RANGIKU: You never
want to get dirty.
And yet you chose the
dirtiest job of all.
YUMICHIKA: That may be.
But I won't tell
you where it is.
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers!
CHAD: Golden.
RANGIKU: You know, I
just realized something.
CHAD: What?
-Shouldn't we have
left Noba in his Gigai
rather than putting him
into a stuffed animal?
I mean, his abilities are
stronger in the Gigai, right?
-There's one problem.
-What do you mean?
-Well, uh, to do
it, the bodies would
have to join together
if he was in the Gigai.
Noba's shy.