What's going on
here, dammit!
I'm not understanding
any of this!
Damn it!
Isn't there anything
I can do to stop it?!
Here's some advice. Act now
while you can. That is if you
want to protect your family.
[dialing]
[recorded female voice]
You have reached X-cution.
This card number is
currently unregistered.
Are you a new member?
If so, please say your name now.
Ichigo... Kurosaki.
Thank you, Mister Ichigo
Kurosaki. We have been
expecting your call.
Welcome to Xcution.
Please redial this number
followed by the digits
"zero-zero-eight-zero-zero."
Mister Ichigo Kurosaki.
Huh?
Next, please hang up
your phone before the
second ring tone ends.
Your call will be transferred
on your third try.
[ring]
Okay well that was a
real pain in the ass.
Aw, don't say that, if I didn't
make it complicated, it'd be a
real pain in the ass for me.
We need to talk.
Well that's obvious.
If you didn't want to talk,
you wouldn't have called.
Ichigo!
Hm?
There you are!
Do you know
anything about Chad?
Could you be a little
more specific, Orihime?
What about him?
What's up?
How's he doing?
"Doing"? Did he catch
the flu or something?
Oh! So then, you
don't know either?
I figured he should know
about what happened to Uryu,
so I went by his first
period class to tell him.
And guess what? he hasn't
been coming to school lately.
Since you're close, I
thought you'd probably know
something about where he is.
I'm surprised.
Guess you haven't
heard from him either.
I'll bet he's just sick.
Think I'll go drop by his
home with a get-well gift today.
[chuckle] Say!
How 'bout you join me
and we could both go
check in on him?!
Sorry.
Uh?
I've got stuff
to do today, so.
Heeh! Oh that's okay!
I know this was kinda sudden!
I can go see him and I'll let
you know tomorrow how he's
doing, alright?!
Sounds good!
Thanks.
Oh...
Has something
happened to Chad too?
What the hell is
going on here?
[Kugo]
Tonight's not good.
How about tomorrow?
Let's say, 8 p.m.?
Show up in front of the rundown
apartment building that's at
Seven-One Seventh Street
in the Chobara District.
I'll hear what you want
to talk about to then.
Relax.
I think I'll be
able to help you.
[Orihime]
Chad!
Hey, Chad!
You home?!
[sigh] From the look of
things I'd say he's not home.
[Ryuken]
Assuming the attacker was human
and targeting individuals with
unique abilities,
It's logical that the
next person in line
could be Sado or you.
[gasp]
No! Don't! I mustn't
think like that!
I pray that Chad will be
back at school tomorrow
feeling all better!
Seventh Street.
Number
Seven-One.
Rundown apartments.
This is it.
Hey.
Hnh?
Five minutes early.
So very punctual.
Not five minutes.
More like three.
So, what did you
want to talk about?
Some of my friends
were attacked.
Yeah, so?
So I want your help.
To figure out who did it?
I get this distinct feeling
that you don't trust me.
Look buddy, you know all
about me and about my dad.
I don't think you're
an ordinary human.
Oh really?
Your assumption's right,
I don't trust you.
Yet, you're the
only guy I can--
You can ask about this?
Right?
Fine.
Follow me.
[Kugo]
You know, I wish we
could've taken care of what
I was asking about first.
You mean about
my father?
You sound so serious.
I don't need you
to check on him.
That was just an
excuse that I used to
get your attention.
An excuse?
We're here.
We'll use that
card you have.
This is big.
We knocked out five rooms
on each side and three
stories above and below.
One of our members
is kind of wealthy.
Now then, before we go on,
Let me explain to you what
our objective is here.
Your objective?
That's right.
Our objective in
contacting you.
Here's the deal.
We want to restore your
Soul Reaper powers to you.
[Riruka]
God, you are unbelievable!
What kind of person would
allow himself to sleep in
a place like that!
You're a grown man!
What are you, stupid?
I mean really! Do you know
what it's like having to
go out looking for you?!
I never imagined you'd
be in a place like that!
Come to think of it,
why did he send me to
find you, anyway?!
Ginjo should have
had to go find you
himself, right?!
Anyways, what
was I saying?
Y'know! Why don't you
say something to me!
You realize it's all your
fault I'm so upset, right?!
C'mon-Speak up!
You do think, don't you?!
Damn... you!
[thud]
Owwwwwwww!
[gasp]
What's wrong?
You're looking at me
like you didn't hear me.
Your ears aren't playing
tricks on you, Ichigo.
We want to restore all of
your Soul Reaper powers.
How...
Could you do that?
Could something like
that even be possible?
Wait, are you saying this
just to jerk me around?!
What's your angle here?
Huh??!
Who the hell are you people?!
[gasp]
Just calm down.
I can't answer all
of your questions,
if you ask them
all at once.
Sit down.
We have a long
night ahead of us.
I'll explain everything.
[Kugo]
Want something to drink?
Oh, so what's with that look?
I wouldn't serve
a minor alcohol.
Oh wait, you're
not a drinker.
I guess you're a lot more
straight-laced than you look.
Go ahead, have something.
There's no menu, but we've
got pretty much anything
that you would want.
No thanks.
Hm.
Okay, well then just go
ahead and bring him some
orange juice or something.
Right.
First of all, we are humans.
But like you suggested earlier,
we're not "ordinary" humans.
You see we are different
from most people in that
we've been born with this
certain special ability.
What ability?
Explain yourself.
I think showing you
would be faster.
Hm?
Ahh!
[awestruck gasp]
What I just did, was to
draw out the "soul" of the
liquor out of that glass.
That was my skill that
"helped" me to drink it.
Our special ability...
is to draw out the "soul"
in any object, and to put
that object to use.
You seem confused by
what you've seen.
Were you under the false
assumption that only
living things have souls?
Every object in this world
has a soul, not just
animals and plants.
Sure Its soul might be small.
But a telephone pole,
a chair, even a pen.
Anything you can think of, no
matter how lifeless it may seem,
possesses some kind of a soul.
You've felt that feeling of
mastery that happens when
you're using a tool that
you're well acquainted with.
It leads to
maximizing your
ability.
The fact you can "become one"
with the object shows you
understand the tool's soul.
And that object's soul is
specifically endowed with
the power to help its user.
We have the ability
to draw that soul out.
Plus we can give it a boost
with our own soul, amplifying
it into an even greater power.
I can draw the soul out of
asphalt and increase its
rebounding force to jump higher
than you could ever imagine.
As you just saw, I can make
a liquid's soul move and
leap right into my mouth.
Or I can will it to support
my weight, so that I can
literally walk on water.
And if it's an object I'm
particularly familiar and
compatible with,
I can change that object's
physical form to suit me.
In my case, it's this
necklace I wear.
What's
happening
to it?
[gasp]
Like this for example.
The term we've given
to this unique ability
is "Fullbring."
Full bring?
Hey I'm back!
Riruka.
You're back earlier
than I expected.
So did you locate him?
I sure did!
Hey, isn't that your
sword glowing over there?
What's that doing out?
Are you stupid?!
It's so damn
dark in here!
You really need to put
in some more lights!
I can't see a damn thing!
I have no plans to add lights.
Get some glasses.
Hmph! I hate
wearing glasses!
But I hate contacts
even more!
Contacts make my
eyes dry out as soon
as I put them in!
It's 'cause my eyes
are so ginormous!
Nobody actaully
asked you.
Who is that girl?
That's Riruka Dokugamine.
She's one of us.
Say what?! So there's
someone here?!
I'll be sure to introduce
you to him later.
Now bring your guy here.
Hrrgh!
Don't you boss me around!
Hey you, you can
come on in here now!
[gasp]
Chad!
Ichigo.
Chad! Just what in the hell
are you doing here?!
Why haven't you been
going to school?!
[Ichigo]
Chad, what's going
on with you!?
Say something!
Calm down, Ichigo.
You stay out of this!
I'm talking to my friend dammit!
What've you got to say!?
Give me an answer Chad!
Just calm down.
Don't make me
ask you again.
If you'll listen to me,
you'll understand.
Now take a breath
and sit down.
You too, Chad.
What? Are you saying these
two guys know each other?!
Well it would've been nice
to have been told that!
[Riruka]
Hey Ginjo, what's
the big deal, huh?
Am I the only one
around here who's being
kept out of the loop?!
Let's get Chad some
water or something.
You're
ignoring me?!
Wait a minute!
You were calling this guy
"Ichigo"! That's Kurosaki?!
Turn up the lights!
I wanna get a good look at him!
Maybe later.
"Later"?!
Okay. Now that everyone's
here, let's get started.
Not yet! Wait a sec!
Let's see this Ichigo!!
He's so hot!
Augh!
Hey there!
Uh, are you okay?
No.
I'm not. It's all
because of you.
She's fine.
Alright then, let's
get back to our talk.
Uh, right.
Before you
return to your
talk Mr. Ginjo,
perhaps you wouldn't
mind putting that
sword away.
Yes, you're right.
Very well then.
You can pay for the
floor tiles later.
I'll do that.
Now that you've seen
it with your own eyes,
you comprehend our
skill, right?
Yeah, I get it.
Very well. Then we
can move on in our
discussion.
[Kugo]
Do you know the reason why a
Hollow has a hole in its chest?
What are you getting at?
The pain of not being saved
by a Soul Reaper tears its
heart out, leaving a hole.
But do you know where that heart
goes when it's been torn out?
When that heart is lost
it becomes its own mask.
But it is not simply a mask.
Each Hollow's
individualistic appearance
and its very unique powers,
are all embodied and
created from the heart
that was torn out.
We've all shared a sad
event before we were born.
All of our mothers were
attacked by a Hollow.
[gasp]
The end result of our mothers
being attacked by Hollows,
was that the remnants of
those Hollow's powers
were left behind.
So when we were born,
the power inside of us was more
like that of a Hollow, rather
than that of a Soul Reaper.
Therefore we found
our power loathsome.
Since you yourself
once possessed Hollow
powers, Ichigo,
I'm quite sure you
understand how we feel,
having this burden.
Mm.
So naturally, you
can understand that
we would like to rid ourselves
of this power that we have.
It's taken us many
years to find others
with powers like ours
but now we have finally
gathered together.
Finding each other has led
us to an interesting discovery.
We've discovered that if
we find someone who is our
exact polar opposite.
By that I mean someone
who possesses both Soul
Reaper and human powers,
it's possible for us to
exchange powers with them.
So you mean?
That's right.
There was this one
other person like you.
Who was born of a Soul
Reaper and a human being.
[Gasp]
A number of our former
members yielded their powers
to that specific person.
And as a result of that
exchange, all of them
were able to return to
being ordinary humans.
You understand?
We want to become
ordinary humans again,
so we will help you
regain your Soul
Reaper powers.
Sound good?
That's not what I came
here to discuss with you.
What's that?
Listen. I only came here for
one reason, to find out why bad
stuff's happening to my friends.
As for me getting back
my Soul Reaper powers,
That's beside the point.
So you're saying you don't
want your Soul Reaper powers?
[Ichigo]
Ah damn, I left something
at Ginjo's place.
I better call him.
[recorded female voice]
You have reached Xcution.
[Ichigo]
Yeah hi, I left something at--
[recorded female voice]
Mr. Ichigo Kurosaki?
[Ichigo]
Yeah, I left something--
[recorded female voice]
Please redial this number
followed by
Zero-Zero--
[Ichigo]
Aww I gotta do this again?!