[theme music]
NARRATOR: Ichigo finally
emerged victorious
after a brutal
battle with Grimmjow.
But before he could
celebrate his triumph,
he was confronted with an
even stronger opponent,
Espada Number Five, Nnoitra.
Nelliel had regained
her Espada powers,
but as she attempted to
save Ichigo from Nnoitra,
she reverted to her
helpless childlike form
again just as she found herself
on the brink of victory.
With no one to help, Ichigo was
left in a desperate situation,
and Nnoitra moved
in for the kill.
Suddenly, Ichigo was
saved by the last person
he expected to see.
ZARAKI: What's going on here?
ICHIGO: Kenpachi.
-So, you next?
Come on.
You're next, right?
-Kenpachi, I don't get it.
Why are you here?
Am I wrong?
I thought the Soul Society
had pulled out of this fight.
-Kisuke Urahara.
It seems that a while ago, he
was given a bunch of orders
from the old man.
That was back when the
showdown was set for winter.
Kisuke was ordered to stabilize
this underground cavern called
Garganta.
He was to make sure it
was safe so captain level
personnel could pass
through Hueco Mundo.
I swear, I already said that
I can more than handle this
by myself.
So you finally attacked.
-I would strongly suggest
that you stand down.
We are here only to
heal everyone's wounds.
We have no intention
of fighting you.
-Arrancar.
Arrancar.
[laughter] Hueco Mundo is
a treasure trove of riches.
BYAKUYA: Were you the one
who fought this woman?
-No.
I did not fight her.
However, I was about to deliver
the blow that would finish her.
-Were you?
-Among all the Espadas
my Sonido is the fastest.
And by adding a small step,
I've created something else,
something that resembles
a pseudo clone.
Yes, you might think of
it as playing with magic.
Too bad for you
that Gemelos Sonido
is not limited to
only two bodies.
Farewell, nameless
soul reaper captain.
Your defeat was caused
by the arrogant act
of not stating your name.
-Actually, you are the
arrogant one here, Espada.
There's no need to fret.
Your arrogance will
not be your undoing.
Though you will taste defeat.
The reason is simply
a difference in skill.
[panting]
-I can't believe how cold it is.
I'm so stupid.
I should have worn
something heavier.
I've got to say, that wasn't
nice of Captain Kuchiki,
leaving me the moment
after we showed up.
I thought I made it clear to
him I can't use the Flash Step,
but he took off anyway.
I-- [screaming]
That really hurt.
I wonder which way
I'm supposed to go.
-What a funny thing to say.
I, arrogant?
Now, what makes
you believe that?
You are an enemy, but
you're also a captain.
The fact of the matter is I
consider you to be my equal,
and I have conducted
myself in that manner.
I am not an arrogant being.
-Now, that's interesting.
-Hm.
-Imagine an Arrancar
considering himself my equal.
That attitude already displays
a certain amount of arrogance.
-How very rude.
It explains things.
It appears your
arrogance is part
of the very nature
of your being.
Very well then, I shall
crush your pride along
with your body.
I shall turn them both into
pulp to be discarded along
with the rest of the garbage.
Subside.
Brujeria.
You're very jumpy.
You expected me to mount
an attack of some kind,
but surprisingly,
nothing happened.
Now, you're wondering
if my threats are empty.
It makes sense.
Unfortunately for
you, they're real.
You're left leg
now belongs to me.
-What's this supposed to mean?
-All things are subject
to control in this life.
Subordinates are under the
control of their superiors.
The masses are under the
control of their king.
Clouds are under the
control of the wind.
The light of the moon is
under the control of the sun.
The power of my
Brujeria is to control
whatever my eye stares at.
I call this power Amor, and
you will now experience it.
You still appear to
be confused, I see.
I sympathize with
your predicament.
It must be frustrating
to try and grasp
this concept with a
limited intellect.
Though you don't
get it, your body
will experience the full effect.
Let me demonstrate.
Left leg, come to me.
It is meaningless to resist.
Your control does not
extend to that limb.
Now then, another step forward.
-How astonishing.
You didn't hesitate
to slash the muscles
and tendons of your leg.
It really was your
only effective move.
I am now unable to
control that appendage.
Excellent.
A decision and swift action.
All right then, let's
try something else.
Oh.
You're able to move that
well, even on one leg.
I have to hand it to you,
captain, I am truly impressed.
-Damn you.
[panting]
-Ah.
I think I hear him at
the end of the hall.
Finally, I caught up with you.
That was pretty mean to leave
me behind, Captain Kuchiki.
I told you before I wasn't
any good at doing Flash Step.
Oh, this has been a
terrible experience.
I'm not very fast,
and I was so hungry.
And I felt uncomfortable
in this strange building,
and it was freezing
cold everywhere I went.
And I didn't know my
way around the inside.
And I almost got lost.
And ahh--
[gasp] Captain Kuchiki,
you've been injured, sir.
Your leg is really bleeding.
What's happened to Miss Rukia?
Is she all right?
Miss Rukia.
-He is quite a chatterbox.
Is he one of your subordinates?
-Hanataro Yamada.
-Yes, captain.
-Stay back.
-Yes, I'm moving back right now.
I'm very sorry, sir.
I'm in the way, aren't I?
BYAKUYA: Let me make
myself very clear.
I will say it once more.
You have to stay back.
I cannot guarantee that I'll be
able to fight without getting
you involved.
-Captain, both of them appear
to have stabilized now.
That's good.
-Isane, it's important
we remain vigilant.
If we had been a little bit
later with our treatment,
we might easily have lost them.
If we're not home,
we're in Hueco Mundo.
We have to remind
ourselves we're
in the middle of enemy grounds.
There's no telling
what might happen,
so we have to be on guard.
-Yes, ma'am.
Can you feel that?
It's Captain Kuchiki.
UNOHANA: It's not only
his spiritual pressure.
Captain Kurotsuchi
and Captain Zaraki
have also begun to fight.
Yes.
I can feel the three of them
have their spiritual pressure
operating at full strength.
They're severely challenged.
That's the kind of danger
they face with the Espadas.
-I'm worried.
Will they be all right, Captain?
-Let's have faith.
I'm sure they're up for the job.
That's what they're trained for.
When they're done, we'll
heal their injuries.
After all, that's what
we're trained for.
-You're pretty tough.
I have to give you credit.
-So are you.
I have to ask you though, where
you getting all that strength?
-What is that, Captain Kuchiki?
Captain, are you all right?
Ahh.
-Oh.
-What's happening?
Why did you cut
your arm like that?
-Hado number one.
Sho.
-Who's there?
Miss Kuchiki.
-Stay back, Hanataro Yamada.
-Yes, Captain.
ZOMMARI: I see.
-Miss Rukia, Rukia,
are you all right?
Can you hear me?
-You instantly disabled not only
your left leg but your left arm
as well.
Once those objects were
out of your control,
you immediately
regarded them as enemies
and slashed them, even though
they were part of your body.
So coldly analytical,
an impressive display
of detachment in the
face of painful choices.
However, that detachment, in my
view, seems dangerously rash.
-Rukia, if you can
hear me at all,
we have to move you out of here.
Can you open your eyes?
-Of your four limbs, only your
right arm and your right leg
remain functional.
Under the circumstances,
you display
a high level of arrogance.
Considering your disabilities,
challenging an Espada
is hardly a rational act.
That must be
apparent, even to you.
-As I told you--
-Hm.
-The difference between
my power and your power
is as wide as the gap
between heaven and earth.
But this talk is tedious.
It's true I discarded my
left arm and my left leg,
but even without their use, you
and I are still far from equal.
-How unfortunate.
I thought you might
listen to reason,
but you appear to have even less
understanding of your abilities
than I first thought.
There was something
I forgot to tell you
when I explained myself.
These eyes of mine have fairly
unique and specific powers.
They control one
object for each eye.
I'm glad you realize so
quickly what that means.
Earlier, I released Amor using
just two of my eyes, which
means in addition to control
of your two left limbs
I have the power to
control something else.
And the unpredictability
of this power
makes it impossible for
you to defend against it.
As I mentioned, I am only able
to control one area per eye.
However, if I control
the head, my control
extends to the entire body.
It's quite dynamic.
And it's not affected
by a person's injuries.
Don't move.
You see the dilemma.
Throw down your sword,
Captain Kuchiki.
Face the fact you have lost.
Hm.
-Bakudo number 61, Rikujokoro.
-What is this?
Damn it, I command you.
Move.
-You wanted to control me.
Let me tell you, you don't
have nearly enough power
to ever make that happen.
Bankai.
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
-What?
What is this?
Damn you.
You want to see power?
I will control everything,
using every ounce of Amor
in my spirit.
BYAKUYA: Useless.
According to what
you said earlier,
you can control one
object for each eye.
And by my count, you have a
total of 50 eyes on your body.
Keeping that in mind,
tell me, with those 50,
which of the hundreds
of millions of swords
covering the sky, do
you intend to control?
You told me earlier it
was meaningless to resist,
that there was
nothing I could do.
I'm going to offer you
the same advice now.
Struggle as much as you like,
but it's meaningless to resist.
-Damn it.
No.
I'm in control.
Move as I command.
Do you hear me.
-Gokei.
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
-This can't be happening.
[theme music]
HANATARO (VOICEOVER): That
Espada Zommari Rureaux
ended up looking like a pumpkin.
ZOMMARI (VOICEOVER): Yeah.
Well, your captain was a tube
of fish cake in his hair.
Pumpkins and fish
cake are both foods.
They're at an equal level.
BYAKUYA (VOICEOVER): Fish
cake is a processed food.
It's at a much higher
level than a pumpkin.