[theme music]
-I can't believe we got stuck
guarding such a boring place.
-They say there are a
lot of bizarre things
in the Department of
Research and Development.
Some of them must be
dangerous, or they
wouldn't have posted us here.
-It's still boring.
Huh?
Hey.
-Huh?
-Who is that?
-A Ryoka!
-It's a fine day today.
-Please keep up the good work.
-Yes, ma'am.
[explosion]
-Hm.
Lieutenant.
What could that be?
-I don't know.
But whatever it is, it
has immense spirit energy
and it's coming this way.
-Lieutenant.
We have a report
of Ryoka nearby.
We are here to intercept them.
-Feel that?
Something's different.
The spiritual
pressure just changed.
-Yes.
It's hard to tell for sure
because of all the battles
going on all over the place,
but the presence of oneof
the bounts just vanished.
And now I'm getting
a different one.
-What's the matter now?
-I think--
-It's Kariya.
-Ah huh.
-He's finally revealed himself.
-Which way?
-Uh, it's that way!
-All right.
Hey Chad.
-Ichigo.
-What's happening?
Are you all right?
-I'm fine.
No problem.
-You sense the Bount.
Just like us.
-Yes.
There's no doubt about it.
It's Kariya.
-Let's go.
-You're right.
No time to lose.
-So, this is all there is?
Haven't you got anyone
worth fighitng around here?
-Get her!
-Nieder.
-Leave them to me.
-Hi-yah!
Huh?
-So the Quincy boy has returned.
What an annoying child.
So now you're trying
to lure me in, are you?
That's interesting.
Let's see what you're up to.
You just never learn, do you?
When are you gonna give
up on this quest of yours
for revenge?
URYU: This isn't about revenge.
-Huh?
-Even if it were,
who are you to talk?
Why do you proceed when there
is no point to this fight?
-Huh?
What are you talking about?
And for that matter,
I could ask you
why a Quincy would be taking
sides with Soul Reapers.
I always thought
that the two of you
were supposed to
be mortal enemies.
-I'm not.
I've never allied myself
with the Soul Reapers.
For me, the goal is to try
and stop senseless violence.
-You're not making
any sense at all.
-Perhaps.
But on my honor as a Quincy,
I will put a stop to this.
-Well, then good.
If you really want to
die so badly, I can help.
ICHIGO: Ran'Tao.
I assume you know about Uryu
and about his special Quincy
accessory.
How long do you believe
that'll keep on working?
-I'm afraid there's
no way of knowing.
It could become useless today,
or it could be tomorrow.
With all the destructive
energy it has,
it's conceivable that it
could obliterate everything
inside a 20 square mile radius
if it goes off accidentally.
-(IN HEAD): I made up my mind.
I decided I was
going to do this,
no matter what might happen.
I know that somehow, these
Bounts have to be stopped.
Here I come!
-Enjoy your death!
-Now you shall
witness my true power.
My, my.
That wasn't a very
good shot at all.
-Damn.
-He's just a boy, after all.
What do you expect?
-I expect him to die.
Well, at least he's
fast, if nothing else.
Why have you ended our fusion?
-Oh, just shut.
You know I hate the
feeling of being fused
with you for the length
of a whole battle.
-You tell him.
I know exactly what you mean.
-That's cold!
-So, what are you planning
to try next, Quincy boy?
-(IN HEAD) The way
things are going,
all I can hope to do is
keep dodging her attacks.
That'll have to do.
-If you won't
attack, then I will.
-That was a pretty
lame shot, Quincy boy.
-(IN HEAD) Damn it.
Just when I need it most,
my power keeps dropping.
It's definitely unstable.
Even if I hit her, it would
probably have no effect.
My reishi level decreased
just before my third attack.
That's why the arrow had no
velocity when I released it.
I know that when I absorb enough
reishi, and I'm at full power,
I have the ability to
destroy my opponent.
But when I absorb
too much reishi,
there's also the danger that the
arrow could go off accidentally
and destory everything
in the vicinity.
And of course, it'll also blow
away the person who fired it.
-What's wrong, Quincy?
Are you brooding over the
last minutes of your life?
-(IN HEAD) Can I do this?
Is it possible for me
to control this arrow?
I've got to.
I've got to do this.
Did I get them?
-Ha ha!
-No way.
-Oh, yes.
And now you see me
in my true form.
In this state, I boast perfect
protection against all strikes.
Your attacks are now
completely ineffective.
-I've noticed that his arrow's
power is different every time
he releases it.
-Yes.
It appears he's
unable to control it.
But you must admit thatif I
hadn't shielded us just now,
it would have been a close one.
-Enough with your
boring explanations.
-(THINKING) Damn.
I finally fired an arrow
at her at full power,
and it didn't hit her.
Still, I can't give up.
It is not an option.
I have to keep on firing.
-Do it now.
-(THINKING) That's good.
[laughter]
-I've got to hit her.
Dammit.
-What a fool.
Using a weapon he
cannot even control.
-Huh?
-Now it's my turn!
Honestly, if you wanted to
have a chance against us,
then you should have
brought a better weapon.
NEIDER: That wasn't
even a challenge.
-Hm.
You are even more naive
than I thought, Quincy boy.
[gasping]
-Where are you going?
-There should be a Bount
crest here somewhere.
-A crest?
-The original.
The first Bount
crest ever created.
-I've never heard of this crest.
I don't know where it is.
-I wasn't asking you to
tell me where it is, was I?
I'll find it myself, and when
I do, I'm going to take it.
ICHIGO: And then what, Kariya?
What are you going to
do once you have it?
-Oh, it's you again.
Be careful.
This man is dangerous.
-I know.
I know all about this guy.
Kariya, what do you plan to
do with this crest you're
talking about?
-If you want to know, you'll
just have to defeat me.
[scream]
-Dammit!
-Where'd he go?
-He ran away.
We need your help.
You have to tell me
where the crest is
that he's searching for.
-I'm sorry, but I don't know.
I wish I did.
-We don't need to
know where it is.
All we have to do now is follow
Kariya's spiritual pressure.
-You're right.
OK, then.
Let's go.
-Hm?
It's resonating.
The crest must be in this room.
Hm.
Where is it?
ICHIGO: Kariya!
Bankai!
Tensa Zangetsu.
-Heh.
-You're gonna have to
go through me first.
-I must admit, you
are a nuisance.
I won't be able to
take my time and search
until I deal with you.
-Run, Chad!
Nice try.
This has gone on long enough.
It ends now!
-Whoa!
-What the hell is that?
-The crest.
I never expected it to be here.
All this time, it's remained
hidden in this place.
This is the crest I have been
searching for all this time.
[speaking german]
-Ichigo.
-Kariya.
What are you doing?
-In this very moment, I have
gained the ultimate power.
-What do you mean?
-Ultimate power?
KARIYA: For eons, I have been
investigating and researching
ancient records.
Once I narrowed it down, I had
Ichinose begin searching here.
And soon he was able to
track it to somewhere
here in the Department of
Research and Development.
The name of this
original crest is Jokai.
Its incredible power can
purify and erase everything.
-The Jokai Crest?
KARIYA: This chamber is where
the infamous experiments that
led to the creation of
the Bounts were conducted.
-They were?
KARIYA: When the accident
occurred and the experiments
were halted, the
incredible energy
that made up the foundation for
the experiments and the Jokai
Crest was sealed away,
and now I have become one
with that very energy.
I wonder if you can
comprehend what that means.
It means that I
now have the power
to blow up the
Seireitei at any time
by releasing the
Jokai Crest's energy.
-You what?
-Do you expect us
to believe that?
-Believe whatever you like.
What you or anyone else
thinks is not important to me.
-Those eyes.
He's serious.
-No!
Really?
-What are you going to do then?
I imagine you want to
attack to try to stop me.
But if you do, I will release
the Jokai Crest's energy.
If you are that foolish,
then go ahead and attack.
Otherwise, go and tell the
people of the Seireitei this.
I will give them
one day's grace.
Until then, may they
all tremble in wait.
-Hey, come back here!
-Ichigo.
-Chad.
-If all that he said
is really true--
-Do you think we've killed him?
NEIDER: My, my.
It does look that way.
-Well, it was thanks
to the Quincy boy
here that we were able to
get into this place at all,
so I suppose we owe him out
thanks for that at least.
UYRU: Where do you
think you're going?
[theme music]
RIRIN: Aw.
Kariya got away from us again.
I really should have
come in my Gigai.
NEMU: There's one in the
Department of Research
and Development that Mayuri's
using for her experiments.
RIRIN: Oh, can I borrow it?
NEMU: Would you like the
squid type, the octopus type,
or the eel type?
RIRIN: I don't
want any of those!
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
guide to Soul Reapers.
MAYURI: Ow, ow, ow!
That hurts.
ICHIGO: Huh?
It's Mayuri Kurotsuchi.
What's wrong?
You look terrible.
MAYURI: Carry me inside.
CHAD: Where can I lift you?
Here?
MAYURI: Ow, ow, ow ow.
Not there.
You're going to tear me apart.
ICHIGO: Gah.
Fine.
Then how are we
supposed to carry you?
MAYURI: Carry me piggyback?
ICHIGO AND CHAD:
Rock, paper, scissors.
Rock paper scissors.
MAYURI: Oh, please.
If you don't want to carry
me, just tell me straight out!