The Zanpakuto. Its
unique shape and
abilities are defined by
its Soul Reaper.
The Soul Reaper is able
to harness the power of
the Zanpakuto by learning
its name and forming a
synergistic unit.
The Zanpakuto is born
with its Soul Reaper and
dies with its Soul
Reaper.
That is the existence of
a Zanpakuto.
Hey.
How long are we gonna
have to stick around this
place anyway? I'm so
freakin' bored here.
Eh, I'm gonna take a look
outside.
Not a good idea.
Huh?
It's too soon. Not
everyone has arrived
as of yet.
Everyone who?
How many more are coming?
Well, I can't be sure,
exactly.
Aw, who cares about our
numbers? In fact, why
don't I go out there
and handle this myself!
Shut up. Rushing into
things is foolish.
You said it! An
impatient man is
so unattractive.
Huh?
Welcome back.
I have brought us a new
friend. Look after him.
Hey, that guy's pretty
good looking.
Be straight with me, how
long are we gonna be
stuck down here waiting?
You'll have to bear it
a bit longer.
The rest of our comrades
will be joining us very
soon.
Aw, come on!
The era of the Soul
Reaper is coming to
an end.
Ichigo.
Can you hear it, Ichigo?
Hold on. Why
am I---
Ichigo!
Huh?
Surely you are able to
hear it, Ichigo.
What, your voice? Of
course I hear it.
No, Ichigo, that is not
what I mean.
Huh?
Sorry, I don't hear
anything other than you.
What're you talking
about?
Forget about it.
What? No, I can't forget about it now.
Listen, Old Man! Hey! Answer me!
Roar, Zabimaru!
Scatter, Senbonzakura.
Lieutenant!
Ban-kai!
Whoa.
Hihio, Zabimaru!
Heh!
[cheering]
You haven't forgotten,
have you?
When Senbonzakura is
controlled directly by my
hands, it has twice the
speed.
Your slow Bankai is no
match for it.
Here I come.
Hear my voice.
Now, Hikotsu Taiho!
Look at that. You used
your Bankai?
Captain? Is something
wrong?
No.
Captain? Huh?
Wow fellas, that was
quite the sparring
session.
Yes Lieutenant Abarai,
your skills have
improved.
Oh have they? Thank you.
Um, Captain?
That will be all for
today.
Uh, yes sir. I
appreciate the
opportunity.
Byakuya?
Please excuse me.
Wonder what's eating
that guy.
Hyorinmaru!
What's the matter?
What was that about?
Hyorinmaru.
Just come on out already!
Agh! Rangiku!
Get out here, Haineko!
Are you seriously ignoring
me?! You think that I'll
just take this from you?!
You better watch
yourself!
Hey.
Are you even listening?!
That's it, I'm mad.
You are lazy, moody and a
brat! What a useless
Zanpakuto! Whoever
forged you was--
Rangiku!
What's the yelling
about, huh?
Hey don't scare me like
that. I was just having
a friendly chat with my
Zanpakuto.
That was a chat?
Excuse me.
Hello there, Rangiku.
Shiro.
Momo? Isane?
Why do you always refuse
to call me Captain?
What brings you girls
around here?
Thi does. It's a special
notice announcing a
lieutenants meeting.
Oh, thanks!
Something wrong, Shiro?
You two... don't you
have somewhere to be!?
R-Rangiku!
Uh, what were you doing
in here?
Ohh. Just talking to my
Zanpakuto.
Our enemies are getting
more crafty all the time.
So we have to hone our
skills too.
And yet that silly
Haineko! She just
refuses to manifest.
I'm telling you, she
can be so lame.
Oh! You really
shouldn't badmouth your
Zanpakuto like that.
You must be more
forgiving towards it.
When I was at my lowest
point, Tobiume was so
concerned about me.
That's when I realized...
No matter what happens,
I am never alone!!
So you're telling me
you even drive your
Zanpakuto crazy?
Umm... Speaking of
Zanpakuto problems...
My Itegumo has also been
slow to respond the past
two or three days.
Yours too, Isane?!
Yes. And this has never
happened before.
You're lucky it's
just this once! With
Haineko, it's been
constant.
It's the first time,
that's what concerns me!
Um, Toshiro? Where are
you going?
Where do you think? I'm
still on duty.
Oh! But we brought over
some sweet baked bean
desserts that we got from
Captain Unohana.
Let's have a tea break,
Captain. They are your
favorite treats!
Captain?!
So strange.
What does this mean?
[giggling]
Well. This is it. We've
reached our destination.
Let's get started! Come
on!
Reveal yourself.
Who's out there?!
An urgent summons?
What could be going on at
this hour of the night?
What the...?
We're all being
summoned? Captain!
Yes, I received the
same urgent message.
What did we miss?
Captain Hitsugaya.
You have any idea
what's going on? Why
were we called here?
I'm not really sure. I've
asked, but it seems no one
else knew about this meeting
ahead of time.
And well...
What is it?
Is that Rukia?
Huh?
You were summoned too?
Yes. I'm not sure
why, but I got the call
just like the others did.
Well, it's certainly
an interesting group.
Are the two of you
filling in for Captain
Zaraki?
We've never been the
captain's stand-ins
before. This is a
first.
Right, but at present
our captain and
lieutenant are actually
away. So if you order
us to stay and listen in,
we have no choice.
Oh yeah? Where'd they
run off to?
Not sure. It happens
all the time though.
None of you people
know why the Head Captain
sent for all of us at such
an unreasonable hour?
This sucks. And this
fog is a mess.
Ah, Lieutenant Sasakibe.
What's going on here?
And where is the Head
Captain?
Whoa! Captain?!
Scan the area, and remain
alert.
He's in bad shape,
he's gone into cardiac
arrest.
Start resuscitation.
Yes, ma'am!
Hmph.
I'm afraid the Head
Captain won't be
joining us tonight.
And just who the hell are
you?
And how do you know the
Head Captain isn't
coming?
Captain!
We're waiting. What
did you do with Head
Captain Yamamoto?!
So, you refuse to answer?
Well in that case...
I'll just beat the
answer out of you!!
Well then. This just
got way more interesting.
Shall we get involved,
Ikkaku?
Stay back! Can't you
see that my Captain is
fighting him!?
Keep out of this or the
two of you are gonna get
hurt.
Bankai! Kokujo Tengen
Myo-oh!
We demand the Head
Captain! Tell us
where he is!
I should warn you, your
feeble attacks won't
touch me.
We'll see!
Behind you!
Captain, no!!
That strike! What
was that!?
A Zanpakuto attacked its
own master?! Impossible!
What the hell?
What the hell is
going on here?!
My, my. How intriguing.
Huh?!
Who... are you?
Tenken? But how?!
How... could
this... ugh.
Captain!
Hold on!
Let go of me,
Yumichika!
Reign over the frosted
heavens! Hyorinmaru!
Sting all enemies to
death! Suzumebachi!
Captain!
Shikai doesn't
work!
You're right.
Now roar, Zabimaru!
Growl, Haineko! Huh?
Extend, Hozukimaru!
What's wrong with this
thing?!
There's no more
Spiritual Pressure in my
Zanpakuto!
Tobiume, what's
wrong?
Wabisuke?!
You're right. The
Spiritual Pressure is
indeed absent. The
question is why?
It's very simple. You
and your precious
Zanpakuto, are no
longer united as one.
I freed them. Released
them from the Soul
Reapers' control.
Freed our Zanpakuto?
Is that possible?
What's that?
What are you trying to
pull now you psycho?!
Oh, that wasn't me. Your
own Zanpakuto are
responsible for this
destruction.
No!
I'm afraid it's true,
dear. They have all
been released from the
Soul Reapers' control!
[laughing]
What is that?!
Put out the fire! Hurry!
There's someone over
there!
Who is it?!
An intruder?!
[laughing]
What is it?!
Heh!! Too easy!
Must he be so barbaric?
Huh?
Good evening. If I were
you I'd start running.
I apologize, but I
don't have time to play
with all of you.
Don't even try. You
guys don't have a
prayer.
Hmm?
We've been summoned.
Come along.
Hmph.
This was just a preview.
A small demonstration,
so you would begin to comprehend
the power of my comrades.
And as for the Zanpakuto,
which you foolishly thought
you owned. Well, cast your
eyes on their true form!
Somehow the Zanpakuto
managed to manifest
themselves?!
That's insane!
Hmmm? Oh!
How is this possible?
This is nuts.
Out of the way!
How dare you!
Hm? Brother?
Enough of this. Tell us
who you are.
I am known as
Muramasa.
And this night marks the
end of the Soul Reapers'
reign over the Zanpakuto.
From now on...
It'll be the Zanpakuto
who rule over the Soul
Reapers.
Hey Ichigo, what's
bothering you?
I bet I don't get much
screen time in this new
story arc.
Don't you get some
action in the next
episode?
I doubt it.
Wow, you're pretty
negative.
With that lousy attitude,
you won't get any screen
time.
Damn it, you're right!
I'll stop complaining
now.