Aahh!
Calm down.
I'm a Soul Reaper.
(o.m. uneasy breaths, gasp of
fright)
Are you all right?
What happened?
[shriek]
Aaaa-Aaahhh!
AAAHHHHH!!!!
With these reports of Soul
Reapers going missing,
You sure you really
wanna do this?
Go out without a gigai?
If something happens,
don't say I didn't warn you.
Ugh.
Hey, you're the one who's
making me transport all
this merchandise for you!
And I can't tell you what
a big help you've been!
With all this trouble recently
I haven't been able to use my
normal transport route.
Heh-heh. It's tied up
a lot of my inventory.
No wonder there's so
much stuff on that cart.
Any items of interest?
I'll cut you a great deal.
No thanks!
Duh-huh-huh-huh... Boss?
We're all done and
ready to go, sir!
Okay, okay. Give me
a couple minutes
and I'll be ready.
Where are you going?
We're gonna close up the shop
in a bit and all of us are
finally going to take a much
needed vacation together.
Yeah, well, you see,
we had pretty much
sold out of everything
on the shelves,
and we didn't have
any new merchandise
coming in,
so I kinda thought we
might as well take a vacation.
But now, of course, we do
have new merchandise so, uh,
Back to work, everyone!
On second thought, we'll
stick with the vacation idea.
Oh, brother.
If you'll excuse us,
we'll be on our way.
[sigh]
Rukia, I checked 'em out,
all the places where they
were said to be last seen.
From the looks of things, those
Soul Reapers were obviously
attacked and probably consumed.
I see. That means we're
talking about Hollows.
No. We're not.
Huh?
Hollows would've left
residual Spirit Energy.
There was none at any
of the sites.
It was something else.
[running, panting]
Huagghh!
He he he ha ha ha ha ha!
Had enough yet,
Soul Reaper?
Drgghh...
Ehh...
Heh. What a
pathetic specimen.
You wouldn't even make
a good appetizer.
But what the hell.
Hehehehuhuhuhu!
[Rukia]
Dance!
Sodenoshirayuki!
Somenomai, Tsukishiro!
Geh!
So it is targeting
Soul Reapers.
That was close,
thanks for the backup.
I know you from
somewhere.
Eh?
Seriously?
You really remember me?
Yes! That's right, the one and
only Soul Reaper in charge of
Karakura Town!
Zennosuke Kurumadani,
that's me!
Aah hah hah haa!
Unbelievable. This clown is
the guy who took over for me?
[menacing chuckle]
Huh?
Augh!!
Sorry, that trick's not
going to work on me.
Kisuke was right,
This guy's Spiritual
Pressure is different
from the Hollows'.
It's you!
Eh?
He he he ha ha ha!
I've found you! Haha!
Hado Number
Thirty Three!
Sokatsui!
Agh!
Hehehoohahaha!
Now I'm sure of it!
There's no mistaking
that technique!
I thought if I went
on a rampage in this
town, you'd appear,
and I was right!
What are you saying?
Do we know each other?
What, you really
don't remember?
It's me! Me! Look!
Augh!
Wait, are you?
Shrieker!?
Correct!
But you can't be!
No, it's not
possible! You...
You fell into the
depths of hell!
[Rukia]
The Zanpakuto can only
wash away sins a soul has
commited as a Hollow.
those who committed
terrible crimes while alive,
go to the underworld.
Yearrghhh...
[gurgle]
[Rukia]
How? How did you
escape from Hell?
Aw, wouldn't you like to know?
But if you think I'm going
to tell you, think again!
Get her!
Not that old trick.
Huh! Nice move.
I don't remember you being that
good the last time we met.
That was a long time ago.
I'd lost my powers back then;
you don't know what
I'm capable of now!
I've got your back,
don't worry!
You fool!
Stay back!
Eeeyahh!
Wha?!
All right.
I'll finish with you first!
Eeesh...
Stay here!
I've been waiting a
long time for this!
I'm going to make this
messy and painful!
It can't be!
His strength and speed
are at a whole new level!
Eh?
Eaugh!
Now you're mine!
[gasp] A chain!
Yes, a chain. And it can't be
severed by the likes of you!
Ah!
Now, die!
Not quite yet!
Somenomai! Tsukishiro!
There, that takes
care of his leeches.
[gasp] Oh no!
Ngh!
Oof!
How is that possible?
I didn't sense the
presence of those
leech bombs.
Where did they come from?
He he he he! What's the matter,
tired of running? Or just tired?
Hoohoo, ha ha ha ha ha!
Good morning!
Tsuchinamazu!
What did you just do?
Heh ha ha ha ha ha!
I just bought us
time to get away.
Th-that was an
escape technique??
Ah!
Get down!
Kurumadani!
[Rukia]
He has leech bombs
in his body as well!
Hoohoohehehehehehe!
That's right.
My new body is
like one giant bomb!
Damn it!
Get outta here
while you can!
No!
Hehehehe! You're right,
things are different.
You're not the only one who's
gotten stronger since then!
Just what...
what are you?
Ah, the chain.
Do you know
where it comes from?
Hehehehahahaha!
This chain is from hell!
And I, am a Sinner of Hell!
A Sinner!
Impossible! There is
no way a Sinner could
ever escape from Hell!
Wrong! I did! Just to
get my revenge on you!
Hoohoohehehehehe!
[gasp]
Aurr augh... no!
What happened?...
What are you doing?
Shut up!!
[gasp]
Renji!
Hey. You all
right, Rukia?
What are you doing here?
Got a report from the
Department of Research
and Development.
Some kind of weird Spiritual
Pressure was detected in the
World of the Living.
So who is this guy?
He says he's a
Sinner from Hell.
He's a Sinner?
Get outta here.
You interfering little bastard!
Things were just getting good!
Haaa ha ha!
Your aim's a little off!
Hehehe ha ha ha ha!
That's one Soul Reaper down,
now for the other!
Bankai!
Hihio Zabimaru!
Hikotsu Taiho!!!
Bleaggh!
[struggling]
Hrrgh!
[gurgle]
Bleaagh!
He he he ha ha ha ha!
Oh, it'll take more than that to
get rid of me! I'll keep
returning from the depths of
Hell!
Hoo hoo he ha ha ha!
Heeee ha ha ha!
Speaking of Hell,
what the hell was
all that?
Don't know, but,
I don't like it.
This emergency meeting of the
captains is now called to order.
[Retsu]
But I see that Captains
Zaraki and Kurotsuchi
have not yet arrived.
Even so. You can explain
it to them later.
This matter cannot wait. There
is a reason I summoned you all
here on such short notice.
It is this. A short while ago,
we received the profoundly
disturbing news
that a Sinner has appeared
in the World of the Living.
A Sinner? Impossible!
Excuse me. When you say
"Sinners", you're talking
about the beings that
reside in Hell, right?
[Jushiro]
When people die, their souls
are sent to the Soul Society,
the home of souls.
However, the souls of
people who committed
heinous crimes while alive
are unable to enter the
Soul Society and are
plunged instead into Hell.
For their crimes, these Sinners
are bound in chains and
condemned for all eternity.
This is the first time in the
history of the Soul Society that
a Sinner, a resident of Hell,
has escaped his bonds and
found his way back to the
World of the Living.
It can only mean one thing. That
something's gone terribly wrong
down there.
I doubt that. There are
gatekeepers of Hell who're
known as Kushanaada and
their control is absolute.
Yes. But I've heard there are
other beings living deep in the
bowels of Hell, beings with
great and mysterious powers.
Whatever. If these things are
suddenly free to stroll in and
out of the World of the Living,
we've got a big
problem on our hands.
The situation is grave.
I propose we send Renji Abarai
and Rukia Kuchiki back to the
World of the Living,
since it was they who first
encountered this Sinner.
And should the need arise,
I will provide them with
the procedures necessary
to infiltrate Hell itself
and safely return.
Captain, will we be asking
Substitute Soul Reaper Ichigo
Kurosaki for his help?
No. We must not.
(c.m. surprise grunt)
In fact, I want you to be
sure to give both Abarai
and Kuchiki strict orders
not to involve the Substitute
Soul Reaper in this matter.
Not under any circumstances.
[coughs]
[deep voice]
Szayelaporro.
Oh. Aaroniero.
Well, well. Yes, I thought I
sensed someone else there,
falling alongside of me.
So I guess it was you, was it?
I must say, that's one sturdy
fish tank you've got there.
Huh. Were you hoping
it would break?
No! Well, at least not
before I got the chance
to crack it open
and run a full chemical
analysis on the liquid
sloshing around in there.
Shut up, you bastard!
I don't know what this place
is, but Lord Aizen's not
around to protect you here!
You'll get a better idea of
what's inside me when my
Glotoneria devours you!
Knock it off!
Oh?
Didn't you just say it
yourself? We don't even
know what place this is.
Why don't we find out where we
are first, before spending our
energy killing each other?
Might be a more
productive use of time.
I really don't care
where we are.
Ditto. There's plenty
of time for that later,
after I watch you die.
I don't think you're grasping
the difference in our abilities.
I'm Espada Number Eight and
you're Number Nine, remember?
However you do the math,
you come up short.
We'll see about that!
Heh heh heh heh.
You two are funny.
So you're wondering where
you are, eh? If you really
want to know, I'll tell you.
Welcome to Hell.
[Aaroniero]
Who are you, anyway?
Why don't you come down
here if you're so tough?
Heh. You're hilarious.
The way you go on and on
about killing each other.
You two are in Hell,
you're already dead.
Just what kind of
nonsense is that?!
Indeed, you're right.
Thanks for jogging my
memory, whoever you are.
Yes, it seems I did die.
And I have that damned
despicable Soul Reaper
to thank for it.
So the question now is, is
there a way to get out of this
infernal wasteland you call
Hell and return to Hueco Mundo?
Of course there isn't,
don't be ridiculous.
You sure of that?
You'd better tell
us if there is.
Let's begin again.
My name's Shuren.
And the only way you will
survive here is if you do
exactly as I say, understood?
Oh, is that right?
Taikon,
Gunjo,
Garogai.
Our guests don't seem
to like Hell very much.
Teach them to be
more appreciative
of our hospitality.
Raaaaghh!
Aaroniero!
Auggh!
A Gran Ray Cero, eh?
So that's an Espada's Cero.
Disappointing, I must say.
Sorry to have to tell you this,
but you're of no use to me.
That does it! Don't get
cocky with me, Sinner!
[Shuren]
I knew it. Their power
was nowhere near great
enough to open the gate.
Gunjo, what about the
one we sent to the
World of the Living?
Sir. He survived
and has returned.
As he was of no further
use, I silenced him.
But the experiment succeeded.
I see!
Then my friends, it would seem
our days in the darkness are
about to come to an end.
As I've suspected,
it will have to be you.
I'm going to bring you down,
Ichigo Kurosaki.
[Renji]
Thank goodness you're
all right, Rukia.
[Rukia]
Thanks for the help, Renji.
Now let's get on back to
the Soul Society.
[Renji]
Right. I'm only glad no one else
got banged up besides us.
[Rukia]
Yeah. Let's just hope there
are no more surprises.
[Zennosuke]
Zennosuke Kurumad-- Auugh!