[theme music]
NARRATOR: In order
to save Orihime,
who was kidnapped
by the Arrancars,
Ichigo, Chad, Uryu,
Rukia, and Renji
have all snuck into Hueco
Mundo, the realm of the Hollows.
The journey to Aizen's
fortress has been hard fought,
as our heroes have struggled
against endless attacks
from the Arrancar forces.
Upon breaking into the
fortress, the group
split up and took five different
paths in search of Orihime.
Each path was guarded by
members or fallen members
of the Espada, and
our heroes found
themselves locked
in desperate battles
against deadly opponents.
-Whirl, Giralda!
Come on!
The time is finally here.
Let the great battle commence.
Now, at full strength, fight!
Fight, nino!
-All right then.
-That wasn't even good enough
to be a warm up exercise.
-Hado number 73!
Soren Sokatsui!
-You blew your chance.
If you had the skills to hit
us directly with that Kido,
you might have easily
inflicted a serious injury.
-It was critically important
to me, and it proved my point.
I had to reassure myself that
you weren't actually Kaien.
Now that I know the truth,
I have no reservations
about this battle.
I can fight you without
holding back and destroy you.
-It's the end game.
Allow me to demonstrate for you.
I'll show you what an Espada
sword release actually
looks like.
Devour her!
-Glotoneria!
-Damn it.
-Now watch this!
Spin around!
Aw, what's wrong?
You're not giving
up already, are you?
URYU (VOICEOVER):
I'm in trouble here.
-You can't keep that up forever.
You're just wasting your time.
-Damn.
-Oh hot dang.
I'm really in trouble now.
PESCHE (VOICEOVER):
I should've known
it was a mistake to follow the
weakest looking of those five
intruders.
His opponent is so strong.
I don't think he has a chance.
What should I do?
There's no way he can survive
against this Arrancar.
I guess I should save him.
Wait a minute.
I need to think
carefully about this.
What would I be able
to do out there?
Well, I can't let
him face her alone.
Maybe I can sneak up on
her before she sees me.
she's really hot
from this angle.
I can almost see her panties.
-Aw.
How does that feel,
Mr. Four-Eyes?
Did you get a boo boo?
It appears to me you don't even
have the strength to respond.
It's time for the final-- Hm?
PESCHE (VOICEOVER):
I'm almost in position.
Just a little bit further.
-And who are you,
you little insect?
-Ow.
-Wait.
You're Pesche Gautiche,
if I remember correctly.
PESCHE (VOICEOVER): What?
Impossible.
I can't believe he
remembered my whole name.
He only head it once.
And-- And you're Uryu
Ushida, aren't you?
-Yeah, that's right.
PESCHE (VOICEOVER):
He's smiling at me.
Could it be?
You like me!
Don't you?
-What?
Where are you coming
up with this stuff?
I'm just trying
to get out of here
without getting blown to bits!
-Will you both shut your mouths?
Ugh.
And what are you
supposed to be, goofball?
A big termite.
-How dare you?
That is insulting.
At the very least, refer
to me as a stag beetle.
-They're not really
that different.
-Termites are little, white
bugs who hide from the light.
Stag beetles are
shiny, black, and cool.
-Excuse me.
You're wearing white.
-Who are you to talk?
You're wearing more
white than I am.
You'd never make it
as a stag beetle.
-Hey, why are you
comparing me to an insect?
It doesn't matter
what color I wear.
I'm proud of your whites.
-You gotta be kidding.
You're proud of your whites?
You sound like some kind
of detergent commercial.
-Are you making fun of me?
-I told you both to
shut your mouths!
Ha.
Well, well, isn't that sweet?
you're friends
with that termite.
-You're way off base.
He's a Hollow.
He's no friend of mine.
-How can you be so cruel?
Just when we were starting
to get to know each other.
-Be quiet.
-A lover's spat?
-How could you
treat me like this?
You remembered my name?
-Are you stupid.
I said I wasn't
your friend in order
to keep her from attacking you.
I was trying to save your life.
-I appreciate your kindness.
It almost worked.
-It would've worked
if you would shut up!
I don't even
understand why you're
following me in the first place.
Ichigo told you all to go home.
-I'm glad you brought that up.
You've touched on a very
important point, Uryu.
-You're getting
pretty chummy, pal.
-The fact is, I'm
actually looking for Nel.
After you guys ran away,
she went chasing after you,
screaming for that guy Ichigo.
I took off in the direction
I thought she had gone,
but I can't find her
or this Ichigo person.
Wait!
I've got it.
Could it be that you
are actually Ichigo?
-I'm Uryu, you nut job.
You even called me Uryu
just a few minutes ago.
-Ichigo is the spiky
haired Soul Reaper.
Don't you remember?
-Spiky hair?
But there were two of those.
Which one was he?
-He was the orange one.
If you had paid attention,
you'd know who is who.
-What are you two
babbling about?
-Now look what you've done.
Because I was dealing with
you, she's caught up to us.
-No.
Leave this lady to me, Uryu.
-What are you talking about?
You'll never defeat
her in battle.
You don't have the power.
-I-It'll be all
right, my friend.
You don't know this, but
I have a special ability.
-Oh, yeah?
And what would that be?
-I can create a fluid
that makes anything
it touches incredibly slimy.
-That's completely useless.
-All right.
You two are starting
to get on my nerves!
-Stop, Pesche.
She'll destroy you.
-She'll never get the chance.
-Look out!
She's aiming right for you!
-What?
-He did it.
-Ha ha ha ha ha!
Did you see that?
Your weapon had no effect on me.
You're not so
powerful after all.
You're just a cranky Arrancar.
I didn't want to see
your panties, anyway.
-What?
You were peeking, weren't you?
-Uh, no.
Not exactly.
I mean, I might have seen
what color they were,
but I couldn't
make out the brand.
Hey, and you should wear pants
if you're gonna attack people.
Wait.
What are you looking
at me like that for?
I told you, even if I wanted
to, I didn't get a good look.
-Oh, yeah?
-Come on.
You at least know I'm
telling the truth.
You have to back me up here.
-No, I don't.
-Excuse me?
I can hear you, you know?
Do you think I'm
deaf, or something?
-Oh, that hurts!
Now I'm mad.
You obviously haven't
learned your lesson
from my special attack.
-You want a lesson?
Try this!
Ah!
Huh?
You save d life, Uryu.
I thank you for that.
-I don't need the thanks.
Just stop provoking her.
-All right.
But I must repay you for
your kindness in saving me.
I won't provoke her anymore.
I'll just defeat her, and that
way you and I will be even.
-I can see this isn't
going to go well.
-So you're going to
defeat me, are you?
-I would have done
it before, but I
was showing you some mercy.
-Hey, thanks for that.
You going to be firing
that strange liquid again?
-Don't you weren't warned.
-Is that all you've got?
I have no intention of getting
near that stuff, so spit away,
termite boy.
-Huh?
Ah!
Oh!
Ow!
[crash]
-All right!
I can produce an infinite
amount of this fluid.
You made a big mistake
in underestimating me.
-Is that even possible?
PESCHE: Ha ha ha.
I call this liquid
Infinite Slick.
-OK, it works, and the
name is pretty cool.
What could be more annoying?
You know, you should run away
while you have the chance.
-Why?
URYU: Isn't it obvious?
You caught her by
surprise this time,
but she won't fall
for that trick again.
-Rip, Golondrina!
From the way you've
been reacting,
you don't take me
very seriously.
You're the first enemy I've
encountered in a while,
so I was going to
take my time with you.
-Huh?
-But now I've change my mind.
You've irritated me.
I, Cirucci Sanderwicci,
Arrancar number 105,
am going to crush you.
Now, let me see.
Which one of you shall
I slice up first?
Now, let me see.
Which one of you shall
I slice up first?
-Ah!
-Wah!
-Hah!
You can run pretty fast
there, can't you, four eyes?
-Ah!
She's like a lumberjack
with a chainsaw!
-Ha ha ha!
What's your hurry, boys?
I'm not finished yet.
-I'm not gonna run away
from her like this all day.
-Well then, let's join forces
and take her on together.
Are you just gonna stand
there and ignore me?
It's humiliating!
-Enough already!
I'll make this quick.
I'm going to cut the two of
you into tiny little pieces
and feed you to your friends.
-She is one sick puppy.
You just figured that out?
-Good.
At least you're paying
attention to me.
Hey, wait!
-Hah!
Not so fast, four eyes.
Haven't started carving yet.
-I see.
Those wings are shielding
her from my attacks.
That explains the reverberation
I've been hearing.
Those feathers are all
vibrating at very high speeds.
-That weapon won't
work on me, you fool!
Get the picture?
Quit hiding, four eyes.
I've got something for you.
Hm?
I told you that
weapon won't work.
PESCHE: Hey, Uryu?
Just wanted to remind
you I'm still here!
-That's great.
But why?
I thought I told
you to run away.
-I think you've been
trying to protect me why.
Else would you keep
attacking this woman
even though it's hopeless?
-Well, it won't be hopeless
if you stay out of my way.
Now, get lost.
-Stop there, Cirucci.
-Huh?
-There's a saying that he
who chases after two hairs
catches neither.
You should quit chasing
after my friend here,
and focus your attention
on me, instead.
-You're an idiot!
-Fine, mean whatever you say.
-Didn't she even want to
think about it for a minute?
Wait.
Why are you in the
line of fire, Uryu?
I'm trying to protect you,
in case you didn't notice.
-Try and follow what
I'm saying to you.
I don't want your protection.
-The tone of your voice
tells me you don't mean that,
so I'll fight alongside you.
-Argh.
-If you morons have
finally got this settled,
I will now slice you
both into pieces!
-I have to do something
about those feathers.
-Do we have any strategy
in mind besides running?
-Actually-- Pesche!
Get ready to use your
Infinite Slick again!
-My infinite what?
What are you talking about?
-Infinite Slick, you idiot!
That's the weird
fluid from before.
That's the name you
gave it, remember?
-I have a lot of names in
my head, like Joe, or Sam.
You expect me to
remember 'em all?
-Just make some of it now,
or I'll make you make some!
-Heh, heh, heh.
Well, that proves my theory.
You're helpless without me.
OK.
Here we go.
Unfortunately, it
appears I'm all out.
-What do you mean?
Didn't you call
it Infinite Slick
because it would never run out?
-I may have exaggerated.
-You lied!
-Well, I wouldn't
exactly call it a lie.
I just wanted to
give the impression
that I could make endless
amounts of it if I needed to.
-You were lying!
-Yeah.
I lied.
Sorry.
URYU: Why would you lie to me?
PESCHE: You were
putting pressure on me,
and frankly, it
sounded a lot cooler!
URYU: How cool is it going
to be when we're dead?
-That's not fair!
Sometimes you make stuff up
just to go with the flow!
-The only thing that's going to
be flowing here is our blood!
-Ah-- wah!
-That's just great!
Now I've seen it all.
You've gone and attacked
yourself with your own weapon!
-Nice move.
Allow me to finish
what you've started.
[shout]
[laughter]
URYU: You should check
your name, Cirucci.
-Mm.
I know about that move.
It's called a Flash
Step, isn't it?
-Nice guess.
But mine is called Hirenkyaku.
-Ah.
Hirenkyaku, huh?
Interesting.
All right.
Let's see if I can
tell the difference.
[whimpering]
-He got away again.
Ha.
So, you seem to be pretty
good at running for cover.
But how long do you think
you can keep that up
while carrying that dead weight?
PESCHE (VOICEOVER): She may
be a nasty piece of work,
but she's telling the truth.
As long as Uryu
has me on his back,
he won't be able to attack her.
[laughter]
PESCHE (VOICEOVER): She's
becoming more accurate.
We can't keep on like this.
Oh, I think I'm a
burden to you, Uryu!
I can't let you lose the battle!
Use me as a shield
to create an opening!
Goodbye!
Go on, leave my corpse behind!
[crying]
-Now what?
Why are you crying?
-Huh?
-You are the biggest
freak I've ever met.
-Shut up, you big bully.
I just got carried away with
the beauty of my sacrifice.
-Pesche.
-Yes?
-This may hurt you a
bit, but you'll be OK.
-What?
You're not actually planning
to use me as a shield
and leave my corpse
behind, are you?
Wah!
Whoa!
Ah!
Whose side are you on?
Wah!
-Sorry about that, Pesche.
I had no choice.
Now I can concentrate
on winning this fight.
-Say goodnight, four eyes!
URYU (VOICEOVER): I see.
The blades continue to
vibrate even after they've
separated from her body.
The blades easily reload
onto the frame of the wing.
As long as those
wings are operative,
I have no opening to
attack at close range.
It's apparent that my long
distance attacks will always
be deflected by her feathers
before they can impact.
-All right!
Let's see you get
away from this!
URYU (VOICEOVER):
I have no choice.
[gasp]
-What the hell?
What is that?
-It's too bad.
I was really hoping to
hold off on using this
until much later in the battle.
So, shall we continue?
[theme music]
PESCHE: Prepare
yourself, Cirucci!
We're about to unleash
our special combined
attack of friendship,
Infinite Pesche Quincy!
CIRUCCI: Bring it on!
I'll repel it with my
vibrating feathers!
URYU: Sorry to put
a damper on things,
but not only is he not
going to fight you,
his attack technique
doesn't even exist.