ICHIGO (NARRATING):
I'm Ichigo Kurasaki.
And other than having the
ability to see spirits,
I used to be an ordinary
high school student.
But the day I met
Rukia Kuchiki, I
was given the powers
of a soul reaper
in order to protect the
world of the living.
As I began my work as a
substitute soul reaper,
I found myself thrown into
a never ending battle.
In the midst of everything,
my best friend Orihime Inoue
was abducted by ex soul
reaper captain Sosuke Aizen.
My friends Chad and
Udi you joined me
as I raced to rescue Orihime.
Once we arrived in Hueco
Mundo, we entered a fight
with powerful enemies
known as arrancars.
We were too late to
keep Aizen from entering
the world of the living But
luckily, the 13 court guard
squads were already
there to stop it.
An all out war was
about to begin!
[theme music]
[foreign language]
NARRATOR: Soul
reapers and arrancars
faced off against each other
throughout Karakura Town.
Rangiku Matsumoto
squared off against three
of Harribel's proxiones,
Apacci, Mila Rose, and Sung-Sun.
Rangiku noticed that her three
opponents did not get along
and tried to use that
to her advantages
as she confronted them.
But fighting three
against one took its toll,
and gradually pushed
her into a corner.
Then an unexpected
helper suddenly appeared.
-[gasp]
Like I said, you
don't stand a chance!
Nice try!
You don't have what
it takes to handle me,
let alone the three of us.
[gasp]
-[grunt]
What?
It's you.
Momo.
-Not bad.
And she's a lieutenant, no less.
Not that it matters, though.
An extra lieutenant doesn't
really change the equation.
Sorry, cow.
Time to die.
-[gasp]
-What the-- what is this?
-Now snap.
Tobiume!
-[grunting]
-[panting]
-Are you sure you're
all right, Momo?
-Yes.
Sorry about that.
I had never used that
combination of techniques
before.
RANGIKU (VOICEOVER): Incredible.
Having the ability
to combine several
of these kido in her
own unique fashion?
[gasp]
-Thrust, Cierva!
-Eat your fill, Liona!
-Strangled to death, Anaconda!
-[grunt]
-It can't be!
-[battle cry]
[grunting]
Take that and that and that!
[grunting] That!
-What's bothering you?
-Your partner over there.
Lilinette is the
name she goes by?
She's pretty wild.
You all right with that?
-[grunting]
-She's not very effective.
Why don't you say
something to her?
-[sigh]
I gave up trying.
She never listens to me.
But so what?
Why do you care?
I would expect you to
be concentrating more
on your own situation.
-How polite of you.
You wouldn't want
me to lose focus.
-[battle cry]
-Bakudo number eight.
Seki.
-[battle cry]
[groan]
[grunting]
No way.
-I've been in many
battles, and I've
seen hundreds of
different ceros.
So I'm going to
tell you the truth.
Your cero is immature.
It's not even at
the level of Menos.
As you just observed,
I can knock it down
with my bare hands.
You are completely unmatched.
You should stop and go home.
I'll give you one
chance to withdraw.
If you continue, you're
facing certain death.
-I didn't think
my attack would be
enough to outright defeat them.
But they're virtually unscathed.
-Their injuries heal when
they take resurrection form.
That's how they've all
managed to make it this far.
-[grunt]
Sorry I haven't been
more help to you.
-Mila Rose.
Sung-Sun.
Let's get this over with.
It's time to end
this silly battle
and get back to Master Harribel.
-I don't know why you're getting
so worked up over these two.
We're going to need
to step up our game.
-No other choice, really.
-Man, I can't
fricking believe this.
We're really going to waste
it on this pair of losers?
-[grunt]
-Quimera Parca.
-[gasp]
What the?
What in the world is that?
-[gasp]
-Quimera Parca.
It's our pet, created
when the three of us
combine our left arms together.
You have to admit,
he's a work of art.
We like to call him Ayon.
-[gasp]
RANGIKU (NARRATING): Why do I
feel so cold all of a sudden?
It's like I'm peering
into a deep pit,
and the bottom is so far
away I can't even see it.
-[grunting]
-Just the kind of
strength I'd expect
from someone who's achieved
the rank of captain.
-If you continue to waste time
talking, you will be destroyed.
You won't escape next time.
-[grunt]
-[moaning]
-[gasp]
Haineko!
[cry]
[moaning]
-Oh, did I forget to warn you?
Ayon is deadly, so
you have to be careful
when you're around him.
-[moaning]
-[cry]
Rangiku!
-[gasp]
[grunting]
Rangiku.
-Rangiku!
Rangiku!
Bakudo number 37, Tsuriboshi!
-[gasp]
-Don't worry, Rangiku.
I'm going to heal your injuries!
MOMO (NARRATING):
He really got her.
He smashed her from just
bellow the ribs down
through the intestinal area.
She can't breathe
with these injuries.
I have to hurry!
[gasp]
[moaning]
There are broken bones
throughout my body.
Both Rungiku and myself
have been taken out
within moments of each other.
This is crazy.
There is no way we can
win against this thing.
-Bakudo number 37, Tsuriboshi!
-[gasp]
Izuru.
Shuhei.
-You did an extremely effective
job holding him off, Momo.
Rest a while.
Izuru.
Let's get rid of this monster.
-What the?
Who are these bozos?
SPEAKER (OFFSCREEN):
They must be her friends.
I saw them coming from the
direction of the pillars.
-So if you saw them coming, why
didn't you try and stop them?
I thought you were in
a much better position
to see their approach.
Or are your eyes just useless
holes sitting on your face?
-What's that?
-Stop it, both of you.
We're right in the
middle of a battle.
Concentrate!
-Hmph.
-[grunt]
-They must be here to
help their friends.
What is it with these guys?
They love to interfere in
other people's battles.
Ayon!
Don't give them the
opportunity to butt in.
Kill them both now!
Ayon!
[groan]
Looks to me like he's
trying to ignore us.
-Don't be stupid.
Look at him.
What makes you think he has the
capacity to hear a word we say?
-Well, he's got to have eardrums
on him somewhere, doesn't he?
-I'm not absolutely sure.
I've never seen him react
when we speak to him.
Maybe he just reads our minds.
But apart from
that, would you mind
not asking me to agree with
you when we're having to fight?
It's very annoying.
-Really?
I have to presume that Ayon
gets his nasty side from you.
-That may be so, but he
gets his face from you.
Those ugly horns are
exactly like yours.
-Don't force me to kill you
before I kill those soul
reapers.
-This fighting stops now!
It doesn't matter
who Ayon takes after.
-That's because he gets
his temperament from you.
I'm sure he's doomed to
be alone and unmarried
because no one can stand him.
-Get bent, lady!
[interposing voices]
-What are those women
screaming about up there?
They've lost it.
-Yeah.
Don't worry about them, Izuru.
-You're right.
-Know what?
I'm going to kill
both of you, some day!
-If you've got the
game, bring it all!
-Mmm-hmm.
-I knew it was a bad
idea to bring him out.
He's nearly uncontrollable.
-Izuru.
I'll handle this guy.
You can go take care
of Momo and Rangiku.
-[groan]
Wait a minute.
You sure you want
to fight him alone?
-Who said anything
about fighting alone?
After you've done
emergency first aid,
hide them both using Kido,
then come back here to help!
-Rangiku needs assistance
quickly or she might die.
Don't forget, you're a
former member of squad four.
-I'm afraid that
was a long time ago.
-I'm counting on you.
-All right.
Let's do it.
-What the hell?
Why are you just
standing there, Ayon?
They just grabbed that big cow!
-Bakudo number 73.
Tozansho!
I'll heal your injuries
as soon as as I can.
Just hang in there, Momo!
-Don't worry, I'm all right.
It's Rangiku.
Hurry up and help her!
[gasp]
IZURU (NARRATING): Momo's
in pretty bad shape herself.
She's either got a broken rib
or even worse-- one of her lungs
is collapsed.
However, Rangiku's condition
is even more critical.
Here goes.
I hope my healing
skills are still sharp.
SHUHEI (NARRATING): This
thing is a complete unknown.
I'd better try and
evaluate its capabilities.
Hado number 11, Tsuzuri Raiden!
Didn't have an effect.
[grunt]
-Well, now That was
a pretty good move.
-This one's stronger than
either of those two cows.
-Ha.
In my opinion, they're all the
same, judging by that attack.
SHUHEI (NARRATING):
It was effective.
I can beat him!
This thing's weakness is Kido!
[scream]
[gasp]
-Surprise!
-Damn monster.
He had no trouble breaking free.
He's a lot more powerful
than I suspected.
Damn it!
-Shuhei!
-[grunting]
IZURU (NARRATING): I've got
to finish healing Rangiku.
-[grunting]
Let go of me!
[grunting]
[gasp]
[moaning]
TETSUZAEMON (NARRATING):
It hasn't noticed me
yet I think I've got it.
[gasp]
[scream]
-Tetsuzaemon!
[moaning]
-I guess this fight's over.
That was fast.
-I thought they'd be able to
generate a much better effort.
How disappointing.
APACCI (OFFSCREEN): Ayon
was too strong for them,
and they were too cocky.
It serves them right.
Ayon, hurry up so you can
finish off the rest of them!
-[MOANING
-[gasp]
[gasp]
It's coming!
Damn it!
I need a little more time!
I'm so close to finishing!
Come on, Rangiku.
You're almost there!
[gasp]
Inexcusable!
Making your head captain come
out here to the front lines?
You squad members are
quite a disappointment.
[theme music]
[foreign language]
SPEAKER (NARRATING): Let's go.
Our battle has just begun.
SPEAKER (NARRATING):
You're right.
Our battle has just begun!
SPEAKER (NARRATING):
Isn't that what
they say just before
they cancel your series!
SPEAKER (NARRATING):
All right, soul reapers.
It's time to focus.
Our battle has just begin!
SPEAKER (NARRATING):
Head captain,
do you know something we don't?