[Inaba]
I've underestimated all your
powers? Is that what you said?
Yes. Is it not true?
I've never been very
interested in what others do.
So it's difficult for me
to say that I truly know
all of you thoroughly.
But, Captain Unohana.
Don't you think that the
same could be said of you?
What do you mean by that?
Oh, you'll find out.
[gasp]
Captain Unohana.
You'll have to forgive me.
I've already collected
your Reishi.
And it's all thanks to
the Lieutenant Kotetsu
that I created!
What are you going to do now?
Heh heh heh heh heh!
Got to give the old man credit.
He's good.
How you holding up,
Shunsui?
Not bad. I still have
a bit more left in me.
Hmm.
[Toshiro]
I've been expecting you,
Byakuya.
I'm just going to
cut to the chase.
My orders are to stop
anyone from getting
through past this point.
If you wish to turn back and
leave, now's your chance.
You stand in my way,
and I will eliminate you.
That makes this an
easy choice, then.
Bankai! Daiguren Hyorinmaru!
Yaaaaah!
Oh! Kisuke.
So it seems everyone's
reached the Soul Society
except Captain Komamura.
Wait, how were you able to get
that information from here?
Well, we'd be at a huge
disadvantage if we couldn't tell
what's going on over there.
So I placed devices
on the captains that
transmit back to us.
Kisuke.
I can't just sit here!
You have to send me to
the Soul Society!
Huh?
But Ichigo!
What're you
talking about?!
This isn't the time
to be resting!
I've gotta go help them!
Just calm down!
Let the others handle
the Soul Society!
I mean, look at this!
The ladies are
still in a coma!
And let's not even get
started on how messed up
the guys got out there!
Bed-ridden,
Soul Reapers,
and Four-Eyes!
That's it. Next time your
threads start unraveling,
you're on your own!
That's all we have around here!
And why am I being lumped with
the others? I'm not injured!
And right now, each one of them
is more useless than the last!
There's almost no one who
can put up a decent fight.
If you leave, who
knows what'll happen
if we're attacked!
You're the one who
said you'd protect
Nozomi, remember?
You promised!
How're you going to do that
if you're not around?!
And besides Ichigo,
you really do need
some rest.
Yeah, listen to Orihime!
Be a good boy and stay
right here!
[Nozomi]
Can I ask a question?
Hmm?
Yeah. Sure.
What is it?
Why are you so
determined to protect me?
What's in it for you?
Oh! Well, because uh...
Eh, that's a good question...
Who knows?
Uh?
I guess I don't
really know myself.
Seriously!?
He doesn't know?!
Well, at first, it was
less about protecting you,
and more about protecting my
friends in the World of the
Living by stopping Kageroza.
Wow, talk about being blunt!
Then maybe if I had just
stayed in the Precipice World...
No!
You always keep trying to
take everything on yourself.
I'm Sorry, but I'm not
gonna let you do that.
If you don't want to
tell us your story, fine.
I've told you that before.
But you knew that
something terrible would
happen if Kageroza caught
you, didn't you Nozomi?
You don't have to
do this yourself!
You aren't alone anymore.
Not alone...?
[gasp]
[Kon]
Hey...
Hey!
[startled]
Whuh?
What's going
on with you?
It's nothing.
Anyway, I don't know why
I want to protect you.
Except that I heard a voice,
And it told me I'm supposed
to help you out.
Are you some kind of idiot?
Hey, you don't call someone
an idiot to their face!
Especially not
somebody who
saved you!
It's just... I didn't
hear any voice.
Listen, kid, you're kinda
missing the whole point here.
[chuckle]
Heh, boy, you really are
an idiot, aren't you?
Heh.
Stop calling me that.
It's Ichigo.
This should help restore
some of your Spirit Energy.
That's a form of
Kido, isn't it?
And I thought you
were just a kid
with an attitude.
Stop calling me that.
It's Nozomi Kujo.
All right.
I'll remember that.
Bakudo Number Sixty-Two!
Hyapporankan!
Bakudo Number Sixty-Three!
Sajosabaku!
Hado Number Eighty-Eight!
Hiryu Gekizoku Shinten Raiho!
No incantation!
Bakudo Number Eighty-One! Danku!
Lieutenant Kotetsu.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
[Isane]
Where's the original
Captain Unohana?
She's a wise woman
and a wily opponent.
She never really had
any intention of
fighting us at all.
So it would
appear.
But, I don't
understand.
She knew that she didn't have
much of a chance to win this
fight, especially not when it
was three against one.
And if she were to die here,
the original captains would lose
their only means to heal and
recover in the Soul Society.
Someone who would take the
risk of fighting us anyway
would not be fit to be
captain of Squad Four.
Then right from
the start?
Yes, that Kido was
apparently only
meant to distract
us from her escape.
She pulled a
fast one on us.
Well then, we need
to get moving.
Yaaaaahh!
Sennen Hyoro!
[gasp]
Enough.
You really thought
you could fool me
with this ice double?
No, you're too smart
for all that.
I am well aware of
your skills, Byakuya.
Trying to capture you
will be no easy task.
Huuah!
One question.
A question from you?
How unusual!
Why?
What do you mean?
Why would someone of
your caliber choose
to follow that man?
What, Kageroza?
If you knew,
would it matter?
Never mind.
There's someone I want to
protect no matter what.
In order to keep her safe,
I'll do whatever it takes!
Sennen Hyoro!
The same technique again?
Huuaah!
So that's his strategy;
To limit my range and prevent
me from moving freely by
creating these pillars of ice.
Sorry, Byakuya.
My goal is to settle the
score with my original.
What I'm determined to
protect, my original
wants to protect as well.
But he doesn't have
what it takes!
Don't you see?!
Only the power Kageroza gave me
will make it possible!
So until she's safe,
I cannot lose to anyone!
Hyoryusenbi!
Bankai.
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
[gasp]
Using any means necessary,
including the powers of
another.
That is how someone
with no honor thinks.
I won't lose to someone who's
tossed away their pride.
Yaaah!
What?!
Are you all right, Jushiro?
Yes. But I'm no match for
the power of those flames.
What will it be, young ones?
Even with only one arm,
my powers are more than
enough to stop both of
you from taking me down!
Yes, you're right.
However...
We're not done yet!
Pathetic!
You've already
reached your limits!
Cut us some slack!
You're just too
strong, Old Man Yama!
Earlier in our fight,
you said something
about having honor.
Yes, that's right.
We still have our honor.
Is this your idea
of having "honor"?!
The real versions of the two
of you would follow through
on their convictions
regardless of my wishes,
but they would
never compromise
their true nature.
I know that more than anyone.
But you two lack the
original's conviction.
To my eyes, it's nothing more
than a rebellion by impostors.
That really hurts, coming
from you, Old Man Yama.
Master Genryusai.
Certainly, to you
originals,
what we're doing might seem
like a selfish rebellion
by mere pretenders.
But still! We Reigai have our
own way of pursuing our beliefs!
And what's that?
We cannot tell you
that just yet.
Well, then, I have no
choice but to crush you!
Huh?
Wait, is that...?
Seems she finally
decided to show up!
[Jushiro]
Captain Unohana!
[Shunsui]
You sure took your sweet
time getting here!
I noticed right from the
beginning that the two of you
were fighting at full power,
even willing to throw away your
lives in order to kill me.
As if you were in a
hurry to end this fight.
But it seems I was mistaken.
Yes.
Sorry about that,
Old Man Yama.
It wasn't that we
were in a hurry.
See, we were able to push
ourselves to our limits,
thanks to her.
Please understand, sir.
Unless we did that,
we had no chance
of winning against
you at all.
Fine, then.
It does not change the fact that
this is a fight to the death!
[panting]
You think I've thrown
away my pride?
I suppose it might appear
that way, I'll grant you that.
After all, we can never
become the originals.
And even if we defeat
the originals,
Reigai are still Reigai.
And that's precisely the reason
why I will use any and all means
to protect my own intentions!
That's the one thing I can hold
onto with pride as a Reigai!
You probably think I kept
using Sennen Hyoro in order
to restrict your range,
and also take
away your freedom
of movement.
But you would be wrong.
By using Sennen Hyoro to
establish a perimeter
around you, I forced you
to destroy it.
Someone like you, who
uses speed as a weapon,
would surely have to keep
their surroundings clear.
[gasp]
When you destroyed that ice,
it turned into a powdery snow.
It obscured our vision,
and created the opportunity
I needed for my next move.
Hyoten Hyakkaso.
[gasp]
There's no way for
you to escape now!
That should have restored
some of your Spirit Energy.
Aah! It's just like that
time when Miss Unohana
healed me. Awesome!
Seriously?!
[weary faint]
Hey, watch out!
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Maybe that effort was
more taxing on your
body than usual
'cause you haven't
used your Soul Reaper
powers in a while.
Can you stand up?
Yeah.
Why's no one worried about me?!
[Ichigo]
Kisuke.
[startled]
Nh!
Yes?
Send me in.
Are you sure, Ichigo?
If I just wait, I'm
going to start losing
my Spirit Energy again.
Right now, I'm strong enough
to take the fight to them!
Ichigo, you can't!
Kon, accept it.
No, I won't!
Ah! Say something!
Stop this fool
from doing this!
We could try,
but I doubt
he'd listen.
[dripping with sarcasm]
Sure, he won't listen,
so don't even try!
You won't stop him
that way, Four-Eyes!
We'll manage on our own
here somehow, Ichigo.
We promise that we'll
find a way to keep Nozomi
safe while you're gone.
Agh! You guys are hopeless!
Why are all of you so stupid?!
Fine, go take care of
that bastard Kageroza
and get back here!
Just be quick about it!
Yeah, I will.
Alright, Kisuke.
Very well then.
But let me say
this first.
Returning to the Soul Society
is going to be far riskier than
when you went the first time.
Are you sure you
want to do this?
You bet!
I'm damn sure!
All right. Let's
get you ready then.
Ah!
Huh?
Spiritual Pressure...
What's going on?
What?!
Ngh!
[panting]
You're still alive, Byakuya?!
How can this be?!
If my Senbonzakura had been
even a moment later...
...I would have
been in trouble.
You're good, it's true, but as
long as there's moisture in the
air, I still have the advantage.
There!
Yaaah!
It felt like I hit him.
What is this?!
[gasp]
Gokei.
Senbonzakura Kageyoshi.
Should've known.
There is one thing...
that the both of us share.
To protect my pride...
I'll use any means necessary.
Hey, What's with the
sad face, Nozomi?
Nothing,
I'm okay.
Don't worry; you'll be safe.
Everyone's going to be looking
out for you while I'm gone.
Kon. Got that?
Yeah, of course!
I've looked after
her this long.
She's in good hands!
Right. Hold onto him like
he's a good luck charm.
Whaddaya mean,
good luck charm?!
Ichigo, be very
careful, all right?
Yeah.
Now get going and
finish this already!
You got it!
Ichigo.
Mm?
Please come back.
Ah.
[chuckle]
Yeah, I promise.
Well, I better get going!
Rest assured.
Nozomi will return to us.
I promise.
[Jushiro]
Seems Captain Hitsugaya's
Reigai has fallen.
[Shunsui]
Yes, how unfortunate.
[Jushiro]
Indeed.
This life-size toy figure
and box full of candies I
had prepared for him will
now go to waste.
[Shunsui]
He wouldn't have
liked it anyway...
[Jushiro]
You think so?