[charging up yell]
Huuaahh!
Don't tell me you really
think you can stop me with
the power you possess now!
It's hopeless!
[gasp]
Hm?!
Hyaaaahh!
So what do you mean by that?
Take a look at this world!
This world of yours used
to be full of hope,
filled with skyscrapers!
Now it looks like the
rundown small town it is!
This place has
sunk to a new low!
The rain that continued to fall
on this world has subsided, but
now everything has submerged
itself into this ocean!
And this all happened
because you lost hope and
stopped moving forward!
Augh!
I cannot leave you like this.
I know what has to happen.
I will rip out the
root of your despair!
Huaagh!
It's been a long time, Ichigo.
What's with that look of yours?
Don't act like you
don't know me!
What? You again?
Heh.
But how?
[Ichigo]
I watched you disappear after I
defeated you in our last fight!
Huh. So, did you forget?
I warned you. The only way
you could really control
me was to stay alive.
At least until the
next time I showed up!
[gasp]
Damn!
And all this time,
I thought I had
destroyed you for good.
Oh really? Well,
too bad for you.
So what's up with the new look?
It looks ridiculous on you.
That's right. This is
your first time seeing
this form isn't it?
Hunh?!
This is exactly how you
looked when you defeated
Ulquiorra Shiffer.
[gasp]
I looked like he does?
That's right. This form
is the manifestation of
your greatest fear.
You feared letting your soul be
consumed by your destructive
impulse to become a monster.
It's what prevented
you from Hollowfying.
So then,
What is it that you
want me to do here?
Am I supposed to fight this
guy now and defeat him?!
No.
He is not the opponent that
you will fight against.
You will fight us....
...as one.
Now what?!
I don't understand.
What's happening?!
This,
Is our true form, Ichigo.
We are the same.
The two of us are your power.
Here I come, Ichigo!
[deep explosion]
Uh?!
[lightheaded gasp]
What's wrong?!
That's quite impressive.
So close to me, yet
you're still able to hang
on to your existence.
Who are you?!
[Tatsuki]
Run, Keigo! Run!
[scared gasp]
You need to get going now!
You can't do anything to
help here, so move! Do it!
I--! Mmh!
It's no good.
I can't move!
What should I do?
I have to get out!
Michiru! I should
let go of her!
It's no use. There's
not enough time left,
It's too late!
[gasp]
Hm?!
You seem in distress,
young lady.
It's at times like this,
when you need a real hero.
The Spirits are
aaallways with yoouu!
Heh heh heh heh HEY!
Yes viewers,
I'm back and beautiful!
Don Kanonji's in the house!
Everyone's favorite Spirit
Hunter has been resurrected!
That's right, I've come
back to give it to ya!
Count your blessings,
because The one and only
Don has returned!!!
Uh. Huh?
Huh?
And just who might you be?
Hunh..!
You gotta be kidding me!
Have you been livin'
under a rock!?
You don't watch much
television, do ya smart guy?
All right! I'll tell
you one more time!
I am the--!
So what'd you come here for,
Don Kanonji?
Why'd you do that?!
I was just starting to do my own
special copyrighted,
one-of-a-kind introduction!
How can you be so cruel?
Come on!
For your own good,
go back home, will ya?
There's no way you can help
out with anything here.
[downtrodden]
Uughh...
Uhh... Huh?!
[Aizen]
You know...
Right now you are barely
withstanding my Spirit Energy.
And I should I say, I
admire you for still
being here in one piece.
Listen to me! There's
nothing you can do!!
Run away as fast as
you can! Do it now!
"Run away"!?
And allow this monster to take
the lives of the innocent?
You should always know,
this one thing.
A hero doesn't run
from danger.
They must be a shining symbol
of hope to kids everywhere.
Bwa-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Cannon Ball!!
Super Spirit Hunter Cane!
Kanonji Buster!
Huaaahh!!
You should stop. If a mere
human like yourself touches me,
you will cease to exist.
Unh!
Kanonji!
Ah.
I'm just in time. [exhale]
Huuuuuuahh!
Don't tell me you really
think you can stop me with
the power you possess now!
It's hopeless!
Wuaaaah!
If you don't take this
fight more seriously,
You will die.
He's not kidding around!
But is he really
trying to kill me?
So, come on!!
Huaaagh!!
Now you're done.
[Ichigo]
Hold on.
I'm not even close to "done".
No matter how many times
you knock me down,
I'll keep getting up.
Until you teach me exactly what
the Final Getsugatensho is!
Interesting.
But you don't deserve to
learn anything with that
half-hearted resolve!
Hyaaaahh!
Since you won't
teach me willingly,
Guess I'll just have to
force it out of you!
Kyaaaaahh!
So you've finally decided to
take this fight seriously.
No matter. You still
won't be able to land a
single blow against me.
Take this!!
[Rangiku]
I made it in time!
Aizen!
[Rangiku]
Gin!
Rangiku.
Huuh?
Young lady listen ta me!
You have put yourself in
the middle of a situation
filled with danger!
A lady like you
shouldn't be here!
Start running.
[stammering]
O--o--ooo...
All of you, get going,
I'll stall them!
There's no other way,
move while there's
still time!
What!? Do you know who I
am, lady?! I'm Don Kano--!
Mmmmph!
You need to shut your
mouth, use your brain,
grab those kids and get
them outta here right now!
Do you want me to tear
off that stupid 'stache,
burn your hat,
and smash your shades
into your face so no
one'll recognize you?!!
[whimpering]
In that case, it's
all yours girl!
Color us outta here!
But!
If you find a hero is what you
need, call out for "Don Ka--
Oof!!
Oww! I hope ya didn't hurt
your throwin arm, lady!
See ya!
Who could she be?
Is she a friend of Ichigo's?
Their kimonos look similar.
She's so beautiful.
That stupid Ichigo.
He never even
mentioned her to me.
When you said you
"made it in time",
did you mean in time
to save those humans?
Or were you referring to
seeing me destroy Karakura
Town and creating the Ouken?
Well, whatever the reason,
you were wrong.
What is it? Do you find it
difficult to speak to me?
[Gin]
Captain Aizen.
Please excuse my
former colleague.
I'll get her out of
your sight immediately.
I really don't mind.
I'm in no hurry.
You can talk with
her right here, gin.
But I insist!
It's fine, really.
Well, well.
[Aizen]
He is always such
an amusing child.
[panting]
You arched your body
at the last second.
A useless effort.
[panting]
He's strong.
And his speed is incredible!
[Ichigo]
I couldn't react fast enough to
block with my Zanpakuto.
Eyagh!
Now you see the
difference in our power.
You think you can force
anything out of me?!
Don't make me laugh!!
Hyaaahh!
You won't get away!
You need to shut up!
Whatever it takes, I
will get it out of you!
That's enough!
What the hell?!
Now! You will disappear
from this world of yours!
Yaahh!
Let go of me!
You seem pretty worn down.
Why'd you come?
I lost track of your
Spiritual Pressure,
so I took the Senkaimon
to get the jump on you.
After all, I had a better feel
for where the real Karakura
Town had been transported!
I'm not asking how you
happened to get here.
I want to understand why
you would bother coming
here when you're in such
a weak condition.
Ugh.
You don't know?
Because you're here.
Finally, I can
ask you directly.
Tell me. Why did you choose
to go to work for Aizen?
Answer me! Why on earth did
you go and betray Izuru?
You betrayed his trust in you!
Is that really what
you want to know?
Huh?
You're upset that
I betrayed Izuru?
Sounds to me like,
you're really talking
about yourself.
That's a shame.
You really should've
stayed where you were.
Oh, Rangiku.
You're a pain.
Damn!!
What's he thinking?
Why is he trying to kick
me out of this world?!
I don't have
time for this!
Kheh.
Getsuga
Tensho!
So you're back again.
Yeah, sorry!
But you should know I
don't give up that easily.
So I'm going to be
here a little longer!
"A little longer"?
Yeah! So what do you say we
get this party started!
I'm bringing all I've got!
Hyaaaaa!!
Hraaaaaah!!
What's changed in you?
Not sure.
But I'll tell ya,
My friends are counting on me!
I won't let them down!
[Tatsuki]
Okay Don Kanonji,
that's far enough.
Really. I can walk.
Oh no! You're much
too weak, girl!
I said...
Hm?!
I'm fine!!
You have got to
start paying better
attention when
people talk to you!
I hope I didn't
hurt your head.
[exasperated sigh]
[Keigo]
Tatsuki!!
[Tatsuki]
Keigo!!
I told you to run away!
What's with you?!
And where did you
get that sword?
I saw Afro Dude lying
in a heap back there,
so I borrowed his sword!
I've never done kendo or
anything, but I figure it's
better than having nothing!
Who's Afro Dude?
I'll explain later.
Anyway let's get going!
So where's Chizuru? And
Mizuiro?!
When you left, didn't
you go looking for him?!
I found Mizuiro!
He's over there!
Chizuru's with him, too!
Now's not the time for
questions, Tatsuki!
We have to go now!...
I feel that guy's presence.
I sense him closing in on
us as we speak!!
[White Zangetsu]
So "everyone's waiting for you"?
That may be important
to you, but it's really
of no concern to me.
It's clear that's
how you think.
You've told me
all that before.
What happens to what you want to
protect is no concern of mine.
What you want to protect,
Ichigo, is not the same thing
that I want to protect!
But here's how I see it.
What I want to protect
has never changed.
It may be very different
than what concerns you,
but that's not the issue!
I will protect whomever
I want to protect!
And that's what you'll
use Getsugatensho for?
That's right!
What's this?!
It's his sword.
Something's different!
Here's a question, Ichigo.
Earlier you said something.
If I keep knocking you down,
You'll keep getting up.
Right. So what are
you getting at?
Very well.
Then allow me to test you!
I'm ready!!
Haaaaa!!
Hyaaaaaaa!
[panting]
[Isshin]
Hurry...
Ichigo!
[Keigo]
Quick Tatsuki!
We have to run!
[Tatsuki]
But where can we go?!
He's going to catch us!
Wait...
You have a plan?
To escape without a plan.
Such things can lead to love.
As the two continue
their escape, they soon
find themselves in love
with each other and--
[Tatsuki]
[punch] Die.