[Kon]
Let me oouuut!
Let me out of here!
I'm being held captive,
against my will!
I'm telling you,
it's toy abuse!
Somebody call the cops! The kid
who lives here makes me do slave
work, doesn't feed me, and keeps
me locked up all the time!
Hey! Quiet!
Get away from the window
and stop your whining!
The neighbors are gonna
think I'm doing something
weird up here in my room!
I don't care what they think!
That's none of my business!
I want to know why I have to
stay cooped up all day, every
day, in this crappy, cramped,
and filthy hole of yours!
[sigh] Life was good
while you were away
in Hueco Mundo.
There was no one to stop
me from going out and
stalking some hot chicks.
Wait a minute.
You did what?
No wonder the neighbors have
been acting so strange and
giving me the stink-eye!
You've been
destroying my
reputation!
Huh?
Oh?
Oh!
Ooohhhh!
I love watermelons so much!
Even when they're
out of season!
Aagh! Put me down!
Let go of me!
[Kon]
I want those melons!
They're so firm,
and fully-packed!
I'm just trying to help!
She's a little top-heavy!
You moron!
You're not going anywhere!
I wanna give her a hand or two!
Don't worry, melons, I'm coming!
What's the matter with you?!
Hello! Excuse me!
Yes?
I think I'm lost!
I heard the Karakura
Mart was somewhere
around here.
Uhh...
It's not that far away.
Just go back the way you came.
Then turn left at the
intersection.
Go straight,
and you'll see it.
Okay, I got it!
Thank you very much!
No problem!
Awwww! You sent
my melons away!
What's the matter with you?!
Get out of the window and
back in the room!
If she sees you,
there's gonna be
trouble! Are you nuts?!
[klaxon]
Huh?
What?
Damn! It's a Hollow!
Get out of there!
Look after things
'til I get back!
Okayyy...
Behave yourself,
d'you hear?
Whatever.
Huh?
Oh boy...
Just what I need,
more craziness.
[Kon]
He he he he!
Nice try, Ichigo!
But you can't expect me
to sit at home and behave
myself on such a nice day!
It's been too long since I've
been able to use your body to
get out in the world and
experience some excitement!
Huh?
[gasp]
Hey, it's the babe
who owns the melons!
Ah!!
Sweetie-pie!
[gasp]
Watch out!
Whoa!
Huuh??
Huddawhuddawhaaaauuu!
Blugh! Blargh!
Help! Help!
Somebody help me!
I! Oh! Oh! Oooh! Aah!
Huh?
[kon]
Aaaah-choo!
[groan]
I'm so sorry. You'll probably
catch a cold because of me.
Forget it, it's no big deal.
And besides, this body
doesn't belong to me,
so the bottom line is,
if it catches a cold,
what do I care?
Hm?
Nothing. Don't listen to me,
I'm just talking to myself.
Oh, by the way,
Didn't you come by earlier,
asking for directions?
Did you find the place
you were looking for?
Yes, but afterwards I
got distracted by a man
flying through the air.
Huh?
Things like that happen
to me sometimes...
Are you here, Ken?
I'm home!
I got lost for a while.
That's why I'm so late.
Sorry, I'll make your
lunch right away!
Here you go!
Thanks for being patient!
What do you think?
Do you like it?
Is it good?
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, and by the way, guess what?
On my way home, I saw
someone flying through the
air in a black kimono!
Someone in a
black kimono?
Oh, do you know who it is?
I have no idea!
That's really strange!
I wonder if you saw a
ghost or something.
It's possible. I've been
seeing things like that ever
since I was a little child.
Well I tried to not let it
bother me, but then Ken, he...
[humming]
Hey sweetie,
should we go out,
or stay in tonight?
I think we
should break up.
Huh?
I mean, lately, you've been
getting more and more peculiar.
You see people no-one else
sees, and you talk to
people who aren't there.
It's getting really creepy.
You're a great cook and all,
but you're weirding me out
with all this 'ghost' stuff.
[breaks down crying]
I don't see these visions
because I want to!
They just appear
out of nowhere!
Then, to add insult to injury,
Ken told me he was going to
leave, right after he finished
eating! Isn't that awful?!
Yeah it's kinda
odd, when you
think about it.
What difference would it make,
whether he left before or
after he ate his meal?
Well, that's it!
I'm killing myself!
What?!
It's too difficult
to bear!
I can't go on living,
now that Ken's broken
up with me!
Thanks for rescuing me,
even though it will only
postpone the inevitable!
Hey wait a minute!
You're not gonna like it
very much when you die!
Once you're gone, the
Hollows will come and
try to eat your soul,
and going to the
Soul Society isn't
that great, either!
[Boy]
Heads up, mister!
Huh?
D'auugh!
...
[Ichigo]
Oh, man. I don't see
a Hollow anywhere!
Huh?
Rukia!
Oh, Ichigo.
Did something
happen over here?
Yeah. At the end
of the alley.
Do you think a
Hollow did that?
No, there's too much damage.
An ordinary Hollow would
only go after human souls.
So a Hollow's
not responsible?
I said an ordinary
Hollow wouldn't do this.
[Rukia]
Recently, there have
been five identical
incidents like this one.
That many, huh?
Yes. As a result, the Soul
Society's been put on special
alert for these kind of cases.
The Spiritual Pressure of the
Hollow believed to be
responsible for the incidents,
appears and disappears
with each event.
As a result,
it's been extremely
difficult to track it down.
But in this case,
we might have
caught a break.
This woman was
killed recently.
Whatever attacked her couldn't
have made it very far in such
a short period of time.
Our priority is clear.
We have to stop the next
attack before it happens.
I want you to scout the
area and see if you can
find what caused this.
What about you?
I'll follow you after I
secure the crime scene and
turn it over to the others.
You'd better get
going, Ichigo.
I'm on it!
What a dummy you are, Ken.
Breaking up,
after all I did for you.
I'm home!
I'm so glad to see you, darling!
Here, enjoy your dinner!
I will! Thank you so much!
You fool. One thing's for sure.
When I'm dead, you won't get
any more meals from me.
[footsteps]
Ah!
Did I hear you right?
You want to die?
Well, today's your lucky day.
I've come here...
...to grant your wish!
Huh?
What? What are you
talking about?
It's simple, I'm going
to help you die.
[gasp]
I see. Apparently, you
can sense a Hollow's
Spiritual Pressure.
What are you saying?
Are you even human?!
Not really. I'm just temporarily
borrowing this human body.
Anyway, why are
you so afraid?
You kept saying
you want to die,
and I'm offering to
grant your wish.
Yeah, I understand,
but this is so sudden.
It's, well, I feel I have
to prepare myself for it.
Heh! What a silly thing for
you to be focusing on, at the
moment you're about to die.
Relax, my dear, there's
no need to be afraid.
The pain will only
be momentary.
Now, just open your mouth.
[gasp]
My mouth?
Why should I do that?
It makes it easier...
when I do this!
AAAAAAAAAAHH!
I'm sensing a Hollow!
And he's close!
Noooo!
Yes, that's good!
Open your mouth wider!
That way, I can leech onto you
and suck out your nutrients!
You'll end up just like
that man over there!
[Kon]
The Great Kon,
to the rescue!
Oof!
The Great Kon
Kick Attack!
Hey come on, what are you
waiting for?! Run for it!
Oh, right!
Huh? The Hollow's Spiritual
Pressure disappeared again!
Damn! What the hell
is going on here?!
That was close, but we
should be safe for now.
I don't understand
what's happening!
What was that monster?!
It's called a Hollow.
A Hollow?
That's right. It attacks people
and sucks out their souls.
But it looked so
human at first.
I don't really
understand it myself.
But I think it's an
unusual type that uses
a human as a host.
Oh, dear!
But why?
Huh?
Why did you save me?
I never asked you to
interfere, you know!
Huaah?!
If you hadn't stepped in,
I could have died right there,
just like I wanted to!
It would have been
much better if you'd
just left me alone!
Come on, now...
You can't be serious.
How can you say
something like that?
[gasp]
Life is precious!
You should hold onto it
with all your might!
[Kon]
That guy who was
killed over there,
I can guarantee you he didn't
want to die, especially in
such a hideous way!
How come you...
know so much?
I guess you've noticed
by now I'm not a
normal human being.
Fact is, I was
supposed to be killed
off a long time ago.
But in spite of everything,
I'm still here.
If I can survive what I had to
go through, then so can you!
But I'm just so frightened.
I'll protect you.
Hm?
I promise I'll
protect you.
And in return, you
have to promise not to
give up on yourself.
Do you really mean it?
You have my word.
Hold it
right there!
Huh?
[heavy panting]
Excuse me, who are you?
My boyfriend.
Huh?!
Haruko!
Huh?
Hm?
I'm sorry!
I was way off-base!
Huh?
I made a mistake! I want to get
back together, if you'll let me!
I miss your cooking!
It was so delicious!
[sniff]
Tell me, is it too late?
Of course not!
I forgive you!
I'm so glad you apologized!
Let's just forget what happened!
Come here, Haruko!
Oh, Ken!
Haruko!
Ken!
Uh... heh heh...
[kissing]
It's all for the best.
I suppose things weren't
meant to work out between me
and those beautiful melons.
Oh well.
Huh?
Forgot about that.
Nothin' else happening. I might
as well go home and throw this
in with the rest of my laundry.
[explosion]
Huh??
Damn it!
Huh?
Heh heh heh heh!
Aaah ha ha ha ha!
What the hell?
This isn't good! Is that the
Hollow inside you, Haruko?!
[chuckle]
Aagh!
Damn it...
Eh he he ha ha!
[choking]
Bastard! You were determined
to take over her body,
no matter what!
And whose fault is that?
You didn't follow up to
destroy me!
After you knocked me down and
left me, I happened to run
into Fatso here, and guess
who he was looking for?
Hello! Haruko! Can you hear me?
Where did you take off to?
Ghhh!
Hoo hoo hee ha ha ha ha!
You were inside Ken when
he found the two of us!
Yes, I was. But the little
twit didn't realize!
She dropped her guard,
and without giving it
a second thought,
she ran over and
threw herself right
into my waiting arms!
Hoo hoo ha ha ha ha!
[gasp]
[giggles] Just as I thought,
this woman possesses
considerable spirit energy!
I'll have to take my time,
sucking every last drop
from her body!
No way!
Haaa!
Nice try!
I'm not gonna let you have her,
so get ready for some pain!
If I have to pound
her out of you,
I'll do it until my
fists are rawww!
Heh!
Haaaaaa!
What happened to me?
It really doesn't matter.
You're all right now.
But why?
Why did you save me?
Don't you remember?
I promised I'd protect you.
[gasps]
How dare you interfere
with my feeding!
Look out!
Augh!
[Kon]
Oh, no!
Ah-ha! Now the truth comes out,
literally! I suspected you
weren't an ordinary human!
So it turns out you were a Soul
Candy all along. [chuckle]
I guess I'll eat you first,
then take my time enjoying
the other two.
Hold on there!
Wait a minute!
Stop! Stop...!
[Ichigo]
Huaaaaaah!!
Getsuga...tensho!
Rrrrrrgh!
[Kon]
Ichigo!
Eee..
[Hollow]
Eeeyaaghhhhh!
[Ichigo]
Man, you get yourself into
the worst situations.
Well, that guy's gone for good.
Are you feeling all right?
You saved me again!
[wails]
I was so scared! I thought
we were done for! [sobbing]
Ichigo, are you
all right?!
Huuh?
What is the meaning of
this?! Your behavior's
unacceptable, Ichigo!
Haruko!
Believe me, I have
no idea what's going
on here, Rukia!
Please! I'm begging you, Haruko!
I made a terrible mistake!
Please come back!
Just forget it!
I've decided to start over with
somebody who appreciates me!
Right?
What?! Hold on!
[Ichigo]
What's going on here?
I don't understand!
I never said--
How can you say
that, darling? You
promised to protect
me, remember?
Beg your pardon?!
That wasn't me! That
was another guy, Kon!
What are you talking about?!
Those words came right out
of your mouth!
I've heard enough.
It's time to end this mess.
[Rukia]
We'll sort it out later.
Huh?
[coughing]
Tell me
something...
'cause I can't remember.
Why are we at the park?
Well... I have no idea.
[stomach growl]
Huh?
Uhh...
Your stomach's trying
to pass on a message!
My bad. I must be a lot
hungrier than I thought I was.
Well, let's go home
and take care of that.
Sounds good to me!
I think I'll start
with a chicken, then
cook up some pasta...
Sounds yummy!
And a nice chocolate
cake for dessert!
Stop! I'm gonna need a towel
in a second! I'm starting to
drool on myself!
[Kon]
Wait a minute! Is that it?!
After all that drama we
went through, and he
still gets the girl?!
This isn't right! It's not fair!
I thought I was the star of this
episode! I demand a rewrite!
Call my agent!!
[Kon]
Damn, you get to
have all the fun!
[Ichigo]
What's fun about this?!
[Kon]
What's the matter, Ichigo? She
isn't your type? Just what kind
of girl do you like?
[Ichigo]
The kind that makes me
fall in love with her!
[Kon]
Ha ha ha! Oh, you
need to be romanced?!
[Ichigo]
You're making my head hurt!