[music playing]
[theme music]
NARRATOR: Ichigo's mission
to Hueco Mundo continues.
He has now defeated Grimmjow,
and successfully rescued
Orihime.
The fight against Sosuke
Aizen and the Espada goes on.
But we will pick up that
narrative at another time.
For now, let us
turn our attention
to the Soul Society, where a
totally new storyline unfolds.
The curtain is about to rise
on a battle unlike anything
our heroes have
ever seen before.
-Wow!
Have you heard the latest news?
They're bringing
in a new captain
to take over command
of Squad Three.
-Yes, of course
I've heard about it.
As a captain, I've
been notified.
It will be made official
at the meeting tomorrow.
-It must be Izuru Kira.
That's very strange though.
I wonder when he found
the time to master Bankai.
-Izuru received
no such promotion.
-No.
You've got to be kidding.
-Stop making such a mess.
I'm not kidding, and
frankly, I haven't
been briefed on
any of the details.
-Is that right?
The truth is, I never
thought Kira was good captain
material anyway.
Squad Three's pretty tough.
You think the new captain
will be able to take charge?
-We'll find out
tomorrow, Rangiku.
Now forget about this
and get back to work.
-You don't have to be so rude.
I'm just curious.
-Yesterday an expedition
returned safely
to the Soul Society.
Their long-term
assignment has been
completed without suffering
a single casualty.
This is a truly
great accomplishment.
As you all know, Squads
Three, Five, and Nine
of the 13 Court Guard Squads
are presently without captains.
Therefore two other
captains and myself
summon the expedition
units leader,
and tested his qualifications.
The purpose of our
examination was
to determine his ability to
fill one of the three posts
currently available.
I am pleased to say our
decision was unanimous.
And so, at this
time, I would like
to introduce you
to the man who will
be taking over the position
formally held by Gin Ichimaru.
The new captain of Squad
Three, Shusuke Amagai.
-So this character,
Shusuke Amagai,
know anything about him?
-Nope.
-I don't like the idea of some
newbiw coming along and being
put in charge of the squad.
-I hear that he's been away
on a long assignment, working
on suppressing Hollows.
-That doesn't mean
anything to me.
The problem is, some guy
I've never even heard of
has just become my captain.
How am I supposed to
follow his orders?
-Yeah, I know what you mean.
But lieutenant Kira
isn't much better.
-Right.
-Good morning, everybody.
A new captain, huh?
I sure hope he turns
out to be nice.
-It's looking so good.
-Huh?
Interesting.
He carries two Zanpakuto.
-Hm.
He's got some style,
I'll give him that.
-I'm Shusuke Amagai.
As you're probably aware,
I'm new to this position.
I look forward to
working with you,
and I'll do the best I can.
-First of all,
welcome to the team.
There's a lot of protocol
involved with being a captain,
and it's hard to get used to.
So feel free to ask
my advice at any time.
-Thanks.
I just hope I don't
become a bother.
-Who else oversaw
his examination
with Head Captain Yamamoto?
-Beats me.
Does it really matter?
The bottom line is, we
have one less open position
in the squad.
We should count our blessings.
-Well, I suppose you're
right about that.
-So there's a body in place.
But it doesn't mean
he can do the job.
Now he has to prove to
us that he's any good.
-We finally filled
one of the openings.
-It's progress, but we still
have two spots remaining.
And that represents
quite a problem.
In any world, including our
own, an empty leader's seat
only invites discord and
negative opportunities.
When evil tries to
expand its influence,
such squads are most vulnerable,
and provide the easiest entry
point to mount an attack.
-That must be him.
Not too impressive.
-Good morning.
Which one of you
is the Lieutenant.
-That would be me, sir.
I'm Lieutenant Izuru Kira.
-My name is Shusuke Amagai.
I'm here from headquarters.
I'm the newly appointed
Captain of Squad Three.
Pleased to meet you.
-Pleased to meet
you as well, sir.
Welcome to the squad.
-Allow me to introduce you.
This is my associate,
Makoto Kibune.
Along with me, he'll also
be joining the squad today.
He was part of my
expeditionary patrol unit,
and is very skilled.
That's why I wanted
to bring him along.
He will be our new third seat.
-Thank you, sir.
I do appreciate your confidence.
-That guy doesn't
look like much.
Are you sure he's
the new captain?
-Well, if not, he's
in big trouble.
He's wearing a captain's coat.
-Oh yeah.
-Is there a problem?
-Well, to be frank, I mean--
-He's trying to say,
that up until yesterday,
we were doing fine
without a captain.
-Quiet.
-Hey, believe me, I
understand how you feel.
-What?
-After all, you've
just had some guy
you've never seen before
suddenly show up out of nowhere
and say, hi, I'm
your new Captain.
I don't blame you in the least.
I'd be annoyed if I
were in your shoes.
But let me tell you something,
and I really mean this.
My primary duty as Captain is to
protect my men, no matter what.
That's what being a
captain's all about.
-What's the problem?
For all you know, this
guy might turn out
to be really good Captain.
-Well, that's true.
In theory, but, the
Squad's got a bad attitude.
And no one trusts the
guy enough to give him
a chance to prove himself.
It's miserable.
When I think about
going in there
and having to face
that resistance,
day after day, I get sick.
-Geez.
What kind of wimp are you.
It's no different than having
a transfer student arrive
at school.
You just have to let the class
show the new guy the ropes.
-Yeah, but what if
that doesn't work?
Do you see the problem?
Then I'm the one
stuck in the middle.
-OK, OK.
I can see this is making
you nervous and uptight.
Well I know just what
will do the trick.
Voila!
Good old sake.
Drink up and forget all
about your troubles.
-No way.
I can't be drinking in
the middle of the day.
-Oh come on.
It's tastier because
you're drinking it
in the middle of the day.
Hey, that's it!
Throw a party for
the whole squad,
and have the Captain
as the guest honor.
Once they've got
some sake in them,
they'll be buddies in no time.
-Oh, it's as simple
as that, huh?
-Come on, give it a shot.
I mean, what have
you got to lose?
-Well, well.
So you've been hiding sake
in my quarters, have you?
-Captain.
I can explain.
It's Izuru's fault!
-Rangiku!
-Ah!
-What's happening?
-We decided to throw a
welcome party for you
and Third Seat Kibune, sir.
-Huh?
You did all this for us?
What a nice surprise!
Thank you, everybody.
-I've been told this is
one of the very best ways
to establish an
atmosphere of camaraderie.
Here you go, Captain.
I'll pour for you.
-Well, you don't have to.
-Sorry, is something the matter?
-No.
Thanks.
Oh, that seems like a lot.
-What?
-Uh, don't worry, it's nothing.
-Good.
Listen up, men.
We're now going to
begin the welcome party
for Captain Amagai
and Third Seat Kibune.
-Mm.
-This is bad.
I've never been to such an
uncomfortable party before.
This is the exact opposite of
what was supposed to happen.
I know what we need!
Let's have a toast to
get everything rolling!
Sir, out of respect,
how about you begin!
-Well, fine.
It's a pleasure to
have met you all.
-Wow, Captain.
You're quite an
experienced drinker.
-To be perfectly
honest, not so much.
-Sir, tell me.
Are you all right?
-I'm fine!
I mean, for you guys to
throw me a party like this,
makes me happy.
Really, really, happy.
This is the nicest thing
anyone's ever done for me.
-Captain, you sure
you're all right?
-Uh huh.
-Whoa.
-Captain Amagai!
-Somebody go check on him.
-Captain!
Captain!
Say something.
-What's going on?
-Actually, the Captain's
kind of a lightweight.
He can't hold his liquor.
-Huh?
-But it was just one little cup.
-He gets drunk from
sake-flavored pickles.
-If he's so sensitive, why
didn't he just turn me down
when I offered it?
-He probably thought it
would have been bad form.
Under the circumstances,
he must've
been worried that it would
be seen as a rude gesture.
-Oh.
Someone go get a bucket
of water and a towel.
-Yes, sir.
-He's passed out cold.
What now, Lieutenant?
-I guess there's no
point in continuing
to have the party, when the
guest of honor's unconscious.
-Should we start
cleaning up, then?
-Hold on a minute.
-Since we're set up
anyway, why don't we
use this as an opportunity
to get to know everybody?
I want to meet the whole
squad, and put names and faces
together as quickly as I can.
[music playing]
[footsteps]
-Is it a holiday?
I heard Squad Three
is having a party.
-Yes, in the middle of the day.
It's a welcome party
for Captain Amagai.
-Very smart.
-What makes you think so?
-Why wait for the evening?
If you start drinking
sake during the day,
it's more effective.
That's when you can
get really plastered.
I wonder if Captain Amagai
is a two-fisted drinker?
-Don't ask me.
-Maybe we'll end up being
really good friends.
He seems nice.
-Too nice for you.
-You're so mean, Nanao.
Now you've gone and
hurt my feelings.
[music playing]
-Thank you.
-Hm.
-Well now what?
-We ignore him.
I don't know what's
the big deal.
We managed fine until now
with just Lieutenant Kira.
Who needs a big
wuss for a captain?
-You've got that right.
-What was I thinking?
I was a fool to
listen to Rangiku.
-Ah, Lieutenant Kira.
-How's it going?
-Really well.
Everyone in Squad
Three is very close.
-They've been through a lot.
-They give you a lot
of credit for being
the one who kept the
Squad together and focused
after they lost their captain.
Well done.
-Um, it wasn't really me.
-Attention!
Squad Three of the 13
Court Guard Squads.
This is an emergency.
Menos have appeared in the
Precipice World, at area 0035.
[howling]
-They're heading directly
toward the Soul Society.
Our sensors report 13 of
them at the present time.
-Can that be right?
-How could so many get
through our defenses?
-Impossible.
-Attention.
I am ordering Squad Three
to mobilize and exterminate
all of the Menos who have
infiltrated the Precipice
World.
Complete your battle
preparations immediately,
and report to the stated
coordinates at once!
-We have no choice.
We have to mobilize, now.
-We have no leader.
-That cannot be helped.
I'll ask them to shut down
the restrictive current.
You must take command.
-I see your point.
Squad Three!
We're going to the Precipice
World to destroy the Menos.
-It looks like Squad Three
is going into action.
-I know.
The Seireitei may be
moving toward change.
-What?
-Someone from one of
the expedition units
has suddenly become a captain.
That has never
happened up til now.
-Yes, you're right.
It's very curious.
That's why I'm
interested to find out
the names of the
other two Captains
who examined Shusuke
Amagai, and gave
their blessing to
his appointment.
-I don't who they are.
But I can say, with
absolute certainty,
there's something
new in the wind.
Something we've
never seen before.
-We'll enter the
Precipice World as one,
then split off into groups of
four to confront the enemy.
These are Menos, so be careful.
-Charge!
[music playing]
-They're coming!
-All troops spread out,
and move into position!
Raise your head, Wabisuke!
[yelling and fighting]
-Five of the thirteen
Menos have been destroyed.
There are only eight remaining.
-Good.
Hang in there, men.
Just a few more to go.
-Yes sir!
-Now what?
-Oh no, the restrictive
current's released!
But why?
It was supposed to
have been quarantined.
-The restrictive current.
-What do you mean?
That's impossible!
[rumbling]
-The restrictive current
cleaners are bearing down.
The distance between
them and Squad Three
is 200 yards and closing fast.
-Third Seat Kibune,
what's going on?
-I don't know.
I'm certain my request to shut
down the restrictive current
was received.
-Fall back!
-I'll bring up the rear,
and try to distract them.
Get everyone out of here.
-Thank you, Third Seat Kibune.
Let's go.
Don't look back!
-It's too late!
We won't make it.
-Coming through.
[gasps]
-Captain Amagai, no!
-Stay back, everyone.
-Is he nuts?
-I thought I made it clear when
I spoke to you earlier today.
As long as I'm your
Captain, I will protect you.
-Please pay close
attention, everyone.
You're seeing Captain
Amagai's true strength.
[yelling]
[gasps]
-Makoto.
Are you certain you
requested a shut down
of the restrictive current?
-Yes, sir.
-I can't believe the
Department of Research
and Development would
make such a grave error.
Something's strange about this.
Once we're home,
we'll investigate.
Was anybody badly hurt
during the battle?
-No, Captain.
-Good.
Lieutenant.
-Sir.
-You did very good work, today.
Just what I'd
expect from someone
who's been able to
keep his squad together
without a Captain.
-Just doing my job.
-Well I'm glad
everyone's all right.
Let's go back.
-That guy's something
else, isn't he?
-Yeah, no kidding.
[murmurs]
-Captain Amagai!
-Somebody do something.
-It's amazing.
He saved us all, but he
was drunk the entire time.
-I could use some
assistance here.
-Oh, of course.
We should get back to the base,
before the captain wakes up.
-Right.
[music playing]
[theme music]
-Why did you order the
Third Squad to take action?
-It was a good
opportunity for the men
to see the new
Captain's abilities.
-According to my
report, Squad Three
was in the middle of a party.
You sent him out
while he was drunk.
-But he took care of
business, didn't he?