[MUSIC - BEAT CRUSADERS,
"TONIGHT, TONIGHT, TONIGHT"]
MAN: Hi, it's me.
I just got in.
I just parked the van, so
I'll be there in a minute.
No, I actually already ate.
But, uh, thanks.
Huh?
[grunts] What the hell? [grunts]
[screams]
-We're too late.
-Squad 3790 reporting.
We found the target and are
moving in for the capture.
After them!
[grunting]
-Ah!
-Oh, no!
-Are you all right?
-What happened!
[moaning]
-Stealth Force reporting.
WE found the target, but
failed to capture it.
We have one seriously injured
and require the Relief Squad
immediately.
[playground noises]
-What in the world
could they be planning?
-Ichigo, just asking
that over and over
isn't going to give
you the answer.
-But not knowing
is so aggravating!
-It was on the news today.
They said that
people from all over
have suddenly been disappearing.
-Does that mean--?
-The Bounts must have
something to do with this.
Those things they release
must be attacking people.
-[sigh] And as usual, Ririn and
her little friends didn't pick
up anything with
their sensors either.
-Hm?
[sigh]
-The Bounts are behind this.
But we don't even know
where they're hiding.
Hey, Renji.
What have you heard
from the soul society?
Do they even know
what's going on here?
-The Stealth Force
seems to be here.
But that's all I really know.
They haven't told
me anything else.
-Then I guess that
we're just going
to have to concentrate
on finding the Bounts
and those flying
monsters ourselves.
-Is there a way to do that?
-Right now, Urahara
is busy working
on a powerful new sensor I
asked him to make for us.
But we can't wait for it.
Until the sensor's
finished, we'll
just have to hit the streets
and hope we get lucky
and run into them.
-Poor Uryu.
I hope he'll be all right.
He seems like he's still in
shock over Yoshino's death.
I tried to get him
to talk about it,
but he barely said
two words to me.
I'm really worried about him.
-Unfortunately,
there isn't really
anything we can do to help him.
-Uryu's fallen in love
with the Bount woman, huh?
What an idiot.
-Don't make fun of him.
You want ought show
a little respect.
-Oh, yeah?
That's good.
And what would you know
about being respectful?
-What are you trying to say?
RUKIA: That's enough!
Honestly, is there anything
you two won't argue about?
This not the time to be
fighting among ourselves!
KARIYA: Gentleman, it was
several years hundred years ago
in this very underground chamber
that we lost many dear friends.
It is for that reason that
I find it especially moving
that we will begin
our final plan here
in this hollowed place.
Our fallen allies will
lend us their fury
and give us unlimited power.
It seems that the Soul
Society has made their move.
But we have nothing
to worry about.
The minerals in the rock
walls surrounding this play
shut out all spiritual pressure.
Not only that, the bodies
of our newly-born dolls
also contain large amounts
of that same mineral.
This is the time for us
to restore our energies.
Now then, gentleman, for those
who haven't seen them here
are the products of
my recent research.
Bittos.
These amazing creatures suck out
the souls from living humans,
and then deliver their
contents back to us.
They're the result of
new technology developed
by Ugaki and myself.
-Hm.
-Ah, so this is
what you were doing.
KARIYA: Sadly, their
creation required
us to sacrifice
one of our friends.
-What's the difference between
using the dolls, Master Kariya,
and simply sucking out
people's souls ourselves?
Is the point just to
make it less dangerous?
-The essential difference
is that the souls
the Bittos collect are
of extremely high purity.
They're highly concentrated.
So now we shall turn them
loose to begin sucking souls,
a practice that has long been
considered taboo by our tribe.
The energy we gain this way
will be gradually stored up
in our bodies.
And the result will be an
increase in our abilities
to more than 10 times
their current level.
-What did you say?
-More than 10 times?
Can that possibly be?
-It's true beyond a doubt.
KARIYA: With this new
power, we shall finally
be able to fulfill our
most cherished wish.
I still go first.
Let this moment
be forever etched
in your memories, the moment
when our tribes laws fall away
and our destiny changes forever.
[grunt]
Ah!
All pain and regret
has been washed away.
I feel nothing now but
boundless joy and immense power.
How wonderful.
-Fascinating.
Obviously the Bittos really
do concentrate the souls
in their bodies.
It's more powerful
than I expected.
Mm.
Yes.
[sighing]
MABASHI: Huh?
-You can drink it if you
want to, but count me out.
-Mabashi.
MABASHI: Are you all really
going to go along with this?
Are you serious?
-Oh, are you afraid, Mabashi?
What a baby.
-Listen to me!
Am I the only one who's
serious about honoring
the laws and code of our tribe.
Tell me something, Sawatari.
-What is it, Mabashi?
-Some people say that
there was a time when
you were known to
have sucked out
a great number of living souls.
Is that not true?
SAWATARI: Yes, that is true.
But that was a
very long time ago.
-And now look at the
results, old man!
It's aged you by 150 years.
Which is why it was
taboo, you fool.
-You're so annoying.
What matters is that we
are going to gain power.
It isn't like we can
ever die or anything.
-What are you talking about?
-Calm down, everyone.
Let's not ruin Master Kariya's
moment in history here.
After all, we're on the same
side in this, aren't we?
Please allow me to take a few
seconds and explain how I--
-Shut up!
I don't want to hear it!
This goes beyond
breaking the laws.
It's an abomination!
-Watch it, Mabashi.
-[laughs] Controversies are
commonplace in this world.
There's nothing wrong with
expressing one's opinion.
-[gasp]
-Ordinarily.
-[grunts]
[cough] [grunt]
[grunt]
KARIYA: Mabashi, the next time
your opinion differs from mine,
be aware that expressing
it may cost you your life.
But by all means, say
whatever you like.
-[grunts]
-As I told you all once
before, from now on,
I am the law of the Bount tribe.
-The Stealth Force has failed?
-Impossible.
-Not only that, several
were seriously injured.
Their bodies were pierced
by some kind of Bounts doll.
Furthermore, a
number of human souls
have been removed and stolen
by these same monsters
since the Bounts released them.
-How cruel of them.
There's nothing attractive
about what the Bounts do.
-Captain Hitsugaya,
do we have any idea
what the Bounts' plans are?
-Gathering information
about such things
is the Stealth Force's job.
That's why you're going to
the World of the Living.
-Us four?
HITSUGAYA: That's correct.
I've already given
all of your names
to the Captain's Committee.
You've all been cleared
to leave immediately.
-But why were we chosen?
-A monster has appeared, and
monsters are our specialty.
It doesn't matter that
it isn't a Hollow.
-Then these monster dolls
are our target, right?
HITSUGAYA: No.
It's the Bounts themselves.
YUMICHIKA: I-- I
have a question.
-And what's that?
-This sounds like it could be
some pretty messy business,
Captain.
These lieutenants may not mind,
but I don't like ugly things.
How exactly did I get included
in this questionable mission?
-When I talked to
Zaraki, he told me
you were the one with
the most free time.
-He said what?
-Is that a problem?
-No.
No, sir.
I'm happy to go.
-I have a feeling these
Bounts are up to something
even worse than what
we've seen so far.
We can't afford to leave this
up to just Ichigo and Lieutenant
Abarai.
It's up to you.
LIEUTENANTS: Yes, sir.
-Hm.
-It's not too bad,
considering it was a rush job.
-I think it's a
great job, Kisuke.
-Now then.
My sincere apologies for
having interrupted you earlier.
-Yes.
URAHARA: So what did she say?
-Yoruichi gave me
this exact message.
"I will be investigating
some issues
in the Soul Society for a while.
And while I'm gone,
I want you to watch
the Bounts'
movements carefully."
-Oh, I see.
And how are things on
the other side now?
SUI-FENG: Various entities
are gathering information
on the Bounts.
But so far, there's little
that's known for certain.
And they have no convictions.
-Hm.
Fine.
Very well, then.
Thank you for your help.
-I'll take my leave now.
I have to get back and make my
report to Lady Yoruichi as soon
as possible.
How curious, though.
-What's curious?
SUI-FENG: It's hard for me
to believe Lady Yoruichi ever
lived in a run-down
shack like this.
-What did you say?
-Calm down.
Calm down.
-Huh?
-I'm sorry if it
doesn't suit you.
But we actually find it
quite comfortable here.
-I suggest you keep in mind
that if anything happens
to Lady Yoruichi, I
know where to find you.
[breaking glass]
-What horrid manners she has.
-Let's do what we can to avoid
angering the Punishment Force.
-Hey, Uryu, Jinta.
Sorry to ask you
this late, but I
need you to go out and
get something for me.
JINTA: All right.
I'm coming!
-Calling this a shack.
The nerve of her.
JINTA: Excuse me.
-Hm?
-I think you should probably
go back to your room.
What if someone were
to come after you?
-Thank you.
-How are you feeling, anyway?
Are you OK?
You look a little pale.
-I'm fine, really.
Wasn't Urahara just calling you?
JINTA: Oh, right.
RUKIA: All right, everyone.
It's all up to us.
Let's split up and
be on the lookout.
ICHIGO: Anyone fighting
a monster should give off
elevated spiritual pressure.
-Right.
Understood.
-Do you really think
they'll come out?
-We may not encounter
them right away,
but they'll definitely
be coming back.
We have to stay on our toes.
-Hey, what are the two of
you doing back in those Gigai
again?
-That's a silly question.
You know it's my duty
to protect Orihime.
And obviously, I'd be of
no use as a stuffed animal.
-This is a dangerous mission.
-Hey, that's not fair!
I need to get into a Gigai, too.
If--
ICHIGO: That's
enough out of you.
Let's get going.
-Ah.
[glugging]
-Huh?
-Ah, what a feeling.
Such strength.
[sighing]
-How does it feel?
All right?
-It feels fantastic,
Master Kariya.
-It's amazing!
-[laughs] I feel as if now
I've become at least 100 years
younger.
-It exceeds even my
own expectations.
I was hoping to humbly
advance our cause.
But now I can see by
creating these dolls, what
we have declared for the
Bounts is an entire new age!
-This is still
just the beginning.
If we continue to
absorb these souls,
an even more wonderful world
will open itself up for us.
-Positively addictive!
-Yes, I want more of it already.
-Obviously, all of the endless
time I spent researching this
was not in vain.
-Mabashi.
-[grunts]
-What's the matter?
There's nothing to be afraid of.
-I don't want to do it.
-Master Kariya, may
I request permission
to at least treat his
more series wounds.
-No need for that.
In a moment, he'll be cured.
-Ah!
-Now, Bittos.
-Stop it!
-[laughs]
[choking]
-Ah!
I told you, didn't I?
There's nothing to be
afraid of, Mabashi.
Welcome Mabashi.
Welcome to the new world.
-Talk to me, Ririn.
Are you picking up
any trace of 'em?
-No, nothing.
I just don't know
what's going on.
-What we really need is for
Kisuke to finish that sensor.
-This is so irritating.
KURUDO: You know,
there's one thing
I've always been curious about.
ORIHIME: What?
KURUDO: What do you
suppose Chad and Noba find
to talk about when it's just
the two of them together?
-Um, it's probably
just the simple stuff.
Like, what do you want
to have for dinner?
And, sure is nice
weather we're having.
And sometimes, I bet that
they say things like,
it's good to top your
noodles with chocolate.
For sure.
-That sounds more like you.
-Oh?
-[sigh] I can't imagine them
having a real conversation.
They're the two most silent
people I think I've ever met.
[grumbling]
-Damn that Ichigo.
Where could that guy
have disappeared to now?
And the same for Rukia.
She's abandoned me.
After all my love
and devotion for her,
this is the way I get--
[squeak]
-What?
[mumbling]
-What do you think
you're doing, Big Foot?
-Oh, it's you, the
mysterious little critter
from Ichigo's place.
-Who are you calling a little
critter, you clumsy oaf?
-What are you doing
out here in the street?
-Huh?
I felt like taking
a walk, that's all.
-And that's all?
-That's all.
Is there a law against going
out for some fresh air?
-[laughs] You got left behind.
So then you decided to go
out and look for a Ichigo
on your own, didn't you?
-Huh?
Hey, that isn't fair!
But you are partly
right about it.
It's just that I was so
worried about my dear Rukia
that I wanted to--
[shouting]
-Hey, where are you going?
I wasn't finished
with my story yet.
[whimpering]
-Now Roar, Zabimaru!
-Someone's spiritual
pressure just rose.
-Yes, it's Renji.
-He started fighting someone!
-It's Renji.
-Then let us go.
-Where exactly were
you planning to go?
You were thinking about
revenge, revenge for her?
-No, it isn't revenge
that I'm after.
-Whatever it is, you're going
to need to recover your Quincy
powers first, before you can
attempt to accomplish it.
That is a thorny path.
Early on, the Bounts
said that they
needed to have the powers of a
Quincy-- as I heard it anyway.
Then later on, they said
you were of no use to them.
And you were merely an observer
in the end, when Yoshino died.
Which one do you
think is the truth?
-What do you think?
URAHARA: Who knows?
But did you ever
think about what
would happen if you were
able to regain your powers
and about what you
might be capable of?
-No, what I think
about is the fact
that if I hadn't been
there, she might have lived.
-Do you know that for sure?
-I have to find out
the truth for myself.
-Too preserve your
honor as a Quincy?
-Yes.
That's just the kind
of tribe we are.
-He's young.
But that's not such a
bad thing to be at all.
-Don't be afraid, boy.
Everything's all right now.
Just stay right there.
What the-- wow.
These monsters
really are targeting
the souls of living humans.
-Heh.
Then I'll slice
every last of them!
UGAKI: Master Kariya?
-Yes?
What is it?
-A Soul Reaper has begun to
destroy some of the Bittos.
-Hm.
How impertinent.
Imagine his surprise
when he learns
what happens when
Bittos are damaged.
[grunting]
[whimpering]
-Hey, you don't look
hurt or wounded.
Oh, that's right.
You can't even hear me.
Hm?
-[whimpers]
-Hm?
Looks like I only
made more of them.
BOY: No, no!
No!
RENJI: Come on, boy.
You're coming with me.
Give me all you got.
100 or 500, bring it on.
I'll destroy you all!
[theme music]
RIRIN: Ichigo, Kisuke
says he finished
building the sensor we
need to track the Bounts.
ICHIGO: All right!
Now we'll know where they are.
RIRIN: He said he designed
it to match you perfectly.
ICHIGO: To match me?
RIRIN: Yeah!
And he said he can't wait to
see the look on your face.
ICHIGO: I've got a really
bad feeling about this.
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers!
GROUP: Golden!
CASHIER: Bye!
Thank you!
-[grunt]
CASHIER: Goodness, Rangiku.
Are you going on a trip?
-Yes, to the World
of the Living.
And the cosmetics there
just don't work for me.
So I take my own.
It's such a drag
women have to carry
around so much stuff, huh?
I was hoping to cut my hair.
But I knew if I took the
time, the captain would just
freak out.
I don't know why he
always has to be so fussy.
-Oh, so I'm fussy, am I?
-[gasp] Oh, Captain.
-Get your butt in gear already!