[theme music]
VOICEOVER: Soul Reapers.
The spiritual guardians to
the world of the living.
Their job is to maintain the
balance between the myriad
of good and evil souls
that fill this world.
Sosuke Aizen, who
betrayed the Soul Society
and left the Seireitei in chaos
has set his plan into motion,
and the battle between the
Arrancars and the Soul Reapers
has finally begun
to manifest itself.
-Dance, Sode no Shirayuki.
Some no mai.
Tsukishiro!
-Which one?
Which one of you
is the strongest?
Who's gonna take me on?
-Awaken, Snip Tijerita.
VOICEOVER: Captain
Hitsugaya, Renji, and Rangiku
found their abilities
challenged as they were forced
to face the formidable
power of the Arrancar,
and the sight of Rukia
being seriously injured
set Ichigo's blood afire.
-You bastard.
Bankai!
VOICEOVER: Feeling they were
equal to the task, Captain
Histugaya and Renji
through their best attacks
at their adversaries,
but the Arrancars
countered by releasing
their Zanpakutos, which
rendered the Soul
Reapers' attacks useless.
-Huh?
MAN (OVER RADIO): Squad 10.
Come in, Lieutenant Matsumoto.
The restriction removal
has been authorized.
-Message received.
Captain!
Renji!
Gentai Kaijo has been approved.
Go full power.
-It's finally come.
-About damn time.
-What's this?
-Activating Gentei Kaijo.
-Activating Gentei Kaijo!
-They've been
granted Gentei Kaijo?
-What is that?
-Gentei Kaijo.
We captains and lieutenants
of the 13 Court Guard Squads,
in order to avoid unnecessarily
influencing the spirits
in the world of the living--
-Must wear a Gentei Reign,
a spirit restriction seal
in the form of a
squad badge somewhere
on our bodies when we come here.
It severely restricts
our spiritual powers.
-And it can limit
our powers by 80%.
That means--
-That now--
We're five times stronger!
-You're too slow.
When you first came
here, it seemed
you were able to move much
faster than you're moving now.
You'll need to be
that fast again.
What's that technique called?
-Heh.
It's Sonido.
-I see.
We have our own technique,
and we call it Slash Step.
[groan]
-It's over, Shawlong Koufang.
-Growl, Haineko!
-Ryusenka!
-Hikotsu Taiho!
[scream]
-Enough!
We must retreat for now!
-It's too late.
RANGIKU: Captain!
Captain!
Orihim!
Orihime!
Get over here, quickly!
Please hurry!
-Dammit.
That was close.
I was lucky that the
Gentei Kaijo gave me
the element of surprise, and
I was able to find an opening.
If he'd been at full
strength from the beginning
of the fight, I might not
have been so fortunate.
I sure as hell hope
all the other Arrancars
aren't as powerful
as those two were.
Because if that's true,
we've got trouble.
Ichigo--
-Argh!
Come on, jerk!
What's that idiot doing?
I'm gonna crush his balls
when he gets back here.
KEIGO: Hey.
I'm back.
-I'm back?
Keigo, you jerk!
How long's it take to get some
juice from a vending machine?
You have to squeeze the-- huh?
-Well, you see, it's like this.
[moaning]
-See, um-- well, uh-- here's
what kind of happened, sis.
I was going to buy the
juice, and I saw these guys
just lying there in the road.
And when I rescued them, I kind
of forgot about buying juice.
And then I guess
I told them they
could stay at our
house for a while.
Ah!
But if you're absolutely
not cool with that,
I suppose I could try to suck up
enough birth to tell these guys
that there's no roo, and
I'll just to-- ha ha--
-Why, you-- you did an
incredibly good deed!
-Don't kill me!
-Oh!
Wow!
You're gonna let them
both stay with us?
Well, you know me, I'm
totally cool with that!
-Wait a minute.
Have you lost it?
-What?
-That's not what I meant.
I meant, shouldn't we
check with Mom and Dad?
I mean, they might
not-- you know--
-Well, hello.
I'm Keigo's sister, Mizuho.
-We ne talk!
-You need to calm yourself
down and put a cork in it.
After all, you're the one who
brought 'em here, remember?
-Yeah, but you
see-- I was counting
on you being the bad
guy and telling them
they couldn't stay, 'cause
I didn't have the guts!
I knew once they got a look
at you, you'd scare 'em off,
and I wouldn't have to
worry about 'em anymore.
-Oh.
I see.
Too bad.
I'm fine with them here.
-How can you be fine with that?
They're complete strangers!
They might be fugitives
from prison, or something!
-Don't worry.
I want to be the kind of
sister who trusts her brother's
judgement, even if
he chooses to bring
a total stranger into my home.
That's the kind of sister
I truly want to become.
-Cut that out!
Don't give me that stuff about
the sister you want to become.
That's a bunch of nonsense!
-The truth is I love
guys with shaved heads.
-A-ha!
The real truth comes out!
And by the way, he doesn't
have a shaved head.
The guy's bald!
-Who says I'm bald?
-What?
Did I say that?
You're not bald.
-Argh!
Dammit.
What is this guy?
[groan]
-Yah!
[pained grunts]
[shout]
[laughter]
-Is that all there
is to your Bankai?
I gotta say, you've turned out
to be a real disappointment.
You used your Bankai, and all
it gives you is average speed?
Huh?
-Getsuga Tensho!
-Damn.
What was that?
Ulquiorra didn't mention
that move in his report
about your attacks, Soul Repaer.
Not a word.
-So maybe I won't be
disappointing after all,
Arrancar.
-Guess I might have
been wrong about you.
It may turn out that you're
worth killing after all.
VOICE: Ichigo.
What are you smirking about?
You're acting awfully confident.
Huh?
-Hold on.
Just a little longer.
-Do you really think you
can handle this alone?
ICHIGO: Dammit.
He barely has a scratch.
He took the full force
of my Getsuga Tensho,
and he acts like it was nothing.
The Black Getsuga
Tensho is his technique.
If I use it, it might allow
him to control more quickly.
But the reality is I can only
use it two or three more times
before he'll take
control, anyway.
What do I do?
-Hey, Soul Reaper.
Just how long are you
gonna stand there?
-Ichigo.
-All right, then.
Now it's my turn.
-Put your sword away, Grimmjow.
-Tosen?
He's the captain who
defected with Aizen.
-You want to explain
to me why you're here?
-You ask why?
You can't be serious.
You chose to invade the world
of the living on your own,
and you took five Arrancars
without permission.
Then you lost them in battle.
You have disobeyed orders.
You understand that
much, don't you?
Lord Aizen is quite
upset with you, Grimmjow.
Come.
Your punishment for these acts
will be decided in Hueco Mundo.
-Fine, then.
Let's go.
-Hey, you!
Hold on!
Where the hell do you
think you're going?
-Shut up, Soul Reaper.
I'm going home.
Back home to Hueco Mundo.
-No, you're not!
You come here and you attack
us, and then you just leave?
You gotta be kidding me!
Get back down here!
This fight isn't over
until I say it is, dammit!
-Get over it!
The only reason why you're still
alive is because I'm leaving.
Consider yourself lucky.
That attack you
just used obviously
took its toll as well.
I can see it in your face.
I'd say you have about two
or three attacks left in you.
But still, even if you were able
to do it a hundred more times,
you wouldn't stand a chance of
beating me in my release mode.
-Release mode?
What the hell's that?
-Don't forget my
name, Soul Reaper.
And you'd better pray that
you never hear it again.
Grimmjow Jaegerjaquez.
Because the next time you hear
my name, you'll be a dead man.
I promise.
-Where did the Arrancar go?
Back to Hueco Mundo?
Did you win?
-I lost.
-You stupid idiot.
The fact that you're still
alive means that you won.
-You know that's not true.
If you were me, you'd
feel the same way.
Truth is, I haven't been
able to protect anyone.
I couldn't defeat our enemies.
I was useless.
I lost.
Grimmjow.
-Kisuke.
Kisuke.
-It's go be OK, Ururu.
-Welcome back, Grimmjow.
[theme music]
GRIMMJOW: The Arrancar used
some sort of nerve radar
called Pesquisa to search
out spiritual pressure.
Just think, Ichigo.
If you had something
like that, you'd
be able to find where we are.
ICHIGO: Shut up.
I won't need that to find
where you're hiding out.
GRIMMJOW: We'll have a warm
welcome waiting for you.
[theme music]
KON: Illustrated
Guide to Soul Reapers.
-Stop beating me like a drum!
-No matter how you slice
it, when your sword cuts us,
it makes our wounds
heal instantly!
Ha ha!
-Yah!
Ah?
Allow me to explain.
Every time Hisagomaru heals a
wound or cut, a red gauge on it
rises like a thermometer.
And when it is
completely full, it
changes automatically into
the Vermilion Hisagomaru.
Then it has the
amazing attack power
of spitting out all the
injuries it's absorbed.
-Yeah.