[HIROSHI'S MOM] C'mon, Hiroshi,
quit dragging your feet.
[HIROSHI]
Why do I have to go with you?
[HIROSHI'S MOM]
Because we should be friendly
and start on good terms
with the neighbors.
Doesn't the air feel so fresh?
I think it's all the
greenery around here.
[HIROSHI]
Huh, look at that.
Don't you think there's
something kind of weird
about this house, mom?
How so?
[HIROSHI] Well, there's only one
window on the whole building.
It's not much of a view looking
out onto the side of our house.
[HIROSHI'S MOM]
Really, Hiroshi.
You shouldn't be so judgmental
of other peoples' taste.
[doorbell rings]
[HIROSHI'S MOM]
Huh. Guess no one's home.
[doorbell rings]
[WOMAN A]
Yes? Who is it?
[HIROSHI'S MOM] Hello!
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I hope we're not intruding,
but we're the Sakaguchis,
and we just moved in
next door to you.
We wanted to take a moment
to introduce ourselves
to all of our new neighbors.
Here, we brought you
a little gift, too.
It's not much, but I
hope you like it.
[WOMAN A] Oh, thank you.
You shouldn't have.
[HIROSHI'S MOM]
Also, I was wondering.
Do the Numages work
during the day?
No one was home earlier.
Who knows? That house is always
quiet and locked up tight.
But at night, you can
sometimes see a silhouette
in the upstairs window,
so someone must be there.
They just hardly ever
go outside, I guess.
[HIROSHI'S MOM] The rumors
on the block are that a
middle-aged woman
lives there alone.
Some kind of strange, eccentric
type, from what I gathered.
She seems to avoid contact
with the outside world,
isn't that odd?
I guess. But you haven't
actually gotten the chance
to meet this woman yourself,
have you?
I've rung the bell
several times now.
But so far no one's
answered the door.
I think it's very sad.
Thanks for dinner.
What? Finished already?
[HIROSHI] Yeah, I wanna
make sure I get my stuff
unpacked tonight.
Of course the window looks
right into my room.
So much for privacy.
[NUMAGE] Young man...
Young man... Young man...
[NUMAGE] Good evening.
Are you asleep in there?
How are you feeling tonight?
[HIROSHI]
Who is that?
[NUMAGE]
Young man... Young man...
There you are.
[HIROSHI gasps]
[NUMAGE] Are you finding your
new house to your liking?
Young man, how are
you feeling tonight?
Come by and visit me someday.
I'll be waiting for you in here
with the front door unlocked.
[HIROSHI]
What the hell was that thing?
[NUMAGE]
Young man... Young man...
How are you feeling tonight?
[HIROSHI gasps]
[NUMAGE]
Are you asleep in your bed?
Come, let me see your face.
Why didn't you visit me today?
I was waiting for you
with so many sweets.
Shall I come over and see
you instead, then? In your room?
[HIROSHI gasps]
[NUMAGE]
I'm on my way.
What? Are you crazy?
[gasps]
[HIROSHI gasps]
[NUMAGE] There's a good boy.
I'll pass you the laundry pole.
Make sure you grab it.
Hold it tight, okay?
[NUMAGE] I'll use it to cross
over so I can visit you.
[HIROSHI shouts]
What are you doing?
[NUMAGE gasps]
[HIROSHI gasps] Mom! Dad!
Quick, you gotta wake up!
What are you talking about,
son, I don't see anybody.
[HIROSHI'S MOM] And there's no
laundry pole outside, either.
You've gotta believe me!
It happened, I swear
she was out there!
That creepy woman wanted
to come over here.
It's fine. You were probably
just having a nightmare.
It's the second night
of this, dad!
[NUMAGE] Young man....
Oh, young man....
Are you there?
[gasps]
[NUMAGE] Are you awake? How are
you feeling tonight, hm?
[HIROSHI]
Damn it, not again!
[NUMAGE]
Are you asleep right now?
Please, let me see
your pretty face.
Just wait a bit longer.
I'll be joining you soon.
It won't take much more time.
My hands can almost
reach your window.
I'll knock on the glass shortly.
Make sure you open up when I do.
Then I'll be able to see you all
I want. Doesn't that sound nice?
Oh, it's still too far.
Just out of reach.
Don't worry, it won't be long.
I'll be there soon.
I'm coming for you.
[RIKO sobs]
Papa died. He's gone!
[RIKO]
When I was a little girl,
I had terrible, recurring dreams
about my father dying.
No, Riko! Ha, ha! Your papa
is not gonna die. Promise.
[RIKO]
No matter what he said,
my anxiety about it
never went away.
[RIKO] My father's death
is the one thing I fear
most in this world.
If he died, I don't
know what I'd do.
[RIKO] When I married into the
prestigious Tokura family,
they insisted we have
a traditional wedding.
[RIKO] Father. Mother.
Grandfather. Grandmother.
I know I come from nothing,
so thanks for accepting me.
[TOMOKA]
I was thinking, Riko.
[RIKO]
Hm?
From now on. I guess I should
start calling you "sister", huh?
Oh, right.
I'd like that, Tomoka.
[RIKO] My husband, Makoto,
defied his own family
in order to marry me. I didn't
want him to regret it.
[MAKOTO]
Keep your spirits up, Riko.
I'm sure they'll warm up
to you eventually.
[RIKO]
Hm.
[RIKO gasps]
[MAKOTO] Oh, yeah. Those are
my great-grandparents.
They couldn't come to the
wedding on account of their age.
Great-granddad? Great-grandma?
Let me introduce you
to my wife, Riko.
It's an honor to meet you.
[RIKO'S DAD breathes heavily]
Riko. Riko!
[RIKO sobs] I'm right here.
Can you see me, Papa?
[RIKO'S DAD] Riko. I hope you
have a happy life with Makoto.
[RIKO gasps]
Papa!
[MAKOTO sighs] You had that
same dream again, didn't you?
[RIKO] I'm so sorry. I don't
know why it keeps happening.
[MAKOTO] It's okay.
Come on. Get some sleep.
[MAKOTO'S MOM laughs] You are
just too much, Tomoka.
[TOMOKA] Hey! He, he. Come on!
Not you, too, Dad. Stop it!
Grandma, Grandpa,
you should know better!
[RIKO] This house is gigantic,
almost too big.
[RIKO gasps]
Wait. Are you?
[yells] There's a ghost.
I saw it! Right there!
[MAKOTO]
They're not ghosts, exactly.
[RIKO exhales]
Then what are they?
Even the way your
great-grandparents look
is kind of strange.
I think the person you
thought was a ghost
is actually my
great-great-grandmother.
It's nothing to worry about,
she's just old.
She's your what?
How can she still be alive?
She must be ancient.
She's a hundred
and twenty-five.
[RIKO]
No way, are you kidding me?
I didn't think people could
really live that long.
There are a couple of other
relatives you haven't met
that live here, too.
My great-aunt and
my great-uncle.
I think that should
account for everyone.
Those two are
really faint, though.
They're almost gone.
But if you look closely,
you can still see them.
What do you mean "almost gone"?
[MAKOTO] My great-great
grandfather and his
mother used to be around, too.
But they disappeared
a while ago.
[RIKO] I don't understand.
They disappeared?
[MAKOTO] Because,
they're just after-images.
[RIKO] My grandfather-in-law
died the next year,
and the family gathered
for his funeral.
[MONKS chant]
[RIKO'S DAD]
It's been a while, Riko.
[RIKO] I know.
Thanks for coming today,
Papa, it means a lot to me.
Tell me, dear. Are they
treating you well?
Has his family accepted you?
[RIKO]
Yeah.
Thank you so much for travelling
all this way to be here with us.
[RIKO'S DAD] Think nothing
of it. Well then, Makoto,
be sure to take care of my
little girl for me. Please.
You can count on me, Sir.
I promise.
[MAKOTO] Let's go, Riko.
My family's here.
They're already gathering
in the living room.
[RIKO gasps]
[MAKOTO] I guess this is
the first time for you.
[MAKOTO'S DAD]
My father, Ryouzou,
was honored at his funeral.
It was a beautiful service.
Now that it's over,
it's time that we begin.
Everyone.
Focus all of your thoughts
on Ryouzou and his image.
Use every ounce of
strength to envision him.
His actual body
may be cremated,
but with the combined
will of our family,
my father will appear
before us once again.
That's it, everyone. Focus!
Think with all your might.
[TOKURA FAMILY mutters]
Father!
[MAKOTO'S DAD]
We will see you again, Father.
Father!
[MAKOTO'S DAD] Come to us!
[TOKURA FAMILY chatters]
[RIKO gasps]
[MAKOTO] It's not that Grandpa
actually came back to life,
and I wouldn't call him a
ghost or spirit, either.
He's simply a construct
formed by my family's will.
Nothing more. We call
them after-images.
We see them,
but they don't really have any
physical presence to speak of.
They serve a purpose. They seem
real whenever we talk to them.
It's like the loved ones who've
passed away are still there.
Even though that comfort is an
illusion we create ourselves.
Still, the after-images only
ever say things that the
living imagine they would.
Yet, despite knowing
they aren't alive,
we keep making them every
time a family member dies.
They continue to function
as part of our family,
as if nothing had
ever happened.
And help fill the void
that's left behind
when we lose someone.
A bandage for our pain.
But they don't last.
As the years go by,
they begin to grow fainter
and more transparent.
The images fade.
They start degrading.
After around twenty years,
they disappear completely.
Finally leaving this world.
But those twenty years
help the living cope.
It gives us the chance
for a gentle goodbye.
To gradually let go
of those we love.
It's been almost two decades
since we created the after-image
of my great-great-grandmother.
She'll probably be
vanishing sometime soon.
That's why you thought
she was a ghost.
Honestly, I don't think anyone
in our family pays her much
mind these days. I know
I don't, not anymore.
Of course, that's only
because we've had an extra
twenty-two years to come to
terms with saying goodbye
to her for good.
[RIKO]
So, Makoto...
Someday, when my father
dies and it's not a dream,
would we be able to make
an after-image of him, too?
I had a feeling you'd ask
me that. I don't know.
But I understand why you'd
want an after-image
of your own family.
[MAKOTO'S DAD]
You can't be serious, Makoto.
It's completely
out of the question.
What would be the point
in creating an after-image
of Riko's father? Have you
thought this through at all?
[MAKOTO'S DAD] I'm sorry.
It's just not going to happen.
[TOMOKA]
Mm.
[door clatters]
[RIKO]
Please forgive me!
It was wrong of me
to ask you for this.
I'm sorry for making such a
self-centered request of you.
--[MAKOTO'S GRANDMA] Hmm...
--[MAKOTO'S MOM scoffs]
[RIKO sobs]
[TOMOKA]
Hey, Sister.
Please don't think too badly
of our mom and dad, okay?
They're both really nice.
Sometimes they just
come off as mean.
I know. And I realize that
it was selfish of me
to ask for such a thing.
I'll go apologize to
them again tomorrow,
and hopefully this time
they'll forgive me.
Thank you, though.
For always being there
and worrying about me.
Well of course I'm going to
be here for you, sister,
I love you after all.
[RIKO]
I appreciate it.
And never forget that
I love you, too, Tomoka.
[RIKO] I was wondering.
About Tomoka.
[sighs]
I guess you noticed.
My sister is an
after-image.
[MAKOTO] She died from
an illness ten years ago.
Lately, she's begun
to fade a little bit.
Time is catching up to her,
and she's disappearing.
[TOMOKA]
I was wondering, Mom.
Yes, what is it,
my darling one?
[TOMOKA] Could you not
be so hard on Riko?
She's a really good wife.
[sighs] I understand that,
but it can be so difficult.
[TOMOKA] I love you, Mom.
I want to stay with you forever.
Wouldn't it be nice if I never
left the house when I grew up?
It means I'd never
get married, but still...
It'd be okay with you,
right, mom?
Yes, of course, my dear.
Stay as long as you like.
You can stay here
with Mommy forever.
[RIKO]
As the months went by,
Makoto's great-
great-grandmother,
his great-aunt, and his
great-uncle disappeared.
His great-grandparents
also started looking
more transparent. Almost foggy.
Eventually there was another
family funeral to attend,
and I took part
in the ceremony
to conjure up
another after-image.
I had already done so
several times by that point.
And I tried my hardest to
help as a member of the
Tokura family.
Still, even though it'd been
eight years since my wedding,
my in-laws remained distant.
As if they had no desire
to get to know me at all.
I figured it had
to be my own fault,
and I put extra effort
into winning them over.
[RIKO pants] Honey, wait!
You forgot your--
You look nice.
[MAKOTO] Ha, I thought we
agreed to meet at the station
like we usually do.
[MORI] Aw, but I wanted to
see you as soon as possible.
[MAKOTO, MORI laugh]
[RIKO] That was Mori from your
office this morning, wasn't it?
[RIKO] The two of you
are having an affair.
We are.
[RIKO gasps] So... what does
that mean for the two of us?
I'll be honest with you.
I intend to marry her
someday in the future.
You will not! I refuse
to let you divorce me!
Riko. Don't worry, okay?
I'm not going to
end our marriage.
I'll fulfill my duties.
It's my responsibil--
What are you talking about?
How are you going to marry
her without divorcing me first,
you lying bastard?
Let's see what she has
to say about this.
No, don't!
You let go of me!
[MAKOTO]
I said to stop!
--[slap]
--[RIKO gasps]
[MAKOTO gasps]
[MAKOTO]
I'm... I'm so sorry, Riko.
[RIKO gasps]
I should've... been honest.
And told you the truth.
What?
It was ten years ago.
We were supposed to
be married soon,
but then it happened.
The day before our
engagement ceremony.
[ambulance sirens]
[MAKOTO] You were in a serious
car accident... and you died.
I begged my father,
down on my hands and knees.
I wanted us to make an
after-image of you.
[TOKURA FAMILY chattering]
[MAKOTO]
Riko!
You're lying. I'm alive.
[MAKOTO]
If you don't believe me,
then go to your family's house.
There's a marker for you
on the family plot.
That will be your proof.
Then... I really am just...
[RIKO]
I am an after-image.
In ten years,
I'll be gone forever.
[RIKO]
Oddly enough,
realizing this took a
weight off my shoulders.
The next day, I quietly slipped
out of the Tokura house.
[TOMOKA]
Hey, sister.
Where are you going?
[RIKO]
After apologizing profusely,
I bade my sister-in-law goodbye.
Thinking back on it now,
I wonder what Makoto thought
about having a wife
that cried so often.
Always after dreaming
of her father's death.
In fact, I don't think I
ever cried from a dream
about my husband dying.
I suppose. I probably owe
him an apology, too.
Ten short years before I vanish.
I wonder which one of us will
go first, my father or me?
Riko? Is something wrong?
Papa... I'm coming home.