[OGI panting]
[OGI grunts]
[OGI pants]
[OGI] For a minute
there, I was scared.
I didn't think I'd make
it back to Japan alive.
I risked my life to
bring this treasure back.
[SUGIO] You sure that's
what this is, Ogi?
It just looks like
an old jar to me.
I hope it's full of
gold or something.
No, nectar.
Wait, that's it? Must be good.
You've no idea, Sugio.
I got this nectar from
a tribe in South America
I happened across.
They actually worship
the giant plant
that they extract
the stuff from.
The nectar is so delicious
that it tastes like it's imbued
with the power of the gods.
Trust me, you've never tasted
anything like this before.
It's heavenly.
[sighs] Yeah, yeah,
no need to lay it on thick.
It's so sweet.
Seriously unbelievable!
Wanna have a little taste?
[SUGIO] Sure, why not.
Hand the jar over.
Okay, but first, I need to
warn you not to be noticed
while you're eating it. That's
real important apparently.
Huh? Who besides you
would notice me?
Lemme guess.
Is there some kind of
angry nectar god watching?
[OGI laughs]
Yeah, I suppose it must sound
pretty damn crazy to you.
But the tribespeople
were especially adamant
about making sure I
understood what they said.
So whatever you do,
don't be noticed.
It's good!
[knocking]
[KAMEDA]
Hey, Ogi! You home or what?
[SUGIO] What are you
doing back there, Kameda?
Using the side entrance.
Look, the window's open.
That's not cool, man. You can't
just break into Ogi's house.
[KAMEDA]
Come on, he won't mind.
[SUGIO]
There it is.
[KAMEDA]
Time to try this famous nectar.
I'm sure he won't
miss any of it.
But just a taste,
okay, you guys?
I don't want Ogi to
be pissed off at me.
Huh. I'm sure it'll be fine.
Oh, wow. This stuff's amazing!
Here, you gotta try it.
You're right.
I don't even know
how to describe it
except to say it's delicious.
Where'd he get it?
I could eat this stuff all day.
Mm! This is incredible!
I'm not leaving after just
one taste of this stuff.
Let's eat the whole jar.
No way, we can't do that.
This is Ogi's nectar, man.
There's so much.
It's not fair for him
to keep it all to himself.
[YUE]
Before we eat more,
do you smell something
funky in here?
Yeah. Like someone left
meat out and it rotted.
[YUE] I think it's
coming from over here.
[YUE gasps] Does that look
like blood to you guys, too?
[ALL gasping]
I don't know, but... we should
probably get outta here.
[YASUMIN] Come on, you've
got way more than us, man!
[KAMEDA]
I measured it out equally.
Oh, that's it!
So good. Heh!
[YASUMIN]
Aw, yum!
What part of South America does
this delicious stuff come from?
[YASUMIN]
I dunno.
I doubt Ogi could find
it again if he tried.
[ALL gasping]
[RIRUKO] What the hell
just happened to him?
I... think he just exploded.
Look there. His glasses.
[SUGIO]
No, this isn't possible.
How did he get smashed
against the wall?
Call the police!
Don't you dare.
That'll cause problems.
Then what are we
supposed to do?
He's been splattered
all over my room!
[SUGIO]
I don't get it.
How did this happen?
[KAMEDA] Maybe we're all
having the same nightmare.
This can't be real life.
You're right.
This is just a dream.
Soon we'll wake up.
Well, I hope the dream started
after we found this
nectar, at least.
I'd be so depressed if
this stuff wasn't real.
[ALL scream]
[YUE]
Ri-Riruko!
But she was just sitting there!
It's the nectar.
I think if we keep eating it,
we're gonna explode.
No! That doesn't make
a lick of sense.
All of us had the
same amount of it!
Are we all gonna die?
Is this going to
happen to me, too?
Ogi said not to be noticed
when you drink this.
I have no idea what that means,
but that's what
the tribe told him.
So... maybe we just
don't eat it anymore.
[SUGIO groans]
It's no use.
Everything I try tastes so bad.
I can't even swallow it.
[SUGIO]
Ever since I tried that nectar,
I haven't been able
to eat any food.
[YUE]
Mm-hmm...
[SUGIO] The only thing
I can think about is
filling my mouth with
this damn exploding stuff.
Also...
...have you seen the news?
They've found several other
flattened bodies around town,
not just Riruko and Yasumin.
[YUE] I thought for sure
one of them would be Kameda,
but it wasn't.
That's true,
but I did notice that
some of his friends
had been killed.
They must've eaten some of
that cursed nectar themselves.
[SUGIO] Maybe he got
scared and gave it away
so he wouldn't be tempted by it.
[KAMEDA]
Hey, long time no see, guys.
[SUGIO]
Kameda.
Damn, you guys look
really skinny.
I bet I know why.
You can't eat the
food here, huh?
[YUE] I wish we'd never
tried this nectar.
I know.
It's the only thing that
tastes okay to us anymore.
Only, it's way too dangerous
for us to eat now.
You could drink it...
...as long as you were sure
that you weren't bein' noticed.
Well, yeah.
[YUE]
Huh?
I've tested a few things
to see how it works--
what gets you noticed
and what lets you
survive the nectar.
What do you mean "tested"?
What have you been doing?
[KAMEDA]
Don't look at me like that.
Those guys kept beggin' me
for more of the stuff.
[SUGIO, YUE gasping]
[chuckles]
[SUGIO]
So... did you find a trick?
[KAMEDA] No. I gave
away the last of mine.
Still have no idea
how people get noticed.
I can't stand it anymore.
I have to eat some!
[KAMEDA]
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait, hold on.
[YUE gasps]
It's so good.
Dammit! I'm having some, too!
[YUE]
So good!
That time I saw it.
Saw what?
I saw some giant thing
swoop down and smash Sugio
like he was just a
little insect. [laughs]
Yes! Something from the sky
crushed him into a pulp.
I get it. Why didn't
I realize it earlier?
We just can't let it smash us!
I'll show you!
Wait, come back!
[YUE laughing]
See! I'll be fine in the water.
It can't get me out here.
[gasps] This is perfect.
[laughing]
[KAMEDA gasps]
[KAMEDA]
What've we got here?
A map?
[KAMEDA panting]
[KAMEDA] This thing has led me
all the way to South America.
It's gotta take me to the tribe
that gave Ogi the
nectar to begin with.
[KAMEDA]
Dammit. So many mosquitos.
[KAMEDA grunting]
[KAMEDA]
What kind of a plant is this?
No way.
One of its branches just
vanished into thin air.
Now it's back.
What's going on with this tree?
[sniffing] That's it.
The tree smells like the nectar.
I see now!
This is where it must come
from! The source! [laughs]
[KAMEDA grunts, chuckles]
I'll have all the nectar
I could ever want!
[laughing]
[KAMEDA]
U-Uh--
[SAKIYAMA] All the girls at
school are in love with Ootsuka.
Of course they are.
When the two of us
became an item,
they all started ignoring me.
But I didn't care.
Last week, though,
Ootsuka was hospitalized
with mysterious pains
in his stomach.
And now, well...
[chewing]
[SOUICHI giggles]
What a genius I am.
[SAKIYAMA]
Hm?
[SOUICHI giggles]
Looky here.
I've got sharp fangs now!
[SOUICHI giggles]
[SAKIYAMA]
Oh, hey there.
What are you ladies
talking about?
Can you believe that...
[SOUICHI]
What? She dares to ignore me?
Hey. Hey, Souichi!
People are saying you got
a job delivering papers.
[MALE STUDENT B] Like you'd
ever wake up that early.
Uh, what? I have no idea
what you're talking about.
Okay, fine, darn it.
Who told you guys about
my cool new job?
Wait. It's really true?
[RANDOM MALE STUDENT A]
Did you hear?
Souichi joined an adult baseball
team as a pinch hitter
and he hit a home run
in his first game!
[RANDOM FEMALE STUDENT A]
Hey, listen.
I heard Souichi helped a
sick old lady he didn't know
cross the street
yesterday. Isn't he nice?
[FEMALE STUDENT A]
Finally! There you guys are.
I have super big news!
Well come on, let's hear it.
You aren't gonna
believe this gossip.
Souichi's cousin...
...is Kentarou Kagawa!
You know, the guy
from The Smogs!
[FEMALE STUDENT B]
Huh?!
[SOUICHI sighs] Oh, so you
want an autograph, huh?
Come on, don't tease
us. Pretty please?
It shouldn't be
that hard, right?
Just have him sign something
as a favor for his cousin!
Oh, darn, how'd you find out?
I was trying to keep
that stuff a secret.
I didn't want you
guys to know about
my favorite cousin, Kentarou.
Ah, well, I guess there's
nothing I can do about it.
I'll get you some autographs.
In fact, I can probably
get him to sign something
for each of you girls.
[GIRLS squeal]
[GIRLS]
I love you so much, Souichi!
You're the best boy in school!
[SOUICHI]
Ha! And just like that,
all the girls here
are in love with me.
It didn't take long for
them to change their tunes.
[giggles] Ooh,
I've got a good idea.
I'll say I could only
get one autograph
and make them fight
tooth and nail for it.
Whoever beats the other girls
will be the one who
loves me the most.
[SOUICHI giggles]
[SAKIYAMA]
Am I doing this right?
I brought flowers, but what
if he thinks that's stupid?
What if he laughs at me?
No. I'm here.
I can't turn back now.
Do you mind a visitor?
Oh, hey! It's good to see you.
You didn't have to stop by.
[SAKIYAMA]
Don't be silly.
[SAKIYAMA gasps]
[MADOKA gasps]
Hi there, Midori.
[SAKIYAMA]
Oh, uh, hey, Madoka.
What are you doing up here?
I was just in the neighborhood
and figured I'd stop by.
I hate that you went
the trouble of coming,
but I'm really glad
you both did.
Is your stomach
feeling any better?
[OOTSUKA]
Yeah. I'm almost back to normal.
It definitely doesn't hurt
like it did a few nights ago
when I thought I was dying.
I should be gettin'
outta here pretty soon.
[SAKIYAMA]
Good.
More importantly, though,
did you hear that Souichi
saved a little kid
from being hit by a
car the other day?
The dude could've been killed!
Huh?
And apparently the principal was
really impressed by his bravery.
[SAKIYAMA] Somehow, overnight,
Souichi became a hero.
But I was more
concerned about Madoka.
What was she doing
at the hospital?
Did she like Ootsuka?
And if so, how did
he feel about her?
[SOUICHI] I heard Midori
Sakiyama from Class 6-1
likes Souichi.
[giggles] Actually, I heard
her say she loves him!
[FEMALE STUDENTS gossiping]
Hey, did you hear about Midori
Sakiyama from Class 6-1?
She says she's madly
in love with Souichi!
--[FEMALE STUDENTS gossiping]
--Spread the word,
Midori Sakiyama from
Class 6-1 loves Souichi.
She even wants to
be his girlfriend!
Love! Love! Love! Love!
[MALE STUDENT C]
Hey, guys!
You're not gonna
believe this news!
Midori is in love!
She's dating Souichi!
[STUDENTS gasp, chatter]
[SAKIYAMA gasps]
[RANDOM FEMALE STUDENT B]
That's so romantic.
A hero and his heroine!
[STUDENTS chattering]
Stop! I am not dating him!
He's a total creep!
Listen to me, everyone.
Souichi started that rumor
himself. I saw him do it.
He was hiding behind some bushes
where girls were gossiping.
I watched him talk
in a quiet voice.
It was like a
subconscious suggestion.
I bet he made up all those good
rumors about himself, too,
just to trick us
all into liking him!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[SOUICHI]
Crap. This is not good.
Fangs!
Is it true?
Were you lying to us
about all that stuff?
I bet you're not even Kentarou
Kagawa's cousin, are you?
Are you?!
You don't have
any proof, do you?
[SOUICHI giggles]
It's not nice to make up lies
about good people like me.
I have his autograph right here.
Look. Ta-da!
Seriously? This is the worst
handwriting I've ever seen!
t doesn't look anything
like his autograph
I've seen in magazines.
This is obviously something
he just threw together.
There's no possible way that
little creep could be related to
someone as famous as he is.
[RANDOM MALE STUDENT B]
Hey. Where'd Souichi go?
Over there! He's running away!
[STUDENTS laughing]
[SAKIYAMA] A few days
after I exposed Souichi,
something weird happened.
A disturbing photograph
showed up in our classroom,
taped to the blackboard
for everyone to see.
[RANDOM FEMALE STUDENT C]
What is that?
[RANDOM FEMALE STUDENT D]
It looks like it was
cut out of a magazine,
but that can't be right.
Her face is terrifying.
[FEMALE STUDENT J gasps]
I recognize that monster!
What's with you?
You can't be that scared
of her. It's just a picture.
It was in a fashion magazine
my mom brought home
from the grocery store.
[RANDOM MALE STUDENT C]
Nah, I don't buy it.
There's no way
someone this creepy
could actually be a model.
It's a joke.
[FEMALE STUDENT J]
No, look, it's a lipstick ad!
She's a highly respected model.
My sister didn't
sleep for a week
after she saw her
in the magazine.
[RANDOM MALE STUDENT C] Man,
just hurry up and tear it down.
[SAKIYAMA] Strange rumors
started going around
a few days later.
They spread through
our school like wildfire.
A couple of fourth graders
were heading home from school
when they came
across the creature.
It was already nighttime
and the streets were dark.
They couldn't make out
much of the woman's body,
but she was incredibly tall,
towering several feet over them.
She stood in the
middle of the road
and didn't say a word
to them--just stared.
It wasn't until they
turned to go the other way
that she finally said
something to them.
A single question.
[RANDOM FEMALE STUDENT E]
What was it?
[FEMALE STUDENT L] "Tell me.
Do you think I'm beautiful?"
By then, their eyes
were starting to
adjust to the darkness,
and slowly but surely,
her horrible face
came into view.
She was smiling.
They got scared
and tried to run,
but she chased after them.
She was so fast that she was
on their heels the whole time!
Her hair was flailing
wildly behind her,
like a crown of snakes!
"I'm going to gobble you up
whenever I catch you!"
That's what she told them!
You know that rumor?
The woman in it sounds like the
one in the photograph to me.
[ISHIZAKA]
Wait, who are you talking about?
You know, the picture that was
stuck up on the blackboard
the other day--the gross one.
--[YAMADA gasps]
--Oh, yeah. Right.
I kinda tried to forget
about that lady.
[RANDOM FEMALE STUDENT F]
I heard that model lives
somewhere around here.
[RANDOM FEMALE STUDENT G]
Huh?
[RANDOM FEMALE STUDENT F]
Yeah. Apparently, she goes
down to the Maiden's Abyss
on the edge of town
to bathe a lot.
[RANDOM FEMALE STUDENT G]
Ew. Why?
[RANDOM FEMALE STUDENT F] They
say that soaking in the swamp
will make you beautiful.
People come in from
around the world for it.
[MALE TEACHER A]
Hmm. Class,
I know many of you are upset
about some strange
rumors going around.
Rest assured there
is no truth to them.
There's no reason to be alarmed.
Moving on, we have a
happy announcement!
After a long stay
in the hospital,
Ootsuka is all better and
finally in class again.
[OOTSUKA chuckles]
It's good to be back.
[BOYS chattering]
[laughs]
You know, I don't mind coming to
school now that Ootsuka's here.
He makes it seem much better.
One hundred percent.
I don't even care about those
monster stories anymore.
[SAKIYAMA]
Mm-hmm.
By the way, did you hear
the rumor going around
about Madoka?
Huh? I don't think so.
What's the story?
[FEMALE STUDENT A] Someone
said she's been going down and
soaking in the mud at
Maiden's Abyss lately.
You know, the swamp they say is
supposed to make you beautiful.
And I believe it.
Look at her up
against that wall.
She's been standing there for
quite a while looking pretty.
It's so obvious that
she's hanging around
so Ootsuka will notice her.
So, what do you think
you should do, Midori?
If you don't make a move,
she'll steal Ootsuka right
out from under your nose.
[SAKIYAMA groans]
[SAKIYAMA gasps]
[SAKIYAMA]
It's so slimy.
But I have to do this.
It's worth it if it
will make me beautiful.
--[SOUICHI giggles]
--[SAKIYAMA gasps]
[SOUICHI] It worked! I can't
believe you fell for it!
Wha--Souichi.
What are you doing out here?
[SOUICHI giggles] I've been
following you, obviously.
I was wondering how long
it'd take before you did it.
Wading into the swamp
like an idiot.
I made up all those stories--
from the monster in the
middle of the road,
to the idea of Madoka rolling
around in the mud here,
everything was just
a rumor I created
so I could trick
you into tonight.
That magazine clipping
was surprisingly effective,
if I do say so myself.
[SOUICHI giggles]
No. Stop it.
Do not take pictures
of me like this.
[SOUICHI]
But that's the whole point!
I'm gonna tell the whole school
that you came to the swamp
to soak in mud because
you want to be beautiful.
It's payback for
embarrassing me so much.
[SAKIYAMA]
You gross little pervert.
You can't do this.
[SOUICHI]
Just watch!
Huh?
What the heck?
That was kinda weird.
I guess something
must've scared them off.
[SAKIYAMA gasps]
[gasping]
[FUCHI growls]
[whimpers]
[FUCHI]
You there. Boy.
Do you know what
a bad idea it is
to take my photograph
without permission?
How did you know I was
here in the first place?
You're disturbing
my beauty rest.
[FUCHI]
Did a publisher send you?
I'm a pro fashion
model, after all.
That's why anyone who
takes a photo of me
without my permission
has to be dealt with.
[laughs] I'm going to
make sure you never
make this mistake
again. [laughs]
Oh, yes. You look so
tender and delicious.
This will be a treat for me.
--[FUCHI laughing]
--[SAKIYAMA screaming]
[SAKIYAMA] That model
really was in our town.
I've never heard of such
a terrifying coincidence.
But... I wonder what
will happen to Souichi.
[SOUICHI]
Wha--
What a creepy... beautiful lady.