[VISITORS murmur]
[MALE PROMOTER A]
There you are, Mori.
Your new exhibition is turning
out to be a huge success.
Between your
popularity and talent,
you're now the standard all
artists will be held to.
I've been very lucky
to make it this far.
If I'm being honest, I owe much
of this success to my muse.
Nana has been an incredible
source of inspiration
in my recent endeavors.
[MORI gasps]
[gasps]
[MORI] Care to share your
impressions with me?
[MORI gasps]
I suppose. The painting
itself is well done.
But the model is a bit...
She's certainly pretty
at first glance.
But if you look closely,
she's got a really goofy face.
[TOMIE giggles]
[MORI]
I guess that's true.
[MORI chuckles]
[TOMIE giggles] I'm sorry.
But there's an easy fix.
You need to change your model.
I bet your paintings would
be even better, then.
[NANA] You're stopping?
Hey, what's the matter?
[MORI gasps]
Nothing. Trust me.
You're looking even
prettier than usual, Nana.
I'm positive the next
exhibition will be stellar.
[NANA giggles]
You are such a flatterer.
[TOMIE laughs]
Seriously?
I can't believe you're still
using this same girl.
[MORI gasps]
It's you.
And who exactly are
you supposed to be?
[TOMIE]
You remember what you said.
You told me you were ready
to end things with her.
And that after she was gone,
I'd be your new muse and
model in her place, right?
[NANA] What did you say?
Mori. Is that true?
O-Of course not!
Oh, come now. Are you
calling me a liar?
Allow me to refresh
your memory, then.
You said you were tired
of the Nana series,
that when you really
look at her face,
it's so silly that you can't
get motivated to paint. Hm.
[NANA] You. I had no idea
you felt that way about me.
You could have told me yourself.
[MORI] Nana, wait, no,
you've got it all wrong.
[door slams]
[MORI gasps]
I can't believe you.
What the hell was that?
Don't you realize what an
invaluable partner she's been?
Well. If you need a new model,
why don't you just use
me instead of her?
Doesn't that sound nice?
What was your name again?
I didn't catch it.
Oh, that? I suppose
you can call me Tomie.
[MORI] And how did you
find out where I live?
Please, with this giant house,
it wasn't much of a challenge.
[MORI] I wonder if that means
I'm going to have to deal
with uninvited visitors
like you in the future.
Disrupting my work.
Possibly. But you will never
meet another girl like me again,
I can promise you that.
You seem very sure of yourself.
[TOMIE]
Yes. Because, understand,
there's no other girl in the
world quite as perfect as me.
[MORI]
I can't say you lack confidence.
I hope you don't either.
You're a good painter,
I'll give you that.
But will you really be able to
capture my image on your canvas?
We'll see.
I've had plenty of fine artists
try their hands at my portrait.
But in the end, none of them
were able to complete it
in a satisfactory way.
That's my dream.
To have my beauty recorded so
that it will live on forever.
I want it to
be permanent. Eternal.
[MORI sighs]
There. I think it's finished.
[TOMIE] Wow, done already?
Great, let me see.
I'd say it turned
out wonderfully.
[TOMIE giggles]
This is a joke, right?
You can't actually believe
that this is a masterpiece.
[laughs]
Hey, what are you laughing at?
There's nothing funny
about this painting!
[TOMIE]
What are you, blind?
This thing doesn't convey
even a fraction of my beauty.
Oh... What a disappointment.
I obviously overestimated you.
[MORI] Hold on!
Don't leave yet. Please!
We're done here. I have no
use for talentless artists.
[door clatters]
[MORI] Damn it! What didn't she
like about the portrait I did?
[MORI]
Tsk! One more time.
Tomie. I have to
paint Tomie again.
I should be painting her now!
[MORI grunts]
[MORI]
Tomie... Tomie.
It's finished!
No!
[MORI grunts]
It's not right at all!
[MORI pants]
Tomie... Tomie!
--[bell chimes]
--[footsteps]
[MASUDA]
Mm! Hey. Look who it is.
[MORI] Huh? Masuda.
I guess it's been a while.
I heard your next big exhibition
got postponed for some reason.
I hope you haven't
been sick or anything.
Yeah, something like that.
[MASUDA] Oh, did you hear?
Iwata's career has been
seriously blowing
up lately, it's crazy.
Iwata? Are we thinking
about the same sculptor?
Yeah. He's been unveiling
amazing new works
on a regular basis these days.
I'm trying to remember
the title of the series.
It's the model's name, I think?
And you should see
this girl, she's gorgeous.
Huh, I wonder where he
found her. The only pieces
I ever saw Iwata do were
really depressing figurines.
I guess this model's
changed the way he sculpts.
I snapped a photo of them
in town the other day,
if you want to get an idea
of what I'm talking about.
Here you go.
I know it's far from
being my greatest shot.
The girl in question's face is
all blurry. Still hot, though.
It can't be! That's Tomie!
Yeah, that's the
name of the series!
Wait, you know this Tomie, too?
You've been holding out on me.
[knocking]
[MORI]
Iwata! Iwata!
Hey. Sorry it's late.
[IWATA]
Mori. Well, this is a surprise.
Something I can help you with
in the middle of the night?
Uh... maybe.
I heard earlier that you've
been making some really
groundbreaking works
of art lately.
I was wondering if
I could see a few.
I'm not doing any public
viewings of them from now on.
Tomie is mine alone.
[MORI grunts] You can't get
rid of me that easily.
Have you been able to recreate
Tomie's beauty and capture the
thing that makes
her so intoxicating?
I won't leave until I see
it with my own eyes,
I'll force my way
in if I have to.
Is that what you want me to do?
[IWATA] Stop! What are
you doing? Get out!
[MORI]
Shut up! I have to see!
[IWATA groans]
[MORI pants]
[MORI]
Tomie... Tomie...! Tomie!
[gasps]
[MORI]
Tomie?
[TOMIE]
Oh, thank god you're here!
--[MORI] Tomie.
--[TOMIE] Mori!
You have no idea
how scared I was.
Iwata just started smashing
all of his works out of rage
for some reason.
And after he managed to create
the perfect sculpture of me.
I was so excited,
thinking there'd be a
permanent record of my beauty.
But then he started
destroying them,
and I don't understand
why he'd do that!
Tomie. I promise that I'm gonna
make your wish come true.
Let me paint you again,
and this time I swear
that I'll capture you
perfectly on my canvas.
You mean it? For real?
Don't toy with me.
Of course I do.
[TOMIE gasps]
Oh, Mori. I'm so glad!
[MORI chuckles]
Tomie. You are gorgeous.
I don't even know
how you can be real.
You know, today?
Well, it's not the first time
this sorta thing's happened.
[MORI]
What do you mean?
[TOMIE] I've almost been
killed by many men before.
For some reason, it seems
like every one who
falls in love with me
eventually wants to kill me.
To tear me apart.
Isn't that strange?
[MORI gasps]
It's finished. I've done it.
It looks exactly like you.
A perfect recreation
of your beauty!
Here, what do you think?
It's the greatest
painting I've ever done!
How dare you... bastard.
What is that?! You're the
worst artist I've ever met!
You don't mean that. It's you.
An undeniable masterpiece.
I won't let you mock me.
I'm not some kind of monster!
No, please. I beg of you.
Just take a better look.
[TOMIE]
I don't need to!
You're mistaken. What could
be wrong with the portrait?
[TOMIE giggles]
Tomie? What are you laughing at?
Tomie. What's so damn funny?
--[MORI grunts, yells]
--[TOMIE gasps]
[TOMIE laughs]
[MORI]
Afterward...
[TOMIE laughs]
[MORI grunts]
--[TOMIE laughs]
--[MORI grunts]
[MORI] And yet. Even then,
Tomie didn't die.
[TOMIE laughs]
[MORI] Each dismembered
piece of her body
began to come to life.
To grow anew.
Her cells reproduced.
Creating more and
more flesh and bone.
What a horrible ability for
a woman like her to have.
I am certain that with time,
each piece I hacked apart will
grow to look exactly like her.
[TOMIE]
Mori? Is that you?
[MORI]
Tomie?
[engine sputters]
[ANZAI]
Sorry, it's no use.
Someone's gonna have
to come fix it.
But these mountains
are so remote.
How are we supposed to
find help out here?
[footsteps]
[KANA]
Hey, are we lost, Anzai?
[ANZAI]
Nah. Don't worry.
[KANA] But we've been walking
for more than an hour now.
Look over there.
I think I see a shed.
That means there must be some
kind of town nearby, I bet.
A bunch of kids.
They'll have parents.
Sure, but what are they doing?
Hey, guys, what's up?
Can you help us out?
Where do you kids live, huh?
Does anyone have
a phone I can use?
Come on, don't ignore
the adult here.
[BOY A]
We don't have any phones.
Okay, well, can you
point us to a road, then?
[BOYS giggle]
[ANZAI gasps]
[KANA]
Hey, Anzai? Do you hear that?
I think it's those children.
I don't hear anything.
They're behind us.
What's goin' on, guys?
Is there something you need?
If not, we're gonna keep going.
[KANA shouts]
[ANZAI]
Hey! Get back.
What do you think you're doing,
you little brats?
You okay, Kana?
[BOY A]
Blood.
--[BOYS growl]
--[KANA yells]
[ANZAI]
You sure you're all right?
[KANA]
Yeah. What a nightmare.
I can't believe they licked
my blood after they attacked.
Yeah, they bit me, too.
A prank gone too far, I guess.
Hey. Up there.
[footsteps]
[KANA] Doesn't look like
anyone's around.
[ANZAI]
Is it abandoned?
[KANA]
Anzai, look at those stains.
I hope that's paint.
I'm sure. You can't
really think it's blood.
I dunno.
[gasps]
[KANA]
Something's in the puddle.
[ANZAI]
The hell is that?
[KANA]
What do we do now?
[ANZAI] Let's see if we can
luck out and find someone
still living around here.
Hello, is anyone home?
We should go back to the car.
Yeah.
[door creaks]
Can I help you?
Actually, yeah, that would
be great, our car broke down
a ways back, and we're kind
of stranded out here now.
Would you mind if we used your
phone to call for a mechanic?
Unfortunately, I don't
have a working telephone.
More importantly, though.
You seem to be injured, Miss.
[ANZAI] Some weird kids bit
and attacked us in the forest.
[MAN] They're still
out there, huh? Come on inside.
We should tend to
those wounds of yours
before they get infected.
[crows caw]
[ANZAI] Are those children
from this village?
[MAN] No. These days, I'm the
only one who lives around here.
I honestly don't have
the slightest idea
where they came from.
They just show up in
the area sometimes.
Is that bandage too tight?
No, it's perfect, thanks.
Without a phone, we're screwed.
I can't fix that car.
[MAN]
It'll be dark outside, soon.
Why don't you stay here
as my guests for the night?
[ANZAI] So, was the village
empty when you moved in?
[MAN] I'm sure it
might seem odd to you,
but I welcomed the seclusion
given my state of mind
at the time.
Yeah, okay. Sure.
[MAN]
Kana. Your name is very pretty.
And there's something else
about you that reminds me
of someone I once
knew very well.
[ANZAI]
Uh, and who would that be?
A woman who was
very precious to me.
[MAN] Despite this,
she felt very lonely.
[GIRLFRIEND]
Everyone avoids being with me.
They all leave. You'll want to
be rid of me, too. In time.
I know you will.
I realize now that even my blood
doesn't want to be near me.
It wants to abandon me, too.
And so, I'm going to
try to let it escape.
[GIRLFRIEND sighs]
The only way I know how.
[MAN]
You can't!
[GIRLFRIEND]
See? I knew it.
[GIRLFRIEND] It wants to get out
of my body. To flee from me.
[GIRLFRIEND] One day soon.
I'll be absolutely empty.
Drained.
[MAN]
Could she be right?
Was it really that her blood
wanted to escape from her?
It was hard for me to believe,
because the blood that grew
from my love's neck
was still a part of her.
It produced the most
beautiful fruits,
allowing her to live on forever.
[grunts]
Man, why am I so dizzy?
Kana?
[footsteps]
[ANZAI] Wait, are those
bloodstains? Where's Kana?
[gasps]
[MAN] Ah, yes. This is what's
become of the woman I loved.
[ANZAI gasps]
[MAN]
They're so warm.
She's still alive
in here, you see.
[ANZAI] Where is Kana, dammit?
What have you done to her?
What are you talking about?
As far as I know,
Kana should still be in the
room she's sharing with you.
You must have had a bad dream.
[ANZAI grunts]
[MAN]
You're obviously exhausted.
You should go back and
sleep until morning.
[MALE VILLAGER A]
Run...! Run, boy!
Who said that?
[MALE VILLAGER A] Quickly.
Get out of here. Save yourself.
[ANZAI gasps]
Who are you?
[MALE VILLAGER A]
I live here.
[ANZAI] A villager? But I
thought this place was deserted.
What are you doing
in this creepy room?
[MALE VILLAGER A] I was planted
here. Planted by that man.
He appeared a few years ago and
used some sort of devilish power
to turn our villagers into
plants that bear bloody fruit.
He... He destroyed our families.
Men and women. Children.
Everyone. What you see
around you are the remains
of the other villagers,
all that's left.
This room is a living
field that he created
to farm blood from us.
What the hell is happening?
[MALE VILLAGER A] There isn't
any time. Get out of here. Go.
Otherwise you'll end up
a crop. Just like me.
Nothing but a husk.
[ANZAI gasps]
[ANZAI pants]
Kana...! Kana...! Kana!
You're here. Thank God. Get up,
we have to leave right now.
Okay.
[MAN] I'm afraid that
there is no escape.
[ANZAI gasps]
You're wrong.
You two will inevitably return
to this place. Just look.
Her neck is sprouting.
Beautifully.
She's going to be reborn as a
fertile gem of darkness for me.
[ANZAI] Shut up!
Let's go, Kana. Can you stand?
[KANA]
Yeah.
[KANA, ANZAI pant]
[KANA] I can't keep going,
Anzai. Let's take a quick break.
[ANZAI] Sure. Good idea.
We're far enough away.
[ANZAI gasps]
[KANA]
Do you think we're safe now?
What is it?
[ANZAI]
Well...
[ANZAI gasps]
[ANZAI] Isn't there anything
we can do to stop this?
[MALE VILLAGER A]
There is only one way.
You must swallow the fruit that
grows from your own body.
But beware, if you do so,
you will develop an endless
thirst for the blood of others.
It is a desire that
will never be sated.
[KANA slurps]
[ANZAI gasps]