[GIRL A gasps]
[gasps]
Um, excuse me?
I don't want to bother
you if you're busy,
but could you tell
me my fortune?
I especially want to hear
about my romantic future.
[GIRL A] Please, tell me,
will my love be realized?
[PRETTY BOY] Your love...
will never be realized.
[gasps]
[TEACHER]
Ahem. Allow me to introduce you
to your new classmate.
This is Ryuusuke Fukada.
He used to live here in
town when he was younger.
It's possible that some
of you might have been
in school with him then.
[school bell chimes]
[MIDORI] Hey. Do you
remember me, by chance?
[RYUUSUKE]
Huh?
I'm pretty sure that we were in
the same kindergarten class.
Oh! Wait, wait, don't tell me,
your name's Midori, right?
Yeah! Wow, I can't believe
that you remember me.
[chuckles]
[MIDORI] So, Ryuusuke. I wanna
introduce you to my best friend.
This is Suzue Tanaka
from Class B.
[SUZUE]
Nice to meet you.
[RYUUSUKE]
Likewise.
[SUZUE] You know, the
girls in our class were all
talking about you, Ryuusuke,
you're gonna be so popular.
They think you're super cute.
Of course, they all know none of
them stands a chance against
Midori if she goes after you.
Suzue, shut up, what
are you talking about?
You should know.
Midori is super popular
with guys at school.
It's safe to say all of
them want to date her.
Every one of them wishes
they were lucky enough
to be her boyfriend.
They basically clog the streets
looking for fortune tellers to
see if they have any chance
of winning her affections.
Right, Midori?
Will you please cut it out
before he thinks you're serious?
Besides, it's not like
crossroads fortune-telling
is real. It's a kids' fantasy.
[SUZUE] I dunno. I think
there's something to it.
You really think some random
person on the street could have
any insight into your life or
what the future holds for you?
[SUZUE] Well, when you
put it that way...
What do you think, Ryuusuke?
Do you think that
fortune-telling stuff is real?
[RYUUSUKE] You shouldn't mess
around with things like that.
[MIDORI, SUZUE gasp]
[RYUUSUKE]
On a gloomy day like this,
I bet tons of people are heading
to different crossroads at dusk,
asking for their
fortunes to be told.
And every single one of them
is asking the same thing.
"Will my love be realized?"
[GIRL B] I heard a first-year
girl died yesterday.
They found her lying in the
middle of an intersection.
She'd sliced her own neck
open with a box cutter.
There was an ocean
of blood on the street.
That's so sad, why would
she kill herself?
No idea. There was no note
found and the fog was so thick,
no one saw her do it.
There are some people who think
she was after a
crossroads fortune.
But how would they know that?
[GIRL B] Well, apparently
there was a suicide case
just like this seven
or eight years ago.
A girl was trying to get her
fortune read at a crossroads
and ended up committing suicide.
[GIRL C]
Seriously? That's really scary.
[RYUUSUKE]
Out of every place in the world,
how did I end up back
in this damn town?
This is karma. I'm being
punished for what I did.
[WOMAN]
Little boy. Hey, stop running.
[RYUUSUKE pants]
[WOMAN] Little boy.
Please, will you come here?
[RYUUSUKE]
Huh?
All I want for you
to do is listen.
I have a question to ask of you.
There's a man who I have
strong feelings for right now.
I love him with my whole being.
However, he has a wife
and a child already.
[WOMAN]
But you see,
another one of his babies is
growing inside of me. Our baby.
Do you understand me?
I want to be the mother
to one of his children, too.
Only, he's being so cold lately
and says I should get rid of it.
Isn't that horrible?
Still, it hasn't changed
my feelings. I want him.
So much. I'm so deeply
in love with this man
that sometimes I feel like
I could just die for him.
So, what do you say?
What do you think I
should do, little boy?
Um, I don't really know
what you're talking about.
What I'm really asking,
is probably the most important
question in the world.
Will my love be realized?
Of course it won't,
crazy lady. Weirdo!
[RYUUSUKE]
That night I couldn't sleep.
I got so curious about
who this woman was.
And I wondered what happened
to her after I ran away.
So the next day. I went back
to the spot where I'd met her.
[RYUUSUKE] I was the one who
caused her to take her life.
It's my fault she and her
unborn baby are dead.
[MIDORI]
Ryuusuke?
[RYUUSUKE gasps]
Is something wrong?
You've been acting weird today.
[RYUUSUKE]
I'm fine, Midori.
You don't have to lie to me.
I'm here for you if
you need anything.
Thank you.
But it's nothing, really.
[MIDORI]
If you say so.
[MIDORI] Y'know, I was
kind of wanting to ask you
if you'd had a bad experience
with crossroads fortunes
or something after
how you reacted.
You're totally
overthinking things.
Why would they bother me?
I mean, if they do,
I'd understand.
I have pretty bad memories
associated with them, too.
You heard the girls in class
talking about that death
that happened a while back.
There was another woman who
killed herself eight years ago.
The thing is, she was
actually my aunt.
[RYUUSUKE gasps]
[RYUUSUKE]
It can't be. Dammit!
[SUZUE]
Midori! Wait up!
Hey, Suzue.
You've been walking home
alone a lot lately.
Yeah.
[SUZUE] Is something wrong?
Where's Ryuusuke?
Are things not going
well with him?
[MIDORI] I don't know,
that's the problem.
I get the feeling
he's avoiding me lately.
And I honestly can't
figure out what I did.
If you want me to,
I'd be happy to ask him.
I'm sure there's a simple
explanation behind it.
[SUZUE] So tell me the truth,
why are you avoiding Midori?
Did she do something
to upset you?
Hey, are you okay?
I could never be
upset with Midori.
But I don't deserve to like her.
Or even talk to her.
It's all my fault.
That's why I can't be with her.
Ryuusuke. What on Earth
are you talking about?
You're scaring me.
Just explain what's going on.
I'm sure I can figure some way
to help you get through this.
Just be honest and tell
me what happened.
That's enough! Don't ask
me anything else, okay?
She'll suffer less if
we let things die here
and stop talking at all.
[SUZUE] Come on, Midori is
so worried about you.
Don't do this.
Oh, fine. All right.
I'll let it go.
Sorry for cornering
you like this.
Goodbye.
That's it!
[SUZUE] U-Um, hello?
Excuse me, sir.
I was hoping to get
a crossroads fortune.
Could you, maybe help me out?
It's, um... It's about a
really good friend of mine.
She's been worried about
how distant her boyfriend
has been lately and
needs some help.
And I'm pretty sure he's
upset because of something
he won't talk to me about.
What do you think I should
do to get them back together
and make things good
like they were before?
That's the wrong question.
You should worry more
about your own love life.
[footsteps echo]
[MIDORI]
So, I was wondering.
Did Ryuusuke have
anything to say?
Yeah, he did. I talked to him
a little while and he said
he thinks it would be best
if the two of you break up.
I see.
I tried to get a fortune
for the two of you.
I wanted to get you
guys back together,
even if it meant tapping
into the mystical.
Seriously, you went
that far for us?
Yeah. Just the other night.
I actually think I ran into that
pretty boy at the crossroads
everyone talks about.
I wasn't looking for him.
He just appeared out of nowhere.
He was really tall and
dressed head-to-toe in black.
His features were
so sharp looking.
There was such a cold beauty
to him that it gave me chills.
But none of that really matters.
The important thing,
which shook me to my core,
was what he said to me.
It made me realize that
I've been lying to myself.
That everything I was doing was
actually the opposite of what I
truly wanted deep down in
the depths of my heart.
So now, I'm going to start
living far more honestly.
Midori, you have to listen.
I'm gonna be Ryuusuke's
new girlfriend!
I've known this ever
since he transferred.
I'm sorry, Midori, but I
love Ryuusuke so much,
more than anything.
I'd die for him!
So it's kind of really lucky
for me that the two of you
are splitting up.
The timing is perfect!
I can't wait! I'm gonna go tell
Ryuusuke how I feel about him!
[RYUUSUKE] Suzue Tanaka started
to pursue me aggressively.
I tried my best to
turn her down nicely,
but she didn't take the hint.
If anything, things started
to get even worse.
[SUZUE]
Here. Your lunch.
Will you please stop
stalking me already?
If you keep following
me around like this,
I'm gonna call the police.
But, I just wanted to
make sure you had
a lunch to eat today, my love.
[RYUUSUKE]
I brought my own food!
Just eat this one instead!
I'll get rid of the one
in your bag, give it to me!
[RYUUSUKE grunts]
What are doing? Stop it!
You have got to give this up!
Look, I'll be blunt. I don't
like you that way, okay?
Midori's the one I want!
I have no place in my
life for you, so get lost.
You can't say that.
What about all of this
love that I feel for you?
[RYUUSUKE]
I don't care!
But I'm just doing what the
fortune teller told me to.
The pretty boy who I met at the
crossroads said I should worry
about my own love life,
so that's the thing
I'm focusing on now.
And yet, it's no good.
My love for you is never
going to be realized, is it?
I love you so much, Ryuusuke.
Do you hear me?
You've stolen my heart!
I heard they found another
girl dead at an intersection.
[RYUUSUKE]
Hm?
Yeah, that makes
four of 'em in all.
It seems she wanted
her fortune read.
I heard she ran into
that pretty boy.
You know, the one from
those crazy rumors.
I bet he's not even human.
Maybe he's the angel of death.
The pretty boy at
the crossroads.
An angel, huh?
Yeah. Uh, speaking of
fallen angels,
it looks like one from our
school has her eyes set on you.
[school bells chime]
So, I know that I went a
little too far this morning.
It's not that I dislike
you as a person, Suzue.
But I just can't forget about
my feelings for Midori.
There's no way that I can go out
with someone else right now.
[SUZUE whimpers]
Listen. I should have
told you before.
There's a good reason why I've
been avoiding Midori lately.
Eight years ago, the first
time I lived in this town,
it happened.
One night....
[gasps]
Suzue, no!
[RYUUSUKE] The pretty boy
at the crossroads.
I couldn't just sit around doing
nothing while people were dying
in the street.
I had to find him.
So, I started going out
to the crossroads myself
every night at dusk.
People asked me to
read their fortunes,
and I tried to figure out a way
to give them some hope.
I did everything I
could to be sincere,
to show them that the
future was worth living.
I did the opposite of what it
sounded like he was doing.
[RYUUSUKE] I thought maybe that
was the only way I could keep
more people from
killing themselves.
I guess it was pretty obvious
that I was doing this because
of the guilt I still felt
about driving that woman
to suicide eight years before.
Eventually, things went wrong.
Oh, hey. Would you
like a fortune?
Whoa. Are you okay?
[GIRL D] Excuse me, but, will my
love ever be realized?
[RYUUSUKE] Yes! Yes it will!
I'm sure of it.
[RYUUSUKE] This can't
be real. These figures.
They look like different girls
who've killed themselves
at the crossroads.
And if that's true, then...
I love you! I love you
so much I could die!
[RYUUSUKE] Despite what I saw,
I had to keep going
and telling people
their fortunes.
[MIDORI]
Ryuusuke?
Oh, hi, Midori.
Are you going to walk
around town again tonight?
I know that you've been going
around trying to help people
wanting their fortunes
told at intersections.
It's almost as though you
can't help but go out.
Will you tell me why?
What's driving you?
It's just. I don't think
I can stop until I've finally
caught that pretty boy
at the crossroads.
[MIDORI] No! Ryuusuke.
Don't go, please! Ryuusuke!
--[footsteps echo]
--[RYUUSUKE gasps]
[RYUUSUKE]
That was him!
Hold up!
[RYUUSUKE]
Stop!
[PRETTY BOY chuckles]
[RYUUSUKE pants]
[RYUUSUKE]
Damn it! I lost him.
What part of town am I in?
[RYUUSUKE gasps]
This is...
...the intersection
from eight years ago.
How did I end up here?
[gasps]
[RYUUSUKE gasps]
Impossible...
It's you. I...
[RYUUSUKE gasps]
[MIDORI]
Ryuusuke? Where did you run?
It's no use. I don't even
know where I am.
[footsteps]
[MIDORI gasps]
[MIDORI] That's him.
It's... It's the pretty boy.
It's okay, I'll be fine.
After all, I'm not here
to get my fortune told.
I'm not. I'm all right.
Go away!
[shouts]
Oh, there you are.
How'd you find me?
I think someone back there
pointed me in your direction.
It looked like you were
hiding from someone.
It was him! The boy! The one
who wanders the crossroads.
What? Where is he?
Right here. Look!
[RYUUSUKE] But this eerie
boy I was looking for
was nowhere to be found.
And the fog that had
been so thick was gone.
As though it had never existed.
[RIE] My friend Yuuko is known
for talking all the time.
But recently she's
been almost silent.
And when she does speak...
[heavy lisp]
I don't know.
Lately I've been having trouble
saying things correctly.
Are you sure you shouldn't
go to the hospital?
[YUUKO] Mm. I know it's weird,
but I don't feel sick at all,
I'm sure this'll pass.
[RIE]
Despite what she said,
she stopped coming to
class soon after that.
Her seat was empty.
[doorbell rings]
Is no one home?
[YUUKO'S DAD grunts]
[RIE]
What's that?
[thudding]
[YUUKO'S DAD, MOM grunting]
[YUUKO'S DAD] No matter how many
we kill, they keep coming back.
[YUUKO'S MOM]
It's because of this humidity
and all of these clouds.
Whatever, hand me
more of that salt.
Oh! It's so nice
to see you, Rie.
It's been a while.
Way too long.
[YUUKO'S MOM]
Let me guess,
you're here to check
up on Yuuko, right?
She's up in her room.
[YUUKO'S MOM] Yuuko? Rie dropped
by to see how you're doing.
Yuuko?
[YUUKO whimpers]
[YUUKO'S MOM] Honey? Why are you
covering your mouth like that?
[YUUKO grunts]
Just leave me alone, please!
What's wrong?
[YUUKO'S MOM]
It's okay. Let me see.
[YUUKO groans]
What?!
[groaning continues]
[BOTH gasp]
[YUUKO shouts]
[YUUKO'S DAD]
It might be the only way.
[YUUKO'S MOM]
Do you think it will work?
[YUUKO'S DAD]
Yeah. Stay strong.
Let's fill the bathtub with
salt and put her in it.
We'll stop this thing.
[YUUKO'S DAD]
There. That should be enough.
Go ahead and help her
get in. It'll be fine.
I want you to open your
mouth as wide as you can
once you're submerged,
all right?
[YUUKO'S MOM] I'm starting
to get worried.
Hasn't she been in
there long enough?
[YUUKO'S DAD]
Yuuko? You okay?
Oh, no. I think she's
fainted in there! Help me!
Huh? What? These are Yuuko's
pajamas, but they're empty!
Where could she have gone?
[YUUKO'S MOM]
Yuuko?!
[YUUKO'S DAD]
Where are you, Yuuko?
Wait, what's this?
[YUUKO'S DAD shouts] No, no,
what happened to the rest of
my daughter?
Look at the base of
her neck, oh my god,
there's a little body
hanging back there.
The salt must have
caused her to shrink.
[BOTH gasp]
[RIE] Apparently, the creature
still lives out in their garden.
Like an ordinary snail
carrying around a pretty shell.
And just like a slug, it leaves
a trail of slime behind it.
As for Yuuko. They say whenever
someone gets too close,
the shell will stare
in their direction,
and that the look in its
eyes is filled with grief.