[OOYA groans]
[SOUICHI chuckles]
A curse upon you.
Ah... My stomach.
How does it feel?
[groans] I think I'm dying.
Somebody help me!
[chuckles] Are you prepared
to witness true horror?
[school bell rings]
[SOUICHI] There's no one
quite as incredible as me.
How is it possible that
I'm so extraordinary?
I am a man of incomprehensible
power and potential,
basically a superhuman.
[SOUICHI chuckles] I'm on a
completely different level
from the idiots
around me.
And on top of that,
I'm handsome.
[FEMALE STUDENT A] Hey, did you
hear what happened last night?
Ooya from Class Three passed out
in the middle of the street.
What?
I know. Apparently he's
in the hospital now.
[SOUICHI giggles]
That's so sad!
[FEMALE STUDENTS]
Huh?
A tragedy. I wonder what could
have caused such a thing.
[giggling continues]
[SOUICHI] Ooya thought
he was such hot stuff.
Someone had to remind him
that he's not untouchable.
Hm, hm. Unfortunately, I can't
let anyone know it was me.
It would probably be a bad
idea for everyone to find out
exactly how amazing
I really am.
The morons at this school
are all convinced
I'm a perfectly
ordinary student,
a loser like one of them.
But even so, heh, the girls
can't help but hang around
in the classroom just
to be close to me.
He's giggling again.
[FEMALE STUDENT B]
He's such a freak.
And the faces he
makes are so creepy.
[AKIYAMA] I'm done
taking crap from you!
What the heck's your problem?
You are! Obviously.
It looks like Kuroda and
Akiyama are going at it again.
Of course they are,
those two guys are always
at each other's throats.
[KURODA]
I'm warning you, man!
I don't think you've
got the guts.
[KURODA groans]
[BOYS] Fight! Fight!
Fight! Fight! Fight!
[KURODA]
Stop whining.
[SOUICHI giggles]
And just like that,
a new hatred is born.
[squeals]
I wonder if people realize how
kind-hearted I am deep down.
Full of compassion.
For example, on a
wintery day like this,
I bet I can find a new
friend underneath the dirt.
This is perfect!
A hibernating little toad.
[SOUICHI chuckles] I bet it's
pretty cold in the ground,
isn't it, little guy?
You're freezing.
How about you come live
at home with me instead?
It's nice and warm, I promise!
[SOUICHI]
Well, this is your new house!
Do you like it?
I think you will.
I've even got some
water here for you.
Why don't we grab a
seat over there?
That'd be a great idea.
If my butt didn't
feel like it was on fire.
[ALL laugh]
Lookie here, the whole family
watching TV after dinner.
It sounds like
they're having fun.
My big brother, Kouichi.
A pitiful bastard who takes
everything too seriously.
Always finding ways to try
and make me look like a child.
And of course,
my big sister, Sayuri.
The poor girl has somehow
convinced herself
that people think
she's beautiful.
And, honestly, there's really
not anything interesting
at all about the three
adults in the room.
I can't imagine a
more boring group.
[laughs]
[KOUICHI] Hey, Souichi.
If you wanna watch TV with us,
just come in and
grab a seat. Kay?
Otherwise close the door,
you're letting all of the
warm air out of the room.
Just wait. I'll make you
suffer for your idiocy
one of these days,
you arrogant fool.
Did you say
something to me?
Nothing! Not a word.
Oh, I heard what he said.
He called you an arrogant fool.
[KOUICHI]
Is that true?
[SOUICHI whimpers]
Damn you, Sayuri!
Souichi! So how am
I the fool here?
--[SOUICHI giggles]
--[frog croaks]
[giggling continues]
[SAYURI screams]
[SOUICHI]
Look here, Sayuri!
It's your favorite,
a big old toad.
Take that thing outside!
[SAYURI cries]
[KOUICHI]
Stop tormenting our sister!
[SOUICHI chuckles]
Do you get it now?
I'm not a peon like the rest
of you losers I call a family.
In fact, you should all
be bowing down to me!
I am wonted.
Oh! You should look that up.
[KOUICHI laughs]
[SOUICHI]
Huh?
The definition of "wonted."
"Average or commonplace."
Wait, seriously?
Damn you, Kouichi!
How dare you embarrass me!
Huh! Not that it matters anyway.
I don't have time
for this nonsense.
After all, I should really be
focusing on my new project.
Why don't we get to work on it?
What do you think would
be a good punishment, hm?
Yeah, you're right.
A hibernation curse
would be perfect.
Here you go, Kuroda.
It's time for a little dirt nap.
[giggles]
[SOUICHI] You can come out
when spring rolls around.
I'm sure you'll be well-rested.
[YAMADA]
Hey, listen to this.
You know how Kuroda's been
absent the last few days?
It turns out he isn't sick,
he's actually gone missing.
Was he kidnapped? Or worse.
I hope he wasn't
murdered or something.
Why would you even say that?
Hey, Akiyama.
[AKIYAMA]
Huh?
[KAWAI] You're the one who's
always fighting with him.
You have any idea where he is?
Of course not, what are
you trying to say?
[SOUICHI giggles]
[OLD MAN grunts]
Not again.
I'm so tired of this.
Damn kids driving nails
into my cedar trees.
They're gonna destroy them all.
If this is a prank, it's gone
too far, and it's not funny.
Whoever's responsible for
this is going to pay for it.
[OLD MAN]
Huh?
[OLD MAN grunts] What the
hell is this ugly thing?
[OLD MAN]
Damn it.
[OLD MAN grunts]
[OLD MAN]
Huh? Another doll?
Huh. Must be some
kind of mannequin.
How'd it get on my land?
[OLD MAN grunts]
[gasps]
It's a kid.
[YAMADA] Did you hear
they found Kuroda?
He was buried up to his
neck out in the cedar forest.
Wait, you mean he
actually was dead?
[YAMADA]
No, that's the weirdest part,
he was just sleeping,
and I heard he didn't wake up
until he was at the hospital.
He was just taking a
nap in the ground?
He must have been out there for
days in this freezing weather.
How did he survive?
Aw... This isn't fair at all.
It was gonna be so funny when
he crawled out of the dirt
in the spring like some
kind of animal. I hate this.
[YAMADA] Kuroda says he has
no idea how he got out there.
--He doesn't remember anything.
--[SOUICHI] Huh?
God, what a strange dude,
maybe he was hibernating.
[ISHIZAKA laughs]
[YAMADA laughs]
[SOUICHI]
Something's off over there.
They look like they're having
a normal, friendly chat.
But there's an air of tension
between those three today.
I do believe there's been a
change in the status quo
for this trio.
Let's take a closer look,
shall we?
Yamada and Kawai are talking
like they always do.
But Kawai and Ishizaka aren't
saying much to each other.
Not like usual.
Which means...
...something awkward must
have happened between them.
Some kind of heinous,
embarrassing ordeal
has ruined their friendship and
fragmented their little group.
The four-eyed Ishizaka is
probably getting pushed around
by Kawai, who's more outgoing!
I bet that's it!
The seeds of hate are
growing between them.
Ishizaka must want Kawai dead.
I see it in his eyes!
I'll be right back, okay?
[YAMADA]
'Kay.
[SOUICHI] Hey, Ishizaka!
Wait up for me!
[ISHIZAKA]
Oh, hey, what's up, Souichi?
Do you need something?
Is it eating you up inside?
Huh? What do you mean?
Don't worry, I get it.
Cursing someone is a
difficult burden to bear.
And I bet you've
imagined putting Kawai
through some horrible
tortures, haven't you?
You've dreamed of killing him.
But you don't have to
feel bad about it anymore.
Just leave Kawai to me. I'll
curse him so you don't have to.
Everything will work out.
[ISHIZAKA]
Hm?
[SOUICHI giggles]
[KAWAI]
He seriously said that stuff?
You shouldn't talk
to that freak.
[ISHIZAKA] Uh, he said he
was going to curse you.
You should watch your back.
[KAWAI laughs]
Maybe it'll be fun.
Hey, look.
[KAWAI]
It's that old psycho.
[OLD MAN grunts]
Damn kids.
[AKIYAMA]
Be careful.
It's an import.
Really expensive.
[SOUICHI] I'll keep it safe.
Oh, yeah, really nice.
This is perfect. I think I'll
go home and explore the attic
to see what treasures
I can find up there.
[SOUICHI chuckles]
See ya later.
[SAYURI screams] No...!
Keep that thing away from me!
[chuckles] But I went through
the trouble of finding this
giant dead orb
weaver for you.
Go on, eat up. It's delicious.
[SAYURI]
Stop screwing around.
Souichi! What are you
doing to your sister?
Will you please get
him out of here?
[KOUICHI] You can't keep pulling
stupid crap like this, okay?
Get rid of that
spider right now!
I'm not gonna toss
him out like garbage.
Look at the gold
coloring on his legs.
You can't tell me
he's not beautiful.
[KOUICHI]
That's enough!
[SOUICHI whimpers, yelps]
[KOUICHI] Hey, Sayuri. Did you
hear the way he just screamed?
Uh-huh!
--[SOUICHI whimpers]
--[KOUICHI] Well, well.
I think he's more scared of
spiders than he lets on.
[SOUICHI]
Hey, what are you doing?
[KOUICHI laughs]
What's wrong? Take it. Here!
I can't believe you're holding
that thing with your bare hands.
It's so disgusting.
[SOUICHI sighs]
I'm not some dumb kid.
And I don't have time to
waste on such idiotic people.
I have another new project
I have to take care of.
[SOUICHI] I wonder which curse
I should use this time. Hm...
I know. Something with
spiders will do nicely.
[MALE STUDENT A] "In Japan
for the first time in a year.
In my home for the
first time in a year.
It would be natural
to feel relieved now,
but I find it disturbing.
The reason being that
someone else has lived here
during that time. Worse yet
is the fact that it was
the family of my middle
school teacher...
[KAWAI]
Uh, excuse me!
[MALE TEACHER A]
Huh? What is it, Kawai?
[KAWAI] Well, that was
pretty embarrassing.
[KAWAI grunts]
What the--?
Hey, that's strange,
the pain in my stomach
is completely gone now.
I should have just waited it
out instead of making a scene.
Oh, come on.
Is this thing stuck?
[SOUICHI giggles]
[KAWAI] What the hell?
This is so lame!
Guess I'll have to climb out.
[KAWAI grunts]
Hm?
[yells]
[ambulance siren blares]
[MALE STUDENT B] They found him
passed out in the bathroom.
[MALE STUDENT C] Yeah, and he
was wrapped head-to-toe
in toilet paper
for some reason.
So what do you think?
I did this for you,
so please let me know if you're
satisfied with the result.
What result?
Don't worry. It's not
like I'm expecting
anything from you
in return, Ishizaka.
I mean, I did take the
time out of my day
to teach Kawai an
important lesson for you.
But as long as you're
happy with what I did,
that's enough for me.
Don't get me wrong.
The service I performed
for you was definitely one
worthy of payment.
But I'm not the kind of petty
guy who'd demand money
or something from you.
It was just a favor.
Think nothing of it.
You know, you don't
even have to thank me.
Really, I don't
think it's necessary.
He, he. I'm just that kind.
[ISHIZAKA] Souichi. What the
heck are you babbling about?
What do you mean you taught
Kawai some kind of lesson, huh?
What's up?
Is something going on?
No. It's not anything important.
[SOUICHI]
Damn you, Ishizaka.
Not only do you
show me no gratitude,
but you embarrass me afterward.
Don't think that you'll
get away with this.
[phone ringing]
[ISHIZAKA]
Hello. Ishizaka residence.
[SOUICHI] Uh, yes,
is this Yasuo Ishizaka?
Um. Yeah, that's me.
[SOUICHI] Congratulations!
Today is your very lucky day!
You've been selected for
the chance to win a trip
around the world!
Free of charge!
If you would, please come
to Sakurayama Park
next to the elementary
school right away.
Oh, and come alone.
We can go over all the
details when you get there.
So please be sure to show up!
[giggles] What a complete idiot,
he's gonna come.
I better get everything
ready fast.
[dogs barking]
[ISHIZAKA] Okay. So that
was obviously Souichi
on the phone earlier.
I don't know what that creep is
planning, but I'm ready for it.
[ISHIZAKA grunts]
Man, it's cold.
And it's getting late.
The least that freak could
do is show up already.
[thudding]
[gasps]
[ISHIZAKA gasps]
What the hell is that?
[ISHIZAKA shouts, pants]
[ISHIZAKA pants]
[ISHIZAKA]
It's gaining on me!
[SOUICHI giggles]
--[giggling continues]
--[ISHIZAKA pants]
[ISHIZAKA gasps]
[SOUICHI whimpers]
[SOUICHI shouts]
[ISHIZAKA gasps]
[ISHIZAKA]
Wait, Souichi?
No fair. You tricked me!
What a coward.
I can't believe you set that
trap up to take me down.
No, stupid, that insane old
man who owns this land
left that thing.
No telling what he'll do to
you when he finds you.
[SOUICHI]
Do you think he's coming?
Help me get down from here.
[ISHIZAKA] You better get out
of the forest right now.
I'm not sticking around.
I don't want any kind of run
in with that damn psycho.
[SOUICHI whimpers]
Bastard. He actually
left me hanging here.
He should be ashamed of himself,
abandoning me like that
and running back to
the safety of his house.
[SOUICHI grunting]
Damn it, my leg is stuck.
--[shuffling]
--[SOUICHI gasps]
[SOUICHI whimpers]
[SOUICHI gasps]
I found you! You're the
kid ruining my trees.
[SOUICHI meows]
[OLD MAN] Pretending to
be a cat won't help you!
Not after everything you've
done to my beautiful cedars.
I'm gonna tear you apart.
Get down here!
[SOUICHI yells]
Please spare me!
[chuckles] No one's gonna
hear you scream out here!
You're going to die tonight.
[SOUICHI whines]
Show some mercy!
I'll do anything! Mommy!
Please help me!
I don't want to die!
[laughs] Then you never should
have walked into my forest!
[KOUICHI]
Hello, sir. Is there a problem?
[OLD MAN grunts] What are
you doing out here?
Hey, Souichi. Why are you
playing up in that tree?
[whimpering] Brother!
You've gotta save me!
I'm teaching this
little brat a lesson
since he's been messing
with my cedar trees.
Once I'm all done here,
I'll call the cops on him.
Simple as that.
Well, do you have
any actual proof
that my brother is the culprit?
Are you not seeing what's
going on behind me?
[KOUICHI] Fair enough.
You have a point.
I'll take him to the
station myself, then.
[SOUICHI]
Huh?
[OLD MAN] This better not
be some kind of trick,
or you'll pay for it.
Go straight to the police.
[KOUICHI] Of course, if we
do go and talk to the cops,
I'll have to tell them about
all these traps lying around.
Wonder what they'll think
about you setting them up
and hurting unsuspecting people.
[OLD MAN] What? Are you
trying to blackmail me, kid?
Look, I'm just stating
the facts. That's all.
[OLD MAN grunts]
You better not screw with me.
Both of you leave this forest.
If I catch either of you
here again, you're dead.
[KOUICHI]
Come on, Souichi. Let's go.
[SOUICHI whimpers]
[SOUICHI'S FATHER]
Dammit, son.
Why do you always cause
so much trouble for us?
[SOUICHI'S MOTHER]
He's right, Souichi.
The least you could
do is apologize.
[SAYURI]
You tell him, mom.
Hey! I'm not done with you, yet!
Sit down!
I don't have time to spend
listening to you rant, dad.
I've got important stuff to do.
[SOUICHI] The only friend I
need is my cute little toady.
He's probably missed me.
Hello, Toady? It's been
a while, but I'm back.
Time to come out and play, now.
I bet you're excited to see me!
Toady?
[SOUICHI grunts]
[SOUICHI groans] Oh...
He's dead. And he smells.
[thunder crackles]
[MARIE'S FATHER gasps]
I don't want to believe it.
But the thing I've
feared is coming true.
[MARIE]
Papa? You look so frightened.
What's the matter?
[gasps] It's nothing,
Marie. Really.
[MARIE'S FATHER]
After all this time,
my daughter has
finally succumbed
to the doll transformation.
[MARIE'S MOTHER]
Honey? Honey?
She's gone, Marie's completely
one of them now.
--[MARIE'S FATHER gasps]
--[MARIE'S MOTHER] Look at her!
She can't even move.
She won't respond to me.
I'll never hear her voice again.
[MARIE'S FATHER]
My darling daughter.
Have I seen you smile
for the last time?
Is there nothing left of you?
[MARIE'S FATHER] Most people
in this world put their children
to a final rest once they've
turned into dolls.
But I didn't think I could
do that to my Marie.
We kept her at home, with us.
Where she belonged.
Only.... Her transformation
didn't stop there.
Soon we began to understand
how those other parents
must have felt. The horror.
Dearest, I think
the time has come
to put our daughter to rest.
I know.