[MIO breathes heavily]
[MIO whimpers]
[MIO screams]
It's okay.
[MIO]
Someone help!
Don't run! Just hold on!
[MIO grunts]
Let go. I wanna leave.
Wait, aren't you Mio
Fujii from my class?
What are you doing
in my house?
Oshikiri, please.
I just want to go home.
Don't hurt me or do
anything terrible.
[MIO gasps]
What are you talking about?
[MIO, OKASHIRI gasp]
[OSHIKIRI gasps]
[STUDENTS chatter]
[OSHIKIRI]
There she is.
Sitting in class like
nothing ever happened.
Her usual, cheery self.
A different person
from last night.
That's right. It must have
been a different person.
It couldn't be the same
girl I'm looking at now.
Maybe it was just the other
world's version of Mio.
[MIO]
Huh?
[OSHIKIRI] She wandered into
this realm for just a moment.
Long enough to meet me.
Then she passed back
to her own reality.
My house is full of doors that
seem to lead into another world.
One that looks
identical to mine.
[OSHIKIRI] Maybe that girl was
from the other side, lost.
But then, what was she
doing in my house, I wonder.
[MIO]
Hi, Oshikiri.
Uh? Oh, hey, good morning Mio.
Did you need something?
It's your turn. Remember?
You're up for class
journal duty.
[OSHIKIRI]
Oh, right. Thanks.
Are you sure that's all
you have to say to me?
Nothing else on your
mind this morning?
[OSHIKIRI gasps] No. Look.
I wasn't checking you out.
Liar. You totally were.
[MIO giggles] Fine, whatever.
Don't lose that journal, okay?
[AOYAMA] Well, well.
Got a thing for Mio, huh?
That's so cute.
The shrimp's in love.
You're such a tiny
little dude, though.
Look, man, if you
made a move on her,
I think it'd just be an
embarrassing mistake.
She'd tower over you,
imagine how dumb you'd look.
Oh, shut up, Aoyama.
You're starting to
get on my nerves.
[AOYAMA]
Huh?
You've got real big mouth
for being such a weakling.
What's the matter?
Come on, bitch boy!
At least put up
some kind of fight.
Runt! Runt!
--[OSHIKIRI] Bastard!
--Here we go!
[AOYAMA, OKASHIRI grunt]
[MIO]
Get off him! Enough already.
[AOYAMA]
Remember that.
[MIO]
Hey, are you okay?
I'm fine...
[OSHIKIRI] Damn it.
I can't stand that idiot.
[OSHIKIRI gasps]
[AOYAMA]
Oshikiri... Oshikiri...
[OSHIKIRI gasps]
[AOYAMA]
Oshikiri!
Show yourself,
you little pissant.
[OSHIKIRI]
That sounds like...
[AOYAMA]
Oshikiri. Where are you?
[OSHIKIRI]
Aoyama?
Oshikiri.
[gasps]
I finally found you!
[OSHIKIRI shouts]
You're... a monster!
You... I'll murder you.
Tear you apart!
[OSHIKIRI gasps]
[OSHIKIRI]
What's happening?
[MIO] So. I heard you live
in a gigantic mansion.
Like something out of
a movie. Is that true?
Well...
[MIO] I'd love come over
and see it sometime!
[OSHIKIRI]
I wouldn't if I were you.
Aw, why not?
[OSHIKIRI] And I wouldn't
ask about it, either.
Why are you being
so secretive?
Oh, I get it.
You must be a shy one.
That's not the reason.
I never see you talking
to other people, Oshikiri.
I don't think that's a
good thing for anybody.
You need to make some friends
or else you'll turn
into a real weirdo.
[OSHIKIRI grunts]
[crows caw]
[MIO]
Wow, is this it?
I had no idea our town
had any houses this big.
This is your last
chance to turn back.
Are you still trying
to be mysterious?
Believe me, it's for
your own good.
This house has passages
to another world.
[MIO]
Is that some kind of joke?
[OSHIKIRI] It's the truth.
There are places inside
that allow people to travel
between two worlds.
The other one looks a lot like
ours from what I can tell.
I even saw someone who
looked exactly like me once,
just a for second.
[OSHIKIRI sighs] You shouldn't
poke around supernatural places
like this just because
you're bored or curious.
[MIO]
I'm not worried,
I don't believe in any of
that kinda stuff anyway.
Are you sure you're not dreaming
about this doppelganger?
Believe me, I wish I was
hallucinating everything.
If you're serious, then maybe
I can help you somehow.
[OSHIKIRI] Yeah, maybe.
You can come in.
Just keep an eye open
for anything off.
[OSHIKIRI]
Mio? Where'd you go?
It's been three days.
But Mio hasn't come to school,
and she's been reported missing.
Maybe back in the courtyard,
she accidentally wandered
into the other world.
[shuffling]
[OSHIKIRI gasps] Oh, no.
What's in the hallway now?
[MIO]
Hm? There you are, Oshikiri.
I've been searching
for you. Turn me back.
Make my body normal again,
I beg of you!
Oh my God, is that
really you, Mio?
[MIO groans] Oshikiri! I can't
believe you did this to me!
I'll curse you! You won't
get away with this!
[MIO screams]
[OSHIKIRI] That voice.
She sounded exactly like Mio.
But wait. Which one was it?
The Mio from the other side?
[OSHIKIRI] Either way,
it seems like something
really horrifying is going on
in the parallel world.
Wait a sec.
This is the first floor,
but I was upstairs just now.
How'd I get down here?
[MIO]
Stop it, please!
[OSHIKIRI gasps]
[OSHIKIRI]
Was that--?
[MIO] Please, just untie me.
Don't do this! Oshikiri, stop!
[OSHIKIRI]
That's... the other me!
[MIO]
Let me go!
[OSHIKIRI]
And he's got Mio!
I'm afraid it's far
too late to stop.
I still have so much
important research to do.
Aoyama was the first person
I tried the treatment on.
But it was no good,
he grew too large.
Then I experimented on you.
Or, I guess I should say it was
the Mio Fujii from this world,
your counterpart of sorts.
But she turned into nothing
more than a pile of flesh,
so I banished both of those
failures to your side.
And then you showed up, which
was excellent timing, really.
Now I can test my adjusted
formula without having to find
a new specimen from my world.
If it works, it will
increase my height
without unpleasant
side effects.
[MIO] Your height?
You're crazy. Please, you can't.
[OSHIKIRI] Now, if you'll
just hold still.
[MIO]
No! No! Let me go!
[OSHIKIRI]
Don't touch her!
[OSHIKIRI grunting]
[OTHER OSHIKIRI]
You...
About time. I was wondering
when you'd finally show up.
But where are we?
Is this the other world?
To the two of you it is.
To me, it's just home.
[gasps]
Stop!
This is the perfect chance
to test my serum. On myself.
[OTHER OSHIKIRI shouts]
[OSHIKIRI]
Enough!
[BOTH grunting]
No! Stop!
[BOTH OSHIKIRI gruting]
[MIO]
Oshikiri!
Oh, no. Bastard!
[groans]
[MIO yells]
Oshikiri! Oh, God, no.
This has to be some
kind of nightmare!
Turn him back. Demon!
You have to make him
normal again, you have to!
[MIO gasps]
No, stay away from me!
[MIO shouts]
Mio, calm down, it's all right!
I'm the me from your world.
Really? You're not him?
[OSHIKIRI] I promise. I took
the needle off the other one
when we were fighting before.
The monster in front of you
is the Oshikiri who
made this formula.
[OTHER OSHIKIRI]
You think...
You think you've saved
the day, you bastard?
Killing me won't make you safe,
there are infinite
parallel worlds out there.
Do you understand me?
Never forget there are countless
Oshikiris who'd be
happy to murder you.
[OTHER OSHIKIRI groans]
[OSHIKIRI, MIO gasp]
So, Oshikiri, what do we do now?
Can we even find a way
back to our world?
[STUDENTS chattering]
[MALE STUDENT A]
Heyo.
[FEMALE STUDENT B chuckles]
Hi there!
And, we're back.
[MALE STUDENT B] Man, I can't
believe summer break
is already over.
Hey, good morning, Wakayama.
Good morning to you.
Just the man I've
been looking for.
Do you think I could see your
math homework? Pretty please?
Sure. But you really should
start doing your own.
[KOUTA chuckles]
I'll make it up to you.
[KOUTA]
Hm? Ugh.
Souichi! You were told
to stop shooting nails
or you'd get punished for it.
Ah, I'm gonna have to
tell Mr. Yanagida.
[SOUICHI]
Hmph.
[KOUTA]
Hey. There's our teacher now.
[WAKAYAMA]
Excuse me.
I hate to say this, but
Souichi's causing trouble.
He's been shooting...
nails... again.
[FEMALE STUDENT B]
Whoa. Is he okay?
[SOUICHI giggles]
[YANAGIDA giggles]
[SOGA] Huh? Mr. Yanagida?
What are you doing out here?
[gasps]
Your head!
--[SOUICHI giggles]
--[SOGA] Uh?
[YANAGIDA grunts]
[laughs]
Souichi! Now you've done it!
[SOUICHI laughs]
[SOGA]
Huh?!
[YANAGIDA, SOUICHI laugh]
[KOUTA] Our teacher's
been acting so weird.
And have you seen how
strange his face looks
when you get up close?
It's like... it's made of
cloth or something.
[KOUTA]
You think?
[YANAGIDA] So, basically,
this goes like this
and that goes like that
and that's how it works.
Everyone get it?
[STUDENTS murmur]
Sir, please!
You explained nothing.
And this is supposed
to be science class.
What did you say?
Don't be such a dense little
shit, Class Monitor Wakayama.
If you can't understand,
then you must be an idiot.
Give me 100 laps
around the field!
Don't just stand there,
get moving!
[WAKAYAMA pants]
Ha!
I bet you thought you'd
never get in trouble,
huh, class monitor?
Souichi! What the hell'd
you do to Mr. Yanagida?
What do you mean? I'm innocent.
[WAKAYAMA]
Don't play dumb!
[SOUICHI chuckles]
Bleh!
[WAKAYAMA]
Wait!
[SOUICHI]
See ya 'round!
--[WAKAYAMA grunts]
--[SOUICHI gasps]
[SOUICHI whimpers]
[SOUICHI]
Wakayama, you stupid troll.
How dare you pants me
and expose my butt
to the light of day like that?
No one embarrasses me and
gets away with it, dammit.
A curse upon you. Prepare to be
completely ruined by my power!
Huh?
[STUDENTS laughing]
Wakayama, what's with
that dumb beard, man?
I have no idea. I just woke
up and it was on my face, okay?
Honestly, it's not bad,
it makes you look manly.
Yeah!
That doesn't make me
feel any better.
I mean I haven't even
graduated elementary school.
[YANAGIDA] Wakayama,
you arrogant bastard!
What the hell do you think
you're doing with that
fuzzy junk all over your
stupid little face?
Get rid of that
beard right now.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[YANAGIDA chuckles]
I know.
Why don't I shave
it off for you?
Slice, slice! He, he, he!
Why are you backing away?
Slice. Slice. Slice. Slice!
[YANAGIDA grunts]
[YANAGIDA] Wakayama...
Now you've gone and done it.
Teacher's angry.
You're not our teacher!
You're some kind
of cloth imposter!
[WAKAYAMA grunts]
[YANAGIDA giggles]
[WAKAYAMA gasps]
[SOGA] Mr. Yanagida! What are
you doing to this young man?
[YANAGIDA]
Huh?
[SOGA] Stop! The principal
wants to speak with you.
You're to report to
his office right away.
[YANAGIDA giggles]
The principal, huh?
I wonder what he could want.
[YANAGIDA giggles] Maybe he's
gonna offer me a raise.
[WAKAYAMA exhales]
Are you going to be all right?
And is that a beard?
Yes, ma'am.
[SOGA]
What's that?
Mr. Yanagida's finger.
That can't be.
It's a roll of fabric.
Ah, so, he's definitely
a fake then.
[SOUICHI]
Tsk.
[KOUTA] Apparently Yanagida went
nuts in the principal's office
and then ran outta there.
They don't know where he is.
[WAKAYAMA] I hope that
doesn't have to do with why
Ms. Soga's late.
[KOUTA]
Right? It's getting dark.
You sure she said to meet here?
Yeah, I'm positive. She said
to wait outside her apartment.
[footsteps]
That must be her now.
[YAMADA gasps]
[BOYS grunt]
[SOGA grunts]
[ALL gasp]
Crap!
Ms. Soga's been turned into one
of those cloth monsters, too!
[growls]
Time for a lesson!
[WAKAYAMA]
Run for it!
[SOGA gibbers]
[BOYS shout, pant]
[SOGA, KOUTA yell]
[grunting]
[WAKAYAMA]
Kouta!
[WAKAYAMA gasps]
[SOGA yells]
[WAKAYAMA]
Back off!
[SOGA yells]
[WAKAYAMA] I'm sure Souichi's
the one behind this.
Look. Near the rooftop.
Something's moving.
--[SOUICHI giggles]
--[WAKAYAMA] It's him!
So, what now?
[WAKAYAMA]
Let's check it out.
I'll keep watch down here.
[KOUTA]
See anything?
[WAKAYAMA]
No. I don't think so.
[KOUTA gasps]
[WAKAYAMA]
What is it?
[KOUTA gasps]
[WAKAYAMA]
Someone's there.
[WAKAYAMA gasps]
Another one!
[BOTH gasp]
Uh, he looks exactly like you.
[WAKAYAMA]
I noticed.
Souichi must've made
those puppet doubles.
He replaced our real teachers,
and I'm next.
[KOUTA gasps]
Then we'll destroy it.
No, we can't!
[KOUTA]
Huh?
Think about what this
means for a second.
If he brings this to life,
that's how we can figure out
what happened to our teachers.
But what if you're killed
in the process?
I refuse to die.
We should get out of here
before he comes back.
Look, just promise me
you'll take that thing down
if it goes nuts, okay?
[STUDENTS chattering]
Sounds like there's some
kind of big panic outside.
[KOUTA gasps]
It's her!
[SOGA]
Don't screw around with me!
C'mon. Let's go.
Right.
[SOUICHI giggles]
[SOUICHI] Starting today, you
will take the place of Wakayama.
You're going to show up
at school buck naked
and run 100 laps
around the field.
That's the price you
pay for exposing me.
You moron. It's your curse.
--[KOUICHI] Souichi!
--[SOUICHI] Hm?
What are you doing?
You're supposed to be at school.
Oh, hey. You scared
me for a second.
And where did that creepy
doll come from, huh?
Explain yourself, now.
[SOUICHI giggles]
Can't catch me!
[KOUICHI gasps]
Come back!
[SOUICHI grunts]
[KOUICHI gasps]
No way!
[SOUICHI giggles]
What the hell is that thing?
[SOUICHI grunts]
[SOUICHI giggles] Here we go.
This should be quite a fun show.
[SOUICHI]
Hm?
[YANAGIDA] Hey, Souichi! I wanna
play with our nails some more.
Oh, it's you, Yanagida.
Sorry, but I'm amusing myself
with Wakayama at the moment.
[YANAGIDA groans]
[SOUICHI grunts]
[STUDENTS shouting]
[BOY A]
What is that thing?!
[SOGA yelling]
Don't screw around with me!
--[WAKAYAMA gasps]
--[SOGA yelling]
[KOUTA]
Hey! Wakayama!
[WAKAYAMA] I feel like I
suddenly lost all my strength.
That puppet from the attic
must have come to life,
I think it's draining
my soul or something.
Just keep it together.
[SOGA]
Huh? Squeak?
[WAKAYAMA gasps]
[SOGA]
You boys!
You two little hoodlums really
screwed me up yesterday!
Especially you.
Say your prayers, beardo!
[BOY B]
Another one?
--[GIRL A screams]
--[squeaking]
[SOGA]
Squeak squeak?
[SOGA yells]
Hold it!
I know who you are! You're the
monster who burned my face!
[WAKAYAMA gasps]
[YANAGIDA laughs]
Souichi!
[BOY C]
Is that Mr. Yanagida?
[BOY D]
Huh? What happened to him?
--[YANAGIDA giggles]
--[SOUICHI pants]
[SOUICHI yelps]
Right where it hurts!
[YANAGIDA laughs]
I've got you now.
[laughing continues]
--[GIRL E] Gross!
--[GIRL F] Ew!
Let go! Just let me leave.
I wanna go home!
[SOUICHI cries]
Let go! Let go!
Enough already.
Stop it. Stop it!
This isn't worth
the embarrassment.
It's not fair. I hate this!
[WAKAYAMA, KOUTA gasp]
[WAKAYAMA] And so, The bizarre
incident that kicked off
our fall semester
came to an end.
[WAKAYAMA] \
That very day,
someone found Ms. Soga
collapsed in her apartment.
And Mr. Yanagida was
discovered sitting in the park,
staring blankly
into a bonfire.
Both were fine.
I feel a lot better, too,
and the beard is gone.
As for Souichi, well...
[SOUICHI whimpers]