TAKATO AND THE GANG
CAME FACE TO FACE
WITH THE D-REAPER SCOUTS
IN THE PARK
AND DECIDED TO RUN FOR IT.
THEY HID OUT IN THE SCHOOL,
AND THE NEXT MORNING WENT
TO TAKATO'S FAMILY BAKERY
TO COLLECT THEIR THOUGHTS
AND FILL THEIR STOMACHS.
MEANWHILE, IMPMON GOT SOME HELP
FROM SENSEI
AND WENT OFF TO FIND
HIS TAMERS AI AND MAKO.
IT TURNS OUT THEY REALLY
MISSED THE LITTLE GUY.
WITH THE MILITARY
BACK IN ACTION,
THE GANG KNEW
THEY HAD TO HELP OUT.
BUT THE D-REAPER
WAS TOO STRONG.
THEN, OUT OF NOWHERE,
BEELZEMON SHOWED UP
AND SAVED THE DAY.
WHO KNOWS? MAYBE THERE'S
SOME GOOD IN HIM AFTER ALL.
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
♪ WORLD
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMODIFY
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
GOOD EVENING.
THIS IS THE NEWS AT 11:00.
TOPPING OUR NEWS TONIGHT,
WE HAVE A SPECIAL REPORT
ON THE ALARMING
AND DANGEROUS SITUATION
DEVELOPING IN WEST SHINJUKU.
A MYSTERIOUS RED SUBSTANCE
WHICH APPEARED A FEW DAYS AGO
IS THREATENING TO CONSUME
THE ENTIRE CITY,
DESPITE THE MILITARY'S
BEST EFFORTS.
TAKING YOU LIVE
TO THE DISASTER ZONE
IS OUR INTREPID REPORTER
MISS ZAKI.
I'M AT THE SHINJUKU
TRAIN STATION,
WHERE THE RED MASS
IS GROWING QUICKLY.
IT'S ALREADY COVERED
HALF THE TRACKS HERE,
AND SHOWS NO SIGNS
OF STOPPING.
AS YOU CAN SEE, THE ARMY
IS MAINTAINING A PRESENCE
IN THE AREA,
DESPITE THE FACT
THEY WERE UNABLE
TO CONTAIN THE MASS.
ONE THING YOU MIGHT NOT REALIZE
IS HOW HOT IT IS HERE.
IT SEEMS THE HEAT IS GENERATED
BY THE RED BLOB ITSELF.
LET ME TELL YOU, UNDER MY COAT,
I'M SWEATING
LIKE A PIG ON A SPIT.
EVERY TIME I WAKE UP
IN SCHOOL,
I THINK I'M IN A NIGHTMARE.
[ YAWNING ]
WHAT'S UP?
I COULDN'T GET ANY SLEEP
LAST NIGHT.
AND IT'S NOT 'CAUSE GUILMON
SNORED LIKE A DUMP TRUCK.
SOMETHING BUGGING YOU?
MMM...
I SAW JERI YESTERDAY.
WHAT? WHY DIDN'T YOU
SAY SOMETHING?
WELL, I CALLED HER MOM
IN MATSUMOTO TO TELL HER,
BUT SHE SAID JERI WASN'T GONE
TILL THE EVENING.
SO?
SO I SAW JERI
IN THE EVENING,
BUT THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE,
'CAUSE IT TAKES HOURS
TO GET FROM MATSUMOTO
TO HERE.
IT JUST DOESN'T
MAKE SENSE.
YOU SURE YOU'RE NOT
SEEING THINGS?
WHO KNOWS? MAYBE YOUR GOGGLES
WERE ON TOO TIGHT.
HUH?
THAT'S FUNNY.
I DON'T REMEMBER
LEAVING THE WINDOW OPEN.
IT WAS JERI,
OR JERI'S GHOST.
HUH?
I KNOW IT SOUNDS CRAZY.
I MEAN, SHE COULDN'T
GET HERE THAT FAST
IF SHE HITCHED A RIDE
ON A JET PLANE.
AND THE WAY THAT SHE LOOKED --
I DON'T KNOW.
THERE'S SOMETHING ABOUT THIS
THAT GIVES ME THE WILLIES.
OH, PLEASE.
YOU GET THE WILLIES
WHEN YOU LOSE A SOCK.
I JUST HOPE JERI'S OKAY.
SHE'S BEEN FREAKY
EVER SINCE WE GOT HOME.
SHE HAS BEEN THROUGH
A LOT.
I KNOW,
BUT SHE'S NOT JUST UPSET.
IT'S MORE THAN THAT.
IT'S LIKE SOMETHING'S BROKEN
DEEP INSIDE.
IT'S MY BELIEF
THE RED MASS CAME THROUGH
A NETWORK SURVEILLANCE SYSTEM
CALLED HYPNOS,
A GOVERNMENT OPERATION
THAT MONITORS
THE ON-LINE ACTIVITIES
OF HALF THE GLOBE.
BUT A SYSTEM THAT LARGE CAN ALSO
CAUSE VERY SERIOUS DAMAGE.
PROFESSOR HORATO,
DIDN'T HYPNOS
HAVE SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THE GIANT PIG
THAT APPEARED IN WEST SHINJUKU
A FEW MONTHS AGO?
I BELIEVE IT'S CALLED
A DIGIMON.
AH, YOU MEAN THAT MONSTER
THAT TORE UP HALF THE CITY.
WELL, OF COURSE.
THAT KING KONG-SIZED PIG
AND THE RED GOOP
AREN'T NATURAL OCCURRENCES.
THEY'RE OBVIOUSLY
DATA PROGRAMS
THAT HAVE FOUND A WAY
TO APPEAR IN THE REAL WORLD.
AND THE FOLKS AT HYPNOS
ARE THE ONES RESPONSIBLE.
DO YOU BELIEVE THERE'S
ANY WAY OUT OF THIS CRISIS?
AT THIS POINT, IT WILL TAKE
A MIRACLE.
THANK YOU, PROFESSOR HORATO.
WAIT! THIS JUST IN!
WE'VE RECEIVED EXCLUSIVE FOOTAGE
FROM INSIDE THE RED MASS,
AND -- OH, YUCK!
HEY, WHAT'S THIS?
HUH?
OUR PARENTS.
THIS CAN'T BE GOOD.
THERE ARE NOW REPORTS
OF STRANGE BEINGS
IN ADDITION
TO THE RED MASS.
ARE THEY FLESH, FOWL,
OR ARE THEY MORE DESTRUCTIVE,
VICIOUS DIGIMON?
TO ANSWER THIS QUESTION,
WE HAVE WITH US
PROFESSOR ROB McCOY, A MEMBER
OF THE ORIGINAL TEAM
THAT CREATED THESE DIGIMON.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
FIRST, I'D LIKE TO CLEAR
ANY MISCONCEPTIONS
PEOPLE HAVE OF DIGIMON.
THESE ARE ARTIFICIAL
INTELLIGENCE PROGRAMS,
NOT MONSTERS.
WELL, I MEAN, THEY ARE MONSTERS.
DIGITAL MONSTERS, TO BE EXACT.
THEY'RE JUST NOT ALL
DESTRUCTIVE WRECKING MACHINES
LIKE THE GIANT PIG.
HA HA HA HA.
THE DIGIMON'S ABILITY TO EVOLVE
COMES FROM THEIR RELATIONSHIP
WITH CHILDREN --
WHICH MAKES SENSE, OF COURSE,
BECAUSE CHILDREN'S MINDS
ARE RICH IN IMAGINATION.
DIGIMON FEED OFF
THIS CREATIVITY
TO BECOME SMARTER
AND STRONGER.
SO IT'S UNLIKELY DIGIMON
WOULD WANT TO HARM OUR WORLD.
THE RED MASS
AND BEINGS AROUND IT
ARE ACTUALLY PART OF
AN OLD CLEAN-UP PROGRAM
CALLED D-REAPER, WHICH SOMEHOW
ALSO MANAGED TO EVOLVE.
GUYS, HOLD ON A MINUTE.
I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD GO.
WHY NOT?
WHY NOT? WHAT IF IT'S
A TRAP OR SOMETHING?
RIKA,
MY FOLKS AREN'T LIKE THAT.
MAYBE THEY JUST WANT
TO TALK.
YOU KNOW, RIKA,
HE MAY BE RIGHT.
WE SHOULD TRUST THEM.
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
YOU GUYS ARE SO NAIVE!
HUH? UH...
IS THAT...
JERI!
WHAT IS THIS CHAOTIC WORLD?
THESE CREATURES
MINDLESSLY ACT ON THEIR OWN,
BUT THERE IS NO VALUE
IN THE ONE.
ONLY PAIN AND DOUBT
OUTSIDE THE COLLECTIVE.
AHH!
JERI!
AS YOU CAN SEE,
THE BEINGS IN THE RED MASS
ARE CONNECTED BY SOME KIND
OF CABLE.
WE BELIEVE THESE DRONES
ARE NOT INDIVIDUAL ENTITIES,
BUT AGENTS CREATED
BY THE D-REAPER PROGRAM.
THEY OPERATE AS A COLLECTIVE,
MUCH LIKE BEES IN A HIVE.
D-REAPER WORKS BY ABSORBING DATA
AND REDUCING IT TO ZERO,
BUT WHEN IT ABSORBS DIGIMON
ON THE NETWORK,
IT SOMEHOW ACQUIRES
THE DIGIMON'S ABILITY
TO EMERGE AND OPERATE
IN THE REAL WORLD.
[ PANTING ]
TAKATO, WHAT IS IT?
WHAT'S WRONG?
JERI -- I JUST SAW HER.
SHE WAS RIGHT HERE.
WHAT?
HUH?
DID YOU SEE ANYTHING?
NOT ME.
RIKA,
I SENSED A PRESENCE.
REALLY? WAS IT JERI?
I DON'T KNOW.
SHE LOOKED SO --
SO EMPTY.
WHERE ARE WE SETTING UP?
WHO KNOWS?
WHERE'S THE DOUGHNUTS?
YOU'RE BLAMING YOURSELF
FOR ALL OF THIS,
AREN'T YOU?
[ GRUMBLES ]
YOU KNOW,
SOMEDAY THE NETWORK
WILL NO LONGER BE
A FREE WORLD.
IT'S UNAVOIDABLE.
AND THERE WILL ALWAYS BE
SOMEONE TRYING TO CONTROL IT.
YOU JUST HAPPENED TO BE
THE FIRST ONE TO TRY, YAMAKI.
THAT'S ALL.
[ COUGHS ]
I HAVE NO INTENTION
OF BEING THE FIRST
IN A LINE OF FOOLS,
RILEY.
NO, I --
YOU JUST NEED SOME REST.
LET'S SEE.
THE CITY IS ENGULFED
IN MASS CHAOS,
ALL THANKS TO A PROGRAM
I SOMEHOW LET INTO THE WORLD.
I DON'T THIS IS TIME
FOR A NAP, NOW, DO YOU?
HEY!
THE COFFEE BREAK'S OVER,
MY FRIENDS.
I JUST GOT THE ORIGINAL DATA
ON D-REAPER.
HA HA.
BUT HOW'D YOU GET IT?
A PAL OF MINE IN GERMANY
SAVED A COPY.
THAT'S THE GREAT ADVANTAGE
OF HAVING NERDY FRIENDS.
THEY NEVER DELETE ANYTHING.
THIS MAY BE JUST THE LUCKY BREAK
WE'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR.
TAO! COME ON,
WHILE WE'RE STILL YOUNG!
KEEP YOUR HAT ON,
YOU OLD GOAT.
Rika: UM, HELLO?
All: HUH?
HEY, WELCOME HOME.
HA HA HA.
WELL, TO RIKA'S HOME,
ANYWAY.
HOPE YOU'RE HUNGRY.
HOLY MACKEREL!
BUNS AND BEANS
AND SAUERKRAUT,
I'M GONNA EAT
TILL I PASS OUT!
YEAH!
[ GROWLING ]
[ Sniffs ]
IS THIS WHAT I THINK IT IS?
YEP. WELL, I PROMISED YOU,
DIDN'T I?
DO YOU LIKE IT?
GUILMON BREAD,
GUILMON BREAD!
THERE'S A LOAF
SHAPED LIKE MY HEAD.
WELL, I THINK
THAT'S A "YES."
YOUR MOTHER AND I
COOKED ALL DAY.
NOW EAT UP
BEFORE IT GETS COLD.
WOW.
YOU COOK?
HMM? OF COURSE, SILLY.
I'M NOT JUST
ALL LOOKS, YOU KNOW.
WELL, GO ON ALREADY.
AREN'T YOU HUNGRY?
All:
YOU BETTER BELIEVE IT!
[ EATING LOUDLY ]
MOM, WHERE'S SUZIE?
WELL, YOUR SENSEI
WAS NICE ENOUGH
TO LOOK AFTER HER
FOR A WHILE.
OH.
HENRY! CHECK THIS OUT!
I CAN FIT FOUR BITES
IN MY MOUTH!
OH, TAKATO?
YEAH? WHAT'S UP?
WELL, I KNEW YOU MISSED THEM,
SO I BROUGHT YOUR TOOTHBRUSH
AND YOUR FAVORITE PAJAMAS
WITH THE TEDDY BEARS ON THEM.
MOM!
HELLO?
AH, NUTS.
WHERE DID EVERYBODY GO?
WHOA!
YOU'RE PRETTY LIGHT
ON YOUR FEET
FOR SOMEBODY WHO EATS
HIS WEIGHT IN CREAM PUFFS.
YOU SHOULDN'T SNEAK UP
ON PEOPLE LIKE THAT. SHEESH!
EH. SO, WHAT YOU
BEEN UP TO,
YOU DIGITAL DOUGH BOY?
I WAS WITH JERI, THEN,
POOF, SHE DISAPPEARED.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
TO HER.
NOW I'M ALL BY MY LONESOME.
HMM. JERI.
IT WAS HER PARTNER.
I -- HMM.
IMPMON,
NOW WHAT ARE YOU DOING, HUH?
I GOT THIS STABBING PAIN
IN MY HEAD.
I THINK IT'S CALLED
A CONSCIENCE.
I GOT TO DO SOMETHING
ABOUT IT.
OH.
HYPNOS IS A CLASSIFIED
GOVERNMENT PROGRAM.
IT IS NOT RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE RECENT DEVELOPMENTS
IN SHINJUKU.
BUT WHY HAVE YOU KEPT
HYPNOS A SECRET FOR SO LONG?
IS IT TRUE
THAT IT INTRUDES
ON PRIVATE INFORMATION
ON THE NET?
AND DIDN'T THE RED MASS EMERGE
FROM THE HYPNOS NETWORK?
WHAT IS THE GOVERNMENT
TRYING TO HIDE, SIR?
UH, NO COMMENT.
NO COMMENT? WHAT,
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
[ REPORTERS SHOUTING ]
WE INTERRUPT
THIS PRESS CONFERENCE
TO BRING YOU BREAKING NEW
DEVELOPMENTS IN WEST SHINJUKU.
[ PANTING ]
[ GROWLING ]
[ Gasps ] DOBERMON!
NO!
[ GROWLING ]
OH, I ATE SO FAST,
I FORGOT TO BREATHE!
[ Belches ]
[ BELCH ]
I NEED A BIGGER TUMMY,
TAKATO.
DRAW ME ONE?
OKAY.
YOU'RE A PAL.
DRAW HIM
SOME SELF-CONTROL.
AND JUST HOW MANY BUNS
HAVE YOU HAD?
2, 3, 12 --
I LOST COUNT.
HENRY COULD LEARN
A THING OR TWO
FROM YOU, TERRIERMON.
HE'S HANDSOME, BUT SKINNY
AS A MOSQUITO, RIGHT?
HA...RIGHT.
RENAMON?
HUH? OH.
THE FOOD WAS DELICIOUS.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE VERY WELCOME.
WHY DON'T YOU JOIN US?
NO, I CAN'T.
Terriermon: MOMENTIE.
THAT THING'S TOO BIG
TO GO ANYWHERE.
YEAH, I KNOW HOW HE FEELS.
HUH?
THIS IS THE D-REAPER PROGRAM
THAT'S CAUSING
ALL THESE PROBLEMS?
SHIBUMI, YOU ACTUALLY SAW
THE D-REAPER
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD.
DOES IT OPERATE
THE SAME WAY HERE?
NO. ODDLY ENOUGH,
IT ACTS VERY DIFFERENTLY HERE.
YOU SEE, IN THE DIGITAL WORLD,
IT NEUTRALIZED OBJECTS
SIMPLY BY TOUCHING THEM.
BUT IN THE REAL WORLD,
IT'S DEVELOPED
A MUCH MORE COMPLEX APPROACH,
LIKE ITS USE OF DRONES
OR AGENTS.
HEY, CHECK IT OUT.
I PULLED UP A SATELLITE
PICTURE OF THE AREA.
TAKE A LOOK AT THE RED MASS.
IT STAYS WAY THE HECK CLEAR
OF THE PARKS
AND AREAS WITH A LOT
OF GREENERY.
LOOKS LIKE THE D-REAPER AND I
HAVE SOMETHING IN COMMON.
WE BOTH HATE OUR GREENS.
TAO, MY MAN, YOU HAVEN'T
CHANGED ONE BIT.
THE TRICK IS FINDING
SOME WAY
TO USE IT
TO OUR ADVANTAGE.
THANKS, MOM AND DAD.
IF GUILMON COULD SIT UP,
I'M SURE HE'D THANK YOU, TOO.
[ GUILMON GROANING ]
HUH?
[ BEEPING ]
I'M GETTING A HUGE
ACTIVITY READING.
RENAMON, WHAT'S GOING ON?
I'LL FIND OUT.
LET'S GO, BOYS.
RIGHT. COME ON. EH...
UH...
WE'RE SORRY. WE DIDN'T WANT
THIS TO HAPPEN --
HONEST --
BUT WE -- WE HAVE TO --
TO LEAVE.
WE'VE DISCUSSED IT,
AND WE DECIDED
WE DON'T WANT YOU TO GO.
THE FACT IS, ANY OTHER KID
WOULD NEVER BE ALLOWED
TO RUSH INTO DANGER
LIKE THIS, AND YOU KNOW IT.
BUT...YOU'RE NOT
ANY OTHER KID.
YOU'RE ALL VERY SPECIAL,
AND WHETHER WE LIKE IT
OR NOT,
YOU'RE FREE TO DO
WHAT YOU THINK IS RIGHT.
HA.
HA HA.
HONESTLY, BETWEEN YOU
AND YOUR FATHER,
IT'S A WONDER MY HAIR
HASN'T GONE TOTALLY GRAY.
[ GROANING ]
I ALMOST LOST YOU ONCE,
HENRY,
AND THE THOUGHT OF LOSING
YOU AGAIN IS TOO MUCH.
BUT THIS IS JUST
TOO IMPORTANT
FOR ME TO STOP YOU.
REALLY? THANKS, MOM.
AW...
YOU'RE OKAY WITH THIS,
MOM?
OF COURSE I'M NOT.
I WISH YOU HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH ANY OF THIS.
I WISH YOU WERE STILL
A BABY
I COULD KEEP SAFELY
AT HOME.
OH, MOM.
BUT YOU'RE NOT, ARE YOU?
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF,
DEAR.
I WILL.
IT'S HARD TO THINK
WHILE OTHER KIDS
ARE PLAYING TAG,
YOU'RE OUT SAVING THE WORLD.
WITH ALL OUR WORRYING,
WE PROBABLY HAVEN'T TOLD YOU
HOW PROUD WE ARE OF YOU.
WELL, WE ARE.
BUT IF YOU DON'T COME HOME
IN ONE PIECE,
YOU'RE ALL IN BIG TROUBLE,
GOT IT?
GOT IT.
[ GROWLING ]
WAIT FOR ME! WHOA!
THE RED MASS IS INTERFERING
WITH OUR TRANSMISSION,
SO I DON'T KNOW HOW LONG
I'LL BE ABLE TO STAY ON,
BUT FOR THE MOMENT,
IT SEEMS RATHER QUIET
HERE IN WEST SHINJUKU.
AAH!
[ STOMPING ]
WHAT IN THE WORLD
IS GOING ON?
I'VE GOT TO KEEP IT TOGETHER.
[ BEEP ]
HMM?
NOW WHAT?
IT...CAN'T BE.
TAKATO SAID THE ARK
COMMUNICATED WITH HIM
THROUGH MY DEVICE.
BUT THE ARK'S GONE.
SOMEONE MUST HAVE HACKED IN
AND COPIED ITS SIGNATURE.
YAMAKI,
IT'S THE CHILDREN.
THEY'RE HEADED
RIGHT FOR THE RED MASS.
WHAT?
[ GROWLING ]
IT'S OVER THERE!
ALL RIGHT, WHO'S UP FOR
A ROUND OF TARGET PRACTICE?
HYAH!
LET'S GO GET 'EM!
DRAGONATOR!
PYRO BLASTER!
THEY'RE AFTER SOMETHING.
THERE! LOOK!
[ PANTING ]
KYUBIMON!
FOXTAIL INFERNO!
GOOD GOING.
Henry:
HEY...ARE YOU OKAY?
WHO ARE YOU?
IS THAT YOU, JERI?
[ GROANING ]
IT'S NOT.
YEAH, NO KIDDING.
WHO THE HECK ARE YOU,
AND WHY ARE YOU CONTACTING ME?
IT IS THE ARK.
BUT I CAN'T DECIPHER
THE MESSAGE.
COULD IT BE A WARNING,
A CLUE OF SOME KIND?
AHH...THE CHILDREN.
YOU'RE THE TAMERS.
WE'VE BEEN SEARCHING
FOR YOU.
THAT WOULD BE US.
DO WE KNOW YOU?
I KNOW YOU.
HOW ABOUT A LITTLE MORE
INFORMATION THERE, BLONDIE?
TAKATO?
HUH?
YEAH, WHAT IS IT, GROWLMON?
THAT'S NO DOGGY.
THAT'S A DIGIMON.
HUH?
ARE THESE CHILDREN
THE ONES I SEEK?
I THINK SO.
I WISH THEY WEREN'T.
DOLPHIN, WHEN YOU BUILT
THE ARK,
YOU USED THE DIGIMON
CORE PROGRAM, RIGHT?
SO DOES THAT MEAN
THE ARK ITSELF
WILL BEHAVE LIKE A DIGIMON?
THEY DO SHARE THE SAME
PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE,
BUT THAT DOESN'T
MAKE THEM THE SAME.
YOU KNOW, LIKE HUMANS
AND PIGS
ARE BOTH CARBON-BASED
LIFE FORMS,
BUT THAT DOESN'T
MAKE US PIGS.
LISTEN, I JUST WANT TO KNOW
IF THE ARK IS SELF-AWARE.
IT'S CAPABLE OF ACTING
ON ITS OWN.
WE'VE SEEN IT.
BUT IS IT POSSIBLE
FOR THE ARK
TO THINK INDEPENDENTLY
AND MAKE DECISIONS
LIKE A PERSON?
I WOULDN'T HAVE THOUGHT SO,
BUT EVERY I'VE UNDERESTIMATED
DIGITAL LIFE FORMS,
I'VE BEEN DEAD WRONG.
WHY THE SUDDEN INTEREST,
YAMAKI?
I THINK THAT THE ARK
MAY BE TRYING TO TELL US
SOMETHING, DOLPHIN.
SAY WHAT?
[ GROWLING ]
YOUR PARTNER LOOKS
KIND OF TENSE THERE.
DOBERMON'S
JUST ON HIS GUARD.
HE'S BEEN HUNTED MERCILESSLY
EVER SINCE HE ARRIVED
IN THE REAL WORLD.
IT WANTS TO STOP HIM
FROM HIS QUEST.
OKAY,
SO WHAT'S HIS QUEST?
TO DELIVER...
A MESSAGE.
A MESSAGE? FROM WHO?
HEADS UP!
[ SCREAMING ]
TAKE THAT, SQUID FACE!
WATCH OUT!
DIGIMODIFY!
MATRIX DIGIVOLUTION,
ACTIVATE!
GARGOMON MATRIX DIGIVOLVE
TO...
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON
RAPIDMON!
KYUBIMON MATRIX DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DI-DI-DI
TAOMON!
GROWLMON MATRIX DIGIVOLVE TO...
WARGROWLMON!
[ GROWLING ]
TALISMAN OF LIGHT!
GRR!
TRI BEAM!
RAPIDMON!
THAT THING'S WAY TOO STRONG.
WE GOT TO BIOMERGE NOW.
WE CAN'T. THIS ISN'T
THE DIGITAL WORLD.
OUR PARTNERS ARE DATA,
BUT WE'RE NOT.
THERE'S NO WAY
WE CAN BIOMERGE HERE.
THERE IS A WAY.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
All: HUH?
THAT'S WHY I BROUGHT HIM.
DOBERMON?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THIS IS MY QUEST.
I WAS SENT HERE
BY THE DIGIMON SOVEREIGN
TO HELP YOU.
HUH?
BUT HOW?
IT DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
THE ARK APPEARED
SERIOUSLY DAMAGED
WHEN ITS DATA RETURNED
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
ITS POWER WAS ALMOST
DEPLETED.
HOW COULD IT TRANSMIT
ANYTHING?
THANK YOU, ALICE,
BUT YOU KNOW
WHAT I MUST DO.
I KNOW.
I'LL NEVER FORGET
WHAT YOU'VE DONE...
FOR ALL OF US.
[ GROWLS ]
[ GASPING ]
THE DIGIMON SOVEREIGN
ARE FIGHTING THE ENEMY
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD.
BUT THE ENEMY'S
MOST EVOLVED PART
HAS EMERGED TO WAGE WAR
HERE, IN YOUR WORLD.
ONLY YOU, THE TAMERS,
CAN STOP IT,
BY FIGHTING AS ONE
WITH YOUR DIGIMON.
TO AID YOU, I BRING A GIFT
FROM THE DIGIMON SOVEREIGN.
REMEMBER,
THE FATE OF THE WORLD
LIES IN YOUR HANDS!
DOBERMON!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
I CAN'T BE SURE,
BUT I --
I THINK HE'S GIVING US
THE POWER TO BIOMERGE!
THEN LET'S DO IT
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
DOBERMON'S RIGHT.
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES
WHO HAVE ANY CHANCE
OF SAVING THIS WORLD.
WARGROWLMON, LET'S DO IT!
RAPIDMON!
TAOMON!
[ GROANS ]
AND I THOUGHT THOSE WERE JUST
FANCY FIREWORKS.
WILL WE REALLY BE ABLE
TO BIOMERGE?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."