Takato: YAMAKI
AND THE MONSTER MAKERS
WORKED NIGHT AND DAY TO FINISH
THE ARK THAT WOULD GET
THE TAMERS BACK HOME
TO THE REAL WORLD.
MEANWHILE, THE SOVEREIGN ASKED
CALUMON TO GIVE BACK THE LIGHT
OF DIGIVOLUTION. THAT WAY,
THE DIGIMON MIGHT BE
STRONG ENOUGH TO FACE
THE D-REAPER ON THEIR OWN TURF.
ONCE THE DIGI-GNOMES
PITCHED IN,
DIGIMON EVERYWHERE
DIGIVOLVED TO MEGA!
KNOWING THE DIGITAL WORLD
WAS IN GOOD HANDS,
THE TAMERS PREPARED
TO GO HOME.
BUT JUST AS THEY GOT WORD
THAT THE ARK WAS ON ITS WAY,
RIKA AND RENAMON WENT OFF
TO FIND IMPMON.
THEY BETTER HURRY UP, OR THEY'RE
GOING TO MISS THE BOAT.
DI-DI-DI
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON
DI-DI-DI
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS
TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
WORLD
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS
DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON
[ BEEPING ]
THERE SHE IS.
OUR ONE-WAY TICKET HOME.
WHAT IS THAT?
Guilmon: OH, I HOPE IT DOESN'T
BLOW OUR ARK AWAY.
[ SCREAMING ]
IT'S OKAY, SUZIE.
EVERYONE HURRY UP
AND GET ON!
[ Thinking ] JERI, COME ON,
WE GOT TO GET ON!
GUARDROMON, A LITTLE HELP!
BUT OF COURSE.
Henry: LET'S GO! THE ARK
COULD LEAVE ANY MINUTE!
Takato: BUT WAIT! THERE'S
STILL NO SIGN OF RIKA!
Guilmon: TAKATO, GET ON!
IN A MINUTE!
THEN I'M COMING DOWN!
NO! YOU PROMISED DAD
YOU'D GO HOME, REMEMBER?
HE'S MAKING YOU A BIG BATCH
OF GUILMON BREAD.
YEAH...
[ Thinking ]
RIKA, WHERE ARE YOU?
Renamon: IMPMON WAS RIGHT.
WE ARE OUT OF OUR
TEENY-TINY MINDS.
WE'LL MAKE IT.
NOT AT THE RATE
I'M CRAWLING ALONG.
I NEED MORE STRENGTH.
I HAVE JUST THE PICK-ME-UP.
ALL RIGHT!
HELLO? HEY, JERI,
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
OH, WHY WON'T YOU SAY
ANYTHING TO ME, HUH?
YEAH, KID,
ARE YOU OKAY?
WE'LL BE HOME SOON,
JERI.
YEAH, SOONER THAN SOON.
[ CRASH ]
WE'RE MOVING,
WE'RE MOVING!
AAH! HURRY, TAKATO!
BUT THEY'RE NOT HERE YET!
HENRY, DON'T YOU THINK WE'D
BETTER GO LOOK FOR THEM?
YEAH.
NO, I'LL GET THEM.
CYBERDRAMON?
[ CYBERDRAMON GROWLS ]
Ryo: WE'LL BE BACK
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT!
BE CAREFUL!
Kazu: RIKA IS MESSING UP
THE PROGRAM.
THAT ISSOLIKE HER.
OW!
OH, NO! TAKATO!
HOW DO WE STOP THIS THING?
WE GOT TO FIND
THE BRAKES!
ARK! COME ON, STOP!
OR WE COULD JUST
YELL AT IT.
ARK, PLEASE,
TAKATO'S NOT ON YET.
WE CAN'T LEAVE.
STOP IT!
GUILMON, YOU DO REALIZE
YOU'RE TALKING TO A BOAT.
TAKATO, TRY AND JUMP ON.
OKAY!
THIS ISN'T GOOD.
Yamaki:
THIS IS EXCELLENT.
LOOK, THE ARK --
IT'S HEADING BACK.
MM-HMM.
LET'S JUST HOPE THE CHILDREN
ARE ONBOARD.
Woman: ARK TRAJECTORY CONFIRMED.
CALCULATING EMERGENCE POINT.
THE TRACK BEAM IS STRONG
AND STABLE.
ENERGY RESOURCE AT 60%.
IT'S WORKING!
MY LITTLE BABY
IS COMING HOME,
THANKS TO DECENTRALIZED
COMPUTING.
HOT DOG! I DO BELIEVE
I AM A GENIUS!
Man: HEY, GENIUS, YOU GOT
THE NEXT CALCULATIONS?
PIECE OF CAKE.
"THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
PHASE ONE SUCCESSFUL.
NEXT, PLEASE PROCEED
WITH REMAINING CALCULATIONS."
ALL RIGHT.
WITH EVERYONE
ALL OVER THE WORLD HELPING,
WE'LL GET RIKA BACK
IN NO TIME.
OH, RIKA,
PLEASE BE ON THAT ARK.
Henry: NO! KEEP RUNNING!
YOU CAN DO IT!
TAKATO!
AAH!
Henry: CAREFUL, GUILMON,
YOU'LL FALL!
NOT IF I CAN HELP IT!
MOMENTIE! WE'RE COMING!
OH!
AH! IT'S WORKING!
Terriermon: GOOD THING.
MY EARS ARE CRAMPING!
HUH?
OH, NO!
CALUMON!
[ SCREAMING ]
OH, ARK, YOU GOTTA STOP!
PLEASE LISTEN TO ME!
STOP!
WHAT? WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT ON EARTH'S HAPPENING?
WHY DID THE ARK STOP?
GET DOLPHIN -- NOW!
HEY, LOOK. IT STOPPED.
BUT WHY?
[ YELLING ]
Ryo: HEY, WAIT FOR US! HEY!
HMM? IS THAT
WHO I THINK IT IS?
LOOK WHAT THE CAT
DRAGGED IN!
RIKA! MM-HMM!
ALL RIGHT, RIKA!
I KNEW YOU'D MAKE IT!
[ TYPING ]
WHAT'S GOING ON HERE,
DAISY?
I'M NOT SURE, BUT IT SEEMS
AS IF THE ARK'S
ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE
IS SOMEHOW ACTING ON ITS OWN.
THE ARK'S NOT RESPONDING,
DOLPHIN!
HAS THE PROGRAM
GONE RENEGADE?
IMPOSSIBLE. I WROTE
THAT A.I. PROGRAM MYSELF!
THINK -- WHERE DID YOU GET
THE CODE FROM?
IF MEMORY SERVES,
FROM THE DIGIMON CORE PROGRAM!
I USED THE SAME ARTIFICIAL LIFE
PROGRAM THAT WE USED
TO CREATE THE DIGIMON
TO POWER THE ARK.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
I COULD GET THE MACHINE TO WORK.
HERE! THIS IS IT!
BUT EVEN SO, THIS SHOULDN'T
HAVE CAUSED THE ARK
TO THINK FOR ITSELF.
Rika: HEY THERE.
NEED A LIFT?
YEAH!
GOING UP!
WHOA!
AAH!
WELL, MISS TARDY, WHAT DO YOU
HAVE TO SAY FOR YOURSELF?
SORRY.
[ Gasps ] IT'S HIM.
RIKA, ARE YOU OUT OF YOUR
CHICKEN-FRIED MIND?
YOU WENT BACK
TO SAVE IMPMON?
MM-HMM.
WELL, I'VE SAID IT BEFORE
AND I'LL SAY IT AGAIN,
YOU'RE CRAZIER THAN CATFISH.
[ GROANING ]
Guardromon:
CRAZIER THAN CATFISH!
HUH?
HEY, COME UP
WITH YOUR OWN LINE!
[ BUZZING ]
UH, GUYS...
HUH? A DIGIVICE!
WOW! HELLO, HELLO.
AHH...MARINEANGEMON?
I GET IT. YOU'RE MY TAMER,
I MEAN, MY PARTNER.
AND YOU'RE A MEGA!
THAT MAKES ME A TAMER
TO A MEGA!
OH, I THINK I'M GOING
TO FAINT.
Takato: AMAZING. I WONDER HOW
HE ENDED UP IN KENTA'S POCKET.
Kazu: I'M AMAZED
HE'S STILL BREATHING.
HAVE YOU SEEN WHAT KENTA
KEEPS IN HIS POCKETS?
[ Thinking ]
SHE SHOULD'VE LEFT ME
AFTER WHAT I DID.
UH...
HEY!
KENTA, I JUST WANT
TO TOUCH HIM!
NUH-UH! YOU'RE JUST TRYING
TO FREAK HIM OUT!
[ Thinking ]
I DON'T DESERVE TO BE HERE.
DON'T THEY KNOW THAT?
Rika: WOULD YOU CLOWNS
KNOCK IT OFF?
Kazu: YOU CAN'T BOSS ME AROUND.
I AM A TAMER. NYAH!
IT'S MOVING.
WHAT DO WE DO?
THERE'S NOTHING WE CAN DO,
BUT WAIT
AND HOPE IT DOESN'T
CHANGE ITS MIND AGAIN.
Woman: THE ARK'S PROGRESS
HAS RESUMED.
RECALCULATING
ROUTE COORDINATES.
[ SHOUTING ]
YOU CAN DO IT.
KEEP ON TRUCKING, ARK.
JUST A LITTLE MORE.
ALL THOSE KIDS
ARE DEPENDING ON YOU
TO BRING THEM HOME.
OH, NO, THE TRACK'S
OFF COURSE BY 12.4 DEGREES!
HEY, NO SWEAT!
I'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
LISTEN UP! SOMEONE HAS
TO TELL THE CHILDREN'S PARENTS
THAT THE EMERGENCE POINT
HAS CHANGED.
IT'S NOW IN THE MIDDLE
OF SHINJUKU PARK.
Guilmon: THEN TAKATO'S DAD
SAID HE WOULD BAKE A BREAD
THAT LOOKS JUST LIKE ME.
I DON'T KNOW HOW
HE'S GOING TO DO THAT
BECAUSE I DON'T LOOK ANYTHING
LIKE A LOAF OF BREAD.
WELL, MAYBE WHEN I CURL UP
FOR A NAP.
Takato: GUILMON, WHO ARE
YOU TALKING TO?
THE ARK, SILLY.
WHAT -- THE ARK?
WHY NOT? IT'S A REAL
GOOD LISTENER, TAKATO.
I ASKED IT TO STOP
WHEN YOU COULDN'T GET ON,
AND IT DID.
SO THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
WELL, IF YOU CAN HEAR ME,
THANK YOU, ARK.
[ Thinking ]
IF IT WASN'T FOR YOU,
WE'D BE DOING THE BACKSTROKE
IN THE SEA OF CHAOS BY NOW,
INSTEAD OF GOING HOME.
HA HA.
OH, JERI,
WE'LL GET YOU BACK.
I PROMISE.
Rika: DON'T WORRY, JERI.
WE'RE ALMOST HOME.
OH.
HANG IN THERE, OKAY?
SO, TELL ME SOMETHING, RIKA.
WHAT DO I GET FOR SAVING
YOUR LIFE NOT ONCE,
BUT TWICE, HMM?
HOW ABOUT
TWICE THE WHUPPIN'?
YEAH, RIGHT. YOU WISH.
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ BEEPING ]
Kazu: WHY DO I GET THE FEELING
THIS ISN'T JUST TURBULENCE?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
Guilmon: UM, IT LOOKS LIKE
THE LIGHT TRACK IS DISAPPEARING.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN,
TAKATO?
HUH, WELL, I THINK IT MEANS
WE'RE IN TROUBLE!
[ ALARM BLARING ]
HUH? WHAT NOW?
WE'RE HANGING IN THE MIDDLE
OF NOWHERE!
WHAT ELSE COULD GO WRONG?
UH, IT FEELS LIKE
WE'RE FALLING!
I THINK THE ARK HAS LOST
ALL OF ITS STRENGTH!
OH, MAN, WHEN THINGS
GO WRONG...
WE'LL NEVER GET OUT
OF HERE!
BUT WE WERE SO CLOSE.
WITH THE TRACKS GONE,
THE ARK WON'T BE ABLE
TO FIND ITS WAY BACK HOME.
Takato: ARK,
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
I KNOW YOU CAN HEAR ME.
PLEASE, YOU'VE GOT
TO HELP US!
YOU'RE OUR ONLY CHANCE
OF GETTING OUT OF HERE!
JUST A LITTLE FURTHER,
AND WE'LL BE HOME.
OUR PARENTS ARE DEPENDING
ON YOU.
PLEASE HELP US!
HUH?
THANKS.
I TOLD YOU.
IT'S A REAL GOOD LISTENER.
HUH?
EVERYBODY, HOLD ON
TO SOMETHING!
GUYS, THE ARK --
IT'S STARTING TO DISAPPEAR.
Kazu: HEY, ARK, DUDE,
IF YOU GET US OUT OF THIS,
I WILL HAND-WASH YOU
EVERY DAY OF THE WEEK,
VACUUM YOUR INSIDES,
YOU NAME IT!
Kenta: MARINEANGEMON,
I'LL MISS YOU!
[ Thinking ]
COME ON, ARK, YOU CAN DO IT!
I KNOW YOU CAN.
[ SIRENS WAILING ]
THAT'S NORMAL, RIGHT?
THAT DEPENDS ON HOW
YOU DEFINE "NORMAL," JANYUU.
AHH...
HA HA HA HA!
[ GIGGLES ]
[ Thinking ]
BACK HOME, WHERE I DON'T BELONG.
HUH? IMPMON...
Riley: I JUST FOUND
JERI'S PARENTS.
THEY'RE STAYING WITH RELATIVES
IN EAST MATSUMOTO.
Yamaki: SO, WHEN WILL THEY
BE HERE?
THAT'S THE THING --
THEY WON'T.
HUH?
YOU SEE, HER FATHER
SAID SHE LEFT
ON HER OWN, SO SHE CAN
COME BACK ON HER OWN.
WE COULD SEND ONE
OF OUR OPERATIVES
TO TAKE HER THERE,
BUT TO BE ALONE...
THE POOR THING.
WAIT! I'LL TAKE HER HOME!
HUH?
LISTEN TO ME!
JERI'S ALL BY HERSELF.
SHE NEEDS TO BE WITH SOMEONE
SHE KNOWS RIGHT NOW.
BUT, TAKATO,
THAT'S SO FAR AWAY.
HONEY, LET HIM GO.
REALLY?
Guilmon: REALLY?
WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE WE WON'T
KNOW WHERE YOU ARE THIS TIME.
BESIDES, WE TRUST YOU.
MY LITTLE BOY
IS ALL GROWN UP.
[ GIGGLES ]
NOW, REMEMBER, TAKATO,
AS SOON AS YOU'VE GOTTEN
JERI HOME SAFELY, GO STRAIGHT
TO YOUR AUNT'S HOUSE.
WE'LL BE WAITING FOR YOU.
IS THAT OKAY?
MM-HMM. YEAH, MOM.
THANKS.
ALL RIGHT THEN.
THE STREETS OUT OF SHINJUKU
ARE CLOSED OFF,
SO YOU'LL HAVE TO TAKE
A TRAIN.
[ RUMBLING ]
Dolphin: OH, NO, THE ARK --
IT'S DISINTEGRATING!
MY BABY!
GOODBYE, ARK!
GOODBYE, ARK...
AND THANK YOU.
Guilmon: [ Sighs ] I FEEL
LIKE I'VE LOST A FRIEND.
Takato: ME TOO, BOY.
OH...
TIME TO GO, BUT NO TAKATO!
WHY DOES THIS KEEP HAPPENING?
Takato: HOLD ON,
COMING THROUGH!
I WAS WORRIED. IT WAS LIKE
THE ARK ALL OVER AGAIN,
EXCEPT I CAN'T TELL
THE TRAIN TO STOP.
THERE'S NO NEED TO.
WHO'S THE EXTRA
LUNCH BOX FOR?
GUILMON...
JUST ASKING.
UH, HEY, JERI.
Porter: MONSTER ONBOARD!
AAH! STAY BACK!
I KNOW JUJITSU!
WAIT, IT'S OKAY!
I PAID FOR HIM.
I KNOW HE'S KIND OF BIG,
SO I GOT HIM AN ADULT TICKET.
WHO CARES ABOUT THE TICKET?
THAT THING'S A DIGIMON, RIGHT?
AND DIGIMON ARE DANGEROUS!
THAT MONSTER
SHOULD BE IN A CAGE.
YOU TAKE THAT BACK!
HE'S A GOOD DIGIMON,
AND DON'T CALL HIM A MONSTER.
HE'S VERY SENSITIVE.
YEAH.
HA! WHAT DO YOU THINK I AM,
DUMB OR SOMETHING?
NO.
HMM, THAT THING IS
A NATURAL BORN MENACE.
GUILMON'S JUST A BABY.
HE COULDN'T HURT A FLY.
Guilmon: I'M NOT A BABY.
I'LL SHOW YOU.
GUILMON, DIGIVOLVE!
AAH!
GUILMON, CUT IT OUT.
THIS ISN'T HELPING.
BUT I'M NOT A BABY!
LET ME SHOW HIM!
I TOLD YOU,
HE'S A MENACE TO SOCIETY!
[ STOMACH GURGLING ]
HUNGRY. I JUST WANT
MY LUNCH BOX.
HMM...
[ STOMACH GURGLING ]
HA HA HA HA.
HEY, I NEVER HEARD OF A MONSTER
WANTING A LUNCH BOX.
YOUR FRIEND'S PRETTY FUNNY.
YEAH, THAT'S GUILMON.
HE'S A RIOT.
HE REMINDS ME
OF MY KID BROTHER...
UH, EXCEPT FOR THE CLAWS,
OF COURSE. HERE YOU GO.
GEE, THANKS, MISTER.
I'LL JUST PRETEND
I DIDN'T SEE HIM, OKAY?
YEAH, OKAY.
BYE NOW.
HUH, CRAZY KIDS.
Takato: OH...
THAT WAS CLOSE.
GUILMON, WHY'D YOU TRY
TO DIGIVOLVE?
I DON'T KNOW. I CAN'T THINK
WHEN I'M HUNGRY.
I'M STILL HUNGRY...
BUT TOO SLEEPY TO EAT...
HUH? UH...
UM, JERI?
YOU HAVEN'T EATEN
ANYTHING.
AREN'T YOU HUNGRY?
WELL, GUESS NOT.
YOU KNOW, JERI, I'VE ALWAYS
WANTED TO TELL YOU,
YOU'RE THE NICEST GIRL
I'VE EVER MET.
I THINK...
I MEAN, YOU ALWAYS TALKED
TO ME AND STUFF
WHEN NO ONE ELSE WOULD,
AND IT MAY SOUND SILLY,
BUT SOMETIMES, I IMAGINED THAT
YOU MIGHT KIND OF LIKE ME
THE WAY THAT I LIKE YOU.
WELL, I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE
I THINK ABOUT YOU ALL THE TIME,
'CAUSE I DO!
UH, THIS IS HARD.
WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY,
MORE THAN JUST
A FRIEND, JERI,
IS THAT I LIKE YOU.
I REALLY DO.
I HATE SEEING YOU
THIS WAY.
WHEN THIS WHOLE THING
STARTED,
I WAS SO HAPPY,
'CAUSE YOU WERE A TAMER
AND GOT TO COME
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD
WITH US.
THEN LEOMON DIED...
AND YOU BECAME SO SAD.
I THOUGHT IF I BROUGHT YOU
BACK HOME TO THE REAL WORLD,
MAYBE YOU'D BE YOURSELF
AGAIN.
BUT NOW YOU JUST SIT HERE
NOT SAYING OR DOING ANYTHING.
I KEEP THINKING, HOW MUCH
OF THIS IS MY FAULT?
THAT IF I NEVER BROUGHT YOU
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD,
YOU'D STILL BE HAPPY.
BUT YOU'RE NOT.
I'M SO SORRY, JERI.
I'M SORRY YOU HAD
TO GO THROUGH ALL THAT,
THAT I COULDN'T HELP
SAVE LEOMON.
I JUST WISH YOU WOULD TALK
TO ME, JERI!
[ SOBBING ]
[ SIGHS ]
PROTEIN --
26.4 GRAMS...
SATURATED FAT --
15.7 GRAMS...
CARBOHYDRATES --
102.2 GRAMS.
SODIUM --
4.6 GRAMS...
JERI?
[ WHISTLE BLOWING ]
WAKE UP, GUILMON.
WE'RE HERE.
WHERE'S HERE?
WATCH YOUR STEP, JERI.
THAT'S IT.
LOOK, THERE'S YOUR DAD.
[ GRUNTS ]
HELLO, MR. KATOU.
THANK YOU
FOR BRINGING HER BACK HOME.
UM, YOU'RE WELCOME.
COME ON, YOUNG LADY.
BYE, JERI.
GOODBYE.
COME ON, BUDDY,
LET'S GO.
Man on TV: THIS JUST IN...
THERE ARE REPORTS
OF STRANGE SIGHTINGS
AROUND THE EVACUATED
SHINJUKU AREA.
IN RECENT WEEKS,
SHINJUKU HAS SUSTAINED...
JERI!
HUH?
I'VE BEEN SO WORRIED
ABOUT YOU,
BUT YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
Man on TV: WE HAVE JUST
RECEIVED FOOTAGE
OF THE STRANGE APPARITIONS
IN THE SHINJUKU AREA.
GREAT QUANTITIES
OF A RED FORMLESS MATTER
APPEAR TO BE ENGULFING
THE CITY.
EYEWITNESSES SAY THE SUBSTANCE
IS INCREASING
AT AN ALARMING RATE.
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
WHAT'S GOING ON, TAKATO?
THE CHAOS --
IT FOLLOWED US HOME!
WHOA, THAT'S A SOUVENIR
YOU DON'T WANT!
WHAT ARE THE TAMERS GOING
TO DO NOW?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."