WHILE THE GANG TRIED TO FIGURE
OUT WHAT THE DAVA'S PLANS WERE,
IMPMON DECIDED TO HAVE HIS OWN
RAMPAGE THROUGH THE CITY,
BUT RENAMON PULLED HIM AWAY
BEFORE HE COULD SCARE ANY MORE
PEOPLE. IMPMON BROKE DOWN
AND SAID HE WANTED TO BE ABLE
TO DIGIVOLVE, TOO,
AND THAT HE MAY HAVE
HAD A PARTNER ONCE.
WHEN INDRAMON APPEARED,
IMPMON TRIED TO PROVE
HOW STRONG HE WAS
BY FIGHTING HIM ALONE,
BUT THE LITTLE DUDE GOT
THE STUFFING KNOCKED OUT OF HIM.
THE GANG TRIED TO HELP,
BUT INDRAMON WAS TOO STRONG.
IN ONE LAST BURST OF ENERGY,
IMPMON CHARGED THE DAVA.
MAN, I SURE HOPE
HE KNOWS WHAT HE'S DOING.
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
♪ WORLD
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMODIFY
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
UHH! I'M GOING TO KICK
YOUR GIANT HEINIE
AND USE YOUR DATA
TO DIGIVOLVE!
AAH!
IMPMON, STOP.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO BE
BADA-BOOMED,
YOU BIG BLUE BONEHEAD!
DON'T YOU FEEL ANYTHING?
OH, BOY.
GUESS NOT!
OY!
UHH!
WHY WON'T YOU FIGHT ME?
VERY WELL, TRAITOR.
GRRAAH!
OH, THIS IS GOING
TO HURT! OW!
WOW. HE HIT THAT ONE
OUT OF THE PARK.
WE'VE GOT TO HELP HIM.
OR AT LEAST
PICK UP THE PIECES.
UH...WELL, WE BETTER
DO SOMETHING.
I AM A SERVANT OF THE SOVEREIGN,
WILLING TO UPLOAD YOUR DATA.
YOU SHOULD BE GRATEFUL.
[Thinking]
WHAT IS THIS?
OH!
SHOW ME THE MAGIC.
I FEEL STRANGE.
WHAT NOW?
SIR, POWER'S AT 40%.
50...60...
HMM.
HUH?
[GROWLS]
TIME TO GO.
HE DISAPPEARED.
THE WILD ONE
HAS SELF-DESTRUCTED.
ARE YOU SURE?
IS IT REALLY GONE?
I TOLD YOU.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED.
MM-HMM. ACKNOWLEDGED.
I UNDERESTIMATED.
IT WORKED AFTER ALL,
AND BEFORE IT EVEN REACHED
FULL POWER.
ONCE I GET CLEARANCE
FROM THOSE FOOLS,
THE END OF DIGIMON WILL BEGIN.
[SNORING]
TAKATOMON, DIGIVOLVE...
WELL, DON'T YOU GUYS
LOOK COZY.
WHERE IS IMPMON?
I DON'T KNOW.
WE COULDN'T FIND HIM
ANYWHERE.
YOU GUYS,
IT'S GETTING LATE.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
TRY AGAIN TOMORROW.
MORNING.
AREN'T YOU LATE?
NAW, THEY MOVED MY OFFICE.
IT'S A LITTLE CLOSER NOW.
I HAVE MORE TIME.
WOW, MORE TIME. HOPE YOU
USE IT WELL. BYE, DAD.
HE'S DEFINITELY MY KID --
ALWAYS THINKING.
GUILMON BREAD?
EXACTLY. IT'D BE GREAT.
WELL, UH, I DON'T KNOW.
YOU JUST BAKE IT
IN THE SHAPE OF GUILMON.
YEAH, IT GOES LIKE THIS.
OW. WHERE ARE THOSE GUYS?
EASY WAY
TO MAKE BIG DOUGH.
YEAH, AND I'D EAT IT
EVERY SINGLE DAY
FOR BREAKFAST, LUNCH,
AND DINNER.
UH, TELL ME AGAIN.
WHAT IS THIS GUILMON?
AAH!
WHAT'S WRONG?
UHH!
HI, DAD. BYE, DAD.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WE'RE TALKING OVER HERE.
UH, BYE.
SO, PSYCHO BOY, WHAT WAS THAT
ALL ABOUT BACK THERE?
DUH. I HAVEN'T TOLD MY DAD
ABOUT GUILMON YET.
GREAT. THANKS
FOR THE WARNING, CHUMLEY.
YEAH, WE HAD NO IDEA.
HEY, I WANTED
TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
TA-DA!
UM, BLUE?
RIGHT -- MY BLUE CARD.
MADE IT MYSELF.
YEAH, WE THOUGHT
THAT GUILMON AND THE OTHERS
COULD USE SOME HELP,
YOU KNOW?
THE BAD GUYS
KEEP GETTING STRONGER,
SO I THOUGHT I'D SHOW THEM
WHAT A REAL TAMER CAN DO.
HEY, WHAT'S THAT
SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
COME ON, TAKATO.
LET'S JUST TRY THE CARD
IN YOUR D-POWER, OKAY?
MM...MM...
I DESIGNED IT
JUST LIKE YOU SAID.
YEAH,
BUT IT'S NOT QUITE RIGHT.
BUT I STAYED IN THE LINES
AND EVERYTHING.
AAH!
NO WAY!
HEY!
THAT IS
ONE WEIRD LITTLE DUDE.
I'M VERY SORRY
TO KEEP YOU WAITING, MR. WONG.
HE SHOULD BE BACK
ANY TIME NOW.
THIS MUST BE
A TERRIBLE INCONVENIENCE.
CAN I GET YOU
SOME MORE TEA?
NO, THANKS.
VERY WELL.
[CONSTRUCTION SOUNDS]
I DON'T GET IT.
WHERE COULD HE HAVE GONE?
NOT TOO FAR, I IMAGINE.
LOOKED LIKE HE WAS HURT
PRETTY BAD.
IT'S HIS OWN FAULT.
IT WOULDN'T HAVE BEEN SO BAD
IF HE HAD A PARTNER.
RIKA,
YOU DO HAVE A HEART.
UH, I...
HA HA.
MM...HMM!
EXCELLENT.
WE'LL BEGIN
IMMEDIATELY, SIR.
THOSE IMBECILES DON'T UNDERSTAND
ANYTHING BUT RESULTS.
FORTUNATELY,
WE WERE ABLE TO PROVIDE THAT
AND GET THEIR APPROVAL.
ANY NEWS ON FINDING SHIBUMI?
NOT YET, SIR, BUT I'VE GOT
MY BEST MEN WORKING ON IT
AS WE SPEAK.
GOOD.
OH, YOU CAME BACK.
OF COURSE, BOY.
DID YOU THINK I WOULDN'T?
NO. WELL,
I WAS A LITTLE WORRIED.
I'D NEVER LEAVE YOU.
OH, BARF.
I WAS WORRIED, TOO.
THERE'S TOO MUCH LOVE
IN THIS ROOM.
WELL, AT LEAST
THE FOOD'S GOOD HERE.
[SIGHS]
I USED TO SPEND A LOT OF TIME
IN LECTURE HALLS LIKE THIS.
[SIGHS]
LOOKS LIKE THIS WAS
JUST A BIG WASTE OF TIME.
[GATE OPENS]
THERE YOU ARE.
HI.
HEY, HENRY!
NICE TO SEE YOU, TOO,
TERRIERMON.
ANY LUCK?
UNH-UNH.
THERE!
[ALL GASP]
LOOKS BAD.
OH, GREAT --
A DIGITAL FIELD.
[ALARM SOUNDING]
GUESS THEY FORGOT ABOUT ME.
THIS PLACE IS DESERTED.
HURRY!
HUH? HMM.
IT'S A GIANT WILD ONE.
IT'S THE SAME PATTERN
AS THE ONE FROM YESTERDAY.
BIOEMERGENCE
COMMENCING NOW.
[Gasps] OH.
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
THERE'S NOTHING TO FEAR.
THIS PROJECT IS COMPLETELY
SANCTIONED BY THE GOVERNMENT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
WHAT IS ALL THIS?
WE'RE MONITORING
WHAT WE CALL "WILD ONES" --
THOSE SIMPLE
ARTIFICIAL LIFE FORMS
THAT YOU WORKED SO HARD
TO CREATE --
EVOLVED AND FESTERED AND
MULTIPLIED THROUGHOUT THE NET.
THESE MISTAKES OF SCIENCE
HAVE NOW FOUND THEIR WAY
INTO THE REAL WORLD.
AS THEY TRY TO BREACH
THE BARRIER AND BIOEMERGE,
A CLOUD OF FOG-LIKE PARTICLES
APPEAR --
A FIELD OF ENERGY RESULTING FROM
EARTH'S NATURAL ELECTRICAL WAVES
RESPONDING
TO THE DIGITAL INFORMATION
EMITTED BY THE BEASTS.
INSIDE, THE FOG MOLECULES
BEGIN TO CHANGE
AND REARRANGE THEMSELVES
INTO FALSE PROTEINS,
TAKING ON PHYSICAL FORM
IN OUR WORLD.
AAH!
[MURMURING]
ALL OF THIS EXISTS
ONLY TO CLEAN UP AFTER YOU.
OH, I DIDN'T KNOW.
WHAT HAVE WE DONE?
[SCREAMING]
IT'S INDRAMON.
[GROWLS]
RIKA!
HENRY.
TAKATO?
[Thinking] LET'S DO IT.
DIGIMODIFY!
DIGIVOLUTION ACTIVATE!
GUILMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
GROWLMON!
TERRIERMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
GARGOMON!
RENAMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
KYUBIMON!
ALL RIGHT!
AWESOME.
OH...
HURRY!
I AM.
[SIREN WAILING]
HMM.
HUH?
WHOA...AAH!
GARGO LASER!
KYUBIMON, YOU'RE UP.
DRAGON WHEEL!
PYRO BLASTER!
YOUR EFFORTS ARE FUTILE.
OH...
DIGIMODIFY!
POWER ACTIVATE!
GARGO LASER!
YOU FOOL. UHH!
UHH...
YOU SHOULD SHOW
SOME RESPECT.
[SHOOTS BLANKS]
GARGOMON!
HOLD ON!
[Thinking] THIS IS
DEFINITELY NOT GOOD.
YOU BETTER DO SOMETHING.
YEAH, AND HURRY UP.
DIGIMODIFY!
RECHARGE ACTIVATE!
BUNNY PUMMEL!
HMM!
DIGIMODIFY!
STRENGTH ACTIVATE!
PYRO BLASTER!
DIGIMODIFY!
HYPERSPEED ACTIVATE!
DRAGON WHEEL!
HMM!
HEY, TAL.
HUH? D-DOLPHIN?
YEP.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
YOU'VE CHANGED.
I BARELY RECOGNIZED YOU.
YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED
AT ALL, TAL.
WELL, EXCEPT
FOR THE GRAY HAIR.
I DON'T KNOW. I KIND OF LIKE IT.
IT MAKES YOU LOOK DISTINGUISHED.
CURLY.
BABEL.
MM-HMM.
DAISY.
OKAY, NOW THAT ALL THE
PLEASANTRIES ARE OUT OF THE WAY,
YOU MIND TELLING US
WHAT THIS IS ALL ABOUT?
I MEAN, A REUNION OF THE MONSTER
MAKERS IS COOL AND ALL, BUT --
YEAH, WHAT'S THE PLAN?
YOU HAVEN'T TOLD US ANYTHING.
WHERE'S SHIBUMI?
HE'S LIVING SOMEWHERE
OUT IN THE COUNTRY.
WE HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO LOCATE HIM YET.
I'LL ANSWER
ALL OF YOUR QUESTIONS NOW.
THANK YOU
FOR YOUR PATIENCE.
THE GAME --
HE WAS RIGHT.
SHIBUMI ALWAYS SAID THAT
IT WAS MORE THAN A GAME.
HE PREDICTED THAT DIGIMON WOULD
APPEAR IN THE REAL WORLD
AND THAT HUMANS
WOULD CHANGE THEM.
I THOUGHT HE WAS CRAZY. I MEAN,
HOW COULD WE EVER HAVE IMAGINED
THAT DIGIMON WOULD BECOME
A PHYSICAL THREAT TO HUMANITY?
AS POWERFUL
AS YOUR IMAGINATIONS ARE,
I DON'T THINK
YOU CREATED THIS SITUATION.
IT SEEMS THAT THERE WAS
ANOTHER FORCE AT WORK
THAT NONE OF US UNDERSTOOD
UNTIL NOW.
AND WHAT FORCE IS THAT?
APPARENTLY, THE DIGIMON HAVE
AN OMNIPOTENT MASTER.
IT GAVE THEM THEIR LIFE
AND THEIR POWER.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
YOU'RE PERSISTENT --
AN ADMIRABLE QUALITY.
WELL, WE'RE JUST GETTING
STARTED. AM I RIGHT, GUYS?
HUH?
WE CAN CONTINUE FIGHTING
IF YOU WISH,
BUT YOU ARE NO MATCH FOR ME.
BEHOLD THE POWER
OF THE HORN OF DESOLATION!
KEEP FIGHTING.
DON'T GIVE UP.
YOU GUYS ARE TAMERS, RIGHT?
I KNOW I COULD HELP
IF I COULD BE A TAMER.
OH...
AN OMNIPOTENT MASTER?
YES, THEY CALL IT
"SOVEREIGN."
BUT THE DIGIMON WE CREATED WERE
SIMPLY COMPUTER APPLICATIONS.
INTELLIGENT, YES,
BUT ANARTIFICIALINTELLIGENCE.
WHAT KIND OF POWER
DOES THIS SOVEREIGN POSSESS
THAT COULD TURN THEM INTO
LIVING, BREATHING CREATURES?
THAT, MR. WONG,
IS A QUESTION
ONLY YOU AND YOUR COLLEAGUES
CAN ANSWER.
THE TIME OF RECKONING
IS NIGH.
OH! GROWLMON!
NOW'S OUR CHANCE.
WE CAN'T.
IT'S NOT WORKING.
MAYBE RIKA'S RIGHT.
MAYBE THE MILITARY
SHOULD HANDLE THIS ONE.
[GIGGLES]
[Thinking] INSECTS!
NO!
PYRO BLASTER!
YOU ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE
FOR THIS.
THERE'S NO WAY YOU COULD HAVE
KNOWN THIS WOULD HAPPEN.
THEN WHY HAVE YOU
BROUGHT US HERE?
I BELIEVE THE ONLY WAY
TO SAVE OUR WORLD IS
BY COMPLETELY DESTROYING
THE DIGIMON,
BUT THEY'RE STRONG
AND OUT OF CONTROL.
IF WE CAN EARN THEIR TRUST,
THEY WILL UNDOUBTEDLY
LOWER THEIR DEFENSES.
HUH?
THAT, MY FRIENDS,
IS WHY YOU'RE HERE.
WHO BETTER
TO WIN THEIR CONFIDENCE
THAN THEIR ORIGINAL CREATORS?
THOSE KIDS ARE
IN THE LINE OF FIRE.
OH -- KAZU AND KENTA!
THIS BUNNY AIN'T BACKING DOWN
FOR NOBODY.
I BELIEVE MY PURPOSE
IN THIS WORLD IS
TO DESTROY EVIL ABERRATIONS
LIKE YOU.
I'LL NEVER LET YOU
OR YOUR SOVEREIGN
OR ANYONE ELSE MESS UP
MY FRIENDSHIP WITH TAKATO.
YOU'RE WRONG, WEAK ONES.
AAH!
UHH!
ARE YOU OKAY?
YOU CAN'T KEEP THIS UP.
I'M FINE.
UH...
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHERE ARE THEY?
WHAT IF THEY'RE GONE?
AND NOW THE FINAL LESSON.
AW, NUTS.
HEY, TRY THIS CARD.
I'VE GOT A COUPLE, TOO.
AW, THANKS.
HEY, GUYS, LOOK.
HMM.
DIGIMODIFY!
POWER ACTIVATE!
GARGO LASER!
DIGIMODIFY!
HYPERSPEED ACTIVATE!
DRAGON WHEEL!
DIGIMODIFY!
ENERGY ACTIVATE!
I'M COMPLETELY OUT OF CARDS.
DO YOU GUYS HAVE ANY?
[GROWLS]
OH, THIS ONE'S USELESS.
IF I ONLY HAD
A BLUE CARD.
DUH!
TAKATO, I'M SUCH A DORK.
WHAT?
WHY DIDN'T I THINK
OF THIS BEFORE?
USE MY BLUE CARD
ON GROWLMON.
UH...
KAZU, DUDE, YOU DREW THAT.
IT'S NOT REAL.
HEY, TAKATO CREATED GUILMON
WITH A DRAWING,
AND HE'S A CRUMMY ARTIST.
GEE, THANKS A LOT.
COME ON, TAKATO.
ALL RIGHT NOW.
CONCENTRATE. CONCENTRATE.
ARE YOU CONCENTRATING?
HEY, CHUMLEY, I'M NOT HOLDING
YOUR HANDS 'CAUSE I LIKE YOU.
PAY ATTENTION.
[Thinking]
YOU CAN DO IT, TAKATO.
I CAN DO THIS.
SO CAN I.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
I AM.
YOU ARE?
YEP, LET'S DO IT.
DIGIMODIFY!
MATRIX DIGIVOLUTION ACTIVATE!
GROWLMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
WARGROWLMON.
[YELLING]
YOU DARE
TO CHALLENGE ME?
RADIATION BLADE ATTACK!
SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
NOW, LOOK,
YOU BIG BLUE BULLY!
HERE'S A MESSAGE
FOR YOUR SOVEREIGN.
AAH!
SAY UNCLE.
NEVER.
ATOMIC BLASTER!
[SCREAMING]
SO, DOES THIS MAKE ME
A TAMER OR WHAT?
GIMME A BREAK!
ALL RIGHT, THIS DAVA'S DONE,
BUT WHAT'S YAMAKI UP TO
WITH HENRY'S DAD?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."