SO IT TURNS OUT REIKA'S MOM
IS THIS SUPERMODEL
WHO ISN'T AROUND THAT MUCH.
THAT'S PROBABLY WHY
REIKA BECAME THE DIGIMON QUEEN.
SHE GOT RENIMON
AFTER WINNING A BIG TOURNAMENT
AND KNEW THAT ONE DAY
RENIMON WOULD DIGIVOLVE,
BUT NOT SOON ENOUGH FOR REIKA.
THEN IMPMON, THIS ANNOYING
LITTLE DUDE WHO HATES TAMERS,
TRIED TO CONVINCE RENIMON
TO DUMP REIKA.
WHEN DOKUGUMON TRIED
TO EAT REIKA FOR DINNER,
RENIMON FINALLY DIGIVOLVED
INTO KYUBIMON TO SAVE HER.
WOW, I GUESS THERE'S MORE
TO BEING A DIGIMON TAMER
THAN JUST TAMING, HUH?
DI-DI-DI
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON
DI-DI-DI
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS
TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
WORLD
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS
DIGIMODIFIED
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON
DID YOU CATCH
THAT ENERGY FLUCTUATION?
I'M ALREADY SEARCHING
FOR THE SOURCE.
THIS AREA SURE HAD
A LOT OF ACTIVITY LATELY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK IS
GOING ON?
I THINK SOMETHING BIG
IS GOING DOWN.
LIKE HOW BIG?
IF THESE READINGS ARE CORRECT,
AND I THINK THEY ARE,
WE'RE GOING TO GET A LEVEL
OF BIOEMERGENCE
UNLIKE ANYTHING
WE'VE EVER SEEN BEFORE.
WHY WOULD SHE RISK HERSELF
TO SAVE ME?
CAN DATA
REALLY HAVE FEELINGS?
I NEVER THOUGHT
THIS WOULD BE SO COMPLICATED.
NO NEED TO MAKE BREAKFAST.
WE OWN A BAKERY.
THAT'S ALL WE MAKE.
MORNING, GUILMON.
MORNING. GUESS WHAT?
LAST NIGHT
WHILE I WAS SLEEPING,
IT FELT LIKE I DISAPPEARED
AND WENT SOMEPLACE ELSE.
YOU DIDN'T
BREAK OUT AGAIN, DID YOU?
OH, I GET IT.
THAT WAS A DREAM.
A DREAM?
LIKE WHEN I THINK OF SNACKS?
NO, IT'S LIKE GOING
INTO YOUR OWN WORLD
INSIDE YOUR HEAD.
DO YOU DREAM?
EVERYONE DOES, BUT --
IS YOUR DREAM WORLD
AS BORING AS MINE --
ALL WHITE AND BRIGHT
AND EMPTY?
MINE'S FULL OF STUFF.
THAT'S WHERE I FIRST
THOUGHT OF YOU, GUILMON.
I MUST HAVE
THE MOST BORING ONE EVER.
CAN I PAINT
MY DREAM WORLD BLUE?
IT'S WEIRD, THOUGH.
I'VE NEVER HEARD OF ANYONE
TALK ABOUT A DIGIMON DREAMING.
[ GASPS ]
WHY IS YOUR FACE
ALL FUNNY?
YOUR LEGS!
HEY!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
DID I DO SOMETHING WRONG?
NO, BUT SOMETHING REALLY WEIRD
IS GOING ON HERE.
WAIT.
START AT THE BEGINNING.
OKAY, WE WERE JUST WALKING,
AND THEN --
I DON'T KNOW. IT'S LIKE
HALF OF HIM WAS THERE,
AND THE OTHER HALF WAS STARTING
TO BE RUBBED OUT BY AN ERASER.
WELL, DIGIMON
AREN'T OF THIS WORLD.
MAYBE SOME OF THEM
CAN'T LAST LONG HERE,
AND THEY GET PULLED BACK
INTO THEIR WORLD
OR SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
OR MAYBE OUR WORLD
ELIMINATES THEM
LIKE THE BODY
GETS RID OF A VIRUS.
BUT GUILMON JUST GOT HERE.
I DON'T WANT HIM
TO DISAPPEAR.
HE JUST CAN'T GO BACK
TO THE OTHER SIDE.
MOMENTIE.
THE WORLD I'M FROM,
THE WORLD YOU'RE FROM --
THEY'RE REALLY BOTH THE SAME
IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
YEAH, WELL,
THANKS, PROFESSOR,
BUT I WANT HIM HERE.
THAT MAY NOT BE POSSIBLE,
TAKATO.
WHAT? WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO SAY, HENRY?
DO YOU KNOW SOMETHING?
TELL ME.
I JUST KNOW THAT NOTHING
CAN LAST FOREVER, TAKATO --
NOTHING. I'M SORRY.
WELL, THIS CAN, AND IT WILL.
[ CELLULAR PHONE RINGS ]
THIS HAD
BETTER BE IMPORTANT.
SIR, WE'RE GETTING
SOME STRANGE READINGS,
AND ONE OF THE RESEARCHERS
NEEDS YOU
TO EXPLAIN SOMETHING TO HIM.
I DON'T KNOW
WHY I BOTHER EXPLAINING.
NONE OF THESE IMBECILES
UNDERSTAND WHAT I SAY, ANYWAY.
SO WHAT SHOULD I TELL HIM?
THAT HE'S AN OFFICIOUS
LITTLE TOADY.
[ Sighs ]
I'LL BE THERE SHORTLY.
WHAT WAS THAT?
HMM. COULD HAVE SWORN
I FELT SOMETHING.
WHAT'LL I DO IF HENRY'S RIGHT
AND GUILMON
COMPLETELY DISAPPEARS?
HE CAN'T LEAVE ME.
MAYBE IF HE DIGIVOLVED,
HE'D HAVE ENOUGH STRENGTH
TO FIGHT WHATEVER'S
TRYING TO ERASE HIM.
DIGIVOLVE?
HUH?
BAD!
GREAT.
NOW JERI THINKS I'M CRAZY,
AND SHE'S CRAZIER
THAN CALUMON.
WELL, KIDS, THE CITY WANTS ME
TO TALK TO YOU
ABOUT THE TUNNEL
BENEATH THE PARK
THAT'S FOR USE
WHEN THE RAIN CAUSES FLOODING,
BUT IT SEEMS LIKE
A USELESS LESSON TO ME.
I MEAN, EVERYBODY ALREADY KNOWS
ABOUT THE TUNNEL, RIGHT?
I DON'T.
SO THIS TUNNEL --
AW, POOR GUILMON MUST BE
BORED OUT OF HIS MIND.
JUST ONE GAME OF TAG,
PLEASE?
CALUMON? GREAT.
HEY, TAKATO'S HOME.
SO, YOU GUYS
STAYING OUT OF TROUBLE?
NOPE.
CALUMON, WHERE DO YOU HANG OUT
WHEN YOU'RE NOT HERE?
YOU MUST HAVE A HOME,
RIGHT?
I CAN GO ANYWHERE I WANT
IN THE WHOLE WIDE WORLD,
SO I DON'T NEED
TO HAVE A HOME, SILLY.
AREN'T YOU LONELY?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN LONELY?
LIKE WHEN YOU'RE BY YOURSELF,
MAKING PICTURES
OF ALL KINDS OF COOL MONSTERS
AND STUFF,
BUT THERE'S NO ONE AROUND
TO LOOK AT YOUR DRAWINGS
WITH YOU.
UH...NOPE.
NEVER FELT LIKE THAT.
SEEMS KIND OF SILLY.
[ Giggles ]
HEY, YOU KNOW?
IT IS SILLY.
[ SIGHS ]
I'M ONLY GOING TO GO
THROUGH THIS ONE MORE TIME,
SO DO TRY TO PAY ATTENTION.
THE NETWORK OF INTERLINKED
ELECTRONIC DEVICES
AROUND THE WORLD --
THE INTERNET, THE STOCK MARKETS,
AND EVEN
WIRELESS COMMUNICATIONS --
HAS ESSENTIALLY CREATED A WHOLE
NEW PLANE OF EXISTENCE --
A DIGITAL PLANE.
THIS SYSTEM -- HYPNOSE --
MONITORS THAT WORLD
AND RECORDS EVERY EXCHANGE
OF INFORMATION ACROSS IT,
LOOKING FOR ANYTHING
OUT OF THE ORDINARY.
SIMPLE ENOUGH FOR YOU?
DO YOU KEEP TRACK
OF PERSONAL DATA?
HOW ELSE COULD WE MONITOR
CRIMINAL ACTIVITY?
IF ANY OF THE GENERAL PUBLIC
FOUND OUT ABOUT THIS,
WE'D BE
TREATED LIKE CRIMINALS.
MAKE SURE
TO KEEP THIS VERY QUIET.
REALLY?
GEE, THAT NEVER OCCURRED TO ME.
LISTEN, THERE'S NO NEED
FOR ANY OF YOU TO WORRY.
WE'VE GOT EVERYTHING
WELL UNDER CONTROL.
NO, YOU'VE GOT NOTHING
UNDER CONTROL, YAMAKI.
YOU'VE SHOWN YOURSELF
TO BE POWERLESS
TO STOP THOSE ANOMALIES.
FIND A WAY TO PREVENT THEM
FROM BIOEMERGING,
AND FIND THE ONES
THAT HAVE ALREADY COME THROUGH.
THEN ELIMINATE THEM.
MAYBE CALUMON'S RIGHT
ABOUT NOT NEEDING A PARTNER.
UH...
GUILMON, DO YOU WANT
TO LEAVE ME?
NO.
DO YOU WANT ME TO LEAVE?
SOMETIMES, GUILMON,
YOU CAN BE VERY CONFUSING.
OW! HEY!
DON'T BE SO GRABBY.
TAKATOMON --
LET'S SEE, HE'S GOT THESE, UM...
HUGE EARS --
UH-HUH. THERE.
THIS MUST BE WHERE CALUMON
HAS BEEN HANGING OUT,
SO KEEP YOUR EYES PEELED.
HUH?
GUILMON, WHAT'S WRONG?
[ PANTING ]
WHY DO I ALWAYS END UP
CHASING HIM?
[ GRUNTS ]
HUH?
RENIMON!
WHO WERE YOU EXPECTING, BOYS?
YOUR MOMMIES?
VERY FUNNY.
I DON'T THINK
I HAVE A MOMMY, DO I?
WAIT, TAKATO'S MY MOMMY.
AW, JEEZ, GUILMON,
DON'T CALL ME THAT.
WHY NOT? YOU'D MAKE
A BETTER MOTHER THAN A TAMER,
THE WAY YOU BABY YOUR DIGIMON.
HEY!
NOW ARE WE GOING TO FIGHT
OR ARE WE GOING
TO FLAP OUR GUMS ALL DAY?
WHY DO YOU WANT TO POUND
ON GUILMON ALL THE TIME?
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
IT WOULD IF YOU WEREN'T
SUCH A COWARD.
REIKA.
WHY DO YOU KEEP
FOLLOWING ME AROUND?
YOU IN LOVE WITH ME,
LOVERBOY?
I'M NOT
FOLLOWING YOU AROUND, OKAY?
ARE YOU GUYS
GOING TO FIGHT?
WHO? UH --
MM-HMM.
NAH, SHE'S A GIRL,
AND SHE'D KICK MY BUTT.
YOU KNOW, FIGHTING
ISN'T ALWAYS THE ANSWER.
THE COWARD'S CREDO.
LOOK, MAYBE THE TWO OF US
GOT OFF ON THE WRONG FOOT.
I'M TAKATO,
AND YOU'RE REIKA, RIGHT?
YEAH, SO WHAT?
WHAT, ARE YOU
WRITING A BOOK ABOUT ME,
OR ARE YOU IN LOVE?
[ GROANS ]
I ADMIT I SAW YOU
IN A DREAM A WHILE BACK,
AND THAT'S WHAT'S BEEN
REALLY BUGGING ME,
BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT MEANS.
BUT DON'T GET
THE WRONG IDEA.
I'M NOT FOLLOWING YOU AROUND
'CAUSE OF THAT.
I JUST HAD SOME QUESTIONS
ABOUT DIGIMON, OKAY?
ALL RIGHT, KID, DON'T GET
YOUR UNDERWEAR ALL BUNCHED UP.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN "KID"?
WE'RE THE SAME AGE.
I'M CALLING YOU KID
BECAUSE YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT ANYTHING.
YOU SHOW UP TALKING ABOUT
SEEING ME IN A DREAM.
DO YOU KNOW
HOW WEIRD THAT IS?
I'M -- I'M SORRY.
I JUST THOUGHT --
WELL, THAT MAYBE
WE COULD WORK TOGETHER.
WE CAN'T.
REIKA! YOU HOME?
OH, HI. SORRY, I'M NOT USED
TO REIKA BRINGING BOYS HOME.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
TAKATO.
HE'S NOT GOING
TO BE HERE LONG.
WHY DON'T I MAKE SOME SNACKS
FOR THE TWO OF YOU?
IT'LL ONLY TAKE A SECOND TO POP
SOME COOKIES IN THE OVEN.
HOW WOULD YOU
LIKE THAT, TAKATO?
THANKS.
THAT'S OKAY, GRANDMA.
HE'S NOT STAYING. YOU'RE NOT.
WELL, BYE.
HOPE YOU COME AND SEE US AGAIN.
SURE.
YOU'RE NOT.
LET GO!
UM, SO LISTEN...
WHAT I WANTED TO ASK YOU
WAS WHETHER OR NOT
DIGIMON TURN BACK INTO DATA.
I MEAN, DO THEY EVER
JUST DISAPPEAR
AND GO BACK
TO THEIR OWN WORLD?
OF COURSE.
NOT LIKE WHEN YOU
DEFEATED VILEMON,
BUT JUST, LIKE,
FOR NO GOOD REASON?
DIGIMON ARE JUST DATA, ANYWAY,
SO...PROBABLY.
DOESN'T THAT MAKE YOU
SAD AT ALL?
HMM.
STOP PUSHING.
MOVE FASTER, THEN.
WELL, THANKS, REIKA.
IT'S NOT EVERY DAY YOU GET
TO MEET YOUR DREAM GIRL.
SORRY, I JUST
COULDN'T RESIST.
UGH!
BYE.
RENIMON, BYE-BYE.
HMMPH.
HEY.
YEAH?
YOU MENTION THAT DREAM AGAIN,
AND I'LL SEND YOU
TO DREAM LAND FOR GOOD.
MAN, SHE CAN'T TAKE A JOKE.
GOT ANOTHER WEIRD READING.
FOR ONCE
IT'S NOT A WILD ONE.
THIS IS
WHAT I WAS TALKING ABOUT.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
DATA LIKE THIS.
SEND A TRACER.
ALREADY ON IT.
WHAT?
THE TRACER WAS ABSORBED.
WHAT IS GOING ON?
THAT REIKA'S
A BARREL OF LAUGHS, HUH?
WHAT ABOUT RENIMON?
HER IDEA OF A JOKE IS
TO PUNCH ME IN THE FUNNY BONE.
MAN, I WAS HOPING REIKA WOULD
HAVE MORE ANSWERS FOR ME --
SOMETHING THAT WOULD MAKE
THIS PROBLEM GO AWAY.
MNH-MNH.
I'VE ALWAYS LOVED DIGIMON,
AND I ALWAYS THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE COOL TO HAVE
A REAL ONE OF MY VERY OWN,
AND THEN LIKE MAGIC
YOU APPEARED
AND EVERYTHING WAS GREAT,
BUT NOW I'M NOT EVEN SURE
IF YOU'RE GOING TO BE ABLE
TO STAY WITH ME OR NOT, GUILMON.
I GUESS I THOUGHT IF I COULD
LEARN MORE ABOUT DIGIMON,
I'D BE ABLE TO STOP
WHATEVER'S TRYING TO ERASE YOU.
I'M SCARED, GUILMON.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
CALUMON TOLD ME
THAT BEING SCARED IS POINTLESS.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE TRYING
TO ICE SKATE ON SAUSAGES.
I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT, GUILMON,
BUT I JUST WANT TO SPEND
AS MUCH TIME WITH YOU
AS POSSIBLE, YOU KNOW?
YEAH!
HEY, LET'S DO SOMETHING
REALLY FUN TOMORROW.
WE COULD PLAY TAG
UNTIL WE DROP,
OR EAT
UNTIL WE CAN'T MOVE.
IT'S HAPPENING AGAIN.
GUILMON!
I FEEL WEIRD.
I MUST BE
DREAMING AGAIN, RIGHT?
GUILMON --
EVERYTHING'S FADING.
NO!
I THINK I'M GOING AWAY.
NO, GUILMON!
PLEASE HOLD ON.
I JUST GOT USED
TO HAVING YOU AROUND.
I CAN'T IMAGINE
LIFE WITHOUT YOU ANYMORE.
YOU CAN'T GO!
WELL, I'LL DO MY BEST
TO STAY HERE.
GUILMON --
PLEASE...DON'T LEAVE ME.
GUILMON...
NO.
HE'S GONE.
GUILMON'S GONE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
IT'S LIKE HE WAS NEVER HERE,
AND THERE'S NOTHING I CAN DO.
[ BEEPING ]
WHAT'S THIS?
THAT'S GUILMON'S SIGNAL.
THE TUNNEL.
HELLO, HELLO, HELLO.
STOP SAYING HELLO
AND GET HENRY...
UH, PLEASE.
IT'S SOME ANGRY KID
FOR HENRY.
I'M NOT ANGRY.
I HOPE TAKATO'S ALL RIGHT.
HE'S NEVER BEEN OUT
THIS LATE BEFORE, HAS HE?
OH, WE WERE THE SAME WAY
WHEN WE WERE KIDS --
ALWAYS RUNNING AROUND, PLAYING,
LOSING TRACK OF TIME.
I VAGUELY REMEMBER.
THAT WAS ABOUT THE TIME
THE DINOSAURS DIED OFF, RIGHT?
OH, STOP.
WE'RE NOT THAT OLD.
I HOPE HE'S OKAY, THOUGH.
I'M SURE HE'S FINE.
I MIGHT BE HARSH ON HIM
FROM TIME TO TIME,
BUT I DO TRUST HIS JUDGMENT.
BUT SINCE HE'S NOT HERE,
LET'S EAT THE ICE CREAM
WE SAVED FOR DESSERT
AND TELL HIM IT MELTED.
UM...I ALREADY ATE IT.
"SO I SAID,
'GIRLFRIEND, AS IF.
DON'T GO THERE.'"
GRANNY CHAT? HMM.
YOU KNOW, I BET YOUR MOM
WOULD GET YOU A COMPUTER
IF YOU WANTED ONE.
COMPUTERS ARE BORING.
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
MAYBE THAT'S YOUR MOTHER NOW.
WOULD YOU GET THAT, HONEY?
UGH. GREAT.
MY LITTLE YUGOT PROGRAM
SHOULD DISINFECT THE AREA.
SHOULDN'T WE STUDY
THE PHENOMENON, SIR?
DON'T GET SOFT
SOFT ON ME, NOW, RILEY.
THIS LITTLE ANOMALY,
OR WHATEVER IT IS,
HAS CAUSED ME
MORE GRIEF THAN IT'S WORTH,
AND IT'S ABOUT TO BECOME
NOTHING MORE
THAN AN UNPLEASANT MEMORY.
BUT SIR, UNAPPROVED PROGRAMS
ARE STRICTLY FORBIDDEN.
FORBIDDEN?
THOSE FOOLS UPSTAIRS
CAN'T EVEN BEGIN
TO UNDERSTAND THIS TECHNOLOGY,
LET ALONE THE IDEA THAT THERE'S
A WHOLE DIGITAL WORLD OUT THERE.
WHO DO THEY THINK THEY ARE
TO FORBID ME ANYTHING?
YES, SIR.
THIS IS IT, YOU GUYS.
THIS IS
WHERE HE DISAPPEARED.
REIKA.
SHE'S DISAPPEARING, TOO!
DON'T MOVE.
TERRIERMON?
CHECK IT OUT.
IT'S HAPPENING TO TERRIERMON.
WHATEVER IT IS
THAT'S CAUSING THIS,
IT SEEMS
ONLY TO AFFECT THE DIGIMON.
RENIMON, YOU BETTER LEAVE
BEFORE YOU START
TO DISAPPEAR, TOO.
REIKA?
IT'S OKAY. YOU CAN GO.
I SUPPOSE YOU WANT ME
TO GO, TOO, HUH?
FINE.
DON'T ORDER
MY DIGIMON AROUND. GOT IT?
SHE'S MINE.
I'M JUST TRYING
TO KEEP THEM OUT OF DANGER.
WHY BOTHER?
DIGIMON ARE JUST DATA.
WHO CARES IF THEY DISAPPEAR?
BE QUIET.
I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU SAY.
GUILMON WAS MY FRIEND,
AND I'LL DO EVERYTHING I CAN
TO FIND HIM --
WITH OR WITHOUT YOU.
I'M GETTING A SIGNAL.
COME ON, LET'S GO
AND FIND GUILMON.
[ Mocking ]
LET'S GO AND FIND GUILMON.
[ BEEPING ]
WASTE OF TIME.
HE'LL BE HOME ANY MINUTE.
I'M SURE OF IT.
HE'S PROBABLY TURNING THE CORNER
FOR HOME RIGHT NOW.
YEAH...
BUT IT IS GETTING
KIND OF LATE, ISN'T IT?
DONE.
I'VE GOT TO STATE MY OBJECTION
ONE MORE TIME, SIR.
THIS PROGRAM COULD CAUSE
WIDESPREAD NETWORK DAMAGE.
AND I'VE GOT TO WARN YOU
ONE MORE TIME
THAT YOU'RE
WALKING ON THIN ICE, RILEY.
START THE PROGRAM
BEFORE THAT ICE BREAKS
AND YOU DROWN.
YES, SIR.
WHY DON'T THEY EVER MAKE TUNNELS
THAT AREN'T DARK AND SCARY?
[ DOOR OPENS ]
HEY, REIKA,
YOU DECIDED TO COME.
THAT'S AWESOME.
AHEM.
UH, YOU KNOW, WHATEVER.
A TAMER DOESN'T
WALK AWAY FROM DANGER.
YEAH, RIGHT.
ENOUGH TALKING.
LET'S GO FIND GUILMON.
YEAH.
UM...IT IS KIND OF SCARY
DOWN HERE, THOUGH, RIGHT, GUYS?
OH, BROTHER.
HOW LONG
IS THIS STUPID TUNNEL, ANYWAY?
MY TEACHER SAID IT GOES
ALL THE WAY TO THE NEXT TOWN.
THAT'S SO STUPID.
YEAH, SO YOU SAY.
IT'S TOO BAD THEY DON'T HAVE
ONE OF THOSE PEOPLE MOVERS.
YOU KNOW, LIKE AT THE AIRPORT?
THAT WOULD COME IN HANDY RIGHT
ABOUT NOW, DON'T YOU THINK?
IT'S NOT FUNNY, YOU KNOW.
I DON'T WANT TO WALK
ALL THE WAY TO THE NEXT TOWN
JUST TO FIND
YOUR LITTLE FRIEND.
WELL, IF IT MAKES YOU
FEEL ANY BETTER, REIKA,
THE TUNNEL MIGHT FLOOD
AND WE COULD ALL SWIM THERE.
[ BEEPING ]
IT'S JUST MY LUCK TO BE STUCK
WITH A COUPLE OF COMEDIANS.
WILL YOU GUYS CAN IT?
LOOK.
FORGET THE DIGIVICE.
TAKE A LOOK AT THAT.
WHAT IS IT?
I'VE PINPOINTED
THE ENERGY FIELD.
WELL DONE.
PREPARE TO DELETE THE AREA.
GUILMON MUST BE
INSIDE OF THAT THING.
I KNOW HE IS.
GUILMON!
DON'T BE STUPID. HOW COULD YOU
POSSIBLY KNOW THAT?
I DON'T KNOW HOW.
I JUST FEEL THAT HE'S IN THERE.
[ BEEPING ]
[ GASPS ]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
DIGIVICES CONNECT US
TO OUR DIGIMON.
MAYBE WE CAN USE THEM.
LOOK, SOMETHING'S HAPPENING.
IT OPENED.
GUILMON!
HOLD ON, I'M COMING.
HEY, WAIT.
STUPID.
AAH!
WHOA!
MAYBE THE DIGITAL WORLD
FROM THE TV SHOW IS REAL
AND WE'RE IN IT.
GUILMON --
I THINK I SEE HIM.
COOL. THIS IS
HOW I FLY IN MY DREAMS.
WAIT UP.
YOU AND YOUR DREAMS.
[ Grunting ]
THERE HE IS.
GUILMON, WAKE UP.
RIGHT NOW? FIVE MINUTES.
DON'T WORRY, BOY.
I'LL GET YOU
OUT OF THERE SOMEHOW.
[ RUMBLING ]
WHAT'S THAT?
SIR, SOME UNUSUAL DATA
HAS ENTERED THE ZONE
CREATED BY THE ENERGY FIELD.
I DON'T CARE.
JUST RUN THE PROGRAM.
DELETE EVERYTHING NOW.
WHAT'S THAT?
LOOK, IT'S BEING ERASED.
I CAN'T REACH HIM IN TIME.
HELP!
HEY!
HUH? OH.
HA! I THOUGHT I WAS GOING
TO LOSE YOU FOR SURE.
HE'S CREATED A ROAD FOR US.
YEAH, WELL, RENIMON COULD HAVE
DONE THE SAME THING.
YOU OKAY?
SKATING ON SAUSAGES.
HAVE YOUR REUNION LATER.
WE'VE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE WE'RE ERASED.
THE ZONE HAS BEEN
DELETED, SIR.
PROBLEM SOLVED.
I NEVER WOULD HAVE GOTTEN
GUILMON BACK WITHOUT YOUR HELP.
I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO THANK YOU GUYS.
THAT'S EASY.
JUST SAY THANK YOU.
MOMENTIE.
THE LITTLE ONE
DIDN'T EVEN DO ANYTHING.
WELL, NEITHER DID YOU.
LOOK AT YOU --
BLUBBERING OVER DATA.
TAKATO!
WE BOUGHT MORE ICE CREAM!
THAT COULD ONLY BE
MY PARENTS.
YOU WERE REALLY BRAVE,
YOU KNOW THAT?
YEAH? FIRST TIME FOR EVERYTHING.
WELL, SOMETHING TELLS ME
YOU BETTER GET USED TO IT.
YOU WERE BRAVE,
TOO, YOU KNOW.
THAT'S BECAUSE OF YOU.
GOOD NIGHT, GUILMON.
TOMORROW I'LL BRING YOU
SOME ICE CREAM.
YAY! ICE CREAM.
WOW, THAT WAS
A CLOSE ONE, HUH?
AND KNOWING THESE GUYS,
I BET THERE WILL BE
PLENTY MORE TO COME,
SO KEEP WATCHING
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."