SO TAKATO AND THE OTHERS WERE
UP TO THEIR EYEBALLS
IN SOVEREIGN STEW.
WHILE THEY WERE FIGHTING
ZHUQIAOMON,
AZULONGMON SHOWED UP!
HE TOLD THEM
ABOUT THE TRUE ENEMY --
THIS FORCE THAT
WAS COMING TO DESTROY THEM.
SHIBUMI FLEW IN AND EXPLAINED
THAT IT WAS THE D-REAPER --
A PROGRAM WRITTEN TO GET RD
OF ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE.
NOW IT'S AFTER THE DIGIMON!
MEANWHILE, RYO MET UP
WITH EBONWUMON.
HE TOLD THEM THAT
THE LAST SOVEREIGN, BAIHUMON,
WAS BELOW FIGHTING SOMETHIG
REALLY NASTY.
SOUNDS TO ME LIKE THE D-REAPR
MAY HAVE SHOWN UP
SOONER THAN THEY THOUGHT!
DI, DI, DI
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS
TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE WORLD
DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS.
DIGIMODIFY.
DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON!
Rika: DO WE HAVE A PLAN
OR ARE WE JUST GOING TO
STAND AROUND ALL DAY?
Kazu: WHY DON'TYOUCOME UP
WITH SOMETHING?
I SAY WE CLIMB ON ZHUQIAOMON
AND FLY AROUND
AND SCOPE THINGS OUT.
OH, THAT'S SMART.
LET'S ASK THE SOVEREIGN
WHO WANTED TO TURN US
INTO DIGICASSEROLE IF HE'LL GIVE
US A PIGGYBACK RIDE
CHICKEN.
I'M NOT CHICKEN.
[ ROARING ]
NEVER MIND.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ ROARING ]
ZHUQIAOMON, WHAT'S WRONG?
THE TRUE ENEMY IS NEARBY.
I SEE THE CHAOS IT BRINGS
IN MY MIND'S EYE.
UH. HMM.
WELL, I GUESS THE TRUE ENEMY
IS CLOSER THAN WE THOUGHT.
OH, GREAT.
WE STILL HAVEN'T FOUND CALUMON.
UM, MR. AZULONGMON,
WILL YOU HELP US?
PLE-E-ASE?
OF COURSE.
THE CATALYST MUST BE RETRIEVED
AT ALL COSTS.
PREPARE YOURSELVES, CHILDREN.
IT IS TIME.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
Kenta:
WHERE'D EVERYTHING GO?
Kazu: WHY CAN'T THE DIGIMON
SOVEREIGN TELL US
WHAT THEY'RE GONNA DO?
I THINK HE ATE US.
WE'RE DOOMED!
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
MMM. OHH!
WE'RE FLYING!
OH, I THINK I'M GONNA BE
SICK AGAIN -- TOTALLY.
IT'S FREAKY.
Guilmon: I LIKE IT.
IT FEELS LIKE
WE'RE IN THE MIDDLE
OF A BIG POOF
OF COTTON CANDY.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU THINK,
TAKATO?
JUST A MINUTE, GUILMON.
HEY, JERI,
ARE YOU DOING OKAY?
JERI, YOU WERE ALWAYS
SO CHEERFUL AND KIND AND NICE.
SO IT'S JUST...WEIRD
TO SEE YOU LIKE THIS.
YOU'RE WRONG.
I'M NOT NICE.
HUH?
WHEN MY REAL MOTHER DIED,
I SWORE I WOULDN'T LET ANYONE
TAKE HER PLACE.
SO WHEN MY NEW
STEPMOTHER CAME,
SHE WANTED TO BE MY FRIEND,
BUT I NEVER GAVE HER A CHANCE.
YOU SEE, I'M NOT NICE.
I'M...AWFUL.
THAT'S NOT TRUE!
YOU'RE THE NICEST PERSON
I KNOW.
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT'S WRONG WITH JERI?
HER HEART IS FULL
OF SADNESS.
I KNOW. IT'S BECAUSE LEOMON'S
GONE, ISN'T IT?
BECAUSE SHE WAS POWERLESS
TO STOP IT.
POOR JERI.
MY MOTHER, THEN LEOMON.
LEOMON SAID EVERYONE
HAS THEIR OWN DESTINY.
MAYBE MINE IS TO BE ALONE.
Ryo:
I DON'T SEE ANYTHING.
YOU SURE
ABOUT THIS, CYBERDRAMON?
MY ULTIMATE ENEMY WAS HERE.
I CAN STILL SMELL HIM.
WHAT ABOUT BAIHUMON?
WHERE'D HE GO?
PROBABLY STILL FIGHTING
THE ENEMY.
YEP. HE'S A STUBBORN ONE,
THAT ONE.
[ GRUNTING ]
THERE HE IS.
OH!
[ GROWLING, ROARING ]
BAIHUMON, YOU LOOK TERRIBLE.
[ GROWLS ]
"BAIHUMON -- OMEGA,
GUARDIAN OF THE WEST."
HE'S ONE OF THE FOUR
DIGIMON SOVEREIGN.
OH, WOW!
[ ROARING ]
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HIM?
[ GROANS ]
AH. UGH.
OH.
Ebonwumon: HE'S EXHAUSTED.
YOUTRY FIGHTING THE TRUE ENEMY
AND SEE HOW YOU FEEL.
YOU KNOW, CYBERDRAMON,
WHATEVER DID THIS TO BAIHUMON
ISN'T JUST AN OPPONENT.
IT'S A NATURAL DISASTER.
Cyberdramon:
I MUST DEFEAT HIM.
HOLD ON THERE,
MR. FEISTY McANGRY.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT TALKING ABOUT
FIGHTING BAIHUMON,
'CAUSE I WON'T LET YOU.
I'M NO SPRING SOVEREIGN.
BUT I CAN STILL GIVE IT
THE OL' ONE, TWO.
YEP, HE'S ONE.
I'M TWO.
HE WANTS TO DEFEAT
WHAT BAIHUMON WAS FIGHTING.
AND WE BETTER FIND IT
SOON.
I JUST HOPE YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
GETTING US INTO, CYBERDRAMON.
KIDS TODAY.
CAN'T TELL IF THEY'RE BEING
BRAVE OR PLAIN CRAZY.
DEFINITELY CRAZY.
Azulongmon: I HOPE WE ARE
IN TIME TO SAVE THE CATALYST.
Terriermon:
REALLY? NO KIDDING?
SO WHAT DO YOU SAY
YOU STEP ON IT, HUH?
Henry: TERRIERMON.
I KNOW.
WE HAVE ARRIVED.
I DON'T SEE ANY SIGN
OF CALUMON.
OR THE BOTTOM, EITHER.
HE MUST BE WAY DOWN THERE.
Kazu: AW, MAN!
WHY COULDN'T HE HAVE PUT CALUMON
IN A NICE MEADOW OR SOMETHING?
WAIT A MINUTE.
I SEE SOMETHING.
WHAT IS THAT? A LAVA LAMP?
Azulongmon: IT IS CHAOS.
YEAH, I'LL SAY.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING DESTROY
SO EFFORTLESSLY.
OH, THAT'S NASTY.
HOW MUCH OF THAT STUFF IS THERE?
I SURE HOPE CALUMON
IS OKAY.
Azulongmon: I NEVER THOUGHT
THE TRUE ENEMY
WOULD COME THIS FAR
SO QUICKLY.
THE CHAOS!
I MUST PUT AN END TO THIS...
NOW!
ZHUQIAOMON!
STRANGE HOW THE CATALYST
IS BOTH THE SOURCE OF OUR POWER
AND THE KEY
TO OUR DESTRUCTION.
Henry: BUT WHY?
THE TRUE ENEMY IS DRAWN
TO THE POWER
THE CATALYST GIVES US.
IT SEEKS IT OUT AND DEVOURS
EVERYTHING IN ITS PATH.
SO YOU'RE SAYING
WHEREVER CALUMON IS...
YOU CAN BE SURE
THE ENEMY WILL APPEAR,
LEAVING A WAKE OF DEVASTATION.
POOR CALUMON.
IT SEEMS LIKE SOMEONE'S
ALWAYS CHASING HIM.
I HAVE NIGHTMARES
LIKE THAT.
ME TOO.
[ GROWLS ]
SOMEONE'S COMING!
HEY, IT'S CYBERDRAMON!
AND RYO'S WITH HIM!
DUDE, HE ISSOCOOL!
YEAH! DID HE GET TALLER?
[ GRUNTS ]
HEY, IT'S THE WHOLE GANG.
I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D BE HERE.
ARE WE GLAD TO SEE YOU!
SAME HERE.
HEY, RIKA,
YOU'RE LOOKING GOOD.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA LEAVE AGAIN
ON MY ACCOUNT, ARE YOU?
PLEASE. WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE, ANYWAY?
RIKA, YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED
A BIT.
HOW OBSERVANT OF YOU,
RYO.
YOU HAVEN'T CHANGED, EITHER.
YOU'RE STILL AS ANNOYING
AS EVER.
Henry: RIKA!
[ GRUNTING ]
ZHUQIAOMON!
YOUR WING!
I COULDN'T EVEN GET CLOSE.
THE CHAOS OVERWHELMED ME!
I WARNED YOU NOT TO
UNDERESTIMATE THE TRUE ENEMY.
IT DOESN'T EAT, SLEEP,
OR FEEL PAIN.
IT EXISTS ONLY TO DESTROY.
SO HOW CAN WE DEFEAT
THIS CHAOS?
YEAH. I MEAN, HOW ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO KICK ITS BUTT
IF IT DOESN'T EVEN HAVE ONE?
GOOD POINT.
MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T EVEN TRY.
Takato:
HENRY, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WE SHOULD JUST FOCUS
ON GETTING CALUMON.
Kazu: IF THE CHAOS
HASN'T HAD HIM FOR LUNCH.
DON'T SAY THAT!
HEY, I'M JUST TELLING IT
LIKE IT IS.
THINK ABOUT IT.
CALUMON'S ABOUT AS TOUGH
AS BUTTERSCOTCH PUDDING.
Calumon: IT'S NOT LIKE
I'M BUTTERSCOTCH PUDDING.
I AM BRAVE AND STUPENDOUS
AND NOT A SCAREDY-CAT!
[ GRUNTING ]
WHOA!
W-W-WHO-O-O-A!
[ WHIMPERING ]
AW, IT'S NO USE!
I'M STILL SCARED.
[ CRYING ]
SOMEONE HELP ME. ANYONE.
[ GRUMBLES ]
THE CHAOS IS INCREASING.
HOLD ON TIGHT!
[ GRUNTS ]
OH!
[ GRUNTING ]
AAH!
Kazu: OH, MY HEAD HASN'T HURT
THIS BAD SINCE I HAD TO LISTEN
TO KENTA'S KNOCK-KNOCK JOKES.
Kenta: HEY!
COME ON, DUDE.
THEY ARE PRETTY BAD.
YOU GUYS, WE HAVE TO COME UP
WITH A PLAN AND QUICK!
YEAH, BUT THE CANYON'S
WAY TOO DEEP,
AND THE CHAOS
SEEMS TO BE EVERYWHERE.
IT'S LIKE EVERYTHING'S
AGAINST US.
WE SEEMED DESTINED TO FAIL.
DON'T SAY THINGS
LIKE THAT, JERI.
WE CAN'T GIVE UP.
RENAMON?
MM-HMM.
HEY, RIKA!
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
WHAT'S IT LOOK LIKE I'M DOING?
RIKA, COME BACK!
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS!
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
I'VE NEVER MET ANYONE
SO STUBBORN.
WE BETTER GO GET HER.
SHE'S GONNA HATE ME
EVEN MORE FOR THIS.
[ GRUMBLES ]
RIKA!
RYO! BE CAREFUL!
YEAH, RIKA.
WHY ARE THEY DOING THIS?
ARE THEY CRAZY?
DUDE, THAT'S WHAT I'VE BEEN
SAYING ABOUT RIKA FROM DAY ONE!
THE GIRL'S CRAZIER
THAN A SOUP SANDWICH.
LOOK...THE CHAOS!
[ GASPING ]
IF WE FALL, HOW LONG DO YOU
THINK IT WOULD TAKE
TO HIT THE BOTTOM?
IT MIGHT BE BEST
IF WE DON'T THINK ABOUT IT.
OH. OH!
[ BOTH SIGH ]
UM, RENAMON,
CAN WE CHANGE OUR DESTINY?
YES, OF COURSE.
WELL, THEN, DO YOU THINK WE CAN
SOMEHOW CHANGE LEOMON'S DESTINY?
THAT'S DIFFERENT.
SO WE CAN'T CHANGE IT.
I KNEW IT.
WE CANNOT ALTER THE PAST,
RIKA.
BUT WE CAN CHOOSE TO ACCEPT IT
AND LET IT MAKE US STRONGER.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT JERI?
IS SHE DESTINED TO BE SAD?
FOR A WHILE.
WHETHER SHE STAYS THAT WAY
IS HER CHOICE.
WE ARE ALL RESPONSIBLE
FOR OUR OWN DESTINIES.
BUT...
BUT WHAT?
...THAT'S SOMETHING JERI
HAS TO LEARN FOR HERSELF.
WE CANNOT DO IT FOR HER.
I JUST WANT HER TO BE OKAY.
WE ALL DO. HMM?
Calumon:
CHUGA, CHUGA, CHUGA,
WHOA!
AW, NUTS.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
RIKA! OVER HERE!
WHOA!
[ LAUGHING JOYFULLY ]
CALUMON!
OHH!
[ LAUGHING JOYFULLY ]
I'M SO HAPPY YOU'RE HERE.
I WAS COLD AND LONELY
AND SCARED.
I KNOW.
EVERYTHING'S ALL RIGHT NOW.
WATCH OUT!
MY BACKPACK!
THAT WAS CLOSE.
NO KIDDING.
RIGHT. COME ON.
LET'S GO.
[ BOTH GASP ]
[ GROWLS ]
GET IN HERE QUICK.
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU
PUTTING YOURSELF
IN DANGER LIKE THAT?
WHAT ARE YOU YELLING
AT ME FOR?
YOU'RE DOWN HERE, TOO!
UGH. SO WHAT ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO DO NOW?
THE CHAOS IS EVERYWHERE.
WE'LL BE TRAPPED SOON.
BUT I THINK I HAVE AN IDEA.
CYBERDRAMON, LET'S DO IT!
DIGIMODIFY!
AVENGING KNIGHT, ACTIVATE!
[ GROWLING ]
Rika: SOME PLAN, GENIUS.
Ryo: WATCH AND LEARN.
DESOLATION CLAW!
[ ROARING ]
SEE? WHAT I TELL YA?
NOW'S OUR CHANCE.
MM-HMM.
HEY, RYO,
THAT WAS PRETTY GOOD...
FOR A BOY.
VERY FUNNY.
[ GRUNTS ]
ALL I DID WAS DELAY IT.
THOSE ROCKS WON'T HOLD FOREVER.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE THE CHAOS BREAKS THROUGH.
WE HAVE TO GET OUT
AS SOON AS WE CAN.
OR WE'LL END UP
LIKE MY BACKPACK.
[ CALUMON WHIMPERING ]
[ SIZZLING ]
THIS IS UNACCEPTABLE.
HOW CAN YOU ALLOW THOSE HUMANS?
IT'S FOR A GOOD CAUSE,
ZHUQIAOMON.
Kazu: SO, WHAT DO YOU GUYS
THINK OF MY IDEA?
[ GRUNTING ]
DO I ROCK OR WHAT?
WELL, I HAVE TO ADMIT,
ONLY A WARPED MIND LIKE YOURS
WOULD THINK OF RAPPELLING DOWN
A BOTTOMLESS PIT
ON AZULONGMON'S BEARD.
[ GRUNTS ]
HEY, IT SEEMS LIKE THAT RED
STUFF HAS SLOWED DOWN A LITTLE.
MAYBE RIKA AND RYO FOUND A WAY
TO BLOCK THE CHAOS.
[ SIGHS ]
I HOPE TAKATO'S OKAY.
THEY LOOK KIND OF SILLY,
BUT I THINK THEY'LL BE FINE.
THAT IS AS LONG AS AZULONGMON
HERE DOESN'T SNEEZE...
OR HICCUP OR DECIDE TO SHAVE.
HURRY, CHILDREN.
YOUR TIME IS RUNNING OUT!
RIKA, YOU GO FIRST.
OKAY.
BYE!
THAT BARRIER WON'T HOLD
FOR LONG.
Takato: RIKA!
Kazu:
ANYBODY DOWN THERE?
HEY, YOU GUYS!
HI!
WE'VE COME TO RESCUE YOU!
WHAT?! DO I LOOK LIKE
I NEED RESCUING?
Ryo: ACTUALLY,
I THINK WE ALL DO.
AH! [ GRUNTS ] OH!
HURRY!
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME!
RIKA, WHAT IS IT?
WHAT'S WRONG?
WOULD YOU SAY SOMETHING?
YOU'RE MAKING ME NERVOUS!
I'M NOT GOING, RYO.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
WE'RE JUST KIDDING OURSELVES.
THERE'S NO WAY WE CAN ESCAPE.
AT THIS RATE, THE CHAOS WILL GET
US AND EVERYONE ABOVE, TOO.
BUT WHAT ELSE CAN WE DO?
I WANT YOU TO TAKE CALUMON.
WHAT?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
[ GRUNTS ]
TO STOP THE CHAOS.
WHAT?! DON'T BE CRAZY!
YOU'LL KILL YOURSELF!
RIKA, COME BACK!
RIKA!
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG.
I HOPE RIKA'S OKAY.
Ryo: RIKA, DON'T DO THIS!
PLEASE!
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
THANKS.
RIKA, GO BACK.
NO.
PLEASE!
NO WAY.
LISTEN TO ME FOR ONCE, PLEASE.
I'M BEGGING YOU!
GO BACK NOW AND THERE'S A CHANCE
YOU'LL SURVIVE.
STAY AND YOU'LL BE WALKING
INTO CERTAIN DEATH.
YOU'RE STAYING.
I'M A DIGIMON.
FIGHTING IS MY WAY OF LIFE,
NOT YOURS.
WHAT KIND OF PARTNER WOULD I BE
IF I LET ANY HARM COME TO YOU?
RIKA,
WHY WON'T YOU ANSWER ME?
WE CAN CHOOSE
OUR OWN DESTINY, RIGHT?
YES.
THEN I CHOOSE...
...TO STAY AND FIGHT
WITHYOU!
RIKAAAA!
HA! HA!
BIOMERGE ACTIVATE!
RENAMON, BIOMERGE TO...
...SAKUYAMON!
THE LIGHT -- IT'S SO WARM!
[ LAUGHS ]
SAKUYAMON --
I FEEL HER STRENGTH, HER POWER,
HER THOUGHTS.
I AM SAKUYAMON.
AND SHE IS ME.
HOLY COW!
AREN'T THEY BEAUTIFUL?
THEY BIOMERGED.
[ Rika's and Renamon's voices
echoing together ]
I, SAKUYAMON, PROTECTOR
OF ALL THINGS TRUE,
WILL DO MY DUTY.
RIVER OF CHAOS --
OH, RED SEA OF DESTRUCTION,
FOLLOW NOW MY VOICE
AND FEEL THE TWIN BLADES...
OF BEAUTY!
HAH!
AND OF TRUTH!
THEN FALL BEFORE MY LIGHT!
OHH!
WHO IN THE WORLD IS THAT?
SHE ROCKS.
"SAKUYAMON" --
A SHAMAN DATA-TYPE DIGIMON --
MEGALEVEL."
RENAMON AND RIKA BIOMERGED
TO MEGA!
TAKATO, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
OH, YEAH.
YOU SAVED OUR LIVES,
SAKUYAMON.
IT'S NOTHING.
I MUST ADMIT, RIKA,
YOU WERE UNBELIEVABLE!
OH, YEAH.
[ GIGGLES ]
Azulongmon:
EXCELLENT WORK, CHILDREN.
DON'T YOU THINK, ZHUQIAOMON?
THEY DID ALL RIGHT...
FOR HUMANS.
Terriermon: DID ZHUQIAOMON
JUST SAY SOMETHINGNICE?
SO, WHAT HAVE YOU GUYS
BEEN UP TO?
WE WERE LOOKING FOR YOU.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
WE WERE DOING, SILLY?
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
I THOUGHT ABOUT CREAM PUFFS
MOSTLY! HA HA!
Kazu: WE LOOKED DEATH
IN THE EYE TO RESCUE HIM,
AND HE'S GOING ON
ABOUT CREAM PUFFS!
Rika:EXCUSEME?
RYO AND I WERE LOOKING DEATH
IN THE EYE.
YOU WERE SWINGING ON A ROPE
LIKE A MONKEY.
WHATEVER.
Takato: I CAN'T BELIEVE
WE FINALLY DID IT!
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP,
AZULONGMON!
Azulongmon: I DID NOTHING.
IT WAS YOU, HUMANS AND DIGIMON
FIGHTING TOGETHER,
THAT STOPPED THE CHAOS.
Jeri: RIKA!
HUH?
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
WHAT'S WRONG?
OH, RIKA!
I THOUGHT I'D LOST
ANOTHER FRIEND.
NOT A CHANCE.
[ LAUGHING ]
OH, HI, JERI!
HMM?
OH, NO.
YOU LOOK SO SAD.
I GUESS THIS MEANS
WE CAN FINALLY GO HOME.
[ LOUD RUMBLING ]
HUH?
THE CHAOS!
I KNEW IT.
THE HUMANS ONLY DELAYED
ITS PROGRESS.
CAN NOTHING STOP
THIS MADNESS?
Takato: MAYBE IT'LL DIE DOWN
IN A MINUTE LIKE A GEYSER...
...OR NOT.
AAH!
NO ONE CAN FIGHT THIS.
IT'S EVERYWHERE!
WHAT'LL WE DO?
[ GASPS ]
IT'S TIME FOR YOU TO LEAVE.
THIS IS NOT YOUR BATTLE.
WE WILL STAY TO DEFEND
OUR WORLD!
AND WE'LL FIGHT
TILL THE BITTER END!
MAN! I HOPE OUR GUYS GET OT
BEFOTHATHAPPENS!
TO FIND OUT, KEEP WATCHING
"DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS"