JERI AND CALUMON NEEDED
TO BE SAVED AND FAST!
SO THE TAMERS USED THE RED CARD
SHIBUMI MADE FOR THEM,
AND THE FINAL BATTLE AGAINST
THE D-REAPER WAS ON!
MEANWHILE, THE MONSTER MAKERS
FRANTICALLY PUT
THE FINISHING TOUCHES ON THEIR
PLAN TO DELETE THE BIG BLOB.
THEN, JERI TOOK ACTION,
BUT THAT JUST ADDED FUEL
TO THE D-REAPER'S FIRE!
THIS GIANT THING ROSE OUT
OF NOWHERE,
AND IT LOOKED LIKE GALLANTMON
WAS DONE FOR!
BUT GRANI CAME TO THE RESCUE
AND GAVE HIS LAST REMAINING
STRENGTH
SO GALLANTMON COULD DIGIVOLVE
IN CRIMSON MODE!
OH, MAN, THIS IS IT, GUYS!
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
♪ WORLD
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMODIFY
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
Takato: GUILMON, I CAN'T
BELIEVE WE'RE FLYING!
THANKS TO GRANI,
WE'LL GET THERE IN NO TIME!
HOLD ON, JERI,
WE'RE COMING!
CALUMON,
COME OVER HERE, QUICK!
OH, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO TELL ME TWICE!
I'M THROUGH SITTING AROUND!
IT'S TIME -- TIME I DID
SOMETHING MORE THAN JUST CRY.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
OUR HANDS FULL HERE!
I HOPE SAKUYAMON,
MEGAGARGOMON,
AND JUSTIMON ARE DOING OKAY!
HEY! YEAH, I'M TALKING
TO YOU!
DOWN HERE!
I GOT SOMETHING FOR YOU!
MEGA BARRAGE!
TERRIERMON,
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WE'RE OUT OF AMMO.
NOT THAT IT MATTERS.
OUR LAST ATTACK DID AS MUCH
DAMAGE AS A WATER BALLOON!
[ Thinking ] I'LL HAVE
TO COME UP WITH ANOTHER PLAN.
HE DIDN'T EVEN MAKE
A DENT!
I HAVE AN IDEA!
CYBERDRAMON?
READY!
SAKUYAMON, LISTEN TO ME!
I WANT YOU TO SEND ALL
YOUR POWER TO MY BLADE!
QUICKLY!
WHAT? YOU CAN'T BE SERIOUS.
HAS THE FIGHTING GONE
TO YOUR HEAD OR SOMETHING?
THE FORCE OF IT
COULD KILL THE BOTH OF YOU!
IT'S A CHANCE I'M WILLING
TO TAKE, RIKA.
WE'VE TRIED EVERYTHING ELSE,
AND WE HAVEN'T EVEN LANDED
A SCRATCH.
BUT WITH THE COMBINED FORCES
OF YOUR STRENGTH AND OUR BLADE,
WE COULD GIVE THE D-REAPER
SOMETHING TO REALLY HOWL ABOUT.
OR YOU COULD DIE. DID YOU EVER
THINK ABOUT THAT, HOTSHOT?
WELL, THEN THERE WILL BE
JUST ONE LESS PERSON
TO POKE FUN AT YOU,
RIGHT, PUMPKIN?
YOU BIG TWERP.
YOU'RE JUST DOING THIS
TO IMPRESS ME, AREN'T YOU?
SO, IS IT WORKING
OR NOT?
COME ON, SAKUYAMON,
IT'S NOW OR NEVER!
RIKA, ARE YOU SURE?
RYU MAY BE OUT OF HIS POMPOUS
MIND, BUT HE'S ALSO RIGHT.
IT'S THE ONLY CHANCE WE HAVE
OF DESTROYING THAT THING.
HYAH!
AAH!
ALL THE POWER OF MY BODY,
MY SOUL,
MY MIND --
I NOW SEND TO YOU.
ALL THE STRENGTH
WITHIN MY HEART, MY SPIRIT --
TO YOU, I NOW FREELY GIVE.
RYU, HOLD ON TO SOMETHING.
[ GROANING ]
JUSTIMON!
WHAT IS HE DOING?
HE'S DOING EVERYTHING
HE CAN!
HE KNOWS WE CAN'T
PLAY IT SAFE ANYMORE!
HUH?
TIME TO GO ALL OUT!
COME ON!
TAKE YOUR BEST SHOT!
NO FORCE ON EARTH CAN STOP ME
FROM SAVING MY FRIEND.
LEOMON,
IF YOU CAN HEAR ME,
I FINALLY UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU SAID ABOUT DESTINY.
THE POWER TO CHANGE OUR LIVES
LIES IN OURSELVES!
JUSTIMON!
[ SCREAMING ]
HAVE TO...CONTROL...
ENERGY!
SAKUYAMON!
SEE, IT WORKED! I TOLD YOU
IT'D BE A PIECE OF CAKE,
DIDN'T I?
WELL, IF ANYONE
CAN DO IT...
IT'S YOU, RYU.
GOOD LUCK!
[ GROANING ]
Renamon: RIKA,
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
I GUESS...THAT TOOK MORE
OUT OF US THAN I THOUGHT.
CALUMON, IT WORKED!
HOW'D YOU DO IT?
WITH A LITTLE HELP
FROM LEOMON. AAH!
WHAT IS THAT?
HYAH!
JERI!
LOOK! THE KERNEL --
IT'S CRACKED!
COME ON,
NOW'S OUR CHANCE!
I DON'T THINK SO!
[ YELLING ]
WHO NEEDS AMMO WHEN YOU'RE
A WHUPPING MACHINE?
[ YELLING ]
ALL RIGHT!
TIMBER!
IT'S GETTING HIGHER!
I...DON'T KNOW HOW MUCH
TIME WE HAVE!
OH, TAKATO...
WHERE ARE YOU?
[ YELLING ]
I'M COMING, JERI!
HUH?
NEGATIVE, GALLANTMON.
WHO IS THAT?
HUMANS AND DIGIMON EXIST
ONLY TO DESTROY
OR BE DESTROYED!
AN EXERCISE IN FUTILITY!
[ GROWLS ]
YOU HAVE TO BE KIDDING ME!
HUMANS DESIRE
TOTAL ANNIHILATION.
THEREFORE, THEIR EXISTENCE
IS POINTLESS.
NO! YOU DON'T GET
TO DECIDE THAT!
MY LIFE ISN'T POINTLESS,
AND NEITHER IS GUILMON'S
OR MY FRIENDS'
OR ANYONE ELSE'S!
WE HAVE A RIGHT TO LIVE
AND TO PROTECT THE PEOPLE
WE CARE ABOUT!
SOMETHING A WARPED FREAK
LIKE YOU COULD NEVER UNDERSTAND!
WHAT HAPPENED?
IT'S THE DIGIMON SOVEREIGN!
THEY MUST'VE COME THROUGH
FROM THE OTHER SIDE!
BOY, WHEN THEY COME THROUGH,
THEY REALLY COME THROUGH!
SIR, I'M DETECTING A MASSIVE
WORMHOLE IN THE HEART
OF THE D-REAPER BUBBLE!
ALL RIGHT.
ENGAGE OPERATION DOODLE BUG.
DOODLE BUG LAUNCH
IN T-MINUS 10 SECONDS.
BOOTING SYSTEMS NOW.
TAO, ARE YOU SURE
THAT THIS IS SAFE?
WELL, ARE WE READY?
I GUESS WE'RE AS READY
AS WE'LL EVER BE, DOLPHIN.
Daisy: WHAT IF --
WHAT IF IT DOESN'T WORK?
IT'LL WORK, DAISY.
IT HAS TO.
OH, LOOK AT THE LIGHT.
ISN'T IT PRETTY?
LOPMON, WHERE'D YOU GO?
WE'VE BEEN IN TIGHTER SPOTS,
RIGHT, CALUMON?
WE'LL ESCAPE,
OR SOMEONE WILL RESCUE US!
ANY SECOND NOW...
I HOPE.
YOU ARE PERSISTENT, BUT YOU'RE
ONLY DELAYING THE INEVITABLE!
I'VE ESTABLISHED AN OPEN
COMMUNICATION LINE.
RIGHT, THIS IS IT.
HENRY, TERRIERMON, COME IN!
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
IS THAT YOU, DAD?
HENRY, LISTEN TO ME.
I'VE LOADED A PROGRAM
INSIDE OF TERRIERMON.
WHA--
MY EAR FEELS REALLY FUNNY.
SO THAT'S WHAT IT WAS.
Terriermon: HOLD EVERYTHING!
WHAT'S INSIDE ME?
I'M SORRY.
I SHOULD'VE TOLD YOU.
HENRY, IT'S THE JUGGERNAUT
PROGRAM.
THE JUGGERNAUT?
[ Gasps ] WHY DID YOU PUT IT
INSIDE OF TERRIERMON?
JUGGERNAUT WAS DESIGNED TO WORK
LIKE A SMALL-SCALE BIG BANG.
THE PROGRAM CREATES AN INTENSE
ENERGY VORTEX THAT SUCKS IN
ALL DIGITAL LIFE FORMS,
AND NOTHING CAN ESCAPE IT.
WHY WOULD YOU
ACTIVATE IT NOW?
HENRY, LOOK BELOW YOU.
IT'S A WORMHOLE,
CONNECTING THE REAL WORLD
TO THE DIGITAL DIMENSION.
WHOA...
IT TRANSFERS D-REAPER'S DATA
FASTER THAN THE SPEED OF LIGHT.
THAT'S HOW IT EVOLVES
AND GROWS SO RAPIDLY.
BY USING JUGGERNAUT,
WE CAN REVERSE THE PROCESS
BY SENDING D-REAPER BACK
WHERE IT CAME FROM
AND DEVOLVING IT
INTO A HARMLESS PROGRAM.
THAT'S JUST WHAT
WE'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR!
YOU GUYS ARE AMAZING!
WE'VE MADE THE NECESSARY
MODIFICATIONS TO JUGGERNAUT,
SO IT WON'T HARM YOU
OR ANY OF YOUR FRIENDS.
YOU JUST TELL ME
WHAT TO DO.
ALL RIGHT,
BUT LISTEN CAREFULLY.
Henry: ALL RIGHT,
WHAT DO YOU SAY, TERRIERMON?
YOU UP TO IT?
LIKE YOU EVEN HAVE
TO ASK.
GOOD LUCK, MEGAGARGOMON.
THE WORLD'S COUNTING ON YOU.
YEAH...
THANKS FOR REMINDING ME.
Yamaki: DON'T WORRY, JANYU.
EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE.
Janyu: I WISH
I COULD BELIEVE THAT.
THE REVERSAL'S BEGUN.
THERE'S NO TURNING BACK NOW.
SO FAR, EVERYTHING IS GOING
AS PLANNED.
BUT SOMETHING'S BUGGING ME.
WHAT IS IT?
Terriermon: HERE WE GO!
Daisy: IT'S WORKING!
THE D-REAPER'S ACTIVITY
IS BEGINNING TO DROP!
COME ON, MEGAGARGOMON!
YOU CAN DO IT!
SOMETHING'S WRONG. I KNOW
I'VE FORGOTTEN SOMETHING.
HENRY, I'M GOING
TO PASS OUT!
HANG ON, TERRIERMON!
WE CAN'T GIVE UP!
NOT NOW!
YOU DO NOT DESERVE
TO EXIST!
Guilmon: TAKATO...
IT'S NOT TRUE, IS IT?
NO, IT IS NOT,
AND IT'S ABOUT TIME
WE PROVED IT!
WE DO DESERVE TO EXIST!
YOU DON'T!
THEY DID IT. THE ROTATION
OF THE VORTEX HAS BEEN REVERSED.
AND IS THAT A GOOD THING?
WHEN THE REVERSE SPIN EXCEEDS
THE SPEED OF LIGHT,
IT'LL WARP THE GRAVITATIONAL
FIELD AND CREATE
A BACKWARD FLOW OF TIME,
CAUSING THE D-REAPER TO DEVOLVE
INTO ITS MOST BASIC STATE.
YEAH, A PROGRAM
THAT'S LESS COMPLEX
THAN A SIMPLE CALCULATOR.
HOLD ON, YOU TWO,
JUST A LITTLE BIT LONGER.
Terriermon: I'M GOING
TO BE SICK!
LOOK, THE D-REAPER'S BEING
SUCKED INTO THE WORMHOLE!
JERI!
WHERE IS SHE?
JERI! CALUMON!
[ Thinking ] THINK HAPPY
THOUGHTS, HAPPY THOUGHTS!
HANG ON, WE'RE COMING!
GALLANTMON, WATCH OUT!
HUH?
IT'S BACKING OFF!
[ D-REAPER SCREAMING ]
IT WORKED.
IT ACTUALLY WORKED!
THE D-REAPER'S GONE!
MEGAGARGOMON,
YOU DID ALL THAT?
WE DID IT!
I REMEMBER!
MY CALCULATIONS FOR THE RED CARD
ALGORITHM WERE OFF!
OFF? WHAT DO YOU
MEAN OFF?
IT WORKED PERFECTLY.
TO GIVE THE DIGIMON THE ABILITY
TO MOVE FREELY
INSIDE OF THE D-REAPER,
I CREATED THAT RED CARD
TO CHANGE THEIR WAVELENGTHS --
THEIR VERY DIGITAL MAKEUP.
Curly: WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
WE SAW THE RESULTS
OURSELVES.
THE CHILDREN AND THE DIGIMON
WERE UNAFFECTED.
NO! THE PROBLEM IS,
I DIDN'T TAKE INTO ACCOUNT
THE HUMAN-DIGIMON HYBRID.
NO! WAIT!
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING, SHIBUMI?
IT'S HAPPENING SOONER
THAN I EXPECTED.
THE DIGIMON WON'T BE ABLE
TO HOLD THEIR MEGAFORMS.
WHAT ABOUT THE CHILDREN?
[ GROANING ]
CYBERDRAMON,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I-I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
Renamon: RIKA,
I'M GETTING WEAKER.
I CAN'T HOLD THIS FORM.
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING?
JERI!
AAH!
GUILMON, ARE YOU OKAY?
I DON'T KNOW, TAKATO.
I FEEL FUNNY ALL OVER.
GUILMON!
TAKATO!
HUH?
HUH? HUH?
TAKATO, GET JERI!
WE HAVE TO GET RIKA
AND RYU OUT OF HERE NOW!
I KNOW,
BUT WHAT ABOUT THEM?
TERRIERMON?
TERRIERMON!
RENAMON, YOU HAVE TO...
I'M ON IT.
Calumon: JERI,
WAKEY, WAKEY.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
JERI, IT'S ME.
TAKATO. YOU CAME.
WELL, OF COURSE I DID.
WHAT DID YOU THINK --
I'D LEAVE YOU?
I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW GOOD IT IS
TO SEE YOU.
I MISSED YOU, TOO.
HEY, JERI! CALUMON!
HEY, GUILMON!
HA HA HA!
OH! HA HA HA!
WE HAVE TO GET OUT,
AND SOON!
I KNOW, BUT HOW? IT'S NOT LIKE
WE CAN JUST CALL A CAB.
Kenta: HEY, DOWN THERE!
NEED A RIDE?
TRY A BUBBLE!
NO CUP HOLDERS,
BUT IT'S A SMOOTH RIDE!
IT'S KAZU!
AND KENTA!
CRAZY NUT BAGS!
WHAT SAY
WE SPLIT THIS DUMP?
Henry: NO, WE CAN'T.
NOT WITHOUT TERRIERMON!
HE'S STILL DOWN THERE!
MARINEANGEMON, CAN YOU GET HIM?
TERRIERMON, WE'RE COMING
FOR YOU!
ARE YOU OKAY?
SAY SOMETHING!
ANYTHING!
MOMENTIE...
EVERYONE'S...ALL TOGETHER.
YEAH, THERE'S NOTHING
CAN KEEP US APART.
RIGHT?
WHAT DO YOU SAY, GUILMON?
MM-HMM!
THAT'S RIGHT! HA HA!
Yamaki: THE NIGHTMARE
FINALLY ENDED.
IT STILL SEEMS STRANGE
A MISGUIDED PROGRAM
COULD CAUSE SO MUCH DAMAGE,
BELIEVING IT WAS DOING
THE RIGHT THING.
MAYBE WE HAVE MORE IN COMMON
WITH THE D-REAPER
THAN WE'D LIKE TO BELIEVE.
BUT TODAY, WE WON
BY COMING TOGETHER,
WHICH MAKES ME BELIEVE
THERE'S HOPE FOR US...
ALL OF US.
Takato: THE PARK'S
NEVER LOOKED MORE BEAUTIFUL.
Kazu: DUDE, EVERYTHING
LOOKS BEAUTIFUL!
I COULD KISS THE DIRT!
IT'S FINALLY OVER.
WE DID IT.
TAKATO, I'M GLAD
WE'RE HOME.
YEAH, IT'S GOOD
TO BE BACK...
WITH THE PEOPLE
YOU CARE ABOUT MOST.
[ GASPS ]
IMPMON!
IMPMON, IT'S GOOD
TO SEE YOU.
HEY, WELL, UH,
I JUST WANTED YOU GUYS
TO MEET MY TAMERS --
AI AND MAKO.
WELL, HELLO THERE.
JERI, I...
IMPMON.
I'M SO GLAD
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME.
I NEVER WANTED ANYONE
TO GET HURT.
JERI, WILL YOU --
UM, WHAT I MEAN IS,
COULD YOU EVER FORGIVE ME?
COURSE.
OH, OH.
TAKATO,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
GUILMON,
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
I DON'T KNOW.
RENAMON.
I FEEL STRANGE.
HENRY...
TERRIERMON!
CYBERDRAMON!
RYU...I'M FADING!
KAZU!
THERE YOU ARE, HENRY!
LOPMON, TERRIERMON!
I THOUGHT I --
DADDY'S WHAT'S WRONG?
WHY ARE THEY ALL GROWING
SO SMALL?
MM.
DAD, HELP US!
MR. WONG, WHY ARE GUILMON
AND THE OTHERS DE-DIGIVOLVING?
DE-DIGIVOLVING?
DAD, TELL US!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
HENRY, I --
THE WHOLE WORLD WAS IN DANGER,
AND THERE WAS
ONLY ONE WAY OUT.
WE HAD TO TAKE IT, EVEN IF IT
MEANT LOSING THE DIGIMON.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, LOSE?
WHERE ARE THEY GOING?
THEY HAVE TO RETURN
TO THE DIGITAL PLANE,
OR THEY'LL DISAPPEAR
FOREVER, LIKE THE D-REAPER.
THEY WERE NEVER MEANT
FOR THIS WORLD.
BUT GUILMON'S MEANT
TO BE WITH ME.
HE'S A PART OF ME.
I PROMISED HIM
WE'D ALWAYS BE TOGETHER.
I PROMISED!
NO! THIS CAN'T BE!
I WON'T LET IT HAPPEN!
YOU KNEW, DIDN'T YOU? YOU KNEW
THIS WOULD HAPPEN
WHEN YOU SCANNED TERRIERMON!
I HAD NO OTHER CHOICE.
THE FATE OF THE WORLD
WAS AT STAKE.
I COULDN'T LET EVERYTHING
AND EVERYONE WE LOVE
BE DESTROYED, HENRY.
HENRY!
MOMENTIE.
OH, TERRIERMON, NO.
DON'T GO!
RENAMON, STAY! YOU CAN
FIGHT THIS, CAN'T YOU?
RIKA, I KNOW WE'LL SEE
EACH OTHER AGAIN ONE DAY.
NO, RENAMON, PLEASE!
I LOVE YOU!
GUILMON...
WE'LL PLAY AGAIN SOON,
WON'T WE, TAKATO?
YEAH.
Kazu: GUARDROMON,
I LOVE YOU, MAN!
Kenta: MARINEANGEMON!
Ryu: BYE,
CYBERDRAMON!
Ai and Mako:
IMPMON, WE'LL MISS YOU!
Jeri: THANK YOU,
CALUMON!
BYE-BYE! DON'T GO!
MOMENTIE, HENRY!
STAY STRONG, RIKA!
REMEMBER, TAKATO,
YOU PROMISED.
YOU PROMISED, TAKATO!
HENRY, WHERE'D THEY ALL GO?
WHERE'S LOPMON?
I LOVE MY LOPMON AND TERRIERMON!
I DON'T KNOW
WANT THEM TO GO!
HENRY?
I KNOW IT HURTS NOW, SON,
BUT IN TIME,
IT'LL GET BETTER,
YOU'LL SEE.
OH, HENRY, I...
I'M SORRY.
I'M SO SORRY.
[ SOBBING ]
I PROMISE, GUILMON.
JUST YOU WAIT.
WE'LL BE TOGETHER AGAIN SOON.
Takato: EVEN THOUGH I THOUGHT
I'D NEVER BE THE SAME,
THE WORLD SOON WENT BACK
TO NORMAL,
AND AFTER A WHILE,
SO DID I.
RUFF!
LIFE BECAME EXACTLY
WHAT IT WAS
BEFORE I MET GUILMON.
KAZU STILL MADE BAD JOKES,
AND MISS NAMI
STILL GAVE TOO MUCH HOMEWORK.
SOMETIMES, I GO BY
OUR OLD HANGOUTS
JUST TO SEE IF HE'S THERE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I
BOTHER, 'CAUSE HE NEVER IS.
MOST TIMES I'M OKAY, BUT...
THERE'S JUST ONE THING
THAT BUGS ME --
A PROMISE I MADE
TO A FRIEND,
A PROMISE I DON'T THINK
I CAN KEEP.
[ GIGGLES ]
HUH?
ACTUALLY, SCRATCH THAT.
I THINK I'M GOING TO KEEP
THAT PROMISE, AFTER ALL.