RIKA AND THE GUYS GOT SUCKED UP
BY ONE OF THOSE DATA STREAMS,
WHICH SPIT THEM OUT
INTO THIS DEEP RAVINE.
THERE THEY MET JIJIMON AD
BABAMON,
THIS WACKY OLD MARRIED COUPLE
WHO LOVED TO FIGHT AND
LOVED TO COOK.
AFTER STUFFING THEIR FACES,
KENTA AND KAZU DECIDED TO
SERENADE THEIR HOSTS.
THEN THEY ASKED THEM IF THY
WANTED TO BE THEIR PARTNER.
WELL, SOMEHOW, THE GUYS ENDED
UP BEING TAMED BY THE DIGIMO,
WHICH DIDN'T PLEASE RIKA
AT ALL.
SHE GOT EVERYONE ON THIS KITE
SHE AND RENAMON BUILT,
AND THEY ALL FLEW BACK UP
TOWARDS THE REAL WORLD.
BETTER LUCK NEXT TIME, GUY.
♪ DI, DI, DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI, DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI, DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE WORLD
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS.
DIGIMODIFY.
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON!
Kazu: I CAN FLY!
Rika: NOT IF YOU LET GO.
Kenta: I'M GONNA BE
SICK AGAIN.
GREAT. HE HAD TO BE
NEXT TO ME.
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU, KAZU?!
KENTA, RIKA!
WHEN THE DATA
STREAM ENGULFED THEM,
THEY COULD HAVE BEEN TRANSPORTED
ANYWHERE IN THE DIGITAL WORLD.
YOU'RE KIDDING ME.
WELL, IF WE WERE SUCKED UP
BY ONE OF THOSE THINGS,
WOULDN'T IT TAKE US
TO THEM?
NO.
YOU SEE, THERE'S NO GUARANTEE
THAT WE WOULD BE SENT TO
THE SAME PLACE.
IT'S BEST WE THINK
OF ANOTHER OPTION.
OH, TERRIFIC.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO BE SEARCHING
FOR CALUMON, NOT EACH OTHER.
MAYBE THEY'LL FIND
HIM FIRST.MOMENTI.
[ JERI SIGHS ]
WHAT'S WRONG, JERI?
I'M JUST TIRED.
I'M NOT SURPRISED.
WE'VE BEEN WALKING
OUR BUTTS OFF.
WHY DON'T WE TAKE A BREAK?
UH-OH.
HUH?
DON'T GET COMFY JUST YET.
SHEESH! THAT VILLAGE LOOKS LIKE
A PETRIFIED BUBBLE BATH,
IF YOU ASK ME.
Takato: MAN, I CAN SEE WHY NO
ONE'S HANGING AROUND.
IT'S NOT EXACTLY WHAT YOU'D CALL
ONE OF THE WORLD'S MOST
BEAUTIFUL VACATION SPOTS, HUH?
WHOEVER'S THERE,
COME OUT NOW!
UH, YOU SURE GET LOUD
WHEN YOU'RE TIRED.
HUH? THAT'S ODD.
THOSE TIRE MARKS LOOK LIKE
THEY CAME FROM A BIKE.
[ VEHICLE APPROACHING ]
HUH?
DOES THAT SOUND CLOSE TO YOU?
HUH? HUH?
AAAAH! AAH!
IT'S AFTER US!
Leomon: LET'S GO!
[ TIRES SQUEALING ]
HEY, COME ON.
WHAT DID WE EVER DO TO YOU, HUH?
NOBODY'S DRIVING IT.
HOW DOES IT KNOW WHERE WE ARE?
SEPARATE QUICK.
WE'LL THROW IT OFF TRACK.
I COULD RUN IF I WASN'T IN
A HEADLOCK.
WHERE'S A STOP SIGN
WHEN YOU NEED IT?
DON'T LOOK NOW, BUT I THINK IT
LIKES US BEST.
GREAT.
AND I THOUGHT THIS DAY
COULDN'T GET ANY BETTER.
IT'S GAINING ON US.
KEEP GOING!
UH, THIS COULD BE
A PROBLEM.
AAAH!
OHHH!
AAAAAH!
OHHHHH!
Takato: NO!
OHHH!
HE COULD HAVE SAID,
"EXCUSE ME."
HUH?
LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE NEEDS TO
GET A NEW COOKIE CUTTER.
UH, HEY, GUYS, IT'S NICE
TO MEET YOU.
UH, HI.
OH.
CHUCHIDARUMON, CHAMPION DIGIMON
WITH A TENDENCY TO STARE?
GREETINGS AND SALUTATIONS.
OHHHHH. OHHHHH.
THANK YOU FOR SAVING
ONE OF OUR VILLAGERS
FROM THAT
HORRIBLE METAL BEAST.
PLEASE, ACCEPT
SOME REFRESHMENT.
WE DON'T HAVE MUCH IN THE WAY OF
FOOD AROUND HERE,
BUT WHAT WE DO HAVE
IS YOURS.
WE APPRECIATE THE GESTURE,
BUT, UH...
IT MAY NOT BE
FOR PEOPLE.
I'LL HAVE ONE!
BUT, UH...
[ GULPS ]
MMM, DELICIOUS!
WELL, IF YOU SAY SO.
[ LAUGHS NERVOUSLY ]
[ PANTING ]
WHERE AM I?
IT'S LIKE FOG CITY AROUND HERE.
TYPICAL -- MOTHER NATURE
HATES ME.
EVEN IN THE DIGITAL WORLD,
MY LIFE STINKS.
UHHH!
AAAAAAAAAAHHHHHHH!
ARE YOU A DIGIMON?
ALL RIGHT, FELLA,
WHAT'S THE DEAL?
WHO DO YOU THINK YOU --
OOH, NICE COSTUME.
HMM!
YOU GONNA THROW ME A BONE HERE
OR JUST STARE AT ME ALL DAY?
HEH, MUST BE A STATUE.
YOU WANT TO BECOME
STRONG, DON'T YOU?
AAAAHHH!
OKAY, SO YOU'RE A DIGIMON
AFTER ALL.
THAT DON'T MEAN
YOU HAVE TO SCARE ME!
I KNOW A LOT MORE ABOUT YOU THAN
YOU REALIZE, MY LONELY FRIEND.
I CAN HELP YOU DIGIVOLVE,
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT.
IT'S VERY SIMPLE, ACTUALLY.
DID YOU SCRAMBLE YOUR BRAINS
FOR BREAKFAST?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
HEY, YOU'RE MAKING MY FEET
ALL TICKLY.
Takato: THANKS FOR THE FOOD.
IT REALLY WAS DELICIOUS.
Chuchidarumon: WELL, I'M GLAD
YOU ENJOYED IT.
I DON'T MEAN TO BE RUDE,
BUT AREN'T YOU PUTTING
THE VILLAGE IN DANGER
BY ASSOCIATING WITH HUMANS?
HMM? I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN, PAL --
IN THE DIGI DARK AGES?
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT DEVAS.
THERE'S BEEN A RUN ON 'EM
LATELY.
DEVAS? I'M SORRY, BUT I DON'T
THINK I'VE EVER HEARD OF THEM.
I WOULDN'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
THOUGH.
THIS IS THE FORGOTTEN VILLAGE
OF DISCARDED DATA.
NOBODY CARES ABOUT WHAT HAPPENS
TO US, I'M AFRAID.
THAT MAY BE TRUE,
BUT WHAT ABOUT THE METAL BEAST
OR WHATEVER THAT WAS?
IT WAS A MOTORBIKE.
BUT STILL, HOW COULD
A MACHINE THAT BIG
BE CONTROLLED WITHOUT
A DRIVER?
HMM. WE DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS
OR WHERE IT CAME FROM.
IT JUST SUDDENLY APPEARED ONE
DAY OUT OF NOWHERE
AND STARTED WREAKING HAVOC
ON OUR VILLAGE.
WHAT? ARE YOU SAYING THAT ALL
THAT DAMAGE OUTSIDE
WAS CAUSED
BY THAT WACKO BIKE?
YES. WHEN THE BEAST IS ON
THE PROWL,
OUR HOMES ARE DESTROYED, AND OUR
PEOPLE ARE AT RISK.
IF ONLY WE KNEW WHAT IT WANTED.
THERE ARE SOME WHO SAY IT MUST
BE SEARCHING FOR A RIDER,
BUT WHO IN THE VILLAGE WOULD BE
STRONG ENOUGH TO TAME IT?
BUT COME ON. YOU CAN'T LET IT
PLOW YOU ALL DOWN, RIGHT?
THAT'S RIGHT.
NOW LET'S GO OUTSIDE
AND BASH IT!
TERRIERMON!
YOU CAN'T PUT YOUR FRIENDS
IN PERIL.
YOU HAVE TO STAND UP TO THAT
BIKE ONCE AND FOR ALL.
YEAH. OTHERWISE, THERE WON'T BE
ANY OF YOU LEFT.
HERE'S AN IDEA -- PACK UP YOUR
DOMES AND MOVE TO A NEW PLACE.
UHHHH!
LET'S JUST BASH 'EM.
TERRIERMON!
OOOOOH.
WE'VE LIVED HERE ALL OUR LIVES.
WE WERE CREATED BY
DISCARDED DATA.
THE WHOLE REASON FOR OUR
EXISTENCE
IS TO STORE THIS INFORMATION.
THOUGH WE'RE LOST AND FORGOTTEN,
THIS VILLAGE IS OUR BIRTHRIGHT.
YOU CAN'T STAY HERE
AND LET THAT MANIACAL MACHINE
RUN ALL OVER YOU
LIKE A LAWN MOWER.
HUH?
CAN I SEE YOU OUTSIDE?
UH...
WHAT?
LOOK, TAKATO, THESE GUYS HAVE
THEIR OWN WAY OF DOING THINGS.
I DON'T THINK THAT WE, AS
OUTSIDERS,
SHOULD TELL THEM
WHAT TO DO.
THEY DON'T WANT TO MOVE,
SO DON'T PUSH IT.
I MEAN, ITISTHEIR DECISION
AFTER ALL.
AND ANYWAY, IT'S TIME TO GO.
WE'VE GOT TO SEARCH
FOR ALL THE OTHERS.
THEY'VE BEEN GONE
FAR TOO LONG NOW.
LET'S GO INSIDE
AND GET READY TO LEAVE.
WE'LL TAKE OFF AS SOON
AS JERI WAKES UP.
Guilmon: YEAH,
MORE ON THE BACK.
OH, THAT'S GOOD.
OH, YEAH.
WHAT ABOUT THOSE
LITTLE GUYS?
WE CAN'T JUST LET
THAT DERANGED BIKE
TURN THEM INTO DATA DEBRIS.
AND I WON'T!
WE'VE GOT TO HELP 'EM OUT.
TAKATO...
THAT'S THE STUFF!
AGAIN!
IT'S WEIRD, BUT I THINK I
ACTUALLY AGREE WITH TAKATO.
IT'S KIND OF TOO BAD THESE TREES
CAN'T TALK.
THEY COULD TELL ME
WHERE EVERYBODY IS.
OHHHHH.
OHHH.
IT FEELS KIND OF YUCKY.
OHHHH.
WHY IS IT THAT WAY?
BEING ALONE MAKES MY FACE
ALL WET.
SO I SUPPOSE YOU'RE
A DEVA?
YES, I'M A DEVOTED SERVANT
OF THE SOVEREIGN.
YOUR LIFE AMONG HUMANS
IS A WASTE OF TIME.
I CAN SHOW YOU HOW TO ACHIEVE
YOUR FULL POTENTIAL.
WHY SHOULD I TRUST
A BIG, UGLY MUTT LIKE YOU?
AND, INCIDENTALLY,
I HATE HUMANS!
IS THAT SO?
I SUSPECT THAT
YOU REALLY DO CARE FOR THEM.
AHHH!
YOU GOT A LOT OF NERVE, YOU
FLEA-BITTEN LUNATIC!
YOU DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT ME!
HMM.
AAAH!
WAIT A MINUTE.
THIS IS MY OLD HOUSE.
[ LAUGHS NERVOUSLY ]
HEY, GUESS WHO'S BACK?
[ GASPS ] [ GASPS ]
HUH? HUH?
[ LAUGHS NERVOUSLY ]
I'M...HOME, GUYS.
HE'S HERE!
OH, BOY!
HUH?
I WANT HIM!
GIVE HIM TO ME!
NO, DADDY!
HEY, THAT ISN'T FAIR!
LET GO!
YOU SEE, IMPMON, HOW EASILY
YOU ARE FORGOTTEN.
THERE'S SIMPLY NO PLACE
FOR YOU IN THE HUMAN WORLD.
WE ARE THE ONLY REAL FAMILY
YOU HAVE.
[ CRYING ]
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
[ CHUCHIDARUMON SCREAMING ]
AAAH!
OHHH. OHHH.
HURRY UP, 'CAUSE THAT BIKE
DOESN'T LOOK FIRST
BEFORE IT CROSSES
THE STREET.
OHHH.
TERRIERMON...
FINALLY -- SOME BASHING!
DIGIMODIFY.
DIGIMODIFY!
DIGIVOLUTION ACTIVATE!
♪ DI, DI, DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI
TERRIERMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DI, DI, DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI
...GALGOMON!
♪ DIGIMON
GARGO LASER!
[ LAUGHS ]
HUH?
OH, NUTS.
FIST OF THE BEAST KING!
GUILMON!
OKEY-DOKEY!
NICE HORSY.
ALL RIGHT, GUILMON.
LET'S SEE YOU POP A WHEELIE!
UH-OH. I THINK HE LOST
HIS HEAD.
STAY HERE.
HMM?
[ BEEPING ]
OH, IT SAYS IT'S METALKOROMON,
A ROOKIE MACHINE DIGIMON.
HEY, GUYS, IT'S A DIGIMON.
I'M SO HAPPY YOU SAVED ME.
THANKS A LOT.
GIVE ME THAT AGAIN.
DID YOU SAY WE SAVED YOU?
Jeri: OH, NO! LOOK!
GUILMON'S GONE BERSERK!
[ GROWLS ]
GUILMON?
OKAY, OKAY, YOU'RE RIGHT.
I CAN'T GO BACK THERE.
THEY WOULDN'T WANT ME ANYWAY.
WHO WOULD?
I'M SUCH A WEAK LITTLE NOTHING!
I WANT TO BE STRONG!
THEN GIVE YOURSELF
TO THE SOVEREIGN.
IF I DO, THEN YOU'LL MAKE ME AS
STRONG AS I WANT, RIGHT?
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
Takato: GUILMON'S TAKEN THIS A
BIT SERIOUSLY, DON'T YOU THINK?
WE'VE GOT TO GET AWAY
FROM THIS VILLAGE
BEFORE WE CRASH AND BURN.
HE'S RIGHT ON OUR TAIL.
I DON'T LIKE THAT BIKE.
IT TAKES OVER YOUR MIND AND
CAUSES YOU TO GO BONKERS.
AND THAT'S NOT THE ONLY ROTTEN
THING IT DOES.
ONCE YOU GET ON IT, YOU'RE STUCK
BECAUSE IT'LL KEEP GOING
UNTIL IT FINDS ANOTHER RIDER IT
LIKES EVEN BETTER.
SOME WEIRD BIKE.
I AGREE.
IT REMINDS ME OF THE STORY
OF THE RED SHOES.
I NEVER HEARD THAT ONE.
IF YOU WORE THE RED SHOES, YOU'D
START DANCING FASTER AND FASTER,
AND YOU'D KEEP
DANCING FOREVER.
YOU'D NEVER BE ABLE
TO STOP.
[ GROWLS ]
GUILMON, LISTEN TO ME.
YOU'VE GOT TO FIGHT IT!
[ GROWLS ]
PYRO SPHERE!
DIGIMODIFY!
WAR GREYMON BRAVE SHIELD
ACTIVATE!
I'VE GOT TO GET ON
THAT BIKE.
WHAT?
WHEN GUILMON GOT ON IT,
METALKOROMON WAS ABLE TO MAKE
HIS ESCAPE.
IF I GET ON THE BIKE,
GUILMON WILL BE ABLE TO DO
THE SAME THING.
DON'T BE A FOOL!
ARE YOU GONNA SIT THERE
STARING ALL DAY,
OR ARE YOU GONNA MAKE ME
DIGIVOLVE?
SHOW ME WHAT YOU GOT!
THE DIGIMON OF THIS WORLD HAVE
BEEN ROBBED
OF THE ABILITY TO DIGIVOLVE
WITHOUT THE USE OF HUMANS.
THE POWER OF WHICH I SPEAK CAN
BE OBTAINED THROUGH MY MASTER,
BUT YOU MUST FIRST
PROVE YOURSELF WORTHY.
IF YOUR AMBITIONS FOR
POWER ARE REAL,
I MUST ASK YOU TO CARRY OUT
A QUEST FOR THE SOVEREIGN.
WHAT KIND OF QUEST?
SOME HUMAN-LOVING DIGIMON HAVE
TRESPASSED INTO OUR WORLD.
I BELIEVE YOU ARE QUITE
FAMILIAR WITH THEM.
THE DEVAS THEY DEFEATED
WERE NEVER UPLOADED.
INSTEAD, THEIR DATA WAS
DISCARDED AS IF IT WERE REFUSE.
HUH?
GUILMON AND ALL HIS FRIENDS?
YOU MUST REALLY LIKE
THAT BREAD.
WHAT MAKES YOU SAY THAT?
MORE.
WELL, IF IT ISN'T
THE DUMB-DUMB CLUB.
DID YOU MISS ME, BOYS?
JUST IGNORE HIM.
EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
YOU CAN'T SMELL HIM.
LET'S GO.
GUILMON, COME ON!
OHH.
A PARTNER?
I WANT TO DIGIVOLVE!
IT'S NOT FAIR!
I'M THE STRONGEST!
I DESERVE IT!
I DON'T NEED A PARTNER.
HOLD IT.
LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT.
YOU SAYING YOU WANT
'EM DESTROYED?
AH, CRUD.
DON'T TELL ME THAT'S MY QUEST.
DO I HAVE ANY CHOICE?
FOR ONCE, I REALLY AM
SICK TO MY STOMACH.
BUT IF YOU MAKE ME DIGIVOLVE,
I'LL DO IT.
I'LL DO ANYTHING
YOUR SOVEREIGN WANTS!
THEN RELINQUISH YOUR SOUL!
AAH! AAAAAAH!
HEY, JERI, TELL US MORE ABOUT
THE RED-SHOE STORY.
I MEAN, IT DID HAVE
A HAPPY ENDING, RIGHT?
WELL, AS I REMEMBER...
THERE WAS SOMETHING ABOUT
THE RED SHOES NOT COMING OFF,
AND THEN SOMETHING
HORRIBLE HAPPENED.
BUT I CAN'T REMEMBER EXACTLY
WHAT IT WAS.
SOMETHING REALLY HORRIBLE?
[ GASPS ]
[ GASPS ] [ GASPS ]
ENOUGH!
NO!
LEOMON!
[ ROARS ]
AAAAH!
HUH?
WHAT?
GUILMON!
[ Sobbing ] GUILMON!
DON'T WORRY, TAKATO.
HE HAS A VERY HARD HEAD.
OHHHHH.
HUH?
OH, THAT WASN'T FUN.
NEXT TIME, I THINK I'LL WALK.
THAT'LL BE JUST FINE
WITH ME, BOY.
IT OCCURRED TO ME
THAT IF THE BIKE WAS IN COMPLETE
CONTROL OF THE RIDER'S MIND,
THEN ALL THE RIDER NEEDED WAS
A NOT-SO-GENTLE WAKE-UP CALL,
AND THE SPELL
WOULD BE BROKEN.
HEY, WHERE'S IT GOING?
HUH?
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE THAT BIKE
WON'T BE CAUSING
ANY MORE TROUBLE AROUND HERE
AFTER ALL.
THANKS TO YOU,
THE CHUCHIDARUMON ARE SAFE.
I'M REALLY SORRY, TAKATO.
I DON'T KNOW WHY I
GAVE YOU SUCH A HARD TIME
ABOUT BUTTING IN ON THEIR
PROBLEMS.
I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN BETTER.
YOU NEVER LISTEN TO ME ANYWAY.
THAT MUST BE WHY I LIKE
YOU SO MUCH.
YEP, I THOUGHT YOU DID
REALLY GREAT.
IT WAS NOTHING.
[ LAUGHS NERVOUSLY ]
THEN HOW COME YOUR FACE IS ALL
RED AND SWEATY-LOOKING
JUST LIKE MINE?
WOULD YOU CRAM IT, GUILMON?
IT IS NOT.
NOW THAT THAT'S BEEN SAID, LET'S
GO LOOK FOR CALUMON.
[ RUMBLING ]
OHHHH! OHHHH!
SOMEONE'S RIDING SHOTGUN.
[ TIRES SQUEALING ]
WHOEVER'S JUMPED ON HAS ABSOLUTE
CONTROL OVER THAT CONTRAPTION.
DOES THAT MEAN THAT HE'S
MASTERED THE MACHINE
AND TAMED THE BEAST WITHIN?
[ TIRES SQUEALING ]
[ METALKOROMON BEEPING ]
WHO IS THAT GUY?
THEY CALL ME...BEELZEBUMON.
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
OH, MAN!
LOOKS LIKE TROUBLE JUST ROE
INTO TOWN,
AND THAT CAN'T BE GOOD.
SO TUNE INTO THE NEXT
"DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS"