WHILE TAKATO TRIED TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT WAS UP WITH JERI,
THE MONSTER MAKERS WENT
ON THE AIR TO EXPLAIN
ABOUT THE D-REAPER.
LOOKS LIKE THAT THING HAS BEEN
SENDING OUT AGENTS
TO DO ITS DIRTY WORK.
THE KIDS GOT
A NOTE FROM THEIR PARENTS
TO GO TO RIKA'S HOUSE, WHERE
THEY ALL GOT SOME COMFORT FOOD
AS WELL AS
SOME PARENTAL GUIDANCE.
AND THEN IT WAS
OFF TO FACE THE ENEMY.
BUT THE D-REAPER
WAS MORE INTERESTED
IN THIS GIRL ALICE
AND HER FRIEND DOBERMON.
TURNS OUT THE TWO OF THEM
HAD BEEN LOOKING FOR THE TAMERS.
KNOWING THAT THEY COULDN'T
BIOMERGE IN THE REAL WORLD,
THE SOVEREIGN SENT DOBERMON
TO DELIVER A MESSAGE
AND A GIFT.
I JUST HOPE ALICE
DOESN'T TAKE IT TOO HARD.
DI-DI-DI
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON
DI-DI-DI
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS
TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
WORLD
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS
DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON
DON'T GO.
I HAVE TO DO THIS, ALICE...
FOR ALL OF US.
[ GASPS ]
THE DIGIMON SOVEREIGN
ARE FIGHTING THE ENEMY
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD,
BUT THE ENEMY'S
MOST EVOLVED PART
HAS EMERGED TO WAGE WAR
HERE IN YOUR WORLD.
ONLY YOU, THE TAMERS,
CAN STOP IT
BY FIGHTING AS ONE
WITH YOUR DIGIMON.
TO AID YOU, I BRING A GIFT
FROM THE DIGIMON SOVEREIGN.
REMEMBER, THE FATE OF THE WORLD
LIES IN YOUR HANDS!
DOBERMON.
Takato: WHAT'S HAPPENING?
Henry: I CAN'T BE SURE,
BUT I-I THINK HE'S GIVING US
THE POWER TO BIOMERGE.
THEN LET'S DO IT
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
DOBERMON'S RIGHT.
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES
WHO HAVE ANY CHANCE
OF SAVING THIS WORLD.
WARGROWLMON, LET'S DO IT!
RAPIDMON!
TAOMON!
[ ALL YELLING ]
Takato: [ Thinks ] IF THIS
DOESN'T WORK, WE'RE SUNK.
[ Thinking ] I THINK
I WAS PRETTY SELFISH
WHEN I WAS YOUNGER.
I HAD SO MANY BROTHERS
AND SISTERS,
THE ONLY WAY I COULD BE HEARD
WAS TO ASSERT MYSELF.
WHEN I LEARNED MARTIAL ARTS
FROM SENSEI,
HE TAUGHT ME
THAT WE LEARN TO FIGHT
IN ORDER TO AVOID FIGHTING.
BUT I USED MY POWER
AGAINST A NEIGHBORHOOD KID
AND I HURT HIM.
AFTER THAT, I ALWAYS FELT
LIKE I HAD TO HOLD BACK,
THAT FIGHTING WAS WRONG.
BUT THIS IS DIFFERENT.
THIS IS A BATTLE
THAT MEANS SOMETHING.
FIGHTING FOR A PURPOSE
IS DIFFERENT
THAN JUST FIGHTING TO FIGHT.
THIS IS SOMETHING
I HAVE TO DO --
SOMETHING ONLY TERRIERMON,
MY FRIENDS, AND I CAN DO.
BIOMERGE ACTIVATE!
TERRIERMON BIOMERGE TO...
DIGIMON
DI-DI-DIGIMON
DI-DI
MEGAGARGOMON!
[ Thinking ] SOMETIMES
I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M THE SAME PERSON
WHO ONLY THOUGHT
ABOUT FIGHTING DIGIMON
AND DOWNLOADING THEIR DATA.
BEING THE BEST WAS
THE ONLY THING THAT MATTERED.
BUT NOW THAT I'M FRIENDS
WITH HENRY AND TAKATO
AND THE OTHERS,
I REALIZE THAT THERE'S
MORE TO LIFE THAN JUST FIGHTING,
AND THAT THERE'S COURAGE
IN FRIENDSHIP, TOO.
WHAT MAKES IT TOUGH NOW
IS I HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT SOMEONE ELSE
BESIDES JUST ME.
NOW I DON'T KNOW
IF I WANT TO FIGHT AT ALL,
SEEING ALL THE PAIN
IT'S CAUSED.
I MEAN, LOOK AT JERI.
BUT THIS ISN'T REALLY
ABOUT FIGHTING.
IT'S ABOUT HAVING THE STRENGTH
TO DO WHAT NEEDS TO BE DONE
TO SAVE THE WORLD.
BIOMERGE ACTIVATE!
RENAMON BIOMERGE TO...
DIGIMON
DI-DI
DI-DI-DIGIMON
SAKUYAMON!
DIGIMON
DI-DIGIMON
[ Thinking ] THE FIRST TIME
I BIOMERGED WITH GUILMON,
I DIDN'T HAVE A CLUE
WHAT WAS GOING ON.
I MEAN, I ALWAYS KNEW
I HAD AN ACTIVE IMAGINATION,
BUT I NEVER DREAMED
I'D ACTUALLY BECOME A DIGIMON.
BUT THEN WHEN WE MERGED
AND I FELT GUILMON'S STRENGTH
FLOWING THROUGH ME,
IT WAS LIKE A FEELING
OF SAFETY AND STRENGTH
UNLIKE ANYTHING
I'D EVER KNOWN.
THANKS TO HIM,
I KNOW WHAT IT IS
TO FEEL A PART OF SOMETHING
MUCH GREATER THAN MYSELF,
AND NOW THE FATE OF NOT ONE
BUT TWO WORLDS
RESTS ON OUR SHOULDERS.
BUT I KNOW I CAN DO IT
AS LONG AS I HAVE MY FRIEND --
ALL MY FRIENDS --
BY MY SIDE.
NOTHING'S GOING
TO TEAR US APART -- NOTHING.
BIOMERGE ACTIVATE!
DI-DI
GUILMON BIOMERGE TO...
DI-DI-DIGIMON
DIGIMON
DI-DI
GALLANTMON!
Henry: ALL RIGHT,
LET'S SHOW THIS THING
IT CAN'T PUSH US AROUND.
Terriermon: WELL, YOU KNOW,
ANY MORE THAN IT ALREADY HAS.
Guilmon: WE CAN DO ANYTHING
IF WE WORK TOGETHER.
Takato: [ Thinking ]
AND SOMETHING TELLS ME
IT'S GOING TO TAKE
EVERYTHING WE'VE GOT.
OH, DOBERMON, I WISH
THERE HAD BEEN MORE TIME.
Takato: WE CAN'T LET
DOBERMON'S GIFT BE IN VAIN.
THE D-REAPER'S GOT
TO BE STOPPED RIGHT NOW.
Guilmon: YOU HEAR THAT,
YOU BIG BALL OF BADNESS?
I'M DRAWING
A LINE IN THE SAND --
WELL, IN THE AIR --
AND YOU WON'T GET PAST IT.
OH, YOU CAME BACK!
[ GIGGLES ]
OH, NO! DON'T GO YET!
NO!
DOBERMON!
AAH!
LIGHTNING JOUST!
YAMAKI -- I MEAN SIR!
LOOK, IT'S THE DIGIMON.
THEY'RE FIGHTING
THE D-REAPER'S AGENTS AGAIN.
THEY'VE COME BACK?
THE CHILDREN --
WE CAN'T JUST LET THEM FIGHT
THAT THING ON THEIR OWN.
MEGA BARRAGE!
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOME WAY
WE CAN HELP THEM. THINK, GUYS.
HOW'D A BUNCH OF HACKERS
GET MIXED UP
IN SO MUCH TROUBLE
OR CAUSE SO MUCH TROUBLE
FOR OUR CHILDREN?
I'M SORRY, ALICE.
Yamaki: JANYU?
I'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING.
LIKE WHAT?
[ GRUNTS ]
CRYSTAL SPHERE!
MEGA BARRAGE!
[ Thinking ]
GOODBYE, DOBERMON.
YOU DID SOMETHING
NO ONE ELSE COULD --
YOU GAVE THEM A CHANCE.
Janyu: I CAN'T JUST STAY HERE!
JANYU,
YOU CAN'T HELP THEM NOW.
WASN'T IT YOU
WHO ALWAYS SAID
THAT EACH PERSON
HAS THINGS THEY MUST DO,
THINGS ONLY THEY CAN DO?
I KNOW,
BUT THEY'RE CHILDREN.
THEY'RE THE ONLY ONES CAPABLE
OF FIGHTING THE D-REAPER.
Man: THE DIGIMON
HAVE RESUMED THEIR ATTACK,
BUT IT IS UNCLEAR
WHO HAS THE UPPER HAND.
AMETHYST WIND!
THE DIGIMON APPEAR
TO BE DOING SOME DAMAGE,
BUT THE DANGER FOR THEM
REMAINS EXTREME.
LIGHTNING JOUST!
AAH!
YOU'VE ALREADY DONE
MORE THAN YOU THINK, JANYU.
YOU HELPED CREATE THE DIGIMON
THAT ARE OUT THERE FIGHTING.
WITHOUT YOUR CREATION,
THERE'D BE NO HOPE AT ALL.
AAH!
LET'S GET HIM!
Terriermon: I'M GETTING,
I'M GETTING.
POWER PUMMEL!
YOUR SON AND HIS FRIENDS
ARE LIVING OUT
WHAT YOU ALWAYS
TALKED ABOUT --
DIGIMON AND HUMANS,
BOTH OF THEM
WORKING TOGETHER IN HARMONY.
TRUST IN THEM
TO WIN THE FIGHT.
I DO BELIEVE IN THEM,
IT'S JUST --
HE'S MY SON, YAMAKI.
I KNOW.
SO USE YOUR WEAPONS
AS A PROGRAMMER TO HELP HIM.
WE NEED YOU HERE.
WELL, THEN WHAT ARE WE
ALL DOING STANDING AROUND?
IF WE'RE GOING
TO STOP THAT THING
OR AT LEAST GIVE THOSE KIDS
A FIGHTING CHANCE,
WE'D BETTER GET HACKING.
THANKS, YAMAKI.
Terriermon: HEY!
DID THAT ACTUALLY WORK?
Henry: [ Sighs ]
OF COURSE NOT.
AAH!
AAH! IT'S GOT US!
Takato: WHY DON'T THE BAD GUYS
EVER JUST STAY DOWN?
I'LL MAKE IT STAY DOWN.
SPIRIT STRIKE!
Rika: IT SEEMS LIKE NO MATTER
HOW MANY OF THOSE THINGS
WE TAKE DOWN,
MORE JUST TAKE THEIR PLACE.
THEN WE'LL KEEP
TAKING THEM DOWN.
THE BATTLE RAGES ON
WITH NO CLEAR VICTOR IN SIGHT.
HEY, DAISY,
REMEMBER THE ARK YOU PROGRAMMED
TO BRING THE CHILDREN HOME
FROM THE DIGITAL WORLD?
MM-HMM.
DO YOU THINK
THERE'S ANY WAY
YOU COULD SOMEHOW REESTABLISH
A CONNECTION WITH IT?
I GUESS SO, BUT WHY?
IT'S POWERLESS NOW.
IT CONTACTED ME.
HUH?
THAT'S RIGHT.
I RECEIVED A MESSAGE FROM IT
ON MY HANDHELD
ASKING FOR INSTRUCTIONS.
THE ARK STILL HAS SOME POWER,
BUT NOT A LOT.
I THINK MAYBE
WE CAN STILL USE IT
AGAINST THE D-REAPER SOMEHOW.
MAYBE.
I'D LIKE THIS TO STAY BETWEEN US
UNTIL WE'RE SURE.
I DON'T WANT TO GIVE
THE OTHERS FALSE HOPE.
OKAY. I'LL GET STARTED
ON IT RIGHT AWAY.
Man: SOME WONDER WHETHER
THESE DIGIMON ARE TRULY HELPFUL
OR WILL ULTIMATELY
TURN ON HUMANITY,
BUT FOR NOW,
THE CITY HAS ADOPTED THE POLICY
"THE ENEMY OF MY ENEMY
IS MY FRIEND"
AND IS WATCHING WARILY
TO SEE WHAT WILL HAPPEN NEXT.
WHAT'S THAT MEAN?
THAT THEY DON'T KNOW
A GOOD THING WHEN THEY SEE IT.
Guardromon: KAZU,
I'M BEING ATTACKED!
OH! OH!
RUSTY BUCKET OF BOLTS!
I TOLD YOU NOT TO STAND
ON MY FLOWER BED, DIDN'T I?
IS THIS NORMAL BEHAVIOR
FOR YOUR MOTHER?
I'M SURPRISED THAT YOU'RE
NOT ALL COVERED WITH DENTS.
Man: WITH BOTH SIDES
TRADING VIOLENT VOLLEYS...
EVEN IF YOU'RE NOT MEGA,
WE'VE GOT TO TRY TO HELP.
THE BATTLE CONTINUES TO RAGE
WITH FEROCIOUS VIOLENCE,
SHAKING THE BUILDINGS
WITH EACH ATTACK.
HENRY.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
SUSIE, I CAN'T JUST SIT HERE
AND WATCH THIS ON TV ANYMORE.
WE CAN'T IGNORE
THIS BATTLE.
THOSE ARE OUR FRIENDS
AND OUR FAMILY
THAT ARE FIGHTING
OUT THERE, SUSIE.
THEY NEED HELP,
AND YOU'RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN GIVE ME STRENGTH.
ME?
YES. YOU'RE MY TAMER.
IT'S TIME TO ACT LIKE ONE.
OKAY.
DO I NEED A JACKET?
NICE D-REAPER.
OH, NO!
HENRY!
GUILMON!
HE'LL BE ERASED!
NOT IF I CAN HELP IT.
I JUST HOPE I'M NOT TOO LATE.
AAH!
Guilmon: NO ONE'S
ERASING MY BUDDIES!
YOU OKAY?
Terriermon: OH, YEAH,
AND HERE'S A LITTLE GIFT
TO SHOW THE D-REAPER
JUST HOW OKAY I AM!
MEGA BARRAGE!
AAH!
SHIELD OF THE JUST!
Terriermon: WE ACTUALLY
DESTROYED THAT THING?
THAT WAS EASIER
THAN I THOUGHT.
Henry: YEAH, RIGHT.
Man: WITH A MIGHTY EXPLOSION,
IT LOOKS AS IF THE TIDE
OF THE BATTLE HAS TURNED
IN FAVOR OF THE DIGIMON,
BUT WE ARE STILL WAITING
FOR THE SMOKE TO CLEAR
TO BE CERTAIN.
THE QUESTION IS --
CAN THESE DIGIMON
TRULY DEFEAT THIS ENTITY
OR ARE THEY JUST SIMPLY
DELAYING THE INEVITABLE?
Gallantmon: SEE, D-REAPER?
WE CAN TAKE
WHATEVER YOU THROW AT US,
SO WHY DON'T YOU JUST
GIVE IT UP AND SURRENDER?
GALLANTMON,
WE CAN'T JUST TALK TO IT.
WE MUST DESTROY IT.
SAKUYAMON'S RIGHT.
THE TIME FOR TALKING'S OVER.
Terriermon: THAT THING'S
STILL MOVING?
JEEZ, HOW MANY TIMES
DO WE HAVE TO DESTROY IT
BEFORE IT STAYS DESTROYED?
KENTA, I MADE
P.B. AND J. FOR YOU.
KENTA?
OH.
KENTA?!
Guilmon: D-REAPER,
THIS ENDS RIGHT NOW!
Takato: [ Thinks ] YEAH,
AND HOPEFULLY NOT FOR US.
HUH?
LET GO!
Takato: IT'S NO USE,
SAKUYAMON.
GET OUT OF HERE
BEFORE IT GRABS YOU, TOO!
GALLANTMON, NO!
THE D-REAPER IS
PULLING HIM INSIDE. TAKATO!
WE'VE GOT TO SAVE THEM
BEFORE THEY'RE DELETED!
HURRY UP ALREADY.
THE GUYS ARE IN TROUBLE.
MY JETS DON'T RUN
ON NAGGING, YOU KNOW.
HEY, LESS LIP,
MORE ZIP, HUH?
Girl: SUSIE, IT'S TIME
FOR "BERNARD THE DINOSAUR."
SUSIE?
SUSIE, ANSWER ME!
OH, SUSIE.
THANK GOODNESS.
SUSIE, YOU OKAY?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT HAPPENED
TO YOUR FRIEND LOPMON? HUH?
AAH! THAT'S LITTLE LOPMON?
WHOA, WHAT A GROWTH SPURT!
THAT'S NOT LOPMON.
THAT'S ANTYLAMON.
SHE'D SAY HI,
BUT SHE'S BUSY
SAVING THE WORLD AND STUFF.
OKAY.
[ GASPING AND PANTING ]
AW, NUTS!
HUH?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S MORE AMAZING --
THAT WE'RE
INSIDE THE D-REAPER OR THAT
WE'RE INSIDE THE D-REAPER
AND WE'RE STILL ALIVE.
Guilmon: TAKATO,
I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN HOLD
OUR MEGA FORM MUCH LONGER.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WE'RE GOING TO BE DELETED?
Guilmon: NO WAY.
WELL, I DON'T THINK SO.
MAYBE. WE BETTER LAND.
OKAY, BUT LAND
SOMEPLACE SAFE.
HUH?
HEY, WHAT ABOUT
OVER THERE?
YEAH, THAT LOOKS SAFE --
AT LEAST AS SAFE
AS WE CAN GET IN HERE.
I DON'T GET IT.
WHY IS THEREANYPLACE
THAT LOOKS SAFE IN HERE?
HEY, WHY ISN'T IT
EATING THE TREES
THE WAY
IT EATS THE BUILDINGS?
DOES IT HATE VEGETABLES?
I DON'T KNOW.
THE ORGANIC MATERIALS
COULDN'T BE ANALYZED.
HUH?
JERI! WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
THIS IS THE MOST DANGEROUS
PLACE THERE IS.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE HE--
WAIT A MINUTE.
WHATAREYOU DOING HERE?
COME ON, SHORTY,
PICK UP THE PACE, WOULD YOU?
[ SIREN WAILING ]
WHOA.
HUH?
HEY, WALKING MEANS NOT STOPPING
SUDDENLY, YOU KNOW?
LOOK AT THAT, IMPMON.
I WANT TO GO OVER THERE.
HUH?
WHAT, ARE YOU CRAZY?
THAT THING'S JUST
A GIANT ERASER TO US.
Takato: WHY DID YOU
RUN AWAY BEFORE?
DIDN'T YOU SEE ME?
WELL, I GUESS
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I'M JUST GLAD
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
I'VE BEEN WORRIED
ABOUT YOU.
YOUR CONCERN IS ILLOGICAL.
THIS BEING
IS IN NO PHYSICAL DANGER.
SHE IS
A VERY INTERESTING SAMPLE.
HUH?
IT WAS EASY TO ASSIMILATE
THE BEING YOU CALL JERI
BECAUSE HER DATA WAS SO SIMILAR
TO THE D-REAPER.
HER THOUGHTS
WERE FOCUSED ON DESTRUCTION
AND WHAT YOU HUMANS
CALL SADNESS AND DESPAIR.
JERI, WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH YOU?
SNAP OUT OF IT!
THIS ISN'T FUNNY!
SHE HAS PROVEN
TO BE INVALUABLE
IN THE D-REAPER'S
STUDY OF HUMANS.
HEY, JERI, STOP!
BUT YOUR KIND DOES REMAIN
DIFFICULT TO DECIPHER.
TAKATO,
THAT'S NOT JERI.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT, GUILMON?
OF COURSE IT IS.
JUST LOOK AT HER.
TAKATO, IT'S NOT!
IT JUST HAS TO BE HER!
Calumon: BUT I KNOW
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE THERE.
YEAH, WELL,
THINGS AIN'T ALWAYS
WHAT THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO BE.
YEAH, WELL, I DON'T CARE.
I'M GOING.
HEY!
YOU'RE BEING MEAN,
IMPMON!
HEY, MEAN WOULD BE
LETTING YOU RUN IN THERE
AND GET ERASED
QUICKER THAN YOU CAN SAY,
"IS THIS A DELETE KEY
I SEE BEFORE ME?" SEE?
WOW, IMPMON,
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU CARED.
SURPRISED ME, TOO.
I'LL BET.
D-REAPER SAMPLED
THE BEING KNOWN AS JERI
IN ORDER TO ANALYZE
THE LIFE FORMS
THAT CREATED THE NETWORK
AND THE D-REAPER.
YOU ARE
CONFUSING CREATURES --
DISORDERLY, ILLOGICAL,
AND WITHOUT RESPECT
FOR BOUNDARIES.
STOP TALKING
THAT WAY, JERI!
[ Growls ] IT'S ONE
OF THE D-REAPER'S AGENTS!
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE
WITH HER?
BECAUSE
OF YOUR INHERENT DEFECTS,
THE D-REAPER HAS DETERMINED
THAT ALL HUMANS
AND DIGIMON ARE
TO BE DELETED IMMEDIATELY.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
LISTEN, TELL ME WHERE JERI IS
RIGHT NOW OR YOU'LL BE SORRY.
THE D-REAPER IS UNABLE
TO BE SORRY
OR TO BE SAD OR HAPPY.
THOSE EMOTIONS
ARE PART OF THE REASON
HUMANS ARE
TO BE ELIMINATED.
YOU'D SACRIFICE
YOURSELF FOR JERI,
WOULD YOU NOT?
YOUR FEELINGS
OF CONCERN AND COMPASSION
DO NOTHING
BUT MAKE YOU WEAK.
WHAT YOU CALL WEAKNESSES
ARE WHAT'S GOING TO HELP US
BEAT YOU.
YOUR DEFIANCE IS POINTLESS.
YOU CANNOT WIN.
THIS ISN'T OVER.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE
MORE THAN WORDS TO STOP ME.
HMM.
TAKATO, WE GOT
TO GET OUT OF HERE NOW!
I SWEAR I'LL SAVE JERI
IF IT'S THE LAST THING I DO!
YOUR EMOTION
WILL GET YOU NOWHERE.
THE D-REAPER
WILL DELETE EVERYONE.
TELL THE D-REAPER
IT'SGOING TO BE DELETED!
Terriermon: WE'VE GOT TO SAVE
GALLANTMON BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE!
YEAH, BUT HOW?
WE CAN'T JUST --
Kazu: LOOK OUT BELOW!
HUH?
HERE COMES THE CAVALRY!
HEY! GUYS!
WHAT?
IT'S KAZU!
I'VE COME
TO OFFER MY HELP.
IT WAS MY IDEA,
YOU BIG LUG NUT.
OH, RIGHT.
WHO'S THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
Kazu: TYPICAL.
ALWAYS SOMEONE
STEALING MY GLORY.
IS THAT A FRIEND OR A FOE?
AND CAN JERI BE SAVED?
CAN ANYBODY?
GET ALL THE ANSWERS ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."