THAT CRAZY IMPMON GOT HIMSELF
POUNDED ON BY INDRAMON
AND WENT INTO HIDING,
BUT THEN YAMAKI FIRED UP
THE JUGGERNAUT PROGRAM,
AND INDRAMON DISAPPEARED, TO.
HENRY'S DAD WENT TO WORK FR
HYPNOS WITH OLD BUDDIES OF HIS.
WHATEVER YAMAKI'S PLANNIG
TO DO WITH THEM
WAS EVEN APPROVED BY THE GUYS
UPSTAIRS.
WELL, THE GANG WAS LOOKIG
FOR IMPMON
TO SEE IF HE WAS ALL RIGHT,
INDRAMON REAPPEARED.
EVEN THE CHAMPIONS
COULDN'T STOP HIM.
BUT THEN TAKATO USED
A BLUE CARD KAZU HAD MAD,
AND IT MATRIXED DIGIBALL
GREYMON INTO WARGRAMMON
THE DEVA WAS DEFEATED,
ALL THANKS TO KAZU.
IS THAT GONNA GO
TO HIS HEAD OR WHAT?
♪ DI, DI, DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI, DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI, DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE WORLD
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS.
DIGIMODIFY.
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON!
WELL, HELLO THERE, JERI.
GOOD MORNING, MR. MASTUKI.
CREAM PUFFS SURE LOOK GOOD
TODAY.
THEN AGAIN,
THEY ALWAYS LOOK GOOD.
ALL SET?
MM-HMM.
IS...TAKATO...HERE?
NO, HE'S OUT RIGHT NOW.
THANKS. I'LL TELL TAKATO
YOU DROPPED BY.
Young man: HEY, JERI!
HUH?
WERE YOU LOOKING
FOR TAKATO?
UH-HUH.
WHAT A COINCIDENCE.
SO ARE WE.
COME ON. JOIN OUR POSSE,
AND WE'LL TRACK HIM DOWN.
KAZU, WAIT A MINUTE!
WHERE ARE WE GOING?!
YOU'RE SQUISHING MY CREAM PUFF!
Man: EVERY DAY, PEOPLE IN THE
CITY GO ABOUT THEIR BUSINESS,
BLISSFULLY UNAWARE OF THE DANGER
THAT IS TO COME.
WE ARE THE SILENT GUARDIANS,
THEIR ONLY PROTECTION AGAINST
THE DIGITAL MENACE.
BUT THE KEY TO CONTROLLING
THE DIGIMON
LIES IN THE CODE YOU'RE WORKING
ON, MR. WONG.
AND EVERY SECOND YOU AND YOUR
TEAM WASTES
BRINGS US AN HOUR CLOSER
TO CHAOS.
IT'S NOT AS SIMPLE
AS COPYING SOMETHING
FROM THE SIDE OF A CEREAL BOX.
SHABUMI'S CODE -- IT'S ENCRYPTED
AND HIGHLY COMPLEX.
TELL THAT TO YOUR CHILDREN WHEN
THEIR WORLD IS DESTROYED,
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT THESE
MONSTERS WILL DO
IF WE DON'T STOP THEM SOON.
THIS ISN'T A GAME LIKE IT WAS IN
YOUR COLLEGE DAYS, MR. WONG.
IF YOU CARE FOR YOUR CHILDREN,
YOU'LL GET ME THAT CODE AT ONCE.
[ SIGHS ]
WOULD YOU GUYS QUIT
PULLING ME?
I'M NOT A STUFFED TOY.
I CAN WALK ON MY OWN.
YEAH, BUT YOU'RE POKY.
COME ON, WE WANT TO GET THERE
BEFORE CHRISTMAS.
WHY ARE WE IN THE BUSHES?
Shh!
I can't see.
Is he there?
Oh, yeah.
Really?
Are they all there?
What are they doing?
Do they have
a secret handshake?
Stuff a sock in it,
would you? Amateurs.
SO, THAT'S MY THEORY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
HMM.
MM-HMM.
I STILL DON'T...GET IT.
IT'S ELEMENTARY, GOBBLEHEAD.
THE SOVEREIGN DIGIMON'S BEHIND
ALL THIS.
I THINK HE'S RESPONSIBLE
FOR ALL THE DEVAS
APPEARING.
SO, THE SOVEREIGN'S
A DIGIMON?
YEAH,
BUT NOT A REGULAR ONE.
AM I A REGULAR ONE?
YOU'RE A REGULAR GOOFBALL.
WELL, THEN, WHO IS HE?
HMM.
MAYBE A SANDWICH
WILL HELP US THINK.
COME ON!
LESS TALK, MORE ACTION!
FIGHT,
FIGHT, FIGHT, FI!
IT'S NICE
THEY'RE GETTING ALONG.
MAN, CHECK IT OUT.
THEY LOOK TOTALLY INTENSE.
THAT'S SO COOL.
WHAT IS?
BEING ONE OF THEM,
TALKING ABOUT REAL DIGIMON
KICKING DEVA BUTT.
I'D DO ANYTHING
TO BE A TAMER.
WOULDN'T YOU, JERI?
NOT REALLY.
THINGS LIKE THAT DON'T USUALLY
HAPPEN TO ME.
WELL, I COULD
TOTALLY BE A TAMER,
AND I'D HAVE THE
MOST AWESOME PARTNER,
JUST LIKE OMNIMON!
YEAH? WELL, MY PARTNER
WOULD BE IMPERIALDRAMON.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, JERI?
ME? I-I TOLD YOU.
I'M NOT INTO DIGIMON.
I DON'T EVEN COLLECT THE CARDS.
OH!
SO, IS THERE, UH,
SOMETHING YOU WANT
TO TELL US, JERI?
YOU ARE ONE STRANGE BANANA,
YOU KNOW THAT?
AAH!
HUH?
OH, TERRIFIC!
WAIT -- WHERE'D THEY GO?
HOW'D THEY DISAPPEAR?
SOME KIND
OF DIGITAL WARP TRICK?
THEY PROBABLY LEFT WHEN WE WERE
YAKKING IN THE BUSHES.
MUST BE ON A MISSION.
I BET ANOTHER BAD DIGIMON
SHOWED UP
WITH FANGS AND HORNS
AND STUFF,
AND THEY'RE TRACKING IT DOWN.
MAYBE IT'S A DEVA!
WE GOT TO BE THERE!
COME ON!
OH, MAN, I HOPE
THEY DON'T START WITHOUT US!
I GUESS I'LL JUST GO HOME.
WHOA!
CALUMON!
MMM! SOMETHING SMELLS
YUMMY GOOD!
[ LAUGHS ]
YOU WANT ONE?
BUN, BUN, BUN IN TUM!
YUMMY, YUMMY, BUN, BUN!
[ LAUGHS ]
HMM.
MM-MMM.
MM-MM-MM-MMM.
GUESS I'LL HAVE ONE, TOO.
MORE YUMMY,
GOODY SNACKY STUFF?
YOU WANT MORE?
YES, PLEASE. THANK YOU.
HERE YOU GO.
[ Singsong voice ]
ANOTHER TREAT FOR ME.
[ GIGGLES ]
I WONDER...
[ GULPS ]
Could I ever be a tamer?
Could Calumon be my partner?
CALUMON?
GOOD FOOD!
YOU LIKE ME?
I LIKE YOUR FOOD.
I LIKE YOU, TOO.
THEN IT'S SETTLED.
CALUMON...YOU AND I
ARE GOING TO BE PARTNERS.
WHA--
SAY HELLO TO YOUR NEW
DIGIMON TAMER.
OHH!
WELL, IS THAT
THE WAY YOU BEHAVE
TO YOUR NEW TAMER?
NO.
YOU DON'T THINK
I'M COOL ENOUGH LIKE TAKATO.
IT'S NOT THAT.
THEN WHAT IS IT? YOU SAID
YOU LIKED ME, DIDN'T YOU?
UM...NO.
NOW, I KNOW
I MAY NOT LOOK LIKE ONE,
BUT I COULD BE A GREAT TAMER
AND HELP YOU WITH A LOT.
[ RUMBLING ]
OH, NO, OH, BAD, BAD,
OH, NO, OH, BAD!
A TAMER NEVER PANICS.
[ GROWLS ]
[ GASPS ]Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â [ GASPS ]
NOW, IS THAT ANY WAY
TO GREET...
YOUR WORST NIGHTMARE?!
[ BREATHING QUICKLY ]
NYAH!
ARE YOU MY PARTNER,
MR. WHATEVER-YOU-ARE?
I AM A MIGHTY DEVA
WHO SERVES THE ALL-POWERFUL
SOVEREIGN DIGIMON!
WHY WOULD I JOIN FORCES WITH A
PATHETIC HUMAN?!
THANK GOODNESS. NO OFFENSE, BUT
YOU'RE WAY TOO BIZARRE.
I CAN'T TELL IF YOU'RE A MOUSE,
A SPIDER, OR A NUTCRACKER.
[ GASPS ]
WAIT A MINUTE.
IF YOU'RE NOT MY PARTNER,
THEN YOU MUST HAVE COME HERE TO
FIGHT ME AND CALUMON!
BEAT HIM, CALUMON!
NYAHH! OHH!
OH! OH! OH!
AAAH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
AAAHH!
LET THE GAMES BEGIN!
HMM.
I DON'T GET IT.
WHY DIDN'T YOU USE A SPECIAL
ATTACK OR SOMETHING?
WHAT KIND
OF A DIGIMON ARE YOU?!
THE CUDDLY, CUTE KIND WHO
DOESN'T LIKE TO FIGHT
AND GETS CRAMPS
WHEN HE EATS TOO MUCH.
[ LAUGHING ]
[ BOTH PANTING ]
TOO POOPED -- CAN'T MOVE.
MAYBE WE LOST HIM.
YA-HA!
AAAH!
IT'S BEEN NICE KNOWING YOU,
CALUMON.
[ CHUCKLES ]
I CAN'T MOVE.
ME NEITHER.
[ WATER BUBBLING ]
AAAH!
[ GASPS ]
WHOA!
IT'S A MIRACLE!
I WONDER WHAT THIS MEANS.
Calumon: MAYBE THE FOUNTAIN
DIDN'T LIKE THE WAY HE TASTED.
AH!
I KNEW IT!
IT'S LEOMON!
HE'S SO BIG!
OH! THIS MUST BE A SIGN!
HE'S MEANT TO BE...
MY PARTNER!
HMM.
[ GROWLS ]
[ GIGGLES ]
YOU SHOULD
GET OUT OF MY WAY!
YOU SHOULD PICK ON SOMEONE
YOUR OWN SIZE.
A TRUE WARRIOR BATTLES
THOSE WHO ARE STRONG.
ONLY A COWARD FIGHTS
DEFENSELESS LITTLE GIRLS.
YOU WILL PAY FOR YOUR
IMPERTINENCE, WARRIOR!
YAAH!
HE'S AMAZING!
YEOW!
MY HERO!
HUH? HEY, WAIT!
MR. LEOMON?
WHAT IS IT, KID?
YOU'RE MY...PARTNER.
I'M YOUR WHAT?
I'M HONORED
TO BE YOUR TAMER.
TAMER?
YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW LONG
I'VE DREAMED ABOUT THIS.
YOU WANT TO
CLUE ME IN HERE, PAL?
I THINK HER BRAIN'S GONE
ALL FUNNY.
CALUMON, STAY OUT OF THIS!
WELL, IT HAS.
NOW, WHERE WERE WE?
YOU'RE A STRANGE LITTLE HUMAN.
YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY?
I AM JUST FINE.
OKAY.
UH, SEE YOU ROUND, KID.
WAIT, WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE TOGETHER!
UH-OH!
[ EXHALES ]
FOUND HIM!
HUH? AW, NUTS!
THIS GAME IS FUN!
YEAH!
HMM.
HUH?
[ GASPS ]
HE'S HERE!
Be quiet!
CALUMON!
GUILMON!
LEOMON.
HUH?
CHAMPION LEVEL --
HIS BRAVERY IS MATCHED BY HIS
FIST OF THE BEAST KING ATTACK.
HEY, PICKING ON CALUMON
ISN'T VERY BRAVE.
YOU JUST
DON'T UNDERSTAND, KID.
WELL, I THINK I DO.
PREPARE TO FIGHT!
YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING.
WE CAN TAKE YOU,
RIGHT, GUILMON?
UH-HUH?
COME ON, BOY, GO GET HIM!
OKAY.
[ SNARLS ]
I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT YOU,
BUT IT SEEMS YOU'VE LEFT ME
NO CHOICE.
Jeri: THERE YOU ARE!
JERI?!
I WANT YOU BOTH TO MEET MY
PARTNER, MR. LEOMON.
UM, WOW. REALLY?
LOOKS LIKE I'M A TAMER JUST
LIKE YOU. PRETTY NEAT, HUH?
WELL, I GUESS CONGRATULATIONS
ARE IN ORDER?
NOW, HOLD ON, KID.
SIR, YES, SIR.
ALL I'VE BEEN HEARING ABOUT
IS PARTNERS AND TAMERS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THOSE ARE,
BUT LET'S JUST GET ONE THING
STRAIGHT.
I'M A LONE WARRIOR --
THAT'S THE WAY IT'S ALWAYS BEEN,
AND THAT'S THE WAY
IT'S GOING TO STAY.
DO I MAKE MYSELF CLEAR?
YES, SIR -- CRYSTAL.
BUT, UM...
BUT WHAT?
Takato: DOES THAT MEAN JERI'S
NOT YOUR PARTNER, MR. LEOMON?
CALL ME "LEOMON,"
AND FOR THE LAST TIME, I DON'T
KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS!
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT
IT MEANS...
LEOMON.
AAH!
PLEASE STOP DOING THAT.
PARTNERS ARE INSEPARABLE,
LIKE YOU AND I WILL BE.
I DON'T THINK SO.
BUT WAIT.
THAT'S JUST THE BEGINNING.
OKAY.Â Â Â OKAY.
THAT WAS FUN.
JERI SURE CAN RUN FAST.
UH-HUH!
HUH?
[ HUMMING ]
JERI'S A TAMER?
ARE YOU SURE?
SHE'S CHASING HIM?
MAKING EYES?
TAMERS DON'T DO THAT.
WAIT. I'LL ASK.
HEY, JERI!
YEAH?
ARE YOU SURE
HE'S YOUR PARTNER?!
YES!
HOW COME?
'CAUSE IT'S DESTINY!
OKAY, THANKS!
YOU CAN'T ESCAPE DESTINY,
MR. LEOMON!
SHE SAYS IT'S DESTINY.
THAT DOESN'T SOUND GOOD
AT ALL.
OKAY, I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
HENRY'S ON HIS WAY.
I GUESS
I SHOULD TELL RIKA, TOO.
JERI...
THAT JUST ISN'T POSSIBLE.
WAIT. I'LL ASK.
HEY, JERI!
YEAH?
DO YOU HAVE A DIGIVICE?!
NO, I DON'T!
THAT'S A NEGATIVE.
ANYTHING ELSE?!
NOPE, THAT'S ALL!
MR. LEOMON, WAIT UP!
NO DIGIVICE?
SHE'S OBVIOUSLY NOT A TAMER.
SHE'S DELUSIONAL.
OH, WHATEVER.
I'M COMING RIGHT DOWN.
RIKA'S COMING, TOO.
[ PANTING ]
AAAH!
[ GASPS ]
[ RUMBLING ]
JERI, ARE YOU OKAY?
[ GROWLS ]
NYAH!
WHO OR WHAT IS THAT, HUH?
HE'S BEEN CHASING ME.
HE SAYS HE'S A DEVA!
A DEVA?! YOU'RE KIDDING.
LOOKS LIKE WHOEVER PUT HIM
TOGETHER LOST THE MANUAL.
KUMBHIRAMON --
DEVA DIGIMON, ULTIMATE LEVEL.
HIS DEVA CLONE ATTACK MAKES
HIM SIX TIMES THE TROUBLE.
DEVA CLONE?
WHOA!
ABOUT TIME.
THIS JUST DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE.
NYAH!
Henry:
WHAT'S LEOMON DOING HERE
IF HE'S NOT JERI'S PARTNER?
Calumon: I DON'T KNOW,
BUT I'M NOT ASKING HIM.
LEOMON'S A HERO!
THE DEVAS DON'T GOT NOTHING!
'CAUSE RAT FACE IS
A ZERO! YAY!
YOU'RE ABOUT TO BE OUTNUMBERED,
YOU OVERSIZED ALLEY CAT!
DEVA CLONE!
NYAH!
Jeri: LEOMON!
STAY BACK!
THERE'S TOO MANY OF THEM!
STAY HERE. IT'S SAFE.
GIVE IT TO ME --
YOUR DIGIVICE!
OKAY.
DIGIMODIFY.
DIGIMODIFY!
[ ROARS ]
DIGIMODIFY.
DIGIMODIFY!
GUESS I'M NOT
LEOMON'S TAMER...
AFTER ALL.
TERRIERMON!
WHOA!
DIGIMODIFY.
DIGIMODIFY!
DIGIVOLUTION, ACTIVATE!
HERE WE GO!
HMM.
DIGIVOLUTION.
♪ DI, DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI, DI, DIGIMON
TERRIERMON, DIGIVOLVE!
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
GARGOMON!
WHOA!
[ LAUGHS ]
IT'S YOU!
[ LAUGHING ]
I'M GOING AFTER HIM.
NOT WITHOUT ME, YOU'RE NOT.
BUNNY PUMMEL!
[ CRYING ]
SHE'S CRYING.
THIS IS FOR YOU, KID.
[ ROARS ]
GLAD TO HAVE YOU WITH US.
FIST OF THE BEAST KING!
[ SCREAMING ]
AAAAH!
[ SLASHING ]
MY WORK HERE IS DONE.
[ CRYING ]
I SHOULD GO
BEFORE HER TEARS MAKE ME STAY.
GOODBYE, JERI.
JERI...
GO ON!
PLEASE,
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE!
I'M SORRY, JERI.
COME ON, TERRIERMON.
MOMENTI,JERI,MOMENTI.
IT'S SO SAD!
I CAN'T WATCH!
GUILMON, WAIT!
I'VE MADE A FOOL OF MYSELF.
HOW COULD I THINK
I WAS SPECIAL ENOUGH TO HAE
A PARTNER OF MY OWN?
Man: HEY, WOULD YOU STOP
WORKING SO HARD?
YOU'RE MAKING THE REST OF US
LOOK BAD.
COME HERE.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
HUH?
HELLO? OVER HERE.
HEY, THEY'RE LIKE THE PORTABLES
WE USED TO HAVE.
IT'S JUST LIKE
OLD TIMES, HUH?
[ RUMBLING ]
WHOA, WAS THAT AN EARTHQUAKE!
I GUESS JERI WON'T BE THE ONY
ONE WHO'S SHAKEN UP NOW.
TO FIND OUT,
TUNE IN TO THE NEXT
"DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS"
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI, DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI, DI