TAKATO AND THE GANG
KNEW THE THING TO DO
WAS TO RESCUE CALUMON
FROM THE DIGIMON SOVEREIGN.
BUT HENRY DIDN'T WANT SUSIE
TO BE IN DANGER.
SO KAZU AND KENTA VOLUNTEERED
TO WATCH SUSIE AND JERI
WHILE THE OTHERS
WENT TO CONFRONT HUGELMO.
THE FIREBIRD SOVEREIGN
TURNED OUT TO BE MORE
THAN EVEN THE ULTIMATES
COULD HANDLE.
IN THE END,
IT TOOK THE COMBINED STRENGTH
OF HENRY AND TERRIERMON
TO DEFEAT HIM.
THEY BIOMERGED TO MEGAGARGOMON.
AND PUT OUT
THE BIG BIRD'S FIRE...
SO THEY THOUGHT.
MAN,
THAT IS ONE TOUGH TURKEY.
♪ DI, DI, DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE WORLD
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS.
DIGIMODIFY.
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON!
Woman: IF I TWEAK
THE ALGORITHM,
THE ERROR MESSAGE DISAPPEARS.
PRETTY GOOD WORK,
DON'T YOU THINK?
Man: IT'S GOT TO BE BETTER
THAN PRETTY GOOD.
THIS ARC HAS TO BE PERFECT.
THIS STUPID PIECE OF JUNK
SURE TAKES ITS TIME PROCESSING.
I'LL BE AN OLD MAN
BEFORE IT'S DONE.
DON'T SAY IT.
IF YOU MEAN ASKING HOW YOU
COULD POSSIBLY GET ANY OLDER,
I'D NEVER SAY THAT,
YOU FOSSIL.
HE'S RIGHT.
EVEN WITH HYPNOS,
THIS IS TAKING TOO LONG.
WE NEED MORE JUICE.
DON'T WORRY.
PEOPLE EVERYWHERE ARE HELPING.
WE'VE GOT THE PROCESSING POWER
OF THE WHOLE PLANET. HMM.
WHAT IS IT, BABBLE?
SOLUTION ON THAT STICKY
ENCRYPTION PROBLEM.
SEE, WE'LL BE FINE.
THIS IS THE KIND OF WORK
I'VE ALWAYS WANTED TO DO.
IT'S JUST LIKE OLD TIMES
WHEN WE WERE FIRST
MAKING DIGIMON. REMEMBER?
LISTEN, I LIKE TO JOKE AROUND
AND REMINISCE AS MUCH AS ANYONE,
BUT KEEP WORKING.
LIVES DEPEND ON THIS.
I KNOW THAT.
BUT IT'S STILL
PRETTY EXCITING.
[ SIGHS ]
[ BEEPING ]
HANG ON, GUYS,
JUST A LITTLE WHILE LONGER.
AND THEN ALL OF YOU
WILL BE HOME SAFE AND SOUND.
I PROMISE.
ALL WE NEED IS JUST
A LITTLE BIT MORE TIME.
I JUST HOPE THAT A LITTLE BIT
ISN'T TOO LONG.
YOU THOUGHT YOU COULD
STAND UP TO ME, FOOLS?
YOUR DEFIANCE HAS DONE NOTHING
BUT SEAL YOUR DOOM!
WELL, THIS IS NOT
GONNA BE GOOD.
[ Echoing ]
SONIC ZEPHYR!
OH!
AAH!
WE'VE GOTTA FIGHT BACK!
[ ELECTRONIC RIPPLING ]
[ BEEPING ]
[ Echoing ] DIGIMODIFY!
MATRIX DIGIVOLUTION, ACTIVATE!
RENAMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
UVIMON!
UVIMON MATRIX, DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DI, DI
♪ DIGIMON
TAOMON!
TALISMAN SPELL!
[ GRUNTS ]
UGH!
OH, THANKS, TAOMON.
Taomon:
IT'S NOT OVER.
I BETTER THANK YOU
WHILE I CAN.
LOOK!
HE'S COMING AROUND AGAIN!
YOUR PUNY SHIELD IS NO MATCH
FOR MY POWER!
WE'VE GOT TO GET OUT
OF HERE NOW!
[ GRUNTING ]
Rika: YOU DID IT!
[ ROARING ]
THAT'S WHAT I CALL
A CLOSE CALL.
HOW LONG CAN YOU KEEP THIS UP,
TAOMON?
[ GROANS ]
I GUESS NOT LONG.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
OH, NO!
HE'S COMING BACK!
THERE'S NO ESCAPE!
[ STRAINING, GRUNTING ]
Takato:
HE'S GAINING ON US!
HOW ABSURD OF ME!
AAH!
THIS IS WORSE
THAN A CARNIVAL RIDE!
WE'LL NEVER BEAT HIM
IF WE JUST KEEP RUNNING AWAY!
Takato: WE'LL NEVER BEAT HIM
IF WE'RE DESTROYED.
WHAT DO WE DO?
HEY! CUT IT OUT!
Rika: THERE'S GOT TO BE
SOMETHING WE CAN DO!
YEAH, GET BEATEN UP!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
HUH?
MM-HMM.
[ GRUNTS ]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
NO! COME BACK!
[ Echoing ]
PYRO SPHERE!
HAH!
[ Echoing ]
TERRIER TORNADO!
YOUR EFFORTS ARE FUTILE.
SURRENDER.
YOU CAN'T POSSIBLY WIN.
Terriermon: IF YOU THINK
WE'RE GONNA GIVE UP,
YOU GOT A MILLION THINKS
COMING!
PYRO SPHERE! HAH!
TERRIER TORNADO!
YOU ARE NOTHING MORE
THAN IRRITATING INSECTS.
YOUR POWERS ARE JUST
AS INSIGNIFICANT.
SURRENDER OR BE DESTROYED.
I DON'T SUPPOSE
THERE'S A THIRD CHOICE.
AAAAH!
GUILMON!
TERRIERMON!
AAAH!
[ SPLASHING ]
DO YOU SEE HOW FOOLISH IT IS
TODEFYME?
[ BOTH COUGHING ]
WE GOT TO SAVE TERRIERMON!
HUGELMON, PLEASE!
STOP THIS!
YOUR FATE IS SEALED!
[ PANTING ]
THESE TWO WILL BE
THE FIRST TO GO!
SAY GOODBYE TO YOUR FRIENDS!
PLEASE, DON'T!
IT JUST CAN'T END THIS WAY!
AND YET, IT WILL.
NO ONE WILL STOP
OUR DIGIVOLUTION.
BLAZING HELIX!
THEY'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO WITHSTAND THAT.
TAOMON, DO SOMETHING!
I'M SORRY, TAKATO.
NO!
LIGHTNING WHIP!
WHAT IS THIS?!
[ ELECTRICAL BUZZING ]
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
OH.
WHO DARES DEFY ME
IN MY OWN DOMAIN?
SHOW YOURSELF!
CEASE YOUR ATTACK,
HUGELMON!
[ ROARS ]
[ ALL GASP ]
Hugelmon: YOU?
WHAT DO YOU WANT WITH ME?
YOU'VE BEEN A FOOL,
HUGELMON!
WHAT?!
KAZU, WHAT'S THAT BIG
BLUE CLOUD?
OBVIOUSLY,
SOME KIND OF BLUE CLOUD.
AZULONGMON,
HE'S ONE OF THE FOUR SOVEREIGN.
I DON'T GET IT.
WHY'S HE FIGHTING HUGELMON?
GOOD QUESTION.
I HOPE THE TWO OF THEM
HAVEN'T DECIDED
TO JOIN FORCES.
THEY COULD FINISH US OFF
IN ONE SHOT.
OH, THAT'S JUST GREAT.
WE CAN'T EVEN BEAT
ONE SOVEREIGN.
WHY DON'T WE JUST FIGHT
ALL THE DIGIMON AT ONCE?
HOW DARE YOU!
THE HUMANS MAY COST US OUR ONE
CHANCE OF SURVIVAL.
BUT NOT ALL BELIEVE
AS YOU DO.
TERRIERMON,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
YOU GOT ME.
I ASK YOU TO PUT ASIDE
YOUR SENSELESS QUEST
TO DESTROY THE HUMANS.
SENSELESS?
THEY ARE AN INFECTION.
THEY MUST BE DESTROYED!
BLAZING HELIX!
[ GRUNTS ]
AURORA FORCE!
Humans: AW, NUTS!
DID HE SAVE US?
WHOA!
Kazu: WHOA!
SOMETHING BIG IS GOING DOWN!
Kenta: I HOPE THAT CLOUD
DOESN'T COME THIS WAY.
WHOA!
UGH.
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
TELL ME SOMETHING.
WHY ARE THEY FIGHTING?
AREN'T THEY BOTH SOVEREIGNS?
I GUESS EVEN THEY
HAVE DISAGREEMENTS.
YOU'RE NOT KIDDING!
ENOUGH!
THIS FIGHTING IS AS POINTLESS
AS YOUR VENDETTA
AGAINST THE HUMANS!
THE HUMANS ENDANGER
OUR FUTURE!
AND THEY DESTROYED
MY SERVANTS!
TRUE, BUT YOU SENT THE DEVAS
TO ATTACK THEM FIRST.
I DID IT TO PUSH FORWARD
OUR DIGIVOLUTION.
IF WE CAN OVERCOME THE HUMANS
AND THEIR SHACKLES,
THAN WE SHALL BECOME
POWERFUL ENOUGH
TO FIGHT OUR TRUE ENEMY.
YES, THAT IS ONE THEORY.
BUT SOME OF US BELIEVE
THAT IT'S OUR DIGIVOLUTION
ITSELF THAT'S LEFT US
VULNERABLE.
IF WE WISH TO DEFEAT
THE TRUE ENEMY,
WE'VE GOT TO STOP ADVANCING,
NOT DIGIVOLVE FURTHER.
THAT IS WHY YOU CHANGED
THE CATALYST
INTO THE FORM OF A DIGIMON --
TO HIDE IT.
IT WASN'T I.
HOWEVER,
IT WAS A WISE DECISION.
WHAT ARE THEY SAYING?
AND CAN'T THEY HURRY IT UP?
AZULONGMON IS TRYING TO CONVINCE
HUGELMON NOT TO DESTROY US.
SO I SAY,
GIVE HIM ALL THE TIME HE NEEDS.
YOU MEAN HE'S OUR ALLY?
WELL, IT SURE IS NICE TO KNOW
THAT THERE'S SOMEONE
WHO'S FINALLY ONOURSIDE.
WHO'S THIS TRUE ENEMY
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT?
I DON'T REALLY KNOW.
BUT SOME SAY
IT'S NOT EVEN A DIGIMON.
DOES THAT MEAN
IT'S A HUMAN?
NOT HUMAN, EITHER.
IT'S DIFFERENT
FROM THE DIGIGNOMES, TOO.
IT'S A BIG MYSTERY.
I ONLY HOPE WE'RE AROUND
TO SOLVE IT.
WHY WOULDN'T WE?
OH.
YOU'RE SO ARROGANT,
AZULONGMON!
YOU THINK YOU'RESOSUPERIOR,
BUT YOU'RE NO BETTER THAN ME.
YOU BURST INTOMYREALM
WITH YOUR HIGH-AND-MIGHTY STANCE
THAT YOU'RE RIGHT,
AND I'M WRONG.
BUT YOU DON'T HAVE ANYMORE PROOF
THAN I DO.
AND JUST WHAT HAVE YOUR IDEAS
GOTTEN YOU, HUGELMON?
THE CATALYST!
WOULD IT HAVE KILLED THEM
TO PUT IN AN ELEVATOR
WHEN THEY BUILT THIS?
OR AN ESCALATOR OR STAIRS
OR ANYTHING?
YOU'RE PLAYING A DANGEROUS GAME,
HUGELMON.
THIS IS NO GAME.
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
I WILL USE THE CATALYST
TO SAVE US!
OR A ROPE. UH!
AAH!
UH.
THEY USED THAT TERM
"CATALYST" AGAIN.
WE'RE SURE THAT'S CALUMON?
MM-HMM.
DIGIMON WERE MEANT TO BE FREE
FROM HUMANS.
IT IS OUR RIGHT.
IT IS OUR DESTINY.
NOW WHO'S BEING ARROGANT?
WHAT IF YOU'RE WRONG?
LOOK AT HOW POWERFUL
A CREATURE WAS CREATED
WHEN HUMANS AND DIGIMON
DIGIVOLVED TOGETHER?
MAYBE THAT IS OUR DESTINY.
MAYBE THAT'S WHAT WILL SAVE US
FROM OUR TRUE ENEMY.
I WON'T EVEN DISCUSS THAT
ABOMINATION.
I REFUSE TO BELIEVE
THAT IS THE ANSWER.
IT CAN'T BE.
ARE YOU SURE?
SURE ENOUGH TO RISK
THE EXISTENCE
OF THE ENTIRE DIGITAL WORLD?
YES. THE HUMANS
WILL BE OUR UNDOING.
[ GRUNTING ]
I SHOULD ENTR
THE RUN-SWIM-AND-GET-ME-ONP
TRIATHLON.
ENOUGH!
YOU'RE SO SURE
THAT YOU'RE RIGHT.
PROVE IT BY STOPPING ME,
IF YOU CAN.
BLAZING HELIX!
DON'T DO IT, HUGELMON,
[ Echoing ] PLEASE!
I'VE GOT
TO MAKE HIM UNDERSTAND.
TAKATO!
HE'S WRONG.
HUMANS AND DIGIMON
ARE MEANT TO FIGHT TOGETHER!
NO, TAKATO!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
[ GRUNTS ]
GUILMO-O-O-O-O-ON!
WHAT?
NOW WE'LL SEE.
COME ON, TAKATO.
YOU CAN DO IT.
[ Echoing ]
BIOMERGE ACTIVATE!
♪ DI, DI
GUILMON, BIOMERGE TO...
♪ DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI
♪ DI, DI, DIGIMON
GALLANTMON!
[ ROARING, GRUNTING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
AHH!
[ STRAINING, GRUNTING ]
THIS DIGIVOLUTION
IS POWERFUL.
Guilmon and Takato:
LIGHTNING JOLT! HAH!
BUTNOTPOWERFUL ENOUGH!
YOU, TOO, SHALL BE DEFEATED!
Takato: NOT UNTIL YOU SEE
THAT HUMANS AND DIGIMON
ARE MORE POWERFUL
WHEN THEY WORK TOGETHER!
[ GRUNTING ]
YOU'LL NEVER SURVIVE
THAT LONG!
PHOENIX FIRE!
Guilmon: WE WANT TO PROTECT
THIS WORLD AS MUCH AS YOU!
SPARE ME YOUR LIES!
I KNOW YOU ONLY WANT TO HELP
THE HUMANS
TAKE OVER
THE DIGITAL WORLD.
WELL, YOU SHALL NOT SUCCEED
AS LONG AS I LIVE!
Guilmon: BUT IT'S NOT A LIE.
SILENCE!
[ GRUNTS ]
AAH!
Takato: IF THE ONLY WAY TO MAKE
YOU BELIEVE IS TO DEFEAT YOU,
THEN SO BE IT!
AAAAAAAH!
HAH!
HAAAAAAAH!
I CANNOT ALLOW YOU
TO TAKE OVER MY WORLD!
Guilmon:
WE DON'T WANT TO.
Azulongmon: THAT'S ENOUGH!
HUH?
WHA?
THIS FIGHTING IS POINTLESS.
THE TRUE ENEMY IS WHAT WE SHOULD
BE FOCUSING OUR ENERGIES ON.
NOT EACH OTHER.
HUGELMON,
GIVE THE HUMANS A CHANCE.
THEY REALLY DO WISH TO HELP.
[ GROANS ]
Takato: THAT'S WHAT WE'VE BEEN
TRYING TO TELL YOU.
Ryo: THERE'S THE WHITE CASTLE.
WE MUST BE CLOSE.
GEE, I HOPE WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO GO AFTER BIOMON.
IT'D BE AWFULLY EMBARRASSING IF
WE ATTACKED THE WRONG GUY, HUH?
MAN, HE COULD BE ANYWHERE.
HE'S CLOSE.
I SENSE HIS PRESENCE.
YOU THINK HE'S IN THAT FOREST
DOWN THERE?
IF I FLY IN
AND KNOCK IT ALL DOWN,
WE'LL KNOW.
NO, IT MIGHT BE A TRAP.
[ GROWLING ]
WHAT IS IT?
THAT!
[ CRACKLING ]
HOLY COW!
[ Irish accent ]
WHY'D YOU HAVE TO WAKE ME?
I WAS HAVING THE NICEST DREAM!
WELL, MIGHT AS WELL
SEE WHO IT IS.
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
"EBONWUMON --
MEGABEAST DIGIMON."
HE'S ONE OF THE SOVEREIGN.
SO, EBONWUMON,
THIS LAND IS YOUR DOMAIN?
NOT BIOMON'S?
OH, IT'S BIOMON'S, ALL RIGHT.
I'M JUST WATCHING IT FOR HIM.
PSST. ASK HIM.
OKAY, OKAY,
MR. ERNEST O'EAGER.
HEY, DO YOU KNOW WHAT IT MEANS
WHEN YOU DREAM
YOU'RE RIDING IN A FOUNTAIN,
POURING A GLASS OF JUICE
AND GOING OVER A WATERFALL?
[ GROWLS ]
I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS TALKING.
IT'S TIME TO FIGHT.
LET'S LAY IT DOWN.
EASY THERE,
FIGHTY McBATTLE.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING TO GO UP
AGAINST THE CREATURE,
YOU'VE SENSE TO TAKE ME.
HE'S THATAWAY.
YEAH, YEAH.
GO ON AND CHECK IT OUT.
Ryo: WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I DON'T SEE ANYTHING.
OH!
AAH!
[ GRUMBLING ]
CAN YOU TELL WHAT'S
GOING ON?
[ GROWLING ]
THERE'S A GREAT BATTLE BETWEEN
BIOMON AND SOMETHING ELSE.
[ GROWLS ]
SOMETHING ELSE?
Ebonwumom:
HEY, ENTHUSIASTIC VAN EAGER,
LEAVE IT TO BIOMON.
YOU'D BE TOAST
IF YOU GET INVOLVED.
[ GROWLING ]
HE'S RIGHT.
YOU'D BE TOAST.
Kazu: GUARDROMON, YOU SURE
WEREN'T BUILT FOR COMFORT.
HEY, GUYS!
HI!
HUH?
ARE YOU A SIGHT
FOR SORE EYES!
YEAH, YOU TOO.
HOW YOU DOING, JERI?
ARE YOU OKAY?
MAYBE WE SHOULDN'T
HAVE COME HERE.
ALL WE'VE SEEN IS PAIN.
HUH?
I KNOW IT HURTS, JERI.
BUT WE HAVE TO BEAR THE PAIN
AND PRESS ON.
NOW,
WHO IS THIS TRUE ENEMY?
WE DON'T KNOW.
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW ITS NAME.
NONE OF US HAVE EVER
HAD CONTACT WITH IT.
WHATEVER IT CALLS ITSELF,
WEKNOWWHAT IT WANTS --
TO DESTROY US
AND THE DIGITAL WORLD.
WHERE DID IT COME FROM?
NO ONE IS SURE.
BUT IT'S BEEN HERE SINCE
THE FORMATION OF THIS WORLD.
LONG AGO, IT DISAPPEARED
AND HID ITSELF DEEP BENEATH
THE LAYERS OF THE DIGITAL WORLD.
BENEATH THE DIGITAL WORLD?
YES.
ALLOW ME TO SHOW YOU.
COOL! VISUALATE!
Kenta: AND YOU ALWAYS
MADE FUN OF ME
FOR MY LOVE
OF CHARTS AND GRAPHS.
NERDY IS AS NERDY DOES,
KENTA.
OH.
Azulongmon: IMAGINE THIS HOLE
AS THE REAL WORLD
SURROUNDED BY LAYERS
THAT MAKE UP THE DIGITAL WORLD.
IT'S SIX LAYERS DEEP.
THAT'S WHERE
YOU FIRST ARRIVED.
IN THE BEGINNING,
THIS IS ALL THERE WAS
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
IT WAS EMPTY, STARK,
INHOSPITABLE.
Kazu: JUST LIKE A PARTY
AT KENTA'S HOUSE.
Kenta: HEY!
Takato: GUYS,
LET'S NOT MAKE THE ULTRAPOWERFUL
DIGIMON ANGRY
BY INTERRUPTING HIM, OKAY?
SORRY.
Azulongmon:
ARE YOU FINISHED?
YES.
IT'S JUST...
KENTA!
THE EARLY DIGIMON,
OUR ANCESTORS,
LIVED ON THAT PHYSICAL LAYER
WITH THE DIGIGNOMES
AND THE TRUE ENEMY.
TALK ABOUT A FULL HOUSE.
IN THOSE EARLY DAYS,
THE TRUE ENEMY DESTROYED
MANY OF OUR ANCESTORS
AND DIGIGNOMES.
THOSE WERE DARK TIMES,
INDEED.
THERE SEEMED TO BE NO DEFENSE
AGAINST THE TRUE ENEMY.
NOTHING WAS ABLE TO STOP
ITS UNENDING DESTRUCTION.
IT SPREAD A DARK PALL
ACROSS THE DIGITAL WORLD.
Hugelmon: AND IT'S COME BACK
TO WIPE US OUT OF EXISTENCE.
IT IS OUR GREATEST FEAR.
Ryo: SEEMS TO HAVE
QUIETED DOWN, HUH?
SO WHY DOES THAT
ONLY MAKE ME MORE NERVOUS?
SOMETHING DANGEROUS
IS STILL DOWN THERE.
SOMETHING SO DANGEROUS
THAT WE CAN'T BEAT IT?
IF IT SCARES THE SOVEREIGN
THAT MUCH,
IT MIGHT BE SOMETHING
THAT NO ONE CAN BEAT.
Takato: SO WHY DID
THE TRUE ENEMY COME BACK NOW?
YOU'RE GETTING AHEAD
OF YOURSELF.
ONE DAY, THE TRUE ENEMY
JUST DISAPPEARED.
WITH THAT THREAT GONE,
THE DIGIMON BEGAN TO DIGIVOLVE.
NEW WORLDS WERE CREATED.
THOUGH THE PHYSICAL LAYER
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD
CONTINUED TO EXIST,
FEW LIVED THERE.
INSTEAD, WE DIGIMON EXPANDED
INTO NEW WORLDS.
FOR THE MOST PART,
WE LIVED IN PEACE AND HARMONY.
Kazu: MAN,
HOW COME WE HAVEN'T SEEN
ANY OF THAT PEACE
AND HARMONY?
WE SOVEREIGN DIGIMON
CREATED OUR OWN LEVEL
AND FOCUSED OUR EFFORTS
ON PROTECTING
THE REST OF THE DIGITAL WORLD.
BUT THE POWER WE ACHIEVED
AWOKE THE SLUMBERING TRUE ENEMY.
SO YOU SEE,
IT'S OUR OWN FAULT.
UNLESS WE CAN FIND A SOLUTION,
WE WILL BE THE CAUSE
OF OUR OWN DESTRUCTION.
[ RUMBLING ]
Ryo: MAYBE WE'LL GET TO SEE THIS
THING SOONER THAN WE THINK!
WHOA!
SOMETHING BIG IS GOING ON
IN THAT GORGE,
AND I WANNA KNOW WHAT!
ON SECOND THOUGHT,
MAYBE WE CAN JUST ASK AROUND
AND FIND OUT.
IT IS THE CATALYST THAT HAS
ALLOWED US TO DIGIVOLVE
BEYOND WHAT WE ONCE WERE.
SONIC ZEPHYR!
OOH! OOH!
Azulongmon: WE HAD TO CONVINCE
THE TRUE ENEMY
THAT WE WEREN'T DIGIVOLVING
TO THE POINT
WHERE IT WOULD BECOME
NECESSARY TO ELIMINATE US.
SO THE CATALYST WAS HIDDEN
IN THE FORM OF A DIGIMON.
[ GRUNTING ]
...OR A DUMBWAITER
OR A HOT-AIR BALLOON.
HECK, I'D TIE MYSELF TO A DUCK
IF HE COULD FLY ME OUT OF HERE.
BUT HOW?
YOU DON'T HAVE THAT KIND
OF POWER.
TRUE.
BUT SOMETHING ELSE DOES.
AH, RIGHT ON CUE.
THE DIGIGNOMES!
[ GNOMES CHATTERING ]
HEY! [ GIGGLES ]
NO WAY!
IT'S MR. MAZUNO!
I HEARD THERE WAS TROUBLE
IN THE LAND
OF THE DIGIMON SOVEREIGN,
AND I WANTED TO SEE IT
FOR MYSELF.
SO THE DIGIGNOMES WERE GRACIOUS
ENOUGH TO BRING ME HERE.
[ LAUGHS ]
HEY!
THEY HELPED AZULONGMON
AND MR. MAZUNO,
NOT TO MENTION ME AND HENRY.
IT'S LIKE THEY GRANT
WISHES OR SOMETHING.
Azulongmon: YES,
THAT'S A GOOD WAY OF PUTTING IT.
WHO IS THIS GUY?
HE'S A FRIEND
OF MY DAD'S.
HE'S HUMAN?
MR. MAZUNO?
DO YOU KNOW THE NAME OF THIS
TRUE ENEMY
THAT LIVED WITH THE DIGIMON
AND DIGIGNOMES
WHEN THE DIGITAL WORLD
WAS FIRST CREATED?
HMM?
Guilmon: LOOKS LIKE
A "YES" TO ME.
IT'S NAME...
D-REAPER.
D-REAPER?
YEAH,
BUT WHAT EXACTLY IS IT?
WHEN THE NETWORK
WAS FIRST CREATED,
A PROGRAM WAS DESIGNED
TO CONTROL THE GROWTH
OF ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE.
THE D-REAPER DELETED
ANY A.I. PROGRAMS
THAT EXCEEDED
THEIR ORIGINAL PARAMETERS.
I WOULD IMAGINE
THAT'S WHY THE SOVEREIGN
HAVE BEEN FIGHTING SO HARD
TO STOP ITS RETURN.
YEAH,
NO WONDER THEY FREAKED.
BUT THEY SHOULDN'T HAVE.
D-REAPER WAS
A RELATIVELY SIMPLE PROGRAM
WRITTEN TO DO ONLY ONE THING.
IT SHOULDN'T HAVE THE STRENGTH
TO DESTROY SUCH ADVANCED DIGIMON
AS THE SOVEREIGN.
UNLESS...
MAYBE IT'S MUTATED.
MUTATED?
IT GREW ANOTHER ARM
OR SOMETHING?
I THINK IT MUST'VE INCORPORATED
THE DATA OF WHAT IT DEVOURED
AND LEARNED TO USE IT.
WHICH MEANS THE D-REAPER
MAY HAVE DIGIVOLVED
PAST THE DIGIMON
AND IS MORE POWERFUL
THAN THEY ARE.
TERRIFIC.
WHAT'S THE BAD NEWS?
[ Echoing ]
MR. MAZUNO?
NOT YET!
PLEASE, NOT YET!
I HAVEN'T FINISHED.
[ ALL GASP ]
WHERE'D HE GO?
I DON'T KNOW.
MR. MAZUNO?
Kenta: WHAT IF THE D-REAPER
GOT TO HIM?
Ryo: THERE'S GOT TO BE A WAY
TO FIND OUT
WHAT'S IN THAT CHASM.
WHAT IF WHATEVER'S
IN THE DARKNESS
IS JUST TRYING TO LURE US IN
WITH THAT LIGHT SHOW?
YOU KNOW, I'M REALLY TEMPTED
TO GO EXPLORING.
[ GROWLS ]
I GUESS WE SHOULDN'T.
I FEEL SO POWERLESS.
[ GROWLS ]
Ebonwumon: BETTER TO FEEL
POWERLESS THAN TO FEEL DEAD,
MR. IRATE McANGRY.
[ GROWLS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THERE REALLY IS A TOP.
THOSE LOOK PRETTY DANGEROUS...
WHAT IF THE D-REAPER
IS UNSTOPPABLE?
...MAYBE MORE DANGEROUS
'CAUSE THEY'RE PRETTY!
MAYBE YOU SHOULD JUST TUNE
INTO THE NEXT
"DIGIMON DIGITAL MONSTERS."
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI, DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI, DI
♪ DI, DI