TAKATO AND THE GANG STUMBLD
INTO A FORGOTTEN LITTLE TOWN
THAT WAS BEING TERRORIZED Y
THIS DERANGED MOTORCYCLE.
WHEN IT ATTACKED, LEOMON CAME
TO THE RESCUE
BEFORE ONE OF THE CHUCHIDARUMON
GOT MOWED DOWN.
GUILMON AND TAKATO TRIED TO
HELP THE LITTLE DUDES OUT,
BUT WHEN GUILMON JUMPED
ON THE BIKE,
THE MACHINE ENDED UP
CONTROLLING HIM!
THANK GOODNESS LEOMON WAS THERE
TO BREAK THE SPELL.
MEANWHILE, IMPMON MADE A PACT
WITH THE DOG DEVA CHATSURAMON
IN ORDER TO FINALLY DIGIVOLV.
HE WENT INTO THE LAVA A ROOKIE,
BUT CAME OUT A MEGA DIGIMO.
SAY HELLO TO BEELZEBUMON.
♪ DI, DI, DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI, DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI, DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE WORLD
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS.
DIGIMODIFY.
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON!
Rika:
WELL, THIS IS JUST GREAT.
HOW MUCH LONGER DO WE HAVE TO
WAIT BEFORE SOMETHING HAPPENS?
I WONDER WHERE THEY ARE --
NOT THAT I KNOW WHERE WE ARE.
SO MUCH FOR YOUR IDEA
THAT WE'D FIND THEM IF WE JUST
WAITED HERE.
I SAID WE MIGHT FIND THEM
HERE -- MIGHT, MIGHT.
"MIGHT, MIGHT" --
THE ONLY THING I FOUND
IS SAND IN MY UNDERWEAR.
I MIGHT AS WELL BE WEARING
SANDPAPER SHORTS.
OH, GEE, THAT'S NEW --
THE WIND IS BLOWING.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M LOOKING AROUND.
WHAT? WHERE YOU GONNA GO?
WHAT IF TAKATO AND THEM COME BY?
WE'LL HAVE TO GO OUT LOOKING
FOR YOU, THEN, WON'T WE?
WELL?
ALL RIGHT,
SO IT'S NOT A PERFECT PLAN,
BUT I DON'T SEE YOU COMING UP
WITH ANYTHING BETTER.
BUT WE THOUGHT OF THE
SITTING-STILL IDEA.
YEAH, THAT'S BEEN WORKING
LIKE A CHARM SO FAR.
LOOK, JUST STAY HERE
AND SIT ON YOUR BRAINS
UNTIL I GET BACK, OKAY?
YEAH? WELL, WE WILL.
YEAH? WELL, GOOD.
THAT'S SURE PUTTING HER
IN HER PLACE.
MAKE SURE YOU DON'T LEAVE
IN CASE THE OTHERS COME BY.
DID YOU SEE HOW THEY LOOKED
AT EACH OTHER
LIKE THEY WERE TALKING WITHOUT
REALLY SPEAKING?
YOU'RE PARANOID.
'CAUSE EVERYONE'S AGAINST ME.
I'M NOT AGAINST YOU.
YOU'RE NOT HELPING, EITHER.
MAN, IT FEELS LIKE WE'VE BEEN
WALKING FOR DAYS.
[ SNIFFING ]
SMELLS LIKE IT, TOO.
PHEW.
I JUST WISH WE HAD
A BETTER IDEA
OF WHERE TO START LOOKING FOR
RIKA AND THE OTHERS.
MOMENTI!
IF WE'RE MEANT TO FIND THEM,
WE WILL, RIGHT?
I SURE HOPE THAT RIKA AND THE
OTHERS ARE ALL RIGHT, THOUGH.
THEY COULD BE ANYWHERE.
THOSE STREAMS OF DATA SEND YOU
TO A DIFFERENT PLACE EVERY TIME.
YEAH, BUT IT ONLY MATTERS THAT
THEY'RE SAFE.
EVEN IF WE WERE WITH THEM,
THEY STILL MIGHT NOT BE SAFE,
BECAUSE WE ATTRACT TROUBLE
LIKE A MAGNET.
HEY, RELAX ALREADY.
MAYBE THEY'RE WAITING BACK BY
TAKATO'S GOOFY FLAG.
YEAH. MAYBE THEY ARE.
TERRIERMON'S RIGHT.
LET'S GO TAKE A LOOK.
IS THERE ANYTHING BUT SAND AND
WIND IN THIS STUPID WORLD?
ROCKS.
HELPFUL AS ALWAYS, RENAMON.
REMIND ME TO GET YOU A STAND-UP
COMEDIAN UPGRADE CARD
WHEN WE GET HOME.
LET'S GO.
STUPID SANDY WIND -- BLECH!
SHOOT. THEY'RE NOT HERE.
Guilmon: NOT UNLESS THEY'RE
PLAYING HIDE-AND-SEEK WELL.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
WE'LL NEVER FIND THEM LIKE THIS.
WE SHOULD SPLIT UP
AND GO LOOKING FOR THEM.
I DON'T KNOW.
THEN WE'D ALL BE LOST.
WELL, WE'VE GOT TO DO
SOMETHING
INSTEAD OF JUST
WANDERING AROUND
AND HOPING WE RUN INTO THEM.
IT DOES SEEM KIND OF POINTLESS.
IF ONLY WE HAD SOME CLUES.
[ SNIFFS ]
WHAT IS IT, BOY?
HMM. [ SNIFFING ]
I SMELL RENAMON.
YOU DO?
AND SHE WAS HERE
JUST A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
[ SNIFFING ]
I THINK SHE WENT
OVER THAT WAY. YEAH.
WHAT IS --
AND I THOUGHT
GUILMON WAS WEIRD. LOOK.
I THINK TERRIERMON IS PRACTICING
TO BE A MIME.
IT WOULD NEVER WORK. HE'D
HAVE TO BE QUIET TO BE A MIME.
Kenta: YOU CAN'T EAT SAND.
Kazu: WHAT ABOUT A SANDWICH?
Rika:
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
WHAT?
WASN'T THAT KAZU'S VOICE?
HMM. IT COULD HAVE BEEN.
WHAT PART OF "STAY HERE"
DIDN'T THEY UNDERSTAND?
I TOLD YOU WE SHOULD
HAVE GONE THE OTHER DIRECTION.
NO, I SAID WE SHOULD
GO THE OTHER DIRECTION.
THEN WHY'D YOU LISTEN TO ME?
YOU NEVER LISTEN TO ME.
I HAVE NEVER MET TWO MORE
USELESS GUYS.
Kazu:
I'M NOT GONNA CARRY YOU.
EVEN THE DEVAS WERE
MORE HELPFUL.
AHH.
HEY, WE THOUGHT WE'D COME
AND HELP YOU.
[ SCOFFS ]
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
TO WAIT BY THE FLAG.
YEAH, BUT RIGHT AFTER YOU LEFT,
WE KIND OF GOT TO THINKING
YOU MIGHT NEED OUR HELP IF YOU
RAN INTO TROUBLE.
WHY WOULD I --
OH, DIDN'T YOU GUYS THINK --
OHH! FORGET IT.
LET'S JUST GO BACK.
SO SOON?
TAKATO AND THE OTHERS MAY HAVE
COME BACK TO WHERE THE FLAG IS.
THAT WOULD BE JUST AWESOME.
USELESS.
RIKA, ANOTHER DATA STREAM
IS COMING.
YOU'RE RIGHT -- WE'D BETTER GET
OUT OF HERE QUICK
BEFORE IT CARRIES US OFF
TO WHO KNOWS WHERE.
COME ON. LET'S GO.
HEY, WHAT'S THE RUSH?
YEAH, WE'VE GOT PLENTY OF TIME.
IT'S MILES AWAY.
HUH?
WHOA!
WHOA! WHOA!
Rika: MILES, HUH?
Kenta: MAYBE LESS.
THAT'S ABOUT AS MUCH FUN
AS A KICK IN THE HEAD.
NOW I KNOW WHAT
A PRETZEL FEELS LIKE.
WHERE ARE WE, ANYWAY?
INSIDE SOME
WEIRD GIANT CLOCK?
REGARDLESS, WE'RE NOT ANY CLOSER
TO FINDING THE OTHERS,
AND IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE THERE'S
AN EASY WAY OUT OF HERE.
MAYBE IT'S A GRANDFATHER CLOCK,
AND IF WE FIND THE GRANDFATHER,
HE'LL TAKE US OUT.
DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
IT'S A GIANT'S WRISTWATCH.
OHH!
I'M RIDICULOUS NOW?
FACE IT -- YOU WERE ALWAYS
RIDICULOUS.
QUIET!
HUH?
I AM SO SICK AND TIRED
OF YOUR AWFUL SUGGESTIONS!
HAVE EITHER OF YOU EVER HAD
A GOOD IDEA?!
UH... UH...
WELL, ONCE.
THE TWO MOST USELESS PEOPLE
ALIVE, AND I'M THE BABYSITTER
PUTTING EVERYTHING BACK TOGETHER
WHEN YOU MESS IT UP!
WHY'D IT HAVE TO BE ME?!
HEY, YOU THINK THIS IS ALL FUN
AND GAMES FOR US?
YOU THINK WE ENJOY
YOUR SNOTTY ATTITUDE
AND YOUR TALKING
BEHIND OUR BACKS?!
HMPH.
[ MECHANICAL TICKING ]
WHAT IS THAT TICKING?
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE THIS REALLY IS A CLOCK.
MAYBE IT'S A BOMB, BUT I GUESS
YOU CAN HANDLE THAT YOURSELF.
WELL, IF YOU WANTED TO HELP,
YOU COULD.
IF WE HAVE TO.
MM-HMM.
HEY, LOOK.
IT IS A CLOCK.
Kazu: YEAH,
AND NOT A VERY GOOD ONE.
THAT'S HOW THE CLOCK ALWAYS
LOOKS TO ME IN MATH CLASS.
I THINK THE SECOND
HAND'S JUST STUCK.
SHOULD WE UNSTICK IT?
MIGHT AS WELL, OTHERWISE, THIS
TICKING IS GONNA DRIVE ME CRAZY!
NO, STOP!
HUH?
[ CLOCK CHIMES ]
OH, MOST HORRIBIMINABLE!
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?!
FIXED IT.
OH, TRAGEDOUS!
OKAY. WHO THE HECK
ARE THESE GUYS?
Rika: THE TALL ONE'S CLOCKMON --
CHAMPION LEVEL --
SPECIAL ATTACK --
TEMPUS FUGIT.
THE OTHER GUY IS HAGURUMON --
ROOKIE LEVEL --
SPECIAL ATTACK --
COG CRUSHER.
CLOCKMON?
HAGURUMON?
THIS IS NOT GONNA BE GOOD!
GET READY!
HERE IT COMES!
WELL, MAYBE NOT.
CUCKOO! CUCKOO!
[ GULPS ] [ GULPS ]
YAAH! YAAH!
YAAH! YAAH!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
IS IT AN EARTHQUAKE?
WHOA-OA! AHH!
WE'LL NEVER MAKE IT HOME!
OH. WELL, THAT WASN'T SO BAD,
NOW, WAS IT?
ALL THE GEAR HAS STOPPED.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHEN THE GEARS ARE MOVING,
EVERYTHING'S SUPERPERFECTIONAL,
BUT WHEN THEY AREN'T...
AHHH! AHHH!
AHHH! AHHH!
[ RUMBLING ]
[ ROARING ]
GOOD GRAVY!
[ ROARING CONTINUES ]
Rika: MEGADRAMON --
A VIRUS DRAGON DIGIMON.
UH-OH. HE'S ULTIMATE LEVEL.
SPECIAL ATTACKS ARE PARRY FORCE
AND DARKSIDE ATTACK.
HE LOOKS TOUGH.
[ GROWLS ]
WHY IS HE LOOKING
AT RIKA?
THAT CAN'T BE GOOD.
I MUST PROTECT MY TAMER.
[ GROWLS ]
A TAMER?! WOW!
YOU'RE KIDDING!
THAT MEANS SHE'S BEEN TO THE
REAL WORLD BEFORE!
OH, WHAT I WOULDN'T GIVE TO HAVE
THE CHANCE TO SEE THAT WORLD.
IT WOULD BE FABULOUS.
IT WOULD BE WONDERFUL!
WELL, IT'D BE OKAY,
I GUESS.
YOU'VE BEEN THERE --
REALLY AND TRUTHFULINGUSLY?
I HAVE.
MOST MAGNIFLUENT --
IT'S SAID THAT IF YOU LOAD
THE DATA OF A DIGIMON
WHO HAS A TAMER,
YOU'LL GAIN THE POWER TO GO
TO THE REAL WORLD!
THAT'S WHY MEGADRAMON'S
INTERESTED IN YOUR TAMER.
HE'S A SCOUNDREL!
HE'S A BEAST!
HE'S NOT ALL BAD, I GUESS.
THAT'S ABSURD.
IT TAKES MORE THAN JUST DATA TO
GET TO THE REAL WORLD.
HE'LL NEVER LOAD YOUR
DATA, RENAMON.
YOU'RE A WAY BETTER
FIGHTER THAN HIM!
NOW, SIC HIM!
AS YOU WISH.
[ GRUNTS ]
I'M ALMOST FRIGHTENED
OF THIS.
NO!
DIGIMODIFY.
DIGIMODIFY!
DIGIVOLUTION, ACTIVATE!
DIGIVOLUTION.
RENAMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
...KYUBIMON.
WOW, A DIGIVOLUTION --
IT'S AMAZING! IT'S INCREDIBLE!
IT'S OKAY, I GUESS.
I'VE NEVER SEEN IT BEFORE.
[ PANTING ]
I WANT TO DIGIVOLVE
LIKE THAT, TOO.
FOX TAIL INFERNO!
PARRY FORCE!
NO! LOOK OUT!
MY BEST GEAR!
YOU'RE INJURED AND DAZED!
AH, YOU'RE OKAY.
[ ROARING ]
JEEZ, LOUISE!
DRAGON WHEEL!
DARKSIDE ATTACK!
KYUBIMON!
NO!
[ PANTING ]
[ GROWLING ]
WHO THE HECK IS THAT GUY?!
HE ROCKS!
CYBERDRAMON --
ANOTHER ULTIMATE --
SPECIAL ATTACK --
DESOLATION CLAW.
WELL, HE'D BETTER
USE IT SOON.
[ CHUCKLING ]
GOOD TRY...
BUT NOT GOOD ENOUGH!
[ GROWLING ]
DESOLATION CLAW!
WHOA.
CYBERDRAMON, BACK OFF!
WHAT?
THAT'S NOT THE OPPONENT
WE'RE LOOKING FOR.
Kazu: WHO'S THAT?
Kenta: YEAH.
AND WHO'S HE LOOKING FOR?
Hagurumon:
IT'S RYO, OUR PROTECTORLY GUY.
IT'S HIM.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE'S HER!
CYBERDRAMON,
WHAT DID I SAY?!
DESOLATION CLAW!
SO, IT'S TO BE
THE HARD WAY, IS IT?
Kenta: WHAT'S HE GONNA DO?
Kazu: I DON'T KNOW, BUT I'M
GONNA STICK AROUND TO FIND OUT.
CYBERDRAMON, OBEY!
[ SNARLS ]
STOP IT! YOU WILL OBEY ME,
CYBERDRAMON!
[ GROWLING ]
FINALLY.
HE DOESN'T EVEN REMEMBER ME.
[ EXHALES ]
HUH?
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
UH.
THE NAME'S RYO.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
DOESN'T SPEAK MUCH,
DOES SHE?
HELLO?
I'M RIKA, AND THIS IS
KYUBIMON.
YOU'RE LUCKY
HE DIDN'T HURT YOU.
HMM?
YOU HAVE TO BE CAREFUL
AROUND HERE, YOU KNOW.
SOME DIGIMON BELIEVE THE DATA
FROM A DIGIMON WITH A TAMER
WILL GET THEM INTO
THE REAL WORLD.
YEAH,
WE ALREADY KNEW THAT.
OH, UH, SORRY.
JUST TRYING TO GIVE
YOU GUYS SOME HELP.
RYO!
HAGURUMON'S NOT MOVING!
WELL, LET'S SEE WHAT
WE CAN DO TO HELP.
OH. IT SEEMS
YOU'RE MISSING A GEAR.
HERE YOU GO.
MAGNIFLUENT!
HEY, NO PROBLEM. I'M HAPPY TO
HELP OUT WHERE I CAN.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THIS GUY?
THERE'S STILL ONE LITTLE
PROBLEM THAT HASN'T BEEN SOLVED.
OH, NO! IT'LL BE THE END OF US!
IT'LL BE TRAGIC!
AH, I GUESS IT WON'T
BE THAT BAD.
DON'T WORRY --
I'M ON TOP OF IT.
[ GEARS GRINDING,
CLOCK TICKING ]
HE DID IT! WE'RE SAFE!
WELL, I GUESS IT WASN'T THAT BIG
A DEAL AFTER ALL.
GREAT. EVERYTHING'S SET.
THANKS, RYO.
PLEASE. I'M GLAD TO DO IT.
LET ME KNOW IF YOU NEED
ANYTHING ELSE.
OKAY.
THANKS, RYO. WE WILL.
UM, WAS THERE SOMETHING
ELSE, GUYS?
RYO, DO YOU THINK
THAT MAYBE SOMEDAY
I'LL BE ABLE TO GO
TO THE REAL WORLD?
SURE. JUST KEEP DREAMING, AND
YOU CAN MAKE ANYTHING HAPPEN.
A-AND MAYBE I'LL
GET A TAMER LIKE YOU?
YOU BET, BUDDY.
OF COURSE YOU WILL.
OH, MOST OUTSTANDISH!
I'M GONNA WORK OUT,
EAT A LOT,
AND OIL MY GEARS
EVERY DAY.
AND I'LL SEE YOU
IN THE REAL WORLD.
YOUR TAMER'S
THE BESTINGEST.
SEE YOU LATER, GUYS.
I THINK RYO LIKES ME.
HE LOVES YOU, HE ADORES YOU,
BUT I THINK HE LIKES ME BEST.
YOU'RE JUST JEALOUSEASONAL.
What's with this guy?
Stupid perfect hairdo, stupid
perfect teeth,
always knowing just the perfect
thing to say,
even though
he's probably lying.
He really bugs me.
YOU THINK IT IS?
UM, MR. RYOS, SIR --
GUYS, YOU CAN
JUST CALL ME "RYO."
WE CAN CALL HIM RYO!
RYO AKIYAMA?
UM, YEAH.
YEAH!
UH, WHAT'S WRONG?
[ GROWLS ]
WAIT UNTIL THE GUYS AT HOME
HEAR THAT WE GOT TO FIGHT
ALONGSIDE RYO AKIYAMA!
HE'S WON EVERY DIGIMON
TOURNAMENT THERE EVER WAS.
I'M GONNA BE THE MOST POPULAR
KID IN SCHOOL!
HEY, IT'S NICE
TO MEET YOU, TOO.
I HAVEN'T SEEN OTHER KIDS SINCE
I CAME TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
IT GETS KIND OF LONELY.
WELL, YOU'LL HAVE PLENTY
OF COMPANY NOW,
'CAUSE IT'S NOT JUST US --
OUR FRIENDS ARE HERE SOMEWHERE
IN THIS WORLD, TOO.
Terriermon: UNLESS YOU WERE
FOLLOWING THE SMELL
OF BIG BLOCKS OF STONE,
YOU REALLY MESSED UP.
Guilmon: I CAN'T HELP IT.
THE SCENT DISAPPEARS HERE.
Takato: GREAT.
HOW ARE WE EVER GONNA FIND THEM?
Henry: THEY PROBABLY GOT SUCKED
UP BY ANOTHER DATA STREAM.
Jeri: MAYBE THEY'RE EXPLORING
THAT CAVE.
IT WOULDN'T HURT TO LOOK.
IT MIGHT.
SURE IS CREEPY.
THAT'S NOT CREEPY --
IT'S REALLY, REALLY FRIGHTENING.
SMELL ANYTHING,
GUILMON?
LOTS OF STUFF.
OH, YOU MEAN RENAMON? NO.
WHAT IS THAT?
BEATS ME. [ SNIFFING ]
CHECK IT OUT.
IS IT DANGEROUS, GUILMON?
NO, I THINK IT'S OKAY.
IS THIS EVEN STONE?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
IT'S SO SMOOTH.
YEAH. HEY, JERI,
I'M REALLY SORRY ABOUT DRAGGING
YOU INTO ALL OF THIS.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME? THIS IS SO
GREAT! I'M LEOMON'S TAMER!
[ LAUGHS ]
AHH!
GUYS,
WOULD YOU KNOCK IT OFF?
WE REALLY SHOULDN'T
MESS WITH THIS
UNTIL WE FIGURE OUT
WHAT IT IS.
HEY, THAT LOOKS LIKE FUN.
COME ON, LEOMON.
DON'T BE SHY.
HUH? I'M NOT.
HEY, THIS KIND OF FEELS
LIKE BEING IN AN ELEVATOR,
DOESN'T IT?
ELEVATOR?! ELEVATOR?!
AHHH! AHHH!
Takato: THAT'S OVER.
AAHHH! AAHHH!
WHOA! WHOA!
WHOA! WHOA!
FASTER, FASTER!
WHEN WE FIND
WHAT THE SOVEREIGN SEEKS,
YOU AND I WILL BE REWARDED
BEYOND OUR WILDEST DREAM...
AND SEVERELY PUNISHED
IF WE DO NOT.
TAKATO'S FLAG.
OH, THEY MUST BE NEARBY.
THEY SURE CAPTURED
RIKA'S SCOWL.
THEN AGAIN, I DON'T KNOW IF I'VE
SEEN HER ANY OTHER WAY.
MAYBE I CAN MAKE HER
LOOK HAPPIER.
[ LAUGHING ]
WHOA! UGH!
I GUESS THE WIND WANTS HER TO
STAY ALL SCOWLY.
HEY, I CAN USE THIS
TO SHOW OTHER DIGIMON WHAT MY
FRIENDS LOOK LIKE.
[ Straining ]
TRY TO STOP ME NOW, WIND!
WHOA!
WELL, I HOPE WE FIND YOUR
FRIENDS SOON.
YEAH, ME TOO.
BUT FIRST WE HAVE TO FIND US.
WE KEEP GETTING LOST.
[ CHUCKLES ]
SO, HOW LONG HAVE YOU
BEEN HERE ANYWAY, RYO?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT MONTH IS IT?
OCTOBER.
WOW. I DIDN'T REALIZE
I'D BEEN HERE SO LONG.
IT MUST BE SO COOL
TO BE ON YOUR OWN --
NO CHORES OR HOMEWORK --
I'D BE IN HEAVEN!
WHY? YOU ALWAYS MAKE ME DO
ALL YOUR CHORES
AND HOMEWORK, ANYWAY.
Don't embarrass me
in front of the Ryoman.
IT DOES GET LONELY, THOUGH.
WHY'D YOU COME HERE, RYO?
'CAUSE OF THIS GUY.
HE'S HARD TO CONTROL.
HE'S NOT REALLY THE
KIND OF DIGIMON
YOU'D TAKE TO, LIKE,
A BIRTHDAY PARTY,
UNLESS YOU WANTED HIM
TO SMASH THE CAKE,
BREAK ALL THE PRESENTS,
AND BLOW UP THE HOUSE.
BUT SOMEONE'S GOT TO
KEEP HIM IN LINE.
COOL. IT'S LIKE SUMMER CAMP,
BUT INSTEAD OF LEARNING
ARTS AND CRAFTS,
YOU LEARN BUTT-KICKOLOGY.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
SO, SOME STUPID KID
FELL INTO THE DIGITAL WORLD
AND CAN'T GET OUT.
I BET HE WANTS TO GO HOME
TO HIS MOMMY,
BUT HE CAN'T FIGURE IT OUT --
SOME HERO.
RIKA!
YOUNG LADY,
I AM NOT ABOUT TO STAND BY AND
LET YOU BAD-MOUTH
THE COOLEST GUY
IN TWO WORLDS.
WHAT ARE YOU
GONNA DO ABOUT IT?
OH, WELL, I JUST --
DON'T LISTEN TO HER, RYO.
SHE'S JUST UPSET YOU BEAT HER IN
THAT DIGIMON TOURNAMENT.
YEAH, YOU BLEW AWAY
THE DIGIMON QUEEN!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YOU MAKE IT SOUND LIKE I'M
WEAKER THAN HIM, WHICH I'M NOT.
YOU'RE JUST UPSET WITH RYO
BECAUSE YOU CAME IN SECOND,
BUT IT'S NOT HIS FAULT
YOU PLAYED BADLY.
KAZU!
YOU DIDN'T MAKE IT PAST THE
THIRD ROUND OF THAT TOURNAMENT.
YOU TALK BIG,
BUT YOU WOULDN'T EVEN KNOW WHAT
TO DO WITH A DIGIMON
EVEN IF YOU COULD GET ONE,
WHICH YOU CAN'T!
OKAY. RELAX.
I DO REMEMBER YOU.
WELL, GEE, THANKS.
THAT MEANS SO MUCH TO ME,
OH, GREAT ONE.
YOU WERE GOOD.
STILL AM.
Kazu: AREN'T YOU
FORGETTING SOMETHING?
HE DID SAVE KYUBIMON TODAY,
YOU KNOW.
WE WOULD HAVE BEEN IN SERIOUS
TROUBLE WITHOUT HIM.
I DON'T REMEMBER ASKING
FOR HERO BOY'S HELP.
LISTEN, IT JUST LOOKED LIKE YOU
WERE IN TROUBLE, SO I --
YEAH, WELL, I WASN'T.
SO, I TAKE IT YOU GUYS DON'T
KNOW HOW TO GET OUT OF HERE?
NO. KENTA DOESN'T REALLY KNOW
MUCH OF ANYTHING.
HEY, CHEAP SHOT.
YOU NOTICE
HE DOESN'T DENY IT?
I CAN GET YOU HOME,
BUT YOU HAVE TO GO THROUGH
ANOTHER DIMENSION FIRST.
WE HAVE TO FIND OUR
OTHER FRIENDS.
I CAN HELP WITH THAT, TOO.
IT'S NICE TO MEET NEW PEOPLE,
MAKE NEW FRIENDS --
WELL, SOMETIMES.
HMPH.
WE GET TO TRAVEL WITH
THE RYO AKIYAMA.
ISN'T THAT AWESOME, KENTA?!
YEAH. UH, IS THAT OKAY
WITH YOU, RIKA?
I DON'T SEE WHY WE NEED
THIS GUY AT ALL.
HOW DO WE KNOW THERE'S NO DIRECT
WAY TO THE REAL WORLD?
I BET THERE IS, AND HE JUST
DOESN'T EVEN KNOW IT.
WHY WOULD I LIE ABOUT THAT?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT I'M NOT
STICKING AROUND TO FIND OUT.
KYUBIMON.
UH, WHAT DID I DO
TO GET HER SO UPSET?
WHO KNOWS?
SHE'S WEIRD -- ALWAYS CALLING US
"STUPID" AND STUFF.
SHE THINKS SHE'S BETTER.
YOU'RE ALWAYS CALLING
MSTUPID.
THAT'S DIFFERENT.
IS SHE GONNA BE OKAY?
IT'S TOUGH TO SAY. THERE'S A LOT
OF DANGEROUS STUFF THERE.
ONE MISSTEP,
AND SHE'S IN TROUBLE.
MAN, I THOUGHT THESE GUYS WEE
SUPPOSED TO FIND EACH OTHE,
NOT SPLIT UP EVEN MORE!
SO, SEE IF THEY GET BACK
TOGETHER
ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS"