TAKATO AND GUILMON WERE
TAKING ON DARK LIZARDMON
WHEN YAMAKI SHOWED UP
WITH THE BOYS FROM HYPNOS
AND CUT THE BATTLE SHORT.
THEY TOOK DARK LIZARDMON
BACK TO THE LAB
TO RUN ALL THESE CREEPY TESTS
ON HER,
AND IT LOOKS LIKE SHE'LL ONLY BE
THE FIRST
IN A LONG LINE
OF DOOMED DIGIMON.
THEN HENRY'S DAD GOT A VISITOR
FROM HIS PAST.
I WONDER WHAT HE HAS TO DO
WITH ALL THIS.
YAMAKI FINALLY GOT APPROVAL
FROM THE DUDES UPSTAIRS
TO USE THIS PROGRAM
CALLED JUGGERNAUT
TO CONTROL THE SUPPOSED
DIGI-INFESTATION.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT MEANS,
BUT IT SURE DOESN'T SOUND GOOD.
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
♪ WORLD
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMODIFY
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
[ PANTING ]
LEAVE ME ALONE! AAH!
WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME,
YOU BIG BULLY?
NOTHING, PALLY,
JUST YOUR DATA.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
[ ALL GASP ]
MUST...GO...NOW.
HEY, TERRIERMON,
ARE YOU OKAY?
MOVE!
OUT OF MY WAY!
HMM.
WHOA, IT LOOKS LIKE
THE SKY'S ON FIRE.
GOODBYE.
BEASTS OF MAYHEM,
TIME TO GO AWAY.
THE WORLD WILL SOON BE FREE
OF THIS HIDEOUS PESTILENCE
FOREVER.
[ CHUCKLES EVILLY ]
WELL, LOOK WHO'S COME
TO MARVEL AT MY BRILLIANCE.
HURRY!
I AM.
COME ON.
WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
ABOUT TIME.
UH-OH.
THIS DOESN'T LOOK GOOD.
WHAT'S THAT?
AAH!
HUH?
[ CHUCKLES EVILLY ]
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
GUILMON, THEY'RE ALL LEAVING.
TAKATO.
HUH?
[ CHUCKLES ]
HEY, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU DON'T LOOK SO GOOD,
BUDDY.
THANKS A LOT,
BUT ACTUALLY,
I AM FEELING WEIRD.
GUILMON!
UM, HEY, ARE YOU
MOPING OR SOMETHING?
THIS IS BAD.
IT'S LIKE SOME HUGE
DIGIMON VACUUM CLEANER.
WHAT -- WHAT IS HAPPENING?
[ SCREAMING ]
[ WAILS ]
THAT SOUND --
MAKE IT STOP!
HOLD ON. IT'LL BE OVER
IN ABOUT 80 SECONDS.
WE HAVE TO FINISH THIS.
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING?
WE HAD NO OTHER CHOICE.
HUH?
LET'S JUST SAY WE'RE
CONTROLLING AN INFESTATION.
ALL VERMIN MUST GO.
BUT YOU CAN'T JUST
DESTROY ALL THE DIGIMON.
GUILMON'S
MY BEST FRIEND.
REALLY?
THIS FOUL BEAST?
[ GROWLS ]
HMM. YOU NAIVE LITTLE BOY.
THIS THING ISN'T CAPABLE
OF FRIENDSHIP.
IT'S NOTHING MORE THAN A
DANGEROUS ARTIFICIAL LIFE FORM.
WAIT A MINUTE.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
DIGIMON ARE --
WELL, THEY'RE COOL,
THAT'S ALL,
AND THIS ONE HAPPENS
TO BE MY BEST FRIEND.
LOTS OF THEM
ARE FRIENDLY!
HEY, ARE YOU LISTENING?
TAKATO...
HUH?
IT'S COMING.
WHAT IS?
[ SCREAMING ]
[ BEEPING ]
AN ANOMALY HAS INFILTRATED
THE JUGGERNAUT.
IT'S COMING THROUGH
THE VORTEX.
WHAT? BUT --
BUT THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
THIS PROGRAM IS FLAWLESS.
I DESIGNED IT MYSELF.
NOTHING CAN GET THROUGH THERE.
THIS CANNOT BE HAPPENING.
WHAT HAVE I DONE?!
[ SCREAMING ]
WARNING --
VORTEX BREACH IMMINENT.
2 OUTS, AND THE BASES LOADED.
THIS COULD BE IT.
OOH, THERE WON'T BE
ANY STEALING TODAY.
HUH?
AND HERE WE GO AGAIN.
HUMANS CREATED US,
BUT NOW WE ARE FREE.
THE TIME HAS COME
TO CLAIM OUR PLACE
IN THE REAL WORLD.
YOU HAVE BUT ONE PURPOSE --
TO SERVE THE DIGIMON.
NO, YOU'RE WRONG.
WHO ARE YOU?
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
I AM ONLY A REPRESENTATIVE
OF THOSE
WHO ARE TO BE YOUR MASTERS.
I CAN'T LET YOU DO THIS!
I WILL NEVER BE A SERVANT
TO ANY OF YOU DATA SCUM!
IT'S BECAUSE OF YOU
THAT ALL THIS HAPPENED.
I SHOULD THANK YOU.
YOU HAVE OPENED THE PORTAL
TO THE REAL WORLD
FOR ALL OF US.
IF OUR WORLDS OVERLAP,
WE COULD ALL BE DESTROYED.
WE'VE GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO PLUG UP THAT HOLE.
STUPID!
I NEVER SHOULD HAVE ALLOWED
CHILDREN
TO INTERACT WITH DIGIMON!
WHAT WAS I THINKING?
[ SOBBING ]
YOU --
YEAH, ME.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
[ Growling ]
IT'S YOUR FAULT.
HUH? LEAVE HIM ALONE.
[ GRUNTS ]
YOU'RE NOT WORTH IT.
HEY, WHO'S THE THUG?
TROUBLE.
YOU IGNORANT
DIGIMON-LOVING FREAKS!
YOU AND YOUR DISGUSTING PETS!
NOW LOOK WHAT YOU'VE DONE!
YEP, THAT WAS
DEFINITELY RUDE.
YOU READY?
MM-HMM.
WE'VE GOT TO GET UP THERE.
RENAMON.
THAT'S THE WAY UP.
RIGHT. DON'T GO YET.
OKAY, WHY NOT?
WHAT'S UP?
NOT YOU.
I MEANT UP THERE.
SO DID I. BE QUIET.
HMM.
WHERE ARE YOU?
I DON'T GET IT.
THERE'S NOTHING THERE.
IT DOESN'T MAKE
ANY SENSE.
IT'S A DIGITAL FIELD.
THERE'S GOT TO BE
SOMETHING THERE.
HOLD ON.
THERE YOU ARE.
BUT WHY AM I NOT
RECEIVING ANY DATA?
WHAT KIND OF DIGIMON
IS THIS?
WHO CARES?
WHAT'S HE GOING TO DO,
BITE ME?
WE CAN TAKE HIM.
YOU READY?
YEP.
WAIT. RENAMON
WILL HANDLE THIS.
I'LL MAKE HER DIGIVOLVE.
REIKA! YOU CAN USE
THIS CARD!
♪ DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMODIFY!
DIGIVOLUTION ACTIVATE!
RENAMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON, DI-DI
♪ DI-DI
CUBIMON!
OH, YEAH!
NOW WE'RE TALKIN'.
HOW ABOUT A DANCE,
BIG BOY?
[ GROWLS ]
TOUGH GUY, HUH?
[ BOTH SCREAMING ]
DRAGON WHEEL!
IT'S HUGE. [ Gasps ]
AAH!
SAMURAI TIGER TAIL!
COME ON!
CUBIMON!
CUBIMON, NO!
RENAMON!
[ GASPS ]
THAT'S IT.
I'M GOING, HENRY.
THAT TIGER'S TOAST.
♪ DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMODIFY!
DIGIVOLUTION ACTIVATE.
CALUMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON, DI-DI
GARGOMON!
♪ DI-DI
TURBO LASER!
GO GET 'EM!
YEAH!
HUH?
RENAMON.
RENAMON? ARE YOU --
SO STRONG.
ULTIMATE.
POSSIBLY EVEN MEGA.
DON'T TRY TO TALK.
IS RENAMON ALL RIGHT?
CAN'T MOVE.
Henry: NOTHING.
AW, MAN. THERE'S JUST NO DATA
ON THIS GUY AT ALL.
WE'RE FIGHTING
COMPLETELY BLIND HERE.
IF CUBIMON WAS DEFEATED
THAT EASILY,
THEN WE DON'T STAND
A CHANCE.
[ GROWLS ]
HERE, KITTY, KITTY!
GARGOMON!
I'VE GOT TO HELP HIM.
WITHOUT ANY DATA ON THAT THING,
I WON'T KNOW
IF I'M USING THE RIGHT CARDS.
GRR. HE'S GONE
AROUND THE OTHER SIDE.
GARGOMON!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
LITTLE FRAIDY CAT.
WHERE ARE YOU?
COME ON OUT AND FIGHT.
OH, NUTS.
HA HA HA HA.
[ ROARS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ Thinking ] GARGOMON.
THAT'S ENOUGH. MY TURN.
UH, HUH? HEY!
I'M GOING TO NEED A LOT
OF PEANUT BUTTER AFTER THIS ONE.
HERE GOES NOTHING.
COME ON, BOY.
♪ DIGIMON, DI-DI
GUILMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON, DI-DI
GROWLMON!
GOOD LUCK, BOY.
I GOT HIM.
ARE YOU OKAY?
IT'S ALL UP TO GROWLMON.
HENRY.
WHAT IS IT?
[ Whispers ] HE ALWAYS CIRCLES
AROUND BEFORE HE ATTACKS.
WE MIGHT STILL HAVE
A CHANCE.
HE ALWAYS CIRCLES AROUND
LIKE A SHARK
JUST BEFORE HE ATTACKS.
THAT'S WHEN GROWLMON
CAN GET HIM.
OKAY. THANKS.
THERE HE IS.
NOW, GROWLMON! DO IT!
AAH! DRAGONFLY!
AHH!
PYROBLASTER!
UHH. UHH.
I CAN FEEL IT.
IT'S OVER.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HIM?
TAKATO!
HEY, KAZU.
WHAT?
ABOUT TAKATO -- ARE YOU
JEALOUS THAT HE'S A TAMER?
HUH? HA!
ME JEALOUS OF HIM?
HMM. HUH?
WHOA! WHAT IS THAT?
HUH?
[ MURMURING ]
TAKATO!
HMM?
IS THIS A DREAM?
[ Groans ]
WHY AM I FEELING PAIN
WHEN GROWLMON'S THE ONE
THAT GOT HURT?
AND WHILE WE'RE AT IT,
WHERE AM I?
Growlmon: TAMER.
HUH?
TAMER, IT'S NOT
OVER YET.
HEY, GROWLMON, YOU'RE ALIVE!
OH, WAIT. YOU DON'T
EVEN RECOGNIZE ME, DO YOU?
OF COURSE. IT JUST SEEMED
LIKE SUCH A SERIOUS MOMENT.
YEAH, IT WAS,
BUT DON'T DO THAT AGAIN,
OKAY?
OKAY. SORRY.
ANYWAY, LIKE I WAS SAYING,
YOU'VE GOT TO
LET ME FIGHT AGAIN.
SO WE MADE
A COUPLE MISTAKES.
NO BIG DEAL.
I KNOW I CAN TAKE HIM,
BUT I'M REALLY GOING TO
NEED YOUR HELP THIS TIME.
ARE YOU IN?
TAKATO, I NEED YOU.
YEAH. UH...
BUT I'M NOT WORTHY.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT!
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE GOTTEN HURT
IF IT WASN'T FOR ME.
I'VE BEEN A COWARD, GROWLMON,
AND I'M SO SORRY.
BUT IF YOU'RE REALLY WILLING
TO GIVE ME ONE MORE CHANCE,
THEN I HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO TAKE IT.
GROWLMON!
TAKATO!
WE WILL FIGHT
ONE MORE TIME...
TOGETHER!
HUH? WHOA!
AHH!
HEY, UH, HI, CALUMON.
DID ANYONE EVER TELL YOU
YOU TALK IN YOUR SLEEP?
WELCOME BACK.
HOW YOU FEELING?
WHAT A WUSS. I CAN'T
BELIEVE YOU FAINTED.
WHAT? HA HA HA.
HUH?
UNH?Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â HMM?
GUNS WON'T STOP HIM.
IT'LL TAKE SOMETHING
A LOT STRONGER THAN THAT.
BRILLIANT, EINSTEIN.
WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST?
EVEN GROWLMON CRUMPLED
LIKE A STUPID RAG DOLL.
I HAVEN'T FINISHED YET.
HUH?
WEHAVEN'T FINISHED YET.
GROWLMON IS STILL WILLING
TO FIGHT,
AND AS LONG
AS I'M STILL BREATHING,
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE
BY HIS SIDE.
IT'S TIME TO USE THE POWER
THAT BROUGHT US HERE
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
ARE YOU GUYS READY?
'CAUSE WE'RE GONNA DO THIS
EVEN IF YOU'RE NOT.
HE'S GOT THE CARD.
OKAY, I'M WITH YA.
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
THIS BATTLE
HAS ONLY JUST BEGUN!
♪ DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMODIFY!
MATRIX DIGIVOLUTION!
HUH? [ Thinking ]
CRYSTAL MATRIX ACTIVATE!
[ GASPS ]
♪ DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON, DI-DI
GROWLMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON, DI-DI
WARGROWLMON!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
OUR LITTLE BOY'S
GROWN UP.
I'LL GIVE YOU THAT ONE.
OHH!
YEAH!
WARGROWLMON --
CYBORG TYPE,
ULTIMATE LEVEL.
NICE PRESENTATION,
BUT NO ONE BEATS MIHIRAMON.
SAMURAI TIGER TAIL!
[ GRUNTS ]
HOW WERE YOU ABLE TO DIGIVOLVE
TO THIS LEVEL?
DON'T TELL ME THAT HUMAN
HAD SOMETHING TO DO WITH IT.
[ GRUNTING ]
WHAT'S WRONG?
UM, YOU DON'T LOOK
SO GOOD.
I FEEL EVERY HIT.
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S ENOUGH.
OH, SO YOU WANT TO PLAY
WITH THE KITTY, HUH?
ARMORED TIGER TAIL!
RIGHT. TIME TO TAKE THE TIGER
BY THE TAIL.
LET'S DO THIS TOGETHER.
AS YOUR TAMER,
I SAY FINISH IT!
WELL, IF YOU SAY SO,
TAMER.
YOU'VE BEEN
A VERY NAUGHTY KITTY.
ATOMIC...
BLASTER!
AHH!
FOOL! YOU AND YOUR HUMANS!
DIGIMON COULD HAVE HAD
SUPREME POWER
OVER BOTH WORLDS,
BUT YOU HAD TO RUIN
EVERYTHING.
AHH!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THOSE KIDS WERE ACTUALLY ABLE
TO DEFEAT HIM.
AND ALL THIS TIME I THOUGHT THEY
WERE JUST PLAYING A STUPID GAME.
THIS IS GOING TO REQUIRE
ADDITIONAL RESEARCH.
AWESOME.
THAT IS
ONE BIG DIGIMON.
IS THAT GIANT THING
REALLY GUILMON?
HMM. AMATEUR.
HE DIGIVOLVED TWICE.
THAT'S HIS ULTIMATE FORM --
WARGROWLMON.
UH, DID TAKATO LEAVE?
NO WAY. A REAL TAMER
NEVER LEAVES HIS DIGIMON.
TAKATO ROCKS!
YOU WERE PRETTY COOL
OUT THERE, CHUMLY.
UH-HUH. AND CUTE.
OH, YUCK.
EW, PLEASE.
TAKATOMON.
HUH?
YOUAREWORTHY, TAMER.
THANK YOU
FOR FIGHTING BY MY SIDE.
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING
BUT TRUST YOU
AND, I GUESS, MYSELF.
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE GOING TO NEED
A LOT MORE PEANUT BUTTER.
WHOA! HOW ARE YOU GOING TO HIDE
THAT GUY
FROM YOUR PARENTS, TAKATO?
LOOKS LIKE IT'S GOING TO BE
A WHOLE NEW WORLD
ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."