OH, MAYBE WE SHOULD TALK
ABOUT THIS.
WELL, IF YOU GIVE ME A CHANCE,
I'M SURE WE CAN WORK IT OUT.
I JUST WANTED TO PLAY.
OKAY. LET'S PLAY.
I DON'T LIKE THIS GAME.
[ WHIMPERING ]
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE PLAYING IT RIGHT?
AW, NUTS. OH!
GAME OVER!
[ GASPS ]
AAH!
[ HORNS HONKING ]
HEY!
HUH?
I HOPE THE OTHER DIGIMON HERE
AREN'T AS RUDE AS THAT ONE.
BULL'S-EYE, BABY!
DARKTYRANNOMON DIGIVOLVES
TO METAL TYRANNOMON
WHICH MAKES YOU HISTORY.
OH, MAN, THAT HURT! THAT WAS
LIKE SOMETHING I WOULD DO.
HOW DID YOU THINK OF THAT?
WHAT CAN I SAY? HEY, YOU'RE
DEALING WITH A SUPER GENIUS.
YEAH, IN YOUR DREAMS,
DOOFUS.
TAKATO,
WILL YOU HURRY UP?
IF WE'RE LATE, MRS. SAACHI'S
GOING TO MAKE US STAND
IN THE HALL AGAIN.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
DON'T LEAVE WITHOUT ME.
OH, MAN.
HUH?
WOW, I DON'T REMEMBER
HAVING A CARD LIKE THIS.
AAH! AAH!
WHAT WAS THAT?
UM. THIS IS NEW.
OH, GREAT.
MY CARD READER GOES MENTAL,
AND I'M LATE FOR SCHOOL
AGAIN.
THANKS FOR WAITING, KAZU.
Takato: OH, NUTS!
[ BELL RINGS ]
[ SIGHS ]
I HEARD THAT.
YOU KNOW THE RULES.
IF YOU SHOW UP LATE,
YOU'LL HAVE TO WAIT.
WHO -- ME?
[ LAUGHTER ]
I-I'M SORRY I'M LATE,
MRS. SAACHI.
NOW, I WANT YOU ALL
TO PAY CLOSE ATTENTION.
THIS IS GOING TO BE
ON YOUR TEST.
YEAH, THAT WORKS.
RED IS DEFINITELY A POWER COLOR.
I'LL GIVE HIM
THE STRONGEST ATTACK EVER.
NO ONE WILL EXPECT THAT,
ESPECIALLY FROM A ROOKIE.
I'M GOING TO MAKE HIM
EVEN BETTER THAN AGUMON.
I'LL CALL IT PYROSPHERE!
Woman: ARE YOU DESIGNING
A HALLOWEEN COSTUME?
HMM? NO, IT'S A DIGIMON.
DON'T YOU KNOW ANYTHING?
WELL, TAKATO,
DESPITE YOUR APOLOGY,
YOU CERTAINLY DON'T SEEM
VERY SORRY ABOUT BEING LATE,
DO YOU?
UH...YES?
UH, I-I MEAN NO, MA'AM.
NO, ACTUALLY,
I-I DO MEAN YES.
I MEAN, I-I'M SORRY.
I'M REALLY SORRY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ BELL RINGS ]
[ KIDS PLAYING OUTSIDE ]
NOW, WHAT SHOULD I CALL HIM?
RED DINO FIREMON.
NO, THAT'S STUPID.
BLAZING DRAGON
LIZARDMON.
YEAH, GET REAL.
HEY, HOW ABOUT GIOMON?
COOL! NOW, THAT'S A NAME!
[ SQUEAKS ]
AAH!
I-I'M ALMOST DONE, MA'AM.
I'M JUST TAKING A TIME-OUT.
[ GIGGLES ]
HUH?
YOU'RE KIND OF FUNNY.
UM, YOU SEE, I'M...
HAVING A REALLY OFF DAY.
THERE IT IS.
BAD FLUTE.
BAD.
O-KAY.
ARF! ARF!
YOU'D BETTER HURRY UP
AND WRITE THAT APOLOGY.
[ GIGGLING ]
UH...
I'M PICKING UP AN ABNORMAL
GERMINATION ENERGY PATTERN.
IS IT A WILD ONE?
I CAN'T TELL YET,
BUT THE LEVELS ARE INCREASING
AT AN EXPONENTIAL RATE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
LIKE IT.
[ HORNS HONKING ]
OH!
OH! OH!
OH, MAN,
WHAT ELSE CAN GO WRONG?
I HOPE MY CARD READER
ISN'T BUSTED.
HMM?
I'M DREAMING.
WAIT A MINUTE.
THIS IS REAL.
OHH.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
I'M GOING NUTS.
I'M SITTING
INSIDE OF A DINOSAUR
WITH A DIGIVICE.
RIGHT.
HEY, IT'S EMPTY.
OHH.
FOR A PLACE
WITH SO MANY PEOPLE,
HOW COME THERE'S NO ONE
TO PLAY WITH, HUH?
Woman: THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
HAVE A GOOD DAY.
HI, MRS. MISABA.
TAKATO, SLOW DOWN.
WHOOPS.
HI, DAD. I'M HOME.
HI, SON.
WHAT'D YOU LEARN AT --
THE USUAL.
2 PLUS 2 EQUALS 4.
I GOT A LOT OF HOMEWORK.
CALL ME WHEN DINNER'S READY.
TAKATO, THANKS A LOT.
WHAT'S UP?
OH, NOTHING.
IN SOME FAMILIES,
KIDS ACTUALLY
GIVE THEIR MOTHERS A HUG
WHEN THEY COME HOME
FROM SCHOOL.
HMM?
[ GRUNTS ]
WHERE'S THAT BLUE CARD?
IT'S GONE.
IT IS JUST A GAME,
BUT IN THE REAL WORLD,
GAMES DON'T CHANGE SHAPE
ON THEIR OWN.
THAT'S GOT TO BE IT!
THAT BLUE CARD
MADE IT TRANSFORM.
IT'S NOT FROM THIS WORLD.
SO IF I'M RIGHT,
THEN I'M --
[ THUNDER CRASHING ]
WHOA.
WELL, IF I AM RIGHT,
THEN THIS THING
IS A REAL DIGIVICE...
WHICH WOULD MAKE ME --
HA HA HA --
[ GROANS ]
OH, IT'S STUCK.
DON'T TELL ME
I BROKE IT ALREADY.
Woman: TAKATO, COME DOWN!
DINNER'S READY!
OKAY!
BEFORE IT GETS COLD,
PLEASE!
COMING, MOM.
HUH?
WHOA.
A DIGI-EGG.
HA HA.
MY VERY OWN
REAL LIVE DIGI-EGG!
TAKATO!
GIOMON.
DIGI-ARMOR, ENERGIZE.
[ Echoes ]
GIOMON.
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
AHEM.
IT'S LINZMON VERSUS RENAMON.
RENAMON, DIGIMODIFY.
AHH.
SPEED ACTIVATE.
A DIGIMON TAMER.
DIAMOND STAR!
HUH?
I'M ALIVE. GOOD GAME.
THERE'S DEFINITELY SOMETHING
WEIRD ABOUT THOSE TOWERS.
Man: WELL, GOOD MORNING.
ABOUT TIME YOU'RE UP.
GOOD MORNING, DAD.
AHA.
SO WHAT'S GOING ON?
HUH? HA HA.
NOTHING.
OH, SECRET, HUH?
NO. UM, HEY, DAD?
YEAH?
WHEN YOU WERE MY AGE,
DO YOU REMEMBER ANYTHING
ABOUT DIGIMON?
I MEAN, DID THEY
HAVE THEM BACK THEN?
HA HA. 'FRAID NOT.
AW, TOO BAD.
HEY, WHAT IF IT WASN'T
JUST A TV SHOW OR A GAME?
WOULDN'T IT BE AMAZING
IF THEY REALLY EXISTED?
I SUPPOSE.
WHY DO YOU ASK?
WELL -- HA HA --
NO REASON. NEVER MIND.
THANKS, DAD.
YOU'RE WELCOME, I GUESS.
[ DIGIVICE BEEPING ]
WELL, I'M SURE THEY'RE REAL.
THEY GOTTA BE.
GOTTA BE.
[ PEOPLE TALKING,
HORNS HONKING ]
WHOA, I WONDER WHY
THOSE FUNNY METAL DIGIMON
KEEP SPITTING UP
ALL THESE PEOPLE.
THEY MUST BE
REALLY GOOD FIGHTERS,
OR EITHER THAT
OR THIS IS THE WORSE CASE
OF INDIGESTION I'VE EVER SEEN.
BUT IT'S TRUE.
YOU GOTTA BELIEVE ME.
GUYS, I'M NOT KIDDING.
DIGIMON ARE REAL.
I SAW THEM -- DIGIMON --
REAL ONES FIGHTING
RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME.
TWO OF THEM WERE GOING
AFTER EACH OTHER...
AND THEN YOUR EYES OPENED
AND YOU WERE BACK IN BED
LIKE NOTHING HAD EVER HAPPENED.
YOU SAW THEM FIGHTING
ON THE BED?
NO! LISTEN,
THIS WAS NOT A DREAM.
I'M NOT MAKING IT UP.
NUMB.
MY HANDS, THEY WERE NUMB
FROM THE RAIN,
IT WAS SO COLD.
HEY, MAYBE YOU MADE
YOUR OWN COLD PUDDLE.
WHAT?
THAT'S SOME DREAM.
MORE LIKE
A BED-WETTING NIGHTMARE!
HA HA HA HA.
I DID NOT WET THE BED!
MAYBE HE FROZE HIS HANDS
WIPING HIS BABY TEARS.
POOR MR. SLEEPYHEAD,
MADE HIS OWN WATERBED
I DIDN'T WET ANYTHING!
NICE STORY, TAKATO.
WHAT A BABY.
[ SIGHS ]
IT WAS REAL.
I SAW THEM AND HER.
WHO WAS THAT GIRL?
WHAT A TAMER.
WAIT A SEC.
HER DIGIVICE --
IT'S THE SAME.
MINE IS EXACTLY THE SAME.
HUH?
[ DIGI-EGG SHATTERS ]
MY DIGI-EGG'S HATCHED.
I MISSED IT.
GOOD THING I DON'T HAVE
ANY REAL PETS.
I CAN'T EVEN KEEP TRACK
OF A DIGITAL ONE.
BUT WHERE COULD HE BE?
I'VE GOT TO FIND HIM.
WHOA.
IS THAT A COMPASS?
WHY DID IT STOP?
BULL'S-EYE, BABY.
THE TOWER OF POWER!
HIGH-LEVEL WILD TYPE.
BIO-EMERGENCE IS NOW IMMINENT.
PRIMARY TRACER ACTIVATING.
SHALL I STOP HIM?
NOT JUST YET.
KEEP THE TRACER LOCKED.
I'M INTERESTED
TO SEE WHAT THIS ONE DOES.
AFFIRMATIVE.
LOCKING NOW.
THIS WAY.
I'LL SHOW THEM.
I'LL SHOW EVERYBODY.
DIGIMON ARE REAL,
AND I'M GONNA PROVE IT.
TELUMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
HUH?
OHH. PRETTY.
HENDRI, COME HERE.
LOOK AT THE PRETTY LIGHT.
HUH?
[ ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ]
SOMETHING'S COMING.
ALMOST THERE.
EW, GROSS.
I DON'T EVEN WANT TO KNOW
WHAT THAT SMELL IS.
AAH!
WHOA.
THIS IS IT.
HE'S ALL MINE.
HE'S GOING TO BREACH.
I CAN'T STOP HIM.
WHERE?
LOCATION --
WEST SHIJUKU.
NICE ENTRANCE.
SO HARD TO SEE.
WELL?
IS IT? IT LOOKS LIKE HIM.
HMM? HMM?
IT IS HIM.
WOW. HE'S PERFECT!
[ SNIFFS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
OH.
HE'S AMAZING.
OH, MAN.
AND REAL.
HE'S ACTUALLY REAL.
A REAL LIVE DIGIMON.
WOW. AH.
AH. [ Sniffs ]
HI THERE.
MY NAME IS TAKATO,
AND I THINK I CREATED YOU.
GIOMON?
[ GROWLS ]
UH, GESUNDHEIT?
WOW. I GUESS
YOU DON'T LIKE RATS, HUH?
AH. [ Sniffs ]
HMM?
WHOA!
OKAY, JUST STAY CALM.
EVERYTHING'S GOING TO BE FINE.
HERE'S A PLAN --
I SCREAM AND RUN.
OR NOT.
PLEASE, DON'T DO IT!
GIOMON, STOP!
Davis: AW, DUDE, THAT'S HARSH!
WILL TAKATO GET TOASTED
ON GIOMON'S GRILL?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."