AFTER AN ALMOST-FATAL BLOW
FROM THE D-REAPER,
IT LOOKED LIKE BEELZEMON
WAS A GONER.
BUT GRANI CAME TO THE RESCUE
AND BROUGHT THE INJURED IMPMON
TO SAFETY.
THEN THE GLOBAL TASK FORCE
SHOWED UP
AND DROPPED ALL THESE JAMMING
DEVICES ON THE BIG BLOB.
BUT THE D-REAPER EVOLVED
EVEN FURTHER.
KNOWING THEY COULDN'T FIGHT
WITHOUT LOSING THEIR STRENGTH,
THE TAMERS RETREATED WHILE
THE MONSTER MAKERS WORKED ON
A PLAN TO DESTROY
THE MUTATED PROGRAM.
SHIBUMI MADE A RED CARD
TO HELP THE TAMERS FIGHT
INSIDE THE D-REAPER ZONE,
AND HENRY CALLED THEM ALL
BACK TO THE CITY
FOR THE FINAL BATTLE.
ONCE MORE INTO THE BREACH,
DEAR FRIENDS.
ONCE MORE.
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
♪ WORLD
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMODIFY
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
WE'LL BE BACK --
ALL OF US.
HUH?
[ PANTING ]
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
BIOMEREGE ACTIVATE!
♪ DI-DI-DI
GUILMON BIOMEREGE TO...
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DIGIMON
♪ DI-DI
GALLANTMON!
[ Thinking ]
THAT'S MY BOY.
DON'T WORRY!
YOU KNOW WHAT?
HE LOOKS PRETTY GOOD UP THERE.
[ Sniffles ]
HE SURE DOES.
WHEN WE BECOME SAKUYAMON,
EVERYTHING SEEMS POSSIBLE.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN,
RENAMON?
ALWAYS, RIKA.
TIRED...
CALUMON, DON'T GIVE UP!
[ GRUNTING ]
[ GROANING ]
HE CAME HERE FOR ME.
NOW LOOK AT HIM.
[ GRUNTING ]
HUH?
OKAY, HERE'S THE PLAN, GUILMON.
LISTEN UP.
FIRST WE SAVE JERI,
THEN WE DESTROY THAT THING.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE A GOOD PLAN,
TAKATO.
BUT, UM, HOW DO WE PLAN
TO DO IT?
WELL, I'M STILL WORKING
ON THAT PART.
OH, WOW, WHAT'S THAT?
HUH?
LET'S CHECK IT OUT.
LOOK!
Both: IT'S SAKUYAMON!
BOY, ARE WE GLAD TO SEE YOU!
HEY, HENRY.
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
WE WERE WAITING ON YOU.
SORRY. MY DAD, YOU KNOW.
WELL, YOU MISSED IT.
I HAD TO BE QUIET
IN A TICKLE.
YOU HAD TO BE QUIET.
IMAGINE THAT.
IMPOSSIBLE.
WELL, IT WAS DEFINITELY
WORTH THE WAIT.
MR. MIZUNO MADE THIS CARD
FOR US.
IT WILL LET US FIGHT
INSIDE THE D-REAPER.
SO WHAT DO WE DO
WITH IT?
WELL, RIKA, I'M GUESSING
THE USUAL.
WHAT'S THAT?
YOU WEREN'T PLANNING
TO LEAVE WITHOUT US...
WERE YOU?
HI, GUYS.
HI YOURSELF.
WE DIDN'T EXACTLY
FORGET ABOUT YOU.
PLEASE. HOW COULD YOU?
IF YOU TWO ARE FINISHED,
LET'S GET TO WORK.
ALL RIGHT, DIGIVICES OUT.
DIGIMODIFY!
FOR JERI!
WE'RE COMING FOR YOU!
FULL SPEED AHEAD!
I PROMISE, THIS WILL BE
OUR LAST BATTLE, RENAMON.
IT'S NOW-OR-NEVER TIME.
[ EXPLOSION ]
AAH!
THEY DID IT.
FOUR DIGIMON HAVE NOW ENTERED
THE QUANTUM BUBBLE.
I'M PREPARED
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS.
I JUST WISH THERE WERE
ANOTHER WAY.
SO DO I, JANYU.
BELIEVE ME.
UNFORTUNATELY,
THERE ISN'T.
WE JUST HAVE TO TRUST
THE CHILDREN.
AND WE WILL.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYONE,
IT'S TIME.
BEGIN THE FINAL PREPARATIONS
FOR OPERATION DOODLEBUG.
BABEL, WHAT'S SAY WE START
LINKING IN THE SATELLITES?
YOU GOT IT.
DON'T GIVE UP NOW, KIDS.
WE'RE MAKING YOU A MIRACLE.
OKAY, SO NOW WHAT?
IT ALL LOOKS THE SAME TO ME.
WELL, HE DOES HAVE A POINT.
JERI'S IN HERE SOMEWHERE.
I KNOW IT.
LOOK! OVER THERE!
THAT LOOKS PROMISING.
IT'S A START.
Both: WE'RE RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE COMPANY.
I'LL CLEAR THE WAY.
JUSTICE BURST!
HUH? OH, GREAT.
HERE YA GO,
YA FLYING FREAK!
LET'S NOT DO THAT AGAIN.
NO KIDDING.
[ GROWLING ]
[ EXPLOSION ]
RIDE 'EM, COWBOY.
SWEET FLYING, GRANI.
AAH!
NO! RENAMON,
WE'VE BEEN HIT!
BUT THEY'RE JUST CHILDREN.
CAN THEY POSSIBLY WIN?
THEY HAVE TO,
AND THEY KNOW IT.
ALL RIGHT, THIS SECTION
IS DE-BUGGED
AND READY FOR INTEGRATION.
HOW ARE YOU DOING
OVER THERE?
IT'S STARTING TO COME
TOGETHER NOW.
DAISY, ARE YOU READY?
NOT QUITE, BUT I WILL BE.
THIS SECTION IS GOOD TO GO.
I'M LINKING IT IN NOW.
SO FAR, SO GOOD.
NOW IF IT ONLY HAD A HEART.
ARE YOU READY WITH THE HIGSFIELD
CALCULATIONS, SHIBUMI?
IT'S A NASTY LITTLE PROBLEM,
DOLPHIN.
BELIEVE ME,
EINSTEIN HAD IT EASY.
AMETHYST MANDALA!
[ GRUNTS ]
CALUMON, WAKE UP.
ARE YOU OKAY?
CALUMON,
PLEASE TALK TO ME.
[ Faintly ] CAN'T.
PLEASE BE OKAY.
YOU HAVE TO BE.
[ Sobbing ] CALUMON...
I CAN'T --
I CAN'T STAND THIS
ANYMORE.
I CAN'T STAND FOR YOU
TO SUFFER BECAUSE OF ME.
OH, CALUMON.
[ GASPS ]
COULD THIS BE OUR DESTINY?
HANG IN THERE, JERI.
WE'RE ON OUR WAY.
YOU THINK MAYBE
SHE'S INSIDE THAT THING?
HOW ARE WE EVER GOING
TO GET IN THERE?
NEVER MIND, IT DOESN'T MATTER.
WE JUST WILL.
[ BOTH PANTING ]
MAYBE THE REST OF US CAN MAKE
SOME KIND OF DISTRACTION.
GRANI, WE'LL BE BACK FOR YOU
WHEN WE FIND JERI.
JUST WAIT HERE, OKAY?
[ BOTH GASP ]
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
GLORIOUS CHAOS.
[ BOTH SCREAMING ]
ALL SHALL FALL TO RUINS.
MANKIND AND HIS MACHINES
WILL BE DELETED!
[ WHISTLE BLOWS ]
WOW, YOU DID IT.
OF COURSE I DID.
IT WAS MY IDEA.
WELL, I DID ALL THE WORK.
THOSE TWO -- SILLY.
RIGHT.
THIS REALLY ISN'T THE TIME.
COME ON, YOU CAN ALWAYS
ARGUE LATER.
HOW DID YOU GET THAT
OUT OF WHAT HE SAID?
I DON'T GET IT.
HE SAYS THREE WORDS,
AND YOU RAMBLE FOR HOURS.
MM, HE'S A DIGIMON
OF FEW WORDS,
BUT WE UNDERSTAND
EACH OTHER.
UH-HUH.
WHATEVER. HE'S RIGHT
ABOUT ONE THING.
IT'S TIME FOR US TO STOP
YAPPING AND START ZAPPING.
YEAH!
WHAT HE SAID.
HUH?
STAY WHERE YOU ARE.
PUT YOUR HANDS IN THE AIR.
YOU ARE UNDER ARREST.
[ ALL GASPING ]
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
THIS IS THE CRAZIEST
PLACE I'VE EVER SEEN.
EVEN THE DIGITAL WORLD
MADE MORE SENSE THAN THIS.
BUT I GUESS IF MR. MIZUNO
CAN GET US IN HERE,
MY DAD CAN GET US OUT --
HOPEFULLY WITH ALL THE PIECES
IN THE RIGHT PLACES.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT THIS IS ALL REAL,
THAT WE'RE ACTUALLY
GOING INTO BATTLE.
A LITTLE MORE
THAN A CARD GAME.
DID YOU EVER IMAGINE
WHEN ALL THIS STARTED
THAT WE'D END UP
HAVING TO SAVE THE WORLD?
HOW COULD I?
I WAS TOO BUSY CALLING MYSELF
THE DIGIMON QUEEN.
Renamon:
YOU BELIEVED IT, OF COURSE.
AND WHY NOT?
YOU ARE THE QUEEN --
SECOND ONLY
TO THE DIGIMON KING.
Rika: GIVE ME A BREAK.
[ Laughs ]
Takato: YOU GUYS
HAVEN'T CHANGED A BIT.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT,
TAKATO.
THINK ABOUT IT.
I MEAN, HERE WE ALL ARE,
TRYING TO SAVE JERI.
IN SOME WAYS,
WE'VE CHANGED A LOT.
IN OTHER WAYS,
WE HAVEN'T CHANGED AT ALL.
LOOK AT RIKA. SHE USED TO
JUST WANT TO FIGHT WITH US.
NOW SHE'S TIRED OF FIGHTING,
BUT SHE STILL LIKES TO ARGUE.
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT'S FUNNY.
IT IS. I GUESS WHEREVER
YOU GO, THERE YOU ARE.
MM-HMM.
Guilmon: THIS IS VERY
INTERESTING, TAKATO,
BUT WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
AI, IS IMPMON
REALLY GOING TO BE OKAY?
SHH. LET HIM REST.
HUMANS -- YOU GOT TO LOVE THEM,
TAKING CARE OF A WORTHLESS
PUNK LIKE ME.
WORTHLESS?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU'RE JUST THE GREATEST,
IMPMON.
WE SAW YOU.
YOU WERE WONDERFUL.
YOU'RE JUST TRYING
TO MAKE ME FEEL BETTER.
I WAS TOTALLY USELESS
OUT THERE.
Both: MNH-MNH.
HUH?
[ ALL GASP ]
Both: COOL.
[ GIGGLING ]
SO TIRED.
CALUMON, I THINK IT'S TIME
WE GOT OURSELVES OUT OF HERE,
DON'T YOU?
WE CAN LAUGH TOGETHER
AND BE FRIENDS AGAIN
AND EAT CREAM PUFFS.
YOU CAN HEAR ME,
CAN'T YOU?
I KNOW YOU CAN!
I'VE HAD IT WITH YOU.
YOU STOLE MY VOICE AND UPSET
MY DAD AND MY FRIENDS!
YOU EVEN SNOOPED AROUND
IN MY HEAD
AND MESSED WITH MY MEMORIES.
LOSING LEOMON
BROKE MY HEART,
BUT I NEVER SHOULD HAVE
LET YOU TAKE
THE BEAUTIFUL MEMORY
OF MY FRIEND
AND TURN IT INTO
SOMETHING UGLY.
IT WAS WRONG OF ME
TO BELIEVE
THAT FEELING NOTHING WAS
BETTER THAN FEELING SAD.
THE SADNESS WAS REAL.
IT WAS HUMAN.
I MISUNDERSTOOD LEOMON.
HE NEVER MEANT FOR ME TO THINK
MY LIFE HAD NO MEANING.
HE SAID WE ALL HAVE
OUR OWN DESTINY,
AND THAT'S NOT
THE SAME THING.
EVERY ONE OF US
HAS A DESTINY
THAT'S DIFFERENT
AND THAT'S SPECIAL.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT?
THANK YOU, LEOMON.
YOU CAN'T DELETE
EVEN ONE OF US
WITHOUT DELETING SOMETHING
THAT THE WHOLE WORLD NEEDS.
EVERY ONE OF US HAS SOMETHING
IMPORTANT TO DO.
JERI...OOH...
UHH! AHH!
JERI!
HUMAN BEINGS ARE INSIGNIFICANT.
THERE IS NO IMPORTANCE
TO YOUR LIVES,
NO USEFUL PURPOSE.
YOU SHOWED THE D-REAPER
THE TRUTH,
SUBJECT KATOU, JERI.
HUMAN BEINGS
DESIRE DESTRUCTION.
DESIRE ANNIHILATION.
YOU'RE WRONG!
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND!
HUMAN BEINGS CAUSE PAIN AND FEAR
TO OTHER HUMAN BEINGS.
HUMAN BEINGS WAGE WAR
AND DESTROY OTHER HUMAN BEINGS.
NO!
YES, JERI KATOU.
HUMAN BEINGS CREATED DIGIMON
TO FIGHT BATTLES AND LOAD DATA
SO THEY WOULD GROW
IN STRENGTH AND ABILITY.
DIGIMON HAVE ONE PURPOSE --
TO SATISFY THE HUMAN NEED
FOR DESTRUCTION.
BUT THAT IS NOT TRUE
OF US ANYMORE.
YEAH! WE'RE NOT FIGHTING
ANYONE BUT YOU!
YOU HAVE IT ALL WRONG,
D-REAPER.
YOU'VE NEVER FELT
THE STRENGTH
AND THE HAPPINESS
OF BIOMERGING.
WE'RE GOOD FOR EACH OTHER.
HUMANS AND DIGIMON --
WE MAKE EACH OTHER BETTER,
AND WE'RE NOT GONNA
LET YOU STOP US!
HANG ON, JERI!
JERI!
[ GROANING ]
WHAT'S THAT?
OH, NO!
TELL ME THIS ISN'T HAPPENING!
NO ONE FOR US
TO PLAY WITH.
I DON'T FEEL MUCH
LIKE PLAYING ANYWAY.
I WISH I COULD FIGHT,
BUT WITHOUT BIOMERGING,
I WOULDN'T HAVE THE STRENGTH.
I'LL JUST HAVE TO LEAVE
THE FIGHTING TO THE OTHERS.
OH...
[ GASPS ]
YAMAKI,
SOMETHING'S HAPPENING!
WHAT IS GOING ON OUT THERE?
EXCELLENT.
IT'S FINALLY CONNECTED.
THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT
WE'VE BEEN WAITING FOR.
THE D-REAPER
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD
HAS TO MAKE
A MATERIAL CONNECTION
WITH THE D-REAPER HERE
FOR ITS FINAL ATTACK.
THIS IS WHEN
IT'S MOST VULNERABLE.
BUT IT DOESN'T KNOW THAT,
AND WE HAVE A LITTLE SURPRISE
IN STORE FOR IT.
I'M SURE IT WILL GO OUT
WITH A BANG --
A GREAT BIG BANG.
THEN LET'S DO IT.
OPERATION DOODLEBUG
IS GOOD TO GO.
[ ALARM WAILING ]
RILEY, PREPARE TO ENGAGE
THE JUGGERNAUT ON MY SIGNAL.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
NOT THIS TIME.
JUGGERNAUT HAS BECOME
OUR TRUMP CARD
AGAINST THE CHAOS.
JUGGERNAUT IS ON-LINE.
READY ON YOUR COMMAND.
BUT WERE'S THE POWER
COMING FROM?
[ Thinking ]
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
FORGET ABOUT THAT!
LET'S GO!
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING
THERE.
WHERE?
COME ON!
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS WAITING FOR?
I WON'T BE ABLE TO FACE HIM
EVEN TO ASK FOR FORGIVENESS.
THIS IS UNFORGIVABLE.
IT'S SHOWTIME. HUH?
THIS IS HORRIBLE!
SOMETHING IS RISING
OUT OF THE VORTEX
IN THE CENTER
OF THE QUANTUM BUBBLE.
THAT CAN'T BE!
[ ROARS ]
WELL, I'M SPEECHLESS.
I AM...NOT SCARED.
I AM...SCARED WITLESS.
[ ROARING ]
[ MUFFLED SCREAMING ]
I AM NOT...SCARED!
[ GROWLING ]
NEITHER AM I!
WELL, MAYBE A LITTLE.
YEAH, IT'S BIG AND SCARY.
SO WHAT? I DON'T CARE.
ME NEITHER.
LET'S GO, GUILMON!
NO, WAIT!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
SHIELD OF THE JUST!
AH, NUTS!
YOU WON'T WIN!
NO! GALLANTMON!
[ SCREAMING ]
Jeri: PLEASE LISTEN TO ME.
HUMANS CHANGE THEIR DESTINY
EVERY DAY.
EVERY DECISION WE MAKE
ALTERS THE WORLD.
BUT YOU WANT TO DELETE
EVERYTHING,
THE GOOD AND THE BAD.
Takato: [ Echoing ]
JERI! JERI!
TAKATO.
[ GROWLING ]
ARE YOU OKAY?
I THINK SO.
I'VE HAD JUST ABOUT
ENOUGH OF YOU, D-REAPER!
[ GRUNTING ]
IT'S TOO STRONG!
Rika: I THINK THAT'S OUR CUE,
HENRY. YOU READY?
READY.
WELL, THEN LET'S GO!
MEGA BARRAGE!
SPIRIT STRIKE!
[ SHRIEKING ]
[ Grunting ] NO!
Calumon: DON'T CRY.
I'M COMING.
[ GROANING ]
GOT TO...GET UP,
GET GOING,
GET JERI OUT OF HERE.
TAKATO, WE CAN HANDLE THIS.
YOU JUST FOCUS
ON FINDING JERI.
THANKS, RYO.
[ SHOUTS ]
JUSTIMON, DON'T!
LET'S DO IT!
[ PANTING ]
IT WON'T BE MUCH LONGER.
JERI, WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
AHH.
AHH!
[ SCREAMING CONTINUES ]
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING!
GUILMON!
I'M SORRY, TAKATO.
NO!
Grani: DO YOU WANT TO FLY,
GALLANTMON?
WHO -- WHO ARE YOU?
DO YOU WANT TO FLY?
I WILL GIVE YOU MY WINGS.
WINGS? I COULD FLY?
Both: GRANI!
I CAN NO LONGER MOVE
ON MY OWN,
BUT I CAN GIVE YOU
THE STRENGTH THAT REMAINS IN ME.
YOU CAN HAVE MY WINGS,
GALLANTMON.
GRANI. YOU REALLY ARE
A DIGIMON, AREN'T YOU?
GRANI, ARE YOU SURE?
I'M VERY SURE.
YOU ARE MY FRIENDS.
YOU TALKED TO ME.
THIS IS MY GIFT TO YOU.
GRANI!
Both: A PART OF YOU WILL ALWAYS
BE WITH US, GRANI.
WE ARE ONE -- GRANI AND US!
FINAL JUSTICE!
CAN THAT REALLY BE
GALLANTMON?
[ SHRIEKING ]
[ JERI GASPS ]
AHH...
AHH!
NOW I'M SPEECHLESS!
DUDE, YOU'RE JUST GONNA
HAVE TO KEEP WATCHING
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."