HENRY MADE GARGOMON STAND
ON HIS HEAD
TO GET HIM TO DEDIGIVOLVE
BACK INTO TERRIERMON.
I MEAN, THERE'S NOT A HAT
IN THE WORLD BIG ENOUGH
TO PULL THAT RABBIT OUT OF.
MEANWHILE, YUMAKI WAS STILL
DOING HIS BEST IMPERSONATION
OF A DIGIWORLD BIG BROTHER.
GORILLAMON BIOEMERGED
FROM THE OTHER SIDE
FOR A REMATCH WITH TERRIERMON,
BUT HENRY DIDN'T WANT HIS FRIEND
TO LOSE CONTROL AGAIN
BY DIGIVOLVING,
SO TAKATO AND GIYOMON TRIED
TO TAKE THE MONKEY DOWN
ON THEIR OWN,
BUT IN THE END,
IT TOOK A GROUP EFFORT
TO DEFEAT THE DIGITAL APE.
ISN'T IT AMAZING
WHAT A LITTLE TEAMWORK CAN DO?
DI-DI-DI
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON
DI-DI-DI
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS
TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
WORLD
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS
DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON
WHY'S EVERYONE
OVER AT THE SOCCER FIELD?
GEE, I DON'T KNOW.
A SOCCER GAME, MAYBE?
AT 7:30 IN THE MORNING?
IT COULD HAPPEN.
LOOK AT THAT!
HEY!
WHOA.
I BET IT'S A PRANK
BY THE HOPSCOTCH TEAM.
ALL THAT HOPPING
HAS JARRED THEIR BRAINS.
IS IT SUPPOSED TO BE
A DRAWING OF SOMETHING?
YEAH, IT'S A MASTERFUL
RENDITION OF A SQUIGGLY LINE.
EVERYONE LAUGHED AT ME WHEN
I SAID THAT CHALK WAS DANGEROUS,
BUT WHO'S LAUGHING NOW, HUH?
NO ONE!
WHOA, CHECK OUT THE VEIN
ON HIS FOREHEAD.
OKAY, OKAY, EVERYBODY.
GIVE ME YOUR ATTENTION...
FOR A CHANGE.
YOU, TOO, KAZU.
AW.
I ASSUME NONE OF YOU
VANDALIZED THE SOCCER FIELD,
THOUGH I WOULDN'T
PUT IT PAST SOME OF YOU,
BUT IF YOU KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT IT,
LET ME KNOW, OKAY?
NOW PICK UP YOUR PENCILS.
IT'S TIME FOR A TEST.
[ GROANING AND COMPLAINING ]
BUT YOU NEVER SAID
ANYTHING ABOUT A TEST.
IT'S NOT FAIR!
[ Crying ]
IF LIFE WERE FAIR,
I'D BE IN MAUI.
MAYBE THIS WILL TEACH YOU
TO PAY ATTENTION IN CLASS.
I DON'T WANT
TO LEARN THAT.
[ BELL RINGS ]
I'M TELLING YOU, MAN.
THERE'S SOMETHING REALLY WEIRD
GOING ON HERE.
THOSE DRAWINGS
ON THE SOCCER FIELD
ARE JUST LIKE CROP CIRCLES,
AND THOSE ARE MADE BY ALIENS.
MM-HMM.
YOU GUYS ARE WAY OFF BASE.
THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS ALIENS.
WHAT IT REALLY WAS
WAS A GHOST,
AND THAT DINOSAUR
THE PRINCIPAL SAW --
IT WAS A GHOST DINOSAUR.
OKAY, BUT HOW DID A GHOST
EAT ALL THE FOOD
FROM THE CAFETERIA?
EVERYBODY KNOWS
THAT MEAT LOAF
IS LIKE A GHOST'S
FAVORITE THING.
BESIDES, WHAT ELSE COULD EAT
THE CAFETERIA FOOD AND NOT DIE?
THAT IS TRUE.
HE'S RIGHT.
SO AFTER ALL THAT,
THEN THEY STARTED SAYING
THAT IT WAS CAUSED BY DEMONS
CONJURED UP
BY LAST WEEK'S SPUD BALLS.
HA HA HA. HUH?
WH-WHAT'S WRONG?
DON'T TELL ME
YOU ATE THE SPUD BALLS.
I SAW WHAT DID IT.
UH-OH.
UM, WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU SAW IT?
IT ALL STARTED THIS MORNING.
I WASN'T FEELING WELL,
SO I WENT TO THE INFIRMARY.
THERE I WAS,
TUCKED IN TIGHT,
WITH NOTHING BUT THE SMELL
OF IODINE AND CAMPHOR OIL
TO KEEP ME COMPANY.
IT WAS SO QUIET,
WHEN SUDDENLY --
[ BOTTLES RATTLE ]
HELLO? WHO'S THERE?
I GOT OUT OF BED
AND FEARLESSLY MARCHED
RIGHT OVER TO THE CABINET
TO SEE WHAT WAS THERE.
[ GASPS ]
PROBABLY JUST A CAT.
I MOVED IN LIKE A LION
STALKING ITS PREY --
STEP BY STEP,
INCH BY INCH.
HERE, KITTY, KITTY.
UH-OH.
AAH!
WHERE'D YOU RUN OFF TO,
NICE KITTY CAT?
SINCE WHEN DO CATS
KNOW HOW TO WALK ON THE CEILING?
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
I WAS LUCKY TO MAKE IT
OUT OF THERE IN ONE PIECE.
MAN, YOU'RE BRAVE.
HERE IT COMES.
OVER HERE.
GIVE ME THE BALL.
NO, PASS IT TO ME.
THAT'S IT. GO, GO!
SOMEBODY COVER NUMBER 11.
SCORE!
NOBODY HAS ANY IDEA
WHO DREW THE CHALK LINES.
HMM.
PROBABLY A PRANK.
YEAH, BUT YOU'D THINK
THEY'D HAVE SOME CLUE,
AND THEY DON'T.
WELL, WHOEVER DID DO IT
MUST BE PRETTY CLEVER.
OH!
[ CHEERING ]
OH! HA HA! OH!
YEAH! YEAH! YEAH!
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH, YEAH!
[ GIGGLES ]
HE'S UNSTOPPABLE --
THE BEST PLAYER EVER.
HEY!
HE'S TOO GOOD.
I WANT MY MOMMY.
Students: YAY, CALUMON!
YAY, CALUMON!
[ Giggles ]
YAY, ME!
GREAT GAME, GUYS. DON'T STUDY
TOO HARD THIS WEEKEND.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
OVER THE WEEKEND,
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THE WORD "STUDY" MEANS.
BYE.
YAY!
YAY?
HOW COME NO ONE'S HERE?
MAYBE THAT
BLACK-AND-WHITE DIGIMON
THEY WERE KICKING AROUND
GOT DESTROYED.
WAIT! OH, I KNOW HOW
TO GET PEOPLE HERE.
[ GRUNTING ]
HMM. A DOOR EARRING?
HMM. IT JUST NEEDS
SOME GENTLE PERSUASION.
[ GRUNTING ]
YAY, ME!
NOW THEY'LL COME...
BUT HOPEFULLY MY WAY,
WITHOUT THOSE
BORING STRAIGHT LINES.
THIS IS OUT OF BOUNDS,
AND THIS IS THE GOAL LINE.
AND IF YOU CROSS THIS ONE,
YOU'LL HAVE TO HOP LIKE FROGMON
FOR THE WHOLE GAME.
PERFECT!
NOW THAT'S A FIELD
THAT MAKES SENSE.
EVERYONE
IN THE WHOLE WIDE WORLD
WILL WANT TO PLAY WITH ME --
THE MOST CLEVER DIGIMON EVER!
HA HA! OH! HA HA!
HA HA HA! WHOA.
HE SHOOTS, HE SCORES!
YAY, CALUMON! YAY, CALUMON!
YAY, CALUMON!
HMM? NO ONE CAME.
BUT IT'S THE BEST GAME EVER.
SO HOW COME IT'S OKAY
TO COME HERE TODAY?
'CAUSE IT'S THE WEEKEND.
WEEKEND?
YEAH, NO ONE'S AT SCHOOL.
SEE?
RIGHT -- WAIT, BUT YOU AND I
ARE HERE, SEE?
BUT NO ONE ELSE
IS GOING TO BE HERE, SEE?
THIS IS EVEN WORSE
THAN THE LAST TIME.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT OUR CHALK BUDGET
IS GOING TO BE THIS YEAR?
AND WE'RE HOSTING
THAT BIG HOPSCOTCH TOURNAMENT.
I HAVE AN IDEA.
WHY DON'T WE JUST USE
SOME GROUND-UP BREAD CRUMBS?
BREAD CRUMB --
HAVE YOU BEEN READING
THAT FAIRY TALE BOOK AGAIN?
I JUST LIKE THE PICTURES.
EAT UP, GUYS.
DON'T WORRY,
IT'S NOT FROM THE CAFETERIA.
HMM? HUH?
[ Sniffing ]
MAKING A NEW FRIEND,
GIYOMON?
[ SNIFFING ]
HMM?
JUST DON'T EAT HIM, OKAY?
[ GROANS ]
WHAT'S WRONG?
I SMELL DIGIMON.
DIGIMON?
CAREFUL,
IT MIGHT BE DANGEROUS.
AND ME WITHOUT A WEAPON --
UNLESS, OF COURSE,
IT'S AFRAID OF RABBITS.
OH, WAIT,
THIS WILL WORK.
BACK THERE.
RIGHT.
Both: HUH?
[ SNORING ]
HEY, HE'S A CUTE LITTLE GUY.
OHH. HMM?
HI.
OH? OH!
HELLO, HELLO, HELLO,
HELLO, HELLO!
HEY, THERE.
YO. UNH-UNH-UNH.
WHAT'S WRONG?
DON'T BE AFRAID.
WE'RE YOUR FRIENDS --
HUH?
[ GIGGLING ]
PLAY!
OKAY.
WHOO!
TELL YOU WHAT --
WHY DON'T WE
PLAY LATER, OKAY?
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO, NO.
[ Thinking ] WHY DO I ALWAYS
GET THE DIFFICULT DIGIMON?
[ GIGGLING ]
THAT TICKLES.
HA HA HA!
OHH.
SO YOU'RE CALUMON?
RIGHT.
OHH. HA HA HA!
I WONDER
WHERE HE CAME FROM.
I DIDN'T SEE ANY DIGITAL FIELD
WHEN WE FOUND HIM.
HMM. I'M AMAZED HE WAS
OUT THERE ON HIS OWN.
HE'S OUT THERE.
HOW DO YOU GET YOUR NOSE
SO TICKLY?
HA HA! OOH.
HEY, MAYBE WE SHOULD FIND
A TAMER FOR THE LITTLE GUY.
IT LOOKS
LIKE HE COULD USE ONE.
YEAH, BUT WHO?
HMM. OH.
I THINK I KNOW SOMEONE
WHO COULD DO IT.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S GO GET HIM.
YEAH.
[ Thinking ] THE RED DIGIMON
IS GREAT,
BUT THOSE OTHER GUYS
NEED TO LIGHTEN UP.
ALL RIGHT, MAKE YOUR MOVE.
HMM. OKAY,
I'LL PLAY MY UPGRADE CARD.
HUH? YOU CAN'T DO THAT.
BUT THAT'S NOT FAIR.
THE ONE WHO JUST PLAYED
THE UPGRADE CARD IS KAZU.
HE'S THE ONE
I WAS THINKING OF.
HMM.
I WON. DOESN'T MATTER
IF IT'S FAIR OR NOT.
DOES, TOO.
AHA!
OH, NO. NOT AGAIN.
HE KNOWS ALMOST EVERYTHING
ABOUT DIGIMON.
HMM. YEAH,
BUT EVEN SO,
I'M NOT SURE
THAT HE'D BE THE BEST CHOICE.
LOOK AT THE WAY
HE PLAYS THAT GAME.
HE GIVES HIS DIGIMON
ALL SORTS OF POWER
SO HE CAN BEAT UP
THE OTHER GUY,
BUT HE TAKES AWAY
ALL THE ENERGY IT USES
TO PROTECT ITSELF.
YEAH, THAT SOUNDS LIKE SOMETHING
KAZU WOULD DO, ALL RIGHT.
HE'S REALLY BIG INTO POWER.
HMM.
AND SO WE ENTER THE RING WHERE
THESE TWO PUGNACIOUS PUGILISTS
PLAN TO PUMMEL EACH OTHER
INTO PULP.
YOU'RE GOING DOWN, GIYOMON.
YEAH. GET OUT.
UPGRADE ENERGIZE.
UPGRADE! UPGRADE!
UPGRADE!
YEAH, WELL, YOUR MOTHER
DRESSES YOU FUNNY.
FIGHT!
[ SIGHS ]
YUP, YOU'RE RIGHT, HENRY.
SO,
WHO CAN WE GET NOW?
HEY, SUSIE!
WHAT?
WHO'S SUSIE?
MY SIS.
SHE'S NICE, I GUESS.
MISS PRETTYPANTS,
TIME TO GET READY FOR THE BALL.
LET'S DO WEAR MY CHIFFON COAT.
HEATHCLIFF LOVES ME IN IT.
IT BRINGS OUT MY EYES.
WHATEVER MISS PRETTYPANTS WANTS,
MISS PRETTYPANTS GETS.
HERE YOU GO.
YOU'LL BE THE BELLE OF THE BALL,
AND EVERYONE WILL BE YOUR FRIEND
FOREVER AND EVER AND EVER.
BY NICE YOU MEAN CRAZY?
PRETTY MUCH.
THEN AGAIN,
CALUMON'S NOT PLAYING
WITH A FULL DECK, EITHER.
YEAH, BUT I WOULDN'T WISH
THE MISS PRETTYPANTS TREATMENT
ON ANYONE.
HOW BAD COULD IT BE?
HMM.
OKAY,
LET'S DRESS FOR THE BALL.
OOH.
HERE'S YOUR
PRETTY PINK DRESS.
AHH!
AND YOUR CUTEST RIBBON.
AHH.
AND YOUR FAVORITE
NECKLACE...
AND YOUR FINEST
EASTER BONNET.
UH...
SEE WHAT I MEAN?
MM-HMM.
OF COURSE, HONEY.
WE CAN GET YOU A NEW DRESS
FOR YOUR DOLL.
YAY! PINK DRESS!
PINK DRESS!
Both: [ SIGH ]
YOU KNOW, A GIRL'S
NOT A BAD IDEA,
BUT WE NEED ONE
OUR OWN AGE.
REALLY?
YEAH. IS THERE ANYONE
FROM YOUR CLASS?
UH, A GIRL
FROM MY CLASS, HUH?
HMM.
[ BARKING ]
YOU SEEM NICE.
LET'S BE FRIENDS.
HUH? AAH!
[ SIGHS ]
MAN, MOM'S RIGHT.
MY IMAGINATION
COULD BE A CURSE.
BUT PLAYING
IS LIKE BREATHING --
I'LL PASS OUT
IF I DON'T DO IT SOON.
WE CAN'T LEAVE.
PRETTY PLEASE?
WE COULD PLAY TAG,
OR RACE EACH OTHER.
I'M SO BORED
I'LL EVEN PLAY CHESS.
I'M BORED, TOO,
BUT WE'VE GOT TO DO
WHAT TAKATO SAID.
HE'LL BE REAL MAD IF WE'RE
NOT HERE WHEN HE COMES BACK.
OOH! BUT HE'LL BE EVEN MORE MAD
IF YOU'RE UNHAPPY, RIGHT?
WELL --
HUH.
[ WHIMPERS ]
UH...
YOU SEE --
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
MAYBE WE SHOULD PLAY.
MM-HMM!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
WE DIDN'T FIND ANYONE RIGHT
FOR CALUMON,
AND IT TOOK ALL DAY.
YEAH. COME ON,
WE'D BETTER GET BACK
BEFORE GIYOMON
EATS THE WHOLE PARK.
LET'S WAIT.
MAYBE HE'LL EAT CALUMON
AND SOLVE OUR PROBLEM.
WELL, THIS IS IT.
OH, NO.
THERE'S THREE DOOR EARRINGS.
THIS THING WEARS
WAY TOO MUCH JEWELRY.
WHO'S IT TRYING
TO IMPRESS?
WE CAN DIG A TUNNEL
UNDERNEATH THE DOOR.
YAY! WHOO-HOO! WHOO!
AND DON'T FORGET THE LINE
THAT MAKES YOU HOP LIKE FROGMON
FOR THE WHOLE GAME
IF YOU CROSS IT.
OKAY, HOLD ON.
WHOA!
ARE WE ALL DONE?
WE NEED A LINE THAT MAKES YOU
CRAWL AROUND LIKE WORMMON.
YEAH! HA HA HA.
OH, I'M STARTING
TO GET DIZZY.
I THINK I'M GOING TO BE SICK.
THIS IS THE MOST FUN EVER!
[ SIGHS ]
OH, IT LOOKS GOOD,
GIYOMON.
WHOA!
WHAT DID YOU DO?
ME?
OH, MAN, THEY'RE GONE,
AND I TOLD THEM,
LIKE, 20 TIMES NOT TO LEAVE.
DOESN'T MATTER HOW MANY TIMES
YOU TELL THEM
IF THEY'RE NOT LISTENING.
EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE.
YEAH, I GUESS.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
HUH?
THAT DOESN'T LOOK
FINE TO ME.
DOES THAT LOOK FINE TO YOU?
IT'S BY THE SCHOOL.
YEAH.
IS THAT AN INKY VOID
THAT MAKES YOU WADDLE
LIKE PENGUINMON?
I DON'T THINK KNOW,
BUT GOOD IDEA.
AHH!
OH!
LOOKS LIKE
SOMETHING'S COMING.
HA HA HA!
GET BACK,
HIDEOUS CREATURE.
BEWARE MY WRATH.
DON'T BE SCARED.
DON'T WORRY. I WOULDN'T HURT
A TINY THING LIKE YOU.
I'M NOT TINY!
I'M A DANGEROUS DIGIMON
WHOSE POWER WILL MAKE YOU
TREMBLE WITH FEAR.
AND YOU'RE TINY.
I'M JUST OVERDUE
FOR A GROWTH SPURT, OKAY?
NIGHTMARE SHOCKER!
DON'T SEEM
SO TINY NOW, HUH?
NIGHTMARE SHOCKER!
GRAAH!
IT'S A DIGITAL FIELD.
ANOTHER DIGIMON
IS COMING THROUGH.
LET'S GO.
RIGHT.
WHY AM I SURE
THIS INVOLVES GIYOMON?
HA HA HA!
WHY ARE YOU PICKING ON ME?
GIYOMON'S THE ONE
WHO INSULTED YOU.
I DON'T CARE.
DEMON DARTS!
[ WHIMPERS ]
OHH!
HA HA HA!
PYROSPHERE!
HUH? AAH!
HEY!
GRAAH!
[ GROANS ]
CALUMON! GIYOMON!
WHO IS THAT?
BEALOMON --
CHAMPION LEVEL --
NASTY LITTLE THING.
THIS WILL EVEN OUT
THE PLAYING FIELD.
DIGIMODIFY --
WILD WING ACTIVATE.
GET HIM!
RIGHT. GRAAH!
AAH!
PYROSPHERE!
UNNH!
NOT SO EASY NOW THAT
GIYOMON CAN FLY, TOO, HUH?
AW, NUTS! GRR!
TERRIERMON, IT'S YOUR TURN.
I'M ON IT.
DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMODIFY.
SPEED ACTIVATE.
NIGHTMARE SHOCKER!
ARE YOU OKAY?
MM-HMM.
HA HA HA!
HAVE YOU HAD
ENOUGH YET, FOOLS?
HURRY UP.
I CAN'T DECIDE.
DEMON --
YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU'RE TOO TINY
TO BOTHER WITH,
BUT A FIGHT'S A FIGHT.
RENIMON?
I HATE TO BEAT UP ON A GIRL,
BUT IF YOU INSIST.
DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMODIFY.
CLONE ACTIVATE.
NIGHTMARE SHOCKER!
YES.
HA! GOT YOU.
THE ONLY THING YOU'VE GOT
IS A SERIOUS CASE
OF THE UGLIES.
LOOK BEHIND YOU.
UH-OH.
DIAMOND STORM!
[ Thinking ] SHE DIDN'T
EVEN THINK TWICE
ABOUT ABSORBING HIM.
DON'T BOTHER
WITH ANY THANKS.
I DID IT FOR THE DATA,
AND THAT'S ALL.
DATA?
DIGIMON ARE LIVING CREATURES,
AND YOU...
KILL THEM!
HE'S RIGHT.
THEY ARE ALIVE.
HMM. NO.
DIGIMON ARE NOTHING MORE
THAN DATA.
RENIMON?
HUH?
[ GIGGLES ]
WHAT IS THAT LITTLE THING?
HI! WANT TO PLAY?
HEY, DON'T YOU TOUCH HIM.
COME ON, RENIMON.
WHY WOULD I WANT
TO WASTE MY TIME
WITH THESE GOGGLE HEADS?
YEAH? WELL, GOOD RIDDANCE.
WHAT'S HER DEAL?
FINALLY, A LITTLE FUN!
HUH?
HA HA HA HA! HO HO!
WAIT, IT'S DANGEROUS
OUT THERE BY YOURSELF.
IT'S DANGEROUS HERE
WITH YOU, TOO,
AND THERE MUST BE PEOPLE
UP THERE
WHO ARE MORE FUN THAN YOU.
GOODBYE, GIYOMON. WHOA!
I HOPE HE'S OKAY.
HE'S A STRANGE
LITTLE DIGIMON.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE HIM.
I DON'T KNOW
IF HE EVEN WANTS A TAMER.
OR HOW LONG
THAT TAMER WOULD SURVIVE.
YOU GOING TO BE OKAY?
YEAH.
FIRST IT'S CHALK,
NOW IT'S CHALK AND HOLES.
I'M ABOUT READY TO PAVE
THIS FIELD OVER WITH CONCRETE.
WE ALREADY HAVE
A PARKING LOT.
YOU CAN BE REPLACED,
YOU KNOW.
LOOK AT THAT!
WHOA!
IS IT SUPPOSED TO BE
A SCHOOL PROJECT OR SOMETHING?
YEAH, IT'S A HOUSING COMPLEX
FOR LOW-INCOME GOPHERS.
I BET IT'S A PRANK
BY THE SHOT PUT TEAM.
ALL THAT LIFTING AND THROWING
HAS JARRED THEIR BRAINS.
WHY ME?
IT WAS ALIEN GHOSTS.
ALIEN GHOSTS AND GNOMES
THAT TRAVEL THROUGH TIME.
YOU KNOW, THEY PROBABLY
WOULDN'T EVEN BELIEVE US
IF WE TOLD THEM
THE TRUTH.
I KNOW.
JEEZ, HOW MANY TIMES
ARE THESE GUYS
GOING TO TRASH THE SCHOOL,
AND WHAT IS THE DEAL
WITH REIKA, ANYWAY?
BETTER KEEP WATCHING
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."