WILL REIKA TRY
TO FIGURE OUT DIGIVOLUTION?
CALUMON SHOWED UP TO PLAY,
BUT REIKA WASN'T IN THE MOOD.
IMPMON APPEARED AND TRIED
TO PICK A FIGHT WITH RENAMON,
WHO WASN'T IN THE MOOD EITHER.
HENRY TRIED TO TEACH TAKATO
THAT THERE'S MORE
TO THIS TAMING BUSINESS
THAN JUST FLASHING
MODIFY CARDS.
THEN REIKA WAS KIDNAPPED
BY ICEDEVIMON,
WHO TRIED TO MAKE REIKA
HIS NEW TAMER.
THE GUYS CAME TO HER RESCUE,
BUT IT WAS ONLY WHEN REIKA
ADMITTED SHE NEEDED HER
THAT RENAMON APPEARED.
SHE DIGIVOLVED INTO CUBIMON
AND DEFROSTED THAT ICY DUDE.
I THINK THE WHOLE EXPERIENCE
KIND OF FREAKED REIKA OUT.
WHY ELSE WOULD SHE SAY
THAT SHE HATED ALL DIGIMON?
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
♪ WORLD
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMODIFY
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
[ SIREN WAILING ]
I HATE DIGIMON.
DIGIMODIFY. ALL RIGHT,
WATCH AND LEARN, BOYS.
I'M COMING IN
FOR AN AERIAL ATTACK.
HYPERWINGS -- HA HA --
YOU'RE GROUNDED, PAL.
HUH?
THAT'S IT. I WIN.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU BEAT ME.
AMAZING. WHAT A GAME.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
A COMBO LIKE THAT BEFORE.
HA HA.
NOT TOO SHABBY, HUH?
PYROSPHERE!
AH! FROZEN CLAW!
DIGIMODIFY!
HYPERWING ACTIVATE.
LET GO! AAH!
PYROSPHERE!
AAH!
I GUESS HAVING
REAL LIFE EXPERIENCE
KIND OF PAYS OFF, HUH?
IT'S HARDLY EVEN
A CHALLENGE ANYMORE
PLAYING THE CARD GAME.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY REAL LIFE EXPERIENCE?
OH, TOO BAD, BUT WE SEEM
TO BE OUT OF TIME.
QUIT PLAYING DUMB,
CHUMLEY.
I HEARD WHAT YOU SAID.
NOW WHAT'S UP, HUH?
OH, YOU MUST BE
IMAGINING THINGS.
WELL, I GOT TO FLY.
IT'S BEEN REAL.
NOW COME ON.
JUST ONE MORE GAME.
HEY, GET BACK HERE, GOGGLEBRAIN.
I WANT A REMATCH.
SORRY. BYE-BYE.
HA HA HA.
HA HA.
OH, NO MORE?
I'M SORRY, BUT THIS IS ALL
THAT WE HAVE LEFT RIGHT NOW.
I'LL BRING YOU
SOME FRESH BREAD LATER
WITH PEANUT BUTTER,
ALL RIGHT?
MM, 'KAY.
GOOD BOY.
WE'RE A GREAT TEAM,
AREN'T WE, GUILMON?
THERE'S NOT A DIGIMON AROUND
THAT'S STRONG ENOUGH
TO BEAT THE TWO OF US.
YEAH.
PEOPLE ARE GIVING ME WEIRD
LOOKS. YOU SHOULDN'T HAVE COME.
I HAD TO.
SUSIE WOULD HAVE HAD ME
IN TIGHTS
AND THAT TUTU BY NOW.
IT'S EMBARRASSING
AND PAINFUL.
WHOA.
THERE'S SOME KIND
OF STRANGE FOG
OVER BY THE WESTGATE BRIDGE.
MY, THE WEATHER
CHANGES FAST HERE.
HERE THEY COME.
DIGIMON.
[ ELECTRONIC SIGNALS ]
I CAN'T SEEM TO SECURE
A TRACER LOCK
ON THE ANOMALY'S DATA.
WE WON'T MAKE IT IN TIME.
IT'S GOING TO BIOEMERGE.
USE YUGOTH.
STOP THAT THING.
IT'S TOO LATE, SIR.
IT'S ALREADY BEGUN.
FULL BREECH ESTIMATED
IN 60 SECONDS. AT THIS POINT,
THE APPLICATION
OF THE YUGOTH PROGRAM
COULD BE EXTREMELY DANGEROUS.
DON'T QUESTION ME.
CIRCUMVENT THE SAFETY GRID
AND RELEASE THE PROGRAM NOW.
THAT WILD ONE IS
A TICKING TIME BOMB. APPLY!
UHH.
[ HORNS HONKING ]
I REALIZE HOW NICE THE VIEW IS
FROM UP HERE,
BUT HOW LONG DO YOU THINK
IT'LL STAY THIS WAY
IF WE DON'T CHECK IT OUT?
HEY, TERRIERMON, WAIT.
COME ON, HENRY.
GOTCHA!
HEY, THAT HURT.
WE'VE GOT TO GO HOME NOW.
WHAT?
WE'RE GOING HOME.
WAIT A MINUTE.
PLEASE DON'T TELL ME
YOU CHANGED YOUR MIND
ABOUT SUSIE AND THAT TUTU,
'CAUSE I WON'T DO IT.
HENRY, LET ME GO.
I WANT TO SEE IT.
TERRIERMON, HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU?
UHH! I WON'T.
DID YOU SEE THAT?
I HOPE NOT.
WILL YOU STOP? WHY DON'T WE
LET SOMEONE ELSE HANDLE THIS
FOR A CHANGE?
CONFIRMED -- YUGOTH HAS
FOUND THE WILD ONE.
MAKE SURE
IT'S COMPLETELY DESTROYED.
I WANT NOTHING LEFT.
YES, SIR.
NO!
WHOA.
HUH.
[ MURMURING ]
"HAVE SOMEONE ELSE
HANDLE IT."
TERMINATION OF WILD ONE
IS CONFIRMED.
TALLY, GET ME AN ANALYSIS
OF THE IMPACT ON THE REAL WORLD
RIGHT AWAY,
PLUS ALL THE DATA YOU'VE GOT
ON THE POINT OF TERMINATION.
NO MATTER HOW THEY PLAY
AT BEING LIVING CREATURES,
THEY'RE NOTHING MORE THAN JUST
TRASH ON THE INTERNET TO ME.
HA HA HA.
I WILL...
HUH?
HAVE MY REVENGE.
HEY, UM, YOU NEVER EXPLAINED
WHY YOU WOULDN'T
LET ME FIGHT BEFORE.
WHAT'S UP WITH THAT?
NOTHING'S UP. I JUST
DON'T WANT YOU TO FIGHT, OKAY?
REIKA WAS RIGHT.
YOU ARE STARTING TO SOUND
LIKE A BROKEN RECORD.
LEAVE HER OUT OF THIS.
IT'S JUST THAT, ON THE NET,
DIGIMON ONLY EXIST
TO DO BATTLE.
SO BECAUSE I'M HERE NOW
YOU WANT ME TO LAY AROUND
LIKE A HOUSE PET,
IS THAT RIGHT?
ARE YOU GOING
TO LET ME EXPLAIN OR NOT?
HENRY, YOU ONCE TOLD ME
THAT MY VERY EXISTENCE
IN THE REAL WORLD WAS WRONG.
IS THAT STILL TRUE?
IS THAT
HOW YOU FEEL ABOUT ME?
'CAUSE IF IT IS,
I'LL SIGN UP
FOR THE MISS PRETTY PANTS
TREATMENT RIGHT NOW.
YOU JUT SAY THE WORD.
HEY, YOU KNOW THAT'S NOT
WHAT I MEANT. WE'RE A TEAM.
YOU NEVER EXPLAINED
WHY YOU WOULDN'T
LET ME FIGHT BEFORE.
WHAT'S UP WITH THAT?
HMM.
UHH.
NOTHING'S UP. I JUST
DON'T WANT YOU TO FIGHT, OKAY?
[ SIGHS ]
I'M GOING TO HAVE TO FIGHT
SOMETIME, BUT WHEN?
OKAY, MOMMY.
AY!
THERE YOU ARE,
TERRIERMON.
HA HA HA.
[ GULPS ]
HUH?
RENAMON!
[ GIGGLES ]
[ Thinking ] OH,
I THINK I'M GOING TO BE SICK.
AND UPSA-DAISY.
HA HA.
HA HA HA.
I'M GOING TO GET SOME MORE MILK,
OKAY? I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
NUMMY, NUMMY --
DELICIOUS MILK.
OOPSIE -- LITTLE SPILL.
LET'S CLEAN YOU UP.
AND NOW IT'S TIME
FOR POTTY.
YAY. HA HA HA.
[ Thinking ] IF SHE
COMES NEAR ME WITH A DIAPER,
I'M OUT OF HERE.
[ Thinking ] I THINK
SHE WANTS ME TO FOLLOW HER.
[ Thinking ]
CATCH ME IF YOU CAN.
[ Thinking ] GUESS I DIDN'T
MAKE ANY FRIENDS YESTERDAY.
I HATE THEM.
HUH?
I HATE DIGIMON --
ALL OF THEM.
HUH?
OH.
[ SIGHS ]
WHO NEEDS THEM, ANYWAY?
RENAMON?
NOPE, JUST ME.
HOW COME YOU THREW THIS AWAY?
HUH? HOW COME?
GET OUT OF MY ROOM,
YOU OVERGROWN RAT.
YOU'RE NOT HAPPY, ARE YOU?
HEY, LET'S PLAY!
THAT'LL MAKE YOU HAPPY.
OH, PLEASE.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
MAYBE LATER
THIS WILL MAKE YOU...
HAPPY! HA HA!
HAPPY, HAPPY, HAPPY!
OH! HA HA!
HOW ABOUT NOW? WELL?
[ SIGHS ]
[ Thinking ]
FOR SOME REASON, TERRIERMON
FEELS LIKE HE HAS TO FIGHT.
WHY WOULD I PURPOSELY
PUT MY FRIEND IN DANGER?
HE JUST DOESN'T UNDERSTAND
THAT IF ANYTHING EVER HAPPENED
TO HIM BECAUSE OF ME,
I'D NEVER FORGIVE MYSELF.
[ LAUGHING ]
[ CAR ALARM ACTIVATES ]
GARGOMON!
UNTIL RECENTLY, I THOUGHT
MY ONLY PURPOSE HERE
IN THE REAL WORLD WAS
TO FIGHT AND LOAD THE DATA
OF THOSE I DEFEATED.
DIGIVOLVING
AND VANQUISHING MY ENEMIES
WERE THE ONLY THINGS
THAT MADE ME FEEL WORTHY.
AND REIKA --
HER ONLY ATTACHMENT TO ME
WAS AS A TAMER
WHO COULD MAKE ME STRONGER,
BUT NOW I'M NOT SO SURE.
THERE'S GOT TO BE
A BIGGER REASON
WHY ME AND MY FRIENDS
WERE CHOSEN
TO BE DIGIMON TAMERS
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
HUMPH.
IT WOULD HELP BOTH OF US IF
WE COULD JUST FIGURE THAT OUT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
RENAMON? HELLO?
[ SNORING ]
SHE'S SURE A LOT CUTER
WHEN SHE'S ASLEEP.
[ SIGHS ]
[ BELL RINGS ]
[ LAUGHING ]
HUH?
HEY, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
OUT HERE?
HAVE YOU TAKEN UP
BIRD WATCHING OR SOMETHING?
I WAS HOPING ANOTHER DIGIMON
WOULD SHOW UP.
I'M READY
FOR ANOTHER BATTLE.
I WANT TO USE THAT
COMBINATION ON GUILMON AGAIN.
I THINK YOU NEED
A VACATION.
HUH?
THERE YOU ARE! THOUGHT
YOU COULD ESCAPE ME, HUH?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
REVENGE, TAKATO,
FOR THAT STUPID COMBINATION
YOU PULLED ON ME YESTERDAY.
I WANT A REMATCH.
YEAH, APPARENTLY
YOU THINK YOU'RE HOT STUFF NOW.
THINK YOU CAN TAKE US AGAIN,
BIG SHOT?
YOU SOUND PRETTY TOUGH
FROM WAY OVER THERE, HUH?
I'LL TAKE YOU BOTH ON
ANY TIME
WITH WHATEVER YOU'VE GOT.
I'M READY NOW.
SAY YOUR PRAYERS,
'CAUSE YOU'RE GOING DOWN.
LET'S GO.
[ LAUGHING ]
HEY, DON'T YOU BOYS EVER
GET TIRED OF DIGIMON?
THAT'S ALL YOU TALK ABOUT.
OH, YOU KNOW, JERI.
KIDS WILL BE KIDS.
MAYBE WE ARE JUST KIDS,
BUT AT LEAST WE HAVE A HOBBY.
NOW SCRAM!
[ GIGGLING ]
COME ON, NIKKI,
WE HAVE MORE
IMPORTANT THINGS TO DO.
SUCH SILLY BOYS.
GIRLS -- I DON'T THINK
I'LL EVER UNDERSTAND THEM.
WELL, CHUMLEY,
ARE YOU READY?
SURE, YEAH.
HEY, HENRY,
ARE YOU COMING ALONG TO --
WHERE'D HE GO? HUH.
ARE WE GOING SHOPPING?
WE'RE DOING NOTHING.
YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO STAY HOME, REMEMBER?
I MAY NEVER GO HOME
AFTER WHAT SHE DID.
SUSIE'S CHAMBER OF HORRORS
IS WORSE THAN BATTLING
ANY DIGIMON.
COME ON!
PATIENCE, GRASSHOPPER.
GUESS WHAT?
I WON, MR. INVINCIBLE.
AAH! I CAN'T BELIEVE
I DIDN'T SEE THAT COMING.
I HOPE YOU ENJOYED
YOUR LITTLE VICTORY YESTERDAY,
'CAUSE YOU'LL NEVER
HAVE ONE AGAIN.
YEAH, ALL YOU'RE GOING TO FEEL
IS PAIN
WHEN WE KEEP WHOOPING YOU.
HA HA HA!
LOOK, IT'S JUST A STUPID
CARD GAME, ANYWAY.
I HAVE MUCH MORE IMPORTANT
THINGS TO DO WITH MY TIME.
WINNING A REAL DIGIMON BATTLE
IS WHAT SEPARATES
THE BOYS FROM THE MEN.
REAL DIGIMON? WHO ARE YOU
TRYING TO KID HERE, PAL?
YOU'RE A LOSER AND A LIAR.
I AM NOT.
HA HA HA!
YEAH, AND I'VE GOT
THE LOCH NESS MONSTER
IN MY BATHTUB.
YOU WANT TO SEE HIM?
SHOW ME A REAL DIGIMON.
I WILL.
GIVE IT UP.
I'M NOT LYING!
OKAY, THEN PROVE IT.
WELL --
HEY, COME ON.
NESSIE'S WAITING.
ALL RIGHT, YOU ASKED FOR IT,
AND YOU'RE GOING TO GET IT.
FOLLOW ME.
Both: ALL RIGHT.
NOW YOU GUYS SWEAR
THAT YOU WON'T TELL
ANYONE ABOUT THIS.
WHATEVER.
I SWEAR.
GUILMON?
YEAH, RIGHT, DOOFUS.
YOU'RE SO FULL OF IT --
GRAAH!
WHAT'S UP?
MOMMY! HELP!
TAKATO, DID YOU CALL ME?
YEAH. WERE YOU ASLEEP?
WELL, IT WAS MY NAPPY TIME.
[ SNIFFING ]
SORRY, I DIDN'T BRING
ANY BREAD WITH ME THIS TIME.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT THAT.
I SMELL A DIGIMON.
YEAH!
[ HORNS HONKING ]
[ BEEPING ]
TRACER IS LOCKED
AND YUGOTH HAS BEEN DEPLOYED.
SAY GOODBYE.
IMPOSSIBLE!
WHAT WAS THAT?
THE WILD ONE
WE TERMINATED EARLIER
JUST COMPLETELY
DESTROYED YUGOTH.
I'M GOING TO ENJOY MY REVENGE
ON YOU PATHETIC HUMANS.
HA HA HA!
I NEED TO KNOW
WHERE HE IS NOW!
[ BEEPING ]
I'VE LOST HIM.
HE'S JUST BIOEMERGED.
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
WHOA, SOMEBODY
NEEDS A TUNE-UP.
AAH! WHAT'S GOING ON?
HEY, GET OFF OF ME!
GREETINGS.
GRR!
WHOA, IT'S THE SAMURAI MASTER
MUSYAMON --
A CHAMPION-LEVEL
WIZARD TYPE.
HE CAN SLICE AND DICE
AN ENTIRE CITY
WITH HIS SHOGUN SWORD.
GRR!
VENGEANCE IS MINE!
♪ DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMODIFY!
HYPERSONIC ACTIVATE!
GRAAH!
DIGIMODIFY!
MEGAPYROSPHERE ACTIVATE!
LET HIM HAVE IT!
PYROSPHERE!
TAKING ORDERS FROM A HUMAN?
PATHETIC.
OH, BOY.
HEY, COME ON.
YOU CAN'T GIVE UP NOW.
YOU CAN DO IT!
LOOKS LIKE
WE'VE GOT COMPANY, HENRY.
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT.
I'VE CONFIRMED THE BIOEMERGENCE
POINT COORDINATES
AT THE WEST INTERSECTION
OF THE SHINJUKU BIG GUARD CABLE.
EXCELLENT.
THE FOG'S SO THICK,
I CAN'T SEE THE SIGNAL LIGHT.
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO CROSS THE STREET?
COME ON, HENRY.
AREN'T YOU CURIOUS?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
HEY, STOP RIGHT THERE.
COME BACK! STOP!
THERE YOU ARE.
WHY DID YOU FLY AWAY?
OH, NO.
FIGHT ME, YOU HUMAN COWARD.
THIS IS BAD.
DIGIMODIFY!
HYPERWING -- ACTIVATE!
SOMETHING DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT.
USE THE WINGS LIKE LAST TIME.
YOU CAN DO IT.
I TRIED...
AND I CAN'T STOP!
IS THAT THE BEST YOU'VE GOT?
TAKATO, WATCH OUT!
HUH? HENRY, HELP ME.
WHAT NOW? IF I DO NOTHING,
WE'LL ALL BE MADE INTO SUSHI.
HEH HEH HEH!
I DON'T THINK I CAN
TALK US OUT OF THIS ONE.
GOODBYE, HUMAN.
WE GOT TO STOP HIM.
WELL, IT'S ABOUT TIME.
♪ DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMODIFY!
HYPERSONIC ACTIVATE!
TIME TO TEACH THIS BAD BOY
IT'S NOT SAFE
TO PLAY WITH KNIVES.
HUH?
UNNH!
FINISH THE JOB.
OKAY.
MAYBE THIS WILL HELP.
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON
♪ DI-DI
TERRIERMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON
♪ DI-DI
GARGOMON!
♪ DIGIMON
WOW.
BOY, HE'LL NEVER LEARN.
HA HA!
SHOGUN SWORD!
CHARGE!
TURBO LASER!
[ Thinking ]
HE DID IT.
I'LL SAVE YOU.
NO!
GREAT JOB, GARGOMON.
HUH? OHH!
HERE YOU GO.
WOW! THANK YOU.
LET'S GO.
I'M GOING, I'M GOING.
HOLD ON.
OKAY.
LET'S GET HER BACK
BEFORE ANYONE NOTICES.
BYE.
MOM, THE DIGIMON --
THEY SAVED MY LIFE.
CAN YOU SEE THEM?
THEY'RE REAL ONES, MOM.
OH, YEAH,
THEY'RE BEAUTIFUL.
COME ON, NOW. LET'S GO.
YOU OKAY
WITH ALL THIS, HENRY?
YEAH. THERE REALLY WAS
NO OTHER CHOICE.
I GUESS TERRIERMON WAS RIGHT.
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO FIGHT.
GOODBYE, HUMAN.
TERRIERMON --
I MEAN, GARGOMON,
I OWE YOU AN APOLOGY.
THERE ARE SOME BATTLES
WORTH FIGHTING.
YUP.
NOW THAT WE'RE WORKING
TOGETHER AS PARTNERS,
I GUESS I NEED TO LEARN
MORE ABOUT TAMING.
MOMENTIE.
HEY, GUILMON,
I OWE YOU AN APOLOGY, TOO.
I REALLY MESSED UP TODAY.
I JUST KEPT SWIPING
ONE CARD AFTER ANOTHER.
I DIDN'T EVEN THINK ABOUT
WHAT MIGHT HAPPEN TO YOU.
NO PROBLEM.
I KIND OF LIKED FLYING, ANYWAY.
TOMEMINE!
MOMENTIE?
MOMENTIE.
MOMENTIE!
MALTAYMON?
All: NO, GUILMON, IT'S MOMENTIE!
HMM.
HAS HYPNOSE LOST CONTROL?
HOW CAN THESE GUYS MOMENTIE
AT A TIME LIKE THIS?
GUESS WE'LL SEE...
ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."