WITH TAKATO, HENRY,
AND TERRIERMON
SUCKED INTO A DATA STREAM,
THE GANG WENT OFF TO FIND THEM.
THEY MET UP WITH ANDROMON,
WHO'S FIGHTING THIS SERPENT
DIGIMON WHO KIDNAPPED JERI.
THE GUYS HAD TO GET THE HEP
OF THE GEKKOMON TO SAVE HE.
ANDROMON DE-DIGIVOLVED
THE GUARDROMON.
HE CAME UP WITH THIS
TROJAN-HORSE IDEA,
AND EVERYONE HID INSIDE USED TO
TRANSPORT THE DATA SHAKES.
JERI HELPED LEOMON DEFEAT
OROCHIMON WITH A LADY
DEVIMON OPTION CARD.
LOOKS LIKE JERI JUST MIGT
MAKE A TOUGH TAMER AFTER ALL.
OH, DID I MENTION KAZU
FINALLY GOT A DIGIMON?
DI, DI, DI
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS
TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE WORLD
DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS.
DIGIMODIFY.
DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON!
JUST A LITTLE FURTHER.
NOW, WHY DOES
"JUST A LITTLE FURTHER"
HAVE TO BE SO FAR AWAY?
AT LAST WE MEET, MR. MIZUNO --
OR WOULD YOU PREFER "SHIBUMI?"
YOU'RE A VERY DIFFICULT MAN
TO FIND.
NOW, IF YOU'LL BE SO KIND
AS TO COME WITH US.
HEY, COME BACK!
HEY!
UH!
WAIT, WE JUST WANT --
HEY!
UH!
OH!
SHIBUMI, WAIT!
MAN, THIS WHOLE WORLD
IS AGAINST ME.
I'M NEVER GONNA GET BACK
TO GUILMON.
COME ON, DON'T
GIVE UP, TAKATO.
I'M SURE WE'LL FIND
A WAY OUT OF HERE.
MMM.
[ GASPS ]
ANY LUCK?
BLEEDELEEDLE!
ONLY BAD LUCK.
WELL, THAT'S PAR
FOR THE COURSE.
NOT EVEN ANY OTHER CAVES
LIKE THIS ONE?
MNH-MNH.
YOU SURE?
YOU WANT TO CHECK?
NOW WHAT ARE WE
GONNA DO?
WE'LL THINK
OF SOMETHING.
YEAH, LIKE WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT MAYBE
WE CAN BUILD A SUBMARINE
OUT OF ALL YOUR
NEGATIVE ENERGY.
YOU'RE RIGHT. SORRY.
[ SIGHS ]
HEY, MAYBE WE CAN
DIG OUR WAY OUT OF HERE!
YEAH, GOOD IDEA!
[ BEEPING ]
DIGIMODIFY!
DIGMON'S DRILL ACTIVATE!
[ WHIRRING ]
OOH! UH!
YOU GUYS OWE ME HUGE FOR THE
HEADACHE I'M GONNA GET!
UH! OHHH!
WAIT. WAIT.
WHAT? THEY'RE HERE,
AND THEY'RE NOT HERE?
WHAT KIND OF EXPLANATION
IS THAT?
TELL ME WHERE
THIS DIGITAL WORLD IS,
AND I'LL GO AND GET KAZU
MYSELF, OKAY?
YEAH, WHAT'S
THE BIG SECRET?!
GETTING THERE IS NOT
QUITE SO EASY, I'M AFRAID.
OH, MY POOR KIDS.
[ CRYING ]
IT'LL BE OKAY, HONEY.
TRUST ME OR TRUST JANYU OR
TRUST SOMEONE, I GUESS.
SHE'S UPSET BECAUSE KENTA
LEFT A NOTE BY THE COFFEE POT
INSTEAD OF SAYING
GOODBYE.
OH, "GOODBYE"?
WELL, I'M SURE
THEY'LL BE COMING BACK.
WHAT PROOF DO YOU HAVE
OF THAT?
PEOPLE!
WE COULD ARGUE ABOUT THIS
ALL DAY,
BUT MR. WONG HERE
CAN EXPLAIN EVERYTHING
IF YOU WOULD JUST PIPE DOWN
FOR ONE TINY MINUTE
AND STOP INTERRUPTING!
FINE.
YOU'RE DOING IT
AGAIN!
I KNOW THIS IS
A TENSE TIME FOR ALL OF YOU,
BUT WE ALL WANT WHAT'S BEST
FOR OUR CHILDREN, DON'T WE?
NOW, WHERE DID I LEAVE
OFF, ANYWAY?
YOU WERE SAYING
SOMETHING ABOUT
WHY IT HAD TO BE CHILDREN.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
I'LL FIELD THIS ONE.
I WAS ONE OF THE FIRST ONES TO
MAKE DIGIMON BACK IN THE '80s.
WHEN WE PROGRAMMED
THOSE EARLY DIGIMON,
WE BASED THEM ON STORIES
OR DREAMS OF OUR CHILDREN.
AND NOW IT SEEMS THOSE CREATURES
THAT WE CREATED
HAVE AN AFFINITY FOR KIDS.
DIGIMON SIMPLY LIKE CHILDREN.
I ALSO THINK THAT THE BOND
BETWEEN THE DIGIMON
AND THE CHILDREN IS BASED
ON IMAGINATION AND BELIEF.
YOU NEED A CHILD'S POWER
OF BELIEF
TO OPEN A GATE
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
BUT HOW DOWE
GET THAT?
I DON'T KNOW
IF I'VE EVER...HAD THAT.
YOU'LL HAVE TO FIND
A DEEPER BELIEF,
OR WE MAY NEVER SEE
RIKA AGAIN.
WHAT IF THEY CAN'T
GET BACK?
DIGIMODIFY!
FRIGIMON SUB-ZERO ICE PUNCH
ACTIVATE!
[ PANTING ]
I SURE HOPE
THIS WORKS!
UH!
WHOA, THAT WAS
A CLOSE ONE.
NOW WHAT?
WE CAN'T DIG OUR WAY OUT
IF THERE'S ONLY WATER
ON THE OTHER SIDE OF THIS ROCK.
WAIT, THERE MUST BE
SOME CARD WE CAN USE.
HEY, WHAT ABOUT THIS?
NO WAY.
NOW WHO'S
BEING NEGATIVE?
I MEAN, IT WORKED
ONCE BEFORE, DIDN'T IT?
BUT IT'S ALL WET.
HOW CAN IT WORK NOW?
HEY, IT'S WORTH A TRY.
[ BEEPING ]
UH, IT TURNED ON.
HOLD ON, WHAT IS --
WHOA!
WHAT'S WRONG NOW?
NOTHING -- SOMETHING'S
ACTUALLY RIGHT FOR A CHANGE.
IT'S AN E-MAIL
FROM YAMAKI!
HEY!
STAY CALM.
WHY DON'TYOU
STAY CALM?
EXCUSE ME?
SORRY -- CALMING.
[ BELL RINGS ]
WE'LL TRY TO GET
IN TOUCH
WITH THE OTHER PROGRAMMERS
ON THE PROJECT
AND SEE WHAT WE CAN DO.
JANYU, WE'LL BE SURE
TO KEEP YOU INFORMED
OF OUR PROGRESS.
AND I'LL BE GLAD
TO HELP, TOO.
HMM?
AND HOW DO YOU PROPOSE
TO HELP US?
I'VE GOT SOMETHING HERE
YOU MIGHT BE INTERESTED IN.
DOES IT HAVE TO DO
WITH JUGGERNAUT?
THAT'S WHAT WE SAW
IN THE SKY YESTERDAY.
EVEN AFTER EVERYTHING
THAT'S HAPPENED,
YOU PLAN TO USE IT
AGAIN, DON'T YOU?!
THAT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
HUH.
HERE, TAKE A LOOK
AT THIS.
UH.
HEY, IT'S FROM TAKATO!
HE SAYS HE'S FINE.
HE SAYS THEY'RE FINE.
THEY'RE FINE.
HOW DID YOU GET THIS,
YAMAKI?
WELL, BEFORE THEY LEFT,
I GAVE THEM A GIFT, ONE
OF MY COMMUNICATION DEVICES.
CAN YOU TALK TO THEM
RIGHT NOW?
POOR RIKA -- LOST
WITHOUT HER GOOD SCARF.
SHE'LL BE FINE.
OH, AND SHE USED HER SCARF
TO CLEAN HER BICYCLE CHAIN.
I'LL TELL THEM
WE'RE HERE.
WAIT, THEY SENT
AN S.O.S. NO.
THERE'S AN ANSWER!
OH, WHAT'S IT SAY?
LET ME SEE. HOLY COW!
WHAT? WHAT'S GOING ON?
ALL OF OUR PARENTS ARE THERE,
EVERY ONE OF THEM!
ALL OF THEM WANT TO KNOW
HOW WE'RE DOING.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE SENT
THAT S.O.S.
NOW THEY'RE GOING TO THINK
THAT SOMETHING HORRIBLE
HAS HAPPENED TO US.
OH, WELL, I GUESS
I BETTER GET WRITING.
OKAY, HOW DO YOU SAY
THAT WE ALMOST DROWNED,
AND WE'RE TRAPPED IN
A CAVE WITH NO WAY OUT
AND MAKE IT SOUND
REASSURING --
IT'S BETTER THAN SCHOOL?
WHAT'S WRONG?
I'M WONDERING
HOW THE COM DEVICE WORKED
WHEN IT WAS ALL WET.
UH, "LET EVERYONE ELSE TALK"?
WELL, OKAY.
"HI, THIS IS RIKA.
"TAKATO FINALLY GAVE ME
THIS STUPID STYLUS
SO I CAN WRITE."
"THIS IS JERI.
I'M, UH, PEACHY."
PERFECT.
THE WATER.
I WONDER -- AH.
HEY, HENRY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK KAZU
WOULD SAY?
SOMETHING SNOTTY, RIGHT?
PROBABLY. YEAH.
CAN I TALK TO MY DAD?
IT'S AMAZING, ISN'T IT?
WHAT DID HENRY
HAVE TO SAY?
I'M NOT SURE YET.
I THINK HE'S WRITING A NOVEL.
OKAY, NOW HERE'S
WHAT I THINK HAPPENED.
WHEN WE TOUCHED THE WATER,
WE THOUGHT WE WERE SUPPOSED
TO GET WET, SO WE DID.
BUT THIS DEVICE DIDN'T KNOW
TO THINK THAT,
SO IT DIDN'T GET WET,
AND IT DIDN'T BREAK!
ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS
BELIEVE THAT WE WON'T DROWN,
AND WE CAN BREATHE
THE WATER!
"BREATHE THE WATER" --
HAS HE GONE CRAZY?
HMM. I DON'T KNOW.
I SUPPOSE IT MIGHT WORK.
NO NEED TO GUESS.
TELL HIM IT WILL WORK.
HUH?
ALL HE HAS TO DO
IS TRULY BELIEVE.
I'M NOT BEING NEGATIVE.
I'M NOT SURE IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
[ INHALES DEEPLY ]
HENRY!
OH, MOMENTI, TAKATO!
OKAY. HERE GOES NOTHING.
WELL, WHAT'S HAPPENING?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I DON'T KNOW YET.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO WAIT.
AW, NUTS.
I HOPE HE'S OKAY.
HE'S BEEN THERE A LONG TIME.
WHERE WAS I?
OH, YEAH.
90.
MAN!
91, 92, 93, 94, 95.
HENRY!
YOU SURE HAD ME WORRIED.
ARE YOU OKAY?
IT WORKED GREAT.
HERE, TOUCH MY HAIR.
HUH?
UH. IT'S DRY.
DOES THAT MEAN THE
NEXT TIME YOU'RE YELLING AT ME,
I CAN PRETEND YOU'RE NOT?
YOU CAN, BUT
I'LL YELL LOUDER.
MMM. YEAH!
I KNEW IT WOULD WORK.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW
IF I HEAR FROM THEM AGAIN.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
LISTEN, YAMAKI,
I KNOW WE HAVEN'T ALWAYS
SEEN EYE-TO-EYE.
IF YOU'D LIKE TO HELP US, WE'D
BE GLAD TO HAVE YOU ONBOARD.
THANKS, JANYU.
WELL, ALL RIGHT.
NOW, IF ONLY
SHIBUMI WERE HERE.
THAT'S NOT GOING
TO HAPPEN.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHY NOT?
IT'S A LONG STORY, BUT I'LL
GIVE YOU THE SHORT VERSION.
I HAD MEN LOOKING FOR
MR. MIZUNO, OR SHIBUMI.
BUT WHEN THEY FOUND HIM,
HE RAN OFF AND THEN
DISAPPEARED INTO THIN AIR.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING,
SHIBUMI VANISHED?!
TAKATO, IT'S OKAY.
JUST BREATHE.
AH! UH!
HA HA.
YOU SURE ARE FUNNY, TAKATO.
YEAH -- HA HA.
COME ON.
OH!
AND SO GRACEFUL.
YEAH, I'LL GIVE YOU
GRACEFUL.
HEY, WHAT'S THAT,
VERTICAL HOPSCOTCH?
I TAKE IT BACK.
YOU'RE NOT FUNNY.
WAIT A MINUTE.
ARE THOSE CRACKS?
MAYBE IT'S A DOOR.
UH! UH!
UH! UH! UH! UH!
STAND CLEAR!
HUH!
OH, GREAT. ANOTHER HEADACHE.
AHHH!
UH!
MMM. MMM. MMM. MMM.
OTAMAMON -- ROOKIE LEVEL --
SPECIAL-ATTACK STUN BUBBLE.
I DOUBT THEY'LL GIVE US
ANY TROUBLE.
HEY, LITTLE GUYS.
YEEEH!
HUH?
MMMM...YA!
UH, THIS COULD BE FUN.
WHY DON'T THE NASTY
DIGIMON EVER GET SCARED
AND SWIM AWAY?
DIVERMON -- ULTIMATE LEVEL --
SPECIAL-ATTACK STRIKING FISH?
STRIKING FISH!
OH, I GET IT NOW!
WAIT! WHY ARE YOU
ATTACKING US?
STRIKING FISH!
WHOA! WHA!
HEY!
YEEEH!
THE CURVEBALL.
[ PANTING ]
YAWHOO!
YA!
OOH!
UH. GOT IT!
AHHH!
YOU SET HIM UP,
I'LL KNOCK HIM DOWN!
TERRIERMON!
OHH!
OOOOOH.
[ CRYING ]
SO, YOU THOUGHT WE
ATTACKED THE OTAMAMON?
WE'D NEVER ATTACK
THESE LITTLE GUYS.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
SOMETIMES I GET OVERPROTECTIVE.
SORRY. SORRY.
AND SORRY AGAIN.
HMMMM.
MOMENNO ONE GOT HURT.
EXCEPT FOR YOU.
IS THERE A WAY
OUT OF HERE?
YOU'RE MAD, AND
YOU WANT TO LEAVE, RIGHT?
NO, WE'RE JUST LOOKING
FOR A WORLD
THAT'S NOT COMPLETELY
MADE OF WATER.
NOT MADE OF WATER --
WHAT'S THE POINT?
SO, YOU DON'T KNOW OF
AWORLDS LIKE THAT?
SORRY. WAIT A MINUTE, THERE IS
A LEGEND ABOUT ANOTHER WORLD.
OKAY. NOW, SOME CREATURES HAVE
GONE THROUGH THIS PIPE
AND NEVER RETURNED, AND SOME SAY
IT LEADS TO A WHOLE OTHER WORLD!
OKAY, I'LL GO CHECK IT OUT.
NO! DON'T!
OH, I AM GOING TO HAVE TO WORK
UP ONE BIG APOLOGY FOR THIS!
AHHHH!
UH!
JEEZ, LOUISE,
WHO PLUGGED IN THE BIG TOASTER?
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
I SHOULD HAVE WARNED YOU.
NOW WHAT DO WE DO?
WELL, IF THIS PIPE
IS THE ONLY WAY OUT,
WE'LL HAVE TO GET
THROUGH IT SOMEHOW.
HEY, HOLD ON A MINUTE.
THE OTAMAMON SPIT OUT BUBBLES
FILLED WITH AIR, DON'T THEY?
THE REAL TRICK IS GETTING
THEM TO STOP.
OH, I GET IT.
[ BUBBLING ]
WOW.
HERE I THOUGHT WE'D NEVER COME
UP WITH ANY GOOD IDEAS.
WELL, IT'S ONLY A GOOD
IDEA IF IT WORKS.
NOW, WHY'D YOU HAVE TO
TELL ME THAT?
[ GIGGLING ]
OH. HMM.
WHY WON'T THEY COME BACK?
UH.
TERRIERMON.
HENRY.
WHAT IF WE'RE IN
A GIANT STRAW,
AND SOMETHING'S
SUCKING US UP?
AHHHHHH!
AH! IT'S A WHOLE WORLD
OF WATER SLIDES.
MAYBE THEY ALL LEAD
TO DIFFERENT UNIVERSES.
THIS ONE'S HEADED RIGHT
INTO THAT BIG BUBBLE.
MAYBE IT'S LIKE
AN UNDERWATER CITY.
AND MAYBE WE CAN FIND
A TUBE THERE
THAT'LL TAKE US BACK
TO THE REAL WORLD.
OR AT LEAST GET ME BACK
TO GUILMON.
HOLD ON.
WE'RE ABOUT TO HIT THE BUBBLE.
All: WHOA!
SO MUCH FOR GOOD IDEAS.
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
WE CAN SWIM DOWN A TUBE
IF WE HAVE TO. WHOA!
WHAT ARE THEY,
SOME KIND OF DIGIMON?
[ CHIRPING ]
COME ON,
LET'S FOLLOW THOSE THINGS.
[ CHIRPING ]
THAT'S WEIRD,
IT LOOKS LIKE A LIBRARY.
OH, GREAT.
WE'RE IN A WHOLE
DIFFERENT WORLD,
AND I STILL CAN'T
GET AWAY FROM HOMEWORK.
UH.
UH!
WHOA.
SHOULD WE JUST
GO IN?
MAYBE WE'RE SUPPOSED TO.
UH.
AHH.
SOMEONE MUST BE HERE.
THERE'S ELECTRICITY.
AND SOMEONE HAD TO
READ ALL THESE BOOKS, RIGHT?
I GUESS SO.
MAN, THIS IS
A STUDYING NIGHTMARE.
YOU COULDN'T GET THROUGH THESE
BOOKS IF YOU READ FOR 100 YEARS.
200 FOR YOU.
YEAH. HEY!
IT'S KIND OF CREEPY.
WHERE IS EVERYONE?
HUH?
IS THAT A GIANT
DIGIVICE, OR IS IT JUST ME?
IT DOESN'T
LOOK LIKE YOU.
HA HA. FUNNY.
I'D HATE TO MEET THE TAMER
WHO OWNS THAT DIGIVICE.
YEAH, HE'D HAVE TO BE
A GIANT.
HEY, SOMEONE'S HERE.
IT LOOKS LIKE
HE'S ASLEEP.
YEAH, AND IT LOOKS LIKE
HE'S TRANSPARENT, TOO.
IS HE EVEN HUMAN?
I DON'T KNOW.
UM, EXCUSE ME, SIR.
ARE YOU AWAKE?
UHH. MMM.
HELLO. BEEN A WHILE
SINCE I'VE SEEN SOMEONE SOLID.
WELL, THAT'S SOMETHING
YOU DON'T HEAR EVERY DAY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
WHO ARE YOU?
ARE YOU HUMAN,
OR SOME KIND OF DIGIMON?
MY NAME IS MIZUNO.
AND AS TO BEING HUMAN...
WELL, THE ANSWER IS YES.
AT LEAST I USED TO BE.
HOW IN THE WORLD DID
YOU GETHERE?
I COULD ASK THE SAME THING
OF THE THREE OF YOU,
BUT WHY WASTE TIME
WITH MEANINGLESS QUESTIONS?
I ALREADY KNOW WHO YOU ARE
AND HOW YOU GOT HERE
BECAUSE, WELL, I'M THE ONE
WHO CREATED YOU.
HUH?
UH-HUH.
WE'RE JUST AS REAL
AS YOU ARE.
YOU DIDN'T CREATE US.
ARE YOU SURE?
MAYBE YOU'RE ALL DREAMING
LIKE ME.
MAYBE ALL BEINGS EVERYWHERE
ARE DREAMING
ABOUT WHAT THEY WILL BECOME.
AND WHEN WE ALL WAKE,
WE WILL BEGIN OUR EVOLUTION.
JEEZ, EVEN MY DREAMS MAKE
MORE SENSE THAN THIS.
HEY, HOW COME OUR DIGIVICES
LOOK LIKE THAT BIG THING
YOU'VE GOT HANGING
FROM YOUR CEILING?
THEY'RE ARCS
FOR TRANSPORTING DATA.
ARCS?
OKAY.
I HEARD MY DAD
MENTION THEM ONCE.
YOU'RE NOT ONE OF
HIS OLD FRIENDS, ARE YOU?
HIS NAME IS JANYU WONG.
HE USED TO WORK
WITH PROGRAMMERS
CALLED
"THE MONSTER MAKERS."
WHAT?
YOU MEAN TAO.
I REMEMBER.
THAT WAS A LONG TIME AGO.
SO YOU'RE HIS SON?
YES, I AM.
MY NAME IS HENRY WONG.
UH! I'M TERRIERMON.
I'M TAKATO.
CAN YOU HELP US GET HOME?
WELL, I SUPPOSE I COULD.
BUT I CAN'T REALLY
PROMISE YOU ANYTHING.
IT'S, YOU SEE...
GETTING ALL THE WAY BACK IS
NOT AS EASY AS YOU THINK.
CAN WE USE ONE
OF THESE DIGIVICES?
OR ARCS?
PERHAPS.
ONE OF THE FUNCTIONS OF THE ARCS
IS TO ACT AS TOOLBOXES
TO STORE, ORGANIZE,
AND CONNECT DATA.
THEY CAN BE USED TO BRING
KINDRED PAIRS TOGETHER,
JUST LIKE THE ANIMALS
ON NOAH'S ARK.
BUT NOT EVEN I'M SURE
OF ALL THEY CAN DO.
HEY, WHAT ARE THOSE
GIGGLING GUYS, ANYWAY?
THEY'RE DIGITAL GNOMES.
I CALL THEM DIGIGNOMES.
ARE THEY SOME KIND OF DIGIMON?
NO.
ABOUT TIME YOU GAVE
US A STRAIGHT ANSWER.
THEY'RE ANOTHER FORM
OF ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE
THAT EVOLVED ON THEIR OWN.
IT JUST SEEMED LOGICAL
TO CALL THEM DIGIGNOMES,
AT LEAST TO ME.
WELL, DID THEY EVOLVE
FROM DIGIMON?
NOT REALLY.
THEY EVOLVED FROM
THE DIGITAL WORLD ITSELF.
JUST AS THE HUMAN
BODY IS MADE UP OF CELLS
AND DIGIMON ARE MADE UP
OF DATA,
THE DIGITAL WORLD IS A LIVING
THING MADE UP OF DIGIMON
AND OTHER CREATURES.
AND AS THE DIGITAL
CREATURES EVOLVE,
SO DOES THE DIGITAL WORLD.
HEY, IT'S
THE BLUE CARD!
WELL, IT MAY LOOK LIKE
A CARD TO YOU,
BUT IT'S REALLY
AN ALGORITHM,
A MATHEMATICAL FORMULA.
A FORMULA?
I DON'T GET IT.
HOW DOES IT WORK?
I'M SURE TAO AND THE OTHERS
FORGOT ABOUT DIGIMON
WHEN THE PROJECT ENDED.
BUT I WANTED TO COMPLETE
OUR WORK,
SO I CREATED AN ALGORITHM
THAT WOULD ALLOW DIGIMON
TO EVOLVE ON THEIR OWN,
BEYOND WHAT WE HUMANS
COULD IMAGINE FOR THEM.
I ORIGINALLY WROTE
THE ALGORITHM
TO PROVE THAT DIGIMON
WERE MORE THAN JUST TOYS,
THAT THEY WERE A TRUE LIFE-FORM
THAT COULD GROW ON THEIR OWN.
BUT I GATHER THAT THE BLUE CARDS
HAVE A DIFFERENT MEANING
FOR THE TWO OF YOU.
SO, HOW DO YOU GUYS USE
THE ALGORITHM I WROTE?
WELL, I DON'T KNOW
ABOUT THE ALGORITHM PART,
BUT WE USE THE BLUE CARDS
TO BECOME DIGIMON TAMERS.
HMM, THAT MAKES SENSE.
I'M GLADYOUTHINK SO.
THE DIGITAL WORLD IS ALL
ABOUT COMMUNICATION,
AND ALL COMMUNICATION IS ABOUT
BRINGING THINGS IN TOUCH.
IT SEEMS THE BLUE-CARD ALGORITHM
IS BEING USED FOR A PURPOSE
I DIDN'T QUITE INTEND --
TO BRING DIGIMON AND PEOPLE
TOGETHER AS PARTNERS.
HUH?
WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
OH!
HEY, THAT'S MY DRAWING
OF GUILMON!
IT SEEMS THE DIGIGNOMES USED
PACKETS OF DATA
TO CREATE HIM
WHEN YOU DREAMED HIM UP --
PROBABLY AN ATTEMPT
TO COMMUNICATE WITH YOU.
OR MAYBE GUILMON DREAMED
HIS DATA INTO EXISTENCE,
AND YOU SIMPLY BECAME
AWARE OF HIM.
DOES THAT MEAN THAT I WAS
CREATED ESPECIALLY FOR HENRY?
PERHAPS.
YEAH, CREATED ESPECIALLY
TO ANNOY ME.
HEY!
WELL, AM I WRONG?
ADMIT IT, HENRY,
YOU'D BE LOST WITHOUT ME.
LOOKS LIKE I'M LOST
WYOU, TOO.
OR MAYBE HENRY
WAS CREATED FOR YOU.
AND GUILMON IS DATA.
SO, DO YOU KNOW OF A WAY
TO GET OUT OF HERE
AND BACK
TO THE REAL WORLD?
YES, THE HIGHEST PLANE.
SO, WE'VE GOT TO
KEEP GOING UP?
HOW MANY LEVELS ARE
THERE TO THIS PLACE?
THERE IS ONLY ONE MORE LEVEL
ABOVE THIS ONE,
AND IT IS THE LEVEL
WHICH THE FOUR MOST POWERFUL
AND MOST EVOLVED DIGIMON
HAVE MADE THEIR HOME.
OH, GREAT.
THE MOST POWERFUL DIGIMON?
YOU MEAN, THE SOVEREIGN?
WAIT A MINUTE?
THERE'S FOUR OF THEM?
IF THEY'RE LIKE GAZULAMON
FROM THE TV SHOW,
THEY MUST BE HUGE!
DO THEY PROTECT
THE DIGITAL WORLD?
IT IS RATHER IRONIC,
DON'T YOU THINK?
THE DIGIMON HAVE TRIED
TO EVOLVE
INTO LARGER AND
STRONGER FORMS
TO SET THEMSELVES APART FROM
THE HUMANS WHO CREATED THEM.
THEY'VE ENDED UP TAKING
ON THE FORMS OF ANCIENT GODS
OF THE HUMANS.
DIGIMON AND HUMANS WILL NEVER
BE ABLE TO SEPARATE THEMSELVES.
THEY LIVE IN THE
SAME WORLD, REALLY.
AND IT'S ONLY WHEN
THAT'S RECOGNIZED
THAT THE NEXT EVOLUTION
WILL BEGIN.
IF THEY PROTECT THIS PLACE,
THEN THEY'RE GOOD, RIGHT?
THAT'S NOT WHAT
SENSEI SAYS.
HE SAYS THAT GOOD AND EVIL
CAN SWITCH DEFINITIONS,
DEPENDING ON
YOUR PERSPECTIVE.
LET'S JUST HOPE OUR PERSPECTIVE
IS THE RIGHT ONE.
OH.
THE SOVEREIGN SEEM TO WANT
TO ACCELERATE DIGIVOLUTION
TO RESIST SOMETHING.
IT SEEMS THEY'RE AFRAID
THEY WON'T SURVIVE
UNLESS THEY FIND A WAY TO DEFEAT
WHATEVER IS COMING FOR THEM.
I WONDER WHAT
THEY'RE AFRAID OF.
YEAH, WHAT COULD DEFEAT
THE SOVEREIGN?
COULD IT BE SOMEONE
LIKE YAMAKI USED TO BE?
OR MAYBE IT COULD BE US!
MAYBE IT'S ME.
[ LAUGHS ]
OKAY.
HUH?
THAT IS ALL
I CAN TELL YOU NOW.
THE REST, YOU MUST LEARN
ON YOUR OWN, I'M AFRAID.
BUT WHAT ABOUT YOU?
I'M VERY TIRED.
I MUST SLEEP NOW.
AH, TO SLEEP,
PERCHANCE TO DREAM.
MAN, THAT GUY HAD
A LOT OF INFORMATION,
BUT I THINK I'M MORE CONFUSED
NOW THAN I WAS BEFORE.
HMM, IS THAT POSSIBLE?
MAYBE THE DIGIGNOMES
CAN ERASE DIGIMON, TOO.
TAKATO, YOU SEEM QUIET
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
SORRY, I WAS JUST THINKING
ABOUT GUILMON,
AND IF WHAT THAT GUY TOLD US
WAS REALLY TRUE.
THEN, IF GUILMON IS A PART OF ME
AND HE'S DATA, AM I DATA?
HMM. WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH DATA?
ALL DIGIMON
ARE LIKE THAT.
I GUESS.
IT'S JUST THAT IT'S WEIRD.
I CAN HANDLE BEING DATA,
BUT IF I LOSE GUILMON, I'LL LOSE
A PART OF MYSELF FOREVER.
I GUESS SOME ANSWERS
ARE MORE CONFUSING
THAN THE QUESTIONS.
SEE IF THEY'LL FIGURE IT OT
ON THE NEXT "DIGIMON" --
"DIGITAL MONSTERS."
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DI, DI, DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DI, DI, DI
DI, DI