MUSYAMON TRIED TO BIO-EMERGE,
BUT YAMAKI STOPPED HIM
WITH HIS FUNKY YUGAT PROGRAM.
THEN HENRY WENT TO RENAMON
FOR ANSWERS ABOUT
THE WHOLE DIGIVOLUTION THING,
BUT I DON'T THINK
IT HELPED THAT MUCH.
MEANWHILE,
TAKATO BROKE DOWN
AND SHOWED KAZU AND KENTA
WHAT A REAL DIGIMON IS LIKE,
SCARING THE PANTS OFF THEM.
MUSYAMON RETURNED
TO THE REAL WORLD
BY DESTROYING THE YUGAT PROGRAM
AND WENT NUTS IN THE CITY.
HENRY REALIZED THE ONLY WAY
TO BEAT THE WACKY WIZARD
WAS TO LET TERRIERMON DIGIVOLVE
TO GARGLEMON.
MAN, I GUESS THERE REALLY ARE
SOME BATTLES WORTH FIGHTING.
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
♪ WORLD
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMODIFY
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
SIR, I'VE DETECTED A DISRUPTION
IN THE NETWORK DATA STREAM.
ORIGIN?
UM, I'M SORRY, SIR.
I'M NOT SURE.
HMM.
LET'S GET HER BACK
BEFORE ANYONE NOTICES.
THOSE KIDS ARE A NUISANCE.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
AW, MAN,
YOU STARTED WITHOUT ME.
HUH? UM, HMM.
WHAT'S WRONG, GUYS?
WHY DID YOU RUN AWAY YESTERDAY?
UM, STUFF TO DO, YOU KNOW.
YOU'RE SO FULL OF IT. AAH!
[ GROWLING ]
AAH! MOMMY!
HOW DID YOU MAKE HIM
LOOK SO REAL?
WELL, HE LOOKS REAL
BECAUSE HE IS REAL.
YEAH, RIGHT.
HEY, I JUST GOT HERE.
DON'T PUT IT UP.
YOU'RE BEGINNING
TO FREAK US OUT, DUDE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I MEAN, YOU MADE A DIGIMON OUT
OF RUBBER EYES AND A FLASHLIGHT
AND YOU'RE TRYING
TO MESS US UP WITH IT.
YOU'RE CRAZY. WHY WOULD I DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
COME ON, GUYS.
I KNOW IT'S FREAKY,
BUT HE'S A REAL DIGIMON.
YOU BEGGED TO SEE HIM,
THEN YOU RAN AWAY
BEFORE HE COULD EVEN SAY HI.
I DON'T THINK
THE LITTLE FOOLS REALIZE
WHAT A DANGEROUS GAME
THEY'RE PLAYING.
IT'S TIME TO ENLIGHTEN THEM.
HMM?
[ Thinking ]
IS SHE REALLY GONE?
I KNEW ALL THAT PARTNER STUFF
WAS NONSENSE.
SHE NEVER REALLY CARED ABOUT ME,
NO MATTER WHAT SHE SAYS.
IF SHE CARED, SHE'D BE HERE.
SHE WAS JUST USING ME.
[ SIGHS ]
A WILD ONE --
IT APPEARS ERRATIC.
TRACER SET
TO MONITOR PROGRESS.
[ BUZZING ]
THINGS
NOT WHAT THEY SEEMED?
RENAMON.
RIKA, WHAT'S WRONG?
HMM?
ONE DOWN.
THAT WAS EASY ENOUGH.
HMM? UHH!
WHERE DID THAT
COME FROM? UHH. MM.
RIKA, WHERE ARE YOU?
[ Thinking ] RIKA'S NOT COMING.
I HAVE TO DO THIS ALONE.
RIKA,
WHY ARE YOU OUTSIDE?
YOU'RE MISSING THE FIGHT.
THAT'S NOT LIKE YOU.
WHERE'S RENAMON?
IS SHE IN THERE?
SHE NEEDS YOU.
LIGHTNING STING!
UHH!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
RIKA!
WHAT'S WITH HER?
DIAMOND STORM!
I DID IT. I DESTROYED THEM
WITHOUT RIKA'S HELP.
[ SIGHS ]
RENAMON JUST WANTED ME
TO HELP HER DIGIVOLVE.
I'M NOT FALLING FOR IT ANYMORE.
I DON'T NEED HER.
OH...
HUMANS CAN BE SO SILLY.
SOMETIMES THEY'RE UP
AND SOMETIMES THEY'RE DOWN.
THEY GOT TO LEARN
TO GO WITH THE FLOW.
RENAMON, RIKA WAS HERE.
I THINK SHE'S WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
SHE IS?
ARE YOU SURE?
SHE WAS ALL WHITE-FACED
AND JUMPY, YOU KNOW?
SHE WAS IN A BAD WAY.
RIKA?
I DOUBT IT.
RENAMON,
YOU TWO FIT TOGETHER.
YOU SHOULD BE PARTNERS,
NOT ENEMIES.
PARTNERS?
HA HA. 'BOUT TIME.
I WANT TO PLAY.
ME TOO.
HA HA HA.
PARTNERS --
YOU KEEP USING THAT WORD.
AM I SUPPOSED TO KNOW
WHAT IT MEANS?
IT'S LIKE THIS --
TERRIERMON AND I ARE BOTH
FRIENDS AND EQUALS.
EQUALS?
EXACTLY. WE KNOW EACH OTHER'S
STRENGTHS AND WEAKNESSES.
HMM.
GUESS WHAT -- HENRY TAUGHT ME
TAI CHI. DO YOU WANT TO LEARN?
HOW DO YOU DO IT, HMM?
YOU START LIKE THIS.
LIKE THIS? OH...
BOTH OF YOU MUST HAVE HAD
SOMETHING IN COMMON
OR YOU WOULDN'T HAVE BECOME
PARTNERS IN THE FIRST PLACE.
IT WAS NO COINCIDENCE.
I'M SURE OF IT.
THIS IS GOING TO TAKE
LONGER THAN I THOUGHT.
WHOA, WHOA!
IT WAS ONE STRANGE CONVERSATION.
I CAN TELL YOU THAT.
WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE SAID?
ABOUT GUILMON? I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S HARD TO PUT IN WORDS.
HE'S NOT EXACTLY
YOUR AVERAGE DIGIMON, HUH?
HE'S MY FRIEND. I CAN RELY
ON HIM NO MATTER WHAT,
BUT RENAMON AND RIKA --
THEY DON'T SEEM TO UNDERSTAND
THAT. I WISH WE COULD HELP.
ME TOO.
SO WEIRD. I BET IT'S
JUST EATING HER UP, HUH?
I'D IMAGINE THAT IT IS,
BUT WITH HER
YOU JUST NEVER KNOW.
HUH?
HEY, WHAT'S THE HOLDUP?
UH, UH...
ARE YOU TAKATO MATSUKI?
UH, YEAH.
YEAH, THAT'S ME.
THAT MUST MAKE YOU
HENRY WONG.
WHAT ABOUT IT?
YOU WERE HANGING AROUND
THE SHINJUKU GUARDRAIL
YESTERDAY, WEREN'T YOU?
YOU'VE BEEN
UNDER OBSERVATION.
THIS GAME YOU'RE PLAYING
IS DANGEROUS.
I SUGGEST YOU FIND
A NEW HOBBY.
JUST WHO ARE YOU ANYWAY,
AND WHAT DO YOU CARE WHAT WE DO?
HUH?
TAKATO!
CONSIDER THIS A WARNING.
WHAT? HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN "WARNING"?
THIS ISN'T EXACTLY
NORMAL ADULT BEHAVIOR, YOU KNOW.
WAIT! HENRY!
TAKATO.
HI, JERI.
HI. I KNOW
IT'S NOT NICE TO LISTEN
TO OTHER PEOPLE'S CONVERSATIONS,
BUT I JUST COULDN'T HELP IT.
WHA--
WHY WERE YOU ARGUING
WITH KENTA AND KAZU?
ARGUING?
IT SOUNDED LIKE YOU WERE
ARGUING ABOUT A REAL DIGIMON.
A REAL DIGIMON?
WOULD YOU STOP REPEATING ME?
IS IT TRUE?
UH -- HA -- HMM,
IF I TOLD YOU THAT IT WAS,
WOULD YOU BELIEVE ME?
YOU WOULDN'T BE SCARED?
I'D BELIEVE YOU.
I WANT TO SEE HIM. PLEASE?
HA HA HA. WHA--
UHH...HA HA.
[ Thinking ] THIS MAY BE
THE ABSOLUTE DUMBEST THING
I'VE EVER DONE.
DOES HE LIVE HERE?
OH --
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
A REAL DIGIMON?
AMAZING, HUH?
WAIT TILL YOU SEE HIM.
I CREATED HIM, YOU KNOW.
YOU DID? WOW. WHAT KIND
OF DIGIMON IS HE?
HE'S TOUGH,
AND, BABY, CAN HE FIGHT.
HIS SPECIAL ATTACK IS
PYROSPHERE.
OH...
[ SNORTS ]
[ Thinking ] WHOOPS.
THIS COULD GET UGLY.
I WAS JUST KIDDING.
IT'S FAKE -- YOU KNOW,
RUBBER EYES, FLASHLIGHT. HA.
I HAD YOU GOING THERE, DIDN'T I?
YOU KNOW
HOW US BOYS ARE.
HUH? BUT YOU...
I'M SORRY IF I --
HEY, TAKATO. I'M HUNGRY.
DID YOU BRING SOME BREAD?
AAH!
UHH.
YOU BROUGHT A FRIEND
INSTEAD.
CUTE.
DID YOU SAY "CUTE"?
YOU MEANT COOL, DIDN'T YOU?
I DON'T MIND "CUTE,"
BUT WHO IS SHE?
OH, SO SORRY.
I'M JERI.
I'M GUILMON.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
IS SHE YOUR GIRLFRIEND?
UH...WELL,
SHE'S A FRIEND.
GUILMON, GUESS WHAT.
I'VE GOT
A LITTLE PRESENT FOR YOU.
I'M GOING TO PUT IT
RIGHT HERE.
PERFECT.
HUH? NOT BAD.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
[ Nervous laugh ]
IT'S CUTE, ALL RIGHT.
[ Thinking ] I CAN'T BELIEVE
I JUST SAID THAT.
[ Thinking ] I WON THE FIGHT.
WHY DO I FEEL LIKE I LOST?
SOMETHING DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT.
SOMETHING IS MISSING.
NOW WHAT IS HE UP TO?
[ GRUNTING ]
[ Thinking ]
HUMANS. LOOK AT THEM.
DOGS HAVE MORE SENSE.
COME ON.
IT'S MY TURN.
NO WAY.
MAMA SAID HE'S MINE.
OH, YEAH?
WELL, YOU GOT TO SHARE.
IMPMON!
HUH?
HE WAS A BAD BOY
AND BROKE MY TOYS.
SO GO AND TEACH HIM
A LESSON. YOU HEAR ME?
BAD BOY?
IT WAS BROKEN
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
BESIDES, WHAT ABOUT
THE VIDEO GAME YOU TOOK FROM ME?
I DID IT BECAUSE YOU ALWAYS
TAKE MINE WITHOUT MY PERMISSION.
YEAH, BUT MAMA SAID
I COULD USE IT
AND SHE'S THE BOSS.
SO TAKE THAT, FAT FACE.
YOU'RE A BIG LIAR. I'M GOING
TO SEND IMPMON AFTER YOU
AND YOU CAN BET
HE'LL FIND OUT THE TRUTH.
[ GRUNTING ]
IMPMON, SHE'S A BIG BRAT
AND A BIG FAT LIAR.
DON'T BELIEVE THAT WEASEL.
NOW GET HIM BEFORE
HE BREAKS SOMETHING ELSE.
IMPMON!
YEAH? UHH...
UHH, UHH...
[ YELLING ]
I'M NOT GOING
TO GIVE IN.
KNOCK IT OFF!
[ CRYING ]
HUH?
UHH. WELL, WHAT?
WHAT IS WRONG WITH YOU?
HMM. NOT A BLESSED THING,
TOOTS. NOW TOODLES! HMM.
♪ DO-BI-DO-BI-DO
♪ DO-DO-DO-DO-DO
♪ DO-BI-DO-DO-DO
QUIT FOLLOWING ME!
I HAVE A QUESTION.
AND YOU THINK I CARE?
ACTUALLY,
I DO CARE. SURPRISED?
I CARE BECAUSE I'M SURE
IT'S SOMETHING STUPID.
HMM. I'VE LEARNED
NOT TO EXPECT MUCH
FROM YOU HUMAN-LOVING
DIGI-DUDS,
BUT MAYBE THERE'S HOPE
FOR YOU, DARLING,
COMING TO YOURS TRULY
FOR THE ANSWERS.
SO TELL ME, FOXY,
WHAT CAN I DO YOU FOR?
WHY DON'T YOU HAVE
A PARTNER?
DOH!
WHY SHOULD A DIGIMON
HAVE A PARTNER?
UHH.
YOU GOT ME.
NO SELF-RESPECTING DIGIMON
NEEDS A PARTNER,
ESPECIALLY A HUMAN.
ARE YOU SURE?
OF COURSE I AM.
HUMANS ARE SELFISH.
I'D STAY FAR AWAY FROM THEM
IF I WERE YOU.
THEY'RE TROUBLE
WITH A CAPITAL "T."
I'M SORRY, FOX FACE,
DID I GO TOO FAST FOR YOU?
AH, FORGET ABOUT IT.
HOW CAN WE DIGIVOLVE
OR INCREASE OUR STRENGTH
UNLESS WE HAVE A PARTNER?
AW, COME ON. YOU'RE NOT
REALLY BUYING THAT ONE.
THE POWER'S INSIDE OF YOU.
FORGET ALL THE REST.
HOW DO I FIND IT?
UH...I GUESS
YOU'RE NOT VERY BRIGHT.
DON'T EXPECT ME
TO TELL YOU WHAT TO DO.
YOU GOT TO FIGURE IT OUT
FOR YOURSELF.
I SEE. I THINK I GET
WHAT YOU'RE TRYING TO SAY.
YOU GET
WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY?
YOU'RE JUST A KNOW-IT-ALL
LIKE ALL THE REST OF THEM --
"I GET IT. I GET IT."
WELL, YOU'RE NOT EINSTEIN
AND, FRANKLY, YOU MAKE ME
SICK TO MY STOMACH.
I'LL LEAVE YOU ALONE THEN.
YOU'LL WHAT?
HEY, I GOT A LOT MORE TO SAY.
DON'T YOU WANT TO HEAR?
AW, BA-BOOM.
HMM. HOW QUAINT.
[ Thinking ] DO I NEED RIKA
TO FULFILL MY DESTINY?
YOU'RE BACK LATE TODAY.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
HEY, WOULD YOU MIND RUNNING OUT
AND GETTING ME SOME POTATOES?
I NEED THEM FOR
A SPECIAL RECIPE I'M MAKING.
WHY?
WELL, BECAUSE IT WOULDN'T BE
POTATO SOUP WITHOUT THEM.
AREN'T YOU HUNGRY, DEAR?
I HATE POTATOES,
AND I DON'T WANT ANY FOOD.
OH...
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO TALK ABOUT IT?
YOU BARELY EVER
SPEAK TO ME.
HOW AM I SUPPOSED TO KNOW
WHAT YOU WANT?
I'M TRYING TO UNDERSTAND YOU,
BUT YOU ALWAYS TREAT ME
LIKE I'M THE ENEMY.
I WAS YOUR AGE ONCE,
YOU KNOW.
IF YOU JUST GIVE ME A CHANCE,
I MIGHT BE ABLE TO HELP.
PLEASE, RIKA,
TELL ME WHAT'S WRONG.
JUST FORGET IT.
YOU WOULDN'T UNDERSTAND.
OH. MAYBE YOU'RE NOT OLD ENOUGH
TO UNDERSTAND THIS,
BUT NO ONE CAN MAKE IT
IN THIS WORLD ON THEIR OWN.
PEOPLE ARE MEANT TO BE
TOGETHER.
YOU'RE EXPECTING WAY TOO MUCH
OF YOURSELF, RIKA.
[ Thinking ] I HATE TO ADMIT IT,
BUT IMPMON COULD BE RIGHT.
I MUST RELY
ON THE POWER WITHIN ME.
I AM ALONE ALONE
IN THIS WORLD.
[ BEEPING ]
[ BIRD SCREECHING ]
SEE YA.
BYE-BYE.
I'LL COME VISIT AGAIN.
OH, OKAY, UH, ANYTIME.
GUILMON, DO YOU THINK
SHE LIKES ME?
WELL...
AH-CHOO!
HEY, HENRY.
HE GOT AWAY FROM ME.
WHOEVER HE IS,
HE SURE IS SNEAKY.
YEAH, I NOTICED.
HE KNEW WAY TOO MUCH
ABOUT US.
[ BIRD SCREECHES ]
HUH? SOMETHING THE MATTER,
GUILMON?
WHAT IS IT?
[ GROWLS ]
THAT'S EITHER A DIGIMON
OR A TRAIN WRECK.
HUH?
[ BEEPING ]
OH, I'D BETTER SEE
WHAT IT WANTS.
UH-OH.
WELL, IT'S NOT SAYING MUCH.
THE LIGHT SURE IS PRETTY.
GIVE IT HERE.
HUH? OH.
BUT, RIKA...OH.
WHATEVER IT SAID
DIDN'T GO OVER VERY WELL.
OH.
[ GROWLS ]
[ BIRD SCREECHES ]
RENAMON'S IN A FIGHT.
WHOA. IT'S HARPYMON.
THAT'S ONE NASTY DIGIMON
WITH A SCREECH
LIKE NAILS DOWN A CHALKBOARD.
RENAMON'S GOING TO HAVE
A TOUGH TIME
DEALING WITH
HER WIND-SEEKER ATTACK.
RIKA?
I DON'T SEE HER ANYWHERE.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
WIND SEEKER!
AAH!
DIAMOND STORM!
HUH?
RIKA.
JUST IN TIME.
HEY, HEY, RENAMON.
LOOK WHO FINALLY MADE
AN ENTRANCE.
[ Thinking ]
IMPMON WAS RIGHT.
I WILLED MYSELF STRENGTH
AND IT CAME.
[ Thinking ] RENAMON WAS
POWERFUL WITHOUT MY HELP.
I KNEW
SHE DIDN'T WANT ME.
SHE'S FROZEN
LIKE A STATUE.
ISN'T SHE GOING TO FINISH OFF
HARPYMON AND LOAD HER DATA?
[ Thinking ]
I COULD LOAD THE DATA
OF EVERY OPPONENT I FIGHT
AND TAKE THEM APART
ONE BY ONE,
BUT WHAT'S THE POINT
AFTER IT'S ALL OVER?
[ SCREECHES ]
WIND...SEEKER!
AAH!
OH, NO!
[ BIRD SCREECHING ]
OH, NO.
RIKA, COME BACK!
[ SCREAMING ]
RIKA!Â Â Â Â Â NO!
OH...
RENAMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
CUBIMON!
WIND SEEKER!
FOX TAIL INFERNO!
YOU'RE NOT
LOADING HER DATA?
NO.
BUT WHY NOT?
BECAUSE I DON'T NEED IT
ANYMORE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I DON'T NEED
AN OPPONENT'S DATA
BECAUSE I HAVE YOU.
UH, BECAUSE OF ME?
RIKA, YOU JUST SAVED MY LIFE.
WHY DID YOU DO IT?
SOMEONE HAD TO DO IT.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE ONCE.
YOU WERE JUST
REPAYING A DEBT?
NO, THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
YOU'RE MY PARTNER.
AND THAT'S WHAT PARTNERS DO.
WE PROTECT EACH OTHER.
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE SAYING?
HA HA. YEAH,
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
WE'LL WATCH
EACH OTHER'S BACK.
UH, I DON'T GET IT.
IT'S OBVIOUS THEY WERE
WORRIED ABOUT EACH OTHER.
PROBLEM IS THEY'RE TOO
HARD-HEADED TO ADMIT IT.
THEY'LL GO ON PLAYING
SILLY GAMES UNTIL THEY DROP.
BEING HONEST WITH EACH OTHER
WOULD BE TOO HARD.
[ LAUGHTER ]
I'M ALWAYS HONEST WITH YOU,
AREN'T I, GUILMON?
YEAH, YOU TOLD ME
I WAS CUTE.
NO WAY. HE MUST HAVE MEANT
YOU WERE COOL.
RIGHT, TAKATO?
CAN'T THEY SEE THE DANGER?
DATA WALKING AROUND
LIKE LIVING,
BREATHING CREATURES --
I CANNOT ALLOW THIS OBSCENITY
TO CONTINUE.
THERE'S SIMPLY
TOO MUCH AT STAKE.
I'M SORRY, CHILDREN.
YOUR TIME IS UP.
HA HA HA.
DUDE, THAT'S COLD.
JUST WHO DOES YAMAKI THINK HE IS
ANYWAY -- THE DIGI-POLICE?
TO FIND OUT, KEEP WATCHING
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."