SUSIE WAS DRAWN
INTO THE DIGITAL WORLD
AFTER SHE SAW TERRIERMON
FLY OVERHEAD
IN THIS OVERSIZE DIGIVIC.
THERE SHE MET THE LAST DEV,
ANTYLAMON,
WHO GAVE HER THE PIGGYBACK RIDE
OF HER LIFE.
THEN MIHIRAMON CAME ALONG
AND TRIED TO TAKE SUSIE
TO THE DIGIMON SOVEREIGN.
WHEN TERRIERMON HEARD
SHE WAS IN TROUBLE,
THE GIANT DIGIVICE
CHANGED COURSE
AND CRASHED
RIGHT IN FRONT OF HER!
ANTYLAMON
ALSO CAME TO THE RESCUE,
BUT WHEN SHE SCARED OFF
MIHIRAMON,
ALL HER DEVA POWERS
WERE SUCKED OUT OF HER,
AND SHE DE-DIGIVOLVED
INTO LOPMON.
AND BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
SUSIE'S GONNA BE HER TAMER!
DI, DI, DI
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS
TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE WORLD
DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS.
DIGIMODIFY.
DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON!
Man: DEEP IN THE LAND
OF THE FOUR DIGIMON SOVEREIGN,
THERE WAS ONCE A SHINING LIGHT.
THIS LIGHT GAVE DIGIMON
THE ABILITY TO DIGIVOLVE,
TO BECOME GREATER AND MORE
POWERFUL THAN EVER BEFORE.
THEN, ONE DAY,
THAT LIGHT DISAPPEARED,
UNTIL...
WHOA-HO-HOOOOO!
[ GROANING ]
HUH?
HEY, WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA?!
[ GRUNTS ]
AAAH! UGH!
[ GROANING ]
OH, WHAT'S THAT
FUNNY-LOOKING THING?
IT'S TOO BIG TO BE AN ICE POP.
OHH!
IT'S PRETTY!
[ GASPS ] OH?
AND IT LOOKS REAL FAMILIAR.
OH!
IT FEELS LIKE
I'VE BEEN HERE BEFORE
A LONG TIME AGO.
[ CRYING ]
I'VE GOT TO GET OUT OF HERE!
OKAY, CALUMON,
TIME TO GET TOUGH.
I'M A DIGIMON.
MAYBE I HAVE
SOME SPECIAL ATTACK, TOO.
...BLISTERING BALL!
BIG-NOOGIE, POKE-YOU-IN-THE-EYE
POWER BEAM!
AW, NUTS!
I GUESS THIS MEANS
I'M STUCK HERE FOR GOOD,
UNLESS SOMEONE RESCUES ME.
[ GROANING ]
HEY, WHO WANTS TO HEAR
ANOTHER KNOCK-KNOCK JOKE?
UH, GUYS?
[ GROANS ] I'M SO BORED.
CAN'T WE HEAD HOME ALREADY?
HEY, KNOCK-KNOCK BOY, WE HAVEN'T
FOUND CALUMON OR TAKATO,
AND YOU'RE YAPPING
ABOUT HOME?!
WHAT, DO YOU MISS
YOUR MOMMY?!
NO. ALL I'M SAYING
IS WE'VE BEEN HERE FOR DAYS
AND WE HAVEN'T FOUND
DIDDLY SQUAT.
HEY, KENTA,
WHAT'S A DIDDLY SQUAT?
NEVER MIND, BUT THANKS
FOR THE PIGGYBACK RIDE.
NO PROBLEMO.
THAT'S SPANISH
FOR "NO PROBLEM" -- I THINK.
[ LAUGHS ] JERI,
HOW ARE YOU HOLDING UP?
I'M JUST PEACHY.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, KYUBIMON?
I'M FINE.
WE'RE ALL FINE,
BUT WE'D BE BETTER
IF WE KNEW WHERE TAKATO WAS.
WHO WANTS TO HEAR
ANOTHER RHYME?
I DO! I DO!
ONE, TWO, THREE, FOUR,
WHO'S THE BUNNY I ADORE?
FIVE, SIX, SEVEN, EIGHT,
MY NEW BUNNY SMELLS LIKE CAKE!
I CAN'T BELIEVE SUSIE'S HERE.
IT'S NOT SAFE FOR HER.
AND MY PARENTS, THEY'RE PROBABLY
CLIMBING THE WALLS BY NOW.
DON'T WORRY. AFTER WE FIND
CALUMON AND THE OTHERS,
WE'LL GET HER BACK PRONTO.
HUH?
HEY! WELL, LOOK WHO'S HERE!
WHAT'S UP, GUYS?
IT'S THE DIGIGNOMES.
IF THEY WERE DIGIMON, MAYBE
WE COULD UNDERSTAND THEM.
SORRY, FELLA,
I DON'T SPEAK GNOME.
OH, LOOK!
THE FIREFLIES ARE BACK!
THEY MUST BE TRYING
TO TELL US SOMETHING.
IF THE DIGIGNOMES
ARE THE ONES
WHO BROUGHT THE BLUE CARDS
TO THE REAL WORLD,
THERE HAD TO BE A REASON FOR IT,
SOMETHING THEY WANT US TO DO.
YEAH? LIKE WHAT?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT I HAVE A FUNNY
FEELING IT'S IMPORTANT.
[ GASPS ]
MAYBE THEY KNOW SOMETHING
ABOUT GUILMON!
WAIT UP!
HEY, I HAVE SOME QUESTIONS
ABOUT MY DIGIMON!
COME BACK!
[ GASPS ] HEY, LOPMON.
YES, HENRY?
DO YOU KNOW A DIGIMON
NAMED CALUMON?
UH, HERE --
THIS LITTLE GUY.
WELL, OF COURSE
I KNOW WHO HE IS.
HE'S THE ONE WHO HOLDS THE KEY
TO DIGIVOLUTION.
THE SOVEREIGN MADE THIS POWER
TO PROTECT OUR WORLD FROM THOSE
WHO WANT TO DESTROY IT.
THAT'S WHY THEY CREATED
US DEVAS
OUT OF DATA FROM DIGIMON
THAT ARE NOW GONE,
TO HELP THEM ON THEIR QUEST.
LOPMON, YOU'RE TALKING FUNNY.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
SHE'S TRYING TO SAY
THAT SHE WAS CREATED
BY THE DIGIMON SOVEREIGN,
SUSIE.
MMM.
UH, LOPMON, DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHERE CALUMON'S BEING HELD?
YES, I DO.
I SAW HIM BEING TAKEN
PAST THE PHOENIX GATE ONE DAY.
THE PHOENIX GATE?
THAT IS WHERE THE DIGIMON
SOVEREIGN ZHUQIAOMON LIVES.
IT'S JUST BEYOND THE SOUTH GATE
I USED TO GUARD.
OH, WOW...
THE LAND OF THE DIGIMON
SOVEREIGN.
WE MADE IT.
WELL, IF WE KNOW WHERE CALUMON
IS, THEN LET'S GET HIM.
NO!
WHY? WHAT'S THE MATTER?
MOMENTI KNOW
YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT SUSIE,
BUT SHE IS A TAMER,
YOU KNOW.
YEAH. [ LAUGHS ]
HA!
HUH?
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
WE'RE NOT GOING ANYWHERE!
WHAT NOW?
[ ELECTRONIC BLAST ]
HUH?
KEEPER OF THE LIGHT,
YOU MUST KNOW YOU'RE NOT
A DIGIMON LIKE THE OTHERS.
YOU HAVE A POWER INSIDE YOU,
A POWER WE NEED.
THERE'S NO WAY
I'M GIVING YOU MY INSIDES,
AND I AM SO A DIGIMON!
ONCE YOU WERE THE LIGHT THAT
GAVE US THE POWER TO DIGIVOLVE.
YOU MUST BECOME
THAT LIGHT AGAIN.
RESISTANCE IS USELESS.
YOU CANNOT ESCAPE YOUR DESTINY
OR THIS CAGE.
OHH!
PLEASE, YOU'RE MAD
TO TRY AND FACE THE SOVEREIGN,
AND I CAN'T HELP YOU.
YOUR DEVA POWERS ARE GONE,
BUT YOU CAN STILL FIGHT.
THE SOVEREIGN MADE ME,
AND THEY CAN DESTROY ME
JUST AS EASILY.
NO, LOPMON.
SUSIE, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I'VE CHANGED.
I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT
OR HURT ANYONE.
OF COURSE YOU DON'T.
NICE BUNNY.
OKAY, BUT WHAT NOW?
CALUMON'S NOT GONNA RESCUE
HIMSELF.
[ RUMBLING ]
AAAH!
WHAT'S THAT?!
I DON'T KNOW, BUT SOMETHING
TELLS ME IT'S NOT GOOD.
THE TIME HAS COME FOR ME TO DO
MY MASTER'S WILL.
UM, LEOMON, DO YOU KNOW HOW YOU
BECAME JERI'S PARTNER?
WELL, HOW DID YOU BECOME
TAKATO'S?
GEE, I'M NOT REALLY SURE.
ONE DAY, HE THOUGHT ME UP,
AND -- POOF -- I WAS THERE.
IT FEELS LIKE WE'VE ALWAYS
BEEN TOGETHER,
LIKE SAUSAGES
AND SAUERKRAUT.
OH, I SEE.
WHAT ABOUT YOU, KYUBIMON?
IT WAS NO ACCIDENT.
I WANTED THE STRONGEST TAMER
SO I COULD DIGIVOLVE --
NO ONE BUT THE BEST.
THE CHOICE WAS CLEAR.
IT HAD TO BE RIKA.
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
IT'S STRANGE.
I DON'T KNOW EXACTLY HOW
I CAME TO THE REAL WORLD.
ALL I KNOW IS WE WERE
SUDDENLY TOGETHER,
AND THAT'S ALL THAT MATTERED.
BUT I'M NOT STRONG AT ALL,
ESPECIALLY FOR A TAMER.
I'M SORRY YOU HAVE TO BE STUCK
WITH ME, LEOMON.
JERI, YOU HAVE
THE TRUE HEART OF A LION.
THAT'S ALL YOU NEED.
IT'S NOT STRENGTH OR POWER
THAT MAKES A GOOD PARTNER,
IT'S HEART.
BESIDES, THERE'S NO ONE ELSE
I'D RATHER BE WITH.
[ SIGHS ]
LEOMON, THANK YOU.
LEOMON, YOU'RE SO SMART
AND SO STRONG.
HOW'D YOU GET TO BE
LIKE THAT, ANYWAY?
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT SMART,
BUT I'M STRONG BECAUSE
I FOUGHT ALL MY LIFE.
LIKE MOST DIGIMON, I THOUGHT
IT WAS THE ONLY WAY.
MAYBE I CAN BE LIKE YOU
IF I SPEND MY WHOLE LIFE
FIGHTING, TOO.
FIGHTING ISN'T EVERYTHING.
YOU HAVE YOUR OWN DESTINY.
YEAH, I GUESS.
I'LL ASK TAKATO.
HE'LL KNOW.
OH, I MISS HIM.
WHERE COULD HE BE?
LOOK, HENRY, I KNOW YOU DON'T
WANT TO LEAVE SUSIE,
SO WHY DON'T YOU STAY
WITH HER, AND I'LL GO?
AND TERRIERMON CAN COME WITH ME
IF THAT'S OKAY WITH YOU.
AW, COME ON,
HOW ABOUT IT, HENRY?
WELL, OKAY, BUT I'M NOT SURE
IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
NOT TO WORRY.
IF IT GETS HAIRY,
WE'LL SKEDADDLE RIGHT BACK.
I'M NOT CRAZY.
I DON'T WANT TO PICK A FIGHT
WITH ANYONE POWERFUL ENOUGH
TO CREATE THOSE DEVAS,
BUT IF LOPMON'S RIGHT
AND THE DIGIMON SOVEREIGN
ONLY WANT TO PROTECT THIS WORLD,
MAYBE I CAN JUST TALK
TO THEM.
WHAT IF -- HUH?
AAAH!
WHAT WAS THAT?!
HELLO, KIDDIES!
BEELZEMON!
YOU'RE NOT WITH YOUR FRIENDS
NOW, ARE YOU, PUNKS?
OH, WELL.
I GUESS I'LL JUST HAVE TO
ANNIHILATE THEM LATER.
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
WHAT DID WE EVER DO TO YOU?
IT'S NOTHING PERSONAL.
IT'S JUST BUSINESS,
AND I'M A BUSINESSMAN.
HENRY!
RIGHT!
DIGIMODIFY!
MATRIX DIGIVOLUTION,
ACTIVATE!
DI, DI, DIGIMON
TERRIERMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
GARGAMON!
GARGAMON MATRIX DIGIVOLVE TO...
RAPIDMON!
UGH!
HA! I'VE EATEN BIGGER DIGIMON
FOR BREAKFAST!
IS THAT SUPPOSED TO
IMPRESS ME? YA!
RAPID FIRE!
NO, BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I BETTHISWILL.
HUH?
DOUBLE IMPACT!
RAPIDMON, NO!
WHOA!
UGH!
AAAH!
[ GASPS ]
I FEEL TOTALLY USELESS.
GUILMON!
GUILMON, WHERE ARE YOU?
[ GUNS COCK ]
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
IS THAT ALL YOU GOT?
THAT'S PATHETIC!
[ Echoing ] GUILMON!
UH-HUH?
HEY, GROWMON,
WHAT'S GOING ON?
IT'S TAKATO.
I CAN HEAR HIM.
Children: HUH?
I THINK I HEARD HIM TOO.
HUH?
ARE YOU SURE?
I DON'T HEAR ANYTHING.
[ Echoing ] GUILMON!
AH!
[ GROWLS ]
Boy: DATA STREAM, 12:00 --
WE GOTTA SCRAM!
ISN'T TAKATO'S VOICE
COMING FROM THERE?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WELL, YOU KNOW
WHAT THIS MEANS.
Kenta: NO, AND PLEASE
DON'T TELL ME.
I'M COMING, TAKATO.
HOLD ON A MINUTE.
YOU'RE NOT ACTUALLY THINKING
OF GOING IN THERE, ARE YOU?
DON'T WE USUALLY RUN AWAY
FROM THE NASTY DATA STREAM?
I'M GOING.
TAKATO IS CALLING ME.
WE'D BETTER MAKE UP
OUR MINDS QUICKLY.
RIGHT. I SAY WE GO.
ANYTHING'S BETTER THAN
SCHLEPPING AROUND IN THE SAND.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
THAT'S SO LIKE YOU.
I CAN'T BE ANYONE ELSE.
PAJIRAMON,
YOU BETTER GRAB ON.
OH, GOOD IDEA.
HUH!
READY!
OKAY, EVERYBODY,
HOLD ON TIGHT.
COME ON, KENTA, DON'T
TELL ME YOU'RE SCARED.
MMM...OKAY, I WON'T.
[ SIGHS ]
JERI.
MM-HMM?
[ GROWLS ]
Kari: HERE HE COMES.
ON YOUR MARKS, GET SET.
MMM...
NOT AGAIN.
NO!
OH!
SOON THOSE FOOLISH CHILDREN.
THEY GATHERED IN ONE PLACE
TO MEET ONE FATE --
THE FATE OF ALL WHO DARE
DEFY THE DIGIMON SOVEREIGN.
[ CRYING ]
OH, SUSIE.
OHH.
OH!
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
[ GROWLS ] RAPIDMON!
TALK TO ME!
ARE YOU OKAY?!
HENRY, HE'S TOO STRONG!
NO KIDDING.
COMPARED TO ME, YOU GUYS ARE
AMATEUR HOUR, YOU KNOW THAT?
PATHETIC HUMANS
AND YOUR DIGIPETS --
YOU MAKE ME WANNA THROW UP,
KICK YOUR BUTTS,
AND THEN THROW UP AGAIN!
WAIT A MINUTE.
YOU'RE IMPMON, REMEMBER?
HMM?
YOU WENT TO CAMP WITH US AND
PLAYED IN THE WATER WITH US.
WE EVEN SAVED YOUR LIFE ONCE.
YOU'RE OUR FRIEND.
IMPMON IS NOTHING
BUT A BAD MEMORY!
AHH!
HUH? YOU FOUND US!
AH!
OH, FINALLY.
WHERE HAVE YOU GUYS BEEN?
TAKATO, I MISSED YOU
SO MUCH.
ME, TOO.
[ Thinking ]
OH! BUT, WHAT IF --
WHAT IF I LOSE HIM AGAIN?
IF MIZUNO'S RIGHT,
HE'S JUST DATA.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, TAKATO?
AND DATA CAN JUST BE...
ERASED.
Kyubimon: BEELZEMON,
THERE'S STILL TIME!
OH, CAN IT!
YOU TALK TOO MUCH,
YOU KNOW THAT?
YOU THINK YOU'RE SO SMART?
WELL, IN A SECOND,
YOU'RE GONNA BE HISTORY!
[ GUNSHOT ]
THAT'S UNCALLED FOR.
GUARDIAN BARRAGE!
YOU WANT TROUBLE?
YOU GOT IT.
WHAT? NO, NO.
PYROBLASTER!
AHH!
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
AHH!
OHH, OH.
I'LL TEACH YOU!
KYUBIMON!
COME ON, YOU HAVE TO
GET UP TO DIGIVOLVE!
I'M TRYING.
[ GROWLS ]
DRAGON WHEEL!
AHH!
UNH!
OH, OHH!
KYUBIMON!
AHHHH!
NICE TRY THERE,
FOX FACE.
OHH, OH, OH.
DON'T YOU TOUCH HER!
ALL RIGHT, THAT'S IT!
GET HIM, GROWMON!
I DON'T CARE
WHO HE USED TO BE.
HE'S NOTHING
BUT A MONSTER NOW!
TAKE HIM DOWN!
TAKATO!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
AAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
SO MUCH FOR FRIENDSHIP,
HUH, PINEAPPLE HEAD?
DON'T WORRY,
I'LL DEAL WITH YOU LATER.
RIGHT AFTER I WIPE OUT
YOUR UPPITY FRIEND.
ALL RIGHT, CHATTY,
ANY LAST WORDS?
[ Weakly ] IMPMON, PLEASE.
BE QUIET!
OH, NO! KYUBIMON,
PLEASE GET UP!
YOU HAVE TO GET AWAY!
THESE STUPID CARDS
ARE USELESS.
I CAN'T DO ANYTHING!
[ GROWLS ]
ENOUGH! I MUST DESTROY YOU
ONCE AND FOR ALL!
AHH!
DON'T BE...SO BLIND.
I SAID QUIET!
AHHH!
HUH?
I DON'T KNOW WHO YOU ARE,
BUT I DO KNOW YOU'RE BEING USED.
THIS POWER
YOU'VE BEEN GIVEN --
IS IT WORTH HURTING THESE
CHILDREN TO KEEP IT?
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING!
TO HAVE POWER IS NOT
TO BE STRONG.
YOU SEE, I KNOW THAT
BETTER THAN ANYONE.
LEOMON.
DO WHAT YOU MUST, BEELZEMON,
BUT I WILL NOT LET YOU
HURT THESE CHILDREN!
AAAHH!
[ GASPING ]
AH!
HEY, YOU!
KYUBIMON!
WHY CAN'T YOU SEE?
WHY WON'T YOU TRY
TO UNDERSTAND THE TRUTH?
[ WHIMPERING ]
I DON'T BELIEVE
HE GOT LEOMON.
WE COULD BE NEXT.
WE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE.
I CAN'T TAKE THIS.
LEOMON, IT CAN'T BE.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ WHIMPERING ]
BE BRAVE, JERI.
PART OF ME WILL ALWAYS
BE WITH YOU.
REMEMBER, YOU HAVE
A LION'S HEART.
NO-O-O-O!
NO, TO HAVE POWER
IS TO BE STRONG.
I'LL KEEP LOADING DATA
TILL NO ONE CAN STOP ME!
NO ONE!
NO ONE!!
[ STAMMERING ]
BUT HE WAS JUST TRYING
TO HELP US AND YOU.
[ GROWLS ]
HOW COULD YOU?
HOW COULD YOU DO THIS
HORRIBLE THING?!
I'LL MAKE YOU HURT.
I'LL MAKE YOU PAY!
[ BOTH SCREAMING ]
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT IS HAPPENING
TO THE TWO OF YOU?
JERI, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
COME ON, GET OUT OF THE WAY!
DON'T TOUCH ME!
EVERYONE JUST
LEAVE ME ALONE!
JERI...
HMM, NICE OUTFIT.
BUT YOU'RE STILL NO MATCH
FOR ME, YOU BIG LUMP!
JUST SO YOU KNOW, METAL MOUTH,
WHEN I'M DONE WITH YOU,
I'M GONNA FINISH YOUR
FRIENDS OFF ONE BY ONE.
YOU'RE WRONG.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S FINISHED.
[ GROWLING ]
[ ROARS ]
TAKE THIS,
YOU BIG DUMP TRUCK!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
[ GROWLING ]
FINISH HIM! DO IT!
TEAR HIM APART!
DON'T DO THIS.
AHH!
YOU CANNOT LOSE --
I WON'T ALLOW IT.
I ORDER YOU TO DIGIVOLVE.
DIGIVOLVE!
NOW!!
OHH. OH. OH! OH, NO!
OHHH!
THE MARK ON HIS CHEST
IS GLOWING.
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO HIM?
Woman: RED ALERT.
I REPEAT, RED ALERT.
DATA IS CONVERGING
IN MASSIVE AMOUNTS
AT THE CORE OF
THE DIGITAL FIELD.
BUT THAT COULD LEAD TO...
A NETWORK MELTDOWN.
THIS IS THE BIGGEST
I'VE SEEN, SIR.
THERE'S JUST NO TELLING
WHAT KIND OF EFFECT
THIS IS GOING TO HAVE
ON THE REAL WORLD.
SOMETHING'S HAPPENING
IN THE DIGITAL PLANE.
BUT WHAT?
NO!
HENRY! SUSIE!
IF ANYTHING HAPPENS
TO THE TWO OF YOU,
IT'S ALL...MY FAULT.
[ GROWLING ]
HE'S DIGIVOLVING.
DO IT. THAT'S IT --
DIGIVOLVE.
I ORDER YOU TO
DIGIVOLVE TO MEGA!
YES. MEGA!
[ GROWLING ]
OH!
[ GROWLING INTENSIFIES ]
GUILMON, WHAT HAVE I
DONE TO YOU, BOY?
I'M SORRY.
UHH!
NO-O-O!
OH, OH.
I DON'T THINK TAKATO
MEANT TO TURN GUILMON
INTO WHATEVETHATIS.
I HOPE IT'S NOT PERMANENT.
TO FIND OUT, KEEP WATCHIG
"DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS"
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DI, DI, DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DI, DI, DI