ONCE DOBERMON DELIVERED
THE POWER TO BIOMERGE TO TE
TAMERS,
THE GANG DIGIVOLVED TO MEGA O
TAKE ON THE D-REAPER.
GALLANTMON GOT PULLED DOWN INTO
THE RED BLOB
AND HAD TO DE-DIGIVOLVE
IN THE PARK.
THEN JERI SHOWED UP.
AT LEAST, IT LOOKED LIKE JER.
SHE WAS ONE OF THE D-REAPER'S
AGENTS,
WHO DIDN'T THINK TOO HIGHLY F
HUMAN BEINGS.
MEANWHILE, SAKUYAMON AND
MEGAGARGOMON
WERE TRYING TO SAVE GALLANTMN
WHEN THIS DUDE FLEW IN FROM
NOWHERE.
I SURE HOPE HE'S FRIENDLY R
THOSE GUYS ARE TOAST!
♪ DI, DI, DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE WORLD
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS.
DIGIMODIFY.
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON!
WHOA.
AND WHO MIGHT YOU BE?
A FRIEND.
A REALLY SHINY FRIEND.
WELL?
WHOA.
I AM JUSTIMON,
CYBERDRAMON'S MEGA FORM,
HERE TO GIVE THE D-REAPER A
TASTE OF MY JUSTICE KICK!
THAT COULD BE THE COOLEST DUDE
I'VE EVER SEEN.
WHAT ABOUT ME?
EXCEPT FOR YOU, OF COURSE.
HEY, HEY!
WHAT'S HAPPENED, GUYS?
THAT'S SO TYPICAL.
CAN'T YOU EVER JUST WALK IN AND
SAY HELLO?
IT'S RYO!
RYO!
I HAD A FEELING YOU NEEDED
MY HELP.
IF WE'RE GOING TO SAVE TAKATO
AND GUILMON
AND TAKE OUT THE D-REAPER,
IT'S GOING TO TAKE ALL OF US
WORKING TOGETHER.
WHAT'S THAT?
RRRAGGH!
WHOA!
LOOKS LIKE SOMEBODY WOKE UP
ON THE WRONG
SIDE OF REALITY!
EVERYONE SCATTER!
AAH!
RRAAGH!
AAAH!
HENRY!
THAT IS IT!
I AM TIRED OF THIS JERK SMACKING
MY FRIENDS AROUND.
YOU WANT TO FIGHT?
LET'S FIGHT!
YOU HEARD US.
BRING IT ON!
RRAGH!
LET'S GO.
HYAH!
AAAAAGH!
NOW GET OUT OF HERE!
ARE YOU KIDDING?
YOU CAN'T BEAT THE D-REAPER
BY YOURSELF.
HAAGH!
NO, BUT I KEEP HIM BUSY,
WHILE WE DO WHAT?
WHILE YOU GUYS RESCUE
GALLANTMON.
HAAGH!
GO!
TRY NOT TO GET KILLED WHILE
WE'RE GONE!
THEN LET'S GO!
AND FAST.
WHAT AREWESUPPOSED TO DO?
FIGHT GALLANTLY?
COOL!
FEAR NOT, RYO!
THE CAVALRY COMETH!
WE'LL SAVE YOU, RYO!
THEN YOU CAN SAVE US!
THE RED MASS IS EXPANDING.
THE D-REAPER SEEMS TO BE
ISOLATING OUR WEAKNESSES
AND USING THEM AGAINST US.
IS THERE ANYTHING IN THE
ORIGINAL PROGRAMMING
THAT CAN HELP US?
SO FAR, NOTHING.
HOW ARE YOU ABLE TO EXIST N
TWO PLACES AT ONCE?
THERE HAS TO BE A BRIDGE OR A
COMMON LINK.
WAIT!
SHIBUMI, I THINK I FOUND
SOMETHING.
WHAT IS IT?
THE D-REAPER'S CONSCIOUSNESS,
THE KERNEL OF ARTIFICIAL
INTELLIGENCE.
THIS CHANGES EVERYTHING.
WE'VE BEEN WORKING UNDER THE
ASSUMPTION
THAT THE D-REAPER IS TWO
SEPARATE ENTITIES,
ONE IN THE DIGITAL WORLD AND ONE
IN THE REAL WORLD.
BUT IF THE D-REAPER IS ONLY A
SINGLE ENTITY
WITH ONLY A SINGLE
CONSCIOUSNESS,
THEN ALL OF ITS AGENTS MUST BE
PLUGGED INTO
AND CONTROLLED BY THAT
CONSCIOUSNESS.
CORRECT.
SO IF WE CAN SOMEHOW SEVER THAT
CONNECTION...
THEN THE KIDS MIGHT JUST
HAVE A CHANCE.
[ JERI GIGGLING ]
JERI, WHERE ARE YOU?!
TA-KA-TO!
HUH?
THE BEING KNOWN AS JERI
HAS SHOWN THE COLLECTIVE YOUR
WEAKNESSES, SUBJECT TAKATO.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
I FORGOT MY FLUTE.
THERE IT IS!
BAD FLUTE!
BAD!
O...KAY.
RUFF!
YOU'D BETTER HURRY UP AND
WRITE THAT APOLOGY!
OH...MMM.
YOU'D BETTER...HURRY...UP!
AAH!
YOUR THOUGHTS BETRAY YOU.
YOUR FEARS WILL BE YOUR
DOWNFALL.
TAKATO, DON'T LISTEN!
ANY SECOND, I'M GONNA WAKE UP
FROM THIS DREAM!
A DREAM?
LIKE THE ONE THAT BECAME
GUILMON?
IT'S ALWAYS DIGIMON,
DIGIMON WITH YOU.
[ LAUGHTER ]
DON'T YOU EVER GET TIRED
OF DIGIMON?
IT'S ALL YOU EVER TALK
ABOUT!
[ LAUGHS ]
IT'S HOT.
MY HEAD FEELS ALL FUZZY
FOR SOME REASON.
TAKATO, SNAP OUT OF IT!
TAKATO!
EACH HUMAN MIND IS SO DIFFERENT,
SO IMPERFECT.
THAT WILL CHANGE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
ONE BY ONE, THEY SHALL
BE WIPED CLEAN
UNTIL THIS REAL WORLD
IS NO MORE!
HOW CAN YOU RUN SO FAST WITH
THOSE LITTLE LEGS, HUH?!
I HAVE BOUNCY FEET.
MAYBE WE CAN HURRY A LITTLE
BIT SLOWER.
NO!
JERI'S IN THERE!
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
ARE YOU TELLING ME YOU KNOW
WHERE JERI IS?
NOT EXACTLY,
BUT I'M POSITIVE THAT SHE'S
AROUND HERE SOMEWHERE.
I'VE GOTTA HELP HER.
SHE WOULDN'T BE IN THIS MESS
IF IT WEREN'T FOR ME.
RAAAAAGGH!
UGH!
AAAAAAH!
[ CRYING ]
BE BRAVE, JERI.
A PART OF ME WILL ALWAYS BE
WITH YOU.
REMEMBER, YOU HAVE A
LION'S HEART.
WILL YOU SNAP OUT OF IT?
COME ON, LET'S GO!
ALL RIGHT, ALREADY.
LEAD ON, CREAM PUFF!
AH! AH! AH!
AAH!
MAYBE IT'S FRIENDLY.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
DON'T YOU HAVE ENOUGH
FRIENDS?!
AH!
OH, MAN, I GOT DIRT UP MY
NOSE!
WE DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR THIS!
RAAAGH!
HEY, YOU GOT WINGS!
GO, CALUMON!
OKAY!
OHH...
OH, NO, YOU DON'T!
NNNGG!
ANTYLAMON!
CAN YOU HEAR ME?!
[ Tiredly ] YES, SUSIE.
LOOK AROUND THE STREET.
IS ANYONE THERE?
YOU SEE WHAT I SEE, AND I
SEE NO ONE.
I SEE STREET SIGNS, BUT MOM
WON'T LET ME DRIVE ANYMORE.
SHOULD I LOOK LEFT OR RIGHT?
RIGHT. YOU KNOW HOW TO TELL
WHICH WAY THAT IS?
YOU HAVE TO MAKE AN "R" WITH
YOUR FINGERS.
MAKE AN "R" WITH MY FINGERS?
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S REALLY MORE OF
AN "O."
[ GASPS ]
CALUMON!
GOTTA GO.
GOTTA GO!
[ GROWLS ]
OKAY, BUDS, LET'S HAVE
SOME FUN!
CORONA BLASTER!
RAAAGH!
BEELZEMON! HURRY!
I THINK I FOUND JERI!
HEY, COME ON.
LET ME IN. LET ME IN.
CALUMON, WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR?
I GOT IT.
I CAN'T SEE ANYTHING.
BUT I CAN SURE FEEL IT.
COME ON! OPEN!
CAN YOU HEAR ME?!
I DON'T
THINK HE'S LISTENING.
SO LET'S KNOCK A LITTLE
LOUDER!
DOUBLE IMPACT!!
WHOA!
HIT HIM AGAIN!
HIT HIM AGAIN! HARDER!
AH-HA!
MMM-UNNGH!
WHOA!
WE'RE COMING, JERI!
DID YOU SEE THAT?
THERE WERE TWO DIGIMON THERE A
MOMENT AGO,
AND NOW THEY'RE GONE.
DO YOU THINK THEY'VE BEEN
DELETED?
NO.
AT LEAST, I HOPE NOT.
OPEN WIDE!
THIS SUCKER'S TOUGH!
HA HA!
[ Grunting ] AS SOON AS IT'S
OPEN, YOU GO IN AND GET HER!
READY WHEN YOU ARE!
[ GRUNTING ]
GOT IT!
HERE I GO!
OR DO I?
YOU AND YOUR CREAM PUFF.
GET GOING, CHUBBY!
I GOTTA GO ON A DIET.
GREAT,
OUT OF THE FRYING PAN...
[ GRUNTING ]
OH!
CALUMON, GO!
SAVE HER!
OH!
OH, JERI, YOU DON'T LOOK
SO GOOD.
WHATEVER IT TAKES, JERI!
I'LL MAKE THINGS RIGHT!
A MOMENT AGO, I COULD SEE THEM
CLEAR AS DAY, BUT NOW...
ARE THEY IN TROUBLE?
OH, NO!
CALUMON AND BEELZEMON ARE GONE?
IF YOU GO AFTER THEM,
YOU'LL BE GONE, TOO!
OH, WHERE'S HENRY?
HE'S NEVER HERE WHEN THERE'S AN
EMERGENCY.
JERI!
OH, I MISSED YOU SO MUCH!
I'M GLAD YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
WHY WON'T YOU TALK TO ME?
DON'T YOU RECOGNIZE ME?
ALL OF YOUR FRIENDS HAVE BEEN SO
WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
OH...
JERI, IF YOU ONLY KNEW HOW
MUCH WE LOVE YOU.
AAAH!
OH!
HMM? MMM...
ARE YOU TAKING A NAP?
OH...
OH, I'D GIVE ANYTHING TO MAKE
YOU HAPPY AGAIN.
OH, MAN,
THEY COULD HAVE AT LEAST LEFT US
A TRAIL OF BREADCRUMBS OR
SOMETHING.
I'M A TAMER, NOT A PSYCHIC.
GIMME A BREAK.
MMM! AAH!
MEGAGARGOMON!
WAIT FOR US!
HEY, COME ON, YOU GUYS!
HOLD ON A SECOND!
SURE, THEY GET TO FLY, BUT I
HAVE TO RUN!
MARINEANGEMON, CAN YOU CARRY ME
FOR A WHILE?
I HOPE JUSTIMON CAN HOLD ON
UNTIL WE GET BACK.
THIS IS WHERE WE LAST SAW
GALLANTMON.
BEFORE THE D-REAPER
TOOK HIM.
WHEN WE GET IN...
LEAVE IT TO US.
WHITE HOT BURNS THE FIRE AS TRUE
FRIENDSHIP'S STRONGEST BOND.
NO WALL CAN OBSTRUCT.
AAAAAH!
UNH!
SO THIS IS GONNA PROTECT US,
RIGHT?
THAT'S THE PLAN.
Henry: THEN HERE WE COME,
GALLANTMON!
Megagargomon: YEAH!
I HOPE.
WE'RE THROUGH!
OH, NO!
WHAT'S HAPPENED
TO THIS PLACE?
AZULONGMON WAS RIGHT.
WHEREVER THE D-REAPER
APPEARS,
IT LEAVES NOTHING BUT A WAKE OF
DEVASTATION AND CHAOS.
Rika: COME ON, GUYS, LET'S MAKE
A LITTLE CHAOS OF OUR OWN.
[ PANTING ]
YOU'RE WRONG.
I'M NOT NICE AT ALL.
WHEN MY REAL MOTHER DIED,
I SWORE I WOULDN'T LET ANYONE
TAKE HER PLACE.
WHEN MY NEW STEPMOTHER
CAME...
NO!
JERI!
MAKE IT STOP!
PLEASE!
SHE WANTED TO BE MY FRIEND, BUT
I NEVER GAVE HER A CHANCE.
YOU SEE?
I'M NOT NICE.
I'M AWFUL.
JERI! NO!
JERI!
NO, PLEASE!
DON'T!
LEOMON SAID EVERYONE HAS THEIR
OWN DESTINY.
HUH?
[ LAUGHS ]
AAH!
YOU'RE NOT HER!
YOU'RE NOT JERI!
YEAH, I KNOW!
THAT'S WHAT I'VE BEEN SAYING!
SADNESS ISN'T NECESSARY,
YOU KNOW.
IT CAN JUST BE DELETED.
TELL ME WHAT YOU'VE DONE
WITH HER!
OH...
[ SIGHS ]
JERI?
OH...
[ LAUGHING ]
AAH!
RUN FASTER, GUILMON!
IF SHE CATCHES US, WE'RE
DONE FOR!
OVER THERE!
SAKUYAMON, NO!
WAIT FOR US!
NNG! UNG!
UNG! UHH!
ARE YOU OKAY, SAKUYAMON?
[ BOTH PANTING ]
[ LAUGHING ]
[ GIGGLES ]
PHOO!
AAH!
KAHUNA WAIS!
MMM...PHOO!
PHOO!
PHOO! PHOO! PHOO!
KAHUNA WAIS!
NO!
THIS IS NOT POSSIBLE!
MARINEANGEMON GOT RID OF
SCARY JERI.
TAKATO, NOW DO YOU SEE
WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN YOU GUYS HEAD OUT
WITHOUT ME?
THE TWO OF US WOULD HAVE BEEN
HERE FASTER,
BUT I WASN'T SURE EXACTLY
WHERE HERE WAS.
IS HERE!
OH, NOT AGAIN.
MARINEANGEMON, TIME TO GO
PHOO, BUDDY.
PHOO!
WOW, KENTA,
SAVEDUS.
HEY, YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHO KNEW?
HUH? AH!
[ GIGGLES ]
[ PANTING ]
PHOO! PHOO! PHOO!
THAT'S MUCH BETTER.
[ SMOOCHES ]
I'M GLAD EVERYONE IS ALL
RIGHT.
Rika: KENTA, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
I'M A TAMER, TOO,
REMEMBER?
FINALLY, WE'RE ALL
TOGETHER AGAIN.
NOW LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
Henry: FIRST, WE'RE GONNA
NEED A DOOR.
SILO MISSILES!
NOW LET'S FINISH WHAT WE
STARTED!
AAAAH!
WHOA!
JUSTICE KICK!
RAAGH!
TRY THAT AGAIN,
CAPTAIN MONKEY BUTT!
MONKEY BUTT!
RRRRGGGH!
OH, MAN, DIDN'T IT KNOW I WAS
KIDDING?
WELL, I WASN'T!
GUARDIAN BOMBS!
YEAH!
DUDE, WE DID IT!
NICE WORK, GUYS!
THANKS!
GUARDROMON, DID YOU HEAR THAT?
HE SAID THANK YOU TO US!
DO WE ROCK OR WHAT?
WE CERTAINLY DO!
AND WHO ON THIS WHOLE PLANET IS
COOLER THAN US?
NOBODY!
[ LAUGHS ]
RRGGH!
TRY THIS ON FOR SIZE!
THUNDERCLAP!
AAAAAAAGGGH!!
WAY TO GO!
EXCELLENT, DUDE!
WE WON!
ALL RIGHT!
AAH!
RRRRGH!
AAH! UHH!
HUH?
NICE TRY, BIGFOOT!
[ SNARLS ]
[ LAUGHS ]
HUH?!
JUSTICE KICK!
NNG!
HUH?
THAT'S ENOUGH!
SPIRIT STRIKE!
SAKUYAMON!
AND MEGAGARGOMON!
I BROUGHT YOU SOMETHING.
MEGABARRAGE!
AAAAAGH!
RRRRGH!
KAZU, YOU MISS ME?
YEAH, LIKE I MISS THE
CHICKEN POX.
NNNNGH!
WHERE'S THIS GUY GETTING
HIS POWER?
THAT RED CORD!
LET'S DO IT!
RRRRAGGH!
AAAAH -- OOH!
THATCOULD HAVE GONE
BETTER.
AAH!
I BEG YOUR PARDON.
NNG! NNG!
NOW'S OUR CHANCE!
...BLADE!
NNG! NNG!
RRRRAGGGH!!
[ PANTING ]
TEAMWORK TRIUMPHS AGAIN.
I'M GLAD I COULD HELP.
I WAS ALMOST TOO LATE.
YOU ARRIVED JUST IN TIME.
THANKS, ANTYLAMON.
IT WAS MY PLEASURE.
SO, I WAS LIKE, "OH, NO!"
AND GUARDROMON FIRES HIS
MISSILES, AND THEY GO "BOOM!"
AND KNOCKED THE ROCK AWAY FROM
JUSTIMON!
IF IT WASN'T FOR US, WE'D ALL BE
D-REAPER DINNER RIGHT NOW!
KIND OF AN OVERSTATEMENT,
HUH?
WELL, YEAH,
BUT YOU GOTTA ADMIT,
YOU AND KAZU TRULY ARE THE BIG
HEROES OF THE DAY.
HENRY!
HENRY, COME QUICK!
YOU HAVE TO HELP!
WHAT'S WRONG?
CALUMON AND BEELZEMON HAVE
DISAPPEARED.
THEY'RE GONE!
WHAT DO YOU MEAN THEY
DISAPPEARED?
INTO THE BIG RED BALL!
WE RESCUE TWO, WE LOSE TWO MORE.
FIGURES.
IT'S ALL MY FAULT.
LOPMON!
THEY VANISHED BEFORE I COULD
STOP THEM,
SO I CAME TO HELP YOU GUYS.
HEY, SUSIE.
YOU'RE A TAMER,
AREN'T YOU?
OF COURSE I AM.
THEN YOU'LL NEED THIS.
IT'S A MODIFY CARD.
I THINK IT'S TIME YOU HAD ONE.
WHEE!
MY FIRST MODIFY CARD!
OH, THIS IS SO GREAT!
NOW I CAN DIGIMODIFY JUST
LIKE HENRY!
OH, BOY.
I CAN'T WAIT.
TAKATO, WHERE ARE YOU?
WE NEVER REALLY GOT A CHANCE
TO THANK HER.
WHO?
ALICE...
HMM?
[ SIGHS ]
THAT POOR GIRL ALICE.
JERI...
WHERE ARE YOU?
TAKATO, ARE YOU OKAY?
I WISH YOU WOULDN'T BE SO SAD.
I'M HERE WITH YOU NOW.
NOTHING CAN BEAT US WHEN WE
STICK TOGETHER, RIGHT?
THAT'S JUST IT, GUILMON.
JERI IS OUT THERE ALL ALONE.
WE HAVE TO FIND HER.
OH...
[ WHIMPERS ]
JERI...
CAN YOU EVEN HEAR ME?
CAN CALUMON AND BEELZEMON
RESCUE JERI
BEFORE THE D-REAPER AGENS
RETURN?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS"