KNOWING THAT GUILMON WOULD
EVENTUALLY DIGIVOLVE
INTO GROWLMON,
TAKATO TRIED TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT HIS CHAMPION FORM
WOULD BE LIKE.
MEANWHILE, IMPMON CONVINCED
GUILMON TO HELP HIM
SCARE YOUNG COUPLES
IN THE PARK.
AND TAKATO WAS FURIOUS
WHEN HE HEARD
WHAT GUILMON WAS DOING
ON HIS NIGHT OUT.
THEN DEVIDRAMON APPEARED
AND THREATENED
TO RIP APART THE CITY.
TAKATO HAD TO GUIDE GUILMON
THROUGH THE BATTLE
WITH THIS 4-EYED FREAK
WITH HIS USE -- OR MISUSE --
OF MODIFY CARDS.
JUST WHEN IT LOOKED
LIKE GUILMON WOULD LOSE,
HE DIGIVOLVED INTO GROWLMON,
LEAVING TAKATO AFRAID
HE HAD CREATED A MONSTER.
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
♪ WORLD
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMODIFY
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
[ GASPING ]
[ Thinking ] HE'S HUGE.
HE'S HUGER THAN HUGE.
I KNOW I WANTED HIM
TO DIGIVOLVE,
BUT NOW HE'S SO SCARY.
I PROBABLY LOOK LIKE
AN APPETIZER TO HIM.
WHY DIDN'T I DRAW HIM
SMALLER?
[ GROWLING ]
I'M JUST A BIG JALAPE O
POPPER WITH LEGS.
AAH!
AT LEAST MAYBE
I'LL GIVE HIM INDIGESTION.
HUH?
[ SOBBING ]
DON'T...
BE...
AFRAID.
OHH. OHH.
[ SNIFFLING ]
I'M SO SORRY.
I'M NOT AFRAID OF YOU.
WAS I REALLY THAT SCARY?
I MEAN,
WHEN I WAS FIGHTING?
[ GROWLING ]
DRAGON SLASH!
ONLY IF YOU FIND
HUGE, SCARY THINGS SCARY.
TAKATOMON, I WANT TO GO BACK
TO BEING GUILMON
SO YOU WON'T HAVE TO BE AFRAID
OF ME ANYMORE, OKAY?
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
LET'S GO BACK TO THE PARK,
RELAX,
AND FIGURE OUT WHAT TO DO.
IT SHOULDN'T BE THAT HARD,
RIGHT?
COME ON!
PUSH HARDER!
I AM PUSHING HARD.
HARDER, HARDER!
I'LL GIVE YOU HARDER.
I THINK NOW I'M STUCK.
UGH.
IT'S JUST NO USE.
UGH. WE HAVE TO FIGURE OUT
A WAY TO GET YOU
TO DIGIVOLVE BACK
TO GUILMON.
SERIOUSLY, I'M STUCK.
HMM. MAYBE I CAN USE
MY DIGIVICE.
COME ON, YOU STUPID THING.
COULD YOU GET
SOME BUTTER OR SOMETHING?
[ GRUNTING ]
TAKATO, UNSTICK ME.
OKAY, YOU'RE UNSTUCK,
BUT YOU'RE STILL
BIG AS A HOUSE.
WELL, ACTUALLY,
AS BIG AS A CONDO.
LET'S SEE.
THE DIGIVICE
MUST DO SOMETHING.
IF I COULD JUST
FIND THE RIGHT BUTTON.
TO SET CLOCK, PRESS 1.
HOLD ON.
DIGIMODIFY!
DIGIVOLUTION, DEACTIVATE.
UH...HMM?
UGH! I THOUGHT IF I
SLASHED THE CARD BACKWARD,
YOU'D DE-DIGIVOLVE,
BUT THAT WAS A BIG GOOSE EGG.
IS "DE-DIGIVOLVE"
EVEN A WORD?
I DON'T KNOW.
WAIT! I'VE GOT IT!
[ GROANS ]
[ SHOUTS ]
AAH!
WHY'D YOU DO THAT?
I THOUGHT MAYBE IF
I SCARED YOU,
YOU'D TURN BACK
INTO GUILMON.
ANOTHER GOOSE EGG.
OKAY, JUST LET ME
THINK FOR A MINUTE.
DIGIMON ARE MADE OF DATA,
AND WHEN THEY DIGIVOLVE,
THEY ADD A WHOLE BUNCH MORE DATA
TO THEIR OLD DATA
SO THEY CAN GROW
EVEN BIGGER.
LESS DATA MEANS
SMALLER SIZE.
OOH, CAN WE HAVE GOOSE EGGS
FOR DINNER?
OF COURSE! THAT'S IT!
WE'LL WORK OFF THE DATA!
FEEL THOSE MUSCLES BURNING!
NOW WORK THROUGH THE BURN!
LOVE THE BURN!
BE THE BURN!
NO PAIN, NO GAIN, RIGHT?
I JUST LIKE NO PAIN BETTER.
COME ON, GROWLMON,
WE'VE GOT TO SWEAT THAT
EXTRA DATA OUT OF YOU.
GOOD. WORK THAT UPPER BODY,
PUSH IT TO THE MAX.
NOW GIVE ME
EVERYTHING YOU'VE GOT.
GOOD! HA HA.
NOW RUN, RUN, RUN!
BOY, THIS LOOKED A LOT
EASIER ON TV.
OKAY, SHOWER OFF.
[ WHINING ]
I KNOW, GROWLMON,
BUT DIGIVOLVING
TAKES A LOT OF ENERGY,
SO MAYBE IF WE
COOL YOU DOWN,
IT'LL GET RID
OF SOME OF THAT ENERGY,
AND YOU'LL CHANGE BACK.
AH-CHOO!
OH, GREAT!
HE'S CATCHING A COLD.
I'M GOING
TO GO DOWN IN HISTORY
AS THE WORST
DIGIMON TAMER EVER.
WAIT A MINUTE. TAMER?
DIGIMON NEED A TAMER'S ENERGY
IN ORDER TO DIGIVOLVE.
CLEAR A SPACE, GROWLMON,
'CAUSE I'M COMING IN THERE,
TOO.
AAH!
IT'S, UH, COLD, HUH?
YEAH! IT'S REFRESHING.
AH-CHOO!
OKAY, WE'LL WORK OUT
TOGETHER.
[ BOTH PANTING ]
JUST A FEW MORE LAPS,
GROWLMON.
[ SIGHS ]
OKAY, THAT'S IT!
TIME TO GET TOUGH!
[ BELL RINGS ]
I WISH THAT GROWLMON
WILL TURN BACK TO GUILMON
VERY, VERY SOON.
WELL, COME ON. YOU GOT TO
WISH, TOO, GROWLMON.
ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE TRYING
TO RING THE BELL,
NOT TEAR IT DOWN.
SORRY.
OKAY, NOW DO WHAT I DO.
I WISH THAT GROWLMON
TURNS BACK TO GUILMON
VERY, VERY SOON.
I WISH THAT I WILL TURN
BACK TO GUILMON
VERY, VERY SOON.
OKAY, THIS IS THE PLAN.
YOU SPEND THE NIGHT HERE,
GROWLMON,
AND HOPEFULLY
IN THE MORNING
YOU'LL BE BACK
TO GUILMON.
HOPEFULLY. HA HA.
OKAY. IN THE MORNING,
WILL YOU BRING SOME BREAD?
AH, YOU BET. BYE.
[ Woefully ] BYE.
DON'T WORRY, GROWLMON.
EVERYTHING WILL BE FINE.
TAKATO?
HUH?
JERI.
UH, HI, JERI.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
OH, NOWHERE.
YOU KNOW, JUST AROUND.
SO, UH...SEE YOU.
DO YOU NEED HELP?
NO, THAT'S OKAY.
WELL, UM,
I DON'T KNOW, REALLY.
[ Thinking ] I CAN'T BELIEVE
I'M GOING TO SAY THIS.
WOULD YOU HELP ME, JERI?
I'VE GOT THIS PROBLEM
WITH MY PARTNER --
I MEAN, MY FRIEND,
MY GOOD FRIEND.
THIS FRIEND HAS GONE
THROUGH ABIGCHANGE LATELY.
I'M TALKING BIG CHANGE
LITERALLY.
MY FRIEND HAS GROWN
A LOT,
AND I MEANA LOTA LOT,
AND IT'S CAUSED
A WHOLE BUNCH OF PROBLEMS,
SO I WANT THINGS TO GO BACK
TO THE WAY THEY WERE BEFORE.
WHAT SHOULD I DO?
TAKATO...MM.
[ Thinking ]
I BET TAKATO HAS A CRUSH
ON A GIRL,
BUT SHE GOT TALLER,
AND NOW HE FEELS GOOFY
NEXT TO HER,
SO HE WISHES
SHE WERE SHORT AGAIN.
THAT'S SO CUTE!
I KNOW JUST WHAT HE MEANS.
THAT GROWTH SPURT I JUST
WENT THROUGH
MADE ME FEEL SO GAWKY,
LIKE EVERYONE WAS STARING --
[ Gasps ] WAIT! I GET IT!
HUH? YOU DO?
JERI LIKES YOU, TAKATO,
BUT ONLY AS A FRIEND, OKAY?
DON'T WORRY.
THERE'S A MILLION
OTHER GIRLS OUT THERE.
UH...YEAH, OKAY, JERI.
THANKS.
MOM, DAD,
WHY ARE GIRLS CRAZY?
THEY'RE NOT.
THEIR HUSBANDS
MAKE THEM THAT WAY.
HMM. RIGHT.
IT'S THE OTHER WAY AROUND.
WOMEN HAVE THAT CRAZY GENE.
THEY'VE DONE STUDIES, YOU KNOW.
AHA. THOSE MUST HAVE BEEN
THE SAME STUDIES
THAT DISCOVERED THAT PIZZA
AND COOKIES ARE GOOD FOR YOU.
RIGHT. YOU SEE, IT'S ALL
VERY SCIENTIFIC.
[ Thinking ] AM I THE ONLY
NORMAL PERSON IN THE WORLD?
[ SNORING ]
IF I RUN ANY MORE,
MY LEGS WILL FALL OFF.
THERE THEY GO.
HEY! YOU ASLEEP?
HEY! HEY! HEY! HEY!
COME ON, LET'S PLAY!
WHAT AM I GOING TO DO?
POOR GROWLMON.
I ALREADY KNOW HOW
TO KNOCK.
[ TAPPING ON WINDOW ]
WHAT?
HUH?
NO, LIKE THIS.
GROWLMON!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
CALUMON SAID THAT 2:00
IN THE MORNING
IS THE VERY BEST TIME OF ALL
TO PLAY.
CALUMON?
HEY! HI!
WHAT ABOUT ALL THAT
TROUBLE WE WENT THROUGH
TO HIDE YOU YESTERDAY?
AW, NUTS.
HE'S MAD AGAIN.
OHH!
BYE. AAH.
CALUMON GETS WEIRDER
AND WEIRDER EVERY DAY.
NOW, WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO
ABOUT YOU?
SORRY TO GET YOU UP
SO LATE.
THAT'S OKAY.
I WAS JUST SLEEPING.
NOT JUST SLEEPING.
SNORING, TOO.
COME ON.
SO, HENRY, YOU SAID YOU HAD
AN IDEA OF A PLACE
THAT YOU COULD HIDE GROWLMON?
YEAH, DO YOU REMEMBER
THAT HUGE TUNNEL
BENEATH THE PARK WHERE
GUILMON DISAPPEARED
THAT ONE TIME?
ARE YOU LISTENING TO YOURSELF?
WE CAN'T KEEP HIM HERE.
HE'LL GO TO THAT OTHER WORLD
AND DISAPPEAR.
I DOUBT IT. I THINK
THAT WAS JUST A FLUKE.
OKAY.
I'M SORRY, GROWLMON,
BUT THIS SEEMS TO BE
THE ONLY SAFE PLACE FOR YOU.
SO STAY HERE UNTIL
I COME GET YOU
IN THE MORNING, OKAY?
OKAY.
SERIOUSLY. DON'T LEAVE,
EVEN IF CALUMON FINDS
THE BEST PLAYGROUND EVER.
SEE YOU LATER.
HAVE FUN WITHOUT US!
[ MOANING ]
HA HA HA. ANOTHER NIGHT
OF FUN FOR IMPMON.
NOW I JUST ACTUALLY HAVE
TO FIND SOME FUN.
OOH! HELLO.
WHAT DO WE HAVE HERE?
CAREFUL. CAREFUL.
CAREFUL!
AW. HEY! ARE YOU GOING TO
SLEEP ALL NIGHT OR WHAT?
AAH!
SO, YOU WANT TO PLAY ROUGH.
HUH?
SERIOUSLY, GET UP!
I DIDN'T COME ALL THIS WAY
JUST TO WATCH YOU SLEEP!
I'M A BUSY GUY.
I GOT TO GO AND MAKE --
WELL, WHAT I GOT TO DO
IS NONE OF YOUR B--
HUH? IMPMON?
YEAH?
I'M NOT SUPPOSED
TO PLAY WITH YOU.
OH, WHY?
'CAUSE TAKATO SAID
YOU'RE A BAD INFLUENCE.
OH. I GET IT.
THEY WERE RIGHT.
I GUESS SIZE
DOESN'T MATTER.
YOU'RE BIGGER, BUT YOU'RE
JUST AS BORING AS EVER.
AREN'T YOU?
WELL...
AAH!
[ CACKLING ]
YOU COULD USE SOME EXERCISE,
BIG BOY.
NOT AGAIN.
COME ON! MARCH!
BADA-BOOM!
YOU KNOW, YOU'RE RIGHT!
I AM A BAD INFLUENCE,
BUT I'M JUST
SO GOOD AT IT!
[ CACKLING ]
HOW COME TAKATO NEVER HELPS OUT
WITH THE HEAVY STUFF?
I DON'T KNOW.
HOW COME YOU NEVER HELP OUT
WITH THE LAUNDRY?
THAT'S DIFFERENT.
OF COURSE IT IS, DEAR.
I'M TAKING THE DAY-OLD BREAD
AND THE DAY-OLD DAY-OLD BREAD.
SEE YOU!
GROWLMON'S GOING TO BE
SO GLAD TO SEE ME.
WELL, THE FOOD ANYWAY.
[ GASPS ]
HE'S GONE!
DOES "DON'T LEAVE"
HAVE ANOTHER MEANING?
YOU SURE HE DIDN'T JUST
WALK DOWN THE TUNNEL?
YEAH, I WALKED UP
AND DOWN THAT TUNNEL
SO MANY TIMES I WORE
A GROOVE IN THE FLOOR.
HEY, TERRIERMON?
YEP?
GO SEE
IF YOU CAN FIND GROWLMON.
I'M ON IT...SINCE I GUESS
I HAVE NO CHOICE.
HMM. HEY.
IT'LL BE OKAY.
UH-HUH.
GROWLMON!
HEY, GROWLMON!
LET'S SEE. IF I WERE
A GREAT BIG DINOSAUR
LOOKING FOR FUN,
I'D GO...
OH, WHO KNOWS WHERE HE'D GO?
DINOSAURS ARE WEIRD.
GROWLMON, COME ON!
THIS ISN'T FUN ANYMORE!
BUT, HONEY, IT'S JUST
A TOUPEE.
YES, BUT YOU WEAR IT
ON YOUR CHEST.
[ GRUNTING ]
GROWLMON!
HOW COULD SOMETHING SO BIG
BE SO HARD TO FIND?
IT SHOULD BE LIKE TRYING TO
FIND A HAYSTACK IN A HAYSTACK.
WHERE COULD HE BE HIDING?
HMM?
[ SNORING ]
GROWLMON!
THE PARK -- WITH A THING --
AND THE KIDS --
ON HIS TAIL -- SNORING!
GROWLMON!
GROWLMON?
WHERE IS HE?
ARE YOU SURE YOU SAW HIM
HERE, TERRIERMON?
TERRIERMON, IS THIS
SOME SORT OF GAME?
IT'S NOT A GAME.
HE WAS HERE.
GROWLMON!
TAKATO, OVER HERE.
HUH?
GROWLMON, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING IN THE BUSHES?
SEE? I TOLD YOU
IT WASN'T A GAME.
FIRST TIME
FOR EVERYTHING.
GROWLMON, WHAT WERE
YOU THINKING?
I TOLD YOU NOT
TO LEAVE THE TUNNEL.
I KNOW, BUT I COULDN'T
HELP IT.
COULDN'T HELP IT? IT SEEMS LIKE
NOT LEAVING THE TUNNEL
IS PRETTY EASY TO DO.
IT IS WHEN IMPMON ISN'T
THROWING FIREBALLS AT YOU.
HUH?
HE WOKE ME UP,
AND THEN BADA-BOOMED ME
RIGHT OUT OF THE TUNNEL.
HEY, WHO'S HUNGRY?
I'M GRILLING UP
SOME DINOSAUR STEAKS!
HA HA HA! BADA-BOOM!
I GUESS YOU WANT YOURS
TO GO, HUH? HA HA!
JUST RELAX. ALL YOU NEED'S
A LITTLE BIT OF TENDERIZING
AND MAYBE A PINCH OF SALT.
PYRO BLASTER!
AH, NUTS, THAT'S GOING TO
LEAVE A MARK.
NOW SEE HERE! I'M NOT GOING TO
FIGHT YOU
IF YOU'RE GOING TO FIGHT BACK,
FUZZY PINEAPPLE HEAD!
I'LL JUST...REST
FOR A MINUTE.
[ SNORING ]
AND WHEN I WOKE UP,
A BUNCH OF KIDS
WERE PLAYING ON ME.
I'M SORRY, TAKATO.
I DIDN'T MEAN
TO BREAK MY PROMISE.
FORGIVE HIM ALREADY.
IT'S OKAY, GROWLMON.
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN BETTER
WITHOUT ALL THE BURNING.
HENRY, PEOPLE!
HUH? WHAT?
AND HE WEARS IT
ON HIS CHEST!
NO!
OH, LOOK, LITTLE BOYS
PLAYING WITH DOLLS. HOW CUTE.
UGH.
SO, HENRY, WHERE DO YOU THINK
THAT WE CAN HIDE GROWLMON?
I DON'T WANT TO SEND HIM
BACK TO THE TUNNEL
IF HE'S JUST GOING TO
GET HARASSED BY IMPMON AGAIN.
IT'S GOT TO BE SOMEPLACE
HE CAN'T BE SEEN.
THAT'S IT. CAMOUFLAGE.
OH, THAT SOUNDS PAINFUL.
WE'RE JUST GOING TO PAINT YOU,
LIKE PUTTING ON MAKEUP.
THAT SOUNDS EVEN MORE
PAINFUL.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
THERE'S PAINT LEFT OVER
FROM WHEN MY PARENTS
PAINTED THE STORE.
BUT WHO'D WANT TO PUT MAKEUP
ON A STORE?
HOLD STILL, GROWLMON.
IT'LL BE OVER SOON.
[ ALL LAUGHING ]
AAH!
[ LAUGHING ]
EW.
ALL DONE, GROWLMON.
MAN, YOU LOOK GREAT.
THAT MUST BE ONE UGLY STORE.
OKAY, NOW, LET'S TEST
IT OUT.
GO HIDE, GROWLMON.
OKAY.
READY OR NOT,
HERE WE COME!
YOU READY?
GROWLMON?
HMM.
WOW, HE TAKES THIS HIDING THING
SERIOUSLY.
WHERE ARE YOU, GROWLMON?
I CAN'T JUST TELL YOU.
YOU HAVE TO FIND ME.
WELL, IF I HAVE TO
LOOK FOR HIM,
YOU HAVE TO LOOK
FOR HIM, TOO.
HMM. IS THAT HIM?
THAT'S A STICK.
OH, YEAH. BUT SEE, THAT KNOT --
IF YOU LOOK AT IT
FROM A CERTAIN ANGLE --
IT STILL LOOKS
LIKE A STICK.
MAYBE HE JUST LEFT.
NO ONE WILL BE ABLE
TO FIND HIM.
AH. GREAT.
PATHETIC.
HUH?
A PERSON MAY NOT BE ABLE
TO SEE HIM,
BUT ANY DIGIMON WHO WANTED TO
COULD FIND HIM IN A HEARTBEAT.
PROVE IT.
RENIMON.
WHERE DO YOU COME FROM
ALL THE TIME?
DO YOU JUST WAIT AROUND
TO SCARE US?
RENIMON.
YES, REIKA.
FIND HIM
AND TEACH HIM A LESSON.
MY PLEASURE, REIKA.
I'LL FIND HIM.
THERE.
WAIT!
YOU GUYS AREN'T TAMERS.
YOU'RE A JOKE.
DIGIMON AREN'T
SUPPOSED TO HIDE.
THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO FIGHT.
YOU BETTER JUST BACK OFF,
REIKA.
OR WHAT, YOU'LL RUN OFF
AND HIDE ON ME?
OOH, I'M SO SCARED.
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
COME ON, YOU GUYS.
THERE'S NO REALLY NO REASON
FOR US TO FIGHT OVER GROWLMON,
IS THERE?
CAN'T WE BE FRIENDS? HUH?
HEY, IT WASN'T SUPPOSED
TO RAIN TODAY.
SINCE WHEN HAS
THE WEATHERMAN EVER BEEN RIGHT?
HELLO! SOMEONE WANT
TO ANSWER ME?
FINE.
UM, TAKATO, I THINK
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A PROBLEM.
PROBLEM? WHY?
THE RAIN'S MAKING
THE PAINT RUN.
OH, SO HE'LL BE BROWN
INSTEAD OF GRAY AND GREEN.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
NO, IT'S MAKING
THE PAINT RUN OFF.
YOU GUYS USED
WATER-BASED PAINT?
YOU'RE EVEN MORE PATHETIC
THAN I THOUGHT.
SEE YOU LATER, LOSERS.
RENIMON.
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO,
GROWLMON?
I CAN'T AFFORD
OIL-BASED PAINT.
[ SOBBING ]
AW.
WHY DOES EVERYTHING I DO
ALWAYS GO SO WRONG?
IF ONLY YOU COULD TURN BACK
INTO GUILMON.
PLEASE DON'T CRY, TAKATOMON.
MY ARMS ARE STARTING TO RUN.
IT'LL BE OKAY, TAKATO.
YEAH, IF WORST COMES TO WORST,
WE CAN ALWAYS MOVE
TO ANTARCTICA.
TERRIERMON.
WHAT?
WELL, WE COULD.
THANKS, GUYS.
SORRY FOR THE WATERWORKS.
HUH?
HEY, IT STOPPED RAINING.
TAKATO, LOOK!
SHEESH, WOULD YOU LOOK
ALREADY?!
HUH?
A RAINBOW. WOW.
OOH, IT'S PRETTY,
WHATEVER IT IS.
[ ALL GASPING IN WONDER ]
NOWÂ Â Â THARE THE COLORS
WE SHOULD HAVE PAINTED GROWLMON.
TERRIERMON, WE WANTED HIM
TO BLEND IN,
NOT STICK OUT
LIKE A SORE THUMB.
WELL, HE'D BLEND IN FINE
IF HE WERE IN THE SKY,
WOULDN'T HE?
OH, I GOT TO EXPLAIN
EVERYTHING TO YOU.
AHH. HUH?
WHAT'S HAPPENING
TO GROWLMON, HENRY?
THOSE FLECKS OF LIGHT
MUST BE DIGITAL MATTER,
AND IT LOOKS THE RAINBOW
IS PULLING THEM
OUT OF HIM,
OR MAYBE THE SUN'S JUST
KIND OF DRYING HIM OUT.
I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S WEIRD.
NOT AS WEIRD AS WHAT
I FOUND
BETWEEN GROWLMON'S TOES
WHEN WE WERE PAINTING HIM.
TRUE.
WHOA!
GROWLMON!
I MEAN, GUILMON,
WHOEVER YOU ARE!
YOU'RE BACK TO BEING
GUILMON!
THINGS ARE FINALLY NORMAL AGAIN.
YEAH.
WELL, AS NORMAL AS THEY GET.
SO, WE NEED TO FIND
A RAINBOW
EVERY TIME HE WANTS
TO CHANGE BACK TO GUILMON?
HOW COME NO ONE WANTS
TO ANSWER ME TODAY?
DOES TAKATO NEED AN INSTRUCTION
MENU FOR GUILMON, OR WHAT?
I WONDER IF THESE GUYS WILL
EVER FIGURE OUT THEIR PARTNERS.
STAY TUNED TO "DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS."