TAKATO WAS JUST AN ORDINARY KID
WHO LOVED DIGIMON,
AND WHO CAN BLAME HIM?
THINGS WERE PRETTY NORMAL
UNTIL HE FOUND
THAT FUNKY BLUE CARD.
IT TURNED HIS CARD READER
INTO A REAL DIGIVICE
THAT SCANNED IN ALL THIS
COOL INFO ABOUT GUILMON,
A DIGIMON TAKATO HAD MADE UP.
I BET HE NEVER DREAMED
HE'D GET A REAL DIGI-EGG
WHEN HE DID THOSE DRAWINGS.
THEN HE SAW REIKA AND RENIMON
FIGHTING LYNXMON.
THE NEXT MORNING,
HIS DIGI-EGG HATCHED
AND THERE WAS NO SIGN
OF GUILMON,
BUT HIS DIGIVICE LED TAKATO
RIGHT TO HIM.
LOOKS LIKE TAKATO'S GOT
A LOT TO LEARN
ABOUT BEING A DIGIMON TAMER,
LIKE HOW NOT TO GET TOASTED
BY HIS OWN CREATION.
DI-DI-DI
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON
DI-DI-DI
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS
TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
WORLD
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS
DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON
[ GROWLS ]
OH, NO.
I'VE CREATED A DIGIMON,
AND NOW HE'S GOING
TO BLAST ME TO SMITHEREENS.
UHH...UHH.
[ SNIFFS ]
OH.
UHH, AND THE LAST THING
I'LL HEAR IS
THAT HORRIBLE GROWL.
HUH?
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO ATTACK ME?
HOW?
THIS IS THE COOLEST.
HA HA HA.
I REALLY CREATED YOU,
AND YOU'RE MINE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT --
MY OWN REAL LIVE DIGIMON.
HI, GUILMON.
[ LAUGHING ]
Takato:
MOM, DAD, I'M HOME.
[ Whispers ] OKAY,
YOU'VE GOT TO BE REALLY QUIET.
HEY, KIDDO.
YOU'RE HOME LATE, HUH?
DINNER'S ALMOST READY.
UH, GREAT.
Dad: WHAT'S THAT?
UH, WHAT'S WHAT?
THAT BOX YOU'VE GOT.
OH, THE BOX.
IT'S JUST -- HA HA.
IT'S, LIKE, A BOX,
YOU KNOW, TO HOLD THINGS.
UH, YEAH.
HMM.
DON'T BE DRAGGING ANY MORE
TRASH UP THERE, TAKATO.
YOU KNOW I'LL JUST END UP
THROWING IT OUT AGAIN LATER.
OKAY.
[ Whispers ] YOU HAVE
TO STAY UNDER THE BOX.
TAKATO?
YEAH -- HA HA HA.
[ Whispers ]
COME ON, GUILMON.
[ GRUNTS ]
NEED A HAND THERE,
SON?
IT'S OKAY. I GOT IT.
HA HA HA.
AAH!
HA HA.
HMM.
HEY, DON'T DO THAT,
GUILMON.
GUILMON?
LISTEN, GUILMON,
YOU'VE GOT TO STAY
OUT OF TROUBLE.
YOU CAN'T KEEP BLASTING THINGS
AND KNOCKING STUFF OVER.
I MEAN, MOM YELLS AT ME
WHEN I BRING A BOX HOME,
BUT A DIGITAL DINOSAUR?
I DON'T THINK SHE'D EVER
BE ABLE TO STOP YELLING.
UNDERSTAND, BOY?
I GUILMON?
RIGHT. I'M TAKATO.
TA-KA-TO-MON?
I'M NOT A DIGIMON.
TAKATO.
TAKATOMON.
[ GROANS ]
NO, I'M A HUMAN BEING.
HOW CAN I EXPLAIN THIS?
LET'S SEE NOW.
THAT'S IT.
I'VE GOT JUST THE THING.
WAIT.
GOOD THING
I HID THIS FROM MOM.
EVERYTHING I THINK IS COOL
SHE THINKS IS TRASH.
SEE, GUILMON?
A DIGIMON TAMER.
GUILMON: OH. GOGGLES.
Woman: SIR, THERE'S ANOTHER ONE
TRYING TO BIO-EMERGE.
Woman #2:
INITIATING TRACKING SEQUENCE.
COMPUTER IS ACQUIRING
A LOCK ON THE TARGET.
STAND BY. THE DATA STREAM
IS CONGESTED.
WE MAY NOT GET A VISUAL.
SEND A TRACER.
BRINGING A TRACER
ON-LINE.
IT'S CLOSING IN
ON THE TARGET.
RUN, RABBIT, RUN.
COMPUTER IS RENDERING.
VISUAL COMPLETION
IN T-MINUS FIVE SECONDS.
WELL, NOW, IT LOOKS
LIKE YOU'VE LOST THE RACE,
MY LITTLE FRIEND.
[ GROWLS, PANTS ]
AAH!
[ SNORING ]
Takato:
WOW, BAD BREATH.
HMM. MM-HMM.
GUILMON:
YEAH, BAD BREATH.
COME ON, AGE CREAM,
WORK YOUR MAGIC.
YOU KNOW, HONEY,
I'VE BEEN THINKING.
OOH, DID IT HURT?
YES, EXACTLY.
UH, WELL, UM, TAKATO --
BEING AN ONLY CHILD --
CAN GET, YOU KNOW...
NO WAY.
BUT, HONEY, I HAVEN'T EVEN
SAID ANYTHING YET.
AND YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
WE CAN'T HAVE PETS HERE.
RIGHT...
WE COULD HIDE IT.
IT'S NOT A QUESTION
OF HIDING IT.
WHAT KIND OF LESSON
WOULD WE TEACH TAKATO
IF WE TELL HIM
IT'S OKAY TO BREAK RULES?
BESIDES, WE BOTH KNOW
THAT TAKATO'S NOT OLD ENOUGH
TO TAKE CARE OF A PET.
AND DON'T SAY YOU'LL TAKE CARE
OF IT UNTIL HE'S OLD ENOUGH.
MM.
Woman: THE STARS
ARE BEAUTIFUL TONIGHT.
Man: NOT AS BEAUTIFUL
AS YOU.
[ Giggles ] OH, YOU.
[ GIGGLES ]
WHAT'S THAT?
HMM? UM,
THE NORTHERN LIGHTS?
Reika: [ Thinking ]
ANOTHER ONE'S COMING THROUGH.
GET IN GEAR, RENIMON,
OR WE'LL MISS ALL THE FUN.
THERE IT IS.
RENIMON.
I'M ON IT.
AAH!
GOBLINMON. LET'S SEE.
HE CHEATS.
HE'S GOT
A FIREBALL GOBLIN STRIKE.
OH, IT'S JUST A ROOKIE.
WHERE'S THE SPORT IN THAT?
WALK ALL OVER HIM,
RENIMON.
[ GROWLS ]
HE'S TOAST.
OHH!
HUH?
[ GROWLS ]
YOU MISSED.
[ GIGGLING ]
MMM. MMM.
Digimon: IS THAT
YOUR SPECIAL ATTACK?
HMM?
WHO ARE YOU,
LITTLE DUDE?
OH, WHAT A CUTE
LITTLE TOY.
DID YOU GET THAT
FOR ME, HONEY?
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO OPEN
YOUR MOUTHS MUCH, MUCH WIDER
IF YOU REALLY WANT
TO SWALLOW EACH OTHER.
UH, WHAT DID YOU SAY?
AN ALIEN! IT WANTS
TO SWALLOW OUR BRAINS!
DON'T DO IT, MAN. I NEED
WHAT LITTLE BRAIN I HAVE.
AAH!
HEY, MAYBE I CAN HELP THEM.
[ GROWLS ]
MISSED AGAIN.
AAH!
WHOOPS.
OH, SO CLOSE.
[ GROWLS ]
HE'S NOT LOSING STRENGTH,
REIKA.
YEAH, THIS IS BORING.
LET'S SEE. WHICH ONE?
DIGIMODIFY
THE BOOST CARD.
DIGIMODIFY!
HYPERCHIP ACTIVATE!
HE DIGIVOLVED,
BUT HOW?
HE SHOULDN'T BE ABLE TO.
HUH?
[ GROWLING ]
HEY, UH,
WHAT'S WRONG, BOY?
GUILMON?
THERE'S NOTHING THERE.
UH...HUH?
AAH!
RENIMON, I'M GOING TO BE
VERY VEXED IF YOU LOSE.
DON'T WORRY, REIKA.
JUST WATCH.
[ GROWLING ]
THAT ALL YOU GOT,
BIG BOY?
[ SCREAMS ]
DIAMOND STORM!
HAH!
HUH?
AAH!
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT,
RENIMON.
NOT EVEN
A CHAMPION-LEVEL DIGIMON
CAN STAND IN OUR WAY
ANYMORE.
NOW DOWNLOAD
FYUKOMON'S DATA.
NEXT TIME, YOU'LL WIN...
WITHOUT MY HELP.
TAKATO.
MM?
DO YOU REMEMBER THAT TIME
YOU FOUND A CAT
AND BROUGHT IT HOME?
I DIDN'T JUST FIND IT, MOM.
THAT OLD LADY
GAVE IT TO ME, REMEMBER?
I KNOW. I JUST WANT
TO REMIND YOU
WE CAN'T HAVE ANY PETS.
ARE YOU LISTENING?
TAKATO.
WHATEVER ANIMAL YOU HAVE
UP IN YOUR ROOM,
YOU'RE JUST GOING TO HAVE
TO TAKE IT BACK, OKAY?
HA HA.
MOM, YOU'RE CRAZY.
AN ANIMAL. HA HA.
GUILMON, COME DOWN HERE.
HEE HEE.
OW! DOWN HERE,
NOT ON ME.
OH, SORRY.
MAN, YOU'RE HEAVY.
HEAVY. YEAH.
I'LL JUST LEAN THAT THERE
AND THAT THERE --
GUILMON, DON'T EAT THAT.
OKAY.
WELL, IT'S NOT PRETTY,
BUT IT SHOULD DO.
NOW, GUILMON,
SINCE YOU CAN'T STAY AT HOME,
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO STAY HERE
WHILE I GO TO SCHOOL,
OKAY?
GO SCHOOL?
I KNOW. I WISH THEY HAD
A CLASS ON DIGIMON.
I'D HAVE
THE BEST SHOW-AND-TELL EVER.
NOW, I CAN'T TAKE YOU
TO SCHOOL,
BUT WHEN I GET HOME,
THE TWO OF US CAN PLAY
ALL AFTERNOON, OKAY?
SO STAY IN THAT BOX.
OH, UH...
PLAY NOW.
AW, I WISH I COULD.
IF YOU GET HUNGRY, EAT THIS.
HUH?
HUH? OH, YEAH.
THIS IS FOOD.
YOU EAT IT. SEE?
AHH. MM-MMM.
NOW YOU.
UH, OKAY.
NOW STAY HERE
AND BE QUIET,
AND I'LL SEE YOU
SOON, OKAY?
BYE, GUILMON.
WANT MORE.
TAKATOMON?
OH.
[ HOWLS ]
TAKATOMON.
Boy: UM, GREYMON
DIGIVOLVES TO METALGREYMON.
Boy #2: THAT'S THE BEST
YOU CAN DO?
I'M GOING TO WARP-DIGIVOLVE
TO WEREGARURUMON.
UH, SPEED ACTIVATE --
TOO BAD. I'VE GOT
A SYSTEM CRASH CARD.
YOU LOSE.
OH.
IF YOU WANT TO PLAY AGAIN,
I'D BE HAPPY TO BEAT YOU.
Takato: HI, GUYS.
HEY, WHERE WERE YOU?
YEAH, YOU'RE LATE.
SORRY. YOU WOULDN'T BELIEVE
WHAT I'VE BEEN THROUGH TODAY.
ONE OF YOUR RARE
TAKE-A-SHOWER DAYS?
HEY.
WHAT'S WITH THE GLASSES,
YOLEI?
HA HA. COOL, HUH?
I'M GOING TO BE
A DIGIMON TAMER.
DIGIMON TAMER?
LET'S GO.
WE'VE GOT TO DIGITAME
GYM CLASS.
[ Sighs ] WHO WANTS TO SWEAT
THIS EARLY IN THE DAY?
I'M JUST GOING
TO PUT THESE CARDS AWAY.
YEAH. OKAY.
[ Thinking ] I WONDER
IF ANYONE CAN CREATE A DIGIMON,
OR MAYBE I'M SOME KIND
OF DIGIDESTINED.
THAT'S WHY I GOT
THAT BLUE CARD.
IT'S STILL MISSING.
WHERE COULD IT HAVE GONE?
Boy: TAKATO.
HUH?
COME ON.
SOMETIME BEFORE WE TURN 50
WOULD BE NICE.
OKAY, OKAY.
I'M COMING.
[ Thinking ]
DID IT JUST DISAPPEAR
BACK TO WHERE IT CAME FROM?
HEY,
YOU GROWING ROOTS?
HEY.
WE'LL BE LATE.
LOOK. HE'S GETTING ALL SWEATY
JUST THINKING ABOUT GYM.
GUILMON: HUH?
NEXT. LET'S GO.
[ BLOWS WHISTLE ]
[ PANTING ]
AAH!
UHH!
SO HOW'D I DO, HUH?
JUST OVER THREE METERS.
ALL RIGHT!
I RULE THE WORLD!
DON'T GET TOO EXCITED
THERE, CHUMLEY.
I STILL BEAT YOU.
YEAH, BUT IT'S EASY TO WIN
WHEN YOU CHEAT...HUH?
TAKATOMON?
[ Thinking ] PLEASE TELL ME
I DIDN'T JUST SEE THAT.
[ BELL RINGS ]
TAKATOMON?
Man: YAMAZAKI!
SO LET ME ASK YOU.
HAVE YOU EVER
EVEN MADE AN EFFORT
TO DO YOUR HOMEWORK
THE CORRECT WAY?
All: [ GASP ]
UHH...NOBODY MOVE.
HMM.
UHH! UHH.
OH...
Boy: [ Trembling ]
WHAT WAS THAT, MR. IWAMOTO?
HUH? AND NOW, CLASS,
WE'LL DISCUSS
SOMETHING IMPORTANT.
WHAT DO YOU DO
WHEN YOU START SEEING THINGS
THAT AREN'T REALLY THERE?
[ HUMS ]
GOOD MORNING,
CARDBOARD BOX.
UH, AHEM, UH, STUDENT,
SHOULDN'T YOU BE IN CLASS?
I IN A BOX.
HMM. WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
GUILMON.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
WELL, MY FRIENDS --
HEY, I AM THE PRINCIPAL.
THAT IS ALL
YOU NEED TO KNOW.
NOW, WHAT ARE YOU DOING
IN THE HALL?
PLAY TIME.
OH, YOU SHOULDN'T BE PLAYING.
IT'S TIME FOR CLASS NOW,
AND JUST WHAT'S WITH
THIS CARDBOARD BOX ANYWAY?
[ Grunting ]
TAKE IT OFF.
NO, TAKATOMON SAID
STAY IN BOX.
MY HERNIA!
WHEN YOU'RE AT SCHOOL,
YOU OBEY THE PRINCIPAL.
SO WHEN I SAY
TAKE OFF THE BOX,
YOU TAKE OFF THE BOX.
UNDERSTAND?
OH, SUCH A STRONG
LITTLE FELLA.
OKAY.
OH!
HA HA HA.
YOU FELL DOWN.
WE PLAY NOW?
[ Trembling ] UHH...
DON'T YOU WANT TO PLAY?
PLAY. HUH?
IT'S A MONSTER.
[ ALARM RINGING ]
[ SNIFFS ]
TAKATOMON.
HUH?
LOOKS LIKE YOUR SOCKS
SET OFF THE FIRE ALARM
AGAIN, KANTA.
VERY FUNNY.
I THOUGHT SO.
UH, YOU KIDS STAY HERE.
I'LL SEE WHAT'S GOING ON.
[ GROANS ]
HEY, TAKATO,
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, BUT I GOT TO GO.
[ FIRE ENGINE SIREN WAILING ]
WHOA, SOMEBODY'S HAD
TOO MUCH SUGAR.
LISTEN. I'M TELLING YOU,
I SAW THIS THING.
WE'VE GOT TO CALL OUT
THE NATIONAL GUARD,
THE ARMY, THE NAVY,
THE AIR FORCE, THE MARINES.
A TALKING DINOSAUR?
I HEAR THE PRINCIPAL'S
FINALLY GONE CRAZY.
WELL,
I'VE ALWAYS SUSPECTED
THAT SCHOOL WAS BAD
FOR YOUR HEALTH.
Boy: HOW MANY TIMES DO I
HAVE TO TELL YOU, TERRIERMON?
YOU'VE GOT TO STAY HIDDEN.
NO. COME ON.
[ MURMURING ]
[ PANTING ]
LIKE THERE'D REALLY BE
A MONSTER
WALKING AROUND THE HALLS.
AS IF!
A MONSTER?
AND THE PRINCIPAL THOUGHT
HE SAW THE LOCH NESS MONSTER
AND BIGFOOT, TOO...
IN HIS BATHTUB.
[ Thinking ]
PLEASE DON'T BE GUILMON.
PLEASE DON'T BE -- UHH!
GUILMON,
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
Takato: [ Thinking ]
WHERE COULD HE HAVE GONE?
I'VE GOT TO FIND HIM.
GUILMON.
HUH? OH.
GUILMON! WHERE ARE YOU?
[ Thinking ]
WHAT IF I NEVER FIND HIM AGAIN?
Woman:
WHERE'S ALL THE FOOD?
YOU KNOW HOW LONG IT TOOK
TO MAKE THE MEAT LOAF
DRY AND CRUSTY?
AND MY WATERY SPAGHETTI SAUCE
IS ALL GONE.
THE CHOCOLATE CAKE --
THINK OF THE CHOCOLATE CAKE.
OH, THEY USED THAT
TO RE-SHINGLE THE ROOF.
IT'S GUILMON, ALL RIGHT.
NO ONE ELSE WOULD EAT
THAT STUFF. OH.
[ Thinking ] WHY'D YOU
HAVE TO COME TO SCHOOL?
EVERYBODY'S GOING
TO FIND OUT ABOUT YOU,
AND YOU'LL BE TAKEN
AWAY FROM ME FOR SURE.
GUILMON,
WHY DID YOU HAVE
TO RUN AWAY?
Boy: GUILMON?
HMM?
UH, YOU SAID GUILMON.
WELL, DIDN'T YOU?
I...
HE'S A DIGIMON, RIGHT?
HOW DID YOU KNOW THAT?
IS HE A DIGIMON TAMER,
TOO?
UHH! IT'S TERRIERMON...
AND HE TALKED!
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
HOW?
HA HA. YOU MUST NOT BE
A VERY GOOD DIGIMON TAMER
IF YOU CAN'T EVEN KEEP TRACK
OF JUST ONE DIGIMON.
UHH...UHH.
TERRIERMON!
WHAT? WHAT?
IT'S NOT MY FAULT
IF HE STINKS AT IT,
RIGHT?
HE'S RIGHT.
[ Thinking ] TERRIERMON,
I'VE GOT TO REMEMBER
TO TEACH YOU THE MEANING
OF THE WORD TACT.
[ Thinking ]
TERRIERMON'S RIGHT.
I CAN'T EVEN KEEP GUILMON
OUT OF TROUBLE,
AND NOW...
HE'S GONE.
I'LL NEVER HAVE A FRIENDSHIP
LIKE TERRIERMON AND HIS TAMER.
I DON'T EVEN HAVE
A DIGIMON ANYMORE.
MAYBE I'M NOT EVEN THE KID
WHO WAS SUPPOSED TO FIND GUILMON
AT ALL.
OH...WAIT A MINUTE.
I BET I KNOW
WHERE HE IS.
HUH?
OH.
GUILMON?
HMM?
OH!
GUILMON!
TAKATOMON, HEY!
OKAY, BOY, OKAY.
GUILMON.
OH? WHAT'S WRONG?
WHAT'S WRONG?
OH, YOUR EYES ARE LEAKING,
TAKATOMON. WHY?
JUST LISTEN.
IF WE'RE GOING TO BE
DIGIMON AND HIS TAMER,
YOU'VE GOT TO
LISTEN TO ME MORE.
YOU'VE GOT TO TRY HARDER
TO STAY OUT OF TROUBLE.
AND THEN YOU'LL PLAY
WITH ME?
YEAH.
TAKATOMON,
I NEED A NEW BOX.
GUILMON, STOP THAT.
BUT IF WE'RE NOT HERE
TO CHASE SQUIRRELS,
WHY ARE WE HERE?
I LIKE SQUIRRELS.
WE NEED TO FIND
A PLACE FOR YOU TO HIDE OUT
WHEN I'M IN SCHOOL
AND STUFF,
AND THIS SEEMED
LIKE A GOOD CHOICE
'CAUSE NOT A LOT OF PEOPLE
COME HERE.
MM. PRETTY.
NAH, THIS FEELS
TOO OUT IN THE OPEN.
WHERE CAN WE HIDE YOU?
HMM.
GRR!
HUH?
UHH!
OH!
HEY!
WHAT A LOUSY FIGHTER,
BUT A FIGHT'S A FIGHT.
WHAT? BUT I...
I DREAMT YOU.
HUH? SO WHAT?
IT'S TIME TO FIGHT,
SO CLAM UP.
RENIMON,
WALK ALL OVER HIM.
WILL TAKATO LEARN TO BE
A GOOD DIGIMON TAMER,
OR WILL HE LOSE GUILMON
IN A BATTLE
BEFORE HE EVEN
GETS TO KNOW HIM?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."