DURING THE BATTLE
WITH THE D-REAPER,
JUSTIMON SHOWED UP
TO LEND A HAND.
HE DISTRACTED
THE MEAN, GREEN AGENT,
WHILE THE OTHERS WENT OFF O
HELP TAKATO AND GUILMON,
AND DID THEY EVER NEED I!
JERI'S DOPPELGANGER HAD TURND
INTO SOMETHING REALLY NASTY
AND WAS CHASING TAKATO AD
GUILMON THROUGH THE PARK!
THANKS GOODNESS KENTA
AND MARINANGIMON SHOWED UP.
THE LITTLE MEGA SCARED THAT
THING AWAY
WITH HIS POWERFUL
KAHUNA WAVES.
MEANWHILE, IMPMON DIGIVOLVD
TO BEELZEMON
TO GET THEM INSIDE
THE D-REAPER'S BRAIN...
BUT THEN GOT CAPTURED.
WELL, AT LEAST THEY FINALLY
FOUND JERI,
BUT WHO'S GONNA FIND THE?
♪ DI, DI, DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE WORLD
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS.
DIGIMODIFY.
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON!
OH.
I'M BORED.
DON'T YOU WANT TO PLAY?
JERI?
OH, NOTHING'S WORKING.
NOTHING,
NOTHING, NOTHING.
[ MECHANICAL BEEPING ]
BEELZEMON,
YOU GOTTA WAKE UP!
HUH?
HEY! YOU MOVED!
WHOO-HOO!
WHERE IS...
LEOMON?
NOT HERE.
[ CRYING ]
Leomon:PART OF ME
WILL ALWAYS BE WITH YOU.
REMEMBER...
NO-O-O-O!
MAMA?
PART OF HER
WILL ALWAYS BE WITH US.
MOM? [ SOBS ]
THERE WAS NOTHING
WE COULD DO.
I'M SORRY.
[ Echoing ]
HER SPIRIT IS WITH YOU.
UNH-UNH.
WHERE?
[ CRYING ]
WHERE ARE YOU RUNNING?
RUN AWAY! AWAY!
AWAY?
[ Echoing ]
OR TO NOTHING?
[ WHIMPERS ]
AAH!
RUNNING AWAY FROM DESTINY?
DESTINY.
DESTINY. DESTINY.
DESTINY. DESTINY.
DESTINY.
THAT THING IS ABSORBING SEVERAL
SQUARE MILES EACH DAY.
NOTHING CAN STAND AGAINST IT.
PRETTY SOON, THE ENTIRE CITY
WILL BE ABSORBED.
ARE WE GOING TO MY HOUSE?
I'M REALLY SORRY, RIKA,
BUT I'M AFRAID IT'S JUST
NOT SAFE THERE ANYMORE.
MR. WONG AND YAMAKI ARE SETTING
UP TEMPORARY HEADQUARTERS,
AND WE'RE GOING TO JOIN THEM.
THEY'RE MOVING AS MUCH OF
THE HYPNOS NETWORK
AS THEY CAN SALVAGE.
BY THE WAY, WHAT HAPPENED TO
YOUR FRIEND RYO?
I DON'T KNOW.
WHEN WE WOKE UP, HE WAS GONE.
THAT'S SO LIKE HIM.
JUSTICE KICK!
UH!
GET THEM WHILE THEY'RE FRESH.
RICE BALLS FOR ALL.
HOT SOUP ON THE WAY.
THEY'RE SO DELICIOUS.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
IT'S JUST A LITTLE SOMETHING
I COOKED UP
WHILE YOU WERE SLEEPING.
SO, WHAT DO YOU THINK, GUYS?
HMM.
PUT IT THROUGH ITS PACES,
WOMAN.
GET READY TO WEEP.
THIS ISSOSMOOTH.
OH, YOU'RE
BREAKING MY HEART.
AND IT'S NOT JUST
ANOTHER PRETTY FACE.
THIS BEAUTIFUL BEAST
IS SOLID CHROME DIGIZOID --
THE METAL OF
THE DIGITAL WORLD.
SHE'S AS SOLID AS A TANK.
DOLPHIN'S BABY
IS STILL WILLING TO FLY.
ALL IT NEEDS IS JUST A LITTLE
HELP FROM ITS FRIENDS.
AND MY MOTHER ALWAYS TOLD ME
IF YOU'RE NICE TO YOUR FRIENDS,
THEY'LL BE NICE TO YOU.
THERE.
HMM. VERY NICE.
WE'VE DECIDED TO NAME
THE ARK THIS TIME.
WE'RE CALLING IT
"GRANI."
AND WHY,
MAY I ASK?
GRANI WAS A MYTHIC WARHORSE.
YOU PEOPLE ARE WEIRD.
[ CHEWING ]
MAY I BORROW YOUR DIGIVICE?
HUH?
I KNOW IT'S A PERSONAL THING,
BUT I NEED IT.
UH, OKAY.
Terriermon: HEY, YOU'RE
DARN TOOTIN' IT'S PERSONAL.
WHAT DO YOU NEED IT FOR,
ANYWAY?
TERRIERMON, WOULD YOU --
FOR GRANI.
WITHOUT OUR HELP,
IT WON'T BE ABLE TO EMERGE
INTO THIS WORLD.
PUT SIMPLY, WE'RE MAKING
OUR IDEAS REAL.
ONLY THIS IS MORE LIKE
TELEPORTATION THAN CREATION.
GRANI'S ORIGINAL DATA
WAS DAMAGED
AND RETURNED
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD.
IT COULD'VE JUST DISPERSED INTO
DIGITAL STREAMS,
BUT GRANI IS SELF-AWARE
AND WOULDN'T LET THAT HAPPEN.
GRANI HELD ONTO
AN IMAGE OF ITSELF
THAT DAISY
WAS ABLE TO REBUILD.
BUT IT STILL EXISTS
AS DATA ONLY --
UNTIL WE GIVE IT A FORM
IN THE REAL WORLD.
THAT'S WHERE THE DIGIVICE
COMES IN.
IT TEACHES DATA TO BEHAVE.
KIND OF LIKE YOU.
BUT YOU DON'T LISTEN.
I BET GRANI WILL, THOUGH.
YOU'RE GONNA MAKE A COPY OF
THE DIGIVICE'S PROGRAM, RIGHT?
YOU'RE PRETTY QUICK.
HUH?
TAKATO.
WHO'S THAT?
JERI'S DAD AND STEPMOM
FINALLY SHOWED UP.
THEY MUST BE DEVASTATED
BY HER DISAPPEARANCE.
I DON'T KNOW.
HE LOOKS KIND OF MAD TO ME.
SO, WHAT IS THIS, ANYWAY?
LOOKS PRETTY BORING TO ME.
ME TOO.
IS IT A GAME?
IT'S THE D-REAPER'S
ORIGINAL FORM.
YOU'VE GOTTA BE KIDDING.
THTHING USED TO BE
THATTHING?
IT EVOLVED LIKE THE DIGIMON --
PROBABLY EVEN LEARNED HOW
BY ASSIMILATING THEIR DATA.
DADDY, LISTEN! LISTEN!
I SAW CALUMON AND BEELZEMON
GO INTO THE NASTY WEB STUFF,
BUT I NEVER SAW THEM
COME OUT!
SOMEONE NEEDS TO GO GET THEM OUT
OF THERE NOW!
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE DON'T KNOW IF IT'S
YOUR FRIENDS,
BUT SOMEBODY IS IN THERE.
YOU'RE A SMART GIRL.
IT APPEARS THAT
THE CORE INFORMATION
IS CENTERED
IN THAT RED SPHERE.
WHY DON'T WE JUST CALL IT WHAT
IT IS -- THE D-REAPER'S BRAIN.
NOW, HOW DO WE GIVE IT
A LOBOTOMY?
AN APT METAPHOR, AS ALWAYS.
THANK YOU, CURLY.
BUT WE STILL NEED
A PRACTICAL SOLUTION.
WHAT WE REALLY NEED IS A SCALPEL
THE SIZE OF A BUS.
NO! YOU'LL HURT HER!
HUH?
WHAT IF JERI'S IN THERE?
YOU MIGHT HURT HER.
UNH.
AH.
WAIT.
HMM?
[ PANTING ]
PLEASE DON'T BE MAD AT HER.
IT'S NOT HER FAULT.
I REALLY MEAN IT.
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME.
[ BELL DINGS ]
MR. KATO, PLEASE.
JUST DON'T BE MAD AT HER.
OH, JERI.
WHY DID WE HAVE TO RUN
FROM THEM?
THIS ISN'T WORKING.
YOU DIDN'T GIVE IT A CHANCE.
NOW DO YOU GET IT?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
I'VE TRIED SO HARD TO BE
A GOOD MOTHER FOR JERI,
BUT NOTHING -- NOTHING I DO EVER
SEEMS TO BE RIGHT.
[ SIGHS ]
IT'S HARD TO BE
A STEPMOTHER.
IT'S HARD TO BE A MOTHER,
PERIOD.
IT'S LIKE...UH...OH...
BOY,
DO I HAVE A LOT TO LEARN.
HOW COULD I HAVE BEEN
SUCH A DORK?
JERI ALWAYS SEEMED
HAPPY ENOUGH.
SHE ACTUALLY
SEEMED TO ENJOY THINGS.
I MEAN, SHE SMILED
ALL THE TIME.
ALL I EVER THOUGHT ABOUT WAS ME
AND MY STUPID PROBLEMS.
I NEVER EVEN THOUGHT ABOUT WHAT
HER LIFE WAS REALLY LIKE.
SHE LOST HER MOM,
THEN HER PARTNER.
I MEAN -- OKAY, FINE.
MY PARENTS ARE DIVORCED,
AND I DON'T GET TO SEE
MUCH OF MY DAD, BUT I COUL.
AT LEAST HE'S STILL ALIV.
POOR JERI.
[ SIGHS ] NO MORE
FEELING SORRY FOR MYSELF.
I GOT IT GOOD.
I DON'T THINK
SHE'LL EVER PLAY AGAIN.
STOP!
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?!
[ HORN HONKS ]
He almost ran us down.
I traced the plates
to a Mr. Matsuki.
SOME RAT FINK
HAS STOLEN MY VAN.
I MUST HAVE LEFT THE KEYS
IN IT AGAIN.
MR. MATSUKI IS HERE WITH ME.
THANK YOU FOR INFORMING US.
SORRY, YAMAKI.
WHO COULD'VE TAKEN IT?
JERI. JERI!
[ GRUNTING ]
JERI!
JERI, COME ON,
DO YOU HEAR THAT?
SOMEONE WANTS YOU.
[ SIGHS ]
HMM. WHAT HAVE I DONE?
[ MUFFLED ]
UNH!
I'M NOT VERY GOOD AT THI.
SHE GOT WHERE SHE IS
ON HER OWN,
SHE CAN JUST GET HOME
ON HER OWN!
TELL HER THAT!
GOODBYE!
WHY DON'T I JUST GO
PICK HER UP, OKAY?
SHE HAS TO LEARN TO TAKE
RESPONSIBILITY FOR HER ACTIONS.
OH. MM-HMM.
I'M DOING THIS
FOR HER OWN GOOD.
IF SHE DOESN'T SEE
THE CONSEQUENCES OF HER ACTIONS,
SHE'LL NEVER LEARN.
NOW I SEE THE CONSEQUENCS
OMYACTIONS.
Jeri: DESTINY.
DESTINY.
J-JERI?!
JERI!
DESTINY.
OH, JERI.
PEACHES.
MR. KATO?
IT'S HER!
IT HAS TO BE HER!
[ ALL GASP ]
WOW. UH...
As Jeri: DESTINY.
DESTINY.
THAT VOICE -- IT'S HERS!
HOW COULD IT BE?!
WHERE IS SHE?!
JERI!
IT'S NOT HER.
THE D-REAPER HAS STOLEN HER
VOICE AND HIDDEN HER SOMEWHERE.
[ GROWLS ]
DESTINY.
STOP IT!
STOP USING HER VOICE!
NO, WAIT!
[ ALL GASP ]
AH!
INITIATING MEMORY SCAN.
SUBJECT -- JERI KATO.
[ NO AUDIO ]
SCAN COMPLETED.
TADASHI KATO --
ORGANIC LIFE-FORM.
SPECIES, HUMAN.
FATHER OF...FATHER?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH IT?
IT DOESN'T
UNDERSTAND THE WORD.
THE D-REAPER AND WE DIGIMON
DON'T HAVE PARENTS.
IT'S A NEW CONCEPT FOR IT.
CONCEPTUALIZE THIS!
INITIATING MEMORY SCAN.
SUBJECT -- TADASHI KATO.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE
IN BED BY NOW?
DON'T SPILL IT.
I'LL DO ANYTHING YOU WANT.
JUST GIVE HER BACK TO ME.
PLEASE GIVE ME BACK
MY LITTLE GIRL.
TAKE ME INSTEAD.
TAKE ME. PLEASE!
MEMORY SCAN INTERRUPTED.
HUH?
CONFLICT ENCOUNTERED.
ATTEMPT RESOLUTION
OF THE INCONSISTENCIES.
ATTEMPT FAILED.
FAILED. F-FAILED.
F-FAILED.
[ Echoing ] FAILED.
OF COURSE YOU FAILED,
YOU STUPID THING.
HOW COULD YOU POSSIBLY
UNDERSTAND HUMAN EMOTIONS?
F-FAILED.
NO! WAIT!
GIVE ME BACK MY DAUGHTER!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
AAAH! GET --
RENAMON?
LET'S DO IT.
BIOMERGE ACTIVATE!
RENAMON BIOMERGE TO...
♪ DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI
♪ DI, DI, DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI, DI, DIGI
♪ DI, DI
♪ DI, DIGIMON
SAKUYAMON! SAKUYAMON!
AAAAH!
JERI, LOOK.
IS THAT YOUR DAD?
HUH? MY DADDY?
[ WHIMPERING ]
DADDY'S HERE?
LATENT-MEMORY SCAN
ACTIVATED.
SUBJECT -- JERI KATO.
INITIATING MEMORY SCAN.
STOP IT!
GET OUT OF JERI'S HEAD
AND QUIT MESSING
WITH HER FEELINGS!
BIOMERGE ACTIVATE!
♪ DI, DI
GUILMON BIOMERGE TO...
♪ DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI, DI
♪ DI, DI
GALLANTMON! GALLANTMON!
LIGHTNING JOUST!
Takato: ALL RIGHT!
Guilmon: IT WORKED!
OH, NO!
GUESS NOT.
WHY WOULD THE D-REAPER CARE
ABOUT THE RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN KIDS
AND THEIR PARENTS?
WHY NOT JUST DELETE IT
ALONG WITH EVERYTHING ELSE?
Mizuno: IT'S SCARED
OUT OF ITS DIGITAL MIND.
IN THAT ONE WAY,
IT'S JUST LIKE US.
IT, TOO, HAS A FEAR
OF THE UNKNOWN.
THE UNKNOWN.
OF COURSE!
MR. MIZUNO, NOT TRYING TO BE
RUDE OR ANYTHING,
BUT AREN'T YOU DONE
WITH THAT YET?
[ BEEPING ]
MOMENTI.
THAT'S A REALLY
IRRITATING THING TO SAY.
JUSTICE KICK!
JUSTIMON, YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
ENOUGH CHITCHAT.
RIGHT! RIGHT!
AAAH!
AH! AH!
Calumon:
JERI, YOUR FRIENDS ARE HERE!
WE'RE IN HERE!
WE'RE IN HERE,
AND WE'RE REALLY LONELY!
LONELY.
[ GASPS ] JERI?
LONELY IS MY DESTINY.
DESTINY.
NO! WE CAN CHOOSE
OUR OWN DESTINY!
AAAH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
STOP!!
TAKE THAT, YOU MONSTER!
NO!
[ GROWLS ]
[ INDISTINCT ]
[ WHISTLING ]
MOLTEN BLADE!
YAH!
Guilmon: THAT WAS FUN.
NOW WHAT?
AAAH!
I DON'T THINK THAT WAS
SUCH A GOOD IDEA, TAKATO.
YEAH, NO KIDDING.
GUARDROMON!
OF COURSE, KAZU!
HA-HA!
AAAH!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU DON'T LOOK SO GOOD.
WHY ARE ALL THE BUILDINGS
SPINNING?
AH, NUTS.
WE NEED TO DESTROY THE BIG ONE,
OR WE'RE TOAST.
Guilmon: WELL, IT'S NOT GETTING
ANY SMALLER.
LET'S GO!
AAAH! AAAH!
WE NEED A NEW PLAN.
[ ALL GASP ]
GRANI'S ALIVE.
I THINK
IT'S TRYING TO EMERGE.
[ BEEPING ]
THEN WHY DON'T WE
MAKE IT SO?
ALL RIGHT, HOW?
THE USUAL WAY, OF COURSE --
WITH A BLUE CARD.
DIGIMODIFY!
HUH!
ISN'T THAT
A BEAUTIFUL SIGHT?
HERE HE COMES.
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
A DIGITAL FIELD HAS APPEARED
IN THE SKY OVER SHINJUKU PARK.
EMERGENCE IS IMMINENT.
GRANI IS
COMING OUT TO PLAY.
SHOWTIME!
BUT WHY ISN'T IT
GOING ANYWHERE?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
DID WE FORGET SOMETHING?
Takato:
WE'VE GOTTA GET UP THERE.
HIGHER, GUILMON!
SORRY, TAKATO.
IT'S JUST TOO BIG.
IT'S OKAY, GUILMON.
WE'LL FIGURE SOMETHING OUT.
WOW!
ALL RIGHT, GRANI!
FORWARD INTO BATTLE,
BOYS AND GIRLS!
NOW THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
I WANT ONE.
HUH?
OF COURSE -- EVERY KNIGHT
NEEDS A LOYAL STEED
TO RIDE INTO BATTLE.
WE NAMED YOU WELL -- GRANI --
AFTER SIEGFRIED'S HORSE.
LIGHTNING JOUST!
YEAH!
HEY, WATCH IT!
Guilmon: JUST IN TIME.
THANK YOU.
GUILMON, YOU KNOW
WHAT OR WHO THIS IS?
OF COURSE.
IT'S THE ARK, SILLY.
HUH?
NOW THAT'S UNEXPECTED.
JERI!
T-TAKATO?
OH, JERI.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO WORRY.
I'LL GET YOU OUT OF THERE
IF IT'S THE LAST THING I DO!
WHOA! THAT GRANI'S
ONE SWEET RIDE.
NOW WE'RE GETTING SOMEWHER.
KEEP WATCHING
"DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS"