JERI DECIDED TO ASK HOW TO PLAY
THE DIGIMON CARD GAME,
BUT WHO COULD BE A BETTER
TEACHER THAN THE DIGIMON QUEEN?
HENRY SHOWED THE GANG THE
SYMBOLS OF THE CHINESE ZODIAC
AND SAID THAT THEY WERE THE
SAME ANIMALS AS THE DEVAS.
LOOKS LIKE THEY STILL HAVE FIVE
MORE TO FACE.
THAT CREEPY KID APPEARED
AND LED EVERYONE ON A CHASE
THROUGH THE CITY,
BUT THEN THE GIANT PIG DEV,
VIKARALAMON, BIOEMERGED
AND STARTED DESTROYING
EVERYTHING IN HIS PATH.
THE TAMERS WORKED HARD FOR TE
STRENGTH TO PROTECT THE CIY
AND THEIR DIGIMON MATRIX
DIGIVOLVED.
TOO BAD YAMAKI IS PLAYING WIH
HIS JUGGERNAUT AGAIN.
♪ DI, DI, DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI, DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI, DI, DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE WORLD
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS.
DIGIMODIFY.
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON!
JUGGERNAUT POWER AT 95%...
100%.
ENGAGE PROGRAM.
[ SNARLING ]
[ GROWLS ]
HOLD IT, HOG BREATH!
EW! WHAT'S THAT SMELL?
HE'S A PIG!
WHAT DO YOU EXPECT?
THIS IS DEFINITELY
NOT KOSHER.
A GIANT ANIMAL HAS NOW MADE
ITS WAY TO MAJI STREET.
AN EMERGENCY EVACUATION ORDER
HAS BEEN ISSUED
FOR ALL RESIDENTS OF THE
SHINJUKU DISTRICT.
PLEASE LEAVE THE AREA
IMMEDIATELY.
[ SIRENS WAILING ]
EVERYBODY REMAIN CALM!
THERE'S NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT!
WE HAVE EVERYTHING UNDER
CONTROL!
THIS STUPID PHONE'S
NOT WORKING,
AND I CAN'T FIND TAKATO.
I'M NOT LEAVING WITHOUT HIM.
WITH ALL
THE POLICE BARRICADES,
HE MAY NOT BE ABLE
TO GET BACK HERE.
WE'LL HAVE A BETTER CHANCE OF
FINDING HIM ON THE STREET.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE!
EXCUSE ME, MA'AM.
YOU'VE GOT FIVE MINUTES
TO LEAVE.
BUT
MY SON NEVER CAME HOME.
WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE
WITHOUT HIM.
IN A FEW MINUTES, YOUR HOME
MIGHT NOT BE HERE.
I SUGGEST YOU COOPERATE.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS IS
HAPPENING!
WELL, ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
WE WERE THINKING ABOUT
REDECORATING.
[ GROANS ]
RAPIDMON!
RAPID FIRE!
YAH! YAH!
BAD MOVE, BUGGY!
BOAR BOMB!
UH-OH! AAH!
P.U.!
NOT ONLY AM I STUCK,
BUT NOW I STINK, TOO!
YOU'RE MINE, INSECT!
[ SQUEALS ]
TALISMAN OF LIGHT!
WOW, YOU GIVE ART APPRECIATION
A WHOLE NEW MEANING!
IT'LL TAKE MORE THAN MY BRUSH TO
BEAT THIS DEVA.
CAN YOU PAINT HIM
A NEW FACE?
I HEARD THAT!
YOU SHALL ALL PAY DEARLY!
SORRY,
BUT WE DON'T CARRY CASH!
BOAR BOMB!
HE'S ERUPTING!
GET AWAY FROM HIM!
UH-OH! HE SPRUNG A LEAK!
WHAAAAAA!
BLASTER BLADE!
AW, NUTS!
HOLD ON, BUDDY!
I'M COMING!
DON'T QUIT, WARGROWLMON!
COME ON,
YOU GOTTA GET UP NOW!
I CAN'T!
[ GROANS ]
[ GROWLING ]
BOAR BOMB!
AAH!
TIME TO OPEN THE GATE!
[ LAUGHS ]
[ GROWLING ]
COMMANDER,
I CAN'T GET ANY CLOSER!
ACKNOWLEDGED.
HOLD YOUR POSITION.
YES, SIR.
AWAITING YOUR COMMAND.
AW, NOW WHAT?
LOOKS LIKE YOUR PAL YAMAKI'S
RIPPED OPEN THE SKY AGAIN.
LIKE THIS DAY
WASN'T BAD ENOUGH.
AND ABOUT TO GET WORSE.
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
STATUS?
JUGGERNAUT HAS REACHED NETWORK
CONTROL LEVEL 4, SIR.
I HOPE WE'RE NOT MAKING A
MISTAKE HERE.
AMAZING THAT YOU AND YOUR
FRIENDS
ARE ACTUALLY RESPONSIBLE FOR
CREATING SUCH A FOUL MENACE.
OBSERVE.
[ GASPS ]
THIS HIDEOUS SWINE IS YOUR
LATEST ABOMINATION.
I NEVER DESIGNED THAT!
WARGROWLMON?
I THINK I'M DONE.
CAN SOMEBODY
TURN THIS THING OFF?
HOW AM I
SUPPOSED TO HELP HIM?
[ GROWLING ]
WHAT CAN WE DO?
WE DON'T HAVE
ANY DECENT CARDS LEFT.
MAYBE IT DOESN'T MATTER WHAT
CARD WE USE, RIKA.
HUH? OKAY, DID THAT PIG MONSTER
EAT YOUR BRAIN?
NO, I'M SERIOUS.
THE ONLY TIME THE CARDS HAVE
BEEN HELPFUL TO OUR DIGIMON
IS WHEN
WE'VE BELIEVED IN THEM.
ALL WE HAVE TO DO IS JUST
BELIEVE IN OURSELVES THIS TIME!
OKAY.
IT'S WORTH A TRY.
DIGIMODIFY.
DIGIMODIFY!Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â DIGIMODIFY!
ACTIVATE!Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â ACTIVATE!
YES.
THE TIME HAS COME
TO ERASE YOUR MISTAKE.
HENRY!
THAT'S MY SON OUT THERE!
WELL, IT'S ABOUT TIME!
YES!
TALISMAN STAR!
NO!
YOUR TURN, RAPIDMON!
OKAY. I HAVE A SNACK FOR YOU,
BACON BUTT!
RAPID FIRE!
OHH!
OOOOOOOOOOHH!
WE'VE GOT HIM NOW, GUYS!
SHOULD I SEND HIM
TO HOG HEAVEN?
HUH? WHOA!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?!
MY STRENGTH'S DRAINING!
ALL RIGHT,
WHO UPSET THE SKY?
TALISMAN SPELL!
RAPIDMON, COME HERE!
OKAY.
THESE SHOULD PROTECT US.
SOMETHING BAD'S HAPPENING
UP THERE.
AND OUR PROBLEM'S JUST
BEGINNING.
[ BEEPING ]
JUGGERNAUT HAS REACHED LEVEL 5.
HOLDING STEADY AT FULL POWER.
HA HA HA HA HA! FULL POWER.
I LOVE TO HEAR THAT.
WATCH CAREFULLY.
THE WORLD IS ABOUT TO CHANGE
FOREVER.
HMPH!
I'VE SEEN ENOUGH.
FACE IT, THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN
DO TO STOP THIS.
I'M SORRY, SIR, BUT YOU'RE NOT
ALLOWED TO LEAVE THIS ROOM!
I HATE TO DO THIS,
BUT MY SON NEEDS ME!
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
YOU CAN'T --
HEY!
HENRY!
HELLO? EARTH TO TAKATO.
WOULD YOU WAKE UP?!
OH, GUILMON.
WE CAN STILL HELP HIM!
I'M SO AFRAID OF LOSING HIM.
WHAT'S THIS ABOUT?
WHEN GUILMON DIGIVOLVES, A PART
OF HIM SEEMS TO DISAPPEAR.
SOMETIMES
I DON'T EVEN RECOGNIZE HIM.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW SERIOUS
THINGS HAVE BECOME.
I'M GLAD THAT HE'S POWERFUL,
BUT I'M AFRAID OF LOSING OUR
FRIENDSHIP.
YOU'RE NOT LOSING ANYTHING,
GOGGLE HEAD.
EVERYONE HAS TO GROW UP.
IT'S NATURAL.
TAOMON COULD BE THE MOST
POWERFUL DIGIMON EVER,
BUT SHE'S STILL
MY BEST FRIEND.
REALLY?
BESIDES, HE'S STILL JUST A
BREAD-SNARFING DOOFUS
ON THE INSIDE.
WELL, THAT'S TRUE.
[ GROANING ]
UH-OH. LOOKS LIKE OUR YIN'S
GETTING YANKED.
MY PROTECTION SPELL'S
BEING DELETED!
AND WE'RE NEXT!
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING!
LEAVE ME ALONE!
YOUR GAME IS BAD!
NO, I CAN'T GO BACK!
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
CALUMON?
HEARING VOICES
IS A BAD SIGN.
WHO'S HE TALKING TO?
I DON'T WANT TO GO!
PLEASE DON'T LET THEM TAKE ME!
HENRY, A LITTLE HELP?!
HOW CAN I HELP THEM WHEN EVEN
THAT GIANT PIG VIKARALAMON
IS ABOUT TO BE DELETED?
THINK, HENRY!
HENRY!
HUH?
DAD!
I NEED...HELP.
JUGGERNAUT
IS ENTERING ITS FINAL PHASE.
IN A FEW MINUTES,
DIGIMON WILL BE HISTORY.
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING?!
HARD TO SAY, SIR.
IT'S A REVERSE PULSE CODE THAT'S
OVERRIDING JUGGERNAUT
FROM A LAYER OF DATA SOMEWHERE
DEEP IN THE NET.
IT'S THAT ANCIENT MACHINE
LANGUAGE AGAIN.
REVERSE ASSEMBLE!
IT'S DECODING.
[ GASPING ]
WHAT DOYOUWANT?
MM.
[ GASPS ]
AS SIMPLE AND PATHETIC
AS YOU ARE,
YOU HUMANS CREATED US
AND THE WORLD WE LIVE IN.
YOU POLLUTED YOUR WORLD AND THEN
STARTED MESSING WITH OURS.
WE HAD TO EVOLVE AND ADAPT JUST
TO SURVIVE.
YOU STILL HAVEN'T SAID
WHAT YOU WANT.
THE ONLY WAY TO PROTECT OUR
WORLD
IS TO DESTROY ANYONE WHO
THREATENS IT.
BUT WE NEED TO BECOME STRONGER,
AND YOU IGNORANT CHILDREN
CAN HELP US.
YOU HOLD THE KEY, AND YOU DON'T
EVEN KNOW IT.
AT THIS POINT,
WE REALLY DON'T CARE
IF YOU HUMANS WANT TO WIPE
YOURSELVES OUT.
WE'VE GOT PLANS, MY FOUL
FRIENDS,
AND YOU'RE IN THE WAY!
AND THAT'S A PROBLEM.
SHUT HIM DOWN!
WHAT'S WRONG?
FEELING SORRY FOR YOURSELF?
WHAT NOW?
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE, WILL YA?
YOU CRAVE POWER, DON'T YOU?
YEAH, SO WHAT?
I CRAVE CHEESEBURGERS, TOO.
YOU HAVE THE ABILITY TO
DIGIVOLVE.
WE ALL DO.
I CAN HELP YOU.
HE'S GOTTA BE LYING.
[ CHUCKLING ]
[ HUMMING ]
GO AWAY!
MMMM,
WELL, GIVE ME WHAT I WANT!
I CAN'T GO BACK THERE!
PLEASE DON'T LET THEM TAKE ME,
JERI!
I'M SCARED!
PLEASE! PLEASE! PLEASE! NO!
PLEASE GO AWAY!
DUDE,
YOU CAN'T HAVE CALUMON!
HOW ABOUT KENTA?
HEY!
[ GASPING ]
I AM MAKUNOMON.
MAYBE HE WANTS A BANANA.
ANYBODY GOT ONE?
MAC-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-W!!
WHOA!
HE COMES HERE TO PLAY WITH
HIS FRIENDS ALL THE TIME.
HUH?
NOW,THAT'S
A GOOD HIDING PLACE.
THESE ARE FROM OUR BAKERY.
HMM.
LOOKS LIKE HE INHERITEDYOUR
APPETITE.
WE NEED A NEW PLAN HERE.
NO, WE NEED A MIRACLE!
TAOMON AND RAPIDMON ARE IN
TROUBLE!
IF WE DON'T DO SOMETHING,
THEY'LL BE DELETED!
JUGGERNAUT'S AT FULL POWER.
I'M AFRAID THERE IS NOTHING
WE CAN DO NOW.
WHAT ABOUT GUILMON?
HUH? LOOK UP THERE!
UGH!
[ INDISTINCT SHOUTING ]
WHAT'S HAPPENING
TO MY SYSTEM?
COMPLETE FAILURE.
WE HAVE TO EVACUATE.
WE'RE NOT LEAVING.
UGH! AAH!
I KNEW SOMETHING LIKE THIS
WOULD HAPPEN.
THE JUGGERNAUT DATA STREAM IS
IMPLODING.
THE ENTIRE PLACE COULD GO UP
LIKE A BOMB!
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOMETHING
YOU CAN DO.
SHUT IT DOWN
AND START IT UP AGAIN!
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE
AT THIS POINT.
THE ENTIRE PROGRAM'S BEEN
CORRUPTED!
IT'S OVER, SIR.
GET OUT WHILE THERE'S STILL
TIME.
HOLD IT!
ARE YOU ABANDONING
YOUR DUTY?
NO, SIR.
I'VE JUST DECIDED MY LIFE IS
MORE VALUABLE THAN YOUR CAUSE.
IT SEEMS THAT ARTIFICIAL
INTELLIGENCE
HAS BECOME TOO SMART FOR ITS OWN
GOOD.
GOODBYE, SIR.
RILEY, GO ON.
GET OUT OF HERE.
GOOD LUCK.
[ GRUNTS ]
I'M BACK, HUMAN FILTH!
STILL WANNA PLAY?
[ GASPING ]
WE'VE GOTTA FIND A SAFER PLACE.
COME ON! LET'S GO!
BUT TAOMON --
SHE'LL BE ALL RIGHT, RIKA.
COME ON!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED,
BUT I'M READY TO FIGHT AGAIN,
AND SO IS THE PIG!
[ GRUNTING ]
FIRE!
FUSION BALL!
WHOA!
KEEP RUNNING!
TAKATO!
GUYS, WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
WE WERE
WITH THAT CREEPY KID.
HE'S REALLY
ONE OF THE DEVA DIGIMON!
HUH?
YEAH, AND HE SAID
SOME PRETTY WEIRD STUFF.
FIRE!
OHH!
WE'RE ALL IN DANGER
IF WE STAY HERE.
COME WITH ME.
WE HAVE TO HIDE.
NO.
WHAT?
I'M DONE HIDING.
YOU WERE RIGHT.
NO MATTER HOW POWERFUL OUR
DIGIMON BECOME,
THEY'RE STILL OUR FRIENDS.
MM-HMM.
AND RIGHT NOW, OUR FRIENDS
NEED US MORE THAN EVER.
UH-HUH.
OKAY. THEN IT'S TIME
WE COME TOGETHER
AND USE
OUR COMBINED STRENGTH!
LET'S DO IT.
MA-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A!
MA-A-A-A-A-A-A-A!
WHAT'S HE DOING?
AAAAAAAAH!
RAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ PANTING ]
MA-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A-A!
[ GROWLS ]
RAAAH!
FUSION BALL!
AAAAAAAH!
AAAH!
[ SNARLING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
AAH!
AAAAAAAH!Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â Â AAAAAAAH!
WHAT'S ALL THE YELLING
ABOUT?!
I HEAR YOU, TAKATOMON.
I FEEL YOUR STRENGTH.
TOGETHER WE CAN SEND THIS PORKER
BACK WHERE HE BELONGS!
[ CRASHING, GRUNTING ]
STOP NOW WHILE
YOU STILL HAVE A CHOICE!
NO WAY!
AS LONG AS TAKATO IS WITH ME,
I'LL NEVER GIVE UP!
[ BOTH GRUNTING ]
RAISE YOUR SNOUT
AND SAY "AHH!"
READY, RAPIDMON?
I'M WITH YOU!
YEE-HAW -- TARGET PRACTICE!
I'LL BLAST THESE HOT HOGGIE
HAIRBALLS OUT OF THE SKY!
TAOMON? YOU'RE UP!
TALISMAN OF LIGHT!
ALL RIGHT!
[ GRUNTING ]
AAAAAAAAH!
ROLL OVER!
OOH! UGH!
ATOMIC...THRUSTERS!
[ SQUEALING ]
WHEW.
THAT WAS
ONE MEAN SAUSAGE MACHINE.
OH, BOY.
LOOKS LIKE THIS HAS NOW BECOME
A WAR BETWEEN THE WORLDS.
WELL...THAT WAS A SCREAM.
[ LAUGHS, GROANS ]
TAKATO!
HMM?
[ GIGGLING ]
HUH? CALUMON!
OH!
YOU WOULDN'T GIVE ME
WHAT I CAME FOR,
SO I HAVE TO TAKE IT.
THIS CREATURE DOESN'T BELONG
HERE,
AND IT'S MY DUTY
TO ESCORT HIM HOME.
GIVE HIM BACK,
MONKEY BOY!
CALUMON IS OUR FRIEND,
NOT JUST SOME PIECE OF PROPERTY!
YAH!
CALUMON!
OH-HO-HO!
IT'S LEOMON!
YOU ODIOUS, IGNORANT APE!
YOU'RE THE ONE THAT DOESN'T
BELONG!
AAH!
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
HEY, GET BACK!
UGH!
LEOMON!
HUH?
UGH!
MY OWN DIGIVICE!
IS IT REAL?
MM-HMM.
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
OUR ENTIRE TOWN HAS BEEN
DESTROYED.
WITH CALUMON'S POWERS,
THE DEVAS WILL WIPE OUT THE REST
OF THE WORLD!
WE'VE GOT TO HELP HIM.
BUT HOW?
WE'VE GOTTA GO.
HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD --
WE HAVE TO GO TO THE DIGITAL
WORLD.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY TO SAVE
HIM!
UH, OKAY, AND HOW
DO YOU SUGGEST WE DO THAT?
SAME WAY WE DO EVERYTHING --
WE WING IT.
YEAH, WE'LL COME UP WITH
SOMETHING.
WE HAVE TO.
COME ON, BOYS.
LET'S GO.
I'M WITH YA!
WAIT FOR ME!
[ SIRENS WAILING ]
IT'S OVER.
WHOA! IS THIS THE END
OF HYPNOS?
AND HOW ARE TAKATO AND THE GANG
GONNA GET TO THE DIGITAL WORLD?
CHECK IT OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS"