TAKATO AND HENRY DECIDED TO TAKE
GUILMON AND TERRIERMON
ON THEIR SCHOOL CAMPING TRIP.
I GUESS CALUMON NEEDED
A VACATION, TOO,
'CAUSE HE WENT WITH THEM.
THEY WERE ALL HAVING
THE TIME OF THEIR LIVES.
EVEN IMPMON COULDN'T RESIST
JOINING IN ON THE FUN.
BUT THEN THIS HYPNOTIZED OWL
TOLD THEM ABOUT
THE COMING OF ZENDERAMON,
A RIGHT BIG CHICKEN WHO EATS
ELECTRICITY TO EXPAND HIMSELF.
AFTER TURNING OUT THE LIGHTS
IN TOKYO,
ZENDERAMON WENT TO THE
HYDROELECTRIC POWER PLANT
TO JUICE UP EVEN MORE.
BUT GROWLMON AND GARGOMON,
AFTER ALMOST GETTING
DEEP FRIED THEMSELVES,
FINALLY THREW
THE OVERGROWN CHICKEN
RIGHT INTO THE FRYING PAN.
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
♪ WORLD
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMODIFY
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
IT'S THREE
FOR THE PRICE OF TWO.
I DON'T EVEN WANT ONE.
AND 7 COMPLETES
MY COLLECTION.
[ Thinking ] MY LUCKY NUMBER
FINALLY PAID OFF.
UHH!
AH! HEY, THANKS A LOT.
WHOA.
WHERE DID THAT COME FROM?
BUT THAT'S NUMBER 8.
I CAN'T HAVE 8.
I HAVE TO GET RID
OF THIS THING.
IT'S PRETTY
WEIRD LOOKING.
HEY, JEREMY, ISN'T THAT
YOUR FAMILY PORTRAIT?
VERY FUNNY.
IT'S PROBABLY A FAKE.
GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
WANT IT BACK?
NAH, KEEP IT.
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU TAKE IT.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
SEE YOU LATER, HENRY.
FINE.
DON'T SAY THANK YOU.
WHAT'S WRONG WITH HIM?
I DON'T KNOW, BUT THAT
STUPID CARD WON'T HELP HIM.
THAT WAS PRETTY RUDE,
WASN'T IT?
YEAH, BUT A CARD'S A CARD.
GIVE IT A SWIPE.
OKAY.
WOW!
TOLD YOU SO, HENRY.
YOU SEE, YOU SEE?
YOU SHOULD LISTEN
TO ME MORE OFTEN.
I DON'T KNOW.
THIS IS WEIRD.
I'M HOME.
DADDY!
AM I PRETTY?
PRETTY AS A PRINCESS.
OHH.
MOMMY, DADDY SAID
I'M PRETTY AS A PRINCESS.
LET ME FIX YOUR CROWN,
YOUR MAJESTY.
HONEY?
YEAH?
UM, BY ANY CHANCE,
DID ANYONE FROM WORK
CALL HERE TODAY?
NO. WHY?
NO REASON.
HEY, DAD, COULD YOU
HELP ME WITH SOMETHING?
UH, SURE.
GREAT.
OKAY, LET ME PLUG IN
MY READER HERE.
MM-HMM.
WHAT IS THAT THING?
IT'S A KIND OF
A HIGH-TECH SCANNER.
WELL, LET'S SOLVE
YOUR MYSTERY.
THE EQUIPMENT'S ALL FIRED UP
AND READY TO GO.
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT.
HERE IT IS.
HMM.
OKAY.
SPEAK TO ME,
O MYSTERIOUS ONE.
WHAT DO THOSE NUMBERS MEAN?
NOT SURE YET.
[ GASPS ]
WHAT?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I THOUGHT
I SAW SOMETHING,
BUT IT'S JUST A BUNCH
OF MEANINGLESS DATA, THAT'S ALL.
ARE YOU SURE?
POSITIVE.
SO TELL ME,
WHERE DID YOU GET THIS CARD?
ONE OF MY FRIENDS
GAVE IT TO ME. WHY?
OH, NO REASON.
[ BEEPING ]
COME ON, KENTA, THINK.
WHO DID JEREMY
GET THE CARD FROM?
WE JUST TRADED CARDS.
I NEVER ASKED.
YEAH, HE WORE NUMBER 7.
I MET HIM ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF TOWN, THAT WAY.
AND THE YOUNG DETECTIVES SET OFF
ON THEIR PERILOUS JOURNEY
IN HOPES OF FINDING ANSWERS
TO THE GREAT BLUE CARD
MYSTERY.
THIS ISN'T A GAME.
SO HE ALWAYS HANGS OUT
BY THE BIG STEPS, HUH?
MM-HMM.
[ Thinking ] THIS IS GREAT.
[ Thinking ]
THIS IS STUPID.
ACTUALLY, I FOUND THAT CARD
IN AKIHABARA.
HUH? WHERE
IN AKIHABARA?
BY THE ELECTRONICS.
UM, WHY?
THANKS A LOT.
WAIT. WHAT'S SO IMPORTANT
ABOUT THAT CARD?
I WASN'T EVEN SURE
IF IT WAS A REAL ONE.
I WAS THINKING
THE SAME THING
UNTIL I HAD IT CHECKED OUT.
IT'S ACTUALLY VERY RARE.
MAN, I KNEW IT.
YOU'RE HIDING SOMETHING.
SPILL IT.
UH, WELL, I DIDN'T THINK
IT WAS IMPORTANT,
BUT THE WAY I FOUND THE CARD
WAS KIND OF WEIRD.
THIS MAN BUMPED INTO ME,
AND THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN
IT WAS THERE.
WHAT DID HE LOOK LIKE?
WAS HE SKINNY, FAT,
SHORT, TALL,
OR SOMETHING IN BETWEEN?
I REMEMBER ONE THING
ABOUT HIM.
HE WAS WEARING
A YELLOW JACKET.
[ TYPING ]
IT WAS ALL SO SIMPLE
BACK THEN,
EXCITING AND FUN.
HAPPY TIMES.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT'S COME TO THIS.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO?
I NEED TO FIND ONE
OF YOUR OLD PLAYMATES
WHO REFUSES TO GROW UP.
WE HAVE REASONS TO BELIEVE
THAT HE MAY STILL
BE WORKING ON THE PROJECT
TO THIS VERY DAY.
I JUST COULDN'T UNDERSTAND
WHY THEY HAD TO
SHUT DOWN THE PROJECT.
WE HAD COME SO FAR.
I THOUGHT I'D NEVER
SEE THEM AGAIN.
BUT THEN THIS STRANGE CARD
APPEARS,
BROUGHT TO ME
BY MY OWN SON.
THERE'S NO WAY I CAN TELL HIM
WHAT THOSE CODES REALLY MEANT.
I STILL DON'T UNDERSTAND
THAT ONE MYSELF.
HOW CAN I LIE
TO MY OWN SON?
WHAT AM I
SUPPOSED TO TELL HIM?
AW, NUTS,
NOT AGAIN.
HEY, I'M SORRY, BOY,
BUT YOU KNOW THEY WON'T
LET ME TAKE YOU
ON THE TRAIN.
YOU'RE TOO BIG.
YOU'RE LUCKY, TERRIERMON.
I KNOW.
HEY!
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
OH, MY CELL PHONE.
I'D BETTER GO BACK FOR IT.
SO, WHERE'S THE LOSER PATROL
HEADED TODAY?
WHAT DO YOU WANT THIS TIME?
JEEZ, TAKE IT EASY THERE,
HELICOPTER HEAD.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
BE INTERESTED
IN A LITTLE REMATCH.
WHY NOT? I COULD USE
A LITTLE EXERCISE.
WHAT DO YOU SAY, HENRY?
CAN I FIGHT HIM?
HELLO, EARTH TO HENRY.
HUH?
OHH!
UH...
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
YOU LITTLE
WING-EARED WIENIE?
I'M TALKING TO YOU HERE.
OR DO YOU HAVE TO ASK
TO DO THAT, TOO?
WHAT A DISGRACE
TO DIGIMON.
DID HE SAY DIGIMON?
WHA?
YOU ARE A DIGIMON,
AREN'T YOU?
BETTER GET BACK, JACK.
BADA-BOOM!
DAD!
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
YOU'RE ONLY A GAME.
I GOT YOUR GAME RIGHT HERE.
LET'S PLAY. HA HA!
DAD, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH.
YOU WANNA PLAY,
PLAY WITH ME.
YOU'RE PROTECTING HIM?
WHAT'S THE MATTER,
ONE MASTER NOT ENOUGH?
YOU HAVE TO HAVE TWO?
YEECH. ALL YOU HUMANS
ARE MAKING MY SKIN CRAWL.
I'LL DEAL WITH YOU LATER,
PEEWEE.
MR. WONG, YOU OKAY?
HENRY, WE NEED TO TALK.
NO, I CAN'T.
NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN,
MR. WONG.
HENRY! HEY!
THE YUGOTH
HAS BEEN ACTIVATED.
TRACKING.
IT'S USELESS.
IT'S COMING FROM THE
JUGGERNAUT CORE AGAIN.
OBVIOUSLY, EXCEPT THIS TIME
THERE ARE TWO OF THEM.
MOMENTIE, HENRY,
MOMENTIE.
RIKA, WHAT ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO SAY
AT A TIME LIKE THIS
TO HELP HIM?
MAYBE YOU SHOULD TRY
SOMETHING DIFFERENT, TAKATO,
LIKE KEEPING YOUR NOSE OUT
OF WHERE IT DOESN'T BELONG.
I HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
WOW, THIS LOOKS LIKE
A FUN PLACE TO PLAY.
IT'S A LITTLE LOUD, THOUGH.
OW!
THERE'S TOO MANY VOICES.
IT MAKES MY HEAD ALL SCRAMBLY.
PICK A CARD, ANY CARD.
I WONDER IF OUR MAN'S
GOING TO SHOW UP.
MAYBE HE'LL
INTRODUCE HIMSELF.
KEEP DREAMING, SHERLOCK.
IT COULD HAPPEN.
IT'S ON SPECIAL,
TODAY ONLY.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHAT'S THE MATTER
WITH THIS THING?
NO WONDER IT'S ON SALE.
[ PEOPLE MURMURING ]
THAT CAN'T BE GOOD
FOR BUSINESS.
UH-OH!
THEY'RE BIO-EMERGING.
[ GROWLS ]
WHO ORDERED THE STEAK?
TERRIERMON, GET HIM.
[ LAUGHS ]
TIME TO WREAK
A LITTLE HOLY HAVOC.
BEAUTIFUL DAY
FOR A STAMPEDE.
I DON'T THINK TERRIERMON
CAN HANDLE THEM ALONE.
PAJIRAMON --
DEVA BEAST DIGIMON,
ULTIMATE LEVEL.
VAJRAMON --
SAME NASTY TYPE,
SAME NASTY LEVEL.
[ SCREAMING ]
IT BEGINS HERE.
I'M NEVER EATING
LAMB CHOPS AGAIN.
AND ENDS HERE.
WHAT'S THAT CRAZY BULL
DOING?
WHY ARE YOU EATING
MY STORE?
HMM?
NEVER MIND.
ENJOY YOUR MEAL.
[ ULULATING ]
WOW, AND I THOUGHT
MY SINGING WAS BAD.
I BET THAT THEY'RE UNSTABLE
SINCE THEY JUST BIO-EMERGED.
THEY'RE EATING ALL
THE DIGITAL EQUIPMENT.
THAT MUST BE WHAT THEY NEED
TO STABILIZE THEIR BODIES
BEFORE ATTACKING.
THEN WE'D BETTER CLEAR
THE TABLE
BEFORE THEY FINISH THEIR MEAL.
I'LL SEND THEM HOME.
WE'LL DO IT TOGETHER.
WHICH ONE DO YOU WANT?
I'LL TAKE THE GLUTTON
WITH THE HORNS.
DEAL. LET'S GO.
♪ DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMODIFY!
THOR'S HAMMER, ACTIVATE!
CRYSTAL FIRE, ACTIVATE.
YAAH!
TASTE THIS, BULL HEAD.
HEE-YAH!
HMM?
NO WAY.
MAYBE I DIDN'T MAKE MYSELF
CLEAR THE FIRST TIME.
SO YOU ARE THE PATHETIC
LITTLE DIGIMON
THAT ANSWERS TO HUMANS.
WHAT IS YOUR NAME, TRAITOR?
NONE OF YOUR BUSINESS!
HMM. AND YOU?
YOU WON'T REMEMBER IT ANYWAY
ONCE I LOAD YOUR DATA.
OOH.
LET HIM GO RIGHT NOW!
I'M AFRAID
I CAN'T DO THAT.
WE'RE WASTING TIME HERE.
OUR ORDERS WERE TO VANQUISH THEM
AND LOAD THEIR DATA,
OR HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN
OUR DUTIES?
I HAVE FORGOTTEN NOTHING.
AAH!
YOU SHOULD FEEL HONORED
TO BE ABSORBED BY ME,
LITTLE SLAVE.
NO! LOOK OUT!
TERRIERMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
GARGOMON!
YOU STILL HUNGRY?
I BROUGHT DESSERT.
AREN'T YOU GOING
TO DIGIVOLVE?
I'D HATE TO JUST TAKE YOUR DATA
WITHOUT SEEING THAT.
PIG.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
DIAMOND STORM!
OH, SURELY YOU CAN DO
BETTER THAN THAT.
DIAMOND STORM!
HA HA HA HA HA HA!
THIS IS GETTING TIRESOME.
VAJRAMON, STOP FOOLING AROUND.
WE HAVE TO DESTROY THEM.
HA HA HA HA HA.
SPEAK FOR YOURSELF.
THIS IS FUN.
HE'S TOYING WITH HER.
TAKE THIS.
IT JUST MIGHT GIVE
GARGOMON AN EDGE.
DIGIMODIFY!
HYPER SPEED ACTIVATE!
I KNOW HOW TO GET YOU,
YOU BIG WOOLY BULLY.
ENOUGH! THUNDER STOMP!
WHOA! HEY!
RELAX. STAY A WHILE.
DIAMOND STORM!
I CAN'T MOVE ANYTHING.
DON'T DO IT!
IT'S MY JOB.
IT'S NEVER TOO LATE
TO CHANGE YOUR CAREER.
HENRY, DO SOMETHING.
GARGOMON!
COOL IT, BEEFCAKE.
OOH, FEISTY.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
LET'S FIND OUT,
SHALL WE?
[ GROWLS ]
UH-OH!
LEAVE HIM ALONE!
THIS IS FOR SHOOTING AT ME,
YOU NASTY LITTLE RABBIT!
TRY THIS.
THAT LAST ONE
ALMOST KILLED HIM.
HEY, I'M JUST TRYING
TO HELP.
GOT ONE.
DIGIMODIFY.
ROCK ARMOR ACTIVATE!
WHOA!
THUNDER STOMP!
WHAT ABOUT THIS?
OKAY.
DIGIMODIFY.
PROGRAM CLAWS ACTIVATE.
GARGOMON!
NONE OF MY OTHER CARDS
EVEN LOOK USEFUL.
HOW ABOUT THE BLUE CARD?
WE HAVEN'T TRIED THAT.
THE BLUE CARD?
WE'VE GOT TO TRY.
BUT I CAN'T DO THAT. WE HAVE
NO IDEA WHAT WILL HAPPEN.
WELL,
WE'RE ABOUT TO LOSE HIM.
WELL, IT WAS FUN.
SAY GOODBYE.
HERE GOES NOTHING.
DIGIMODIFY.
MATRIX DIGIVOLUTION!
[ BEEPING ]
HUH?
WELL, IT SEEMED LIKE A REALLY
GREAT IDEA AT THE TIME.
[ GROANS ]
PATHETIC HUMANS.
PLEASE, DON'T DO IT!
OH!
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
AAH!
GARGOMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
RAPIDMON!
HE DISAPPEARED.
HE SHOOTS...
HE SCORES! HA HA!
THAT'S RAPIDMON, WARRIOR DIGIMON
ULTIMATE LEVEL.
HIS SPECIAL ATTACKS
ARE RAPID FIRE,
MIRACLE MISSILE,
AND TRI BEAM.
GLAD HE'S ON OUR SIDE!
STOP!
RIGHT HERE!
SORRY. HERE.
NO, THIS WAY.
[ GROWLS ]
WE'RE BACK IN THE GAME,
RAPIDMON!
PRETTY COOL, HUH?
LIKE THE NEW LOOK?
CHECK THIS OUT.
RAPID FIRE!
[ GRUNTING ]
LET'S SEE
HOW HE HANDLES THIS.
PAJIRAMON!
YOU FOUL INSECT.
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU CAN DO
WHEN I HAVE A HUMAN SHIELD.
WHICH ONE OF YOU
WOULD LIKE TO GO FIRST?
NOT AN OPTION,
YOU BIG SHREDDER!
TRI BEAM!
AAH!
WE DID IT!
YEAH!
MM-HMM.
YEAH.
THEY BOTH JUST DISAPPEARED.
NOT QUITE. I'M STILL GETTING
A READING ON ONE OF THEM.
DUE TO HEAVY FOG
AND MASSIVE ELECTRICAL OUTAGES
IN THE AKIHABARA DISTRICT
TODAY,
TRAIN SCHEDULES
ALL OVER THE CITY
WERE SEVERELY DISRUPTED.
I WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR SAVING ME.
I HAD TO.
YOU'RE HENRY'S DAD.
I'M SORRY I DIDN'T TELL YOU
ABOUT TERRIERMON BEFORE.
IT WAS REALLY HARD FOR ME
TO KEEP HIM A SECRET
ALL THIS TIME.
YOU ACTUALLY TOOK IT
A WHOLE LOT BETTER
THAN I THOUGHT YOU WOULD.
IT'S OKAY. I UNDERSTAND.
THERE'S SOMETHING I HAVEN'T
TOLD YOU, EITHER, HENRY,
AND IT'S TIME I DID.
REALLY?
YEAH. ABOUT 20 YEARS AGO,
MY FRIENDS AND I
GOT TOGETHER
TO DO SOME DESIGNING
ON A VOLUNTARY
COMPUTER PROJECT.
WE WERE JUST DOING IT
FOR FUN,
BUT WE ENDED UP CREATING
THE VERY FIRST DIGIMON.
THE PROJECT WAS CALLED
FOSSIOVITA,
PART OF THE A.L. MOVEMENT.
WE EXPERIMENTED IN CREATING
ARTIFICIAL LIFE FORMS
ON THE COMPUTER.
WE EVEN FIGURED OUT A WAY
TO INSTILL
A SURVIVAL INSTINCT-TYPE
MECHANISM
THAT FUNCTIONED JUST LIKE
IT DOES IN WILD ANIMALS.
NOBODY EVER EXPECTED
A BUNCH OF COLLEGE STUDENTS
TO HAVE
SUCH INCREDIBLE RESULTS.
WE WERE ACTUALLY ABLE
TO GIVE THE LITTLE CREATURES
INDIVIDUAL PERSONALITIES
AND FIGHTING ABILITIES.
BUT, UNFORTUNATELY,
WE NEVER EVEN GOT TO SEE
THE FINAL VERSION OF THEM.
JUST AS OUR BIGGEST
BREAKTHROUGHS HAPPENED,
THE SPONSORS CUT THE FUNDING,
AND THE PROJECT DRIED UP.
SO ALL THE DIGIMON GAMES THAT
YOU AND YOUR FRIENDS PLAY WITH
WERE BASED
ON A RESEARCH PROJECT
THAT WAS NEVER COMPLETED
AND THAT WE NEVER
EVEN GOT CREDIT FOR.
WELL, THAT REALLY STINKS.
OH, WELL, THAT WAS
A LONG TIME AGO.
AT LEAST THE RESEARCH
WASN'T WASTED.
KIDS ALL OVER THE WORLD
HAVE GOT SOMETHING COOL
TO PLAY WITH.
I DO HAVE A QUESTION
FOR YOU, TERRIERMON.
HUH?
IT'S OKAY.
ABOUT THAT BLUE CARD --
WHEN I WAS ANALYZING IT,
I NOTICED THAT SHIBUMI'S CODE
APPEARED IN THE DATA.
ANY IDEA WHO MIGHT HAVE
DONE THAT?
HEY, YESTERDAY YOU SAID
IT WAS JUST MEANINGLESS DATA.
YOU'RE STILL ALIVE.
MMM...
YOU.
I UNDERSTAND.
WAIT. WHAT'S HAPPENING?
RENAMON,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
HE WANTS TO TALK.
THAT'S CORRECT.
SHE CAN TALK ABOUT
WHATEVER IT IS HERE.
SILENCE,
YOU IGNORANT HUMAN!
SHE'S NOT GOING.
I NEED YOU TO LET ME
DO THIS, RIKA.
HOW CAN YOU POSSIBLY
TRUST HIM?
RENAMON!
I HAVE QUESTIONS
THAT ONLY HE CAN ANSWER.
DON'T WORRY.
I WON'T BE LONG.
WHAT KIND OF QUESTIONS?
I'LL EXPLAIN EVERYTHING
WHEN I RETURN.
IT LOOKS LIKE I'M JUST GOING
TO HAVE TO TRUST RENAMON
THIS TIME.
TRUST? THAT WILL BE
SOMETHING NEW FOR RIKA.
AND WHAT'S UP WITH HENRY'S DAD
AND THAT SHIBUMI STUFF?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."