>> Ok so Kazu, Kenta and Jeri
all went looking for the tamers
who were strategizing in Guilmon's hideout
when they disappeared
Kazu and Kenta went
after them leaving Jeri alone with Calumon.
Somehow she got this wacky idea
that the happy little
dude might be her partner.
Then [inaudible] attack
when Guilmon showed
up and scared him away.
Well, it was love at first sight
for Jeri who thought for sure
that she was Leomon's tamer.
Guardromon and Leomon teamed
up to get rid of Converamon
but Leomon didn't stick around once the fight was won.
Poor Jeri I wonder if
she'll ever get a digimon.
[ Music ]
>> Takato: I'm home!
>> Mrs. Matsuki: Go
ahead have a free sample,
they're only two dollars.
>> Takato: Another
perfect crime.
Hm, hm, hm, hm.
And now to slink away unnoticed.
>> Mrs. Matsuki: Takato!
>> Takato: Uh!
>> Mrs. Matsuki:
What are you doing?
>> Takato: Um, nothing, Mom.
>> Mrs. Matsuki: Uh huh.
And would that nothing
include going
out without doing
your homework, again?
>> Takato: I'm just
going to the park.
>> Mrs. Matsuki: I'm
constantly amazed by how much
of your homework
revolves around the park.
>> Takato: But Mom-
>> Mrs. Matsuki: Don't
'but Mom' me, mister!
You're going to be in
college before you know it;
you need to study once and a
while, Takato, unless you plan
on getting a degree in
playing in the park.
>> Takato: Hm.
I'll be back later and
I'll do my homework then!
Sheesh! She must've gotten
her degree in nagging
with a minor in yelling.
[ Background sounds ]
Looks like another earthquake.
>> Suzie: Henry is it over?
>> Henry: I think so, yes.
>> Suzie: Next time,
make it be over sooner.
>> Anchorman: And now,
another exclusive channel one
earthquake report.
The recent earthquake was
measured at a magnitude of 4.0.
Seismologists are having trouble
pinpointing the epicenter citing
strange readings.
>> Henry: Uh!
Hmmm, I wonder if those strange
readings were caused by digimon
or if the earthquake was.
I'd better check this out.
>> Suzie: No.
>> Henry: Suzie, give him to me.
>> Suzie: No, Tewwiermon
will protect me.
>> Henry: I've got to
go out for a while,
you'll be fine without him.
>> Suzie: I want daddy.
>> Henry: He's at
work, now let go.
>> Suzie: Uh, uh!
>> Henry: Come on Suzie!
>> Suzie: I wish you
weren't my brother [crying].
>> Henry: I'm sorry
Suzie, I-I got to go.
>> Terriermon: You always say
I don't have any tact, Henry,
but I don't know if I've
ever been that mean.
So what's the matter, Henry?
>> Henry: Why?
>> Terriermon: Well, I know
you wouldn't act this way
if everything were fine.
>> Henry: Huh?
>> Terriermon: Jeez,
what's the matter now?
Huh? How many problems can
one guy have at the same time?
>> Henry: Look at that.
>> Terriermon: Okay, you have
a problem with that poster?
>> Hello Henry.
>> Henry: Hi, can I
borrow that chart?
>> I thought guys only liked
posters with girls in bikinis.
>> Henry: It just
reminded me of something.
What are you two doing?
>> Rika: We're going
shopping again.
>> Rika's Grandma:
All she owns is jeans.
>> Henry: Right.
Hey, I was going to go
meet Takato and the others
at the park; wanna
come with me, Rika?
>> Rika's Grandma:
I'll cover for you.
>> Rika: Thanks, Grandma.
>> Rika's Grandma: Hm?
Oh. Hello?
>> Rumiko: So?
>> Rika's Grandma: She
only wanted more jeans.
>> Rumiko: Put her on.
>> Rika's Grandma: Your Mom.
>> Rika: I don't like dresses.
>> Rumiko: How about some
post-shopping shopping?
>> Rika: Oh...
>> Rumiko: It's a
great way to relax.
>> Rika: Sorry, but
I'm going to the park.
>> Rumiko: Th-the park?
But, honey you can't
do any shopping there.
>> Rika: Look mother, I've got
plans with my friends, okay.
>> Rumiko: But.
>> Henry: Bye.
>> Rika's Grandma:
Hi Rumiko, it's me.
>> Rumiko: Mom, what am
I going to do with her?
>> Rika's Grandma:
Oh honey she's fine,
she's just at that age where
her friends are more important
than her looks.
>> Rumiko: What?
More important than her looks?
But. What?
I mean she- oh, oh no, I
think I'm going to faint.
>> Impmon: I bet those
human loving digi-slaves
and their partners are laughing it up thinking
about me taking it on the
chin from that mule, Indramon.
Everyone hates me.
I'd hate me too if
I were everyone.
Just a loser who
can't...digivolve.
>> Kazu: Looks like
I win again, I rule.
>> Kenta: Oh man, I
want a real digimon.
>> Kazu: Yeah, me too.
Then I'd really rule.
>> Kazu: And I've
been practicing, look.
OK, Digi-Modify!
Matrix Digivolution Activate!
What do ya say guys,
impressive, huh?
>> Guilmon and Calumon: Uh...
>> Kenta: So tell me something,
why do you think you get
to have a digimon but the
rest of us don't, Takato?
>> Takato: Hm, I guess the
digimon could just tell
I'm superior.
>> Kenta: You wish.
>> Takato: Hey I bet there are
tons of digimon like Leomon
and the more they keep showing
up the better chance there is
that one of them will
pick you as a partner.
>> Kenta: That would
be really cool I mean
if he didn't just
leave like Leomon.
>> Jeri: Goodbye Leomon.
>> Kazu: Yeah, but it'd be cool
to have one even
for a little while.
>> Takato: Uh-oh.
>> Kazu: What's eating
you, Takato?
>> Takato: That.
>> Kazu: Huh?
>> Takato: Hey what's
wrong, Jeri?
>> Kazu: Come over
already, don't be shy.
>> Jeri: I want to learn
how to play the card game,
now who's going to teach
me how to use these?
>> Kenta: Whoa!
>> Kazu: Jeri.
>> Jeri: What's wrong, don't I
have enough cards or something?
>> Kenta: I'd say
you got plenty.
>> Kazu: Wow.
What'd you do, go out and
spend your whole allowance?
>> Kenta: Yeah and somebody
else's too, it looks like.
>> Takato: I've got half that.
>> Kazu: Hey, I've been
looking for this one forever.
>> Kenta: Which one
does she have?
>> Jeri: Careful
they're alphabetized.
>> Kazu: Jeri, why don't
you trade me this card
for three of mine, okay?
>> Jeri: Um...
>> Kenta: Three cards,
I'll give you five of mine.
>> Jeri: I don't want to trade;
I want to learn how to play.
>> Kazu: I'll throw in three
free lessons, what do you say?
>> Kenta: Me too.
>> Takato: Uh, you're
drooling guys.
>> Rika: Learn from
someone who can really play.
>> Kazu: Hey I rock.
>> Kenta: Right.
>> Jeri: Really!
>> Kenta: Aw.
>> Kazu: Oh...
>> Jeri: Thanks Rika, I
don't know what to say.
>> Rika: Well I'm sure
you'll think of something.
>> Rika: Okay, you've
got attack cards,
defense cards, and
upgrade cards.
Get familiar with the attack
cards; we'll use them a lot.
>> Kenta: If she
gets as good as Rika,
we're going to lose
all our cards.
>> Kazu: Didn't you already
lose most of your cards to me?
>> Rika: It's always a good idea
to keep a strong
card in reserve.
>> Jeri: Rika, do you think
Leomon will ever come back?
>> Rika: Don't know, but
if he doesn't you'll find a
better digimon.
>> Jeri: Yeah.
>> Jeri: Uh.
>> Rika: Like Calumon.
>> Jeri: Don't think
I didn't ask.
>> Kazu: What, no bikini girls?
>> Henry: Doesn't this
remind you guys of anything?
>> Terriermon: Um,
a petting zoo?
>> Takato: Wait I know,
it's the Chinese Horoscope.
Rat, ox, tiger, rabbit, dragon,
snake, horse, sheep, monkey,
rooster, dog, and pig.
So, what about it, Henry?
>> Henry: The Devas.
>> All: Huh?
>> Henry: Have you
guys noticed that all
of the Devas have
had animal forms.
>> Takato: Now that
you mention it, yeah.
>> Henry: I think
there's a connection.
Mihiramon-tiger,
Sandiramon-snake,
Sinduramon-rooster,
Pajiramon-sheep, Vajramon-ox,
Kumbhiramon-rat, Indramon-horse.
>> Rika: So we've still got to
deal with a rabbit, a dragon,
a monkey, a dog, and a pig.
>> Kenta: There's five
more of those things,
how are you guys going
to beat them all?
>> Kazu: Yeah, it's too bad
we all don't have digimon
that can fight.
Okay, I'm making
myself depressed.
And it's getting
late, I'm outta here.
>> Kenta: Yeah, we'll figure
out how you can beat
those Devas tomorrow.
Wait a minute.
>> Kazu: Huh?
Why? What's the matter, Kenta?
>> Kenta: I don't really know,
it's just...doesn't it seem
like there's something really
weird going on around here?
>> Kenta: Something
that's just not right?
>> Kazu: You mean the way
you're pointing at everyone?
>> Kenta: Duh, I was counting.
>> Kazu: You have to use
your finger to read too?
>> Kenta: No!
Well yes, but that's
not what I meant.
>> Calumon: Uh, does
this count as weird?
>> Takato: It's that kid again.
>> Kazu: He defines weird!
>> Jeri: Why is he
staring at me?
>> Kazu: Jeri's got a boyfriend!
>> Takato: What are
you doing here anyway?
What do you want?
>> Kazu: Besides raising the
level of strange in the park.
[ Screaming ]
>> Calumon: That hurts
more than Kenta's singing.
>> Kenta: Hey!
>> Kazu: That kid's a
freak with a capital F.
>> All: Ew.
>> Kenta: Yuck, my neck
hurts just looking at that.
>> Takato: Maybe
he's really a robot.
>> Jeri: Come on; let's
try talking to him, guys.
He probably just
wants to be friends.
>> Takato: Wait a minute, Jeri!
>> Kazu: Don't we have
enough friends already?
>> Riley: I'm detecting
another wild one.
The computer's having trouble
pinpointing it, but it looks
like it's coming from somewhere
in the West Shinjuku area.
>> Yamaki: West Shinjuku?
Pinpoint location now!
>> Riley: Trying to get
a lock on the target.
Whoa, look at that!
>> Tally: There's
a massive amount
of data coming in,
it's too much!
>> Yamaki: What is the problem?
>> Tally: We've never seen
this much data at once,
it's overloading the system.
>> Yamaki: No!
>> Tally: I've managed to shut
down some unnecessary systems
so the computer won't crash, but it's just a temporary fix, sir.
>> Yamaki: Get me
the chief cabinets!
>> Riley: Already on it.
>> Man: This had better
be important, Yamaki.
>> Yamaki: Just a wild one
that could wreck the city.
>> Man: Wreck the city,
does this have anything
to do with the earthquake?
>> Yamaki: I don't know, sir.
We're still looking into it.
>> Man: Get at it and report
back to me immediately.
Don't make me think my trust
in you is misplaced, Yamaki.
I won't brooke another
disappointment.
>>Yamaki: I'm aware
of that, sir.
>> Man: Hmmmm.
>> Yamaki: I'll show
you, I'll show everyone.
>> Impmon: Friends
who needs them anyway?
[ Pause in speaking ]
>> Jeri: Wait!
>> Takato: I think he
was staring at Calumon.
>> Terriermon: Huh?
>> Rika: Hm?
>> Takato: Maybe that's why
Jeri was attacked before,
because of Calumon.
>> Calumon: Yay Leomon!
Yay Leomon!
Yay!
>> Takato: We don't really know
anything about the little guy,
but I've got a feeling
that kid does.
>> Rika: He could be dangerous.
>> Henry: Yeah.
>> Calumon: Faster Jeri, faster!
Whoa!
>> Weird kid: Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
>> Guilmon: Takato!
Slow down!
>> Terriermon: Henry!
>> Henry: What's that
matter, Terriermon?
>> Takato: What's wrong, boy?
A digimon?
>> Henry: No it's an earthquake!
>> Takato: Hey Jeri,
are you alright?
>> Jeri: Yeah, I'm okay.
But that boy got away.
>> Takato: Good, who knows
where he was leading us.
>> Impmon: Huh?
[laughs] What, so even the earth
wants to get rid of me now?
>> Janyu: These readings
are very puzzling.
Let's run full spectral
analysis on the new data.
>> Yamaki: New data?
Why wasn't I informed?
>> Janyu: Yamaki,
you startled me.
I'm sorry, but we
just now collected it.
>> Yamaki: Well give it to me.
>> Janyu: I'm afraid it
wouldn't do you much good
without further analysis.
The digimon have evolved and we
haven't yet got an accurate
picture of exactly how.
We'll need more time.
>> Yamaki: More Janyu?
I've already been more than
generous with the amount of time
you've had.
Now just give me what
you've got so far.
The time has come to act swiftly
against the digimon,
before it's too late.
Your son and his friends can no
longer play this dangerous game.
>> Henry: And all
the earthquakes,
maybe they're tied
to the Devas too.
[growl]
>> Takato: What's
wrong now, Guilmon?
>> Takato: Huh?
>> Henry: Hey, Terriermon!
>> Terriermon: Now
it's a digimon!
>> Henry: Well, wait up!
>> Renamon: If we wait for you
we'll be too old to fight it.
>> Henry: Hey.
Come on, let's go.
[ Pause in speaking ]
>> Henry: Where's the digimon?
>> Terriermon: Jeez,
give it a second.
>> Terriermon: How's
that for timing?
>> Riley: Another massive data
spike, it's that wild one again.
Stand by; the computer's
getting a lock.
Sir, it's bio-emerging!
>> Yamaki: Ready the
Juggernaut program.
>> Riley: But sir, without
analysis of the new data-
>> Yamaki: Spare me
your theories, do it!
>> Riley: Engaging program.
>> Yamaki: Good.
At last these digimon will see
what the Juggernaut is really
capable of and just how
easily we can defeat them.
>> Terriermon: It's
going to be big!
>> Henry: How can ya tell?
>> Renamon: We're
looking up, aren't we?
>> All: Whoa...
>> Kazu: Is that a mountain?
>> Kenta: With teeth?
>> Takato: No, that is
one seriously big pig.
>> Impmon: Nobody loves
me, everybody hates me.
Think I'll-huh?
A digital field?
What's going on?
Oh sure okay I get it, time
for me to go home, right?
I'm not good enough
for this world,
but I don't want to go yet.
>> Takato: Well there's
your pig Deva, Vikaralamon.
He's ultimate level.
>> Kazu: Check out the sky!
>> Takato: What are
those sparkles?
>> Henry: Maybe some
kind of digital energy.
It looks like the digital bits
Growlmon threw off the first
time he turned back
into Guilmon.
>> Kenta: It's on the move!
[ Pause in speaking ]
>> Rika: Yeah, but
where's it headed?
>> Takato: We've got to stop it.
[screaming]
>> Henry: Well, at least
it won't be hard to spot.
>> Kazu: And I thought
Takato needed a haircut.
>> Takato: Hey, you know
I've been trying to get one
for weeks but we've been busy.
>> Kazu: With hair like that
that thing would make one
heck of a street sweeper.
>> Kenta: Oh yeah great, the
streets will be cleaned but all
the buildings will be knocked down.
>> Guilmon: Now Takato!
>> Takato: Mm hm.
>> Renamon: Rika!
>> Rika: I know, I know.
>> Terriermon: Me too!
>> Henry: Mm hm.
>> Takato: Now, Kazu and Kenta
you have a job to do too.
It's up to you to make sure
Jeri and Calumon stay safe.
>> Kazu: Go run and
hide, you got it!
>> Kenta: Stomp on that oinker!
>> Jeri: Mm hm.
[ Pause in speaking ]
>> Tamers: Digi-Modify!
Digivolution Activate!
>> Digivolution.
>> Terriermon: Terriermon
digivolve to...
>> Renamon: Renamon
>> Guilmon: Guilmon
digivolve to...
>> Gargomon: Gargomon!
>> Kyubimon: Kyubimon!
>> Growlmon: Growlmon!
>> Takato: That thing's
worse than an earthquake,
it's an earthquake
with attitude.
>> Henry: The whole city will
be rubble if we don't stop it!
>> Rika: What are you
two, the Obvious Brothers?
>> Takato: The army, they have
no idea what they're up against.
>> Army guy: Target
acquired, it's...a giant pig?!
>> Army guy #2: Sir, we haven't
been practicing our giant pig
maneuvers, oh wait, do we
have giant pig maneuvers?
>> Army guy: All pilots roast
with extreme prejudice.
>> Army guy #3: Oh
that reminds me,
I'm going to have a barbecue
this weekend and I really-
>> Army guy: Would you just
target the blasted pig already?
>> Kyubimon: Let's send
this porker packing, boys.
>> Kyubimon: Dragon Wheel!
>> Gargomon: Gargo Laser!
>> Growlmon: Pyro Blaster!
>> All: Uh!
>> Kyubimon: He didn't
even flinch!
>> Computer: Juggernaut
power at 50% and building.
All systems nominal.
55%.
>> Janyu: Just what's
going on here, Yamaki?
>> Yamaki: Something I
should've done a long time ago.
This Juggernaut system
will allow us
to control the entire network.
>> Janyu: And then what?
>> Computer: 60%.
>> Yamaki: And then, Mr. Wong,
I'll simply use the system
to destroy all artificial
life in the Real World.
>> Janyu: Yamaki, have
you lost your mind?
If you do that all the
children's digimon will be
destroyed as well.
>>Yamaki: A small
price to pay, I think.
Janyu: But why, we were just
starting to make progress.
Really starting to
understand artificial life.
>> Yamaki: Are you willing
to sacrifice the world
and your son for
artificial life!?
>> Janyu: Huh.
>> Computer: Power at 65%.
>> Janyu: It just
seems...like such a waste.
>> Yamaki: I want
you to see something.
Take a look at your
precious artificial life.
That thing will flatten the
whole city if we don't stop it.
So you tell me, Mr. Wong,
what choice do I have
but to destroy it?
Once this abomination is gone
I'll construct a firewall
so they'll never
bio-emerge again.
>> Gargomon: Stinking pig!
>> Kyubimon: Fox Tail Inferno!
>> Growlmon: Uh, he's
not even slowing down.
[ Crashing ]
>> Gargomon: It's no use,
nothing's working,
not even insults.
>> Rika: There's
got to be something.
>> Kyubimon: Maybe if we could
digivolve to ultimate too.
>> Tamers: Hm?
>> Takato: But we
need blue cards
and they don't just
grow on trees.
Hm, and everyone's
depending on us
to save what's left of the city.
We're the last hope.
>> Mrs. Matsuki: You need to
study once and a while Takato!
>> Takato: I bet she's worried
about me or yelling about me.
>> Henry: We've got
to prove we care.
She probably thinks I hate her.
>> Rika: Look mother, I've got
plans with my friends, okay.
I guess...she really does care.
>> Computer: Juggernaut
power at 80% and climbing.
>> Janyu: I beg you, stop this!
>> Yamaki: Get your
hands off of me!
Enjoy your rampage while you
can, you're about to be deleted.
>> Takato: Hm!
I wish I had some kind
of idea of what to do!
>> Henry: Actually,
wishing's not a bad idea.
>> Henry: I want to
protect my sister.
>> Rika: I want to
protect my family.
Uh.
>> Takato: I want to
protect the whole darn city!
Hey it actually worked!
>> Tamers: Let's do it!
[ Music ]
Digi-Modify!
Matrix Digivolution Activate!
>> D-power: Matrix Digivolution.
>> Gargomon: Gargomon
matrix digivolve to...
[ Music ]
>> Rapidmon: Rapidmon!
>> Kyubimon: Kyubimon
matrix digivolve to....
[ Music ]
>> Taomon: Taomon!
>> Growlmon: Growlmon
matrix digivolve to...
[ Music ]
>> WarGrowlmon: WarGrowlmon!
>> Takato: Get him!!!!!!
>> Rapidmon: Okay, you
don't have to yell!
Sheesh!
[ Music ]
>> Rapidmon: You're not
so confident now,
are ya Mr. Big pig?
>> Computer: Power at 100%.
Ready to engage Juggernaut
program.
>> Yamaki: Do it!
Destroy them all!
>> Janyu: No!!!!!!
>> Wow tension huh.
But this is a really [inaudible]
of all of the digimon is it?
To find out keep watching
digimon digital monsters.