I THINK TAKATO REALLY FREAKED
OUT KAZU AND KANTA,
WHEN HE INTRODUCED THEM
TO GUILMON,
'CAUSE NOW THEY WON'T EVEN
TALK TO HIM.
AND RIKA IS STILL KIND OF
FREAKED OUT
ABOUT THE WHOLE PARTNER THING.
I MEAN, RENAMON HAD TO FIGHT
THOSE GUAIBYMON ALL ON HER OWN.
THEN YAMAKI INTRODUCED HIMSELF
AND FREAKED OUT EVERYONE.
IMPMON FREAKED WHEN HE IMAGINED
WHAT IT WOULD BE LIKE
TO BE WITH HUMANS.
HARPYMON FREAKED WHEN SHE GOT
STOMPED ON BY CUBYMON.
BUT WHEN TAKATO FINALLY SHOWED
GUILMON TO JERI,
SHE DIDN'T FREAK OUT AT ALL.
WHO WOULD'VE THOUGHT JERI
WOULD BE THE CALMEST ONE
OF THE WHOLE FREAKIN' BUNCH?
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
♪ WORLD
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMODIFY
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
READY, GUILMON?
DIGIMODIFY!
METALGARURUMON BLASTER!
METAL BLASTER!
[ GROANING ]
[ GROWLING ]
WHEW.
DARKLIZARDMON WAS
ONE TOUGH COOKIE,
BUT YOU DID IT.
MMM. DID YOU SAY COOKIE?
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE
THINKING OF FOOD RIGHT NOW.
WHAT?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
TARGET CONFIRMED.
STRIKE BEAM STAND BY.
INITIATE RETRIEVAL SEQUENCE.
ARE WE SUPPOSED TO FIGHT
THEM, TAKATO?
NO. I MEAN, I HAVE
NO IDEA.
MAYBE WE SHOULD SCRAM
BEFORE WE FIND OUT.
[ Thinking ] I WANT TO STAY.
MAKE ME STRONGER.
MAKE ME DIGIVOLVE!
[ COUGHING ]
TAKATOMON!
GUILMON, WHERE ARE YOU?
GUILMON?
BLAZE!
[ SCREAMING ]
ARE YOU OKAY?
UH-HUH.
WELL, AREN'T YOU
GOING TO THANK ME?
AFTER ALL,
I SAVED YOUR LIFE.
THAT DESERVES SOMETHING.
THIS IS DANGEROUS WORK,
LITTLE BOY.
SHOULDN'T YOU BE NAPPING?
BUT WHO ARE YOU?
I'LL ASK THE QUESTIONS.
WHO DO YOU THINK YOU ARE,
ATTACKING DIGIMON ON YOUR OWN?
DO YOU THINK THIS IS A GAME?
THEY'RE LETHAL CREATURES
WHO SHOULD BE CONTAINED.
IN FACT, FOR YOUR SAFETY,
I SHOULD TAKE YOUR LITTLE
RED FRIEND THERE, TOO.
LEAVE HIM ALONE.
HE'S NOTHING LIKE
DARKLIZARDMON.
SO YOUNG, SO NAIVE.
WHO YOU CALLING NAIVE?
UHH!
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
SHE'S ALIVE.
AND DANGEROUS.
MAYBE I SHOULD TAKE YOUR FRIEND.
HE COULD BECOME DANGEROUS, TOO.
NO! YOU'LL HAVE
TO GO THROUGH ME.
WELL, PROBABLY MORE TROUBLE
THAN HE'S WORTH, RIGHT?
HEH HEH HEH.
DON'T SAY I DIDN'T WARN YOU,
LITTLE BOY.
MISSION COMPLETE. RETURNING
CAPTAIN TO HEADQUARTERS.
WHO IS THAT GUY?
[ TICKING ]
YOU, UH, DID GREAT
TONIGHT, GUILMON.
TAKATO?
YEAH?
I'M GETTING BETTER,
HUH, TAKATO?
IF I KEEP WINNING, I'LL GET
STRONGER AND STRONGER,
AND THEN I'LL DIGIVOLVE
AGAIN
JUST LIKE YOU WANT ME TO.
YEAH, SURE, YOU WILL.
WAITING'S HARD. I WANT
TO DIGIVOLVE RIGHT NOW.
[ Sighs ] I WANT TO WIN.
I'LL CHANGE AGAIN.
CHANGE?
[ GASPING ]
[ GROWLS ]
NO MORE FIGHTS.
HUH? BUT NO MORE FIGHTS
MEANS NO MORE DATA.
HOW WILL I GET STRONGER?
I THOUGHT YOU WANTED ME
TO DIGIVOLVE.
I DON'T. YOU'LL CHANGE.
HUH?
OH, WHAT DID I DO?
TAKATO?
[ PANTING ]
SOMETHING'S APPEARED
ON MY RADAR.
AND I THOUGHT WE WERE
GOING TO HAVE A QUIET NIGHT.
HMM.
IT LOOKS LIKE A WILD ONE,
BUT I...
I CAN'T BE SURE.
THE SIGNAL'S ALMOST
UNREADABLE.
HUH.
MAYBE IT'S A GLITCH
IN THE PROGRAM.
THOSE ENGINEERS
ARE SO UNRELIABLE.
[ SIGHS ]
NOW THE TRACER'S ACTING ERRATIC.
I'M TELLING YOU,
IT'S THOSE ENGINEERS.
THEY'RE ALWAYS GOING TO
KARAOKE PARTIES
INSTEAD OF CHECKING
THE EQUIPMENT LIKE THEY SHOULD.
ACCORDING TO THE TRACER,
IT'S RIGHT UNDER US, BUT...
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
CALUMON, ZOOM ZOOM,
HERE A ZOOM, THERE A ZOOM.
CALUMON, ZOOM, ZOOM,
NO UNDERWEAR ZOOM!
[ GIGGLING ]
OH! SO CUTE.
THOSE CLUELESS TAMERS
AND THEIR DIGIMON,
SO OBLIVIOUS TO WHAT
I'M COOKING UP IN MY LITTLE LAB.
WELL, THEY'LL FIND OUT
SOON ENOUGH,
AND WON'T THEY BE SURPRISED.
HELLO?
WHERE DID IT GO?
YOU SAW IT, TOO, RIGHT?
I THINK THAT LEFTOVER
ENCHILADA YOU HAD FOR LUNCH
IS MAKING YOU SEE THINGS.
COME ON, GIVE IT UP.
I'M TELLING YOU,
IT WALKED AND TALKED AND WHINED.
AND I'M TELLING YOU
IT'S YOUR LUNCH.
SERVES YOU RIGHT FOR
EATING 4-DAY-OLD FOOD.
MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHAT IS THIS PLACE?
LET ME OUT!
I DON'T WANT TO GO BACK!
SIR, UH, WE'RE READY
TO INITIATE THE DATA SCAN,
BUT THE CREATURE
MAY NOT SURVIVE.
HUH. YOU SAY THAT
AS IF I SHOULD CARE.
IT'S NOT AS THOUGH
THAT THING DOWN THERE
IS FLESH AND BLOOD,
YOU KNOW.
EXCUSE ME, SIR,
BUT IT HAS A REAL BODY.
IT'S A LIFE FORM.
A WORM IS MORE OF
A LIFE FORM THAN THIS THING.
THEY'RE JUST PACKETS
OF DATA, COMPUTER CODE,
ZEROS AND ONES.
THEIR ABILITY TO APPEAR
IN OUR WORLD IS A FLUKE,
BUT OUR MONSTROUS FRIEND HERE
IS NOT WITHOUT ITS USE.
BY ANALYZING ITS DATA,
WE CAN LEARN HOW DIGIMON
ARE CREATED
AND HOW THEY CAN BE
DESTROYED.
PROCEED WITH THE SCAN.
I WANT FULL POWER.
YES, SIR.
AAH!
HELP! GET ME OUT OF HERE!
ITS PARTICLES
ARE DISSIPATING.
DON'T STOP UNTIL WE HAVE
ALL OF ITS DATA.
WE'RE ONLY STEPS FROM ACHIEVING
OUR ULTIMATE GOAL.
AAH!
IT'S GONE.
ITS DATA HASN'T
DISAPPEARED, THOUGH,
JUST...THE BODY.
SHOULD I SAVE THE DATA?
I DON'T SEE THE POINT.
WE GOT ALL THE INFORMATION
WE NEEDED
FROM THE SCANNING PROCEDURE.
ELIMINATE ANYTHING
THAT'S LEFT.
WHAT?
UH, YES, SIR.
DESTROYING ALL PARTICLES NOW.
GET USED TO IT. WE'LL SCAN
AS MANY AS WE HAVE TO
TILL THEY'RE ALL GONE.
[ BELL RINGS ]
UH, MORNING, MISS ISAJI.
HUH?
OH, IT'S YOU, TAKATO.
ALL RIGHT, WHAT ARE YOU
HIDING UNDER YOUR SHIRT TODAY?
I, UH,
OH, IT'S MY LUNCHBOX.
IT'S JUST REALLY SMALL
'CAUSE I'M, UH, ON A DIET.
OH, IT'S TOO EARLY
IN THE MORNING
TO START CAUSING TROUBLE.
I HAVEN'T EVEN HAD
MY FIRST CUP OF COFFEE YET.
OH, I WON'T CAUSE
ANY TROUBLE, NOT ME.
I'VE SAID THIS BEFORE.
BOYS WHO BREAK THE RULES
GROW UP TO BECOME
THUGS AND ZOOKEEPERS.
BUT WHAT'S WRONG WITH BEING
A ZOOKEEPER, MISS ISAJI?
OH, TAKATO,
DON'T BE SILLY.
FOR ONE THING, YOU DON'T
GET ANY RESPECT.
YOU HAVE TO WORK
ALL DAY WITH ANIMALS
WHO NEVER DO WHAT
YOU TELL THEM TO DO.
GEE, THAT KIND OF SOUNDS
LIKE WHAT YOU DO NOW.
WHAT?!
UH...[ Laughs nervously ]
NOTHING. BYE, MISS ISAJI.
OH, WELL, AT LEAST ANIMALS
DON'T MAKE WISECRACKS.
MORNING, MISS ISAJI.
HA HA HA.
AND WHAT A LOVELY MORNING
IT IS.
GOOD TO SEE YOU'RE KEEPING
THE STUDENTS IN LINE.
PUT A SOCK IN IT, MORI.
HUH? WHAT DID I SAY?
MISS ISAJI, HELLO?
[ CHATTERING ]
HEY, THERE.
OH, YEAH, HEY, YOURSELF.
[ LAUGHING NERVOUSLY ]
THE TOPIC FOR TODAY
IS VEGETABLES.
TO MANY OF YOU, VEGETABLES
ARE LIKE HOMEWORK ASSIGNMENTS.
[ Thinking ] I'VE ALWAYS WANTED
GUILMON TO BECOME STRONGER
AND DIGIVOLVE JUST LIKE
IN THE CARD GAME,
BUT THAT MAN'S RIGHT.
THIS ISN'T A GAME.
GUILMON'S TOTALLY DIFFERENT
WHEN HE DIGIVOLVES.
WHAT IF HE ENDS UP
LIKE THE BAD DIGIMON
WE FIGHT AGAINST
AND STOPS BEING MY FRIEND?
I DON'T WANT HIM
TO BECOME A MONSTER.
HUH?
[ GIGGLING ]
AT LEAST JERI DOESN'T THINK
HE'S A MONSTER.
HA HA.
ALTHOUGH SHE WOULD SCREAM LIKE
A BANSHEE IF SHE SAW GROWLMON.
I HOPE GUILMON
NEVER CHANGES.
STAND BACK, DENIZENS
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD.
TERRIERMON'S BACK.
WHOA. MUST HAVE PRESSED
THE WRONG BUTTON.
I WONDER WHAT
I'LL FIND IN HERE.
OH, LOOK!
IT'S AN ORPHAN,
ALL ALONE IN THE WORLD,
NO ONE TO LOVE YOU
OR CHANGE YOUR DIAPERS.
SUZIE SUNSHINE
WILL RESCUE YOU.
I'LL BATHE YOU
AND DRESS YOU
AND USE A BIG
POWDER PUFF ON YOU.
YOU'LL BE
MY LITTLE PRINCESS.
OH, YES, YOU WILL!
[ Giggles ]
UH, HEY, GUYS.
HI.
HEY.
SO, WHAT'S UP?
RUFF! RUFF! RUFF!
WHAT ARE YOU BOYS
DOING TODAY, PLAYING DIGIMON?
NO WAY.
DIGIMON'S FOR KIDS.
YEAH, IT'S ALL PRETEND.
WELL, GUILMON'S REAL.
OH, NOT THAT AGAIN.
LISTEN, DUDE,
YOU'RE NOT SCARING ANYONE
WITH THAT OVERSIZED
STUFF DINOSAUR OF YOURS, OKAY?
UH, YEAH.
BUT GUILMON'S NOT A TOY.
WHATEVER. WE'RE JUST NOT
INTO PLAYING DIGIMON ANYMORE.
IT'S LAME.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DUMP ON IT.
IF YOU DON'T LIKE IT,
THEN DON'T PLAY.
UH-OH. WHAT'S WRONG WITH THEM?
I KNOW.
RUFF. BOYS ARE SILLY.
SOMETIMES THEY FIGHT EVEN WHEN
THERE'S NOTHING TO FIGHT ABOUT.
IT'S ALL JUST PRETEND,
RIGHT?
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
KANTA, LET'S GO HANG
AT MY PLACE.
OHH!
YEAH, LET'S LEAVE TAKATO
WITH HIS KIDDIE GAME.
IT'S NOT A GAME.
WHERE'D THEY GO?
DID I SAY SOMETHING
WRONG, TAKATO?
IT'S NOT YOU.
RUFF! HEY, ARE YOU GOING TO
PLAY WITH GUILMON TODAY?
JERI, I'M NOT JUST
PLAYING!
[ GASPS ]
I-I GOT TO GO.
YAMAKI, I'M VERY
DISAPPOINTED.
WE'VE SPENT MILLIONS
ON HYPNOS,
AND WHAT DO YOU GIVE US?
ONE DIGIMON FLOATING
IN A TANK IN YOUR LAB.
IF THAT'S ALL WE NEEDED,
I'D HAVE HIRED
A DOG CATCHER.
CATCHING AFTER THEY BIOEMERGE
ISN'T GOOD ENOUGH.
CAN'T YOU KEEP THEM
FROM APPEARING ALTOGETHER?
IF THE MEDIA FINDS OUT
ABOUT THESE SO-CALLED
WILD ONES,
THINK OF THE PANIC
IT'LL CAUSE.
YES, MA'AM, BUT HYPNOS
IS THE ONLY REASON
THERE HAVEN'T BEEN ANY
MEDIA LEAKS IN THE FIRST PLACE.
ENOUGH TALK. LET'S JUST
LET THE ARMY HANDLE IT
SO I CAN GET ON
WITH MY LUNCH.
I LOST MY BRIEFING,
SO I'M A LITTLE LOST.
WHAT ARE THESE DIGIMEN
OR WHATEVER THEY'RE CALLED?
IT'SDIGIMON,
YOU TWIT.
I'LL EXPLAIN IT AGAIN.
YEARS AGO,
A TEAM OF SCIENTISTS
CREATED ARTIFICIAL
LIFE PROGRAMS
ALSO KNOWN AS DIGIMON.
AH, YOU MEAN PETS
LIKE MY CAT MUFFY.
NO, YOU DOLT.
THEY'RE ADVANCED FORMS
OF INTELLIGENCE.
IN FACT,
THEY WERE SO SMART,
THE SCIENTISTS
COULDN'T CONTROL THEM.
SOMETIMES I CAN'T CONTROL
MUFFY
LIKE WHEN SHE SPITS
HAIRBALLS ON THE COUCH.
MENTION MUFFY AGAIN,
AND I'LL DROP-KICK YOU
TO THE NEXT TIME ZONE.
THE PROGRAM WAS SHUT DOWN,
AND DIGIMON BECAME
A MERE CHILDREN'S GAME,
OR SO WE THOUGHT.
SOMEHOW THEY SURVIVED,
AND EVEN WORSE,
DEVELOPED THE ABILITY
TO SYNTHESIZE PROTEINS
TO TAKE FORM HERE
IN THE REAL WORLD.
SO THEY'RE LIKE A PACK
OF FREAK CIRCUS ANIMALS.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
I AGREE. I MEAN,
WHO DOESN'T LOVE THE CIRCUS?
SIR, THESE ARE NOT
PERFORMING MONKEYS.
THEY'VE UNLIMITED POWERS
OF DESTRUCTION
AND INDEFINITE LIFE SPANS.
THEY'RE A THREAT
TO HUMANITY.
YOU'VE REJECTED MY PROPOSAL
BEFORE,
BUT THE ONLY SOLUTION
IS TO COMPLETELY
ELIMINATE THEM
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD
AND HERE.
I HAVE A PLAN THAT USES
THE DIGIMON'S OWN DATA
AGAINST THEM.
IT'S QUITE ELEGANT,
REALLY,
AND THERE'S NO CAUSE
FOR HESITATION.
IT'S NOT AS IF WE'RE DESTROYING
LIVING, BREATHING CREATURES.
THEY'RE JUST FAULTY PROGRAMS
WHICH SHOULD NEVER HAVE BEEN
CREATED IN THE FIRST PLACE.
THINK OF THE LIVES WE'D SAVE,
THE CHAOS WE COULD AVERT
BY STRIKING EARLY.
THIS PROPOSAL --
WHAT'S IT CALLED?
JUGGERNAUT.
THE BOUNDARY BETWEEN THE DIGITAL
WORLD AND OURS IS THIN.
HOW WE DO KNOW WHAT AFFECT
JUGGERNAUT WILL HAVE
ON THE REAL WORLD?
YEAH, HOW DO I KNOW
YOU WON'T BLOW UP
MY SWIMMING POOL?
I WOULDN'T WORRY
ABOUT THAT.
JUGGERNAUT MAY CAUSE
SOME COMPLICATIONS ON-LINE,
BUT HANG-UPS ON THE NET
HAPPEN EVERY DAY.
I DOUBT ANYONE
WILL EVEN NOTICE.
WELL, THESE MIGHT NOT
BE SIMPLE COMPLICATIONS.
YOU KNOW HOW I FEEL
ABOUT YOUR PREVIOUS WORK,
YAMAKI,
BUT THE CHIEF'S RIGHT.
IT'S TOO RISKY.
THE GENERAL PUBLIC IS BOUND
TO SUSPECT SOMETHING.
SIR, NO ONE KNOWS
THAT HYPNOS EVEN EXISTS.
WELL, I'M NOT GETTING
IN TROUBLE OVER THIS.
CAN'T WE JUST TEST THIS,
UH, JUGGER WHATEVER
AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS?
AND IF YAMAKI
GETS DISCOVERED,
WE'LL DENY HAVING
ANYTHING TO DO WITH HIM.
GOOD IDEA. FOR ONCE,
YOU'VE COME UP
WITH SOMETHING WE CAN
ACTUALLY USE.
GOT IT, YAMAKI?
YEAH, I GOT IT.
WE'LL CONTINUE TESTING.
BUNCH OF FOOLS.
GO ON! HE DOESN'T MIND,
SEE?
YOU STILL MAD AT ME?
I'M NOT MAD. I'M JUST
WORRIED ABOUT YOU, THAT'S ALL.
BUT WHY?
WHEN YOU DIGIVOLVED,
YOU SCARED THE PANTS
OFF ME --
HOW YOU LOOKED,
YOUR EYES.
IT WAS JUST ME.
BUT YOU BARELY EVEN KNEW
WHO I WAS.
WHAT IF ONE DAY, YOU, LIKE,
QUANTUM DIGIVOLVE,
AND TOTALLY FORGOT ME
OR WHO YOU USED TO BE?
I WOULDN'T FORGET YOU.
YOU'RE MY FRIEND.
TAKATO, NO MATTER HOW MUCH
YOU CHANGE,
YOU'RE STILL YOU,
AND NO MATTER HOW MUCH
I CHANGE,
I HOPE YOU KNOW
I'M STILL ME, TOO, OKAY?
GUILMON?
YEAH?
YOU ARE TOTALLY AMAZING.
IT'S LIKE IT WAS
ONLY YESTERDAY
THAT YOU WERE THINKING
AND TALKING LIKE A BABY,
BUT LOOK AT YOU NOW.
YOU SEE THINGS
SO CLEARLY,
MAYBE EVEN BETTER
THAN I DO SOMETIMES.
I GET IT ALL
FROM YOU, TAKATO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WISH I COULD CHANGE,
TOO.
TAKATO DIGIVOLVE.
TAKATO DIGIVOLVE
TO...MEGATAKATOMON!
AAH-WHOO!
[ BOTH LAUGHING ]
GUILMON, I'M SORRY FOR
ACTING ALL WEIRD,
YOU KNOW, YESTERDAY.
WHY? YOU SAID YOU WERE ONLY
WORRIED ABOUT ME, RIGHT?
I KNOW, BUT I SHOULD HAVE
REALIZED
THAT EVEN THOUGH
YOU WERE GROWLMON
ON THE OUTSIDE,
YOU WERE STILL THE SAME
BREAD-SNARFING GOOF
ON THE INSIDE, RIGHT?
RIGHT!
[ BOTH HOWLING ]
HEY, RILEY, WHAT DO
YOU THINK THAT IS?
HMM.
WELL, WHATEVER IT IS,
IT AIN'T PRETTY.
WE SURE DIDN'T GET
AUTHORIZATION FOR THIS.
YAMAKI DOES WHAT
HE WANTS.
IF I WERE YOU,
I WOULDN'T ASK
TOO MANY QUESTIONS.
JUST KNOW ALL HIS PROJECTS
MEAN BAD NEWS FOR SOMEBODY.
RENAMON, WHEN YOU FOUGHT
HARPYMON,
YOU DIDN'T LOAD HER DATA.
THAT'S THE FIRST TIME
I'VE SEEN YOU DO THAT. WHY?
I DIDN'T NEED TO.
BUT HOW WILL YOU
DIGIVOLVE?
I THINK DIGIMON
WITH HUMAN PARTNERS
DON'T NEED TO ABSORB DATA.
SOMETHING SPECIAL ABOUT
THEIR RELATIONSHIP
WITH THEIR TAMERS
MAKES THEM DIGIVOLVE.
I GUESS THE TWO OF US
ARE LIKE THAT, HUH?
I GUESS SO.
I NEVER THOUGHT
I'D FEEL THIS WAY.
IT'S KIND OF WEIRD.
WHAT?
IT'S LIKE I CAN'T REMEMBER
WHAT I USED TO BE
SO ANGRY ABOUT.
I DON'T EVEN FEEL LIKE
POKING FUN
AT TAKATO AND HENRY'S
SILLY DIGIMON ANYMORE.
HUH. YOU'RE RIGHT.
THAT IS WEIRD.
[ GASPS ]
YOU ARE MR. WONG,
I PRESUME.
WHAT? THANKS,
BUT I'M NOT INTERESTED
IN BUYING ANYTHING.
I'M NO SALESMAN,
MR. WONG.
THINK OF ME AS A GHOST
FROM YOUR PAST,
FROM WHEN YOU AND YOUR
RECKLESS FRIENDS
THOUGHT YOU COULD
DO ANYTHING,
LIKE CREATING DIGITAL
LIFE FORMS ON THE NET.
THEY'RE OUT OF CONTROL
NOW, MR. WONG.
SOMEONE HAS TO PAY
THE PRICE.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST
TELL ME WHAT YOU WANT?
I NEED YOU TO HELP ME FIND
ONE OF YOUR OLD PLAYMATES,
ONE WHO REFUSES
TO GROW UP,
WHO IS WORKING ON
THE PROJECT RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
DON'T LIE, MR. WONG.
IT'S UNBECOMING.
WHO ARE YOU?
HUH?
HI, DAD.
HENRY.
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
WHO WERE YOU
YELLING AT?
DADDY, YOU'RE HOME!
HENRY, SAY HELLO
TO PRINCESS KITTY CAT!
OKAY. HI THERE.
OH, THAT BUILDING I WAS IN --
I DON'T LIKE IT AFTER ALL.
THERE'S SOMETHING FUNNY
ABOUT IT,
SOMETHING NOT NICE.
[ GROWLS ]
AAH!
OOH! DID I SCARE
THE ADORABLE CALUMON?
NOT SO TOUGH WHEN
YOU'RE TUMBLING
LIKE A SACK OF POTATOES,
HUH, FAT FACE?
YOU'RE A BIG MEANY WEENIE!
NO WONDER YOU DON'T HAVE
ANY FRIENDS!
AHH, WHAT GOOD
ARE FRIENDS?
YOU RUN AROUND BEING
ALL CUTE AND FRIENDLY,
AND WHAT'S THAT
DONE FOR YOU?
YOU CAN'T EVEN DIGIVOLVE.
NO TAMER WANTS YOU
AS A DIGIMON.
THEY JUST PUT UP WITH YOU
'CAUSE YOU'RE --
WHAT'S THE WORD
I'M LOOKING FOR?
OH, YEAH, PATHETIC.
IMPMON, IS THERE ANYONE
YOU DO LIKE?
NAH. YOU PRETTY MUCH
ALL MAKE ME SICK.
WHAT A YOUNG DIGIMON
LIKE YOU NEEDS
ISN'T FRIENDS,
BUT SOME GOOD ADVICE,
AND IT'S YOUR LUCKY DAY,
'CAUSE I'M IN THE SHARING
KIND OF MOOD.
LIFE, MY FRIEND,
IS ALL ABOUT
THE SURVIVAL
OF THE FITTEST.
THAT'S WHEN THE BEST
AND THE BRIGHTEST --
THAT'S ME --
WIPES THE FLOOR
WITH THE MEEK
AND THE WEAK. THAT'S YOU.
SO IF I BLAST YOU
TO KINGDOM COME
AND ABSORB YOUR DATA
LIKE I'M PLANNING ON DOING,
DON'T TAKE IT PERSONAL.
IT'S NATURE
TAKING ITS COURSE.
OHH!
OPERATION JUGGERNAUT INITIATE.
I'M GETTING
AN ABNORMAL READING.
SIR, IS THIS ALL PART
OF THE PROJECT WE'RE TESTING --
THE JUGGERNAUT?
YES, BUT IT'S NOTHING
TO BE CONCERNED ABOUT.
WE'RE JUST GIVING IT
A TEST RUN.
USING DATA FROM THE DIGIMON
WE'VE CAPTURED,
I'VE CONSTRUCTED A DIGIMON
COMPOSITE TO ACT AS BAIT.
INSTEAD OF US HUNTING FOR THEM,
THEY'LL COME TO US.
YOU'RE BRILLIANT, SIR.
WELL, THAT'S YOUR FIRST
ACCURATE OBSERVATION.
HEY, GUILMON, NOW THAT
WE'RE BACK ON TRACK,
I HAVE ALL THESE ATTACKS
I WANT TO TRY.
MAYBE WE SHOULD HAVE
A TEAM NAME, TOO,
LIKE AWESOME TWOSOME
OR DYNAMITE DUO.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
[ RUMBLING ]
AN EARTHQUAKE?
IT'S COMING.
DINNERTIME, EVERYONE.
WHO WANTS TAKEOUT?
I DO, I DO, I DO!
[ Giggles ]
HEY, DAD. SMELLS GREAT.
I'M STARVING.
NOW, NO SMART COMMENTS
ABOUT HOW THIS STUFF'S BETTER
THAN MY COOKING.
SO, WHAT DO YOU WANT,
FRIED FROG
OR PICKLED PIG FEET?
MMM, MMM.
OH, DAD, GIVE ME A BREAK.
I'M NOT EATING FRIED FROG.
YOU NEVER KNOW.
YOU MIGHT LIKE IT.
HEY, UH, DAD...
DON'T WORRY.
I MADE THAT UP,
BUT DON'T TELL
YOUR SISTER, OKAY?
ACTUALLY, I WANT TO KNOW
ABOUT THAT DIGIMON PROJECT
YOU USED TO WORK ON.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THAT LATER,
OKAY, SON?
OH, OKAY.
SO WHERE'S THE FROG?
WHAT?
AAH!
UH, TERRIERMON!
IT'S GOT ME, HENRY,
LIKE A MAGNET!
CAN'T RESIST IT!
WHAT IS HAPPENING TO YOU?
OPERATION JUGGERNAUT ACTIVATED.
DATA STREAM DISPATCHED.
PROJECTED RESPONSE -- IMMEDIATE.
[ Thinking ] THOSE DIGIMON WON'T
KNOW WHAT HIT THEM.
LET'S SEE THE KIDDIES
DEAL WITH THIS.
THE SKY.
TAKATO,
SOMETHING'S COMING --
A DIGIMON,
AND HE'S REALLY BIG.
OHH.
UH-OH. I HOPE TAKATO AND GUILMON
AREN'T IN OVER THEIR HEADS.
TO FIND OUT,
BETTER KEEP WATCHING
"DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS."