WHILE TAKATO AND GUILMON
WERE DISCUSSING THE BENEFITS
OF DREAMING,
GUILMON BEGAN TO DISAPPEAR INTO
SOME WEIRD ENERGY FIELD.
NOT WANTING TO LOSE HIS FRIEND,
TAKATO WENT TO ASK HIS DREAM
GIRL FOR ADVICE.
NEEDLESS TO SAY, REIKA DIDN'T
ROLL OUT THE WELCOME MAT.
WE FINALLY GOT THE 411
ON YAMAKI
AND HIS TOP-SECRET
NETWORK SURVEILLANCE SYSTEM
CALLED HYPNOS.
WHAT DOES HE HAVE AGAINST
DIGIMON, ANYWAY?
THEN WITHOUT WARNING, GUILMON
TOTALLY DISAPPEARED.
TAKATO, HENRY,
AND THE RELUCTANT REIKA
HAD TO WORK TOGETHER
TO SAVE GUILMON
BEFORE YAMAKI DELETED THEM ALL.
MAN, BEING A TAMER
IS HARD WORK.
DI-DI-DI
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON
DI-DI-DI
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS
TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
WORLD
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DI-DI-DI
DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS
DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON
OKAY, LET'S SEE.
HMM.
I'LL JUST ADD A BUNCH OF SPIKES
DOWN HIS BACK
AND PUT A FEW STRIPES
BELOW THEM.
NAH. THAT'S JUST DUMB.
NOW I CAN'T RIDE ON HIS BACK.
AH, WELL.
THEY STILL LOOK COOL.
NOW, WHAT WILL I CALL HIM?
UH, GILLYMON. GOALIE.
GROWL! GROWLYMON.
GROWLMON. OF COURSE.
GROWLMON.
NOW, WHAT'S HIS ATTACK?
UM, I'VE BEEN DOING
A LOT OF THINKING.
[ GASPS ]
OH, NOT THAT.
NOT ABOUT THAT.
[ GIGGLES ]
YOU SEE, IT'S JUST,
UM --
IT'S COLD OUT HERE.
THAT'S IT. EXACTLY.
AND A FIRE WOULD BE NICE.
HA HA HA HA.
AND A COMFY COUCH.
WITH ME?
UH-HUH.
A FIRE? ALLOW ME.
AAH!
WHAT?
SO I FORGOT THE COUCH.
HA HA HA HA HA!
HA HA HA!
AHA. TASTY GOODY BREAD.
HA HA HA HA.
MMM. HMM?
OOPS. UH-OH. HA HA.
COME BACK HERE.
AHA. HUH?
HMM.
EH. LITTLE DRY, YOU KNOW.
DON'T JUST STAND THERE,
YOU BIG RED LUMP.
GIVE ME SOME MORE.
COME ON.
OKAY.
YOU MUST REALLY
LIKE THAT BREAD.
WHAT MAKES YOU SAY THAT?
MORE.
MORE!
OKAY.
UM, EXCUSE ME, SIR?
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD LEAVE
A LITTLE FOR ME?
TAKATO WON'T BE BACK
UNTIL TOMORROW.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
HOW STUPID YOU SOUND?
YOU DIGIPETS
ARE ALL THE SAME.
TAKATO THIS,
TAKATO THAT.
YOU'RE LIVING IN A CAGE,
MY LUMPISH FRIEND.
ARE YOU REALLY HAPPY
BEING LOCKED UP
LIKE AN ANIMAL
IN THE PETTING ZOO?
MAYBE YOU ARE.
YOU'RE PRETTY SIMPLE.
UH-HUH.
'COURSE I'M HAPPY.
TAKATO'S MY FRIEND,
AND THAT'S PRETTY SIMPLE.
[ CHOKES ]
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
TAKATO'S YOUR FRIEND?
WRONG, BUDDY BOY.
FRIENDS DON'T LOCK THEIR LITTLE
RED PALS UP IN CAGES.
NOW LOOK WHAT YOU'VE DONE.
YOU HAVE MADE ME SICK
TO MY STOMACH.
I THINK I'LL HAVE TO GO
SOMEWHERE
AND PUKE MY GUTS OUT.
UGH.
LISTEN UP, CLASS.
THERE HAVE BEEN NUMEROUS REPORTS
OF A CHILD PLAYING
IN SHIJUKU PARK AFTER DARK.
I DON'T THINK I NEED TO REMIND
YOU OF THIS,
BUT JUST IN CASE I DO,
NO WANDERING AROUND
AFTER DARK, OKAY?
OKAY!
GUESS WHAT I HEARD.
GET THIS, GUYS.
THERE'S SOME KIND
OF PINT-SIZED PYROMANIAC
LOOSE IN THE PARK.
WISH I'D THOUGHT
OF THAT.
ME TOO.
HOW DO WE KNOW
YOU DIDN'T, KAZU?
HUH?
SO, DO YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT I HEARD?
THIS'LL REALLY
MAKE YOU MAD.
REALLY? TELL US.
SOME KID IS GOING AROUND
PICKING ON COUPLES IN THE PARK
WHILE THEY'RE KISSING.
CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
HUH. HMM.
OH, BOY.
YEAH, IT'S A BOY,
ALL RIGHT.
COME ON.
CONFESS.
DON'T LOOK AT ME.
CONFESS TO WHAT?
WE HAVEN'T DONE ANYTHING.
GIRLS NEVER PLAY FAIR.
NO ONE THINKS IT WAS YOU.
DON'T WORRY, TAKATO.
UH...OHH.
[ Thinking ] OH, GUILMON,
WHAT HAVE YOU GOTTEN US INTO
THIS TIME?
YOU THINK IT WAS GUILMON?
I DON'T KNOW, TAKATO.
HE DOESN'T REALLY LOOK
LIKE A KID TO ME.
HEY, THAT'S RIGHT.
CAN YOU SEE HIM
WITH A BACKPACK?
OH.
FULL OF FOOD?
HA HA HA HA HA.
WISE UP, GUYS.
THEY JUST THINK IT'S A KID
'CAUSE IT'S TOO SMALL
TO BE AN ADULT.
DID I ASK YOU?
I DIDN'T THINK SO.
ANYWAY, I HEARD THE PRINCIPAL
TELLING THE TEACHERS
THEY HAVE TO START PATROLLING
THE PARK TONIGHT.
WHA--
BUT THAT'S HORRIBLE.
THEY'RE GOING TO CATCH GUILMON
THIS TIME FOR SURE.
SENSORS INDICATE
A DIGITAL ANOMALY.
ANOTHER CONFOUNDED
WILD ONE, I SUPPOSE.
PUT A TRACER ON IT,
RILEY.
IT WON'T LOCK.
IT'S GETTING AWAY FROM ME.
[ Thinking ] IT'S TIME
FOR A MORE GLOBAL APPROACH.
WHY ARE YOU BURYING
YOUR DINNER?
BECAUSE THEN I GET TO DIG IT UP
LATER AND EAT IT.
HA HA HA. I HAD TO ASK.
LOGIC IS NOT
YOUR MIDDLE NAME.
NOPE. DON'T HAVE
A MIDDLE NAME.
PROMISE ME YOU'LL STAY
INSIDE TONIGHT, OKAY?
OKAY.
UH-HUH.
I AM SO LATE.
[ Thinking ] PLEASE LISTEN
JUST THIS ONCE.
OH, THIS IS SILLY.
HUH?
IT WAS JUST A SILLY
CHILDISH PRANK.
YOU DON'T SEE THE PRINCIPAL
OUT HERE PATROLLING
THE PARK, DO YOU?
OH, MISS ISAJI, ISN'T IT
OUR RESPONSIBILITY
TO SEE TO THE MORAL SAFETY
OF OUR CHARGES?
THEY'RE SO IMPRESSIONABLE,
SO INNOCENT, AND THIS...
ISN'T.
MISS ISAJI!
OHH, MORI,
WILL YOU GROW UP?
MISS ISAJI, IT'S NOT SAFE
FOR A WOMAN ALONE.
MR. MORI.
UH, YES?
I THINK I LEFT MY OVEN ON
OR SOMETHING.
I NEED TO GET HOME
RIGHT AWAY.
WAIT. DON'T GO!
[ Whimpers ] WHO WILL
PROTECT THE CHILDREN?
AFTER BREAD,
BURY THE POTS.
[ WHISTLES ]
HUH?
HEY.
DID YOU COME
FOR MORE BREAD?
SORRY, BUT I JUST
BURIED IT.
HOPING IT'LL GROW?
OH, I NEVER EVEN THOUGHT
OF THAT.
OH! I WAS MAKING FUN OF YOU,
PINEAPPLE HEAD.
DON'T YOU GET IT?
BUT HOW COULD YOU?
HOW ARE YOU GOING TO LEARN
ANYTHING
LOCKED UP
IN THIS STUPID CAGE?
COME WITH ME,
MY LITTLE RED DISCIPLE,
AND HAVE SOME FUN.
HUH? ME GO WITH YOU?
THAT IS, IF YOU'RE NOT
AFRAID OF THE DARK.
NOT AFRAID, NOT AFRAID,
NOT AFRAID. HUH?
GOOD GRIEF.
CHICKEN!
DON'T LIKE CHICKEN.
TAKATO SAID, "PROMISE ME
YOU'LL STAY INSIDE TONIGHT,"
SO I STAY.
BLEH, "TAKATO TOLD ME
TO STAY INSIDE."
IF TAKATO TOLD YOU
TO SET YOUR FOOT ON FIRE,
WOULD YOU DO IT?
I THINK NOT, SO WHY LISTEN
TO HIM THIS TIME, HMM?
AH, FORGET IT.
YOU'RE NO FUN.
AW, BUT I AM FUN, REALLY.
WAIT FOR ME!
SOMETHING JUST DOESN'T
FEEL RIGHT.
I SAY, BOY,
ARE YOU THE ONE?
UH, THE ONE?
THE ONE INTERRUPTING
THE PROGRESS
OF HUMAN COURTSHIP.
I DON'T KNOW.
BOY, ARE YOU OR ARE YOU NOT
INTERFERING
WITH THE OSCULATORY ACTIVITIES
OF CONSENTING ADULTS?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT PART
DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
WELL, ALL OF IT.
YOU MEAN TO TELL ME
YOU DON'T COMPREHEND
YOUR NATIVE TONGUE, BOY?
YES, SIR. UH, NO, SIR.
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
AND I MEAN THAT, SIR.
BOY, YOU'RE STARTING
TO ANNOY ME.
ME TOO, SIR.
TAKATO, I AM SO SORRY
ABOUT THAT.
YOU SEE, OFFICER,
I WAS WALKING HIM HOME
WHEN WE RAN INTO ONE
OF MY FRIENDS.
ARE WE THERE YET?
NO.
ARE WE THEREYET?
NO!
UH, YES. HMM.
EXCUSE ME, BUT AM I
SUPPOSED TO BE HAVING FUN?
JUST WATCH AND LEARN.
HIROKO.
HIROSHI.
MM.
OH, THAT'S NICE.
HUH?
AAH!
YAH!
WHOA! ALIEN!
HA HA HA.
DID YOU SEE THEIR FACES?
THAT WAS ABSOLUTELY
PRICELESS!
OH, HIROSHI, HIROKO.
[ Makes kissing noise ]
IS THAT IT?
I DON'T GET IT.
I'M GOING HOME.
HMM? HEY, WHERE YOU GOING?
I'M JUST GETTING WARMED UP.
[ GROANS ]
HUH? WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE LOOKING AT, HUH?
BADA-BOOM!
THANK YOU, MISS ISAJI.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
SAY YOU'LL STAY OUT OF THE PARK
AT NIGHT FROM NOW ON.
HOW'S THAT
FOR SOMETHING TO SAY?
YES, MA'AM,
BUT I'M NOT THE ONE.
I NEVER SAID
THAT YOU WERE, TAKATO,
BUT YOU HAVE TO ADMIT
IT LOOKS KIND OF SUSPICIOUS.
[ Thinking ] SUSPICIOUS?
OH, WHAT'S MORE SUSPICIOUS
THAN A BIG RED DINOSAUR?
HEY!
THEY'LL LOCK HIM UP,
AND I'LL NEVER SEE HIM AGAIN!
OR WORSE, THEY'LL THINK HE'S
A VICIOUS MONSTER,
A THREAT TO SOCIETY.
HE'S A THREAT TO SOCIETY!
I WON'T LET THEM DO IT!
TAKATO.
[ PANTING ]
[ Thinking ] I HAVE TO BE
THE LOUSIEST TAMER
ON THE FACE OF THE EARTH.
WHY'D I HAVE TO MAKE HIM
SO BIG?
GUILMON!
NO.
YOU PROMISED ME
YOU WOULDN'T GO OUTSIDE.
I'LL NEVER SEE YOU AGAIN,
EXCEPT ON THE EVENING NEWS --
"DIGIMON AUTOPSY."
WHO ARE YOU
TALKING TO, HUH?
[ GASPS ]
YOU HAVE A NEW FRIEND?
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
YOU SCARED ME TO DEATH.
OH, TAKATO, I WISH
YOU HAD BEEN THERE.
I SCARED SOME PEOPLE,
AND THEY SCREAMED REALLY LOUD
AND RAN AWAY,
BUT IT REALLY WASN'T ANY FUN
SO I CAME HOME,
AND HERE I AM.
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
IT REALLY WAS YOU.
THAT'S IT!
GUILMON...
I JUST CAN'T TAKE THIS ANYMORE.
YOU HEAR ME?
I'VE HAD IT WITH YOU!
I'VE HAD IT!
HMM.
TAKATO, WHAT DID I DO WRONG?
[ GROWLING ]
AAH, HUMANS ARE BEGINNING
TO BORE ME.
ALWAYS SO PREDICTABLE,
SO PATHETICALLY -- HUH?
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
SOMEONE'S BIO-EMERGING. BRAVO!
HMM?
AAH!
HEY, YOU THERE -- FOUR-EYES.
WHAT YOU DOING, HUH?
OH, I'M SORRY
WITTLE BABY DRAMON
CAN'T GET OUT
OF THE MEAN OLD DIGITAL FIELD.
HA HA! GUESS YOU'RE NOT
SO TOUGH NOW, HUH?
HA HA! WHAT DO YOU SAY
TO THAT?
NOT A THING.
[ LAUGHS ]
GRRAAH!
OOH, I'M SO SCARED.
HA HA HA HA HA!
BIG BABY DRAMON GOING TO TAKE
IMPMON'S HEAD OFF?
THAT'S SO SWEET.
NANNY NANNY BOO-BOO,
BABY DRAMON DOO-DOO.
WHO'S THE MAN? I AM.
BOO-YAH! HA HA!
HA HA!
COME ON. I DIDN'T MEAN IT.
I'M LAUGHING WITH YOU.
[ LAUGHS ]
GRRAAH!
UH-OH.
UH, THIS IS WHAT'S CALLED
A TACTICAL ERROR.
[ SNIFFS ]
HUH?
HUH? [ Gasps ]
THAT WAS NO PIGEON.
[ GROWLING AND LAUGHING ]
WHAT IS THAT --
A SPY PLANE?
AAH! GUILMON!
ARE YOU READY
TO FIGHT, REIKA?
IS THAT
A RHETORICAL QUESTION?
WHO OUT THERE IS WORTHY OF ME?
AHA!
[ Panting ] HUH?
THAT'S ENOUGH.
THIS IS BECOMING
A PERSONAL EMBARRASSMENT.
GUILMON!
OH!
WHOA -- DEVIDRAMON.
MAN, HE GIVES "THE EVIL EYE"
A WHOLE NEW MEANING.
HMM, CHAMPION LEVEL
VIRUS TYPE. OUCH.
THAT CRIMSON CLAW TAG OF HIS
LOOKS NASTY.
GUILMON!
[ SNARLING ]
OH!
RENIMON.
NOT THIS TIME.
HUH?
I CAN'T.
THIS IS GUILMON'S FIGHT.
OH.
REIKA, WHERE'S TAKATO?
UP THERE.
RIGHT IN THE LINE
OF FIRE. HA HA HA.
THAT DOESN'T HELP.
PYRO SPHERE!
RIGHT.
DIGIMODIFY --
POWER ACTIVATE!
PYRO SPHERE!
[ LAUGHS ]
OH, MAN,
THAT SHOULD HAVE WORKED.
DIGIMODIFY --
HYPER WING ACTIVATE.
NO WAY!
DIGIMODIFY --
SPEED ACTIVATE!
SPEED IS USELESS HERE.
DOES HE HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT HE'S DOING?
OH, FOR GOODNESS SAKE,
HE'S HIS OWN WORST ENEMY.
HE'S A BASKET CASE.
HUH?
HMM.
HAD ENOUGH, ROOKIE?
[ LAUGHS ]
GET OFF HIM!
A LEFT AND A RIGHT
AND A FIGHT, FIGHT, FIGHT!
NOW THAT'S ENTERTAINMENT!
LOOK AT HIM GO!
OLD PINEAPPLE HEAD IS GETTING
SLICED, DICED, MINCED,
AND -- AAH!
LITTLE LESS ENTHUSIASM,
OLD BOY.
LESS ON THE "BOOM,"
MORE ON THE "BAH."
SERVES YOU RIGHT
FOR WALKING OUT ON ME!
I'VE OUTDONE MYSELF
WITH THIS ONE. HA HA!
THIS IS MUCH MORE FUN
THAN SCARING HUMANS.
LEFT, RIGHT, COME ON,
COME ON!
I KNEW GUILMON DIDN'T HAVE IT
IN HIM -- NOT CLEVER ENOUGH.
[ Laughs ] OH!
I'M SEEING THINGS.
IT'S EITHER THAT,
OR A DOG-EARED BUNNY RABBIT
JUST FLEW BY.
GUILMON!
TA...KATO.
[ GROWLS ]
I'M RUNNING OUT OF CARDS.
OH, MAN.
AAH!
OH.
YO, HEY THERE, TAKATOMON.
GUESS WHAT I JUST FOUND OUT --
GUILMON'S INNOCENT.
WELL, MOSTLY INNOCENT.
HUH?
HE WAS SET UP
BY THAT NASTY LITTLE
PUPPY KICKER IMPMON.
NOW GO TELL HIM
YOU'RE NOT MAD ANYMORE.
OH. I WAS WRONG.
YOU HAVE TO GET UP!
I...
AM TRYING.
YOU JUST HAVE TO TRY HARDER.
OH.
I DON'T WANT TO LOSE YOU.
YOU'RE MY BEST FRIEND.
I'M YOUR BEST FRIEND?
YOU'RE NOT MAD?
I CAN'T STAY MAD AT YOU,
AND IT'S MY FAULT
FOR NOT TRUSTING YOU, GUILMON.
TRUST ME?
GUILMON!
WHOA!
DIGIVOLUTION.
GUILMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
[ ALL GASP ]
OH, WOW.
BULL'S-EYE, BABY.
IT'S GROWLMON!
GUILMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
GROWLMON!
[ GROWLING ]
THAT HURTS MY EARS!
GRRAAH!
PYRO BLASTER!
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THIS IS HAPPENING.
THAT WOULD BE
BECAUSE IT ISN'T.
WHAT?
ALL DATA, AUTO-ERASE.
THE PUBLIC WILL KNOW NOTHING
OF THIS DEBACLE.
RILEY, YOU'LL BE IN CHARGE
OF INVENTING
A CONVINCING COVER STORY.
YOU'RE JOKING, RIGHT?
BACK FOR MORE?
GRRAAH!
DRAGON SLASH!
[ ALL GASP ]
THIS IS GOOD.
GOING UP?
MAYBE IT'S NOT SO GOOD.
GROWLMON!
PYRO BLASTER!
GRRAAH!
THAT CREEPY YAMAKI DUDE'S
GOING TO HAVE TO THINK FAST
TO COVER THIS UP.
IS THE DIGIMON OUT OF THE BAG?
KEEP WATCHING
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."