CALUMON TRIED A LITTLE ARTISTIC
EXPRESSION ON THE SOCCER FIELD
AND THE WHOLE PLACE WENT NUTS.
JERI ALMOST LOST HER MIND
WHEN SHE SAW THE LITTLE DUDE
IN THE INFIRMARY
AND TAKATO WAS JUST RELIEVED
TO FIND OUT
THAT THE VANDAL WASN'T GIYOMON,
UNTIL, OF COURSE,
CALUMON AND GIYOMON TEAMED UP
TO DRAW
ANOTHER ATHLETIC MASTERPIECE.
VIYOMON SHOWED UP
TO SPOIL THE FUN,
BUT REIKA AND RENIMON ENDED UP
BEATING HIM AT HIS OWN GAME.
IN THE END, EVERYONE DECIDED
CALUMON WOULD BE FINE
FLYING SOLO FOR THE TIME BEING.
WHO KNOWS?
THERE MAY BE SOME DIGIMON
WHO JUST CAN'T BE TAMED.
DI-DI-DI
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON
DI-DI-DI
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS
TO SAVE THE DIGITAL
WORLD
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS
ARMOR DIGIVOLVE
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON
RAIN FORESTS ARE CRITICAL TO
THE SURVIVAL OF THIS PLANET...
[ Whispers ] WHOA.
SO WHOSE SISTER IS THAT?
YOU MEAN,
THE FASHION QUEEN?
THAT'S REIKA'S MOM.
NO WAY.
I THINK SHE'S A MODEL.
THIS MOST PRECIOUS RESOURCE WILL
HAVE BEEN COMPLETELY DECIMATED.
[ SIGHS ]
BESIDES PROVIDING LIFE-GIVING
OXYGEN FROM THE LUSH CANOPIES...
[ CELLULAR PHONE RINGS ]
HELLO?
THIS IS MAKINO.
WHEN'S THE SHOOT?
NOW? UH, UH, NO, NO.
NO PROBLEM. IT'S FINE.
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
I'D LIKE TO THANK
THE PARENTS AND FAMILY MEMBERS
THAT HAVE JOINED US TODAY
BECAUSE THE ONLY WAY WE...
[ Thinking ] WHY DOES MY MOTHER
ALWAYS HAVE TO DO THAT?
WHATEVER. LIKE I CARE
WHAT ANYBODY THINKS ANYWAY.
WHAT'S THAT?
NOTHING.
THEY LOOK
LIKE TAROT CARDS.
HAVE YOU BECOME
A FORTUNETELLER?
YEAH, RIGHT.
WELL, WHATEVER IT IS,
AT LEAST YOU'RE INTERESTED
IN SOMETHING.
WHEN I WAS YOUR AGE,
I DIDN'T HAVE THE LUXURY
OF PLAYING LITTLE CARD GAMES.
I WAS ALREADY HARD AT WORK.
MM-HMM.
YOU MIGHT START THINKING
ABOUT WHAT YOU WANT TO DO
WITH YOUR LIFE.
MM-HMM.
WELL,
FAME AND FORTUNE AWAITS.
[ SIGHS ]
[ Thinking ] I KNOW
WHAT I WANT TO DO WITH MY LIFE,
BUT SHE'D NEVER UNDERSTAND.
A LITTLE CARD GAME? HA!
TAMING DIGIMON IS A LOT
MORE RESPECTABLE THAN MODELING.
BESIDES, I'M GOOD AT IT.
I DON'T NEED HER APPROVAL.
[ EXPLOSIONS ]
WHOA. TIME FOR ME
TO GO TO WORK.
[ PANTING ]
HI, GRANDMA. I'M HOME.
REIKA, IS THAT YOU?
HELLO?
READY, RENIMON?
ALWAYS.
PARTY TIME.
AND WE'RE
THE ENTERTAINMENT.
I'M GOING OUT
FOR A LITTLE WHILE.
HUH? BUT, HONEY,
YOU JUST GOT HOME.
WELL, MAKE SURE
YOU'RE BACK BY DINNERTIME.
DON'T WORRY, GRANDMA.
I WILL.
WHAT ARE WE HAVING
ANYWAY?
MY SPECIAL
EGGPLANT AND LIVER CASSEROLE.
TERRIFIC.
[ OWLS    @@
[ GROWLS ]
READY, SET, GO!
AND SCISSORS
CUTS PAPER. HA HA.
UNH-UNH-UNH.
READY, SET, GO!
EVERYONE WINS
BUT GIYOMON. HA HA.
[ GROANS ]
NOT YOUR GAME.
HUH, BUDDY? HA HA.
I OUGHT TO PLAY YOU FOR
YOUR PEANUT BUTTER NEXT TIME.
[ GROANS ]
[ GROWLS ]
WHAT'S WRONG, BOY?
ANOTHER DIGIMON JUST APPEARED.
I CAN FEEL IT.
HEY!
[ Thinking ] OH, YEAH.
[ GROWLS ]
BRING IT ON.
ALAMON --
AN ARMORED DINOSAUR TYPE.
LET'S SEE IF HIS DINO-BURST
ATTACK HAS ANY REAL BITE TO IT.
WALK ALL OVER HIM.
MY PLEASURE. UHH!
UHH!
OH! MY TURN! AAH!
SCALY BUM.
TIME TO FIGHT.
DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMODIFY!
AGUMON'S FROZEN WIND
ACTIVATE!
YOU LOOK
A LITTLE OVERHEATED.
HOW ABOUT A NICE COOL BREEZE?
FROZEN WIND!
DINO-BURST!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THIS ISN'T
SOME STUPID LITTLE GAME.
TOO STRONG.
AND FOR DESSERT --
FOX FLAMBé!
COME ON. GET UP.
IF YOU DIGIVOLVE,
YOU CAN BEAT HIM.
[ ROARS ]
PYROSPHERE!
TERRIER TORNADO!
UHH! OH!
UHH.
I KNEW
IT HAD TO BE YOU.
THIS DIGIMON'S MINE.
WHY DON'T YOU WANNABES
FIND SOMEWHERE ELSE TO PLAY?
WANNABES?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO BE
SO NASTY.
WHY ARE YOU ALWAYS MAKING
YOUR DIGIMON FIGHT ANYWAY?
YOU'RE STARTING TO SOUND
LIKE A BROKEN RECORD.
DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMODIFY!
HYPERCHIP ACTIVATE!
YOU SHOULDN'T BE HERE.
STAY OUT OF MY WAY.
BUT WHY?
OH...
LET'S FINISH THIS.
DINO-BURST!
FROZEN WIND!
I THINK YOU NEED
A COLD SHOWER.
HOW IS THIS POSSIBLE?
I ALWAYS HATED
THE ICE AGE.
AAH!
NOW DON'T MOVE.
GOOD BOY.
BYE-BYE, HANDSOME.
DIAMOND STORM!
RENIMON,
IT'S TIME TO GO.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE.
CAN'T WE JUST TALK?
SURE. I'VE GOT
SOMETHING TO SAY.
DON'T EVER TRY THAT
AGAIN, LITTLE BOYS.
RENIMON AND I
WORK ALONE.
DOES THAT QUALIFY
AS A CONVERSATION?
GEE,
I GUESS IT DOES.
HUH. WHAT A PATHETIC
LITTLE GATHERING OF FOOLS.
NO SELF-RESPECTING DIGIMON
WOULD BE A SLAVE TO A HUMAN.
IF THEY DON'T CHANGE,
THEY'RE GOING TO PAY
'CAUSE IMPMON'S PLAN
IS UNDERWAY.
ARE YOU TRYING
TO MAKE ME LOOK BAD?
WHY WOULD I WANT
TO DO THAT?
I ONLY WANT
TO MAKE YOU HAPPY.
I DON'T GET IT.
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
I'M JUST WAITING,
THAT'S ALL.
WELL, I'M NOT GOING
TO WAIT AROUND
FOR YOU TO DIGIVOLVE
WHEN YOU FEEL LIKE IT.
I'M SORRY
TO DISAPPOINT YOU, BUT...
REIKA? I'M HOME.
WHERE ARE YOU? I HAD
THE MOST AMAZING DAY.
I'M OUT HERE, MOM.
I'VE GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO MAKE HER DIGIVOLVE.
IF I DON'T, THEN
I'LL NEVER REALLY BE THE BEST...
AND I HAVE TO BE.
I CAN'T LET HER HOLD ME BACK.
[ CHILDREN WHISPERING ]
I'M TOAST.
YAY!
REIKA NONAKA IS
OUR NEW DIGIMON CHAMPION.
[ CHEERS ]
THAT WAS QUITE AN OVERWHELMING
VICTORY, MISS NONAKA.
WHAT DID YOU DO
TO PREPARE?
I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
IT WAS EASY.
UH, OKAY. GREAT.
[ Sighs ] I AM SO BORED.
WHOA. WHAT'S HAPPENING?
HUH? OH.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
THERE SHE IS.
THE DIGIMON QUEEN.
SHE IS THE CHILD.
YES,
YOU ARE THE ONE.
MAKE ME DIGIVOLVE!
MAKE ME STRONGER.
[ ALL TALKING ]
MY TAMER.
HELP US.
I CAN'T TAME ALL OF YOU.
I JUST WANT
ONE STRONG DIGIMON.
ARE YOU RENIMON?
YOU WANTED SOMEONE POWERFUL,
DIDN'T YOU?
[ GASPING ]
I MUST BE DREAMING.
HUH?
THIS IS DIFFERENT.
HMM.
ALL RIGHT.
LET'S SEE WHAT WE GOT.
I AM DREAMING.
[ Thinking ] MAYBE THIS MEANS
I GET A WISH.
WELL, THERE'S ONLY ONE THING
I REALLY WANT.
I WISH RENIMON WAS MINE,
AND THAT I KNEW
HOW TO MAKE HER DIGIVOLVE.
I WISH I WAS
A REAL DIGIMON TAMER.
[ GASPS ]
I HAVE BEEN SEARCHING
FOR A STRONG TAMER,
AND YOU ARE THE ONE.
IT'S NO ACCIDENT
THAT WE'RE A TEAM.
SHARE YOUR STRENGTH WITH ME
AND WE WILL BE UNSTOPPABLE.
[ Thinking ] BE PATIENT, REIKA.
I WILL DIGIVOLVE,
BUT HOW SOON
MIGHT DEPEND ON YOU.
ALL I REALLY HAVE TO DO
IS DESTROY ONE DIGIMON
THAT'S STRONG ENOUGH
AND LOAD HIS DATA,
BUT IT MAY NOT BE THAT SIMPLE.
AW, AIN'T THAT SWEET?
A DIGIBABE
PINING IN THE MOONLIGHT.
DON'T LOOK TO ME LIKE
YOU'RE TOO HAPPY THERE, TOOTS,
BUT THEN AGAIN WHAT DIGIMON
WOULD BE WHEN YOU GOT TO ANSWER
TO SOME SNOTTY-NOSE KID
LIKE YOU'RE THEIR PET
OR SOMETHING?
AM I RIGHT?
[ BEEPING ]
A DIGIMON.
RENIMON,
IT'S TIME TO GO.
RENIMON?
WHERE ARE YOU?
GET OUT HERE NOW.
IMPMON?
A NEW PLAYER FOR THE GAME.
WELL, I'M IN.
LOOK, I'M NOT A SLAVE.
REIKA HAPPENS TO BE MY PARTNER.
WELL, YOUR PARTNER'S
NOT THAT IMPRESSIVE.
EVEN SO,
SHE'S GOT YOU BELIEVING
THAT YOU CAN'T DO ANYTHING
FOR YOURSELF.
IT'S THE MOST PATHETIC THING
I'VE EVER SEEN.
ALL YOU DIGISLAVES
ARE THE SAME.
DEEP DOWN, YOU WANT TO BE
JUST LIKE ME.
I MEAN, AFTER ALL, WHO
WOULDN'T WANT TO BE LIKE ME?
HANDSOME AND FREE
LIKE A BIRD IN A TREE.
BA-BOOM!
HELLO? THIS IS
CLASS "A" MATERIAL, HONEY.
ANYWAYS, LIKE I WAS SAYING,
I THINK YOU'RE REALLY SAD,
AND YOU KNOW
WHAT THAT MAKES ME, HUH?
ANGRY, THAT'S WHAT,
AND ANGER'S NOT GOOD FOR ME.
TO SEE A GOOD-LOOKING DIGIMON
LIKE YOU GOING TO WASTE
MAKES ME WANT TO THROW UP!
WHY DO YOU THINK
I'M SAD?
WHY? I MEAN,
LOOK AT YOU --
OUT HERE ALL ALONE,
MOPING AROUND IN THE MOONLIGHT
LIKE A PUPPY
THAT CHEWED UP A SLIPPER
AND GOT TOSSED
OUT OF THE HOUSE.
HA HA. YOU'RE
IN SERIOUS DENIAL, LADY.
THERE'S A WHOLE WORLD OUT THERE.
ACTUALLY, A COUPLE OF THEM,
BUT IF YOU'RE HAPPY
FETCHING BONES FOR SOME HUMAN,
THEN BE MY GUEST.
IF THAT'S YOUR BEST MATERIAL,
THEN YOU NEED A NEW WRITER.
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
THAT WAS RUDE, YOU KNOW.
DIDN'T YOUR LITTLE HUMAN
TEACH YOU MANNERS, HUH?
APPARENTLY NOT.
WELL, MAYBE
I CAN TEACH HER SOMETHING.
IN TODAY'S LESSON,
WE'LL BEGIN WITH TOUGH LOVE.
BADA-BOOM!
HUH? UHH!
HEY, TAKE IT FROM ME,
TOOTS.
YOU GOT TO QUIT BEING STUPID
TO REALLY BE FREE.
GET AWAY FROM THAT HUMAN
IMMEDIATELY.
HA HA! BA-BOOM!
A DIGITAL FIELD.
HUH?
LOOKS LIKE A WILD ONE.
THEY JUST NEVER LEARN,
DO THEY?
ESTABLISHING TRACER LOCK
NOW.
EXCELLENT.
SIR, IT'S BIO-EMERGING.
[ PANTING ]
I WONDER IF RENIMON IS
ALREADY HERE.
WHAT'S WITH THE WEBS?
REIKA, RUN!
HUH?
WATCH OUT.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH, I'M FINE.
PERFECT. I WAS JUST THINKING
ABOUT WHAT TO DO FOR DINNER.
EAT DIRT.
OOH, YOU'RE SPICY, TOO.
DOKUGUMON --
WHOA, CHAMPION LEVEL.
FINALLY,
WE'VE A WORTHY OPPONENT.
WITH HER POISON THREAD ATTACK,
THIS SPIDER'S AS DEADLY
AS SHE IS UGLY.
THEN I BETTER STEP ON HER.
DIAMOND STORM! AAH!
POISON THREAD!
VENOM BLAST!
UHH! AAH!
RENIMON, DON'T GIVE UP.
REIKA, GET OUT OF HERE.
POISON THREAD!
REIKA!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ ROARS ]
[ GROWLS ]
DIAMOND STORM!
RENIMON,
YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
THINK AGAIN, CUPCAKE.
REIKA,
GET OUT OF HERE NOW!
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMODIFY!
SNIMON TWIN SICKLES
ACTIVATE!
TIME TO CUT LOOSE. UHH!
WHAT?
TWIN SICKLES!
UHH! AAH!
NOW IT'S MY TURN.
AAH!
LEAVE HER ALONE.
MY PLEASURE.
REIKA, SAVE YOURSELF.
VENOM BLAST!
UHH!
NO!
OH, RENIMON,
WHY'D YOU DO IT?
BECAUSE YOU'RE
MY PARTNER. UHH.
I'M SO SORRY.
RENIMON?
GAME OVER?
REIKA, GET AWAY
WHILE YOU CAN.
DON'T GO AWAY.
PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME.
I HAVE TO.
PLEASE GO. OHH...
WAIT. YOU CAN'T.
RENIMON!
[ BEEPING ]
UHH.
DIGIVOLUTION.
RENIMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
DIGIMON,
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON
CUBIMON.
YOU DID IT, BUT HOW?
IT WAS YOU, REIKA.
YOU MADE ME DIGIVOLVE.
GAME TIME.
LET'S PLAY.
POISON THREAD!
PAYBACK TIME.
FOX TAIL INFERNO!
NOT SO FAST, HOTSHOT.
STEP INTO MY PARLOR.
DRAGON WHEEL!
AAH!
OH, UNBELIEVABLE.
REIKA,
NOW DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
MM-HMM. I THINK I DO.
I COULDN'T DIGIVOLVE
UNTIL YOU REALLY CARED
ABOUT ME, REIKA.
OH.
OH, YUCK.
TIME FOR ME TO FLY
BEFORE I LOSE MY LUNCH.
THAT WAS
SOME VICTORY, HUH?
IT'S NOT
ABOUT WINNING, REIKA.
BUT WINNING
MADE YOU STRONGER.
NO, YOU MADE ME STRONGER.
YOU WEREN'T AFRAID TO SHOW
HOW MUCH YOU CARED ABOUT ME
LIKE A TRUE FRIEND.
HMM. I SEE.
DO ME A FAVOR?
DON'T TELL ANYONE.
WHOA. DOES THIS MEAN
REIKA ACTUALLY HAS A SOFT SIDE?
FIND OUT FOR YOURSELF
ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."