SO IT TURNS OUT
THE D-REAPER WAS DOING
SOME MAJOR DAMAGE
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD
AND THE REAL WORLD
WHEN ALL OF A SUDDEN,
IT EVOLVED AGAIN,
AND THE TAMERS SAW THAT
BEELZEMON WAS TRAPPED INSIDE
THE BIG BLOB'S BRAIN.
GALLANTMON USED GRANI
AND HIS NEWLY INSTALLED
YUGGOTH BLASTER
TO BREAK DOWN
THE D-REAPER'S DEFENSES.
MEANWHILE, BEELZEMON FINALLY
WOKE UP AND BUSTED LOOSE.
HE USED LEOMON'S
FIST OF THE BEAST KING
TO CRACK THE SPHERE.
LEOMON JUST FROZE JERI
IN HER TRACKS.
THEN THE D-REAPER TOOK AIM
AND LET BEELZEMON HAVE IT.
AW, GEE, THAT'S GOTTA HURT!
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
♪ WORLD
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMODIFY
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
[ SCREAMING ]
Sakuyamon: WHAT'S HE DOING?
WHY ISN'T HE PULLING UP?
IS HE CRAZY?
Gallantmon:
WELL, IT IS BEELZEMON.
WE HAVE TO DO SOMETHING.
BEELZEMON, YOU'VE GOT TO
PULL UP BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE!
WE'LL GET HIM.
BEFORE IT GETS US!
AAH!
SORRY, JERI.
I FAILED!
I DON'T LOOK
TOO COOL NOW.
BEELZEMON, HOLD ON!
NO, HE'S DONE FOR!
BEELZEMON!
DON'T GIVE UP!
YOU CAN MAKE IT!
Man on TV: AND ONE OF THEM
SEEMS TO BE DISSOLVING.
IS THIS THE END
OF THE DIGIMON?
Gallantmon: BEELZEMON,
TRY HARDER! YOU CAN DO IT!
EASY FOR YOU TO SAY,
PINEAPPLE HEAD.
FORGET ABOUT ME!
JUST SAVE JERI!
OH, BEELZEMON,
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
NO, THAT'S NOT TRUE!
JERI! AAH!
IS HE...GONE?
BEELZEMON, NO!
HOW MANY MORE FRIENDS ARE WE
GOING TO LOSE TO THIS THING?
THAT'S IT?
HE'S REALLY GONE?
IN THE END,
HE WAS A TRUE FRIEND.
AAH!
THAT'S IT, D-REAPER!
NO MORE!
HUH?
LOOK!
I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
THANK YOU, GRANI.
HE'S OKAY.
WEAK, BUT OKAY.
IT'S ABOUT TIME WE CAN BE
THANKFUL FOR SOMETHING.
NOW, LET'S GO GET JERI.
ARE YOU WITH US?
WITHOUT A DOUBT.
YEAH!
AS LONG AS WE DON'T PLAN
ON TAKING DIVING LESSONS
FROM BEELZEMON.
Yamaki: TAKATO,
GET OUT OF THERE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WHY?
WE'RE GETTING WORD
THAT THE GLOBAL TASK FORCES
ARE ABOUT TO ATTACK.
THE PLANES ARE ONLY A MINUTE
AWAY AND CLOSING FAST.
I'LL TRY TO RAISE THEM
ON THE RADIO.
THEY'RE NOT RESPONDING TO ANY
OF MY TRANSMISSIONS.
GET THEM OUT!
TAKATO, LISTEN TO ME.
THE PLANES ARE HEADED YOUR WAY,
AND WE CAN'T REACH THEM.
IF YOU'RE NOT OUT OF THERE
IN LESS THAN A MINUTE,
YOU WON'T HAVE A PRAYER.
Guilmon: TAKATO...
NO WAY! WE CAN'T LEAVE!
WHAT? WHY NOT?
JERI'S IN THERE!
THAT'S WHY NOT!
SHE'S TRAPPED INSIDE
THE D-REAPER,
IN THAT KERNEL THING!
DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN GET TO HER?
NO! THEY HAVE GOT TO GET OUT
OF THERE RIGHT NOW
IF YOU CAN'T STOP
THOSE PLANES!
THERE'S NO TIME.
THEY'RE ONLY 30 SECONDS AWAY!
HUH?
TAKATO, YOU HAVE GOT TO GET
OUT OF THERE IMMEDIATELY.
WE CAN'T. I'M NOT
LEAVING ANYONE BEHIND.
MAYBE WE CAN STOP THE BOMBS
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE!
THAT IS NOT AN OPTION!
YOU'RE THE ONLY HOPE
WE HAVE.
WE CAN'T RISK LOSING YOU.
NOW FALL BACK!
ALL RIGHT.
SPLIT UP, GUYS.
LET'S SEE WHAT THE TASK FORCE
HAS IN MIND.
I HOPE THIS ISN'T
A MISTAKE.
Pilot:
APPROACHING THE TARGET.
BIRDS WILL BE IN RANGE
IN 20 SECONDS.
READY THE PAYLOAD.
ROGER! YOU MAY ACTIVATE
WHEN IN RANGE.
I DON'T GET IT. THEY KNOW
NORMAL WEAPONS WON'T WORK.
15 SECONDS...
HUH?
MAYBE THE TASK FORCE
IS PLANNING ON USING
SOMETHING OTHER THAN
NORMAL EXPLOSIVES.
DOLPHIN'S RIGHT. I DOUBT
THEY WOULD USE STEALTH PLANES
TO DELIVER
A REGULAR BOMB.
SO ARE THE KIDS
STILL IN DANGER?
I DON'T KNOW.
WELL, WHATEVER IT IS,
WE'RE ABOUT TO FIND OUT.
HERE THEY COME!
Pilot: PAYLOAD AWAY.
DROP WAS SUCCESSFUL.
DEVICES ARE ACTIVE.
WELL, THEY DON'T SEEM
TO BE DOING MUCH,
UNLESS THOSE PULSES
ARE SOME KIND OF LASER BLAST.
MAYBE THEY THINK THE D-REAPER'S
DEFENSES ARE WEAKER
ON THE INSIDE.
MY MONITOR'S GOING HAYWIRE.
OF COURSE, THAT'S IT!
I BET THE PLANES
DROPPED A JAMMING DEVICE.
IT'S A MACHINE THAT SENDS OUT
MAGNETIC WAVES
TO DISRUPT THE D-REAPER'S
COMMUNICATIONS NETWORK.
MM-HMM.
Man: WELL, DID IT WORK? HOPE WE
DIDN'T GIVE Y'ALL A SCARE.
IS THAT REALLY YOU,
JOHNNY?
IT'S ME, ALL RIGHT.
I'M WORKING WITH THE GLOBAL
TASK FORCE ON THIS.
AS I LIVE AND BREATHE,
WHICH IS A SURPRISE ITSELF,
IT'S JOHNNY!
WE LOST HIM.
THOSE MAGNETIC PULSES
ARE INTERFERING
WITH THE TRANSMISSION.
I ONLY HOPE IT'S HAVING
THE SAME EFFECT ON THE D-REAPER.
JERI...
DON'T TALK.
SAVE YOUR STRENGTH.
YEAH, WE'LL BLAST THIS THING
TO DIGITAL BITS!
RIGHT! LET'S DO IT!
I HATE THIS, I HATE THIS,
I HATE THIS!
JUST LET ME OUT!
I HATE THIS.
[ SOBBING ]
I CAN'T TAKE THIS
ANYMORE.
IT'S CURIOUS
WHY EMOTIONS EVER EVOLVED.
SUCH AN OBSTRUCTION TO LOGIC,
AN EVOLUTIONARY STEP
BACKWARD.
WHAT YOU CALL COMPASSION
ONLY BINDS YOU TO OTHERS
WHO CAN MAKE YOU WEAK.
STOP IT! STOP TALKING
IN MY VOICE!
AAH! AAH!
WHOA!
YOUR FEELINGS OF DESPAIR
ARE PROVIDING THE D-REAPER
ALL THE ENERGY IT NEEDS.
NO! STOP!
TAKATO!
HELP ME!
AAH!
[ Thinking ] YOU KNOW,
WHEN IT LOOKS LIKE
I'M HURTING IT,
I'M HELPING IT.
WHAT IF I JUST CAUSED
THE WHOLE WORLD TO BE ERASED?
WHAT IS THAT?
I'M GETTING
MASSIVE ENERGY SPIKES!
ITS HEAT OUTPUT
IS UP OVER 200%!
AND I'M NOT READING
THE MAGNETIC PULSES ANYMORE!
FIND OUT WHAT'S HAPPENING
RIGHT NOW!
COME ON, JERI!
YOU'VE GOT TO HELP ME!
YOU DO REMEMBER WHAT
HELPING IS, DON'T YOU?
THAT'S NOT IT!
NEITHER IS THAT!
THIS IS MY FAULT.
THE WORLD WOULD BE BETTER OFF
WITHOUT ME.
DON'T SAY THAT!
NO! NO! AAH!
JERI, YOU HAVE TO STOP!
THE D-REAPER
WILL KEEP FEEDING ON YOU
UNTIL YOU'RE ALL
DOUBLED UP!
DID I JUST HEAR JERI?
JERI! HOLD ON!
IT IS TOO LATE FOR YOUR FRIENDS
TO HELP YOU, JERI.
I NOW HAVE THE ENERGY
TO EVOLVE EVEN FURTHER!
HEH HEH HEH HEH!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT'S IT DOING?
I DON'T KNOW!
OH, COME ON!
WHEN DO WE EVER KNOW?
BE READY FOR ANYTHING!
WE'VE GOT TO GET TO JERI
BEFORE IT'S...
TOO LATE. NO!
JERI!
WHAT NOW?
HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO FEED IT
IF IT KEEPS CHANGING?
OH, MAN,
THAT THING IS HUGE!
THE MINUTE WE GET USED
TO ONE FORM,
THE D-REAPER BECOMES ANOTHER,
MORE POWERFUL THAN THE LAST.
ARE WE EVER GOING
TO GET A BREAK?
THIS JUST
CAN'T BE HAPPENING!
I'M AFRAID TO FIND OUT
WHAT THAT THING CAN DO!
I BET WE FIND OUT,
WHETHER YOU'RE AFRAID
OR NOT!
LOOK OUT!
[ GASPS ]
OH, GREAT, SOMETHING ELSE
TO FIGURE OUT.
WELL, NO MATTER WHAT IT IS
OR HOW DANGEROUS IT IS,
WE CAN'T GIVE UP ON TRYING
TO SAVE JERI.
NOW LET'S GO GET HER!
Guilmon: UM...
WHAT'S WRONG, GUILMON?
EVEN AT MEGA-LEVEL,
IF WE GO IN THERE,
WE'LL LOSE OUR POWER,
REMEMBER?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT WE CAN DO, TAKATO.
I FORGOT ALL ABOUT THAT.
IT'S NOT WHAT ANY OF US
WANT, TAKATO,
BUT WE'VE GOT TO PULL BACK
AND FIGURE OUT
A PLAN OF ATTACK.
WE CAN'T AFFORD TO, YOU KNOW,
LOSE ANY MORE OF US.
NO-O-O!
Henry: BELIEVE ME, TAKATO,
I FEEL THE SAME WAY,
BUT WE DON'T HAVE
ANY OTHER CHOICE!
THAT THING'S
JUST TOO POWERFUL.
IF WE GO AFTER IT
WITHOUT ANY IDEA
OF WHAT WE'RE UP AGAINST,
WE COULD SACRIFICE
THE WORLD'S ONLY CHANCE
OF SURVIVAL -- US!
Takato:
I KNOW WE NEED A PLAN,
BUT IT SURE FEELS LIKE
WE'RE JUST...GIVING UP.
Babel: RUSHING IN RIGHT NOW
WOULD BE SUICIDE.
DON'T WORRY, TAKATO.
WE'RE WORKING ON A PLAN,
BUT WE NEED TIME
TO PUT IT
INTO ACTION.
BUT JERI
IS STILL OUT THERE!
I JUST KNOW SHE IS!
WE'VE GOT TO GET IN THERE
AND SAVE HER
BEFORE IT REALLY IS TOO LATE!
WE'LL GET TO HER, TAKATO,
AS LONG AS WE STILL CAN.
YOU HAVE TO LEAVE THIS
TO US NOW.
AT THIS STAGE,
WE JUST DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
OH...
Takato: [ Thinking ]
I FEEL LIKE SUCH A COWARD,
BUT I GUESS IT'S OUT
OF MY HANDS NOW.
OH...
STILL, I JUST HAVE TO FIND A WAY
TO GET JERI BACK.
YOU KNOW, GUILMON,
EVEN SOMEPLACE
AS BEAUTIFUL AS THIS
ISN'T VERY RESTFUL
IF YOU'RE ANXIOUS INSIDE.
YEAH...
[ BOTH SIGH ]
Boy: TAKATO! YO, TAKATO!
HEY, TAKATO,
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME.
KAI, WHAT'S UP?
WHEN DID YOU GET HERE?
JUST NOW.
MAN, THE OCEAN SURE IS
RIGHTEOUS HERE!
YEAH, GUILMON AND I WERE JUST
TALKING ABOUT HOW...
RIGHTEOUS IT IS.
RIKA, HONEY,
STOP FIDGETING.
YOU'D THINK A FANCY PLACE
LIKE THIS
COULD AFFORD CUSHIONS
FOR THE STUPID SEATS.
I HEARD THAT,
YOU KNOW.
GOOD.
RIKA...
WHAT?
I DON'T THINK I CAN JUST
SIT HERE LIKE THIS.
I KNOW, RENAMON, BUT THERE'S
NOTHING WE CAN DO RIGHT NOW.
SO, RENAMON,
YOU'RE A GIRL, RIGHT?
ACTUALLY, DIGIMON AREN'T
DIVIDED INTO GENDERS.
BUT ONLY A WOMAN COULD WEAR FUR
THAT WELL.
EITHER WAY, YOU'RE STILL PART
OF OUR FAMILY.
RIKA.
MM-HMM.
I KNOW THIS ISN'T THE WAY
YOU'D LIKE THINGS TO BE,
BUT I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT
TO SPEND TIME
AS A FAMILY RIGHT NOW,
OKAY?
[ Thinking ] BUT I CAN'T STOP
THINKING ABOUT JERI.
SO, KAI, HOW COME
YOU'RE HERE, ANYWAY?
HEY, I COULDN'T JUST STAY
IN OKINAWA
WHEN MY COUSIN WAS DUKING IT
OUT WITH THAT THING.
BESIDES, HAVE YOU SEEN
THIS FANTASTIC VIEW? PRIMO.
MM-HMM.
CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
SURE.
YOU GUYS ARE, LIKE, OUT THERE
TO SAVE THE WORLD OR SOMETHING,
HUH?
WELL, I GUESS SO, BUT I REALLY
JUST WANT TO STOP THE D-REAPER
FROM HURTING MORE PEOPLE...
PEOPLE LIKE JERI.
YOU LIKE HER,
DON'T YOU?
WHAT?
SHE'S YOUR FIRST LOVE,
DUDE.
I DON'T --
I MEAN, UH...
GO ON, ADMIT IT!
YEAH, OKAY,
I GUESS I LIKE HER.
I MEAN, I DO.
THAT'S WHY
YOU'RE IN SO MUCH PAIN.
SHE'S A PART OF YOU.
DOES IT EVER GET
ANY BETTER, KAI?
I MEAN, I DON'T KNOW
IF I CAN TAKE ALL THIS.
WHAT IF SHE REALLY IS GONE?
JERI, YOU'VE GOT TO AT LEAST
TRY TO FEEL BETTER.
IF YOU KEEP GETTING DOWN
ON YOURSELF,
EVERYTHING'S ONLY GOING
TO GET WORSE.
THIS ISN'T YOUR FAULT, YOU KNOW.
IT'S THE D-REAPER.
BUT IT PICKED ME,
DIDN'T IT?
YOUR SELF'S
JUST FEELING SORRY.
YOU GOT TO LOOK ON THE BRIGHT
SIDE OF THINGS, JERI.
THINK ABOUT ALL THE GOOD STUFF
IN YOUR LIFE,
LIKE GREAT FRIENDS LIKE ME.
DON'T YOU WANT
TO BE HAPPY AGAIN?
DO I DESERVE TO BE,
CALUMON?
WHAT IF ALL MY GREAT FRIENDS
GET ERASED BECAUSE OF ME?
WHAT THEN?
AW, JERI, JUST THINK
HOW HAPPY YOU COULD BE
IF YOU DIDN'T WORK SO HARD
TO MAKE YOURSELF SO SAD.
Woman: WE GOT JOHNNY BACK
ON THE LINE.
SO, WHAT'S THE NEWS,
JOHNNY?
IT'S NOT GOOD, DOLPHIN.
THE D-REAPER'S BEGUN EXPANDING
IN OTHER COUNTRIES,
AS WELL.
THE MAGNETIC DISRUPTERS
HAVE BEEN DISRUPTED THEMSELVES,
AND OUR SATELLITE COMMUNICATIONS
AREN'T GOING TO LAST
MUCH LONGER
FROM THE LOOKS OF THINGS.
SO, WHAT'S THE BAD NEWS?
ACTUALLY, THERE ISSOME
GOOD NEWS.
A SENSOR
INSIDE THE D-REAPER'S FIELD
IS STILL SENDING BACK DATA.
REALLY?
EVEN THOUGH MOST
OF THE SENSORS WERE DELETED,
THERE WERE STILL A FEW
THAT REMAINED HIDDEN
AMONG THE BUILDINGS.
WE WERE JUST LUCKY
THE D-REAPER HADN'T FOUND THEM
AND TAKEN THEM OUT.
ANYWAY, THE DATA THEY'VE BEEN
SENDING BACK IS PRETTY STRANGE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
JOHNNY?
AT FIRST, WE THOUGHT THE SENSOR
HAD MALFUNCTIONED.
THEN WE REALIZED
THAT THE D-REAPER ZONE
IS ESSENTIALLY AN EVENLY
DISTRIBUTED REGION OF ENERGY.
THE WEAK AND STRONG FORCES
ARE IN COMPLETE BALANCE
WITH EACH OTHER,
AND THIS IS THE KICKER --
THE PARTICLES INSIDE
ARE TRAVELING AT A RATE --
WAIT, LET ME GUESS.
AT A RATE FASTER
THAN THE SPEED OF LIGHT?
IT'S A QUANTUM BUBBLE!
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN THE MONSTER
MAKERS WOULD FIGURE IT OUT!
WELL, AS FAST
AS THIS THING EVOLVES,
IT WAS THE ONLY NATURAL
CONCLUSION.
I THINK THIS MAY BE THE KEY
TO DESTROYING THAT THING.
IF WE COULD MAKE A TINY BIG BANG
WITHIN THE D-REAPER,
THE ENSUING BLACK HOLE
WOULD SUCK THAT THING OUT
LIKE A VACUUM CLEANER.
YEAH, EASIER SAID
THAN DONE, MY FRIEND.
BUT WHAT THE HECK?
I'M IN THE MOOD
FOR A LITTLE SPRING CLEANING.
HOW ABOUT YOU, CURLY?
I'M ALREADY WAY AHEAD
OF YOU.
MAN, YOU ARE TOO GOOD.
LET'S JUST HOPE THE D-REAPER
IS AS EASILY IMPRESSED
AS YOU.
THIS VORTEX SHOULD REVERT
THE D-REAPER
TO ITS ORIGINAL FORM.
GOOD WORK. BUT WE JUST HAVE
TO BE CAREFUL
THAT IT DOESN'T
DRAWUSIN, TOO.
I GUESS I'LL LEAVE YOU GUYS
TO YOUR WORK.
GOOD LUCK WITH EVERYTHING.
THANKS, JOHNNY.
I KNEW THIS WAS GOING
TO HAPPEN.
WATCH OUT
FOR THE MAELSTROM.
HEY, WAIT!
AREN'T YOU GOING TO STAY
AND HELP US?
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL HELP IN MY OWN WAY.
NOW, DON'T GO DISAPPEARING.
OH, WAIT, THAT'S WHAT I DO.
HA HA HA HA!
WHOO!
AAH!
IT'S HER FAULT.
EVERYTHING IS
ALL JERI'S FAULT.
IF JERI WASN'T AROUND
ANYMORE,
NO MORE BAD STUFF
WOULD HAPPEN.
NOBODY ELSE WOULD EVER
GET HURT,
ESPECIALLY NOT TAKATO.
JERI, PLEASE, YOU'VE GOT
TO SNAP OUT OF THIS.
IF YOU DON'T FIGHT BACK,
THE D-REAPER REALLY WILL WIN.
THE D-REAPER HAS ALREADY WON,
FOOLISH DIGIMON.
THE BEING CALLED JERI
HAS TAUGHT THE D-REAPER
EVERYTHING IT NEEDS TO KNOW
ABOUT HUMANS.
NOTHING THEY HAVE
CAN BEAT THE D-REAPER.
NOTHING.
Janyu:
DON'T WORRY, TERRIERMON,
THIS WILL BE OVER
BEFORE YOU KNOW IT.
MOMENTIE.
HEY, DAD, WHY ARE YOU
SCANNING TERRIERMON?
I NEED TO GET AN IDEA
OF THE COMPOSITIONAL
DIFFERENCES BETWEEN DIGIMON
AND THE D-REAPER,
SO WE CAN FIGURE OUT
HOW TO TARGET IT.
MY HAIR FEELS
REALLY FUNNY.
SORRY. I'LL REDUCE
THE SCANNER'S INTENSITY.
HUH?
D-Reaper: SOON THE NETWORK
WILL BE COMPLETED,
AND THE DESTRUCTION
OF THIS WORLD
WILL TRULY BEGIN!
THE D-REAPERS
FROM ALL OVER THE WORLD
ARE JOINING TOGETHER
TO FORM ONE BEING!
AND THAT'S NOT ALL.
ITS TEMPERATURE'S INCREASING.
IT'S SO BIG. IF THAT THING
GETS ANY HOTTER,
IT COULD CHANGE THE TEMPERATURE
OF THE ENTIRE PLANET.
THE POLAR ICE CAPS WOULD MELT
AND FLOOD MOST OF THE EARTH
IN A MATTER OF DAYS!
HENRY...
IT'S UP TO US.
IT'S TIME TO GO!
NO!
DON'T LISTEN
TO THAT RAG!
DON'T YOU KNOW
HOW LUCKY YOU ARE?
EVERYBODY LOVES TO SEE
YOU SMILING, JERI --
TAKATO, GUILMON,
ESPECIALLY ME.
IT'S TRUE.
CALUMON -- AAH!
OH!
NO!
NO! CALUMON!
TAKATO, TAKATO!
HELP ME!
JERI, NO.
WH-WHAT'S WRONG?
TAKATO, WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I HEARD JERI.
GUILMON, SHE NEEDS US NOW!
THERE'S KAI. WHY DIDN'T YOU WAIT
AT THE TRAIN STATION?
HEY, TAKATO, ARE YOU OKAY?
WHAT'S WRONG, BUDDY?
HONEY?
Man: HENRY?
MR. MIZUNO.
I'VE GOT SOMETHING
FOR YOU.
I PUT AN ALGORITHM ON THIS CARD
THAT MAY GIVE YOU AND THE OTHERS
THE EDGE YOU NEED
OVER THE D-REAPER.
I JUST KNEW
YOU'D COME THROUGH.
HENRY'S CALLING.
IT'S TIME FOR US
TO GO, RENAMON.
I KNOW.
I'M SORRY, GRANDMA AND MOM.
THAT'S HENRY.
SO YOU'RE GOING BACK
TO FIGHT, ARE YOU?
I'M SORRY. I HAVE TO.
THE WHOLE WORLD
IS DEPENDING ON US.
IT'S JUST SO DANGEROUS,
SON.
Janyu: YOU'RE LEAVING,
HENRY? I...
I'M COMING BACK, DAD.
SEE YOU LATER!
YEAH...
BE CAREFUL.
BIOMERGE, ACTIVATE!
RENAMON, BIOMERGE TO...
SAKUYAMON!
AND THIS TIME
THERE'S NO STOPPING US.
THERE CAN'T BE.
I JUST WANTED TO SAY
I LOVE YOU.
WE WISH YOU DIDN'T HAVE
TO FIGHT, BUT WE UNDERSTAND,
AND WE'RE PROUD
THAT YOU'RE OUR SON.
DON'T WORRY.
WE'LL BE BACK SOON,
I PROMISE.
OH, GUILMON.
YOU'RE EVERYTHING TO US,
TAKATO.
PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
I WILL, MOM.
I PROMISE.
COME ON, GUILMON,
LET'S GO!
TAKATO!
YOU CAN DO IT!
HA HA HA HA!
GEE, I MUST HAVE SOMETHING
IN MY EYE...
TO FIND OUT IF THEY CAN SAVE
JERI AND THE WORLD,
TUNE IN TO THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."