TAKATO HAD TO FIGURE OUT
A WAY TO GET GROWLMON
TO DE-DIGIVOLVE
BACK INTO GUILMON.
HE TRIED EVERYTHING
FROM EXERCISE TO WISHING,
BUT NOTHING WORKED.
HE AND HENRY DECIDED
TO HIDE GROWLMON
IN THAT CREEPY TUNNEL
UNDER THE CITY.
BUT IMPMON ATTACKED
AND FORCED HIM
BACK INTO THE PARK.
RUNNING OUT OF IDEAS FAST,
THE GUYS THOUGHT
PAINTING GROWLMON
MIGHT DO THE TRICK.
BUT WHEN IT STARTED TO RAIN,
IT LOOKED LIKE
THE BIG GUY WOULD STAY
THAT WAY FOREVER.
IN THE END, TAKATO WAS
THE ONLY ONE
WHO COULD BRING GUILMON BACK.
MAN, FRIENDSHIP
IS A POWERFUL THING.
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON ♪
♪ DI-DI-DI
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
♪ WORLD
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ DIGIMODIFIED
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON
IT'S A WILD ONE, BUT I'VE
NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE IT.
IT'S TRYING TO BIOMERGE.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT'S BRINGING ALONG,
BUT IT'S BIGGER
THAN A BREAD BOX.
UNBELIEVABLE.
OH!
SIR, IT SUCCEEDED.
[ Thinking ]
DIGIVOLVING.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND IT.
GUILMON!
GUILMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON
GROWLMON!
I'VE SEEN HAMSTERS WITH MORE
BATTLE EXPERIENCE
THAN GUILMON, BUT, STILL,
HE COULD DIGIVOLVE.
AND SO COULD THAT
WEENIE LITTLE RABBIT.
NO!
TERRIERMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DI-DI-DIGIMON
GARGOMON!
AND WHEN IT HAPPENED
TO RENAMON...
PLEASE, NO.
RENAMON!
RENAMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON
CUBIMON!
IT'S WHAT I'VE WANTED
FOR THE LONGEST TIME.
I SHOULD BE SATISFIED.
STILL...
[ THUNDER CRASHES ]
I FEEL LIKE THERE'S SOMETHING
I'M MISSING.
[ GASPS ]
WHAT WAS THAT?
[ Thinking ] THAT'S WEIRD.
I COULD HAVE SWORN
I FELT SOMETHING.
[ GASPS ]
HI! HA HA HA.
[ GROANS ]
SOME DIGIMON
ARE SO STUPID, IT HURTS.
THEY HANG OUT
WITH HUMANS SO MUCH
THEY START ACTING LIKE THEM.
IT MAKES MY FUR STAND.
HAVE THEY NO PRIDE?
I DON'T HAVE ANY FOOD.
SO WHY ARE YOU FOLLOWING ME?
WANT TO PLAY?
HUH?
HERE I GO!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
ESKIMO KISSES!
REIKA!
[ GASPS ]
[ LAUGHTER ]
[ CROWD MURMURING ]
HI.
MOM, WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
WHAT A DAY! UGH!
WE HAD A PHOTO SHOOT,
BUT BEFORE WE COULD START,
ALL THESE PEOPLE SHOWED UP
WANTING MY AUTOGRAPH,
ASKING ME THE SECRET
TO MY YOUTHFUL GOOD LOOKS.
THEY JUST WOULDN'T
LEAVE ME ALONE.
WE COULDN'T GET ANYTHING DONE
ALL DAY.
BEING FAMOUS AND POPULAR
CAN BE A PAIN IN THE NECK.
YOU ARE SO LUCKY YOU DON'T
KNOW HOW THAT FEELS.
YEAH, LUCKY ME.
WELL, GOT TO GO.
WAIT.
REIKA, I THINK YOUR TOY
IS JUST ADORABLE.
YOU HAD TO BE CUTE,
DIDN'T YOU?
BADA-BOOM!
AH, FIGHT BACK,
YOU COWARDS!
I GUESS MY FIREPOWER'S
JUST TOO MUCH FOR YOU, HUH?
I'LL HAVE TO WREAK HAVOC
ELSEWHERE.
LISTEN, YOU LITTLE SQUIRT.
I'M IMMUNE TO YOUR
OOTSY-CUTESY ACT,
SO SCRAM.
OH...
[ SOBBING ]
KEEP GOING, SHORTY.
[ GROWLING ]
RENAMON?
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
YOU CALLED?
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
WATCHING YOU
FROM OVER THERE.
OH.
YOU DON'T LOOK WELL.
REIKA, IS THERE SOMETHING
TROUBLING YOU?
NOTHING. I'M FINE.
HUH? OH.
HEY, FINE AND FOXY.
SO WE MEET AGAIN.
OH, IT'S JUST YOU.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, JUST ME?
COME BACK HERE!
OH, CHECK OUT
MISS HIGH AND MIGHTY.
MAYBE A GOOD FIGHT WILL KNOCK
HER OFF HER PERCH.
HEY, I HEARD TERRIERMON
CALL YOU A FAT-TAILED BULLY!
IF I WERE YOU, I'D TEACH THAT
EGG-SHAPED LOUDMOUTH A LESSON!
HUH.
WHAT? YOU'RE GOING TO LET
HIM GET AWAY WITH THAT?
TERRIERMON WON'T FIGHT.
WHY NOT?
HIS TAMER HAS FORBIDDEN IT.
HUH?
UGH. WHAT KIND OF DIGIMON
DOESN'T FIGHT?
THOSE ROTTEN HUMANS.
THEY'VE MADE HIM A PET --
A DIGIPOODLE.
BUT IF TERRIERMON
CAN'T FIGHT BACK,
I CAN WHUP HIS DOUGHY PATOOTIE
OR STEAL HIS LUNCH
AND GET AWAY
WITHOUT A SCRATCH.
THINK OF THE POSSIBILITIES.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT THIS DRESS
WITH THE LACE AND POOFY SLEEVES?
OR THIS ONE? TRY IT.
IT'LL MAKE YOU LOOK
MORE LIKE A GIRL.
AM I BEING PUNISHED
FOR SOMETHING?
I TOLD YOU BEFORE,
I CAN'T STAND
CUTE THINGS LIKE THIS.
UH, WELL, WHAT ABOUT
THAT STUFFED TOY
I SAW YOU HOLDING?
THAT WAS FOR A SCIENCE
PROJECT.
WE HAD TO MEASURE
THE EFFECTS OF GRAVITY
ON SMALL OBJECTS, SO I
THREW IT OFF A BRIDGE.
OH.
I'M OUT OF HERE.
WELL, I GUESS SHE'S STILL
INTO TOMBOY CHIC. HUH.
REIKA JUST HAS HER OWN STYLE,
THAT'S ALL.
HONESTLY, DEAR, THERE ARE
MORE IMPORTANT THINGS IN LIFE
THAN LOOKING PRETTY.
REALLY? LIKE WHAT?
HUH?
[ PANTING ]
RENAMON?
YES, REIKA?
GO AND SEE
WHAT'S OUT THERE, OKAY?
AS YOU WISH.
WELL, WHO WAS IT?
NO ONE.
DON'T LIE TO ME. I KNOW
SOMETHING'S OUT THERE.
WHAT'S THAT LOOK FOR?
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL DO EVERYTHING I CAN
TO PROTECT YOU.
YOU DON'T NEED
TO PROTECT ME.
I DON'T KNOW WHY YOU EVEN
SAY STUFF LIKE THAT.
BECAUSE, REIKA,
I'M YOUR PARTNER.
LET'S GET THIS STRAIGHT.
I DON'T BUY ALL THIS STUFF
ABOUT PARTNERS
AND FEELINGS.
UH...I DON'T NEED YOU.
I DON'T NEED ANYBODY.
OKAY, HERE WE GO.
DIGIMODIFY, ACTIVATE.
SO HOW'D I DO?
NOT BAD.
NOT BAD?
LET'S JUST WORK ON
STRATEGIES, OKAY?
HAVE YOU HEARD OF COMBOS?
SURE.
UH, I THINK I HAVE.
THAT'S WHEN YOU USE
TWO OR MORE CARDS
AT A TIME, RIGHT?
RIGHT. AND IF YOU USE THEM
IN SUCCESSION,
YOU CAN GET SOME PRETTY
POTENT RESULTS.
IT'S A GOOD THING
TO KEEP IN MIND.
YEAH, THAT AND THE OTHER
MILLION THINGS YOU'VE TOLD ME.
WELL, IF IT ISN'T
THE DUM-DUM CLUB.
Both: HMM?
DID YOU MISS ME, BOYS?
JUST IGNORE HIM.
EASY FOR YOU TO SAY.
YOU CAN'T SMELL HIM.
LET'S GO.
GUILMON, COME ON.
[ MUMBLES ]
I JUST WANT TO HAVE
A FRIENDLY FIGHT --
GIVE YOU ALL A NICE,
FRIENDLY BUTT KICKING.
[ Thinking ] RENAMON WAS RIGHT.
HE WON'T FIGHT.
WELL, HERE'S MY CHANCE TO BLAST
SOME SENSE INTO HIM.
HMM...
TERRIERMON,
DON'T TOUCH HIM.
I KNOW.
BADA-BOOM!
TERRIER TORNADO!
AHH!
AAH!
TERRIERMON, WHAT DID I
JUST TELL YOU?
I DIDN'T ACTUALLY
TOUCH HIM, YOU KNOW.
YOU ARE INCORRIGIBLE.
[ Thinking ]
TERRIERMON AND HIS TAMER --
THEIR RELATIONSHIP
IS SO DIFFERENT
FROM MINE AND REIKA'S.
I WONDER -- IF I ACTED
MORE HUMAN, WOULD SHE ACCEPT ME?
WOULD SHE FINALLY LET ME
GET CLOSE TO HER?
[ GASPS ]
[ SHIVERING ]
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
UH...
NOTHING.
HUH?
GET OUT OF THE WAY!
HEY, I SAW YOU, YOU CREEP!
NOW COME OUT!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
[ PANTING ]
[ GROWLING ]
[ MUFFLED SCREAMING ]
[ EVIL LAUGHTER ]
IT'S SO COLD.
HUH?
WELCOME
TO MY HUMBLE ABODE.
ARE YOU A DIGIMON?
YES.
SO THIS IS
A DIGITAL FIELD?
EXACTLY.
BEAUTIFUL, ISN'T IT?
IT SUITS YOU PERFECTLY.
IT SUITS ME?
THE WAY YOU TREAT PEOPLE,
HOW YOU THINK --
YOU'RE COLD AS ICE.
YOU HAVE NO TIME
FOR WARM WEAK RELATIONSHIPS.
YES.
YOU ALWAYS EXPECT PERFECTION
FROM YOURSELF AND OTHERS.
YOU DEMAND IT.
I AM THE ONLY ONE
WHO UNDERSTANDS YOU, REIKA.
THAT IS WHY WE'RE DESTINED
TO BECOME PARTNERS.
PARTNERS? US?
YES.
NO, I CAN'T.
I-I ALREADY HAVE A PARTNER.
RENAMON?
REIKA, WHERE ARE YOU?
I DON'T NEED YOU.
I DON'T NEED ANYBODY.
REIKA.
WHAT HAVE I DONE?
[ CLICK ]
I WANT
TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
WHAT IS IT?
TO PROVE I'M WORTHY
TO BE YOUR PARTNER,
I'VE SET UP
A LITTLE SHOW-AND-TELL
SO YOU CAN SEE MY POWER
FOR YOURSELF.
[ ALL TALKING ]
WHOA.
HEY, GUYS.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WAIT FOR ME.
FOR YEARS, I HAVE HUNTED
HUNDREDS OF DIGIMON
AND ABSORBED THEIR DATA.
THEY WERE FRIENDS TO SOME,
MAYBE EVEN PARTNERS.
UHH.
BUT AS YOU ONCE SAID,
THEY ARE MERELY
STEPPING STONES.
I NEVER SAID THAT.
AH, BUT YOU DID.
I FIGHT TO DIGIVOLVE.
YOU MAKE YOUR DIGIMON DO
THE EXACT SAME THING.
NO. I COULDN'T SEE IT
BEFORE,
BUT THERE'S MORE TO DIGIMON
THAN FIGHTING.
I WOULD EAT DIRT
BEFORE I'D EVER LET RENAMON
BECOME WHAT YOU ARE --
A MONSTER.
BETTER A POWERFUL MONSTER
THAN A WEAK NOBODY.
IS THAT WHAT YOU REALLY WANT --
TO BE A NOBODY?
I'LL TELL YOU
WHAT I DON'T WANT TO BE --
THE PARTNER
OF SOME FREAK-SHOW DIGIMON.
YOU THINK YOU KNOW EVERYTHING
ABOUT WHO I REALLY AM?
WELL, YOU DON'T.
SO JUST SPIT IT OUT, HORNHEAD.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
AH, YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW EXQUISITE YOU ARE
WHEN YOU'RE ANGRY.
I'VE BEEN SEARCHING SO LONG
FOR SOMEONE LIKE YOU
WITH A HEART OF ICE
AND A WILL OF STONE
AND NOW MY SEARCH IS OVER.
I WANT YOU TO BE MY TAMER.
IN YOUR DREAMS, PAL.
DON'T PLAY HARD TO GET.
YOU WANT TO BE
THE STRONGEST DIGIMON TAMER.
I WANT TO BE
THE STRONGEST DIGIMON.
WE'RE PERFECT
FOR EACH OTHER.
NEVER.
HMM. ARE YOU THINKING
OF THAT PITIFUL EXCUSE
FOR A DIGIMON OF YOURS?
RENAMON, IS IT?
YOU'VE NEVER SETTLED
FOR SECOND BEST BEFORE.
WHY START NOW? WHY
WASTE YOUR TIME WITH BEAUTY
WHEN YOU CAN TAME
THE BEAST?
BUT GO AHEAD --
SUMMON HER.
PERHAPS YOU PREFER
A LIVE DEMONSTRATION
OF WHO
THE SUPERIOR DIGIMON IS.
NO WAY.
THEN I'LL JUST HAVE TO
CALL HER MYSELF.
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
THIS IS IT. DOES ANYONE
HAVE ANY BRIGHT IDEAS?
JUST ONE -- LET'S TRY
NOT TO GET OURSELVES CREAMED.
WHO LEFT THE FREEZER ON?
LOOK. IT'S REIKA.
HUH?
HMM.
ICEDEVIMON. WHOA.
A CHAMPION FALLEN-ANGEL DIGIMON.
AND I THOUGHT
YOU DIDN'T HAVE ANY FRIENDS.
LET HER GO NOW.
MY NEW TAMER AND I WERE
JUST GETTING ACQUAINTED.
SHE'S NOT YOUR TAMER.
REIKA HAS RENAMON.
I THINK IT'S TIME
FOR A LITTLE UPGRADE, DON'T YOU?
LET ME GO,
YOU FROZEN FREAK.
WHAT DO WE DO?
THIS IS NOT GOING TO BE EASY.
HE'S MUCH STRONGER
THAN ANY DIGIMON
WE'VE EVER DEFEATED BEFORE.
WHAT WE REALLY NEED IS
AN EFFECTIVE STRATEGY
TO DEAL WITH HIM.
LIKE A KICK IN THE PANTS.
I WISH
IT WERE THAT EASY. HMM.
READY, GUILMON?
MM-HMM.
GO GET HIM.
READY, SET, AND GO.
HERE'S YOUR CHANCE,
TERRIERMON.
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
[ GRUNTING ]
GOODY, GOODY.
TIME TO FIGHT.
GUILMON, NO!
TERRIERMON!
[ DEVILISH LAUGHTER ]
THIS DOESN'T LOOK GOOD,
NOT GOOD AT ALL.
GOT TO...GET THEM...
OUT OF THERE.
I HEAR ONE BECOMES QUITE WARM
JUST BEFORE FREEZING.
YOU'RE SO TWISTED,
IT'S SCARY.
DIGIMODIFY!
KEY ACTIVATE!
UHH.
UHH...UHH...
I DON'T GET IT.
WHERE'S RENAMON?
[ DEVILISH LAUGHTER ]
RENAMON'S GONE.
I DON'T NEED YOU.
I DON'T NEED ANYBODY.
EVEN IF I CALLED HER,
SHE WOULDN'T COME.
BUT, REIKA, WHY NOT?
COME ON, REIKA. FESS UP.
DID YOU TWO HAVE A FIGHT?
IT JUST PROVES
SHE'S TOO WEAK
TO HANDLE
A SPECIAL TAMER LIKE YOU.
YOU NEED A PARTNER
WHO UNDERSTANDS YOU,
WHO APPRECIATES YOU,
AND WHO CRAVES
YOUR COLD STRENGTH.
[ QUIVERS ]
EMBRACE
THE FUTURE I OFFER YOU.
[ Gasps ] RENAMON?
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
AH, THE INFAMOUS RENAMON.
I'D LOVE TO SIT AND CHAT,
BUT I HAVE TO DESTROY YOU.
NO.
DIAMOND ST--
AAH!
FROZEN CLAW!
UHH.
AAH!
DIAMOND STORM!
FROZEN CLAW!
UHH!
UHH.
REIKA,
SHE HAS TO DIGIVOLVE NOW.
[ Thinking ]
I CAN'T LET HER DIGIVOLVE.
SHE MIGHT END UP
LIKE ICEDEVIMON.
UHH.
[ Thinking ] FORGIVE ME.
WHY DO YOU LOOK AT HER
LIKE THAT?
A DIGIMON IS ONLY USEFUL
IF IT CAN FIGHT.
TELL ME. WHY DO YOU CARE
FOR THIS PATHETIC CREATURE?
SHE'S MY FRIEND.
I CARE
BECAUSE RENAMON'S MY FRIEND.
[ BEEPING ]
OH!
DIGIVOLUTION.
RENAMON, DIGIVOLVE TO...
♪ DIGIMON,
DIGITAL MONSTERS ♪
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGI-DIGIMON
CUBIMON!
WHY DID YOU DIGIVOLVE?
FOX TAIL INFERNO!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING, FROSTY?
DRAGON WHEEL!
TUNDRA FREEZE!
AVALANCHE CLAW!
WHOA.
CUBIMON.
WE'VE GOT TO DO
SOMETHING.
GOT IT.
HUH?
I HAVE AN IDEA.
DIGIMODIFY!
EXPANSION ACTIVATE!
IT WORKED.
ALL RIGHT, YOU GUYS.
NOW IT'S OUR TURN.
I DON'T THINK SO, BOY.
UHH. FOX TAIL INFERNO.
ARE YOU READY, GUILMON?
HMM?
LET'S GET HIM.
OKEY-DOKEY.
DIGIMODIFY!
SPEED ACTIVATE!
HA! BACK FOR MORE
ALREADY?
PYROSPHERE!
FROZEN CLAW!
DIGIMODIFY!
HYPERWING ACTIVATE!
THAT'S IT.
LET GO! AAH!
PYROSPHERE!
NO! NO!
[ SCREAMS ]
REIKA, ARE YOU OKAY?
I HATE 'EM.
WELL, HE'S GONE NOW.
NOT HIM.
HUH?
I HATE DIGIMON --
ALL OF THEM.
HUH?
OH.
[ SIGHS ]
REIKA,
YOU DON'T MEAN THAT.
CUBIMON, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
HEY, WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
AREN'T YOU GUYS
SUPPOSED TO BE FRIENDS?
IS IT POSSIBLE?
DOES REIKA REALLY HATE
ALL DIGIMON?
TO FIND OUT, KEEP WATCHING
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."