WHEN BEELZEMON DESTROYED
LEOMON, TAKATO WENT
BALLISTIC!
HE FORCED GUILMON
TO DIGIVOLVE INTO HIS MEGAFORM,
BUT THE WHOLE THING GOT
CORRUPTED BY TAKATO'S ANGE,
AND MEGIDRAMON WAS BORN.
IT LOOKED LIKE IT MIGHT E
A MATCH FOR BEELZEMON
UNTIL MAKURAMON SHOWED U.
BEELZEMON DESTROYED THE MONKY
DEVA AND ABSORBED HIS POWE.
THEN HE ABSORBED THE ULTIMATE
POWER OF TAOMON AND RAPIDMON.
WITH MEGIDRAMON DEFEATED,
ALL TAKATO WANTED
WAS HIS FRIEND BACK,
AND BOY, DID HE GET HIS WISH!
HE AND GUILMON JOINED FORCS
AND BIOMERGED TO GALLANTMO.
NOW, THAT'S WHAT I CALL
A MEGADIGIMON!
♪♪ DI, DI, DI
♪♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS   ♪♪
♪♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE WORLD
♪♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS.
DIGIMODIFY.
♪♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪♪ DIGIMON!
GUILMON BIOMERGE TO...
GALLANTMON!
RAH!
REMARKABLE!
WHOA! THAT'S AMAZING!
HE MUST BE GUILMON'S
TRUE MEGAFORM!
YEAH, I'LL SAY.
BUT WHERE'S TAKATO?
HUH?
HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON
HERE, HUH?
BEELZEMON, YOU REJECTED
EVERY FRIENDSHIP OFFERED YOU.
IN RETURN, YOU BETRAYED THEM
AND DESTROYED A VALIANT SOUL.
I CANNOT FORGIVE
WHAT YOU HAVE DONE.
YOU CAN'T FORGIVE ME?
I DON'T RECALL EVER ASKING
YOU TO FORGIVE ME!
WE'LL TALK ABOUT FORGIVENESS
WHEN I WIPE YOU
OUT OF EXISTENCE!
SO BE IT!
AAAHHHHH!
UGH!
[ GRUNTS ]
AHHHH!
[ GROWLING ]
HE'S STRONG.
THIS ISN'T GONNA BE EASY.
ARE THEY DANCING
OR FIGHTING?
AAH!Â  AAH!
OH!
DOES THAT ANSWER
YOUR QUESTION?
GALLANTMON,
EXALTED KNIGHT DIGIMON --
HIS LIGHTNING JOUST
AND SHIELD OF THE JUST ATTACKS
ARE UNSTOPPABLE.
AT LAST --
A MEGA ONOURSIDE.
WHY'S YOUR MOUTH OPEN?
WHY'S YOURS OPEN?
THERE IS NO EXCUSE
FOR YOUR ACTIONS!
I WILL SEE THAT
JUSTICE IS SERVED! RAAH!
WAIT...WHERE IS HE?
WHERE'S TAKATO?
MAYBE SIR LANCELOT
SWALLOWED HIM.
YEAH, RIGHT.
UGH! AAH!
[ GASPING ] [ GASPING ]
UGH!
YOU'LL EXCUSE ME IF I'M NOT
IMPRESSED, YOUR HIGHNESS,
BUT I GOT A DEAL TO CLOSE...
..AND YOU HAPPEN TO BE
IN MY WAY.
EVEN NOW, YOU SHOW NO REMORSE
FOR WHAT YOU HAVE DONE.
I HAVE NO CHOICE...
BUT TO DESTROY YOU!
RIGHT.
YAH!
HUH?
[ ENGINE REVVING ]
AAH!
RAAAH!
BRING IT ON!
UGH! YAH!
THAT WON'T STOP ME.
AAH!AAH!
[ GRUNTS ]
OH, MAN!
KAZU, SNAP OUT OF IT!
I THINK TAKATO'S GONE.
HUH? ARE YOU SURE?
WHAT, YOU THINK HE GOT
FLUSHED DOWN THE FALLS?
I'M NOT KIDDING.
HE COULD BE HURT OR DEAD
OR SOMETHING.
I HATE IT WHEN HE'S RIGHT.
OHHH.
WHAT'S WRONG?
I'SUPPOSED TO BE
PROTECTINGYOU,
BUT I'VE FAILED.
YOUR JOB IS TO REST NOW.
YOU HAVEN'T FAILED ANYTHING.
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
UGH.
WHAT'S WRONG,
EXHAULTED ONE?
I THOUGHT MY WEAPONS WOULDN'T
EFFECT YOUR ROYAL HIGHNESS.
[ LAUGHING ]
WHAT'S HE DOING?
NOW YOU SEE ME...
NOW YOU DON'T!
BUT HOW?
DARKNESS CLAW!
UGH! UGH!
AAAH! UGH!
BEELZEMON BODY-SLAMMED HIM!
IF I COULD JUST DIGIVOLVE,
I'D WHUP THAT RAT!
OH!
SUSIE, DON'T MOVE!
STAY RIGHT WHERE YOU ARE.
[ Sobbing ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE GONE.
IT'S MY FAULT.
I WASN'T STRONG ENOUGH
TO BE YOUR TAMER.
OH, LEOMON...
I'M SO SORRY!
[ SOBS ]
HUH?
UGH!Â Â   AAH!
WHERE ARE YOU?
COWARD!
LIGHTNING JOUST!
WHAT?
YAAAAH!
YOU DON'T SCARE ME!
HUH! HUH!
I SHOULD!
AAH!
WHOA!
SUSIE!
NO!!
PERHAPS BEELZEMON IS WORTHY
OF THE GIFTS WE HAVE
BESTOWED UPON HIM AFTER ALL.
BUT THERE IS ANOTHER
WHO HAS BETRAYED ME.
THIS CANNOT GO UNPUNISHED!
DESTROY THE TRAITOR!
AS YOU WISH.
HENRY! OH!
HE'S COMING --
CHATSURAMON!
WHAT A TRAGIC WASTE --
A DEVA THAT PREFERS
THE COMPANY OF HUMANS
TO THE GLORY
OF THE SOVEREIGN.
WHAT DOES HE WANT?
DID YOU DO SOMETHING BAD?
NO, HE'S THE ONE
THAT'S BAD.
YOU MUST BE PUNISHED FOR
WHAT YOU'VE DONE...TRAITOR.
OH! NO!
SUSIE, LET GO!
HE'LL HURT YOU!
I WON'T LET
THE BAD DOGGY GET YOU!
DISGUSTING! I MUST REMOVE
THIS WORTHLESS HUMAN!
NO, DON'T!
IT'S ME YOU WANT.
SHE'S INNOCENT.
INNOCENT?
A HUMAN TRESPASSING INTO
THE LAND OF THE SOVEREIGN
IS UNFORGIVABLE.
I SHALL DESTROY YOU BOTH!
UGH!
NO! WATCH OUT!
SUSIE!
FEEL THE WRATH
OF THE SOVEREIGN!
AAH!
TERRIERMON!
OH!
AAH!
HOLD ON!
GOTCHA. UGH!
HUH?
YOU MAY BE ABLE TO DEFEAT
A ROOKIE, DEVA,
BUT YOU CANNOT DEFEAT ME!
PREPARE YOURSELF!
LIGHTNING JOUST!
RAAAAAH!
NO!
AAH!
LONG LIVE THE SOVEREIGN!
I'LL TAKE THAT!
NO!
HA HA HA!
THAT FILTHY DOG CHATSURAMON
FINALLY GOT WHAT HE DESERVED!
AND NOW ALL THAT BEAUTIFUL
POWER IS MINE!!
SUSIE!
HENRY, I WAS SO SCARED,
AND TERRIERMON GOT HURT --
SUSIE, LET GO OF LOPMON.
HUH? NO!
SHE'S A DEVA!
IT'S DANGEROUS
JUST BEINGNEARHER.
I'M SORRY, BUT IT'S
FOR YOUR OWN GOOD.
HENRY...LOOK!
HUH?
DON'T YOU SEE?
LOPMON'S MY PARTNER.
I CAN'T!
[ SOBBING ]
THIS IS SO CRAZY!
I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M EVEN
HAVING THIS CONVERSATION!
SHE SHOULDN'T EVEN BE HERE!
I'M GOING TO GET TERRIERMON.
OKAY.
AAH!
YAH! YAH! YAH!
AAH! AAH!
HOLD ON, TERRIERMON.
I'VE GOT YOU.
MOMENTI.
TAKATO!
HEY, CHUMLEY,
YOU DOWN THERE?
JUST A THOUGHT, BUT IF HE
REALLY DID FALL DOWN THERE,
ISN'T IT POSSIBLE
THAT HE MIGHT NOT BEABLE
TO ANSWER YOU?
HELLO, BOYS!
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL PROTECT YOU
FROM THIS FIEND.
AAH!
PROTECT THIS!
OW.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU'RE NOT BROKEN AGAIN,
ARE YOU?
I THINK WE'VE GOT HIM
ON THE RUN, DON'T YOU?
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT IT, GUARDRAMON.
THERE'S JUST NO WAY YOU
CAN STAND UP TO THIS GUY.
POINT TAKEN.
I'VE NEVER FELT MORE LE
A WUSS IN MY WHOLE LIF,
BUT THAT PSYCHO BIKER
HAS GONE OFF THE DEEP EN!
IF HE DOES TO GUARDRN
WHAT HE DID TO LEOMON,
I'LL NEVER FORGIVE MYSEL.
UGH!
YOU CAN'T STAY HERE!
IT'S MUCH TOO DANGEROUS!
RUN!
AAH!
TOO LATE!
YOU SHOULD HAVE LISTENED
TO HIM!
NO!
STAY DOWN!
IT'S ALMOST OVER!
OH, WOW!
HE PROTECTED ME!
HUH?
THAT SOUNDED LIKE...TAKATO!
RAAAAAAAAH!
AAH!
GOTTA MOVE, GOTTA GO,
GOTTA RUN!
EARTH TO KENTA!
HELLO?
I'M, UH...
I JUST FELT IT, YOU KNOW?
INSIDE.
THAT BIG DIGIMON IS --
IS TAKATO!
HUH?Â Â Â   HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
YOU MEAN GALLANTMON?
MM-HMM.
RAAAH!
SOMEHOW I JUST KNOW
THAT GALLANTMON AND TAKATO
HAVE, LIKE, JOINED TOGETHER.
TAKATO HAS ACTUALLY BECOME
PARTOF GALLANTMON NOW.
OKAY, THAT'S WEIRD.
UGH!
I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF THIS!
YAH!
HE'S COMING!
NOW!
OH, MAN!
IF TAKATO'S IN THERE,
THEN HE'S TOAST!
WE GOTTA DO SOMETHING!
DON'T MOVE! HA HA!
WHERE IS HE?
YAH!
I'VE GOTTA HELP TAKATO!
BUT HOW?
THIS IS TOO EASY!
HUH?
[ GROANS ]
SAY GOODBYE, PINEAPPLE HEAD!
[ BEELZEMON LAUGHING EVILLY ]
AAAAAAAH!
OH!
IF YOU WON'T SAY IT, I WILL.
GOODBYE.
TAKATO!
WHAT DO WE DO?
NOTHING.
HE'S ON HIS OWN NOW.
OOH!
WHAT WAS THAT?
THAT WAS THE SOUND
OF SWEET REVENGE!
GUARDIAN BARRAGE!
YOU ANNOYING -- UGH! UGH!
RAAH!
UGH!
HUH?
YES!
WELL DONE! YES!
THANKS, KAZU!
THANK YOU, EVERYBODY!
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO!
YEAH. LET'S GET !
KENTA WAS RIGHT!
THEY HAVE MERGED SOMEHOW.
GUILMON AND TAKATO
HAVE BECOME
ONE INDESTRUCTIBLE
FIGHTING MACHINE!
LIGHTNING JOUST!
HAH!
O-O-O-O-O-O-O-W!
[ Sobbing ] STOP!
UGH! UGH! UGH!
YOU CAN'T HURT US ANYMORE.
UGH! UGH! UGH! UGH!
YOU JUST NEVER LEARN.
[ CLICKING ]
[ GROWLS ]
BEELZEMON, YOUR JUDGMENT DAY
IS AT HAND.
FOR THE HORRIBLE THINGS
YOU HAVE DONE,
NOW YOU MUST PAY
THE ULTIMATE PRICE!
SHIELD...OF THE JUST!
AAAAH!
OHHH!
THIS CAN'T BE...HAPPENING!
[ GROANING ]
THIS IS WHERE IT ENDS.
HOW COULD I HAVE LOST?
I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
INVINCIBLE.
WELL, WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR?
GO ON, DO IT.
NO.
DO IT!
I CAN NEVER FORGIVE U
FOR WHAT YOU DID TO LEOMON.
HE WAS MY FRIEND.
HOW CAN YOU BE SO COLD?
YOU'RE NOT EVEN SOY
FOR WHAT YOU DID!
GOODBYE, BEELZEMON!
YAAAAAH!
STOP IT!
[ RUMBLING ]
[ SOBBING ]
JERI, WHY?
HE'S NOT WORTH IT, TAKATO.
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
HE DESERVES THIS!
YOU KNOW THAT!
PLEASE...DON'T DO IT.
I COULDN'T BEAR IT
IF ANYONE ELSE GOT HURT.
PLEASE!
JERI...
PLEASE?
I'M SORRY, JER.
I DON'T GET IT.
W-WHY ARE YOU PROTECTING ME?
I DESTROYED YOUR PARTNER!
[ SOBS ]
I HATE YOU...FOR DOING THAT.
BUT EVEN IF YOU DIED, IT
WOULDN'T BRING LEOMON BACK.
IT'S MY FAULT HE'S GONE,
AND IF YOU DESTROYED
EACH OTHER,
THEN THAT WOULD BE
MY FAULT, TOO.
I JUST CAN'T LET
ANYONE ELSE GET HURT
BECAUSE OF ME.
[ SOBS ]
[ CRYING ]
I'M SO SORRY.
HMM?
OHH.
HUH?
HUMANS!
HE IS MINE!
HE IS NOT!
IS TOO!
THEY WERE SO SELFISH,
I DIDN'T WANT TO HAVE
ANYTHING TO DO WITH THEM!
FRIENDSHIP?
FORGET ABOUT IT!
WHAT GOOD ARE FRIENDS?
YOU RUN AROUND BEING ALL CUTE
AND CUDDLY AND NICE FOR THEM,
AND WHAT'S THAT DONE
FOR YOU, HUH?
YOU CAN'T DIGIVOLVE.
YOU'RE NOT A REAL DIGIMON!
I AM TOO!
IS THAT RIGHT?
WELL, THEN, TOUGH GUY,
WHY DON'T YOU JUST FIGHT ME
AND TAKE MY DATA, HMM?
I DIDN'T NEED FRIENDS,
ESPECIALLY IF THEY WERE HUMANS.
HUMANS DIDN'T CARE ABOUT
ANYTHING BUT THEMSELVES,
AND EVEN WHEN THEY DID SHOW YOU
A LITTLE ATTENTION,
IT'S ONLY 'CAUSE THEY WANTD
SOMETHING FROM YOU!
THEY USED US DIGIMON LIKE
WE WERE SLAVES OR SOMETHIN.
WELL, I WASN'T GONNA TAKE T
ANYMORE!
LOOK -- MORE WEAKLINGS!
UGH! I'LL TAKE THAT!
[ CRYING ]
HEY, THAT WAS BUBBLE-GUM
RASPBERRY ALMOND CRUNCH!
HOW ABOUT A BADA-BOOM
UPSIDE-THE-HEAD CRUNCH?
YAH, BADA-BOOM!
HUH?
MY SHOULDER!!
HOT, HOT, HOT, HOT,
HOT, HOT, HOT, HOT!
WELL, THAT'S JUST
A LITTLE PRESENT FOR YA!
AND...I BROUGHT ENOUGH
FOR EVERYONE!
YOU THINK I NEED A TAMER
TO BEAT YOU?
I DON'T NEED ANYONE!
ALL I WANTED
WAS TO HAVE THE POWER
TO DIGIVOLVE ON MY OWN.
YAAAAAAH!
WAS THAT TOO MUCH TO ASK?
HUH?
I DON'T THINK SO!
THEN, JUST AS I HIT BOTTOM,
OPPORTUNITY KNOCKED.
WHAT DO YOU WANT FROM ME?
BUT THERE'S ALWAYS A CATCH.
YOU'RE SAYING THAT
IF I GO BACK HOME,
YOU'RE GONNA HELP ME
TO DIGIVOLVE?
I'LL BITE.
WHAT DO I HAVE TO DO?
[ EVIL LAUGHTER ]
WHAT CHOICE DID I HAVE?
CHATSURAMON WAS RIGHT.
THERE WAS NO PLACE FOR ME
IN THE REAL WORLD.
AI, MAKO --
THEY NEVER WANTED ME --
EXCEPT TO TORTURE
EACH OTHER.
THEN SURRENDER YOUR SOUL!
AAH!
I DIDN'T CARE HOW I GOT IT,
AND THE SOVEREIGN MADE ME
AN OFFER I COULDN'T REFUSE.
BUT AT LAST, I HAD MY POWE.
I'M GONNA ENJOY
HEARING YOU SCREAM.
HUH!
TRY MY DOUBLE IMPACT!
AT LAST,
IÂ WAS THE ONE IN CONTROL,
AND THE POWER WAS INTOXICATING.
HA HA!
IT WAS ADDICTING!
I COULDN'T GET ENOUGH.
I HAD TO HAVE MORE!
AND I WOULD DO
ANYTHING FOR IT --
ANYTHING!!
HA!
THIS IS TOO EASY!
HMM.
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
UGH!
TO HAVE POWER
IS NOT TO BE STRONG.
LEOMON...
DO WHAT YOU MUST,
BEELZEMON,
BUT I WILL NOT LET YOU HURT
THESE CHILDREN.
WAAAAAAAH!
[ GROANS ]
[ ROARS ]
OH! OH!
OH! OH!
POWER WAS ALL I HAD.
BE BRAVE, JERI.
PART OF ME WILL ALWAYS
BE WITH YOU.
REMEMBER, YOU HAVE
A LION'S HEART.
NO. TO HAVE POWER
IS TO BE STRONG!
I'LL KEEP LOADING DATA
TILL NO ONE CAN STOP ME!
NO ONE. NO ONE!!
I AM NOTHING NOW.
HUH?
WE DID IT!
SURE FEELS GOOD
TO BE ME AGAIN.
AND MY "ME" IS HAPPY TO BE
WITH YOUR "ME" AGAIN.
BUT AS GALLANTMON,
WE WERE
A REAL FIGHTING TEAM!
YEAH, YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE REALLY DID FIGHT
TOGETHER, DIDN'T WE?
OH! OH!
[ CHUCKLES ]
WELL, WHATEVER HAPPENS NOW,
I ABSOLUTELY KNOW
WE'LL ALWAYS BE TOGETHER.
MM-HMM.
HAIL, THE CONQUERING HEROES!
[ LAUGHING ]
HEY!
THANKS, YOU GUYS!
UM, CYBERDRAMON?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHERE WE ARE?
[ GROWLS ]
WHAT'S WRONG?
I'M SENSING THE PRESENCE
OF A NEW OPPONENT,
MORE POWERFUL
THAN WE'VE EVER SEEN.
AND YET YOU'RE NOT
RUNNING OVER ME TO FIND HIM.
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU.
THIS ONE MUST BE REALLY BAD.
OH, GREAT --
OUT OF THE FRYING PAN
AND INTO THE FIRE!
TO FIND OUT WHAT HAPPENS,
TUNE IN TO THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS"