BEELZEMON DECIDED TO TEST HIS
NEW POWERS ON THE CHRYSALIMO,
WHO DIGIVOLVED TO INFERMON,
BUT THE BIG SPIDER WAS NO MATCH
FOR THE SOVEREIGN'S STOOGE.
WHEN THE DIGI-GNOMES LED RIKA
TO WATER,
IT WAS CALUMON WHO ENDED UP
SAVING HER FROM THE RIVER.
THEN ANOTHER HUGE WAVE
CAME ALONG
AND SENT THEM ALL BACK
TO THE DESERT.
THEY FOUND THE REST OF THE GANG
BEFORE BEELZEMON ATTACKE.
MEANWHILE,
BACK IN THE REAL WORLD,
THE GUYS FROM HYPNOS GAVE
JUGGERNAUT ANOTHER TRY.
IT CAUSED THIS HUGE STORM N
THE DIGITAL WORLD,
AND THE TAMERS WERE SEPARATED
AGAIN.
MAN,
THAT WAS ONE SHORT REUNION!
DI, DI, DI
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS
TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE WORLD
DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS.
DIGIMODIFY.
DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON!
Calumon: OHH. I THOUGHT IMPMON
WAS MY FRIEND,
BUT I GUESS HE DOESN'T KNOW THE
MEANING OF THE WORD.
HE PROBABLY DOESN'T EVEN KNOW
THE MEANING OF MEANING,
EXCEPT FOR THE "MEAN" PART.
WELL, AT LEAST THE
SUNSET'S PRETTY.
WAIT! IF THAT'S A SUNSET, THEN
THE SUN'S GOTTEN AWFULLY POINTY.
OH! I DON'T LIKE
THE LOOKS OF THAT!
AHH!I WONDER IF THIS WORLD'S
EVER HEARD OF THE WORD "SHADE."
I HOPE CALUMON'S OKAY.
IF CALUMON'S SO IMPORTANT THAT
THEY'D KIDNAP HIM,
THEN THEY'LL TREAT HIM WELL,
I'M SURE.
DO YOU THINK THAT'S RIGHT,
RIKA?
I DON'T KNOW, JERI!
GROW UP!
W-WHAT?
QUIT ACTING LIKE A BABY.
[ GASPS ]
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU'RE A TAMER NOW,
SO GET TOUGH.
[ WHIMPERS ]
THIS IS ALL SO NEW.
I'LL TRY HARDER.
WE JUST DON'T HAVE THE LUXURY OF
BEING SOFT.
YOU HAVE TO LEARN THAT THIS
ISN'T A GAME, JERI.
THERE'S SERIOUS STUFF
AT STAKE HERE.
RIKA, SHE SAID SHE'D TRY HARDER,
SO LET IT GO, WOULD YOU?
RENAMON'S RIGHT.
I'M SORRY, JERI.
'KAY.
[ GIGGLES ]
MMM.
NOW THAT WE'VE GOTTEN TODAY'S
ARGUMENT OUT OF THE WAY,
CAN WE GET BACK TO FINDING
TAKATO AND THE GUYS?
WHY'D YOU HAVE TO REMIND ME
ABOUT TAKATO?
GUILMON, MAYBE YOU COULD BECOME
MY PARTNER DIGIMON INSTEAD.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
TAKATO'S MY TAMER. HAVEN'T YOU
BEEN PAYING ATTENTION?
HEY, COME ON, BUDDY.
IMAGINE US AS DIGIMON TAMER
AND PARTNER.
IT'LL BE GREAT!
WHA HA HA HA!
I'LL MAKE YOU BANANA SPLITS
EVERY DAY!
GUYS, WAIT.
WHOA!
HUH?
WHERE DID THEY GO?
WHOA!
AAH!
UGH!
WHOA!
NICE CATCH,
RENAMON.
THIS JUST CAN'T GET
ANY WORSE!
AAH!
AAAAH!
OOH!
[ ALL GROANING ]
Jeri:
YOU GUYS OKAY?
YEAH, EXCEPT
FOR BEING REALLY HURT.
[ GROANS ]
NOW I'LL NEVER FIND TAKATO.
AAH!
WHERE ARE WE GOING ANYWAY?
YOU REALLY THINK
I HAVE ANY IDEA?
MOMENTI!
OH,MOMENTIYOURSELF!
OH. WELL, THERE'S PLENTY
OF SHADE HERE.
Renamon:
YES, BUT WHERE'S "HERE"?
[ SNIFFS ]
OROCHIMON!
WHO'S THAT?
HE'S OVER THERE.
COME ON!
[ ALL PANTING ]
OROCHIMON! COME OUT!
THIS WILL GET HIS ATTENTION,
AND HOPEFULLY DO
A LITTLE DAMAGE!
HMM?
WELL, AREN'T YOU
A MOTLEY BUNCH?
AND WHAT DO YOU WANT,
I WONDER.
GO ON, RENAMON.
YOU TOO, LEOMON.
[ GROWLS ]
GUILMON?
HUH?
OKAY, I KNOW
I'M NOT REALLY YOUR TAMER,
BUT WOULD YOU MIND,
ANYWAY?
DON'T WORRY, KENTA.
I'LL PROTECT YOU GUYS.
SO, OROCHIMON HAS SENT YOU
TO FIGHT, HAS HE?
HMM?
Leomon: OROCHIMON?
WHO IN THE WORLD IS THAT?
WELL, HE'S THE DIGIMON
WHO RULES THIS AREA.
AND WHO ARE YOU?
A HUMBLE SERVANT
IN THE FIGHT FOR GOOD --
ANDROMON THE JUST.
Guilmon: "JUST" WHAT?
WELL, HE'S NOT LYING.
ANDROMON -- ULTIMATE LEVEL.
Kenta: LOOK!
WHAT?
AAH
RUN!
Kenta: YOU DON'T HAVE
TO TELL ME!
AAH
Andromon: STAND BACK!
IT'SMYFIGHT!
GATLING ATTACK!
OH, DEAR.
[ GROWLS ]
OHH!
[ GROWLING ]
UGH!
OHH.
OROCHIMON,
ULTIMATE LEVEL!
SPECIAL ATTACK --
INFERNO BLAST!
Guilmon:
AN ULTIMATE --
HE'S GONNA BE DIFFICULT
TO DEFEAT IF I CAN'T DIGIVOLVE.
Kenta: WELL, GIVE IT A SHOT,
WOULD YOU?
Leomon: DON'T WORRY.
WE SHALL PROTECT YOU.
HOW ABOUT SOMETIME TODAY,
HUH?
[ HISSING ]
OH!
STEP BACK, BEAST!
OR SLITHER BACK!
HMM.
[ GROWLS ]
Kenta: HE'S LEAVING!
LEOMON, YOU DID IT!
[ WHIMPERING ]
[ LAUGHS WICKEDLY ]
BUT WHY WAS HE STARING
AT JERI?
[ PANTING ]
ANDROMON'S HURT!
[ BEEPING ]
IS HE EVEN ALIVE?
YEAH, BUT JUST BARELY.
HUH?
HEY! LOOK OVER THERE!
MAYBE IT'S A VILLAGE
WHERE WE CAN GET HELP.
I NEVER THOUGHT FALLING
COULD GET SO BORING.
WE GOT TO FIND A WAY
TO GET OUT OF HERE.
WE MIGHT AS WELL TRY.
GRAB HOLD!
TERRIERMON!
[ GRUNTING ]
HOLD ON!
Jeri: YEP, IT'S A VILLAGE
ALL RIGHT.
Rika: NOTHING GETS
PAST YOU, DOES IT?
WELL, I...HEY!
SOMETHING SMELLS FAMILIAR.
YEAH. SEEMS TO BE COMING
FROM IN HERE.
CHECK IT OUT, GUYS.
HUH?
HMM.
HEY, WHAT ARE THOSE GUYS
DOING?
LOOKS LIKE A FACTORY.
DUH!
YOU SMELL THAT, TOO?
[ SNIFFING ]
IT'S MILKSHAKES.
HMM?
YEAH!
THEY'RE THE SPECIALTY
AT MY FAMILY'S RESTAURANT.
WELL, YOU CAN'T HAVE
ANY OF OURS!
HUH?
AND MAKE SURE YOU KEEP
YOUR GRUBBY HANDS
OFF THE EQUIPMENT.
THAT'S 100% PURE DIGITAL DATA
THEY'RE MIXING IN.
GET IT DIRTY,
AND THE SHAKES ARE WORTHLESS.
LOOK, WE JUST WANT TO GET SOME
HELP FOR OUR FRIEND ANDROMON.
THAT LOUSY ANDROMON!
Jeri: LOUSY?
BUT HE'S A HUMBLE SERVANT
IN THE FIGHT FOR GOOD.
GREAT!
THERE'LL BE MORE TROUBLE!
WHAT'S WRONG?
YES, HE SEEMS LIKE
A NICE ENOUGH GUY.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT HE'S DONE TO US!
WELL, WE WOULD
IF YOU TOLD US.
DON'T BE CHILDISH.
WE NEED HIS HELP.
I'M SURE HE'D TELL US
IF HE WANTED TO.
ACCORDING TO YOU AND TAKATO,
EVERYTHING'S CHILDISH.
[ SIGHS ]
I DIDN'T WANT TO HAVE TO TELL
THIS STORY AGAIN, BUT...
WE USED TO LIVE IN PEACE,
HAPPILY FILLING THE AIR
WITH OUR BEAUTIFUL SINGING.
[ ALL CROAKING ]
BUT THAT DIDN'T LAST LONG.
AAH!
[ GROWLS ]
YOU SLIMY SINGERS
SHALL SERVE ME!
Geckomon: SERVE YOU?!
BUT HOW, OH, BIG TEETHY
AND FANGY ONE?
ALL WE KNOW HOW TO DO
IS SING!
PLUS, PRODUCE MILKSHAKES.
BUT YOU'RE SO LARGE,
OH, SURE-TO-BE-CAUSING
LOTS-OF-PAIN ONE,
WE COULDNEVERMAKE ENOUGH
SHAKES TO FILL --
[ GROWLING ]
DATA SHAKES APLENTY,
COMING RIGHT UP.
[ GROWLING ]
WELL, I HOPE YOU'RE HAPPY MAKING
ME RELIVE THAT HORRIBLE MEMORY.
BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT
THAT HAS TO DO WITH ANDROMON.
I WAS GOING TO GET
TO THAT PART NEXT.
HAVEN'T YOU EVER HEARD OF
BUILDING DRAMATIC TENSION?
TO KEEP THE PEACE,
WE DEVOTED ALL OUR ENERGIES
TO MAKING MILKSHAKES
FOR THAT HIDEOUS CREATURE.
EVERY DAY WE HAVE TO DRAG THEM
DOWN TO THE LAKE.
AND IF WE DIDN'T,
HE'D ATTACK US.
COME AND GET YOUR MILKSHAKE!
HERE, SHAKEY, SHAKEY, SHAKEY,
MILKSHAKE.
YOU KNOW, I THINK HE'S REALLY
STARTING TO MELLOW OUT.
AHH!
[ OROCHIMON GULPING ]
THAT THING HAS GOT A SWEET TOOTH
THE SIZE OF MOUNT FUJI.
BUT ANDROMON?
I'M GETTING TO THAT!
RELAX, ALREADY!
SEE, EVERYTHING WAS GOING ALONG
NICE AND PEACEFUL.
BUT THEN THIS BLOWHARD
COMES ALONG
AND SAYS HE WANTS TO FIGHT
OROCHIMON
AND SET US FREE OR SOME GARBAGE.
WE CAN WIN!
WITH YOUR HELP,
I CAN DEFEAT OROCHIMON
AND DRIVE HIM OUT OF THE POND
FOREVER!
HEY, DON'T ROCK THE BOAT!
OR AT LEAST NOT OUR BOAT!
ROCK YOUR OWN STUPID
BOAT!
VERY WELL, THEN.
I WILL.
Geckomon: BUT WOULD
HE LISTEN? NO!
NOW, HE AND OROCHIMON FIGHT
LIKE IT'S GOING OUT OF STYLE.
AND EVERY TIME THEY DO,
THEY WRECK EVERYTHING
AROUND HERE.
DO YOU KNOW HOW MANY TIMES WE'VE
HAD TO REBUILD THIS FACTORY?
NO.
WELL, IT'S A LOT OF TIMES.
WHAT DID YOU THINK
I WAS GONNA SAY?
IT'S HIS OWN STUPID FAULT
HE'S HURT.
SO IF YOU THINK I'M GONNA HELP
THIS GUY,
YOU'RE TWO SEEDS SHY
OF A MILKWEED POD!
LOOK,
I KNOW YOU'RE UPSET.
ANDROMON'S JUST DOING
WHAT HE THINKS IS BEST
TO HELP YOU GUYS.
AND WE WOULDN'T NEED MUCH HELP
FROM YOU --
JUST A COUPLE OF THOSE
DATA PACKETS
YOU PUT INTO THE MILKSHAKES.
REALLY? THAT'S IT?
I BELIEVE SO.
SO HELP US ALREADY!
BUT HE'LL FIND OUT!
YOU'VE GOT TO LEARN TO STAND
UP FOR YOURSELVES
OR SOMEONE LIKE OROCHIMON
WILL WALK ALL OVER YOU.
I WILL.
STARTING TOMORROW.
Jeri: THIS IS WEIRD.
MILKSHAKES ALWAYS MAKEME
FEEL BETTER.
Renamon:
THE DATA WILL HEAL HIM.
[ GROANING ]
WELL, AT LEAST HE'S AWAKE NOW,
RIGHT?
WHAT ARE THOSE DATA PACKETS,
ANYWAY?
Leomon: THEY'RE LIKE MEDICINE
FOR DIGIMON.
THEY REPAIR DATA THAT'S BEEN
DESTROYED OR CORRUPTED.
WHAT WOULD WE DO WITHOUT YOU,
LEOMON?
IS THIS GUY LIKE THE BRAVEST
DIGIMON OR WHAT,
FIGHTING OROCHIMON
ALL BY HIMSELF?
WOW!
Rika: HE TURNED INTO GUARDROMON,
CHAMPION LEVEL,
SPECIAL ATTACK --
GUARDIAN BARRAGE.
HE MUST'VE LOST A LOT OF ENERGY
DURING THE FIGHT.
YEAH, BUT AT LEAST
HIS WOUNDS ARE HEALED.
Leomon: JERI!
Rika: DO SOMETHING!
Kenta:
GUILMON CAN'T DIGIVOLVE,
GUARDROMON'S OUT COLD,
AND HOWDOYOU DEFEAT THIS GUY?
Leomon: DON'T WORRY, JERI!
I'LL SAVE YOU!
IF YOU WOULDN'T MIND!
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ PANTING ]
[ ALL PANTING ]
HEY, WAIT UP!
OHH, NUTS AND BOLTS.
HUH?
Leomon: JERI!
Guilmon: LEOMON, WAIT!
HE'S TOO STRONG
FOR YOU TO FIGHT ALONE!
[ ALL PANTING ]
TAKATOMON, WHERE ARE YOU
WHEN I NEED YOU?
INFERNO BLAST!
OH, NO! LEOMON!
YOU BETTER NOT HAVE HURT HIM,
YOU BIG, MEAN OL' SNAKE!
AAAH!
I FAILED YOU, JERI.
Guilmon:
DON'T WORRY, LEOMON.
WE'LL GET HER BACK.
EVEN IF IT COSTS ME EVERY OUNCE
OF MY DATA.
Orochimon: SLING US
SOME SHAKES, SERVANT!
Jeri: OKAY!
HE'S MEANER THAN THE CUSTOMERS
AT THE RESTAURANT.
UM, YOU DIDN'T HEAR THAT PART,
DID YOU?
AND SERVE SPEEDILY,
WRETCH!
WHY DO BOYS ALWAYS
HAVE TO BE SO SNOTTY?
JEEZ!
[ GRUNTS ]
YOUR SERVICE PLEASES US.
THANKS. I ALWAYS DO
GET THE BIGGEST TIPS.
YOU SHALL LIVE.
AND THAT'S MY BEST TIP YET.
IF YOU GUYS
JUST HAVE SOME PATIENCE
AND WAIT YOUR TURN,
I'LL FEED YOU ALL.
YOU SHALL.
FOR YOU SHALL STAY
OUR SERVANT ALWAYS!
IF I CAN JUST GET THEM FULL
OF WARM SHAKES,
MAYBE THEY'LL FALL ASLEE,
AND I CAN ESCAPE!
OF COURSE, MASTER!
BUT DISPLEASE US
AND BE DESTROYED!
RIGHT. PLEASE YOU, GOOD.
DISPLEASE YOU, HORRIBLE DEATH.
DRINK UP. THEN IT'S
NIGHTY-NIGHT FOR ALL OF YO.
OR ELSE IT'LL BE NIGHTY-NIGHT
FOR ME.
HMM.
EVEN IF JERI IS USED TO WORKING
IN A RESTAURANT,
THERE'S NO WAY SHE CAN HANDLE
A TOUGH CUSTOMER LIKE OROCHIMON.
IT'S MY FAULT FOR LETTING HER
GET INTO DANGER
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
SHE'LL BE FINE.
WE'LL SAVE HER.
Renamon: OF COURSE.
BUT WE BETTER GET TO HER SOON.
[ GROWLS ]
MAN, I SURE HOPE THOSE GUYS
ARE OKAY.
[ GROANS ]
DID YOU SAY SOMEONE
NEEDS HELP?
GUARDROMON, YOU'RE AWAKE!
[ Groaning ] OROCHIMON.
[ GROANS ]
YOU'RE STILL TOO WEAK
TO FIGHT.
HOW SHAMEFUL.
WHO ARE YOU, ANYWAY?
KAZU.
THANK YOU, KAZU.
AND I THINK I KNOW A WAY
TO RESCUE YOUR FRIEND.
HUH?
WE'VE GOT TO GO AFTER HER!
BUT HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED TO GET
ACROSS THE WATER?
Kenta: I THINK WE NEED A BIG
BOAT OR SOMETHING.
Rika: THERE'S NO "SOMETHING" ABOUT IT.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT WE NEED.
WELL, THEN,
LET'S BUILD A BOAT.
HEY, YOU GUYS!
GUARDROMON'S COME UP
WITH AN AMAZING PLAN
FOR US TO SAVE JERI!
HUH?
I'M OUT OF SHAPE!
Geckomon: IT'S TIME TO DELIVER
THE MILKSHAKES, BOYS.
PUT ON YOUR TRAVELING FLIPPERS.
[ GRUNTING ]
DON'T BE TAKING
ANY FREE SAMPLES.
GOT IT, JOHNSON?
HOW COME OROCHIMON
HAS ALL THE FUN?
YOU WANNA TELL HIM
YOU DRANK HIS MILKSHAKES?
OKAY. NOBODY TOUCHES
THE SHAKES.
HEY, CHECK IT OUT.
IT'S GUARDROMON.
WHAT'S HE DOING
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE ROAD?
[ ALL GRUMBLE ]
HEY, SHORTY! YEAH, YOU!
GET OUT OF THE WAY ALREADY!
OROCHIMON HAS KIDNAPPED
ONE OF THESE KIND PEOPLE.
WE NEED YOUR HELP
TO GET HER BACK --
AND MAYBE TO DEFEAT OROCHIMON
ONCE AND FOR ALL.
YES, PLEASE HELP US.
WE CAN'T DO IT WITHOUT YOU.
HMM.
HMM-UNH.
PLEASE HELP US.
HMM. NAH!
[ WHIMPERS ]
BUT WE SAID, "PLEASE."
PRETTY PLEASE?
QUIT TUGGING AT MY HEARTSTRINGS,
ALREADY!
WE WON'T FIGHT OROCHIMON
'CAUSE WE LOVE PEACE.
AND WE LOVE KEEPING OURSELVES
IN ONE PIECE!
SLAVING OVER MILKSHAKES,
ALWAYS WORRYING ABOUT ATTACKS
BY OROCHIMON...
IS THAT THE PEACE
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT?
[ MURMURING
I THOUGHT THAT PEACE FOR YOU,
GECKOMON,
MEANT SINGING ALL DAY.
OR AT LEAST WHATYOU
CALL SINGING.
[ MURMURING ]
HMM?
[ WHIMPERS ]
OKAY. IF IT MEANS
WE CAN SING AGAIN,
WE'LL HELP YOU.
THANK YOU, GOOD FRIENDS.
[ SIGHING ]
SO, WHAT DO WE HAVE TO DO?
JUST DELIVER THE MILKSHAKE TUBS
AS USUAL.
WE'LL TAKE CARE OF THE REST.
Kenta:
I SURE HOPE THIS WORKS.
Kazu: IT HAS TO.
Leomon: HOLD ON, JERI.
I'M COMING.
Guilmon: TELL HER
WE'RE ALL COMING.
SHE'LL FEEL BETTER
THAT WAY.
Geckomon:
WE'RE ALMOST THERE, GUYS!
Jeri:
FINALLY, THEY'RE ASLEEP.
THE PLAN WORKED LIKE A CHARM.
WELL, A CHARM WITH ONE BIG,
HUGE, GAPING FLAW, I GUESS.
ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T WANT TO
TAKE A NAP?
HOW ABOUT SOME MORE MILKSHAKES,
HUH?
THEY'RE RICH IN MILKY GOODNESS.
[ GRUMBLES ]
[ GULPING ]
SLEEP, ALREADY.
YOU'VE ALREADY HAD
12 COW'S WORTH OF MILK.
Geckomon:
SPECIAL DELIVERY!
ANOTHER BATCH OF MILKSHAKES
FOR YOU, OH, GRUESOME ONE.
[ GROWLING ]
I'VE BEEN FEEDING HIM
WARM MILKSHAKES
TO GET HIM TIRED,
SO I COULD ESCAPE.
HE SHOULD BE SO TUCKERED OUT,
HE'LL BE EASY TO DEFEAT!
Geckomon: OH, NO!
Jeri: WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"OH, NO!"?
THAT'S GOOD, RIGHT?
[ GROWLING ]
IT WOULD BE GOOD, EXCEPT
THE DATA IN THE MILKSHAKES
WILL MAKE HIM STRONGER.
OH, NO.
I FORGOT THAT.
Leomon: WE'LL BEAT HIM NO MATTER
HOW MANY MILKSHAKES HE'S HAD.
Guilmon: WE SHOULD'VE HAD
SOME MILKSHAKES.
THERE'S NOTHING MORE
IMPORTANT THAN A HEALTHY DIET.
BUT WHAT IF YOU GUYS GET HURT?
IT'LL BE ALL MY FAULT.
NO, IT'LL BE OROCHIMON'S FAULT.
[ GROWLING ]
AAH!
GET HIM, RENAMON!
POWER PAW!
I'M NOT YOUR TAMER,
BUT GET IN THERE!
NO ARGUMENT HERE, KENTA.
PYRO SPHERE!
HAHHH!
[ GROANS AND GRUNTS ]
[ GROANING ]
WHOA!
[ LAUGHS WICKEDLY ]
WHAT'S SO FUNNY?
NOTHING.
EXCEPT THAT THE SNAKES YOU
SOUGHT TO SILENCE
ARE SIMPLY SIMULATIONS!
WHAT? THEY'RE FAKE?
[ LAUGHS WICKEDLY ]
Jeri: OH, NO!
WILL WE EVER BE ABLE
TO DEFEAT HIM?
[ GROWLS ]
EVERYONE, GO AFTER
THE CENTER HEAD ONLY!
INFERNO BLAST!
DIAMOND STORM!
[ GRUNTS ]
HE'S NOT EVEN HURT.
PYRO SPHERE!
HAHHH!
AAH!
INFERNO BLAST!
THIS REALLY IS ALL MY FAULT.
IF I JUST HADN'T GIVEN HIM
ALL THOSE STUPID MILKSHAKES.
JERI, YOU'RE A TAMER NOW.
AND AS MUCH AS I HATE
TO ADMIT THIS,
RIKA'S RIGHT.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET TOUGH!
NOTHING'S WORKING!
WE'VE GOT TO CHANGE OUR TACTICS.
IF ONLY I WEREN'T
TOO INJURED TO FIGHT!
"WE'VE GOT TO CHANGE
OUR TACTICS"?
WAIT A MINUTE!
[ GASPS ]
PERFECT!
HE WON'T BE EXPECTING THIS!
DIJIMODIFY!
[ Echoing ]
DIGIMODIFY!
LADYDEVIMON, ACTIVATE!
BOTH: LADYDEVIMON, ACTIVATE?
[ ROARS ]
DARKNESS WAVE!
[ OROCHIMON LAUGHING WICKEDLY ]
[ LAUGHING CONTINUES ]
AAAH!
THAT WASN'T SO TOUGH.
HUH?
YEAH, RIGHT.
NICE JOB.
[ GIGGLES ]
NOW THAT'S WHAT I CALL
BEING A TOUGH TAMER.
AS THANKS FOR GETTING RID
OF OROCHIMON,
HERE'S OUR MOST BEAUTIFUL SONG.
OKAY, EVERYBODY.
ARE YOU READY?
A-ONE, AND A-TWO, AND A --
[ ALL CROAKING ]
[ CROAKING CONTINUES ]
THAT GETS WORSE EVERY TIME
I HEAR IT.
[ GASPS ]
HUH?
OH.
A DIGIVICE FOR ME?
NO WAY!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I'M REALLY A TAMER.
YOU'RE MY PARTNER!
[ LAUGHS ]
OH, THAT'S RIGHT, BUDDY!
I'M YOUR PARTNER!
HUH?
HEY, CONGRATS!
[ KAZU LAUGHING ]
GREAT! NOW EVERYONE'S
GOT A PARTNER EXCEPT ME!
I'LL PROBABLY GET STUCK
WITH BORINGERMON OR SOMETHING!
[ LAUGHTER ]
NO FAIR!
NOT EVERYONE HAS A PARTNER.
WHERE ARE YOU, TAKATO?
AAH!
HEY, KAZU FINALLY
GOT HIS PARTNER --
JUST ANOTHER PERSON
THAT CAN GET LOST.
SO KEEP WATCHING
"DIGIMON DIGITAL MONSTERS."