TAKATO AND GUILMON BIOMERGED
TO GALLANTMON
IN ORDER TO AVENGE LEOMON'S
DEATH.
THE REST OF THE GANG HAD
NO IDEA HOW IT HAPPENED,
BUT THEY SURE KNEW A MEGA
WHEN THEY SAW ONE.
SO DID BEELZEMON.
MEANWHILE, CHATSURAMON GOT
ORDERS FROM THE SOVEREIGN
TO GET RID OF LOPMON,
BUT GALLANTMON SAVED LOPMON Y
DESTROYING THE DOG DEVA.
JUST AS BEELZEMON WAS ABOUT O
GET THE SAME TREATMENT,
JERI SAVED HIM
BY STOPPING THE FIGHT.
I GUESS SHE DIDN'T WANT ANYOE
ELSE TO GET HURT.
AND AFTER SOME SOUL-SEARCHIN,
NEITHER DID BEELZEMON.
NOW ALL THE GANG HAS TO DO IS
RESCUE CALUMON
AND THEY CAN ALL GO HOME.
♪ DI, DI, DI
♪ DIGIMON, DIGIMON
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS ♪
♪ TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE WORLD
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS.
DIGIMODIFY.
♪ DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
♪ DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
♪ DIGIMON!
WHOA!
YOU'RE NOT KIDDING.
COME ON, GUYS.
THERE'S NO SENSE
IN PSYCHING OURSELVES OUT
BEFORE WE EVEN GET THERE.
I THINK THAT THING IS TAKING
CARE OF PSYCHING US OUT, HENRY.
UH-HUH.
WE'VE GOT TO GET CALUMON
SO WE CAN GET SUSIE HOME.
THIS BRIDGE WILL TAKE US RIGHT
TO ZHUQIAOMON'S CASTLE.
CALUMON WILL BE IN THERE.
WHY DO I FEEL LIKE
I'M VOLUNTEERING
TO WALK
INTO THE LION'S DEN?
BUT I GUESS HENRY'S RIGHT.
WE DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
SOMETIMES IT SEEMS LIKE WE NEVER
HAVE A CHOICE ABOUT ANYTHING.
YEAH,
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN.
ALL I EVER WANTED TO DO
WAS BECOME A GOOD DIGIMON TAMER
AND HAVE SOME FUN.
AND NOW SUSIE'S LIFE
IS IN DANGER,
AND I DON'T KNOW
IF WE'LL EVER GET HOME.
I KNOW.
BY THE WAY,
HOW'S TERRIERMON?
HUH?
OH, I'M JUST FINE.
DON'T YOU WORRY ABOUT ME,
TAKATO -- NOT ONE BIT.
LET'S JUST HURRY UP,
BEAT ZHUQIAOMON,
GET CALUMON OUT,
AND GO HOME.
YOU AREFEELING BETTER.
I ONLY HOPE
IT'S THAT EASY.
WE'RE READY TO FIGHT,
GUYS.
Oh!
Huh?
UH, JERI?
ARE YOU GONNA BE OKAY?
LISTEN TO ME.
I DON'T WANT ANYONE ELSE
TO BE DESTROYED EITHER.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE
TO FIGHT ZHUQIAOMON.
YOU NEVER REALLY WANTED TO FIGHT
IN THE FIRST PLACE, DID YOU?
I DON'T THINK FIGHTING'S
FUN ANYMORE EITHER,
BUT YOU'VE GOT TO UNDERSTAND
THIS ISN'T THE KIND OF FIGHT
WE CAN JUST RUN AWAY FROM.
WHY DON'T YOU WAIT HERE?
WHEN WE COME BACK,
WE CAN ALL GO HOME.
ALL OF US?
EXCEPT FOR LEOMON, YOU MEAN.
JERI.
HE'S NEVER COMING BACK,
IS HE?
[ SIGHS ]
NO!
HMM?
NO, NO!
I'M GOING, TOO!
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
YOU SAW ALL THE DANGEROUS STUFF
WE RAN INTO BACK THERE,
AND THAT CASTLE'S GONNA
BE EVEN MORE DANGEROUS.
YOU'RE STAYING RIGHT HERE.
BUT WHAT ABOUT LOPMON?
I'M GOING.
I MUST TRY TO STOP THE FIGHTING.
NO, YOU'LL GET HURT!
I HAVE TO GO, SUSIE.
IT MAY BE FOOLISH
OR NAIVE OF ME,
BUT I HAVE TO TRY TO GET
ZHUQIAOMON TO LISTEN TO ME.
THEN MAKE TERRIERMON
STAY HERE WITH ME.
HE'S HURT BAD ANYWAY.
MOMENTI!
I'M NOT HURT THAT BADLY
AT ALL, SUSIE.
WE'LL BE JUST FINE
WITHOUT YOU.
OOPS!
[ CRYING ]
YOU CAN'T!
YOU CAN'T LEAVE ME ALONE!
NOT AGAIN!
STOP CRYING!
I'M NOT CRYING!
[ GROANS ]
OH, LET'S JUST LEAVE HER HERE
AND GO ALREADY.
NO, I'M GOING!
QUIET!
AAH!
Takato: HENRY!
YOU'RE STAYING!
I ALREADY TOLD YOU THIS PLACE
IS GONNA BE VERY DANGEROUS,
AND YOU'D JUST BE IN THE WAY!
A LITTLE GIRL
IS NO USE AGAINST DIGIMON.
IT'S GONNA HAVE TO BE
UP TO ME ALONE.
YOU GOT IT?
[ CRYING ]
WHAT IS HE TALKING ABOUT?
YEAH, WHAT ARE WE,
CHOPPED LIVER?
IT'S OKAY, HENRY.
SHE CAN COME WITH US.
HEY, KENTA AND I WILL STAY
AND LOOK AFTER HER.
SURE I'D LIKE TO GO
WITH GARGOMON
AND BEAT UP
ON THE SOVEREIGN.
BUT IF I HAVE TO TAKE ONE
FOR THE TEAM
AND STAY BEHIND TO KEEP
THE LITTLE LADY SAFE, SO BE IT.
AND I'M SURE THAT KENTA
FEELS THE SAME WAY.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, KENTA?
UH, UH...
YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT!
IT'S OUR DUTY AS GENTLEMEN TO
STAY BEHIND WITH A LITTLE GIRL.
THANKS A LOT, GUYS.
DID YOU BOZOS JUST HAVE
A GOOD IDEA?
CAN IT, RIKA!
SEE, SUSIE?
YOU WON'T BE ALONE. SEE?
[ CRYING ]
Terriermon: I DON'T THINK
SHE SEES, HENRY.
I'LL BE OKAY.
RIGHT.
THEN WE BETTER GET STARTED.
WE'VE GOT
A LONG WAY TO GO.
DO WE HAVE TO WALK
THE WHOLE WAY?
MOMENTI.
Terriermon:
HEY, THAT'S MY WORD!
HUH?
OH!
Guilmon: YOU HAVE TO ADMIT
THIS DOES BEAT WALKING.
AT LEAST WE'LL BE
DESTROYED IN COMFORT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SUSIE.
HUH?
WHY DID SHE HAVE TO COME
TO THE DIGITAL WORLD ANYWAY?
SHE CAME HERE FOR ME.
YEAH, MAYBE.
YOU SHOULD HAVE GONE
TO THE REAL WORLD.
THERE'S NO NEED
FOR HER TO BE HERE.
BUT SHE IS HERE, HENRY,
AND WE HAVE TO DEAL WITH IT.
I KNOW THAT!
THAT'S WHY I'VE GOT TO GET
CALUMON BACK,
SO WE CAN GO HOME.
CAN YOU IMAGINE WHAT MY PARENTS
MUST BE GOING THROUGH?
OH, I GUESS YOU CAN.
MY MOM AND GRANDMA
MUST BE PITCHING A FIT.
I BET THEY'RE BOTH
DOING JUST FINE.
I MEAN, I DID SEND THEM
THAT E-MAIL
LETTING THEM KNOW
YOU'RE OKAY.
WHAT?
SENT THEM AN E-MAIL?
WHEN DID THIS HAPPEN?
OH. WELL, IT HAPPENED
A WHILE BACK.
WHEN WE GOT SEPARATED
FROM YOU GUYS,
WE GOT E-MAILED
FROM THE REAL WORLD.
SO I KIND OF -- WELL, I GUESS
YOU COULD SAY THAT I --
PRETENDED TO BE ME AND SENT AN
E-MAIL TO MY MOM AND GRANDMA.
THAT SUM IT UP?
WHOA! HOLD ON THERE!
CALM DOWN.
I ONLY DID IT BECAUSE IF I SAID
YOU WEREN'T WITH US,
YOUR MOM AND GRANDMA
WOULD HAVE GOTTEN WORRIED.
SO...
OKAY,
GO AHEAD AND HIT ME.
WHY?
HUH?
THANKS FOR DOING THAT.
YOU DIDN'T PUT A GIRLY HEART
OR SOMETHING AFTER IT, DID YOU?
UH...
DID YOU?
WHAT? I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT A HEART LOOKS LIKE.
HEY!
YOU DID, DIDN'T YOU?
OH, MAN!
WHEN I GET THROUGH WITH YOU,
THE DEVAS WILL SEEM LIKE
CUDDLY LITTLE KITTY CATS.
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY,
TERRIERMON?
I MEAN, YOU'RE UP FOR THIS,
AREN'T YOU?
MOMENTI!
I'M SO UP FOR THIS,
MY EARS ARE POPPING!
THAT'S GREAT.
WE'LL BE ABLE TO HELP SUSIE.
Rika: A HEART?
EVEN A SMILEY FACE
WOULD HAVE BEEN BETTER.
UM, YEAH,
TH-THAT'S WHAT I PUT.
YOU USED A SMILEY FACE?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
HUMAN FOOLS, YOU HAVE DEFILED
MY WORLD LONG ENOUGH.
NOW YOU'LL PAY
FOR DESTROYING MY SERVANTS
AND TURNING THESE OTHER DIGIMON
TO THE SIDE OF HUMANS.
AND YOU'LL PAY DEARLY,
I PROMISE YOU.
SO COME CLOSER,
BICKERING BUFFOONS.
I'LL TEACH YOU WHAT THE TRUE
POWER OF A DIGIMON CAN DO.
A SMILEY FACE?!
Guilmon:
GUYS, WE'RE HERE.
WOW! THIS THING LOOKS LIKE
IT GOES ON FOREVER.
YOU HAVE BETTER EYES THAN ME.
I CAN'T SEE FOREVER.
OOOOOHHHHH!!
UH-OH!
HERE WE GO!
[ GROWLS ]
WHAT IS IT, BOY?
WHAT'S WRONG?
TERRIERMON?
RENAMON, WHAT?
SOMETHING'S HERE.
I CAN FEEL IT.
IT'S LIKE A TERRIBLE
OVERPOWERING ANGER
THAT WILL CRUSH US
IF WE LET OUR GUARD DOWN.
IT'S HIM.
WE'VE GOT TO KEEP MOVING.
YOU'D THINK WE'D LEARN
TO MOVE AWAY FROM DANGER
INSTEAD OF TOWARD IT.
Rika: SOME OF US ARE JUST
THICKHEADED I GUESS.
Guilmon:
SHE MEANS YOU, TAKATO.
YEAH, YEAH, I KNOW.
HE SURE LIKES BIG DOORS,
DOESN'T HE?
MY SOVEREIGN!
PLEASE HEAR MY HUMBLE REQUEST!
[ RUMBLING ]
WELL, IT'S GOOD HE'S GOT
AN OPEN-DOOR POLICY.
GOOD FOR US,
OR GOOD FOR HIM?
I DON'T KNOW.
SOVEREIGN --
TRESPASSERS, YOU HAVE DISTURBED
THE LAYER OF ZHUQIAOMON,
SOVEREIGN OF THE DIGITAL WORLD
AND PROTECTOR
OF ITS INHABITANTS.
LOOK UPON MY COUNTENANCE
AND TREMBLE WITH FEAR,
FOR IN MY EYES
YOU SEE YOUR OWN UNDOING.
[ GROWLING ]
UM, OKAY.
I'M TREMBLING OVER HERE.
YEAH, TREMBLING SURE LOOKS LIKE
THE THING TO DO RIGHT NOW.
[ GRUNTS ]
YOU'VE GOT A FRIEND OF OURS!
GIVE CALUMON BACK!
SUCH A LARGE DEMAND FROM SUCH
A SMALL CREATURE.
WHY SHOULD I GIVE HIM UP?
SO YOU CAN TAKE HIM BACK
TO THE OTHER WORLD?
THE CATALUS BELONGS HERE.
THE CATALUS? WHAT DO YOU
THINK HE MEANS BY THAT?
HE MUST BE TALKING
ABOUT CALUMON.
[ Thinking ]
I CAN'T LET HIM SCARE ME.
I'VE GOT TO GET CALUMON
AND BRING SUSIE BACK
TO THE REAL WORLD.
I'VE JUST GOT TO!
YOU'RE NOT GONNA SCARE ME OFF!
HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
"SCARE YOU OFF"?
WHAT ABOUT US?
RIKA, RENAMON.
HEY, YOU DIDN'T FORGET US,
DID YOU?
TAKATO, GUILMON.
I JUST HOPE YOU KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
GETTING YOURSELVES INTO.
ARE YOU READY TO FIGHT?
ANYTIME, ANYWHERE.
[ Thinking ]THERE I GO SHOOTING
MY MOUTH OFF AGAIN.
THEN LET'S TEACH THIS GUY A
LESSON HE WON'T FORGET!
ALL: DIGIMODIFY!
MATRIX DIGIVOLUTION --
ACTIVATE!
TERRIERMON MATRIX,
DIGIVOLVE TO...
RENAMON MATRIX,
GUILMON MATRIX,
DIGIVOLVE TO...
RAPIDMON!
TAOMON!
[ ROARING ]
WARGRAMMON!
AM I SUPPOSED
TO BE AFRAID?
NO, YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO TAKE
YOUR BEATING
LIKE A GOOD LITTLE VILLAIN.
HUH?!
LET'S GO, GUYS!
YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME.
I WAS JUST ABOUT TO SAY
THE SAME THING.
PHOENIX FIRE!
AAAAH!
AAAH!
UGH!
NO, RAPIDMON!
I THINK THAT WENT REALLY WELL,
DON'T YOU?
HE TOOK THEM DOWN
IN ONE SHOT.
HOW CAN HE BE SO POWERFUL?
YOU DIGIMON DEPEND ON THESE
HUMANS MAGGOTS FOR STRENGTH,
BUT WE DON'T NEED FILTHY
WEAKLINGS
IN THE COMING BATTLE.
PHOENIX FIRE!
WE SHALL SEE WHO'S WEAK.
YOU BROUGHT THE HUMAN
INFESTATION TO OUR WORLD,
AND IF IT CRUMBLES, IT WILL BE
YOUR FAULT.
UGH!
IF HE KEEPS THIS UP,
WE'LL ALL BE ROASTED!
TAOMON, WE'VE GOT
TO FIGURE OUT SOME WAY
TO DIGIVOLVE
TO MEGA LEVEL.
I'VE GOT MY HANDS FULL JUST
TRYING TO MAINTAIN THIS SHIELD.
IF ONLY GUILMON AND I
COULD FIGURE OUT
HOW TO BE GALLANTMON AGAIN.
BUT HOW?
[ BEEPING ]
MAN, TWO SAD GIRLS.
HEY, KAZU.
[ GROANS ]
I HAVEN'T EVEN STARTED
DATING.
I'VE GOT TO DEAL WITH
TWO SAD GIRLS.
ONCE YOU START DATING, I'M SURE
YOU'LL MAKE MANY GIRLS SAD.
WHAT?!
WON'T YOU?
JUST WATCH SUSIE.
HUMANS ARE SO CONFUSING.
OH, LEOMON, YOU'D STILL BE ALIVE
IF IT WEREN'T FOR ME.
CAPITULATE, FOOLS!
HA! WE DON'T KNOW
THE MEANING OF THE WORD!
ATOMIC BLASTERS!
RAPID-FIRE!
Rika: HIS HEAT
IS LIKE A BARRIER.
NOTHING CAN GET THROUGH IT.
PHOENIX FIRE!
AAAH!
PICK ON SOMEONE
YOUR OWN SIZE!
[ GRUNTS ]
ATOMIC BLAST!
OH, NO, NOT NOW!
PHOENIX FIRE!
UGH!
NO! RAPIDMON!
[ ELECTRICITY CRACKLING ]
WITHOUT THE ABILITY TO
DIGIVOLVE, I'M POWERLESS.
I MIGHT AS WELL
NOT EVEN BE HERE.
LOPMON...
YOU ARE
MY LAST REMAINING DEVA.
COME BACK TO ME,
AND I'LL FORGIVE YOUR BETRAYAL.
TOGETHER WE WILL DESTROY
THESE TRAITORS
AND THEIR DISGUSTING HUMANS!
I CAN NO LONGER SERVE SOMEONE
WHO BELIEVES IN VIOLENCE.
THEN YOU'RE
A TRAITOR, TOO.
SAY WHAT YOU WILL,
BUT I SHALL NOT BE SWAYED.
SO BE IT!
PHOENIX FIRE!
AAAH!
UGH!
[ GASPS ]
IT'S LOPMON!
[ BEEPING ]
HUH?
AAAH!
UGH!
[STATIC]
NO, LOPMON!
YOU'RE STAYING!
[ GASPS ]
[ Thinking ]
LOPMON!
HUH?
HMM?
OH!
[ GRUNTING ]
YOU SURE THAT'S SAFE?
NO.
OKAY!
[ Thinking ]
LOPMON NEEDS ME.
MAYBE SHE CAN GET BY
WITH JUST MY PRAYERS.
LOPMON,
YOU CAN'T LEAVE ME!
[ GASPS ]
AAH!
HOLD ON, LOPMON!
I'M COMING!
SHE CAN FLY?!
I FEAR I'LL NEVER UNDERSTAND
THESE HUMANS.
HEY, WHAT'S ALL THE JABBERING
ABOUT OVER HERE?
UH...
UM, WHERE DID SUSIE GO?
SHE FLEW AWAY.
SHE FLEW AWAY?!
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
BUT HOW?! YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO BE WATCHING HER!
I WAS.
I WATCHED THE WHOLE THING.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT,
YOU BIG DOOFUS!
HOT, HOT, HOT!
THANK YOU, WARGRAMMON!
[ Moaning ] MM-HMM.
HAD ENOUGH YET, MAGGOT LOVERS?
NEVER!
UGH!
I MEAN, IT'S NOT LIKE
WE LIKE BEING ROAST.
IT'S JUST --
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN.
WE'LL NEVER GIVE UP!
EVEN IF -- UGH!
RAPIDMON, BACK OFF!
YOU'RE HURT TOO BADLY.
IF YOU SUSTAIN ANY MORE DAMAGE,
YOUR DATA WILL BE DESTROYED!
BACK OFF?!
THERE'S NO WAY I'M GONNA LET
THIS OVERGROWN CANARY STOP ME!
WHAT WAS I THINKING?
I MEAN,
I KNEW YOU WERE HURT,
BUT ALL I COULD THINK
ABOUT WAS SUSIE.
HOW COULD I SEND YOU
INTO BATTLE LIKE THAT?
I GUESS I'M JUST ABOUT THE WORST
DIGIMON TAMER THERE EVER WAS.
NO, IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT!
I SHOULDN'T HAVE PUSHED
YOU TO FIGHT.
I SHOULD HAVE FOUND
ANOTHER WAY.
LISTEN TO ME!
IT'S THE BIRD'S FAULT,
AND I WON'T LET HIM WIN!
YOU STILL MEAN
TO OPPOSE ME?
OR DIE TRYING!
AS YOU WISH!
PHOENIX FIRE!
AAAAH!
UGH! AAAH!
UGH!
NO!
TERRIERMON!
SORRY, HENRY.
I TRIED.
BUT BIRDBRAIN
WAS TOO MUCH FOR ME.
DON'T BE SORRY,
TERRIERMON.
I WAS THE ONE
WHO FAILED YOU.
HA! WHAT ARE YOU, HENRY,
THE CENTER OF THE UNIVERSE?
WHAT, YOU THINK
THE SUN WON'T RISE
IF YOU'RE NOT THERE
TO GREET IT OR SOMETHING?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
JUST LOOK BEHIND YOU,
HENRY.
HUH?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO
EVERYTHING YOURSELF.
THEY'RE ALL HERE TO HELP YOU.
LET THEM.
WHOA!
HUH?!
WHA-- SUSIE?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE,
SUSIE?
WELL, YOU CALLED ME.
DIDN'T YOU, SILLY?
I CALLED YOU?
YOU MAY BE RIGHT.
GUESS YOUR DEMANDING
BIG-BROTHER VOICE
DOESN'T WORK SO WELL, HUH?
WELL, THERE'S NO WAY
I CAN STOP FIGHTING
IF SUSIE'S
GONNA BE IN DANGER.
TERRIERMON, YOU CAN'T.
REMEMBER WHAT YOU TOLD ME
IF I EVER GOT LOST?
MEET BACK AT YOUR HOUSE.
THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'LL ALL MEET BACK THERE.
LOPMON'S COMING, TOO,
RIGHT?
I CAN COME?
MM-HMM.
[ Growling ]
WE JUST GOT TO GET PAST
THAT TURKEY!
YOU'RE GONNA TELL
YOUR FRIENDS
YOU GOT BEATEN
BY A TURKEY, HENRY?
NOT A CHANCE!
COME ON!
LET'S DO THIS TOGETHER!
BIOMERGE ACTIVATE!
TERRIERMON,
BIOMERGE TO...
...MEGAGARGOMON!
HOW DO SPIDERS
DO THIS ALL THE TIME?
THIS IS REALLY HARD WORK.
PLUS, IT'S SO DARK AND DIRTY
IN ALL THIS DIRTY DARKNESS.
HUH?
HEY, A LIGHT.
IT'S ALL WARM AND INVITING
LIKE A BATHTUB WAVING AT ME --
A BATHTUB FULL OF HOPE!
ANOTHER BIOMERGE!
AMAZING!
MEGAGARGOMON!
SPECIAL ATTACK --
GARGO MISSILES.
HE SHOULD BE CALLED
"HUMONGO, ENORMOUS,
SEVEN-STORIES-TALL MISSILE"
FROM THE LOOK OF HIM.
[ GASPS ]
WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
DID I REALLY BECOME A DIGIMON?
CALL ME CRAZY, BUT I THINK WE
BECAME ONE TOGETHER.
THIS IS INCREDIBLE!
I CAN FEEL YOUR POWER
FLOWING THROUGH ME,
GIVING ME STRENGTH!
ME, TOO!
I'M NOT IN PAIN ANYMORE.
THEN LET'S GO GET HIM!
THAT FELT GOOD!
SAY IT AGAIN!
DIGIMON AND HUMANS
DIGIVOLVE TOGETHER?
THIS IS AN ABOMINATION!
YOU HAVE TAINTED THE VERY CORE
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD,
AND YOU WILL PAY!
DESOLATION BLAST!
NOW WHERE WILL YOU RUN?
UGH!
IS THAT ALL YOU'VE GOT?
AND YOU CALL US PATHETIC!
YOU DARE TAUNT ME?
YEP, AND I'LL DO IT
AGAIN, TOO!
HYAH!
POWER PUMMEL!
YAAAAAH!
HYAH!
YAH!
UGH!
THAT STILL NOT ENOUGH
FOR YOU?
MEGA BARRAGE!
UGH!
PHOENIX FIRE!
YOU THINK
THAT SCARES US NOW?
WHY DON'T YOU TRY
THIS ONE ON FOR SIZE?!
GARGO MISSILE!
Rika: HE'S BREAKING UP
ZHUQIAOMON'S ATTACK.
AAAAAH!
YOU THINK YOU CAN DEFEAT ME
THAT EASILY?
AAAAAAAAH!
LOOKS LIKE THAT WOULD BE
A BIG "YES."
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
WE DID IT, HENRY!
YES, WE DID.
NOW LET'S GET CALUMON
AND GO HOME.
AW! I'M JUST
GETTING WARMED UP!
TERRIERMON!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT'S OVER.
YEAH, I KNOW.
[ Thinking ]SO, WHAT'S NEXT?
CAN WE REALLY JUST GO HOME,
OR ARE THERE OTHER
BATTLES WE HAVE TO FIGHT?
THANKS, HENRY. WE'D HAVE BEEN
LOST WITHOUT YOU TWO.
NOT AT ALL.
WE ARE A TEAM, AREN'T WE?
ARE WE GONNA BE SAPPY
ALL DAY?
[ Thinking ]
DIGIMON AND HUMAN TOGETHER --
THEY HAVE THE POWER TO DEFEAT
THE MOST POWERFUL DIGIMO.
COME ON!
LET'S GO FIND CALUMON!
[ ALL GASP ]
OH, NO!
WHOA!
[ LAUGHING EVILLY ]
SURPRISED? YOU DARE BELIEVE YOU
COULD DEFEAT ME?
I AM A SOVEREIGN.
THERE WILL BE NOTHING LEFT OF
YOU BUT ASHES WHEN I'M DONE.
PREPARE TO MEET YOUR DOOM!
MAN, THIS GUY
JUST WON'T STAY DOWN!
MAYBE HENRY AND THE OTHES
WON'T GET HOME.
TO FIND OUT, KEEP WATCHIG
"DIGIMON: DIGITAL MONSTERS"
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DI, DI, DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DI, DI, DI
♪ DI, DI