THE TAMERS AND THEIR FAMILIES
ALL MET UP WITH YAMAKI
AND THE MONSTER MAKERS
TO FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO STOP THE D-REAPER
AND SAVE JERI.
OVERCOME WITH GRIEF,
JERI'S DAD RUSHED OUT
TO FACE THE BIG RED BLOB
AND BEGGED IT
TO GIVE HIS DAUGHTER BACK.
THAT DIDN'T GO SO WELL.
THE TAMERS BIOMERGED AND TRIED
A MORE FORCEFUL APPROACH.
THAT DIDN'T WORK, EITHER.
JUST WHEN ALL SEEMED LOST,
THE MONSTER MAKERS COMPLETED
THE FINISHING TOUCHES
ON THE ARK.
SHIBUMI USED A BLUE CARD
TO BRING GRANI
INTO THE REAL WORLD,
BUT IT TOOK GALLANTMON
TO BRING HIM TO LIFE.
HE CLIMBED ABOARD
HIS TRUSTED STEED,
AND THE TWO OF THEM
RODE OFF INTO BATTLE.
DI-DI-DI
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DI-DI-DIGIMON,
DIGIMON
DI-DI-DI
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS
TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE
WORLD
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE
INTO CHAMPIONS
DIGIMODIFY
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON --
DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
THE D-REAPER'S INSATIABLE.
IT'S TAKEN OVER
MOST OF THE CITY,
THE FREEWAYS,
EVEN OUR COMMUNICATION SYSTEMS.
HOW DO WE KNOW THAT WE'RE
NOT GOING TO BE NEXT?
WE DON'T,
SO DON'T GET TOO ATTACHED
TO THIS PLACE.
WE MIGHT HAVE TO LEAVE
IN A HURRY.
OH...
[ Thinking ]
WHAT ABOUT JERI?
SHE'S STILL OUT THERE
SOMEWHERE,
AND I'M NOT LEAVING
UNTIL I FIND HER.
AAH!
BEELZEMON, WAKE UP!
WE'RE TRAPPED,
AND THE D-REAPER'S GOT YOU
IN AN OCTOPUS THINGY!
THIS IS NOT A GOOD TIME
TO NAP!
Man: LEVEL ONE SYSTEMS CHECK
ON GRANI COMPLETE.
COMMENCING WITH LEVEL TWO.
DAISY, AS SOON AS WE'RE DONE
RUNNING THE SYSTEM CHECKS
ON GRANI, YOU CAN START
INSTALLING THE NEW EQUIPMENT.
THE SOONER, THE BETTER.
WONDERFUL.
I'VE NEVER SEEN A MORE AMAZING
PIECE OF MACHINERY.
WELL, I HAVE.
TAKATO'S PARENTS HAVE
A MACHINE IN THEIR STORE
THAT MAKES BREAD!
[ Laughs ] WELL, I GUESS
THERE'S NO WAY
GRANI HERE CAN COMPETE
WITH THAT.
IT'S TOUGH.
OH...
RILEY!
ALL RIGHT,
WHAT'S ALL THE COMMOTION?
JUST WATCH.
WE STUMBLED ON THIS
WHEN WE WERE GOING THROUGH
GRANI'S MEMORY.
THEY'RE IMAGES IT RECORDED
WHEN IT WAS
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD.
LOOK AT
ALL THE DESTRUCTION.
NO!
[ BOTH GASP ]
OH, NO, ZHUQIAOMON!
THEY CAN'T LAST MUCH LONGER.
ACCORDING THE DATA
WE PULLED FROM GRANI,
ABOUT 47% OF THE DIGITAL WORLD
HAS ALREADY BEEN DELETED.
AT THIS RATE, THE WHOLE PLANE
WILL BE WIPED OUT
IN A MATTER OF DAYS,
IF NOT HOURS.
AND IT COULD BE
THE SAME FOR US.
LOOK AT THESE IMAGES.
WE'VE JUST RECEIVED
SATELLITE PICTURES
FROM GOVERNMENT
INTELLIGENCE.
SO WE'RE NOT THE ONLY ONES
UNDER ATTACK.
WHERE ELSE HAS D-REAPER
APPEARED?
WELL, A MORE ACCURATE QUESTION
IS WHERE HASN'T IT APPEARED?
D-REAPER'S ATTACKING
COMMUNICATIONS SYSTEMS
FROM NORTH AMERICA
TO ZIMBABWE.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE WHOLE WORLD'S
UNDER SIEGE.
MY FAMILY.
WHAT WILL THEY DO?
THIS IS MADNESS.
WE GIVE IT EVERYTHING
WE GOT,
WE PUT OUR CHILDREN
IN DANGER, AND FOR WHAT?
WE DON'T HAVE
ANY OTHER CHOICE.
THERE'S NO PLAN "B,"
SO WE HAVE TO FIGHT.
AND BESIDES, AS LONG
AS WE'RE HERE,
THERE'S ALWAYS HOPE.
THAT'S A LESSON I LEARNED
FROM WORKING WITH YOUR SONS
AND DAUGHTERS, MR. MATSUKI.
THEY DON'T GIVE UP,
AND THEY FIGHT
WITH THEIR HEARTS
AND SOULS.
AND NOW IT'S OUR TURN.
BEELZEMON!
[ GROANING ]
JERI!
HANG ON, KID! I'M GONNA
GET YOU OUT OF HERE!
HEY, JERI, WE'RE GONNA
GET OUT OF HERE! WHOA!
WHAT WAS THAT?
I DON'T SPEAK D-REAPER,
BUT IT SURE SOUNDS MAD.
HUH?
AAH! AAH!
JERI!
OH, BLESS MY BOLTS.
DO YOU SEE WHAT I SEE?
WHAT IN THE NAME OF PETE
IS THAT?
LOOKS LIKE MORE BAD NEWS
TO ME.
IT SEEMS THE D-REAPER
IS TRYING TO DEFEND ITS CORE,
THE KERNEL OF CONSCIOUSNESS.
LOOK, THERE'S SOMEONE
IN THERE.
IT'S BEELZEMON.
LET'S GIVE HIM A HAND,
GUYS. WHAT DO YOU SAY?
[ BOTH SIGH ]
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL BE CAREFUL.
NOW LET'S GO!
HUH? WAIT UP!
HEY, LOPMON,
YOU STAY BEHIND
AND LOOK AFTER SUZIE,
OKAY?
ALL RIGHT.
DON'T WORRY.
YOU CAN COUNT ON ME.
[ PANTING ]
THE KERNEL SPHERE.
I BET THAT'S WHERE JERI IS.
WE'VE GOT COMPANY!
[ GROWLING ]
PREPARE TO MEET
YOUR PROGRAMMER!
SHOWTIME, GUILMON!
YEP, I'M READY.
HANG IN THERE, JERI!
WE'RE COMING TO GET YOU!
BIOMERGE ACTIVATE!
GUILMON BIOMERGE TO...
DI-DI-DI
DI-DI-DIGIMON
DIGIMON
DI-DI-DI
GALLANTMON!
D-REAPER, YOU'VE DESTROYED
EVERYTHING WE LOVE!
IF YOU THINK WE'RE GOING
TO TAKE IT LYING DOWN,
YOU HAVE ANOTHER THINK
COMING!
WE'RE MAD AS HECK, AND WE'RE
NOT GONNA TAKE IT ANYMORE!
BIOMERGE ACTIVATE!
IT LOOKS REALLY DANGEROUS
OUT THERE,
BUT I GUESS THEY DON'T
NEED OUR HELP
IF THEY ASKED US
TO STAY HERE, HUH, LOPMON?
YEAH, I GUESS SO.
OH, I JUST HOPE
YOU'RE RIGHT, SUZIE.
GRANI'S NEW EQUIPMENT
IS INSTALLED.
WE ARE READY FOR TAKEOFF.
WELL, IT'S NOW OR NEVER.
RIGHT. TAKE OFF!
UHH! UHH! UHH!
ALL RIGHT, ENOUGH
WITH THE BOBBING AND WEAVING.
LET'S SHOW THEM
WHAT WE GOT.
SPIRIT STRIKE!
GET 'EM NOW!
WITH PLEASURE!
THUNDERCLAP!
THEY JUST KEEP COMING BACK.
AHH!
MEGA BARRAGE!
HMM?
TAKATO, WE'LL KEEP THE AGENTS
B!SY FOR A WHILE.
YOU WORK ON FINDING JERI.
GOOD IDEA.
GRANI!
LET'S GO!
[ GROANING ]
HEY, YOU D-REAPER SCUM!
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU HAVE EARS
OR WHAT,
BUT LISTEN UP
AND LISTEN GOOD!
YOU MAY HAVE ME
HOGTIED FOR NOW...
[ GROANING ]
BUT I WON'T LET YOU
STOP ME!
[ GRUNTING ]
AAH!
LOOK, JERI, BEELZEMON'S
GOING TO BREAK FREE SOON!
THEN HE CAN HELP
GET US OUT, TOO!
COME ON, BEELZEMON,
YOU CAN DO IT!
BEELZEMON?
[ GRUNTING ]
HUH? WHAT'S GOING ON?
BEELZEMON!
HE WENT BYE-BYE.
JERI!
AAH!
WHAT HAPPENED?
All: BEELZEMON!
WELL, IT'S ABOUT TIME
YOU SHOWED UP.
JERI AND CALUMON
ARE TRAPPED
INSIDE
WHATEVER THAT IS.
I HAVE AN IDEA!
LET'S ATTACK THAT THING
TOGETHER!
YOU GOT IT!
AHH... CORONA BLASTER!
SHIELD OF THE JUST!
OH, MAN! WE DIDN'T EVEN
MAKE A DENT!
AND WE HAVE MORE TROUBLE
THAN WE STARTED WITH.
LOOK AT THIS.
WHAT IS IT, RILEY?
I DON'T THINK I CAN HANDLE
ANOTHER SURPRISE.
YOU'LL LIKE THIS ONE.
OUR RECEIVERS PICKED UP
THE D-REAPER'S SIGNAL.
NOW WE CAN ACTUALLY SEE
WHAT'S GOING ON
FROM THE D-REAPER'S
POINT OF VIEW.
THAT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
FINALLY, A DEVELOPMENT
THAT MIGHT ACTUALLY HELP US.
THIS IS NOT GOOD!
THAT'S JUST WHAT MEETS
THE EYE.
D-REAPER SHOULD BE ABLE TO SEE
THROUGH LAYERS OF PROGRAMMING.
TRANSLATING SIGNAL...
NOW.
[ STATIC ]
IT CAN'T BE.
TAKATO!
[ GASPING ]
MOM, WHO'S THAT?
CHECK IT OUT.
[ PEOPLE MURMURING ]
[ HORNS HONKING ]
Girl: WHAT'S GOING ON?
Girl #2:
LOOK, IT'S TAKATO!
[ STUDENTS MURMURING ]
HE IS SO COOL!
HUH?
[ PANTING ]
TAKATO, YOU CAN DO IT!
[ PEOPLE SHOUTING ]
[ THUD ]
[ WEAPONS FIRING ]
THERE'S TOO MANY OF THEM!
HOLD ON!
WE'RE RIGHT ABOVE YOU.
HENRY!
IT'S MY BABY!
I DIDN'T KNOW.
HOW COULD THEY MERGE
WITH THE DIGIMON?
HOW COULD I HAVE LET IT
GET THIS FAR?
[ Thinking ] I'VE NEVER
FELT SO HELPLESS.
THERE MUST BE SOMETHING
I CAN DO.
OH...
BLAZING ICE!
[ GLASS SHATTERS ]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
LOPMON, WHAT'S WRONG?
I CAN'T SIT BY
WHILE OUR FRIENDS ARE IN DANGER.
I JUST CAN'T.
HELP ME, SUZIE!
HUH? UH-HUH!
AAH!
LOPMON DIGIVOLVE TO...
ANTYLAMON!
GO FOR IT, SUZIE!
DIGIMODIFY! YAY!
ACTIVATE!
THANKS, SUZIE.
I KNEW YOU COULD DO IT.
AHH!
TAKE CARE OF HENRY AND HIS
FRIENDS FOR ME, OKAY?
TALLY, CAN YOU FIND ME
A SATELLITE
THAT HASN'T BEEN DESTROYED
BY THE D-REAPER?
RIGHT AWAY!
GUARDIAN BARRAGE!
FEEL THE WRATH
OF BLACK WAR KAZUMON!
WHAT'S THE BIG IDEA?
[ BOTH SCREAMING ]
BUNNY BLAZE!
HEY, WE'RE SAVED
BY THE BUNNY!
BUNNY, MY EYE!
THAT'S A ONE-RABBIT ARMY!
SHE'S WONDERFUL.
THERE'S SO MANY OF THEM.
I HOPE THE OTHERS
ARE ALL RIGHT.
AHH! UHH! UHH! AHH!
AAH!
YOU ASKED FOR IT,
AND YOU GOT IT!
AAH!
BEELZEMON!
NOW WHAT?
AAH!
OKAY, JERI, DON'T PANIC.
DON'T FREAK OUT.
LOOK AT ME.
I'M FINE! I'M RELAXED!
I'M GOING TO GO
OUT OF MY MIND
IF I DON'T GET
OUT OF HERE!
[ SCREAMING ]
[ GROWLS ]
COMMENCING DATA EXTRACTION
FROM KATOU, JERI'S
MEMORY.
HEY, YOU'RE USING
JERI'S VOICE!
ANALYSIS COMPLETE.
SUBJECT POSITIVELY
IDENTIFIED AS BEELZEMON,
A DIGIMON THAT DIGIVOLVED
FROM IMPMON.
WHOA! HMM?
BEELZEMON, A DIGIMON
THAT TRIED TO HARM
JERI KATOU
AND OTHER HUMAN CHILDREN
WHEN THEY WERE
IN THE DIGITAL WORLD.
BEELZEMON, THE DIGIMON
THAT DESTROYED
JERI KATOU'S PARTNER LEOMON
IN ORDER TO LOAD HIS DATA
AND BECOME STRONGER.
AAH!
BEELZEMON, THE DIGIMON
THAT DESTROYED LEOMON...
DESTROYED LEOMON...
SHUT UP! SHUT UP!
STOP USING JERI'S VOICE!
DESTROYED LEOMON...
IS THAT SUPPOSED
TO MAKE ME FEEL BAD?
WELL, IT'S NOT WORKING!
I DON'T CARE WHAT YOU THINK!
STOP THIS!
AAH!
[ GROWLING ]
WHY CAN'T YOU SEE?
NO!
I'LL KEEP LOADING DATA
UNTIL NO ONE CAN STOP ME!
WHAT I DID
IS BEYOND FORGIVENESS.
I DON'T NEED ANYONE
TO TELL ME THAT.
NO MATTER WHAT I DO,
I CAN'T CHANGE THE PAST.
BUT WHAT I CAN DO
IS SAVE JERI!
AND LET ME TELL YOU, NO TALKING
EYEBALL'S GONNA STOP ME!
CORONA DESTROYER!
HOW'S IT FEEL TO BE ON THE OTHER
END OF THE WHOOPING STICK?
[ SCREAMS ]
COME ON, JERI, HE'S TRYING
TO SAVE YOU.
DON'T YOU EVEN CARE?
I KNOW EVERYTHING LOOKS
VERY BAD RIGHT NOW,
BUT BEELZEMON'S
NOT GIVING UP,
SO YOU SHOULDN'T GIVE UP,
EITHER.
OH, JERI, PLEASE,
SAY SOMETHING.
HOW'D YOU LIKE THAT?
NOT SO CHATTY NOW,
ARE YOU?
WHAT?
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS!
AAH!
NO!
[ GROANING ]
AAH!
TAKE IT.
IT'S MY FAVORITE,
AND YOU CAN SHOOT
THE BAD GUYS WITH IT.
HUH? THANKS, MAKO.
THIS JUST MIGHT COME IN
HANDIER THAN YOU THINK.
THAT WAS A GIFT
FROM MAKO.
I'LL MAKE YOU SORRY YOU EVER
CAME TO THIS WORLD.
I'LL MAKE YOU PAY!
AAH!
WE HAVE TO SAVE THEM.
AHH!
UHH! UHH!
UHH...
Yamaki: TAKATO, COME IN.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
HUH? MR. YAMAKI?
WE GOT THROUGH.
HE CAN HEAR US.
BINGO! HA HA!
THAT'S A BRILLIANT IDEA,
USING THE SATELLITE
TO TALK TO TAKATO.
FORTUNATELY, IT'S NOT
THE ONLY IDEA WE HAVE.
OKAY, TAKATO,
YOU NEED TO LISTEN CAREFULLY.
GRANI HAS BEEN EQUIPPED
WITH A POWERFUL WEAPON
CALLED THE YUGGOTH BLASTER.
I WANT YOU TO USE IT
ON THE D-REAPER.
WITH PLEASURE, SIR!
[ PANTING ]
BEELZEMON!
HMM?
YOU BETTER GET
OUT OF THE WAY!
YUGGOTH BLASTER!
AHH!
UHH!
[ SHOUTS ]
Beelzemon: JERI!
Takato: JERI, YOU HAVE
TO LISTEN TO ME!
BEELZEMON'S BENT ON SAVING YOU.
HE'S GOING TO KEEP TRYING
NO MATTER WHAT,
SO, PLEASE, YOU HAVE
TO LET HIM HELP YOU!
TAKATO?
[ GRUNTING ]
BREAK!
WHY...WON'T...YOU...BREAK?
YOU DUMB STINKIN'
FISHBOWL!
LET...HER...GO!
BE...EL...ZE...MON?
I'M GONNA GET YOU OUT,
JERI,
IF IT'S THE LAST THING
I FREAKING DO!
BEELZEMON...
HE REALLY WANTS TO SAVE ME?
HUH?
I DON'T...UNDERSTAND.
[ GRUNTING ]
[ PANTING ]
AAH!
GIVE ME THE STRENGTH
I NEED!
BEELZEMON?
BEELZEMON, PLEASE HELP ME!
AAH!
FIST...
OF...
THE BEAST KING!
LEOMON?
[ SOBBING ]
YAY, HE DID IT!
BEELZEMON DID IT!
WE'RE FREE!
[ PANTING ]
JERI, GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
[ WHIMPERING ]
LET'S GO, JERI!
WHAT ARE YOU WAITING FOR?
COME ON!
YOU CAN DO IT, JERI!
LET'S GO!
IT'S CLOSING.
HURRY,
BEFORE IT'S TOO LATE.
[ WHIMPERING ]
UHH...
TAKE MY HAND! TAKE IT!
[ WHIMPERING ]
OOH...
I'M TRYING TO HELP YOU!
PLEASE!
YOU'RE NOT...LEOMON.
WHAT?
JERI, TAKE HIS HAND!
AAH!
HUH? TAKATO! IS THAT YOU?
JERI!
NO!
JERI, JUST LET ME
SAVE YOU!
I NEED TO SAVE YOU!
JERI! HUH?
BEELZEMON, WATCH OUT!
HUH?
AAH!
[ GROANING ]
[ BOTH GASP ]
NO, BEELZEMON!
OH, NO.
OH...AHH...
PLEASE! I JUST NEED...
ONE MORE CHANCE!
JERI!
I NEVER THOUGHT I'D SAY THIS,
BUT POOR BEELZEMON.
WILL HE GET THAT OTHER CHANCE?
FIND OUT ON THE NEXT
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS."