CALUMON WAS IMPRISONED
BY THE DIGIMON SOVEREIGN
DEEP IN THE HEART
OF THE DIGITAL WORLD.
JUST AS TAKATO AND HENRY
WENT OFF TO FIND HIM,
BEELZEMON SHOWED UP
SPOILING FOR A FIGHT.
TERRIERMON MATRIX DIGIVOLVD
TO RAPIDMON,
BUT BEELZEMON WAS
TOO STRONG FOR HIM.
HEARING TAKATO
SCREAM FOR HELP,
GROWMON AND THE REST
OF THE GANG
LEAPT THROUGH THE DATA STREAM
TO FIND HIM,
BUT BEELZEMON
WAS STILL TOO STRONG.
LEOMON TRIED TO STOP HIM
ON HIS OWN AND WAS DESTROYED.
TAKATO WAS SO FURIOUS
HE ORDERED WARGRAMMON
TO DIGIVOLVE INTO
THE TERRIFYING MEGIDRAMO.
OH, MAN.
TELL ME WHEN IT'S OVER.
DI, DI, DI
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
CHANGE
INTO DIGITAL CHAMPIONS
TO SAVE AND DEFEND THE WORLD
DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIVOLVE INTO CHAMPIONS.
DIGIMODIFY.
DIGIMON, DIGITAL MONSTERS
DIGIMON ARE THE CHAMPIONS
DIGIMON!
HONEY, I'M GOING INTO
THE OFFICE FOR A WHILE.
JOHN YU, DID YOUR
FATHER TELL YOU
WHAT THE WEATHER IS LIKE
IN HONG KONG RIGHT NOW?
WILL SUSIE NEED A HEAVY JACKET
OR JUST SWEATERS?
I GUESS I SHOULD PACK
A JACKET FOR HER JUST IN CASE.
YEAH, GOOD IDEA.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
STOP RIGHT THERE!
JOHN YU, WE'VE
BEEN MARRIED LONG ENOUGH
FOR ME TO KNOW WHEN YOU'RE
HIDING SOMETHING FROM ME.
SUSIE'S NOT IN HONG KONG.
I DREAMT SHE WAS WITH HENRY,
WHEREVER HE IS,
IN THAT TERRIBLE PLACE YOU
WON'T EVEN DISCUSS WITH ME.
I'M SORRY.
THAT'S NOT GOOD ENOUGH!
OUR CHILDREN ARE DISAPPEARING!
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I CAN'T TELL YOU --
NOT YET.
WHEN CAN YOU TELL ME?!
[ Crying ] WHEN?
[ GROWLING ]
GUILMON!
I'M SCARED!
SOMETHING ABOUT THIS JUST
DOESN'T FEEL RIGHT.
I KNOW GUILMON'S A VIRUS TYPE,
BUT I NEVER IMAGINED
HE'D TURN INTO THIS.
MEGIDRAMON --
A VIRUS-TYPE MEGA.
I AGREE WITH YOU GUYS.
I DON'T THINK THIS
WAS SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN.
THAT CAN'T BE GUILMON,
NOT THE GUILMON I CREATED.
[ GROWLING ]
AHHHH!
I MUST ADMIT, THIS IS NOT A VERY
ATTRACTIVE SIDE OF YOU,
PINEAPPLE HEAD.
NOW YOU'RE DROOLING ON ME!
HE'S HORRIBLE!
HORRIBLE?
SHE'S RIGHT,
AND IT'S MY FAULT.
I MADE HIM DIGIVOLVE.
I CREATED HIM WITH MY ANGER,
MY HATRED.
[ RUMBLING ]
AHH!
AS IF THINGS WEREN'T
BAD ENOUGH ALREADY.
WHOA!
OH, NO!
LOOK AT MEGIDRAMON.
I THINK HE'S
RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS.
THAT'S A HAZARD SIGN
ON HIS CHEST.
HE CAN DESTROY
THE WHOLE DIGITAL WORLD.
[ GROWLING ]
Susie: HENRY, HELP ME!
MAKE IT STOP!
I'M COMING!
[ GRUNTS ]
OH, HENRY!
RAPIDMON!
ON MY WAY!
WHOOPSIE DAISY.
JUST IN TIME.
THANKS, BUDDY.
I'VE NEVER LET YOU DOWN BEFORE,
AND I'M NOT ABOUT TO START NOW.
THE WHOLE LAYER'S
ABOUT TO COLLAPSE.
WHAT COULD BE THAT POWERFUL?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
TOTAL CHAOS -- SOMETHING
I TRIED TO PREVENT.
AS NEAR AS I CAN TELL,
AN ENORMOUSLY POWERFUL DIGIMON
IS DISRUPTING THE BASIC
STRUCTURE OF THE DIGITAL WORLD.
WHAT ABOUT THE CHILDREN?
HAVE YOU GOTTEN
ANY WORD FROM THEM?
I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE
TO REACH THEM.
I'M SORRY.
I SUSPECTED THEY MIGHT BE
AT THE CENTER OF THIS,
BUT BEING RIGHT
GIVES ME NO PLEASURE.
BUT THEY'RE --
THEY'RE JUST CHILDREN.
WHAT COULD THEY POSSIBLY
HAVE DONE TO DESERVE THIS,
AND NOW WHEN
WE WERE SO CLOSE
TO COMPLETING THE ARC
TO RESCUE THEM?
WE'RE TOO CLOSE TO FAIL.
I KNOW THIS MAY BE
HARD TO ACCEPT,
BUT I'M CONFIDENT
THEY'LL MAKE IT OUT.
THEY'RE A VERY
RESOURCEFUL BUNCH
WHO'VE PUT ME IN MY PLACE
MORE THAN ONCE.
TRUE, BUT STILL...
IT'S NOT THE SAME.
THEY'RE OUT THERE
ALL ALONE.
THEY'RE NOT ALONE.
THEY HAVE THEIR DIGIMON.
I HOPE THOSE OTHER KIDS
ARE ALL RIGHT.
[ GASPS ]
[ GROWLING ]
PLEASE, GUILMON,
YOU HAVE TO STOP THIS.
LISTEN TO ME.
[ GROWLING ]
DID CHATSURAMON SET ME UP?
WAS THIS HIS PLAN ALL ALONG --
TO HAVE ME DESTROYED?
JUST WHAT DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE DOING?
IF YOU DON'T END THIS FOOLISH
BATTLE IMMEDIATELY,
YOU WILL DESTROY THE ENTIRE
DIGITAL WORLD.
CHATSURAMON WAS A FOOL TO CREATE
A MEGA AS PATHETIC AS YOU.
I'M NOT PATHETIC.
THE TRUTH HURTS, DOESN'T IT?
OF COURSE YOU'RE PATHETIC.
YOU'RE A PAWN IN A GAME
YOU CAN'T EVEN UNDERSTAND.
THAT'S ENOUGH!
GET YOUR HANDS OFF ME!
I'M A DEVA.
YOU'RE NOTHING,
LESS THAN NOTHING!
YOU TALK TOO MUCH,
MONKEY BOY,
BUT YOU DO HAVE
SOMETHING I NEED!
AAHHH!
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING.
MAKU-- AAHHHH!
YA!
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
THAT'S IT.
HE MUST BE STOPPED!
DON'T! I CAN'T LOSE YOU!
RAPIDMON, NO!
HENRY, HE LOADED A DEVA,
JUST SWALLOWED HIM UP
LIKE AN ICE CREAM CONE.
HE'S GOTTA BE STOPPED
OR WE'LL ALL BE DESSERT.
[ GRUNTS ]
FINE, WE'LL BEAT THEM BOTH.
DIGIMODIFY!
MATRIX DIGIVOLUTION,
ACTIVATE!
KYUBIMON MATRIX DIGIVOLVE TO...
...TAOMON.
[ GROWLING ]
[ GRUNTING ]
TRIBEAM!
TALISMAN OF LIGHT!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
PRIMAL ORB!
THAT'S MAKURAMON'S ATTACK.
BEELZEMON MUST HAVE ABSORBED HIS
POWER WHEN HE LOADED HIS DATA.
GET OUT OF THERE!
I DON'T THINK I CAN.
I'M A BUNNY IN A BUBBLE.
OHM!
[ GASPS ]
WHY DON'T THE TWO OF YOU STICK
AROUND FOR DINNER?
AFTER MONKEY BOY, I'M IN THE
MOOD FOR A LITTLE RABBIT STEW
OR FRENCH-FRIED FOX TAIL.
TAOMON.
THEY'RE BOTH TRAPPED LIKE
FLIES -- TOTALLY HELPLESS.
WHAT NOW?
HUH?
RIKA, USE THE ALIAS CARD!
THE ALIAS CARD?
OH!
DIGIMODIFY!
ALIAS, ACTIVATE!
[ GROANS ]
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
AND HE STOLE ALL
OUR ULTIMATE POWER.
AAHHHH!
[ GROWLING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTING ]
YES, MORE POWER!
AAHHH! YAAHHHH!
MUST...CONTROL...IT.
AAAHHHHHH!
I CAN'T STAND IT!
MAKE HIM STOP!
AAHHH!
Takato: GUILMON! NO.
[ GROANS ]
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
HE BEAT MEGIDRAMON!
YEAH, AND WENT RIGHT
TO HIS HEAD.
[ GASPS ]
NO.
HE'S WHAT I CALL
A REALLY LOUSY WINNER.
THAT'S CREEPING ME OUT.
[ LAUGHING ]
I'M SORRY, JERI.
[ CRYING ]
I JUST CAN'T
TAKE ANYMORE, TAKATO.
I CAN'T.
I KNOW.
I DON'T LIKE IT, EITHER.
STOP!
DON'T COME NEAR ME.
GUILMON WAS SO SWEET AND CUTE,
AND LOOK WHAT YOU DID TO HIM.
HUH?
THE DISTURBANCE APPEARS
TO BE NEUTRALIZED.
I THINK THEY'RE
OUT OF DANGER.
OH, THANK GOODNESS.
I FEEL SO HELPLESS.
WEAREHELPLESS.
I WAS SUCH A FOOL
BUILDING THIS PLACE...
TO THINK THAT I COULD CONTROL
THINGS IN THE DIGITAL WORLD
WHEN THE ONLY THING I CAN DO
IS TO WATCH AND PRAY.
I THINK WE CAN DO MORE THAN
THAT, IF YOU'RE WILLING TO HELP.
I WOULD
LIKE NOTHING MORE
THAN TO MAKE UP
FOR MY MISGUIDED PAST,
BUT YOU'RE ALREADY WORKING
WITH THE BRIGHTEST MINDS
OF YOUR GENERATION.
YOU UNDERESTIMATE YOURSELF.
I ENVY YOUR ABILITY
TO CREATE WHAT YOU IMAGINE.
THEN I THINK IT'S
ABOUT TIME
FOR ME TO CREATE
SOMETHING WORTHWHILE.
IT CERTAINLY IS.
THIS FACILITY AND MY RESOURCES
ARE YOURS TO USE AS YOU SEE FIT.
IF THOSE KIDS ARE
GOING TO SAVE THE WORLD,
THEN THE LEAST I CAN DO IS
TO GIVE THEM A FIGHTING CHANCE.
[ GRUNTING ]
UHH!
COME ON, SUSIE,
I'LL CATCH YOU!
[ GRUNTS ]
[ WHIMPERS ]
OH, GUILMON.
I'M SO SORRY, BOY.
JERI'S RIGHT.
THIS IS ALL MY FAULT.
YOU WERE LIKE
A DREAM COME TRUE.
WHOA, I CAN'T BELIEVE IT!
THERE YOU WERE -- A LIVING,
BREATHING DIGIMON,
AND I HAD CREATED YOU.
GUILMON!
I THOUGHT I COULD CONTROL YO,
AND IT SEEMED TO WORK.
I'M PROUD OF YOU, BOY.
I FIGURED IF I CREATED YU
THEN THAT MADE YOU
A PART OF ME, RIGHT?
IT FELT LIKE YOU WERE
A PART OF ME.
I HAVE TO ADMIT YOU FRIGHTEND
ME SOMETIMES.
YOU GOT PRETTY BIG.
I'M STILL ME.
REALLY?
ALWAYS.
DATA, DNA --
WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE?
YWEREALWAYS YOU,
BUT I NEVER THOUGHT ABOUT
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN IF
I COULDN'T CONTROL MYSEL.
RIGHT, BOY?
NOW I KNOW.
COME ON, JERI.
YOU CAN'T JUST STAY OVER
THERE BY YOURSELF.
IT'S NOT SAFE.
PLEASE?
[ STATIC ]
AW, NUTS. I THINK SHE'S
TOTALLY ZONED OUT, POOR KID.
I'LL JUST HAVE
TO RESCUE HER.
[ RUMBLING ]
[ GROWLING ]
AND NOW NO ONE CAN TAKE ME!
I AM INVINCIBLE!
I'LL OWN THE SOVEREIGNS
THEMSELVES!
IF HE SUCCESSFULLY ASSIMILATED
YOURS AND TAOMON'S ATTACKS,
WE'RE IN SERIOUS TROUBLE.
WE'RE IN TROUBLE.
WHEN LOPMON DIGIVOLVES,
HE'LL BE SORRY.
SUSIE, THE SOVEREIGN TOOK
AWAY MY POWER TO DIGIVOLVE.
I DON'T CARE WHAT HE DID.
WE'RE IN TROUBLE
AND YOU HAVE TO DIGIVOLVE.
STOP IT, SUSIE, YOU'RE JUST
MAKING IT HARDER FOR HER.
HENRY!
[ CRYING ]
COME ON, SUSIE.
RENAMON WON'T LET ANYTHING
BAD HAPPEN TO YOU.
TERRIERMON AND GARGAMON
ARE HERE TO HELP,
NOT TO MENTION ME
AND HENRY.
YOU'LL BE FINE, I PROMISE.
YOU'LL SEE.
I'M NOT VERY GOOD
AT THIS, AM I?
WHAT'S HE WANT?
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I WANT --
TO FINISH THE JOB.
UNLIKE YOU MISERABLE PUKIN'
HUMANS, I KEEP MY PROMISES.
AW, YOU'RE SO CUTE.
YOU'RE SO AFRAID OF ME
YOU'RE ABOUT TO WET YOUR PANTS.
I CAN'T TELL YOU HOW
GRATIFYING IT IS.
IT BRINGS A LITTLE
TEAR TO MY EYE.
OH!
OH, DEAR.
[ GUNS COCK ]
[ CRYING ]
WHAT NOW?
HUH?
TAKATO, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
GET OUT OF THERE.
YOU TOO, JERI.
COME ON!
GUILMON WAS ALWAYS GUILMON
UNTIL I MESSED HIM UP.
NO MATTER HOW BIG HE GOT, HE WAS
ALWAYS MY FRIEND, MY PARTNER,
BUT I LET HIM DOWN.
I ACTED LIKE A FOOL.
I REALLY WANTED BEELZEMON
TO SUFFER FOR WHAT HE HAD DONE.
IT WASN'T ENOUGH TO JUST DEFEAT
HIM, HE HAD TO HURT.
IT'S BAD ENOUGH THAT I FELT THAT
WAY, BUT IT'S WORSE FOR GUILMON.
I MADE HIM A MONSTER.
OH, WHAT A TOUCHING SIGHT --
A BOY AND HIS PATHETIC DIGIMON.
I'LL PUT THEM
OUT OF THEIR MISERY.
NO!
SAY GOODBYE!
TAKATO, GET OUT OF THERE!
IT'S TOO LATE, TAKATO!
RUN AWAY!
GET OUT OF THERE NOW!
TAKATO!
[ Muffled ] TAKATO!
[ LAUGHS EVILLY ]
GUILMON, YOU'LL ALWAYS
BE MY FRIEND.
TA...KA...TO.
GUILMON!
HUH?
OKAY...THIS IS STRANGE.
[CHUCKLES]
IT'S ALL THE SAME,
BUT DIFFERENT.
AM I SUPPOSED
TO DO SOMETHING?
WHAT CAN I DO?
OH, GUILMON, I WISH WE COUD
JUST START OVER.
I'D HAVE BEEN
A LOT MORE CAREFUL
IF I'D KNOWN YOU WERE
GONNA BE REAL,
AND YOU WERE ABOUT
AS REAL AS THEY COME.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND
WHY RIKA THOUGHT
THAT DATA COULDN'T BE REAL.
YOWEREREAL.
WASN'T THAT PROOF ENOUGH?
YOU WERE MY FRIEND.
Guilmon:WE'LL ALWAYS BE
FRIENDS, TAKATOMON,
AND THAT'S PRETTY REAL.
GUILMO-O-O-O-N!
THIS IS DIFFERENT.
NOW WHAT DO I DO?
THERE MUST BE
1,000 GUILMONS HERE.
NO WAY! I CAN'T!
I DON'T WANT TO START OVER!
THERE'S ONLY ONE REAL GUILMON,
AND HE'S THE ONE I WANT!
NOTHING ELSE MATTERS -- NOT
DATA, NOT DNA, JUST MY FRIEND!
[ GASPS ] GUILMON!
I'M COMING, BOY!
JUST HANG IN THERE!
YOU CAN DO IT!
HOLD ON!
TAKATOMON?
GUILMON!
YOU'RE BACK.
IS IT TIME FOR LUNCH,
TAKATO?
[ CHUCKLES ]
MM-HMM.
YOU CAN HAVE ANYTHING
YOU WANT, GUILMON.
Rika: TAKATO, WATCH OUT!
TAKATO!
[ GRUNTS ]
RIGHT, THAT'S ENOUGH.
YOU SURE YOU'RE OKAY?
YEAH, OF COURSE YOU ARE.
WE'RE TOGETHER.
WE CAN DO ANYTHING.
MM-HMM.
WE'RE NOT GONNA DO
THIS AGAIN, ARE WE?
[ GRUNTS ]
I WISH I COULD FIGHT HIM
WITH YOU, GUILMON.
BEELZEMON WOULDN'T
STAND A CHANCE
AGAINST THE TWO OF US
TOGETHER.
I'M SURE THERE'S
A WAY, TAKATO.
MAYBE YOU JUST HAVE
TO WISH FOR IT REALLY HARD.
IT WORKED WHEN YOU
NEEDED A BLUE CARD.
ALL RIGHT, THEN.
I REALLY WANT TO FIGHT
WITH GUILMON!
GUILMON BIOMERGE TO...
...GALLANTMON.
REMARKABLE.
WOW!
THAT'S AMAZING.
HE MUST BE GUILMON'S
TRUE MEGAFORM.
I'LL SAY,
BUT WHERE'S TAKATO?
HEY, WHAT'S GOING
ON HERE, HUH?
BEELZEMON, YOU REJECTED EVERY
FRIENDSHIP OFFERED YOU.
IN RETURN YOU BETRAYED THEM
AND DESTROYED A VALIANT SOUL.
I CANNOT FORGIVE
WHAT YOU HAVE DONE.
YOU CAN'T FORGIVE ME?!
I DON'T RECALL EVER ASKING
YOU TO FORGIVE ME.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT FORGIVENESS
WHEN I WIPE YOU
OUT OF EXISTENCE!
SO BE IT.
AAAHHHHHH!
[ GROWLS ]
NOW, THAT'S WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT!
I THINK TAKATO'S
ON THE RIGHT TRACK NOW,
SO KEEP WATCHING
"DIGIMON -- DIGITAL MONSTERS"
DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DI, DI, DIGIMON, DIGIMON
DI, DI, DI
DI, DIGIMON