My name is Akifumi Yoshimi...
and this is my
niece Hazuki...
She's the one I was
telling you about.
Take a look at this.
At first this
was all we saw.
We assumed it was
some kind of rash
and took her to
the hospital...
But...
-My god!
-a kaimyo.
It sure is.
Wait... Isn't that another
name for the dead?
Zengetsuin
rakugoku dounyo.
This foolish child is doomed
to spend an eternity in...
Hell.
"In Hell?"
Only someone with a serious
grudge could do this.
This was the beginning
of one of our most
shocking cases.
[Music]
My name is Taizo Yoshimi...
and this is my wife Hiroe.
Thank you all so
much for coming.
Welcome.
First of all... let me
say that we're very sorry
to call you all the
way out here for this.
Oh... don't
worry about it.
It's Our pleasure.
Now if you
wouldn't mind...
I'd very much like to go over
the details of the case.
Yes. Of course...
Well, I'm afraid that
there is a bit of a curse
on the Yoshimi family...
Whenever there is a new
head of the family,
strange things
seem to happen.
Thirty two years ago...
when my grandfather
passed away
eight family members
soon followed.
When he first took
over the land,
five of my mother's
siblings died.
She was the only
one who survived.
Then my father died...
and almost immediately
those horrifying marks
appeared on Hazuki.
If his spirit caused this...
it's like he wants to behead
his own granddaughter
from beyond the grave.
Let's see if I
got them all.
That's Hazuki's
father, Kazuyasu.
He's the oldest son...
Next to him is the second
oldest Yashitaka...
Then there's Eijiro.
He's the husband of the
oldest daughter Teruka...
That's Kazuyasu's
wife Yoko...
and the second
oldest daughter Nao
who is just a bit older
than her brother Akifumi.
That's it...
I've got them all...
Sure is quiet though...
Nobody's said a word
all through dinner.
What are these people
doing here anyway?!
And why aren't you telling
them the whole story?
Please... not in front
of the guests, Eijiro.
It's for their
own safety...
It's irresponsible
not to tell them!
The family members
weren't the only ones
who died thirty-two years ago.
What do you mean?
I think we should tell
them the whole story, dear.
Taizo...
I know...
These people are
our last hope,
and this may make
them want to leave...
That's true...
but they have a
right to know...
There's more
to the story...
What we haven't
told you is that
three people outside of
the family died as well.
All three of them were
spiritualists, like you.
I see.
Don't worry. We're not gonna
let that scare us off.
Besides I really want to see
what we're up against here.
Thank you so much.
We've had consultations
with other investigators...
But when they found
out the whole truth
they didn't want
any part of it.
That explains why you went
all the way to Tokyo.
He had to.
I'm sorry about what
happened over dinner.
My brother Eijiro is not
usually like that...
actually...
I've never seen him
behave that way before.
Hold on...
You're saying it's
unusual for him
to behave so coarsely
in front of the guests?
Yeah... After all we
do run a hotel here.
What about Kazuyasu?
Kazuyasu's been...
well, he's been on
edge a bit lately...
For that matter
so has Yashi...
Since the funeral, they've
both had a pretty hard time.
I can understand...
I'm sure they have a
lot on their minds.
What about everyone else...?
Or has anything
strange happened?
Yeah, there was something
that was strange...
After grandfather's funeral
three of our dogs just
suddenly went missing
and then a few days
later we found them.
Their bodies had
washed up on the beach.
Yoko hasn't been the same
since then I'm afraid...
but, to tell the truth,
if you want to know who's
been acting the most unusual,
I'd have to say it
was the children.
You mean Hazuki?
Oh no... There's two other
children in the family
besides Hazuki...
Hazuki has a brother
named Katsuki.
And Teruka has a
daughter named Wakako...
Katsuki and Wakako have been
acting very strange lately.
How so?
Well, it's hard to say...
but they've been sticking
unusually close to each other.
They were never really
like this before...
And on top of that...
they're constantly whispering
things to each other.
When we ask them what
they're talking about,
all they do is just
giggle and wink at us.
Can you tell me how long
they've been doing this?
Yeah, I'd have to say
it was right after
Grandfather's funeral.
Okay. So how is
this angle looking?
Good. Come on back.
Huh...?
Sure is dark in here...
when did the
lights go out?
That's okay.
Base is just a
few doors down.
Oh, miss.
Did someone
just call me?
Oh miss.
You startled me.
I guess you must be
Katsuki and Wakako right...?
So what are you
kids doing up so late?
-Go ahead and ask her.
-Okay.
How many did you
bring here...?
How many of you
are there miss?
How many are there?
There are... five of us.
So there's five.
Not good.
Trouble.
Something's wrong
with these kids...
-Let's go.
-Wait!
Hold on!
You said there was five.
Yes I did...
but why did you
need to know that?
That's not something for
you to worry about miss.
That was creepy.
No wonder Akifumi had so much
trouble talking about them...
There is definitely
something very strange
about those two.
What's wrong with him?
Stop it!
-Lin!
-Right!
Thank God...
At least no one was
seriously hurt.
What in the hell
came over him?
I don't know.
I was talking to him
about what happened
at dinner...
and then...
Hey where are you going?
Don't just walk away
when I'm talking to you!
Not long after that...
he came back
with the knife.
Could anything have put him
in a bad mood before that...?
Something before
dinner perhaps?
No. He was acting completely
normal until this.
He sounded possessed.
That could be...
Looks like we'll need to
call John in on this...
Either that or...
Do you think you
can handle this?
Maybe but wouldn't
Monk be better...?
Don't you think so?
that's probably
not a good idea...
if I did it I'm not
sure what would happen.
What could happen, Monk?
There was this one time...
I was trying to drive a
spirit out of an urn.
I managed to get
the spirit out,
but the urn was
completely shattered.
All I'm saying is this is
pretty dangerous stuff...
dharmic power
is very risky...
And when you're trying to touch
someone directly with it,
anything can happen.
What...? Wait a minute.
Are you trying to tell us
that you've never driven
out a spirit before...?
then how do you go around
calling yourself a spiritualist?
You take care of it then.
I'm sure he'll be safe
since your power's so weak.
What's that
supposed to mean? !
Well somebody needs to...
-can you do it?
-Fine...
But if it takes over
someone else...
don't blame me.
I just know how
to drive them out.
What matters most
right now is that
we remove this
spirit from him.
It seems particularly violent.
I pray in reverence
for thy spirit.
I humbly ask that you
bring your holy presence
into this unhallowed place.
And purify all
who reside here.
I ask that you hear my
plea so that peace...
may reign once
again in this house.
Naru... Maybe Ayako isn't
up to this after all?
Perhaps she isn't...
Regardless, John will
be here tomorrow.
Bring together the gods
of the four corners
and make this place as
peaceful as the Heavens.
Maybe Lin should do this.
He can't since we don't
know the spirit's identity.
Bring together the gods
of the four corners.
Just stay back...
leave quietly...
Lin, take care of Mai.
Praise be to the
goddess Marish-ten!
Descend and grant us
your divine protection!
Naru!
-Naru!
-Don't do it!
Are you okay?
Did it hurt you?
No...
how's Eijiro?
What's going on...?
What happened to me?
I'm just not
getting anything...
ever since that fox
spirit appeared
all I'm able
to pick up...
is static.
Spiritual interference...
it's effecting
the gauges too.
All of the needles
are buried.
It just looked like a
simple fox-spirit...
but I guess you can't judge
these things by appearances,
eh Naru?
Uh...
Hey, are you sure
you're okay, man?
Are you feeling sick?
No...
my back's hurting
a bit that's all...
I think I... I think I'll
go lie down for a while.
Hang on...
I need to change
so I'll walk you
to your room, kay?
Oh my god, I am
such an idiot!
Why didn't I think to
say something like that!
I blew my big chance!
Unbelievable.
-What?
-Ayako...
Just who does she
think she is anyway?
What do you mean by that?
She completely messed up
that exorcism didn't she...?
Come to think of it,
Has she ever been any
real help to us...?
And there's even something
fishy about her claim
to be a priestess.
A real priestess
would never be out
trying to do exorcisms
all by herself.
Everybody knows they
don't operate that way.
-They don't?
-Of course not...
It's obvious to me
that she's just claiming
to be a priestess...
The thing is, she does
know her way around
the double-aspect
Shinto technique...
so I'm guessing she must have
received some kind of training.
Whoah!
What... what
are they...?
Lin! Hallway!
Wait... What's up?
Naru! Ayako!
Is she okay?
This is not good.
We've really gotten ourselves
into quite a bind here...
It's that spirit again.
I thought for sure
that the spirit had
passed through Naru
and out beyond the wall...
But it looks like it
stayed inside him.
I'm afraid Naru's
possessed by that thing.
I don't want to risk going
through all that again.
And, shouldn't
he be tied up
or something like
we did Eijiro,
just to be safe?
This is Naru we're
talking about.
I don't think tying
him up would be enough.
Wait... what do you mean?
Exactly what I
just said, Monk...
Ayako was just damned
lucky, that's all.
How?
Whatever it is that's
possessed Naru...
hasn't gained full control
over his body yet...
Otherwise...
you wouldn't be
alive right now.
In fact, Naru...
is more dangerous than any of
us can possibly imagine.
How could Naru
be... dangerous?
Tell me something...
Do you think you're
pretty good in a fight?
More or less.
And against Naru?
In a fight to the death...
Naru would be
the victor.
So that's out...
I guess rolling him
up in something
and sticking him
in the storeroom
wouldn't do any
good either.
Which also means
we can't wait around
for John to get here...
so we're going
to have to try
and perform
another exorcism.
It is very difficult
to do that
without knowing the
spirit's identity...
and furthermore...
with strong-willed
people like Naru,
once they're possessed it's
all the more difficult
to drive the
spirit out.
If we provoke it into violence
it will be very dangerous.
So, what are we
supposed to do then?
Induce paralysis...
we're going to have to keep
him sedated like he is now...
he'll be much easier
to handle unconscious.
In the mean time,
let's split up and
try to figure out
who that spirit is...
I am a little worried
that if we leave,
Naru will be
defenseless like this.
I'll leave my shiki
here with him...
If I put all
five of them here
they'll work together and
form a perfect barrier...
Nothing will be
able to touch him...
However...
What?
It'll leave me completely
defenseless...
I won't be much help.
Well, it's not like we have
much choice in the matter...
It's not perfect but at least
it's some kind of plan...
So tell me ladies...
Have you two decided yet?
On what?
It's going to be
next to impossible
to do this without
Naru helping us out...
So you girls are
gonna have to decide
on whether you're gonna stay
here or go somewhere safer.
What are you
talking about?
There's no way
we'd abandon Naru!
She's right of course...
What kind of
friends would we be
if we took off
and left him...?
I don't care how
dangerous it is.
We can't leave now
when he needs us.
Alright, it's on then.
We've got to help them.
If we don't then who knows
what will happen to Naru
and the Yoshimi family?
What am I going to do?
How could it have
come to this?
He left me no choice.
But why?
There was nothing
I could do...
he was waiting here
when I arrived...
so of course I thought
you had betrayed me.
How could you think
I would do that?!
It made sense...
what other reason could
there be for him being here?
You were the
only one who knew
where we were
going to meet.
No... It's not like that...
The letters
got mixed up...
I ended up in a completely
different place.
Now that I've killed someone
I've got nowhere to run...
if I turn myself in
they'll kill me.
If you're going to die
I'll go with you.
They're right
behind us Naru!
Just keep running!
A shrine!
Why are we here?
We should be at the sea!
The sea?
What does that mean?
Why am I thinking about
the sea at a time like this?
I'm sorry...
I can't run any more.
It seems, pretty
hopeless to me.
Monk?
Tell me what's to
become of us now?
I guess we'll
have to give up.
Give up?
Eijiro?!
What's going on here?!
I shall curse you from
beyond the grave!
You will not escape me!
Oh, it was just a dream...
I know I closed that
before I went to bed.
Am I still asleep...?
This feels like
a dream...
and there's more of
these white things.
Naru!
Come down here.
So did you have the dream?
You mean...?
The one before?
-Did it scare you?
-Oh no.
I wouldn't say
that it scared me.
That's good.
Hey Naru... are you making
me have this dream?
No, not at all...
All I did was guide
you to this point.
Oh, you guided me here?
So this is what it
looks like from below.
There's a path
over there.
I wonder what
it leads to.
A cave?
Are all of
these spirits?
They are the beings
that died at sea...
This is a place that
souls drift into.
A fish?
There's something strange
about that shrine over there...
It looks... distorted.
Mm-hmm...
And I don't have
any idea why ...
however... this doesn't
feel like a bad place...
Or a good place
for that matter.
Almost like... some
kind of sacred ground.
Sacred...?
Hey... When I first saw
you outside of the cave,
you told me that you had guided
me here through my dreams...
I don't quite
understand.
What are you
trying to tell me?
Naru?
[Music]
Next time
on Ghost Hunt.
The Cursed House, part two!
It's just
getting started!