I was attacked
by evil spirits.
Luckily, when I came to,
I was surrounded
by my friends,
which was a huge relief.
But the nurse's office
wasn't safe either.
Naru!
The ceiling collapsed and
I was nearly killed...!
After that, Naru
realized something.
How can that be?
Is it possible
we're up against...
a kodoku using spirits?
The hauntings
plaguing the school
are being caused by an obscure
form of cursing called kodoku,
and the papers used
for orikirisama
are the talismans for it.
Someone spread these
talismans around school,
falsely claiming they were
harmless Ouija boards.
Whoever's participated in this
has aided in casting
a death curse.
What will happen once
the kodoku is complete?
The person whose name is written
on the talisman will die.
And who would that be?
Hideharu... Matsuyama.
[Music]
Matsuyama?
Wait...
You don't mean that teacher
who's been bugging us...
Do you?
It's him!
You were asked to leave
but it doesn't look
like you're packing up.
Are you coming up with more
bogus ghost stories to tell?
I think it would be in
your best interest
if you didn't hear
our discussion.
Are you trying to plan
how to justify your
fee or something?
It's about time you
cut your losses, son...
We know you're a fraud...
What is that?
Sir, were you aware
that Ouija-boarding has become
popular among the students
at this school?
What, you mean
that stupid game?
This is the board used for
what's called orikirisama...
Someone has been spreading
these around school
without realizing the
dangerous implications.
Why are you
telling me this?
These talismans are used solely
for performing a deathcurse.
Deathcurse...?
That's ridiculous...
You expect me to believe a piece
of paper could kill someone?
who do you think this
silly "deathcurse" is for?
You. And it's very real.
-Isn't that right, Lin?
-Yes.
Hey...! That's not
something you joke about!
Takigawa. Are you able
to read Sanskrit?
Mmm... yeah more or less.
Look at the talisman.
The name written
on the right side
is the person being cursed.
Let's see here...
That can only be read
as Hideharu Matsuyama.
It doesn't have to necessarily
be written in Sanskrit.
In fact, on the left
side of the talisman
the age of the cursed
is in Kanji...
Would you mind
reading that Naru?
When it comes to Kanji
I'm pretty clueless.
It says Tosai Goju-san,
which translates into
fifty-three years old this year.
If I were to guess I'd
say he's around that age.
Writing out the kanji in this
way is more of a formality...
However...
If Matsuyama was
written normally,
anyone could be the suspect.
That's why they went
through the trouble
of writing in Sanskrit.
But... who the hell
would do this?
The person who made
orikirisama so popular
was a freshman in
the art club...
This is an advanced
form of cursing
that no ordinary student could
easily come up with...
It would have to be someone
who had done extensive
research on the subject.
Damn Sakauchi...!
It was him...! That punk...
How could he do something
like this...?
And why did he choose me?
Sakauchi.
Mr. Matsuyama.
Forgive me, but would you
like to know the reason
why Sakauchi chose you?
Why?
Because of how you
treated him ...
His suicide note simply said,
"I'm not a dog"
We were all aware that the
school was trying to control us,
as if we were dogs.
And if you would ask
any of the students
who personified this
type of treatment,
they'd name you.
And I would agree with
them wholeheartedly.
Sakauchi.
I thought I told you not to
bring these books to class.
If you allow your mind to
be warped with this crap
you'll never
amount to anything!
Maybe you should try
reading one of your textbooks
before you waste
your time with this.
The identity of the culprit
is of little use to
us at this point.
The die has already
been cast again you...
Not even the originator of
the curse could stop it now.
Well , what can you do?
Do we have a solution?
Nothing yet.
You could reverse
the zuzhou, right?
I could do that...
but are you certain
you would want to?
We don't have much
choice, do we...?
I doubt many people would
mourn him if he died,
but we can't stand idly by
when he knows it's
going to happen.
Reverse the zuzhou.
You're going
through with it?
We'll be turning the
zuzhou curse back
on the person who started it.
We have very little time
before the last few spirits
finish consuming each other
and complete the zuzhou.
Once that occurs,
death is all that will
await Mr. Matsuyama.
most likely in a very
painful, brutal way.
But before that happens...
I'll be spared, won't I?
I didn't do anything...
Why should I be
the one to die?
I'm innocent!
What a horrible person.
Sir.
Need I remind you that you
were the cause of this...?
Don't forget that.
Wait a minute Naru...
Sakauchi isn't even
alive anymore...
Can you even reverse a
zuzhou onto a dead person?
Turning a zuzhou back on the
deceased is impossible,
but that's irrelevant
since he isn't the
one responsible
for the zuzhou in
the first place.
When you reverse a zuzhou,
it returns to
whoever cast it...
Although they weren't aware
of the consequences...
The students are responsible
for starting the zuzhou.
But...
what will happen to them?
If the students
cast the spell...
and the zuzhou is returned
to whoever started it...
Those foxfires will
attack the students!
You can't do it, Naru!
There's gotta
be a better way!
So you'd rather us
ignore Matsuyama's death?
Failure to realize
the end result
is no excuse for
the students.
Even if they aren't
punished by the law...
if Matsuyama dies they'll
be accessories to murder.
The curse will return
to the students...
This man, who
caused all this,
will repent his sins
in one way or another.
That sounds like a
fair solution to me.
Naru... no!
Mr. Shibuya.
What will happen
to us students
once the zuzhou is
returned back to us?
Since there are such a large
number of people who cast it,
the power should be divided
evenly amongst everyone,
weakening its effects.
At least, that's what
I hope will happen.
Naru!
We came to you to
resolve this matter
If there's really no other
way to finish this...
There isn't.
Then you have our
permission to move forward.
So Mr. Matsuyama gets
off totally unharmed,
but all of the students could
get hurt or even killed?
How come he's the only
one that's safe...?
That's not fair at all!
Murder is never an
option in our society,
no matter how a person
conducts themselves
But the possible death
of hundreds is okay?
I think it's reasonable
for everyone
to bear the responsibility
of their own actions.
But they...
they didn't know
what they were doing.
Ignorance is
hardly an excuse.
I hate you, Naru,
do you hear me?
You're a terrible person!
Lin...
Let's get ready to move.
Right.
Look Mai...
I know...
I know Naru is right...
But still...
I can't always just
do whatever he says,
and I could care less if he
doesn't like me for it,
but it's not right...
It's just not right.
Our hands are tied Mai...
It's a tough
pill to swallow
but there's nothing
else we can do.
I'm stopping him.
What?
I have to, He's making
a terrible mistake.
Mai, wait. How are
you gonna do that?
Mai!
Maybe what Naru said about
the students is right.
But no one hated
Matsuyama so much
that they wanted
to see him dead.
It's reasonable
for everyone
to bear the responsibility
of their actions.
How can he turn the zuzhou
back on the students
when he's fully aware of how
painful it will be for them?
Is that his
idea of justice?
Either way, there's got
be something else
that we can do to
stop this curse!
Oh no! Lin's car is gone!
Where did they go?
Why can't I find them...?
They never went
back to base.
They're not at the
office either...
This is so frustrating...
While they're getting
ready to hurt those kids,
all I can do is
just sit here.
Wait a minute.
It's time I did something.
I'll exorcise the spirits
before they get back.
There's nothing in here.
It still has that
terrible smell.
Water.
I don't know if my weak magic
skills will have any effect,
but here goes...
Naumaku san manda
bazaradan kan...
bazaradan kan.
Naumaku san manda
bazaradan kan...
bazaradan kan.
Naumaku san manda
bazaradan kan...
Rin... Pyo... Toh... Sha... Ka.
Stay strong.
Kai... Jin... Retsu...
Zai... Zen! Begone!
This isn't water...
It's... blood!
Naumaku san manda
bazaradan kan...
bazaradan kan.
Naumaku san manda
bazaradan kan...
Get away from me...!
Stay back!
No!
This is it!
I'm done for.
I knew I wasn't
strong enough...!
On kirikiri bazara!
Monk?!...!
So those were his
hands that grabbed me.
Bajiri hora
manda manda un...
Hatta!
Mai, Run!
You idiot!
Did you really think you
had a chance against them?
You just learned
magic the other day!
I know.
If I hadn't of been
there to save you,
you could have died...!
do You know how
lucky you are?!
I... I'm sorry.
You're okay now...
I'm glad he
made it in time.
It's gonna be okay, Mai...
You're with your friends.
You're safe now.
I'm so stupid.
I ran off on my own, and made
all my friends worry about me...
What was I thinking?
It's awfully quiet, huh?
The only thing I'm sensing
right now is a big void...
It feels as if this
place is deserted.
It seems like classes
should've started already.
Hey!
Come and check
out the gymnasium.
It looks like they're
having a school assembly...
I guess that means the zuzhou
hasn't been reversed...
Let's head back to base.
What are you doing here?
Great.
Looks like Naru
and Lin are back.
We're just wondering
what's going on, that's all.
We're not here to put
on a show for you.
I don't believe this!
They're still planning
to reverse the zuzhou
back on the students...
Those foxfires
could kill them...!
Even Yasu's in danger.
-Lin wait!
-Mai!
Listen to me, Lin...
Don't do it!
Are you still going on
about that nonsense?
You're crazy...!
And you're wrong too...!
Those students don't
deserve to be punished!
They didn't know!
You're in our way,
now leave!
No!
The entire school
is still here...
They're all in the
gym right now...
They don't know what's going
to happen to them, do they?
Ow...! Let go
of me Naru...
Let go!
Everyone. Outside!
Don't bother Lin!
Answer me...!
Why does that jerk Matsuyama
get off scott-free
while everyone else
is put in danger?
Don't you care about
what happens to them?
Even if they are partly to
blame for the zuzhou curse...
they didn't know that
they were doing!!
You're trying to
kill innocent people!
-You're a murderer.
-Calm down.
As long as you
solve the case
then nothing else
matters, right?
And if anyone happens
to die in the process...
it's just an
acceptable loss!
That's enough...
This is our only option.
You actually believe him?
get her out of here,.
No more interruptions.
Sure.
Don't you walk
away from me!
Come on...
Somebody stop him...!
Naru!
Why isn't anyone
stopping him?
-Mai!
-But Monk...!
We can't let him do this!
Have some faith in Naru.
Think about it.
Has he ever let
us down before?
But I...
Has he?
No.
Just believe in him...
Everything will be fine.
But Monk...
Yasu is in the gymnasium with
all of the other students...
Don't you know that I'm
worried about him too?
Yeah.
It's alright.
It's good to know everyone
else is as worried as I am.
I bet Naru is too.
-Is it over?
-Yes.
So what happened?
Mai, wait!
Please be okay!
What is it...?
What are you looking at?
Whoa...
Are those...
Hitogata?
But what happened to all the
students that were in here?
-Naru.
-Hey Monk.
What's up?
I want you and John to
check all the hitogata...
Miss Hara, Miss
Matsuzaki and...
-Mai.
-Yeah?
Split up and check all the names
on any unbroken hitogata...
Wow.
So they actually made a
hitogata for every student.
Just to be clear,
you've never messed around
with orikirisama, right...?
Okay, thanks for your help!
We're good, guys...
Nothing happened to her.
-Wow.
-Wonderful!
There were enough hitogata
to cover all the students...
The effects of the
zuzhou reversal,
which should have
gone to them...
Were completely absorbed
by the hitogata.
Once it was finished the
hitogata were broken,
and any that were unharmed,
represented the students who
never took part in orikirisama.
This had been Naru's plan
from the beginning...
He never wanted
to harm anyone.
Naru.
How did we do?
They're all safe.
They said they'd never
done Orikirisama.
That's great news
Look... If you were planning
to make hitogata for everyone,
wouldn't it have been easier to
make just one for Matsuyama.
Which sounds like
better odds to you?
Four against one,
or four against six-hundred?
Geez...! You dummy!
We could have avoided
all this drama
if you had just told me
that from the beginning.
Transferring a curse to a
hitogata is extremely difficult.
Even Lin wasn't sure that
everyone would be safe.
I just wish that
I had known
Murderer!
That was a terrible
thing to say.
I'm sorry.
I know I said some very
inconsiderate things to you...
You get so caught up in
the welfare of others...
It must have been
awful for you,
and for that I apologize.
Not fair!
I was just about to
apologize myself but no!
Naru had to do
it before me!
Maybe it's just me
but you seem to always take the
best moments for yourself!
I wanted to thank you
for all you've done.
And since Sakauchi's curse is
what started this whole mess,
I was thinking of holding a
memorial service for him,
to keep any possibility of
future problems in check.
That wouldn't
be a bad idea.
It makes me wonder...
Is Sakauchi disappointed
that the curse never happened,
or is he relieved?
How do you think he feels?
Well to be honest...
I'm really not sure
I'd like to think he's happy
that no one was hurt...
Do you know what I mean?
By the way, Yasu.
Tell me the truth.
You were scared back
there, weren't ya?
Oh you mean when
Naru and Lin said
they'd be reversing the
zuzhou back on us?
That's right.
Well, you see...
I had faith.
In what?
In myself.
I've never done anything
that was so bad
that would warrant me dying
at such a young age...
So I was confident
that out of everyone
at least I would come
out of it unscathed.
You'll live a long life
with that attitude.
That's what I plan on.
[Music]
Next time on Ghost Hunt,
The Bloodstained Labyrinth
Part One...
Sounds scary, doesn't it?