It was Christmas Eve
and John stopped by
with a case from
his local church,
so we decided to
go check it out.
They run a daycare and
orphanage out of the church,
and the children
often become possessed
by the spirit of a boy
who used to live there
and went missing over
thirty years ago.
Whenever a child
becomes possessed,
they play a game
of hide-and-seek,
which they call stick,
because the boy that went
missing couldn't speak,
and would bang a stick on
the ground to signal
when he was ready.
Plus from what Father
Tojo has told us...
Lately Kenji's been appearing
a lot more frequently
than he used to which
could be a sign
that the worst may
be yet to come.
May God have mercy
on your soul
Can you... feel it?
Knocking... sounds.
Mai... What are... you doing?
What? No way...!
I think Kenji
just possessed Mai!
[Music]
My exorcism on
Thanat worked,
but it looks like...
Uh... We have our work
cut out for us...
that's what it
looks like...
Don't just stand there,
John, do something about it.
Sorry. I didn't
see that coming.
Why don't you keep her
company for awhile, dad?
Thanat, why don't you go play
with the other children, okay?
'Kay.
Let's go somewhere we can
discuss this privately.
John, has this
happened before?
Uh, no...
Of all the exorcisms
I've done here
I've never seen him possess
another child so quickly.
And the knocking sounds?
This is the first time.
The fact that Kenji's
never done this before
is troubling, to
say the least.
You had said the possessions
were becoming more frequent.
Is that all?
The amount of time the
kids spend hiding
has increased as well...
That's what Father
Tojo told me ...
A few years ago we'd have
one or two possessions a year
but now we get
that many in one week.
I'm afraid that if this
continues another child
will turn up missing
just like Kenji.
In the past when I would
remove Kenji from a child,
he wouldn't put up
any resistance,
but this time was different.
It was an
unpleasant feeling.
What do you believe
would happen
if you drove him out
again right now?
don't rightly know...
If I were to guess I'd say
he'd attempt to possess
another nearby child.
But I'm certain Kenji
would become even angrier
than he already is.
I agree.
I can't take
this any longer!
Keep it together
Takigawa.
You're a professional...
and this is serious.
Let's see if we can find
Kenji before it's too late.
This is it...
They apparently found
Kenji's whistle
against that far wall.
Looks like this is where
the old trash incinerator was.
Oh I see.
The aqueduct is
right behind it.
Looks pretty deep.
Father Tojo said Kenji
was playing hide-and-seek
before he
disappeared, right?
-Takigawa!
-What is it?
So there's a place
to stand here.
Yep... I can see why
he'd choose this spot
cause not many kids would
think to look over here.
But a child his age couldn't
scale a wall this high.
That's true but at the
time this entire area
was under construction.
He could have easily
climbed on some scaffolding
or lumber to get
over the wall.
It surely would have
made it easier for him.
So he starts out by
jumping on some lumber
and then as he's
climbing over the wall,
his whistle gets caught and
falls to the ground...
After he's made it over,
he accidentally falls
in the aqueduct.
Water was cold that
time of year...
Poor kid never
had a chance.
That sound about
right to you?
There's no way of knowing but
it is worth considering...
I am going to see if I can
make any more progress
on finding Kenji.
Lin, continue
babysitting Mai.
Keep her busy.
Naru!
John, Monk,
stay with them.
Uh... Hey there!
What should we play,
Kenji...?
Don't worry. It's okay, your
dad can play with us too.
Would you stop it?
I know it sucks but as long
as he's clinging to you
he won't go off
hiding in the woods...
Now, let's have some fun.
Oh, girls, you
shouldn't have...
It's like a
bakery in here.
It smells delicious.
Thanks John.
They'll be handing
these out tonight
to everyone who comes to
midnight mass tonight.
That's nice...
I'll get my hands dirty
if you need some help.
I'll bet our father-son
team here is game too...
Right?
Now All that's left is to
cover the cakes with foil
and gift wrap them.
You want to help
us with that?
Wait, you're not
doing it right.
Oh... how should I
do it then?
Do it the way I am
you silly goose!
There. Now you match
the cake wrappings.
You want me to
do it again?
Kenji was such a
sweet-hearted child,
and so patient waiting
for his dad.
He would often stand at
the gates of the church,
which was the place
he said goodbye
to his father for
the last time.
And now that he thinks
he's with his dad again,
he literally can't take
his eyes off of him.
imagine the joy he
must feel reuniting
with his dad on
Christmas Eve.
You can't blame him
for being so happy.
All done!
After we get everything
put away, it's play time.
I know it's a
little bizarre
but it's kinda heartwarming
seeing them together.
Yeah... but it is
still pretty weird.
You have to admit it's
cute seeing Mai
act half her age.
Now if only Lin
were more into it.
Enough already!
Hey Lin. What's the matter?
why should I have to put up
with this charade any longer.
Get off of me!
Take it easy, Lin.
You need to understand that
I am not your father...
It's all a big mistake and I
want you to leave me alone.
Mai, wait!
Uhh, I mean Kenji!
What's wrong?
Mai ran off.
That sounds like Kenji
using his sticks.
I think you
made him angry.
Daddy... are you
leaving me again?
I'll be back for you
as soon as I can,.
Now be a good boy and do
what the father tells you to,
okay?
When will you come back...?
Tomorrow...? The next day?
I promise that
we'll be spending
next Christmas together...
Goodbye son.
I'll be a good boy...
I promise...
Please come back soon...
Daddy.
The sound, it
just stopped.
So Monk, why did you
allow Mai to run away?
Well Lin just snapped at
her then Mai got offended
and ran out.
That's very
disappointing.
Let's focus on where Mai
could be hiding from us.
Wait...
I know!
Hey Mai!
-Anything?
-Nothing...
And there's no signs
she fell in the water.
If we're to go off of
what he's done in the past,
he'll leave Mai on his
own accord anytime now.
John drove Kenji out of
Thanat just a few hours ago...
and then Kenji quickly
possessed Mai who was nearby...
Apparently it was the
first time he had done that.
Then...
And this was also the first time
knocking sounds were involved
You said you felt an unusual
resistance from Kenji
when you drove him
out of Thanat.
He must have been quite
reluctant to leave
his father's side with
that reaction.
That could be the case...
The reaction and the
knocking sounds
were definitely more
intense this time around.
You also said the
frequency of Kenji's
appearances have
increased lately.
Up to this point he's
willfully removed himself
from any children
he's possessed,
however this time that
may not be the case...
That's the reason
why I asked you
to keep Mai company.
Yeah but...
let's be fair.
Lin was never made
aware of that.
So... what do we do now?
Do we know what happened
to Kenji's father
or did he just disappear?
Well practically, All I
ever heard was that
after he left Kenji here
he started working
a job over in Osaka.
he was never heard
from again...
a few weeks after
Kenji disappeared
Father Tojo received a letter
stating he had
passed away,
but it never explained
how he died.
So why does Kenji do it?
What?
He hides, and then
signals to the others,
asking to be found.
He eventually comes out
without being found,
so disappearing isn't
his objective...
Now it could be, as
Father Tojo believes,
that he just wants
to be noticed.
But Why Kenji...?
Why do you continue
to play the game?
Because he wants
to go back?
Go back...?
Back to where?
Back To the church.
Oh I see.
He thinks if he can get
back to the church
then his father
will come get him
And the two of them
will go home...
Way to go, dad.
That's it.
Kenji's spirit is lost so
he's forced to possess
the children and play
hide-and-seek.
The only reason he
does this is because
it's his only chance
of being found.
He's trying to
end the game.
All right...
Then let's quit
talking about it
and go find him...
Because the longer we wait
the more worried I get
about Mai's well
being in all this.
I mean it's December and
she's not even wearing
a coat for crying out loud.
It'll take more than the
just the three of us...
I looked everywhere
for a good hour
and came up empty...
Why don't we enlist
the children to help?
And how is that
gonna help us?
The kids weren't able to
find him thirty years ago.
Which is exactly why
we'll be following
the children as they
look for him.
And then we'll explore
the places the children
haven't thought
to look, right?
Now that is brilliant.
Why didn't I
think of that?
Let's hurry.
Time to play a
little game...
When I say go I want you
to find our friend Mai,
who's hiding
somewhere... 'kay?
Sound like fun?
Yeah!
Great...
Ready... Go!
Easy...
It's hide and seek
not... wrestling!
Man these kids are
either sweethearts
or completely out
of control...
You okay, John?
Yeah...
I think they
just get excited
when new people
come to visit.
And though they
may seem happy,
I think many of them are lonely
since they haven't seen
their parents in so long.
I suppose you're right.
Hold on. What are
you getting at?
Are some of these kids
gonna start thinking
that I'm their dad?
Don't worry
we're working...
Honestly!
Nice try kid,
but too obvious.
Of course.
So...
If you watch closely
you'll notice
that the kids only
look in the places
that are easily
accessible to them.
Hey John...
do ya notice...?
none of them are
looking up
Since they're all so small,
they're not considering
anywhere above them to be
a possible hiding place.
And neither are we...
Mai could have
climbed anywhere.
What I'm really more
concerned about
is outside the church.
Man, she could be
anywhere out here.
I'm willing to bet
she climbed up a tree.
I'm gonna go over here and check
this side of the church.
Right. I'll
check this side.
What...?You found
her already? !
We've been
looking for you.
It's okay.
Poor thing...
You must have been
freezing your tail off
being up in that
tree for so long.
You found him!
Ahh...
I swear, what does Lin
have that I don't...?
I mean I'm a nice
guy, right?
Hello Kenji...
That man is
not your dad...
Your real dad is
waiting in heaven
and he wants you
to be with him.
You don't have to play
hide-and-seek ever again.
Kenji...
where are you hiding?
-He's right there.
-Huh?
My god.
No way.
How did he get up there?
Thank you sir.
Any sign of him?
It doesn't look
like he's here.
Let's spread out
and keep looking.
What should I do...?
Father Tojo and the others
are about to leave...
I'm right here.
I'm so cold...
Daddy...
please come get me soon.
I miss you so much daddy.
Daddy!
Oh, hey there.
Well, I guess...
Kenji made it just in
time for Christmas...
Well... What do you say
we throw that party now?
I'm in...
now who wants cake?
All right!
A party sounds nice.
[Music]
Next time on Ghost Hunt,
part one of Forbidden Pastime!
Ohhh. I wonder what that is.