All right!
I wanna know which one
of you hurt the children? !
And who made them carry
those horrible things?
What do you mean?
I'm talking about
those useless charms
you're making them hold...
Take those away from them!
You've brainwashed
the kids
into holding those
ridiculous charms...
And you've done
something to Hazuki.
I can see it
in her eyes...
It's the same thing
you've done to the others!
Oh no, don't tell me
she's possessed too.
How long do you think you
people can get away with this?
This is merely something
you need to make sure
that you're protected.
Please, just carry
it with you, okay?
That thing is useless.
It won't stop anything.
That's not true...
Please, take it.
[Music]
You see...? Your
piece of paper
turned out to be
completely worthless.
We're gonna have
to bind her.
Okay.
Rin...
Pyo... To...
Sha...
Uh... You're sure you're
okay with this...?
I thought we shouldn't use
the nine cuts on people.
This one is called the
Binding of Immobility...
It just keeps her
from moving around.
In the name of our
Lord Jesus Christ...
I command unto thee...
To whatever part of the
body thou mayest be hiding,
show thyself at once,
and flee thee
from the person
which thou hast
occupied.
Leave at once.
Leave the body you
have imprisoned
and seek not a body
that was given unto
God, the Almighty.
In the name of the
Father, the Son,
and the of Holy Spirit,
I forbid thee from entering
this hallowed body again
for all eternity...
In... principio.
Umm...
Hey...
Yoko?
What just... happened?
Who are you?
Yoko had no memory of the
last two days ever happening.
It's like we were
complete strangers to her.
Which can only mean that
she was already possessed
by the spirit before
we arrived here.
Sounds about right...
Of course this also means
it's a fair assumption
that every member of
the Yoshimi family
is possessed.
And then there's Naru...
I still don't understand
why he didn't even
try to run away from it.
-Naru!
-Don't do it!
Oh... 'Scuse me.
I'm interrupting
you guys ...
I can come back.
No it's alright.
Is there something
you need to tell us?
So did you find her?
Not yet...
And we looked
everywhere for her.
When we searched her
bedroom we found that
she had left her wallet
and keys behind,
so I doubt she
could have made it
very far all by herself.
Actually, now that
I think of it,
I don't believe we ever gave
her a charm for protection.
If she still hasn't
returned by morning,
I'll file a missing persons
report with the police...
I guess that's all we
can do for tonight.
Takigawa...
Look...
It's the feed
from the cave.
-John!
-Yeah?
Follow me.
Oh... right.
Hey, should I come too?
No. You watch the base.
What's going on?
What are you seeing, Mai?
I think there may be
something caught
on the rocks down there.
Show me.
Right there.
It bobs up and down
whenever the waves roll in.
No...
Oh god.
Is that...
Wait! Akifumi!
This is terrible.
What they found
in the cave...
turned out to
be Nao's body.
Why can't Naru be here
at a time like this?
Alright Masako.
I think you should
try to channel Nao.
Monk... Shouldn't we
invite the family in here
in case we make contact?
No way.
But you have to take
into consideration
the suddenness of
her death...
She may have things she
needs to tell her family.
It's possible her death
was because of foul play.
Not only that, it's
likely the murderer
is someone in her family.
You think so?
I wish it weren't the case but
that's the grim reality...
That's why we need Masako
to summon her spirit...
Maybe she can tell
us what happened.
Are you... Miss Nao Yoshimi?
Yes.
Nao Yoshimi...
you have passed away
and are now deceased...
Do you know how you died?
I fell...
in the sea.
I was looking...
at the water...
from just outside
the restaurant...
when someone pushed me.
But who did it?
Who pushed you?
Do you remember
anything...?
Even the slightest detail
could help us find out
who did this to you.
I don't know...
I don't want to know
who did this to me.
What's wrong?
Something is
pulling on me...
Let go...
Please! Someone help me,
Let go of me!
-What is it?
-Help her!
But I don't wanna
go in there...
Get away, monster!
Let go of me!
She said...
it was a monster, right?
What in the world
could it have been?
Okay, Nao herself has
confirmed the fact
that she was
indeed murdered...
And most likely by someone
in her own family
Nao? Is that you?
Hello?
This is just like that
other dream I had ...
All of the spirits are
moving up into the sky.
That shrine...
It looks distorted again.
She's back...
Where are you
going, Nao...?
Wait.
I don't get it...
why is she...
What are you doing...
How come...
It's the ritual
of rebirth.
Naru!
Moving through a dark
hole signifies being reborn,
as if she's passing
through the birth canal
for a second time...
As she passes through
the cave again and again,
she's attempting in her own way
to leave this world behind
and be reborn as
something else.
As something else?
This cave
summons spirits.
As soon as a soul
enters the cave...
it will repeat
the ritual...
That's about all
I know so far.
Wait, then does that mean
I'm a spirit right now too?
Yes...
That's why it's best that you
not come close to here alone...
Let's go.
We get to hold
hands again.
Umm, uh...
Naru...?
Remember last
time when you told me
that you showed me the
way into the dream...?
Have you been doing
that this whole time?
-Mai.
-Yeah? What?
Naru...? What
happened to you...?
You were just here.
Where'd you run
off to...?
-Naru?
-Mai...
Mai...
What the...
I'm still at base?
Wait is it already morning...?
Did I sleep through
the whole night?
It sounds like I
ruined all the fun
by waking you up just now...
You were on a date with
him, weren't you...?
I ask because you were
confusing me with someone else
while you
were dreaming.
Oh No No No No,
I promise,
it was nothing
like that at all!
So tell me, did anything
productive happen to take place?
Huh...?
Oh you mean
like a clue?
So you saw
womb cycling...
That's interesting...
I myself have
seen that occur
but only around
shrines and temples.
The dark tunnel is
supposed to replicate
the feeling of being
in your mother's womb,
and when you exit the cave,
it's as if you're
being reborn
into a whole new life.
Wow.
But I don't understand
why Nao would be doing that.
Hey... Good to see ya...
What's up?
Good to see you too!
I called him in
for backup...
So man...
Why don't you
join me at base?
There's something that
I need to show you.
Okay.
Geez, I've been
here five seconds
and I'm already
being put to work.
So we should
catch up later...
See you around, Mai.
Bye... See ya later.
What is that...?
Sounds awful.
Not sure.
I just came
across it while
I was going over
yesterday's data.
It sounds like a
dinosaur snoring.
Yeah.
Hey... guys?
Oh no!
There's smoke coming
from the main building!
Are there any more
fire extinguishers?
Yes, uh... I'll get them.
-Here you go Monk.
-Thanks.
I'm gonna get more
fire extinguishers!
Naru!
I'll be right back!
Lin wait!
Oh no...
Ayako! Help Hiroe with
the extinguishers!
What...? Wait, where
are you going Mai?
Lin!
Kazuyasu's been possessed too!
Stop it.
If you open that door, you
will die, I guarantee it.
Listen up Mai...
Try using the
Nine Cuts on him.
But I'm not supposed
to do that to people.
If I do it I'll just
end up killing him ...
Now that thin wall isn't
going to hold for much longer.
If Naru wakes up, it's over.
Naru!
No... I can't do it!
Careful Lin,
he's dangerous!
I'm so sorry...
but... I have to ...
Rin! Pyo...!
To! Sha!
Kai! Jin!
Retsu! Zai!
Zen!
Mai, I need you to get
Takigawa over here right away!
Have someone
watch the base!
He did what?
C'mon John, let's go!
-Right!
-Ayako!
Masako!
Cover the base!
Got it!
There they are!
Takigawa...! Be careful!
He's been using
whirlwind sickles.
You did it.
You pushed Nao
to her death...
Didn't you Kazuyasu...?!
You're the one who
killed the dogs
and tampered with the car.
Now just admit it!
Just who the hell
are you in there...?!
Why are you tormenting
this family?
Tell me... Who are you...?
And Why are you trying
to release Naru...?
What's your
purpose for being here?
To kill... Death to everyone!
No! Don't do it!
That's awful.
But we can't let
it get us down...
If we leave here with our
tails between our legs...
then the lives that
have been lost
and the effort we've put
in will be for nothing.
You're right.
Now if I can just
find my notes
I can let you know
what I found out...
I'll get right
to the point...
The problem isn't with
the Yoshimi family,
but with the location.
Really...?
You mean the actual ground
the house is built upon?
The land used to belong to
the Fujisako family,
but around a-hundred
fifty years ago,
near the end of
the Edo period,
the family died off...
Soon after the Yoshimi
family bought the property.
But they died off too
after four generations...
The current Yoshimi family
is another branch on the tree,
if you will, from the
Kanazawa area.
That makes sense...
And it explains why we
were only able to find
records for the last
two heads of the family
inside the temple.
So moving on, I found
an interesting story
that could offer
some clues.
It's commonly referred to as the
legend of the ijin killings.
What's Ijin?
The definition of ijin is
"someone from another place"...
Back then villages were
closed communities...
so in addition to being
extremely suspicious of
any kind of outsiders...
If the stranger showed
any signs of power
that impressed the villagers,
they'd become an
object of worship.
What kind of power
would that take?
In those days,
outside of merchants,
most of the travelers were
heavily into religion,
with many of them
practicing shugenja.
They would visit villages
and pray that the upcoming rain
or harvest be
plentiful,
and sometimes would
even fight goblins
and exorcise harmful spirits.
Wow... That's almost
exactly what we do.
Yes. In those days
you all would have
made fine ijin.
Although the customs have
changed over the years,
it's basically the same.
Some of the family
members said that
thirty-two years ago three
spiritualists died here...
We can't leave this place
until we clean it up.
So... Tell us what you know
about this ijin killing legend.
Oh right...
The Okobu you
were told about
is an integral part
of the story.
Okobu?
Long ago, there were
three shugenja monks
that came to the village.
They immediately saw
the Okobu and said
it would bring about a
curse to the village,
so they performed an
exorcism on it.
The Okobu morphed into
a gold statue of Buddha.
The shugenja said "only a
curse on the statue itself
could have caused it to
end up in such a way."
So they offered to build a
shrine for it in the village,
where it could be safe.
However, the village
elder's desire to own the
statue himself drove him to
kill the monks on the beach.
After that, the Buddha statue
turned back into driftwood.
The elder's family became
plagued with misfortune
and eventually died off.
It was dubbed
the Monk's curse.
So three
shugenja monks...
or maybe three "Rokubu?"
Rokubu?
The pilgrims
that traveled to
each of the sixty-six
sacred spots
and would leave a copy
of the holy sutra
were called
the 'sixty-six',
or more commonly,
the rokubu.
Those three mounds we
found near the shrine...
I wouldn't be surprised
if they were the graves
of the three monks that
were killed here.
The graves of the
three rokubu...
Hence the sanroku mounds!
Yeah... Hold on
just one second...
I have some folklore about
the rokubu mounds somewhere.
Ah, here it is.
In year Bunkyu ...
or in eighteen sixty-two,
there was a revolt
by the peasants in the area
that was ultimately suppressed.
The villagers turned
over the five peasants
that instigated the revolt in
exchange for their own lives,
but the men escaped...
When they were caught by
the mob chasing them,
they were beheaded
on the spot.
Five of them?
Soon after there were
countless epidemics
and strange events
surrounding the village,
and it didn't take long for
word of a curse to spread.
But after a temple was erected
next to the rokubu mounds,
the strange
phenomena disappeared.
Hold on...
Next to the rokubu
mounds is right here!
There's more.
After the leaders of the
revolt were beheaded,
the villagers gave
them a proper burial,
but legend has it,
if you disrespect
the graves,
strange growths will
appear on your neck,
and your head will
eventually fall off.
Strange growths
on your neck?
Five graves...
the revolt leaders ...
Those stones
out at the cape!
Those are the graves
of the peasants
that were betrayed and
killed by the villagers.
Of course, drowning in the
sea would be merciful...
not nearly as bad...
as someone chopping off
your head don't you think?
Or having...
the people that you
love betray your trust.
I shall curse you
from beyond the grave!
You will not escape me!
That's it...
That's what this
was all about.
Alright... What do you say
we have a go at this?
Right Now?
So between the five from
the revolt and the three monks,
which do you think is the
most likely culprit?
Honestly, I don't think
we have enough clues
to narrow it down for sure.
I guess we'll just hit them
both at the same time...
That came from
the hall...
Is there someone here?
Takigawa. The temperature
is dropping fast.
The dinosaur!
No... Listen carefully.
It's a sutra!
I don't know about you
guys but I'm convinced
the rokubu behind this...
I'm gonna go see if I
can tell what's going on.
Alright, I want you
girls to stay put.
John, you're
coming with me.
Please Be
careful you two!
Do you guys hear that?
The windows!
Rin pyo to sha kai
jin retsu zai zen!
Mai, remember they're
already dead,
so don't bother holding back!
Nao!
But... why would she be here?
That's the
room Naru's in!
Rin pyo toh sha kai
jin retsu zai gyo!
But why him...? What
do they want with Naru?
Do they want Naru ...
or they want to
release the spirit
that's possessing him...
Nao, please forgive me.
Rin! Pyo!
Whirlwind sickles!
They have us cornered
and outnumbered...
I don't think we can hold
them off for much longer!
Naru! Help us!
[Music]
Next time on Ghost
Hunt, the finale!
I just hope we live
to see the end!