On kirikiri bazara baziri
hora manda manda un hatta!
On amirito
dohanba un hatta!
On biso hora daraki
shabezara hanjara un hatta.
On asan magini un hatta...
On shau-gya-rei
makasan maen SOWAKA!
If you bastards think
you can make it in now...
just try it!
Where's Father Brown?
He's getting Akifumi
and the rest of them.
They should be
here in no time.
Did they show up
down there too?
'Show up' isn't
the right phrase...
They've been attacked by
a mob of drowned corpses.
Its like we're in
a zombie movie.
That sounds like Katsuki!
Oh no!
John! Get to the base!
It's safe there!
What's happening?
Whatever you do, don't let
those white things touch you!
[Music]
Mai!
Ayako...
I... I think I'm...
No blood...?
But I'm sure it
went through me.
Mai, what's wrong?
Monk! Behind you!
Are you okay?
What's it look like...?
I'm gonna be okay,
but man, does
this thing hurt!
Can you get up?
Yeah, now I'm
just angry...
Kyata hanjasa
hadaya sowaka!
They're glowing red.
Now open the door!
Mai! Thank goodness
you're alright.
Looks like everyone's
accounted for.
I'm gonna take
a nap here...
The cold floor's never
felt so comfortable.
Now's a good time
to get some rest...
I sense... they won't be
back for a little while.
If I were to fall
asleep the barrier
protecting us would
collapse immediately.
So... what are we
gonna do now?
First thing... Is we
wait 'till morning...
Once the sun rises
things should quiet down.
Naru!
He's fine...
Somehow he didn't wake up
through that whole ordeal.
-What is it?
-My shiki
that were knocked away in
the fight have returned.
Really?
So those were your shiki.
Yes...
Could you sense
their presence?
Yes...
It's starting to
make sense now...
It explains why the
spirits in this house
felt so empty and hollow.
The reason the spirits
possessing Naru
and the children feel
so vacant is because
they're different
than the norm...
They're in the service
of someone else
so they don't act
on their own.
They're basically slaves
with no free will,
left to the bidding
of their controller,
who exploits their
deepest personal grudges
and uses them as shiki.
These are feelings so
strong they prevent them
from finding eternal rest.
Who could be
doing this...?
And why?
Alright. Breaks over for me.
Time to get back to work.
But Monk you've been holding
up the barrier all night
and haven't
slept a wink.
Why don't you try
to get some sleep?
We just don't have
that kind of time ...
The longer we
wait the more
we're putting
ourselves at risk.
If we get attacked
again tonight,
I don't think we'll be
able to hold them off.
Lin stay here
with them...
I've gotta take
down the barrier...
If it goes much
longer it'll drain
what's left of my energy...
-Come on John.
-Right.
Wait, where
are you going?
Where do you think?
The san-roku mounds.
You heard the sutra
being recited, right?
We're up against
the three rokubu.
I'm pretty sure they're
taking advantage of the fact
that spirits are
attracted to the cave
so they can trap and enslave
them shortly after death.
That has to be what
happened with the peasants
that were beheaded
in the revolt,
as well as the princess and
her lover from the legend.
If you think about it, the
rokubu have had carte blanche
on every spirit from
the area for centuries.
So many innocent souls.
We have no other choice.
We have to act now.
I'll do it.
You guys should catch
up on your sleep...
You're practically
staggering right now.
No offense Ayako but this
is way out of your league.
Why don't you volunteer
after you've actually
done something productive.
Look Takigawa...
I'm only volunteering
because I know I can do it.
you sure about this?
You're gonna have
to trust me...
I can do this...
Let me handle this one.
There aren't many places
like this left in the world.
I can sense a strong
energy from the past here.
The trees are
really alive.
-The trees?
-Yes...
When I was young we had a
gigantic camphor tree
in front of my
parents house.
It was absolutely
gorgeous...
It taught me a
lot of things
that I still keep
with me today.
And, It would always tell
me when the patients
from my parent's hospital
were going to die.
But whenever I would
tell my parents
about these prophecies,
they would scold me.
Wow.
To be honest, when
you get down to it,
I really don't have that
much power of my own...
However...
I am still a priestess.
Huh, she actually
sounds kind of cool.
Let's begin.
I stand here today to
beseech the gods
I call upon them to
descend from the heavens
and join us where
no gods dwell...
to end this...
ceaseless suffering.
I ask that my humble
plea may be heard...
and peace be restored...
unto the spirits
who are trapped...
in this haunted place
I don't get it.
She's reciting the same
prayer she always does...
but this time,
something's different.
May this grove reflect
the High, Heavenly Plain
and may the gods from all
corners come together as one.
It feels like the air
is getting clearer.
Rin... Pyo...
To... Sha...
Kai... Jin...
Retsu... Zai...
Zen!
They disappeared.
It's Kazuyasu and Nao!
Come... The time for you
to achieve eternal sleep
has finally arrived.
Every time she
rings her bell...
the spirits vanish...
Is it possible that
all these spirits
are coming here because
they want to be purified?
Ayako! Behind you!
Well now... She didn't
need us after all.
If you've had that kind
of power all along,
why have you kept it
hidden all this time?
I've never hidden
it from anyone...
Like I said I only use it
when I know it'll work.
I don't normally
bring it up
because it sounds like
I'm making excuses.
Oh... We'd never
think that.
Up to this point there
haven't been any live trees.
When I first began you may have
noticed some elder spirts,
many with long beards,
emerging from the trees.
They are basically the
spirits of the trees,
and I borrow their power.
If a tree has
lost its spirit,
then it's as good as dead.
My rituals don't even need
to be done near a shrine.
Many shrines and
temples in the city
are in poor shape
as they get older,
but with the trees,
no matter what their age,
they are always the same.
So I guess it helped
that the mounds
happened to be
next to a grove,
but what if they
weren't...?
How would you have
gone about it then?
As long as they're
somewhere nearby,
I can summon the spirits to
wherever I need them to be.
Wait, I'm confused.
If it's that easy to do,
why didn't we do that
when were exorcising Eijiro?
My ritual has no effect
on human beings...
I'm really only capable
of purifying a spirit.
Besides, once I
utilize a tree,
I have to let it
rest for six months
before I can use it again.
So if I had tried to
use them on Eijiro,
I wouldn't have been
able to use them
when we needed
them the most.
So I guess that settles
everything, huh?
Not quite.
-uh? uh?
-Huh?
Remember, I only
do spirits...
but there is another
presence here...
something worse.
Well what is it?
Earlier I could sense a power
that wouldn't come near me
during the ritual...
If that power had
been a spirit
it would have wanted
to be purified,
but it was repelled.
I believe there's another
entity out there
we've yet to deal with...
It's very powerful and
it's been using the
Yoshimi family
as its shiki.
So it wasn't the
spirits of the rokubu.
No, I think they were being
used as its shiki as well.
Come to think of it,
Nao said something
about a monster...
If it's capable of
controlling so many spirits...
Then it has to be something with
a whole lot of power, right?
Which means that...
there's only one thing
that could harness
that level of power.
The Okobu...
Isn't it?
The piece of driftwood
that washed up in the cave...
It was shaped like a
statue of Buddha,
so they enclosed it in a
shrine built in its honor.
That makes it a
true yebisu...
Which means we're going
to have to take on a god.
Hey we're back.
What's the matter Monk?
Naru!
Of course!
Thanks to Ayako's
purification ritual,
the spirit possessing Naru
has been cleansed too!
You know it wouldn't hurt
for you to say thank you...
After all I had to put
aside my many resentments
towards you in
order to save you.
It's so good to see
you awake, Kazuya.
He's in kind
of a foul mood.
As usual!
Soo...
Anyway...
It's looking more and more
like the source of the curse
was not the spirits of the
rokubu like we thought.
It's the Okobu.
But how did
you know that?
my brain works
differently than yours.
I oughta...
Consider the shrine...
Behind it is the
cave by the sea...
with another
shrine inside it.
There you can find a
yebisu named Okobu.
There is a path from the
cave to the shrine
that's carved out of the
natural sea wall...
with steps made of stone.
Now why were
those constructed?
There's obviously some
meaning behind it.
It's the divine figure
found within the shrine.
Its presence meant they
had no choice but to build it.
There's no way they would
have gone that far
if it were some minor god.
What's enshrined in that cave
is a god with enough power,
to influence people to
do its bidding.
According to some of the
folklore from this village...
cyclones and
tsunamis disappeared
after the Okobu
was worshipped...
However...
if the Iwai neglected
to worship the Okobu,
calamity would soon
strike the village.
What are Iwai?
They're basically
a kind of priest.
The shrine in
which the Okobu
was originally meant
to be worshipped...
is now cut off from the
smaller shrine inside the cave.
The house is what
caused the separation.
It was probably
part of the shrine
when it was first built.
The grounds surrounding the
shrine were probably divided
and sold as
individual properties.
The land where the Iwai
lived was divided
and sold when the five members
of the revolt were beheaded.
That seems to be the
most likely scenario.
Soon thereafter
that land was sold
and rezoned for
private housing...
It is the Okobu's
belief that
anyone who lives
on that land
must worship it as
their one and only god.
So when the unaware
tenants moved in
and neglected to worship
it, they were cursed.
Naru is amazing.
He solved the mystery
like it was nothing.
We now have to perform
an exorcism on the Okobu.
But is that
really necessary?
I mean all it needs is
to be worshipped, right?
Yes but if the
worshipping stops
the curse will start again.
This may only be a yebisu
but it's still a god...
That's a lot worse
than a monster...
Need I remind you
that you were the one
who said you can't
hunt monsters?
So we should look
the other way...?
You've got to be kidding.
Don't get me wrong.
I had a wonderful time
being possessed...
But it would be
downright rude of me
not to return the
favor in full.
Let's begin.
On haba haba kiuta saba
taruma saba saba kitsudo kan...
On data gato naoo
bay by ya sowaka...
On bata mari ni-oo
haybaya sowaka.
On bazara geenee
harach hataya sowaka.
It sounds... Like
a heart beating.
The... the wall.
The rock is pulsating...
and it's warm, like
a person's skin.
Now it's breathing...?
It's almost like the cave
itself is a living being!
Takigawa look!
The entrance is closing!
Not good.
Don't worry...
It'll open back up
when we terminate
the source.
I can't take this...!
Please Make it stop!
In the beginning
was the Word...
and the Word
was with God...
and the Word it was God.
He was with God
in the beginning.
Through him all
things were made.
Without him nothing was
made that has been made.
In him was life...
And that life was...
the light of all men...
Rin! Pyo! Toh! Sha!
Kai! Jin! Retsu! Zai! Zen!
AD GURAY NAMEH,
JUGAD GURAY NAMEH,
SAT GURAY NAMEH,
SIRI GURU DEVAY NAMEH
On haba haba kiuta saba
taruma saba saba kitsudo kan.
Rin! Pyo! To! Sha!
Kai! Jin! Retsu! Zai! Zen!
There's too many
of them...!
Every time we hit
one, another spawns!
We can't stop now!
They're all... turning red.
Monk!
Tareet sut boreets hara
boreets takimei takimei.
Kara san tan uenbi... sowaka!
Oh no!
Now John... Use the vajra...
and destroy the yebisu!
Right!
John!
Hey wait!
Yasu...! Are you okay?
Well...
At least I'm still alive.
Is that all you've got? !
Why don't you just
shut up already?
We've all been working our
butts off trying to save you,
and this is the
thanks we get?
Why should we
risk our lives?
Just so we can protect
your selfish ego...?
Have you totally
lost your mind? !
If your pride's so important,
then try doing
things yourself
instead of relying on
us all the time...!
Pride means nothing
when other people
do everything for you ...
Get that through
your head!!
Point taken.
Come on Monk, let's go.
We've done enough already.
Sorry to let you down...
but we can't do it.
Hey... What are you doing?
Naru...
Don't do it!
Come on Naru...
What's going on?
It's like there's all this
air flowing out of Naru.
It's so heavy, I feel
like my entire body
is covered in a film
or something.
My ears are
ringing so bad,
I can't even hear anything,
and everything's starting
to look all distorted.
Is Naru doing this
all by himself?
What was... that?
It's gone...
the presence is gone.
This is no longer
sacred ground...
The other spirits
have moved on as well.
Let's go.
Hang in there, you guys.
We're almost there.
Naru?
Naru!
No! Stay with us, Naru!
Oh no... Is he gonna be okay?
Breathe, damn it...! Come on!
No... No...
you can't die.
I'm gonna call
an ambulance!
That was Qigong,
wasn't it, Lin...?
After Naru took that
spirit from Eijiro,
did you stop him because you
knew this would happen?
Yes, I did.
I don't understand...
Is Qigong really
that dangerous...?
It's supposed to be able to
heal people, right...?
So why did Naru end
up in the hospital?
First off, calm down Mai.
The extent of Naru's power
is in a league of its own.
Seriously?
Since childhood...
Naru has caused
poltergeists.
I taught him how
to use Qigong
so he could
control the energy
flowing from his body
because it was too
much to handle
with his conscious
mind alone.
But... the power Naru has
is too much for
one person...
The thing is...
when he uses his power,
his body can't keep up...
and this happens.
It's all my fault...
The only reason he
used his energy
is because I provoked him.
It's his fault for allowing
himself to be provoked.
But still!
Listen Mai, Naru
was well aware of
what would happen in
this situation...
If he had been
thinking clearly,
he wouldn't have allowed himself
to be provoked like that...
Usually he's better at
maintaining his composure.
If I were to guess, he
was probably upset about
the blunder he
made before...
I mean you know how much
pride he has in himself.
It's okay...
I'm sure he'll recover.
He made a mistake and drew a
sword no human can bear...
So... he made
two mistakes...
Which means he'll be in
a bad mood for a while.
Yeah...
He will.
A funeral was held for
Kazuyasu and Nao
at the Yoshimi's home.
And the bruises
on Hazuki's
neck and back disappeared.
With that, one of our most
horrific cases was over,
claiming two victims.
It's amazing they
were the only ones.
Naru!
I'm so glad you're
finally awake!
Where are Monk
and Father Brown?
We're right here, Kazuya.
The hospital released
us the other day.
I'm sorry guys.
-Huh?
Did Naru just...
...apologize to someone?
Well, Lin totally
called this one.
Naru was quickly back
to his old self,
grumpy as ever.
Way to go on the
quick recovery, kiddo.
You're making me
look like an old man.
Well, you know...
hey you'll be out of
here next, Kazuya.
If you're going
to keep talking,
please go outside...
As if it's not
totally obvious,
I'm in the middle
of something.
The funny thing is,
we wouldn't want to have
Naru any other way.
Self-centered, overly
confident, pushy
and, most of all,
narcissistic.
That's how we like him.
Mai... Hot tea.
Oh sure.
That would make
a good picture...
Monk...
Ayako...
John...
Masako...
and Yasu, all
at Naru's side.
It's been a long time
since I've felt like
I'm in a family...
But now I feel like
I really belong.
Why do you always
get to do it?
You're always hogging
the good jobs.
Maybe I'd like to do it!
Sit back down...
You heard Naru yourself.
He asked me to do it!
Sometimes you just
have to step aside Mai!
Sorry, but
this is my job.
I have to do it myself!
If I could have one wish,
it would be to stay like
this with my friends
forever.
[Music]