And then,
the woman led the policeman
through the dark hallways
to the public restroom
in the back.
Once there, the policeman
told her to go back inside
and wait to see if she
could hear the voice again,
and she did just
as she was told.
Do you want me to cover
you with a red coat?
She answered...
Yes.
And then!
The policeman burst
through the door
and found the girl
totally covered in blood,
as if she had a red
coat draped over her.
Mai you know we hate it
when you use that
creepy voice!
That day was
like any other,
staying late after school
telling ghost stories.
Every time we finish a
story we turn off a light,
and then, once
we're all done,
there's always
one light left,
meaning there's another
person in the room.
You're up next, Michiru.
The other person is
supposedly a ghost!
Okay. This one's about
the old schoolhouse.
Do you mean that
creepy old building
down the street
that's collapsing?
But it's not collapsing...
It was being demolished when
the workers suddenly quit.
Because of a curse.
Lots of people have died in that
schoolhouse over the years,
most famously a teacher
that committed suicide.
So when they decided to
build the new school
they started to tear
down the old one,
but then...
The demolition
ended that day.
Last year they started
the demolition again
to make way for
a new gymnasium
but a truck driving
by lost control
and crashed into a
group of kids outside,
killing some students.
But there's more...
I heard about this
from an upperclassman.
One night a student was
walking past the old school
when...
Here goes.
One. Two. Three. Four.
It's the ghost!
It's here to murder us!
Oh, Please tell me
that was you just now!
Am I interrupting?
I thought for sure
it was the ghost.
Sorry I didn't expect
anyone to be here.
But then I heard
your voices
and couldn't
help myself.
Oh no... It's totally fine!
What year are you?
I'm seventeen this year.
Normally someone would
just say they're a senior.
So we were just
telling ghost stories.
I see...
Well maybe I could
join you guys sometime.
Wow... Do you mean you like
telling ghost stories too?
Yeah...
You seem like a
really cool guy.
What's your name?
My name is Kazuya.
His eyes.
They're not smiling.
Okay Kazuya...
I have one question ...
Why are you here?
There are some things
I need to take care of.
What're you
waiting for...?
Do you need our
help for anything?
No... but I would
love to be invited
to join you the next time
you tell Ghost Stories.
Of course!
You're welcome anytime!
How about tomorrow?
After school?
Okay... But Where?
Right here.
Something's
fishy about him.
I better get to
the bottom of this!
[Music]
I love this weather!
And I'm so glad
I left early...
I've got all the cherry
blossoms to myself!
The more I look
at this place,
the more I believe
the stories.
What's that?
A video camera?
But... What's it
doing here...?
I thought this
place was abandoned.
I doesn't make sense
that someone would
just leave it here.
Who's there?
Uh... I'm sorry...
I'll leave now.
Oh no...! Help!
Hey Mister, are you okay?!
Oh no. What should I do? I...
What's going on in here?
It's that guy
from yesterday.
Lin... What just happened?
You're bleeding.
-Can you stand?
-Yeah.
Oh my gosh...
I'm really sorry
about this.
He startled me and I guess
I turned around too fast.
Never mind all that...
Is there a
doctor close by?
There's a doctor just
down the street from here.
No thanks...
You've done enough
already as it is.
But...
We met yesterday, right...?
What's your name?
It's uh... Mai.
Well alright then Mai...
I thought you
might want to know
that you're going to be
late for your first class
since the morning
bell just rang.
I'm late?
I don't believe this!
What the heck was
that all about?
I never want to step foot
in that creepy place again!
Mai, are you leaving now?
We're supposed to
tell ghost stories
-with that cute guy, remember?
-Not me.
Awe, come on, Mai. Please!
This is our chance to tell
ghost stories with a senior!
Did you say ghost stories?
Is that what you three do
after school every day?
Then no wonder I've had
this headache for so long...
I'm very attuned
to spirits...
When they gather in
groups I get headaches.
So you're...
blaming us for that?
Of course I am.
Whenever you tell one of
your little ghost stories
you attract low
level spirits,
and they attract
stronger spirits...
and then we're
in big trouble.
So when you entertain
yourselves with these stories
you're putting me at risk.
So tell me...
If you're sensitive to
spirits like you claim
then do you sense anything
with the old schoolhouse?
Oh my gosh Kazuya
came to find us!
Hold on...
Are you the one
who put these girls
up to telling these
ridiculous ghost stories?
You didn't answer
my question.
Could it be your psychic
abilities are made up?
For your information there are
numerous spirits of those
who died in the war that
gather in the old schoolhouse.
In fact, I'm positive
that building was used as a
hospital during the war.
I've just seen too many
injured spirits there.
I was not aware of a hospital
being here during the war...
I know this school was
founded well before the war
so maybe... this was
a medical school?
Look I don't know.
But I really do
see spirits...
If you're not psychic
you wouldn't understand.
Sorry Kazuya...
Can we do this
some other time?
Yeah I'm not in the
mood anymore either.
No...? Perhaps another day.
Oh, and Mai?
Would you mind coming
with me for a moment?
How's you friend doing?
Yes about him.
He suffered a sprain
to his left leg
and I'm afraid he won't
be walking for awhile.
Gosh. Will you please
tell him I'm sorry?
So what were you two
doing there anyway?
Working.
Oh I get it.
You work for him.
Are you like his
assistant or something?
No, not quite.
He's the assistant.
I'm the boss.
And now my assistant
is stuck in a bed...
I believe it's up to
you to take his place.
Hey now hold on
just a minute!
The camera's broken.
My assistant tried to stop
you from touching the camera...
and it now it's
in several pieces.
Well Uh Can't I just buy
you a new one or something?
It's quite expensive.
Oh, then I don't
know what to do.
You can't afford
to reimburse me
for the damaged equipment,
which means there's only one
other course we can take.
You'll work off the
debt as my assistant.
Your assis... tant...?
You seriously think I should
start working for you?
Well, that's what I said.
What do you do
at your job?
I hunt ghosts.
Huh?
In other words,
I exorcise spirits... ghosts...
my company, Shibuya
Psychic Research
was hired to conduct
an investigation
on the old schoolhouse.
Psychic research?
Is that a question?
Psychic research
is another term
for spiritual investigations.
We basically examine
and scrutinize reports
of supernatural phenomena.
And I run the company.
Oh man!
One week ago, your principal
contacted my company.
Well the problem is...
we constantly have to
run damage control
over a rumor that the
schoolhouse is haunted.
When I checked the records,
I was able to verify that
up until eighteen years ago,
while the old schoolhouse
was still being used,
there would be at
least one or two deaths
inside the structure
every year.
It's also true that when
construction crews
were demolishing the
east side of the building,
there was an accident where
the roof collapsed prematurely.
No workers died
as a result,
though five were
injured in the incident,
which was ultimately
blamed on human error.
Construction ended
with only a third of the
planned demolition work
ever being finished...
A teacher did in fact commit
suicide in the building,
but that was explained
in the suicide note
left by the victim.
The incident with
the truck last year
was a drunk
driving accident.
That's when construction was
stopped for the last time.
No doubt, the rumors played
a part in this decision.
Based on my research,
the existence of
paranormal activity here
is nothing more
than fiction.
For a place this
active as this,
every occurrence has a
reasonable explanation.
We'll set up base here.
Base?
Precisely...we'll conduct
all of our observations
from this room.
Oh yeah of course.
Guess I'm still learning.
Set up those
shelves for me.
I'll start bringing
in equipment.
You're gonna leave me
here all by myself?
Would you rather carry
this stuff in...?
It's heavy. Some of it's weighs
up to a hundred pounds.
I'll stick to shelves.
I can't believe how
stuck up this guy is!
I mean, sure it was my fault
that his assistant got hurt,
but does he have to
act so self- important?
Stop goofing off
and get back to work.
It's official.
I hate him.
What' are those?
An infrared camera and a
thermal-imaging camera.
They're used to shoot
in total darkness.
This one uses thermography
to record temperatures...
When a spirit appears,
the temperature
near it will drop
and show up
on the camera.
It's amazing that you know
how to use all this stuff.
No it's not. My brain just
works differently than yours.
I... see...
After all you are
Mr. Hot Shot boss
so you might as
well do everything...
But what made
you decide to go
into the ghost
hunting business?
Because someone
has to do it.
Well have you
had any cases
that you weren't
able to explain?
No. I'm very
good at my job.
Amazing... he's as
smart as he is handsome.
So you think...
I'm handsome, huh?
Uhh, well I mean,
that's what all the girls
at school are saying!
Well... They have
very good taste.
I can't believe this guy!
Sure he may be
good looking
and extremely successful
at such a young age,
but I have never seen a bigger
narcissist in my life!
From now on your
name is Naru...
As in Naru the Narcissist!
Well that's all we
have to do for today.
For today...?
You mean...!
I'll see you
here tomorrow.
Oh man.
Mai.
Have you been here with
Kazuya all night long?
What were you two doing?
It's kind of a long story.
Paranormal investigations?
So he's not an
upperclassman.
According to him,
he's a ghost hunter.
A ghost hunter?
Mai?
I was wondering if you
would introduce me to him.
Introduce you?
To Naru?
What's this Naru
stuff all about?
That guy has got to be
the biggest narcissist
I've ever met in my life...
I can't believe I actually
have to work for him now!
You know I have many
psychic abilities myself.
And I think I could really
help Kazuya with his work.
You know since he is
a professional and all
maybe it's not such a good
idea for you to get involved.
Well I'm by no
means an amateur!
Let's go, Mai.
That girl is
such a weirdo.
She's been like that
since middle school.
Yeah she's a freak.
Wasn't she in a lot of the
same classes as you, Keiko?
Yeah and she would
constantly bug people
about her spirits
or whatever.
Wait, I know why she
wants to help out.
I bet it's because she's already
fallen in love with Kazuya!
Eww! Gross!
-What's up?
-Checking yesterday's data.
So far there seems to
be nothing unusual.
That's some fancy
equipment you got there.
It seems a bit too high tech
for a couple of children
to be playing with.
And who might you be?
I am Ayako the
shrine maiden...
The principal
wasn't sold on you
so he called me to
drive the spirits out.
I was under the impression
that only innocent virgins
can become shrine maidens.
I see... and... your point!
At the very least I'd say
you're looking a little old
to be calling
yourself a maiden.
Nice...
Very funny you
smart-ass...
What about you?
I would guess you're
too intelligent
to be the shrine
maiden's assistant.
I'm a monk from Mt. Koya.
The name's Takigawa Hosho.
Since when were monks
allowed to have long hair?
Apostate?
I'm just on a little
hiatus okay...?
At any rate,
playtime is over kids.
Now you may have
gotten this gig
because your
office is nearby,
but the principal
himself said
it seemed like a scam to have
a teenager running the show.
Did he now?
The principal's
wasting his money...
There's no need
to have all of us
for such a simple job.
Yeah... All he
really needed was me.
Right... I wouldn't
be so sure.
Oh thank goodness
you're all here.
That haunted
old schoolhouse
has been terrorizing
me for weeks.
You see, I'm a psychic.
The souls of those
trapped there have...
Stop grandstanding...
You're just looking
for attention.
Are you really that desperate
for people to like you?
Excuse me! That
was extremely rude!
You know it's the truth.
She claims to have psychic
abilities in the hopes
that it will somehow
make her popular.
That is totally
uncalled for!
I'm gonna call a
spirit to haunt you.
Hold on Kuroda.
You're the fake...
And you'll regret this.
Whoa... I've never seen
her look so angry before.
Hey Naru...
So... What's up?
What are we
gonna do today?
Wait... What did you just say?
Did you call me Naru?
Sorry... I...
Where did you hear that?
Huh...? You mean...
You've been called
that before?
Of course, that
makes sense.
I can't be the first to
think up something like
Naru the Narcissist.
Morning everyone.
Nice to see you all.
Say hello to John Brown.
G'day mates.
The name's John Brown
and I come from the great
outback of Australia...
I can't express how
excited I am to join you.
Mr. Brown is relatively
new to our country
so please show him the
respect he deserves.
Let me guess! You're looking
for a playground, right?
Well... Actually I practice
the ancient art of exorcism.
Only those who
have been ordained
in the Catholic
church as priests
have the ability to
conduct exorcisms...
You seem young for that.
You really know
your stuff mate.
And to be honest I just turned
nineteen a few weeks ago,
That's why I look so young.
He's nineteen?
That means he's
older than Naru.
So we have an exorcist,
an apostate monk
and a ghost hunter.
Obviously this
bone-headed principal
doesn't have much faith in my
unique cleansing abilities.
Just watch.
I'll clear this
entire place myself.
I'm gonna do
a walkthrough.
See you later.
Uh, excuse me sir ...
You may do as you wish.
I mean...
I'd really like to
work with you on this.
That sounds like Ayako!
-Open up! I'm trapped!
-Stand back!
I'm gonna kick it down.
Just hurry up and do it!
I was looking around
the classroom...
When suddenly the
door slammed shut.
I tried opening it but
it wouldn't budge...
There's definitely
a spirit here...
No there isn't.
I don't sense one
paranormal being.
Ghost!
Relax Mai, she's human.
Masako Hara is
a spirit medium.
Oh... Another one?
Fantastic...
So now they're
calling in a t.v. star?
This is ridiculous.
It's easy to fake
results on television.
The only reason
she gets ratings
is because she's pretty and
wears that silly kimono.
Why thank you. I take
that as a compliment.
Well. Trust me... it's not.
Correct me if I'm wrong
but I don't think I've had the
pleasure of meeting you before.
Yes... We have never met,
but your reputation
precedes you.
Right.
Anyways, there's
a haunting here.
In my professional
opinion...
we're dealing with
an earthbound spirit.
I believe it's a
residual haunting...
A traumatic event
must have happened in this
building in the past.
So you mean like someone
was murdered here
and they have to
spend eternity
searching the halls for
their killer or something?
Close... I think the
entity is afraid
it's going to lose its home,
so it's attempting to
block the construction.
John... What do you think?
Well to be honest,
I'm not sure...
But Usually a haunting
does originate
with a ghost or spirit
occupying a structure.
So It's either... a haunting...
or fiction and folklore...
Are you listening, Mai?
Of course I am.
What do you take me for?
These are things
you need to learn.
Enough talk...
I'm getting rid of this
thing as soon as I get back.
I don't know how long I could
put up with you people.
I wouldn't be so confident
in your abilities...
The spirit that haunts this
site is incredibly powerful.
Kuroda.
Move aside.
The spirit attacked me.
Huh?
It's true...
I was walking
down the hallway
when suddenly my hair
was yanked backwards
with amazing force...
When I tried to flee it
started strangling me.
You're interfering
with me, psychic!
Leave or die!
When did this happen?
A few minutes ago in the
second floor hallway.
That's false.
There is no spirit here.
Yes there are...!
There definitely are...!
And they're angry!
You said it was the
second floor hallway?
What just happened?
Is the camera broken?
No... but it is quite strange.
When a spirit
becomes active,
electronic equipment will
often malfunction...
but here I'm not so sure.
Is it...
a spirit or EM
interference.
It's quite
obviously a spirit.
Interference doesn't cause
someone to be attacked.
But Masako said there
are no spirits here..
Well, let's just say that
I'm a little skeptical...
about her.
It's common for
female mediums
to be either exactly
right or way off base.
Even if she can't
sense any spirits
now doesn't mean the
haunting isn't active.
If what you say is true,
then it's possible that the
spirit that inhabits this place
is very in tune with
your wavelength.
Yeah... That's right.
If that's the case...
then is this all our fault?
Whenever you tell one of
your little ghost stories
you attract low
level spirits,
and they attract
stronger spirits...
and then we're
in big trouble.
So, when you entertain
yourselves with these stories
you're putting me at risk.
Oh No.
Did our telling Ghost
Stories about this place
actually attract
real ghosts?
[Music]
Next time we continue
file number one
with Part two of
"Evil Spirits All Over?!"
You better keep
your lights on!