Oh... So you think
you have a case
that Naru should
investigate?
Yeah. It all happened
earlier this week
when I was on a date
with Akira in the park.
We were just walking
and then all of a sudden
drenched in water.
How weird.
Maybe someone was
playing a prank.
They weren't... There wasn't
anyone else around us.
Oooh...! What were
you two planning
on doing with no
one else around?
Sorry...
You're really freaked
out about this.
Yeah... After this
thing happened
I've been way too freaked
out to go back there...
It really makes me sad
because that's
actually the place
where we had our
first kiss
So... you have fond
memories of the place.
I think there's a good
chance Naru will take it.
oh you really think so?
I can't promise anything.
See... Naru only takes
cases he wants to.
[Music]
So that's pretty much it.
She'll have better luck
taking that case to the police.
How'd I know
he'd say that?
If there's nothing else,
would you mind making some tea?
Yes sir.
It's been six months
since I started working here
and I'm still no closer
to figuring out Naru.
-Here's your tea, boss!
-Fine.
He never goes to school,
never watches TV
or listens to music.
All he does besides work is
read books about psychics
and ghosts and stuff.
You can go now Mai.
For crying out loud,
you could at least say
thank you for once!
-Hey Lin.
-Yes?
Lin is shrouded in even
more mystery than Naru.
The only thing I know
about him is his name
and that he rarely speaks.
What is it?
I was just wondering
if you'd like some tea.
No thanks.
That's how it always is.
Oh well, I guess he
still doesn't like me...
Good Afternoon.
Masako...! Long
time no see!
How are you?
Is Naru here?
Well, Good to
see you too!
Sorry...
I just decided to drop in
because there's a case
I came across that
Naru may like.
So, what is it you
wanted to talk about?
A friend from
the TV station
has specifically
requested your help.
Apparently, there's been
a strange phenomenon
that's been interfering with
the filming of a new show.
There have been hundreds
of cases documented
about spirits appearing
inside film studios.
That's just it.
They haven't shot
anything in the studio.
It's at the park...
Every time they shoot
there, without fail...
The actors are suddenly
doused in water.
That's what happened
to my friend Michiru!
So you've heard of it...
Actually a number of
these types of incidents
have been reported
as of late,
with the first report being
filed nearly six months ago.
It sounds to me like
kids having some fun.
That's exactly what I
thought at first,
but if this is just some
sort of practical joke
than there should be some
evidence left behind
Since the only evidence is the
wet clothes of the victims,
this case is a mystery.
The culprit wouldn't
have to be nearby.
That's exactly what I told
the Director yesterday.
Don't give me
that nonsense!
I've seen it
with my own eyes.
The water appears out of
nowhere, straight from the sky!
Everyone on set is
starting to get worried.
Please help us Masako.
That's everything
I know...
So what do you think Naru?
I would recommend that
if they're concerned
with their safety,
they should either
change locations
or halt their
shooting altogether.
The script calls for
that specific park
and shutting down production
would cost thousands of dollars.
That's none
of my concern.
Wait.
Look I owe the
Director a favor
so I'd really like
to find a way
to work this
out somehow...
You can understand that...
Right Naru?
Good luck.
Everyone knows Naru only
takes cases he wants.
Which park is it?
Say what?
I told him about this
exact same case earlier
and he shot me down, but
he'll do it for Masako?
I cooled down once I
realized technically
my case was still
being investigated.
And so it began...
So this is the location?
This one seems a bit
odd don't you think?
I know, a spiritual phenomenon
that attacks couples?
We have yet to determine
if it's a spirit or not.
I assume that's what we're
about to investigate right?
Where's Matsuzaki?
Uhh, I called her but I guess
she must be running late.
You know how she is.
She'll waltz in here and
say something like...
This is clearly the work
of an earth spirit
Wow Monk! That
was perfect!
This is clearly the work
of an earth spirit
Care to fill me in on
what's so funny?
Now that we're all here let's
begin the investigation
This is a case
about a phenomenon
that only happens under
specific circumstances,
which means that you
will all have to...
Yeah we know. Get to
the point already...
We'll exorcise
the spirit, right?
Huh...? I'm not about to
do my ritual out here
in front of all
these families.
For this case exorcisms
will not be necessary.
Then what exactly do
you plan for us to do?
The plan is to have you
all act as live bait.
Bait?
The term sounds worse
than it really is,
however it's the quickest way
to draw out the spirit.
I have a feeling this was
your goal from the start,
wasn't it Masako?
Now we just have to
divide ourselves
into three bait couples.
Hey Mai...
Here's your big chance to
score a date with Naru.
He's right.
I better...
Okay! I'm in!
Alright. I think Naru and I
should be the first team.
Ayako , You suck,!!
I'm the only girl here who
doesn't look out of place
on Naru's arm...
What can you do...?
I think we make a fantastic
couple, don't you?
Naru?
It's not fair.
What's so great
about her?
Does it make you
resentful...?
That I forced this
case on you.
Miss Hara...
Sensing anything?
I am feeling a faint
presence of some kind.
You're so lame Masako.
This whole "bait"
thing is just a scam.
Don't you, Naru?
Bad idea.
Putting You and
Naru together
would look more like
brother and sister
than an actual couple.
But I however...
Whatever, Masako and
Naru look so alike.
Are you still
whining about that?
So what?
Have you considered the
possibility of Masako
blackmailing him...?
She must have some dirt on him
otherwise he would
have chosen me.
Geez get over yourself.
Not to change the subject
but are you as
surprised as I am
that Naru even
accepted this case?
Yeah... I found it a
bit strange myself.
He refused when I
told him about it,
but when Masako asked him
he changed his mind.
I knew it. She is
blackmailing him.
Everyone. If you don't
take this more seriously
we'll never be able to
draw out the spirit.
Should we be making
out or something?
What about you Masako?
This is your big chance so
you might as well kiss him.
Even the thought of that
is totally unprofessional!
Don't tell me she's
actually going to kiss him!
That would be my
worst nightmare!
Anyway we need to
change some things
to draw the spirit out...
Split up into couples
and act independently
of each other.
If only Lin
were here today.
Then I would have some
actual motivation.
Huh...? So you like...
guys that quiet?
Just the hot ones.
No way!
Of all the days to be
sick... You lucky dog.
We decided to play
rock-paper-scissors
to choose couples.
We ended up with me
and Monk as one team,
and John and Ayako as the other.
Is there a certain
place here
where the phenomenon
tends to occur?
The only thing of
which I'm certain
is the shooting location
was inside this park.
So if it only
happens here
then maybe it really is a
sitebound spirit...
Interesting.
Naru... It's here!
Hold on!
Well uh... That
was kinda weird.
Why is it so quiet now?
No one's here.
It's okay. It was
just a cat.
Oh that's cool
What was that? !
Miss Hara!
It's here...
Right behind Mai...
and It's a woman.
She's young...
Looks to be in
her mid-twenties.
-Miss Hara!
-What happened?
I don't know.
She just collapsed.
What the...
Serves you right!
What's wrong with her?
Did she hit her head
when she fainted
and turn into a crazy person?
She's become possessed.
Huh?
The spirit's
taken over
Oooh... He's hot...!
I would have
totally done anything
to date such a good
looking guy like this
when I was still alive!
Well she's not one
to mince words.
It's hilarious to hear
that coming out of
Masako's mouth.
It's not funny at all!
If she doesn't let
him go this instant,
there is gonna be
a big problem!
Now tell me
truthfully spirit.
Are you the one who
is responsible
for raining water down on
people that come to this park?
Yes that's me...
They can all just die of
pneumonia for all I care!
But Why would
you want that?
Because I hate them.
I hate them coming here
and flaunting their
love in front of me.
Why must they mock me
when I hurt so much?
But What is it that's
making you hurt so much?
Do you really
want to know?
Oh thank you! I'll tell
you every detail...!
It's the most heart-wrenching,
tear-jerking story of lost
love you'll ever hear!
This very park
is the place
where I first set
my eyes on him.
Excuse me Miss.
yes?
Fate brought us
together that day.
Over some leeks?
C'mon...
This sounds like the plot
for some lame old
black and white movie.
We would often meet
here at the park
for the most romantic dates...
Everyone around us
would get so jealous
over how close
we had become.
BUT THEN!
He...
He!
How about we catch
a movie sometime?
No, it can't be.
So that jerk was
two timing you...?
What a piece of garbage.
Yes it's true!
I loved this park
before I met him
and now it only brings
up bad memories!
What's your reason
behind using water?
Tell me! Who is this woman?
I deserve an answer
now say something!
Get lost will ya?
Can't you see You're
bothering my lady friend.
This guy must be the
scum of the earth!
you can say that again.
I was so lonely and
depressed over this guy,
I decided to end
it all right here,
in these gorgeous
gardens that once held
only my most
beautiful memories.
Y'mean suicide?
Yes...
I do
Hey Lady! What do you
think you're doing?
Nooo!
I failed every time,
but once I gave up and
starting walking home...
That was almost
six months ago.
Which is when the first
occurrence happened.
And now I'm stuck
in this awful limbo.
So why don't you just
like go up to this guy
and haunt him directly?
Now Mai that wouldn't
be a very good idea.
It sounds to me like this
creep needs to have
a scare or two put in him.
That's what I thought,
and I did try that.
But...
I curse you!
I can't believe how
much we are alike.
It's like I've finally met
my soulmate or something.
again I was a
total failure!
This guy seems
pretty insensitive.
I couldn't bear going
through this pain alone.
So I decided to haunt
all the couples
that came here and let
them know how I feel!
-Damn it!
-Was that really necessary?
Serves you right!
Stop it!
Attacking random people
just because you're
mad at some jerk
is just gonna make
everyone mad at you.
Is that what you want?
What's with you Mai?
Why are you so worked up?
Well I...
I just can't
stand grudges...
Life is too short.
You know she's right.
If you keep this
up you'll become
what's known as a
sitebound spirit.
Trust us. You'd
be much happier
crossing over now than
trying to get even.
If you'd like to do that,
there's still time.
Are you all in some
nerdy ghost club?
Well Not exactly.
So what do you think?
I would have to imagine
that living in limbo
like this gets
old after awhile.
Maybe it is
time I moved on.
Wait!
Even though I don't believe
in holding a grudge,
crossing over now wouldn't
deal with the problem.
You would only be
sweeping it under the rug.
Well... I mean is it's
not fair for the guy
to get away with it...
And I think you
deserve some closure.
You shouldn't worry.
What goes around
comes around.
He'll get his just
desserts alright.
If she's content
with letting it go
then we shouldn't pry.
It's all up to you.
It's him.
I want to teach that
dirtbag a lesson
he'll never forget.
But you've already
tried that before
and it never worked.
How will this be
any different?
I have an idea.
Excuse me.
You recently did
something extremely cruel
to someone who cared
about you very much.
I sense an evil aura
surrounding him.
I can see it...
The spirit of a woman who
was led to suicide by you.
Who are you people?
I don't know what the
hell you're talking about!
You practically
killed her.
Its said a woman's curse
lasts a hundred generations.
You should have her
exorcised as soon as possible.
You must have me mistaken
for someone else.
I mean why would I
need an exorcism?
hey, you're ...
You're from TV.
Hey... Stop...!
What the hell?
It's... It's you.
How does it feel to be on the
other end of your torment?
Spare me, please!
I didn't mean to hurt
anyone! I swear!
Oh I feel so
much better...
Now I can cross over
without any regrets.
Thank you so much.
And with that, the
woman's spirit was purified.
Mai you were
awesome today.
And let's not forget the
hilarious performance
Masako put on.
What did I do?
You went up to Naru and
started hugging and cuddling!
And then you topped it
off with a big kiss.
I kissed him? Seriously?
Not just once, but
like a dozen times!
No she didn't!
why would you lie to
her face like that?
Wait a minute! You
guys are lying to me?
Well you did hug him
and paw him for awhile.
But I didn't kiss him.
Is that right?
I would never
let you kiss him.
Never in a million years!
Just you wait Masako,
next time I won't eve-...
You're all still here...? Is
there nothing better to do?
We just love being
in your presence...
and must we remind you
why you finished
your investigation early?
Although I do truly
appreciate your help
in the investigation,
I never would
have imagined
that you would have
so much free time
that you'd start just hanging
out here after work.
Are you saying that
I have no life!
You're the one who practically
lives at his office!
Naru I'd like to buy
you some dinner
to thank you for all the help
you've given me today.
Oh please!
Naru would never fall for
such an obvious come on.
That sounds nice.
What...? You're going? !
Of course he is.
This isn't the first time
we've gone out together Mai.
just last week
we saw a movie...
Let's go Naru.
Naru, you idiot!
Why didn't you tell her to
get lost like you always do?
Ayako may be right.
I think she is
blackmailing him.
I always just assumed
they had a patron together.
Patron? !!
Actually, it's quite common
in the US and Europe.
Parapsychology isn't a
recognized field of science yet,
so all research
labs like Naru's
need some type of
financial support.
They'll often find
private sponsors
or even large corporations
to help with funding.
Oh so that's
what you meant.
You had me worried there.
Why?
Well in Japan the word
patron has another meaning,
having to do with
the subject of geishas
Ohh.
Yeah ... file that away
for future reference...
Though you may be right.
If he has a sponsor it
could be Masako's dad.
Then he may feel
obligated to date Masako...
Huh.
For him to afford the
rent on a place like this
he must have a sponsor.
Is it that
expensive here?
It's not just the rent.
You have to factor in the
cost of all this equipment.
Have you ever looked
at the price tag
of one of those high-speed
cameras he owns?
I don't want to know.
It must be nice to
have a date with Naru.
hey Mai...
You wanna go catch
a movie with me?
I guess so.
Then we have a date...
Later we'll grab some food.
Anything you want... 'huh?
Aww Monk. That's so sweet!
He's trying to
cheer me up.
I love you Monk!
That sounds like
a great time!
You've got your
own Lolita now.
It's better than having
a date with my couch
like someone I know
Oh aren't you cute.
I actually do have a date.
But I think Lin's
working late tonight
Oh It's not him.
She means me?
Don't worry John.
I'll play nice.
Be careful John.
She may try to stick
you with the bill.
What a crazy day...!
Lin. You mind closing
up for the night?
[Music]
Next time on Ghost Hunt.
Silent Christmas, Part One!
I love the holidays!