SPR has been hired
to investigate
a series of
dangerous hauntings
that have been occurring
at Rokuryo High School.
Unfortunately we can't
exorcise anything
because Masako is having
trouble seeing the spirits.
I started having
vivid dreams
where foxfires were
swallowing other spirits,
making them grow larger
and more dangerous.
My dreams became a reality
when the dog from the
first day came back,
only bigger and angrier.
Things were starting
to get out of control.
And now, Sakauchi's spirit,
which was trapped
inside this school,
has been swallowed
by a foxfire.
Eventually, even
I was attacked...!
Please, save me, Naru!
[Music]
What...
What happened to me?
Oh no...
Not again.
It's being eaten up by
that ugly purple thing.
Just like Sakauchi.
Now where am I?
Woah, look at
all the books.
This is the kind of
stuff Naru would read...
but there's something
about this room
that feels lonely...
Like whoever lives here,
has been away for
a really long time.
This train pass
is expired.
This is Sakauchi's room.
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry I
couldn't help you.
Mai.
Mai!
Are you awake?
I don't feel so good.
Then don't sit up
so fast... dummy.
Gee thanks...
Just stay still, Mai.
Okay.
Hey.
Morning. G'day.
Hey guys...
So... where am I?
The nurses office.
Why were you wandering around
by yourself last night?
I had to get a videotape.
What?
Naru...
What were you thinking...?
How could you send
her on an errand
in such a volatile place?
Geez... can't even tell
if he's listening to me...
So, what happened Mai?
Hm... Let's see...
The spirits of children, eh?
Masako, can you tell
if they're still here?
They're gone...
I can't feel
their presence.
So uh...
Why didn't you use
that warding magic
like I taught you?
Oh... I totally forgot.
If you're not injured
then there's no need
for us to stay here...
We need to get
back to work...
Matsuzaki...
Keep an eye on her.
Sure thing.
If you're still
not feeling well
you can stay in bed
as long as you want.
Wait.
What is it?
Stay with me.
I'm not going anywhere.
That shrine looks important...
I wonder if this
is another dream...
Come on Mai,
of course it is.
Well, I guess I'd better
start paying attention
'cause it'll
probably come true.
Since this is
a dream then...
Yep, there he is.
It's dangerous out here.
What?
It's not safe here Mai...
Wake up...
Time to go.
Wake up...?
You mean not here
but the nurse's office...
That's not safe...?
That's a... foxfire
Yeah...
It appears to be
sleeping now...
You can see how it's been
feeding on the other souls
due to how large
it's grown...
It'll be hatching
any day now.
What?
Once it hatches,
I don't think we'll
be able to stop it.
There's a total of
four foxfires...
One of the foxfires...
is inside the
nurse's office...
See it?
What?
That's why you
need to wake up.
It's Yasu and John...
Oh no! Don't tell me they're
about to go in there...!
I've got to stop them.
I'll be right back okay!
Please...
Be careful.
What's wrong?
What are you doing,
jumping out of bed like that?
-Calm Down.
-Please Ayako...
Get to the printing
room on the first floor.
John and Yasu are
about to go in there.
One of those things
is waiting for them!
They're in danger!
Please, go.
I don't think I should
leave you alone.
I'll be fine...
Really, Monk taught me
some warding magic called,
the "Immovable One"
or something.
This is a bad idea...
Please Mai.
Okay...
Remember this one too.
Rin...
pyo...
Toh... Sha... Kai...
Jin... Retsu... Zai... Zen..
There's nine of them.
Horizontal first, right?
Yes... Recite them
after you've chanted
the Seal of the
Immovable One...
I'll be right back.
Man, I hope I
feel better soon.
Uh oh...! What did that
girl say happens here again?
On the second
to last bed...
there'll suddenly
be someone in it.
There it is.
Oh my god...!
It's okay, Mai.
Just stay calm and do
what they told you to.
Naumaku san manda
bazaradan kan.
Rin. Pyo. Toh. Sha...
Cold air...
The temperature's dropping.
Where'd it go...?
I think now's a
good time to leave.
Oh no.
Not again...
Why does this kind of
stuff only happen to me...?
Come on Mai.
I need to get out of here.
What the heck?
Where's the door?
Where am I?
What happened?!
The whole floor collapsed!
Is that a mouse?
It can't be.
There's no way
those are mice...
They're something else.
Oh no...
If those kids
come back again...
NO!
Mai!
Naru!
What the...
What happened here?
I don't know.
There was a loud sound and
everything started shaking,
and then the next thing
I knew I was down here.
NARU!
My back feels heavy...
I guess it would, since
the ceiling fell on me.
But why is it so warm?
Mai! Mai!
Can you hear me?
Are you alright?
Answer me!
We're fine.
Huh?
You know you two are lucky
you weren't seriously injured.
I'd expect you to be
more cautious, Naru.
The fact that you're walking
away with only scratches
is a miracle.
This school is in dire
need of major renovation...
The ceiling collapsed
because of weak beams...
It's no big deal.
We should probably take
you to a hospital,
just to be on the safe side.
Really, I'm just fine...
I'm pretty sure
Naru's back took
most of the brunt anyway.
Yeah... If Naru hadn't
protected me ...
Does anyone else think
this is weird...?
It would take an incredible
amount of power for a spirit
to make an entire ceiling
collapse like that.
So this spirit
is more powerful
than what you
usually encounter.
But what's more alarming
is its brutality.
It just hatched...
It's been asleep
up to this point...
After it finished
absorbing enough power,
it hatched like an egg.
If that dream I had
earlier was true...
then ...
Now... No one...
Will be able to stop it.
Go home?
Why?
Apparently they decided
it at their meeting.
But the investigation's
not over!
How can they
expect us to leave
when we haven't
finished our job?
I don't know.
The reason the situation
has become this bad
is because you and
your team of amateurs
have failed to do
what you promised.
Our hands are tied
on this one Mai,
If the client says go home,
you go home.
That's nuts...! Right?
Naru?
But... We're...
We're not done.
That horrible foxfire
I saw in my dream...
We can't just
leave it here.
Look we can't stop now...!
The remaining spirits will
just feed on each other.
They'll keep getting
bigger and more powerful,
until finally,
one gigantic and extremely
dangerous spirit will be left.
What did you just say?
Huh?
They'll feed on each other
until the strongest remains.
Yeah... that's right.
What's... wrong?
How can that be?
Is it possible
we're up against...
a kodoku using spirits?
What is that?
A zuzhou hex...
A curse that dates back
to ancient China...
It's been thought to be
extinct for years now.
Zuzhou normally use
hitogata, talismans
and other charms to curse,
but some can use
living creatures.
That, is a kodoku...
Usually an insect is used,
one known as a
'golden silkworm'...
but exactly what
type of bug that is
still remains a mystery.
Worms and centipedes are
also commonly used...
They take the bugs and
place them inside a pot,
and then bury the
pot in the earth...
Several months later
they dig it up...
What remains,
is a single bug that has
devoured the others.
The curse is performed
with this lone survivor.
The bug takes
possession of the house
owned by the person
being cursed,
and brings in an enormous
amount of wealth.
However, in return,
a human must be sacrificed
for the curse to continue.
If not, the bug will
devour the homeowner.
If one is unable
to feed the bug...
they must exchange all of the
wealth the bug has produced,
plus interest,
for gold and silver,
and leave it in the road.
It's called the golden
silkworm transfer.
But if it's lying
in the road,
then what's stopping someone
from just taking
it for themselves?
Whoever takes it
would see the money
but never really
know what they have.
And then they would
be eaten as well...
Man.
This same idea can also
be used as a death-curse.
You perform the
kodoku curse
and send the bug along
with some gold and silver
to someone you despise...
They don't understand
its meaning,
neglect to feed the bug...
And are devoured
in the process.
Hold on.
The bugs being put in the
pot and eating each other.
That's exactly what's
happening at this school!
That's why I believe
it's a kodoku curse.
So instead of
the usual bugs
we have spirits
eating each other.
If they continue doing this
without us stopping them,
and one powerful
spirit remains...
Then...
What will happen?
I'm not sure...
If someone is doing
this intentionally
in the hopes of
a death-curse...
the remaining spirit will be
used to implement the zuzhou.
But if this happened
purely by chance,
because the school sits in a
spiritually closed-off location,
then there's no telling
what could happen.
Then... if just one
spirit is remaining,
the school it has
taken possession of
will have to feed it,
just like the
homeowner does, right?
Like... the way they
feed a human to the bug.
Now hold on!
But that's how it works...
If it's not fed, then
the homeowner is eaten.
But it's different
in this case.
Who would the
homeowner be?
Yeah right.
Probably the students
that summoned the spirits.
What? Are you serious...?!
Can we do anything
to avoid that?
I mean... Nobody knew
the consequences
when they first started
Ouija-boarding...
If all the students
were eaten,
that would include Yasu too!
Right, Naru?
There's nothing I can do.
However...
Lin... Your thoughts?
Please Lin.
Kodoku is a
form of cursing
that's considered to be lost
among parapsychologists...
In my entire career
I've never even heard of
anyone coming across one.
If this kodoku was performed
as part of a zuzhou curse,
it'll behave the same
as any other zuzhou.
Breaking the curse would
not be too difficult,
but if this is somehow
the product of chance,
then there would be
only two distinct ways
to deal with the problem.
Transferring it
to someone...
or giving in and feeding it.
-Right.
-You can't!
We still don't know
if this is a kodoku.
If a zuzhou is being used,
Lin can take care of it...
but We should continue
with our investigation
Man... I really hope Naru
convinces the Principal
to let us stay.
If they boot
us out of here
then the case is
as good as lost...
But... Knowing Naru
he'll make it work.
Even though he told us
to keep investigating,
I'm not really
sure what to do.
Use your brain for once
Same applies to you...
Wait... I'm sorry I forgot.
You don't have a brain.
Hey Easy...! My cr1anium
can only take so much abuse!
Oh shut up! You don't even
know what cranium means!
Okay, that's enough.
Please, just get along.
Maybe we should
use this time
to organize the
information we have...
It's gotta be better
than this, right?
Yeah.
To start, orikirisama,
which is a form of
Ouija-boarding,
became popular here
at the school
around the end of summer
vacation last year.
Immediately following that,
the school became inundated with
stories of ghost sightings.
Because the school
happens to be
in a spiritually
closed-in location,
the spirits that were summoned
here were trapped here.
Those spirits began
feeding on each other,
creating a situation
common to a kodoku curse.
It's kind of like a
supernatural sumo match.
You know, the way
they do Orikirisama,
with the chant
and everything.
It's so different from
the times I played
with a Ouija board.
There are many different
styles of doing it,
depending on what
region you're in.
Yeah... but even the paper
they're using is weird.
It has the alphabet, numbers,
and the yes and no,
so everything is
normal up to that point.
But I thought in order
to be a Ouija board
you'd have to draw a torii
arch in the middle.
In this version, they have a
squiggly pattern there instead.
Plus... they've got the
character for Demon
encircling the whole thing.
What?
I'm sorry?
What kind of
pattern is it?
I'm not sure...
Oh...! Hey, Yasu...
Do you remember?
I only did it that one
time but I can try to.
You said it was
called orikirisama.
That comes from the
incantation used, right?
On orikiritei, meiritei,
meiwayashimarei, sowaka.
That's it!
And then after
you use the paper
you're supposed to
bury it somewhere.
Yeah, Exactly.
You can only use it once,
and when you're done with it,
you have to dispose of it
at a particular shrine.
A shrine.
There wouldn't happen to be a
shrine nearby, would there?
A little one, with a small
torii gateway and foxes.
It's right down the street.
That's crazy.
Just like in my dream.
This is where you
bury them, right?
It is ...
But what does that have
to do with the case?
Uh-oh, there's someone here.
We're not supposed to let
anyone see us do this right?
I don't believe this.
I told them not to
do that anymore.
Excuse me.
I need to look at
that piece of paper.
It's fine... You're not
in trouble or anything.
Oh... sure.
I knew it.
What Lin...? Is it bad?
To confound a crossroads...
to kill underneath a shrine.
What are you talking about...?
What's that mean?
This is a talisman.
When one of these is used
and then buried
underneath a shrine...
It curses a
person to death.
To... death?
A talisman?
Yes.
If it's buried at a crossroads,
it will confuse a person.
And if it's buried
under a shrine,
it's a death sentence.
Someone spread these
talismans around school,
falsely claiming they were
harmless Ouija boards.
Whoever's
participated in this
has aided in casting
a death curse.
No way!
We should consider
ourselves lucky
that the person behind
this was an amateur.
A professional like me
could easily kill someone
with one of these.
Judging from the evidence
we have thus far
it's obvious we're up
against a kodoku curse.
I agree.
What will happen once
the kodoku is complete?
The person whose name is written
on the talisman will die.
And who would that be?
Hideharu... Matsuyama.
[Music]
Next time on Ghost Hunt,
Forbidden Pastime Part Four!
How is this gonna end?!