I never imagined that
anything this terrible
could happen to Kazuya.
Masako... can you tell
what kind of spirit
is possessing him?
It's hard to see clearly...
he's possessed by something
but I don't know
what it is...
maybe what we're dealing with,
is some kind of hollow spirit.
What exactly
do you mean?
They are colorless and
completely transparent.
They don't
give off emotions,
yet, they do tend to have
a very strong presence...
It could also be that
something is interfering;
attempting to block
us from finding out
the spirit's identity.
She may be
irritating sometimes.
Right now... I know
exactly how she feels.
In any case
we have to find out the
spirit's identity and fast.
Even with all of us
working together...
there's not
much we can do
if we don't know
what we're up against.
[Music]
I'll play back the video
footage from last night.
Okay... that's
Hazuki's room.
And next to that?
The first floor hallway.
White lights!
There's more in
the hallway too.
Amazing.
I'll pull up the room
that faces the cove now.
Sure there are
a lot of them.
Anyone notice they all
seem to be rising up.?
Just like in my dream...
Is there any audio?
No. Nothing.
Not even any vibrations...
None of the gauges
seem to have picked up
anything unusual either...
Except... the temperature
has dropped five degrees.
Come in.
Hey! I brought you
guys some coffee...
sound good?
Thanks! You're
a life saver...
No problem.
Hey um... so over by
the edge of the cove...
I was wondering if you
knew of the cave there
that has an old
shrine inside it?
Also, do you know if there are
some old stone steps by the inn
that go all the way down
to the bottom of the cliff?
Oh no, you didn't go
down there did you!?
Uh! Well...
Not exactly.
Stay away from there...!
Those steps are old
and extremely dangerous!
Hey you two,
whats up...?
Nothing but uh...
it looks like I've
done it again...
I guess... these must be the
steps you saw in your dream?
As far as I know,
they've been here forever.
But they're falling apart so we
don't want to use them anymore.
But it doesn't look like you can
see the cave from this angle.
If we go over there to that
old tea house, you can.
From there, you can
see the whole cave...
It's quite a view.
That's exactly what
I saw in my dream!
So have you
guys seen enough
or would you like
to keep going?
Keep going.
Now there aren't
any fences over here,
so please, be careful.
You're not afraid
of heights are you?
C'mon we're not
that high up...
You kidding me?
I was wondering, sir ...
Oh, you dont have
to call me sir...
It's not like I'm running
the place or anything ...
I just wanted to
ask you something.
Those...
what are they?
I really don't
know for sure.
My grandfather always said
they were some kinda tombstones,
Then he told
all of us kids
that we should never
play around them ...
Oh I see.
What about those
ones...up there?
Oh yeah, those are
Okobu and Mekubo.
The big one
is the man, Okobu,
and the smaller one
is the woman, Mekubo...
According to
local legend,
a long time ago...a man and
a woman jumped into the sea
...and were turned
into these stones.
They jumped
into the sea?
Yeah.
The legend says there
was a beautiful princess
who fell madly in love
with a local fisherman
They would meet up secretly;
trying to spend as much time
as they could together...
But... as luck
would have it,
she caught the eye of
the son of a nobleman
who tried to force her
to marry him instead.!
The princess... wanted
nothing to do with him
so she agreed to
elope with her lover.
They wrote each other
letters to arrange a meeting
but the nobleman's son found
them and switched them up...
The meeting
never took place.
My dream.
When the princess
realized the mistake...
she hurried to find
her lover... but...
when she got there, he had
already killed his rival...
He left me no choice.
But why...?
There was nothing
I could do ...
he was waiting here
when I arrived ...
so, of course I thought
you had betrayed me ...
How could you think
that I would do that?!
It made sense...
what other reason
could there be for
him being here?
You're the only one who knew
where we were going to meet.
No, it's not like that...
the letters got mixed up.
I ended up in a completely
different place.
It was too late
to do anything.
The damage was
already done..
Knowing there was no way out,
the lovers threw themselves..
from this cave to die
together in the sea..
Then that means...
I think of Naru as...
Oh... how embarrassing!
The gods took pity on them and
transformed the young lovers
into stones so that
they'd always be together.
At least that's how
the legend goes anyway...
Uh is there
something wrong?
Uh! Oh... no...
nothing at all.
That's it...!
That's why in the dream,
I thought we were supposed
to be going
to the sea.
So uh...is there
a shrine nearby?
Yes there is...
In fact, I can show it
to you if you want ...
Is this the one?
Uhuh this is the one,
just like in my dream.
Oh, wow... this is
a really nice shrine...
You guys keep
it very clean.
You think so...?
It's on the small side and
it doesn't even have a priest.
My family has been taking care
of it for generations...
we just kinda took it upon
ourselves to keep it clean.
Actually my parents made me
do most of the cleaning.
Oh yeah...
and I know that's really hard
work for a kid, isn't it...?
My parents ran a temple
when I was little,
and I had to clean it...
in the winter, that water
can get pretty cold
It sure can.
I bet your parents ran
a shrine too huh...
so did you have to do all
the cleaning there as well?
Oh no...
My parents never
owned a shrine.
Huh...?
They didn't?
My parents are doctors.
What?! They're doctors?!
So are you telling me
that you grew up rich?
I guess so...
They actually owned the
hospital that they ran.
So yeah I guess you
could call us rich.
Also, I was an only child so my
parents tended to spoil me a bit
not only that but we had several
housekeepers to do all the work.
so I never lifted a finger
to help out with anything.
Well, that certainly
explains a lot.
These stones here...
what are they for...?
Oh! Those are
the sanroku mounds.
Sanroku mounds?
It means "three six mounds,"
but I don't know why...
maybe it's because
there are three here
and six over
by the cape.
Wait ... at the cape
there were only five.
Right ... they said
there used to be six
but one of them
fell into the sea.
So around here... we
still refer to them
as the six stones
at the cape.
So three here... and six at the
cape make up the sanroku mounds.
When you say mounds
you mean gravestones...
Do you think
that perhaps,
the missing mound might
have something to do
with all the problems
your family's been having?
Oh Of course!
See, the mounds...
are the foxes' graves!
It all makes sense!
You mean like the fox
spirit that possessed
Eijiro and... Naru?
That's right...! When
they built the inn...
they must've destroyed a
fox's grave and that's how,
the curse began!
Okay. Slow down.
Heh ... you know Naru
will tell that you anyway.
What do you think Masako?
I'm sorry but I didn't sense
any presence of animals
at the inn
or the mounds...
of course spirits
will lie sometimes...
many times they will
take the form of animals
so that they can better disguise
themselves from humans.
So do you think our fox
was just a disguise?
Perhaps.
Get anything else?
I feel the presence
of many spirits.
I'm not entirely sure
about what they are...
But I believe they're some
type of drifting spirits...
It's odd...
I'm getting mixed
signals from this place.
It doesn't feel good but
it doesn't feel bad either.
This doesn't look
like a bad place.
Or a good place
for that matter.
Almost like ... some
kind of sacred ground.
I once visited a sacred
Native American site.
I'm getting the same
impression here
that I got there.
That it's a holy place
guarded by spirits.
A spirit passage?
So Did Naru tell you
that in the dream too?
Spirits drift
into this place...
maybe it's an area that they
can't resist being drawn to.
Well, Mai if what
you're saying is true...
It kinda makes sense, because
supposedly back in the old days
the bodies of people who died at
sea were drawn to this shore...
that's the reason they
built this shrine here...
and, more recently, it's
where our dogs drifted ashore.
Okay then...
that settles it.
Looks like we're gonna have
to check out that cave now.
I see... so there's a way to
get in from the shore side too.
Yeah this way is a whole lot
safer than those old stairs.
Well I guess we should
go in and take a look.
Is that the shrine?
Uhuh...
Except that, in my dream
it looked really warped.
Masako... You getting anything?
Yes, quite a bit.
It's just like the
Native American sites.
There are spirits drifting
in even as we speak.
Akifumi...
Do you have any idea
what this thing in here is?
Ah, I see...
you've found Okobu.
Okobu...? You mean
as in Okobu and Mekubu?
Right, but instead of a rock,
this is a piece of driftwood.
It's a head
and a hand.
-Sort of like a person.
-Oh! A yebisu...
My parents' temple had
some in similar poses.
Yeah...
They keep this yebisu enshrined
here as a token of big fortune.
So that's Okobu.
The tide doesn't
come in too far...
I guess this will
be okay right here.
I'm surprised... but,
it looks like
the cables will actually
reach down here.
So I guess we will
be able to get
some footage in
here after all.
What's a yebisu?
Basically... it just
means something
that is washed up
on the shore.
Whenever anything unusual
from the sea washed up,
it was considered to be
a sign of good luck.
In Buddhism, it's said that
there's a grand paradise
far to the west...
called Saiho Jodo.
Also, according to ancient
Japanese mythology,
there is a land of eternal
youth that lies somewhere
far beyond the seas.
So they believed that anything
that came from the sea,
had some sort
of special powers.
That's a yebisu.
So then, the Okobu
inside the cave...
That's right, it must be
a yebisu as well...
It probably washed
up on the beach...
And when they noticed it
looked like a statue of Buddha,
they enshrined it.
Yebisu...
something from the sea.
This is a place that
souls drift into.
The cave.
The sacred ground.
The shrine...
and the mounds.
The rocks and the legend of
two lovers who threw themselves
into the sea...
I never heard the legend
until Akifumi told us...
and yet... it was
all in the dream.
All I did was simply
show you the path
to guide you to this point.
If Naru was guiding me, then
there must have been something
about the legend
he wanted me to know.
It must have something
to do with this case...
But in my dream, we
didn't go to the sea.
We went to the shrine, where we
were surrounded by an angry mob.
Even then I was wondering
why we didn't go to the sea.
I knew we belonged there.
And then Eijiro appeared
carrying a katana.
I shall curse you
from beyond the grave!
You will not escape me!
-What's the matter?
-Something terrible's happened!
It's... it's my brother!
Oh my god!
-Akifumi! Call an ambulance!
-I already did!
Get that side!
Come on man
stay with us!
Oh miss?
Oh... hi kids!
Is Uncle Yashi dead?
Well... is he?
Is he dead yet?
What's wrong
with these kids...
Don't worry. There's
an ambulance
on its way here right now.
I guess he's
still alive.
Oh well...
Ever since
grandfather's funeral,
I've been hearing these
voices telling me to...
telling me to
kill the family.
It gets worse...
because every night
I've been killing you
all in my dreams...
Katsuki, Hazuki, Wakako.
All of you.
And then I realized that
if it kept going like this,
I was really going
to do it some day.
He said, he planned to
take his own life in hopes
of preventing that from
happening to the rest of us.
And if we had gotten
there any later,
he would have really
done it too...
this is all our fault.
I'm sorry that we haven't
been able to figure this out.
Oh no... If we had never hired
you guys in the first place...
then your boss, wouldn't be
in the condition he's in now.
Lin, you left your shiki
around Naru, right?
That's right.
Would you know if any
spirits came near him?
Yes I would.
Well... how about if a spirit
left him, would you know that?
Without a doubt, but there
isn't a spirit that exists
that can leave him as long
as that spell is intact...
So... what does that mean?
It means there's more than
one spirit in this house,
doesn't it?
So you think... that
Yashitaka was possessed
by a different spirit?
That's the only
answer I can see.
In that case, we should
definitely check out
the rest of the
family and fast.
She clear?
I do sense the
presence of a spirit,
but it's the same
as with Naru...
It is the same
hollow feeling.
I don't detect a great
deal of bitterness,
or any kind of grudge...
But then... I can't
rule out the possibility
she may be possessed
by an evil spirit...
-John?
-Yeah... what is it?
Do an exorcism on her...
then do one on Yashitaka
at the hospital
just in case, okay?
Okay, I'm on it.
In the beginning...
there was the word.
-I'm scared.
-Don't worry, it'll be okay.
And the Word, it was
God... what's wrong?
I'm sorry...I can't
watch this anymore.
Ayako, make us some charms,
we'll need enough for us...
and the entire family,
as quickly as you can.
Okay.
I'm going to be
out for a bit...
-Akifumi?
-Uh yes sir?
Could you do me a favor and take
me back to your family's temple?
No thank you.
You sure...?
See, this is a charm that will
keep the evil spirits
away from you... but...
it doesn't work unless,
you keep it somewhere
on your person.
I see ... but what happens
if I decide to take a bath?
I can't take it with me,
can I? It's just paper.
Well, yeah that's true but...
Then I guess ...
I'll be passing.
-Thanks.
-Hold on a second. Yoko...!
-I don't want it!
-Hey, wait up!
C'mon...! They're important!
We don't want 'em!
Why are they being
so stubborn about this?
Oh no...
Hey Wakako! Did you know
that your uncle died...?
-Really?
-Wonderful!
My god ...
I knew it!
Afraid so...and
so did Akifumi.
Wow! Uncle Aki died too?
Did he drive his car?
Alright! What did
you do to his car?
-Stop it!
-Let go of me!
Mai, what's going on?
Get back here!
You let her
go right now!
Not until you tell me
what you did to his car!
Let go!
Ayako...! Make Wakako
hold this charm okay?
Stop it! You leave
her alone...! now!
Not until you tell me
about the car...!
otherwise, I'm going to stick
this charm on Wakako so hard!
It'll never come off!
If you do, then I'll
jump into the sea...
How does that sound
to you, miss...?
Listen to me...!
Do you even have the slightest
idea what you're talking about?
Well, if I die...
That'll show 'em.
And just who
will it show, huh?
Them all.
I was right... the
spirits have him too.
And it's not hollow
like Masako said...
this one is definitely
holding a grudge...
Alright! Tell me
who you really are!
You're not Katsuki... are you?
I'm going to
kill you miss.
Not just you ... everyone in
this house is going to die...
including this
little boy ...
Of course, drowning in
the sea would be merciful,
not nearly as bad...
as someone chopping off
your head, don't you think?
Chopping off your head?
Or having...the people you
love betray your trust ...
So tell me...! Did they
chase you to the shrine
and then kill you
there in cold blood?
Did the people of this
house do it to you...?
Is that why
you hate them?
Maybe...
Come out of that
boy right now!
Don't worry, I'll
leave when he dies.
By then, I should
be done with him!
No wait...!
Dharmic power
is very risky.
When you try to touch
someone directly with it,
anything can happen.
I've gotta
stop him.!
I was trying to drive a
spirit out of an urn...
I managed to get
the spirit out...
but the urn was
completely shattered.
Monk is a real
spiritualist...
I'm not as powerful.
Rin! Pyo! Toh! Sha!
Kai! Jin!
Retsu! Zai! Zen!
What was that...?
Oh Katsuki!
I can't believe this!
After I told you how
dangerous it was!
-But he...
-No buts!
Look, I know you have great
talent but just be careful.
You should avoid using
the nine cuts on anyone
no matter what
the circumstance is.
I know and
I'm sorry.
Well anyway...we checked
on the car and found out
that it was leaking
brake fluid pretty badly.
If someone had tried
to take it anywhere,
without knowing about it...
they would have been
in serious trouble..
Do you think...
the kids did it?
We can't be sure...
I mean ... even if the
kids were possessed...
it just doesn't
seem possible...
All right! I wanna know which
one of you hurt the children?!
And who made them carry
those horrible things?!
What do you mean?
I'm talking about those
useless charms you gave them.
I demand that you take
those away from them!
I'm afraid that we haven't
solved anything in this case.
All we have done...
is served as a trigger.
We've managed to
set the spirits off,
and made them more
violent than ever.
And now...
[Music]
Next time on
Ghost Hunt,
"The Cursed House"
Part Three.
Looks like things
are getting worse!