My name is Mai Taniyama,
and I'm a freshman
in high school...
Another mysterious case
was brought to
Shibuya Psychic Research.
A girl believed that her
friend was possessed by a fox,
and a teacher
collapsed after claiming
he could see ghosts.
After the principal
visited us
we agreed to investigate the
events at Yuasa High School.
When we got there weird
things kept happening,
and the stories got
stranger and scarier.
What in the world
is going on here?
We did discover
an incident
about three
months earlier...
a girl named Kasai was
publicly ridiculed by teachers
for saying she
could bend spoons
using supernatural powers.
And then...
I'll curse you to death!
Not long After that,
the unexplainable and dangerous
occurrences started happening.
And poor Miss Kei
was treated horribly
by the other teachers
just because she had
the nerve to defend me!
I don't understand why
this is happening to me...
I have a really bad
feeling about all of this.
Underneath all of these
strange and mysterious events,
I sense a
creeping darkness
that's growing
stronger every day.
[Music]
On sunba nisunba
un bazaar un hatta,
jaku un ban koku,
on dakini shara
kyara heigi yaya.
Drive them out
and purify.
I entreat you
in serenity...
please receive
this humble prayer
and grant my fervent wish.
Our holy Father who
art in heaven...
Hallowed be thy name.
Nothing out of
the ordinary.
No remarkable temperature
changes to report either.
Of course not.
Because there are no
spirits in this building.
There are still unexplained
events happening here...
it is imperative
keep investigating
until we determine
their cause...
Fine.
But no matter
how hard you look
you won't find spirits.
So many foxfires,
burning all over
the building...
was it a dream?
Or could it be...
Wake up Mai!
That was so weird...
I've got a really bad
feeling about this.
I hope everyone can do
their exorcisms fast
so we can get out of here.
Kasai?
Uh, wait a second!
Kasai!
Yeah?
Um, well, can I help
you with anything?
No thanks.
Oh.
Are all those other
people friends of yours?
Huh?
It looks like they're trying
to do some sort of exorcism.
Oh... them, yeah
Monk, Ayako and John are
my friends I guess...
but actually they're
more like my coworkers.
And Masako Hara?
Ohh...
of course you'd
know who she is.
I keep forgetting that Masako
is actually kinda famous.
Yeah, I saw her on tv.
What has she said
about this school?
That there are a lot of
evil spirits hanging around?
Uh-uh, actually she doesn't
think that there are any.
Aren't any...?
Even with all of the
stuff happening here?
It was hard for me
to believe, too...
but she swears she
doesn't see them here.
So what about you?
Are you able to see them?
Oh, no no no no
no no no, not me,
I'm not a spiritualist.
I've never been
able to do that.
What about Mr. Shibuya?
He's a spiritualist, right?
Oh, Nar...
I mean Mr. Shibuya isn't really
a spiritualist per se...
he's more of a
Ghost Hunter...
And I think he may be
an onmyouji as well.
Is he really...?!
So that would mean he
does practice onmyodo...
Naru!
See ya later?
I thought there was something
fishy about that girl.
You're saying she came in here
to check us all out, right?
Maybe she wasn't
checking us out,
maybe she was just
curious or something.
Well, Kasai is aware that
the whole school thinks
her curse is the cause
of all of this...
maybe she thinks
we believe it too
and we're her latest
enemy, y'know?
She wouldn't do that!
Still... she does have powers...
According to a number
of her schoolmates,
she was apparently able to
bend spoons with her mind...
do you think it's possible
she also possesses PK-LT?
What's PK-LT?
I'll explain it
for Mai's sake.
PK-LT is the power to
affect living creatures
using only a
force of will...
the two major divisions
of supernatural ability
are PK and ESP...
or extra-sensory
perception.
This is a special
ability to know things
that normal people
wouldn't sense...
Telepathy and clairvoyance
are in this category.
PK, however, is a
force of will...
moving objects by literally
thinking them into action...
The three categories
are PK-MT...
PK-ST...
and last but
not least PK-LT.
PK-ST is the power to
affect static targets...
spoon-bending
would fall here.
PK-MT is the power to
affect moving targets.
And PK-LT, as I've said,
is the power to
affect living targets.
So, what makes
you think Kasai
is capable of
doing such a thing?
If you can't see
the connection
after everything I've said
then I can't help you.
I'm sorry I'm so
stupid, your highness!
Are we in agreement
then that Kasai really did
invoke a curse on the school?
A curse?!
She admitted it.
She said "I'll
curse you to death!"
Oh, right.
But it's not
really a curse.
It's more like using
psychic powers
to make people suffer...
that's the PK-LT part...
But judging from what I've
heard from a number of students
I don't think the girl
has that much power.
Do you guys
know about the
famous British psychic
Oliver Davis?
They say he can slam an l
aluminum block into the wall...
But he hasn't been
able to perform PK-LT.
This girl can't even seem
to bend spoons very well.
I remember when
I was little
there was sort of a
supernatural craze,
where tons of kids claimed
they could bend spoons
and perform magic...
Of course It turned out
that most of them
were just lying.
Wow... that means you
must be pretty old.
Be that as it may...
It's very important to
remember that in Kasai's case
she truly believed
in her psychic powers.
She felt that she was unfairly
attacked and ridiculed
by her teachers in front
of the entire school...
And then...
I'll curse you to death!
Strange things began happening
after she said that.
Those are the facts...
and we can't ignore them.
Something awful
has happened!
Mr. oshino was in
a bad car accident
and now he's in
the hospital!
I... I was driving...
And there it was,
right in front of me...
It's because of her...
that girl...
it's Chiaki Kasai...
When I was
leaving school...
she ran into me...
and she gave me the most
evil look I've ever seen!
Oh my God she
cursed me...!
She cursed me to die and now
it's really happening...
What do you think, Naru?
Was it Kasai?
I'm really not sure ...
but we can safely say
that things seem to
be getting worse.
Let's hurry back...
we've got a lot to do
and no time to waste.
What's wrong?
I don't know...
I just felt scared
all of a sudden.
C'mon, Kasai, admit it!
Why don't you just stop!
Yeah, stop using your
psychic powers or whatever...
what're you trying to do,
scare everyone to death?!
No... You're wrong.
You know, if poor
Mr. oshino had died
you'd totally be
guilty of murder!
Hey, maybe we
should lay off...
if we say too much
she could freak out
and decide to
curse us next!
What are you girls doing?
Kasai?
Kasai?!
There they go again.
It's kinda sick.
I don't understand
how Miss Ubusuna
can stick up for
her like that.
Don't pay any
attention to them.
It's not your fault.
You've done nothing wrong.
On sunba nisunba
un bazaar un hatta.
The Word was made
flesh and was life...
And that life was
the light of man.
Naumaku san manda
botan on dakini.
Praise be given as the gods
from all corners come together.
On dakini shara
kyara heigi yaya ...
The Word was made
flesh and was life...
Naumaku san manda
bazarandan kan!
Man, they've got their
hands full with this one.
They exorcized the track
team's locker room,
as well as that desk,
so they've hit every place
related to the incidents.
But still I...
I wonder if...
I mean I hope nothing's...
gonna pop out in
this room, too.
Naru!
Oh, how about I
make some tea?
Fine.
Hey, Naru?
I have a question
about Kasai...
I don't know yet.
Okay!
It's just that there's
something bothering me.
What's that?
Did you see it?
Aww, I hope it's
not a power outage.
Quiet.
Now don't make any
sudden movements...
Just stay calm.
It's coming toward us...
I'm so scared,
oh somebody please help!
Naumaku san manda
bazarandan kan!
Ah, so the spirits
have started
showing their faces
in here, too, huh.
Apparently.
Hey, are you alright, Mai?
That woman never looked
at me, not once...
she only looked at Naru!
Mai, snap out of it.
That spirit was
looking for Naru!
Naru?
That woman just now...
It wasn't a coincidence,
I know she came for him.
I had a dream last night...
and I saw foxfires
all over the school...
That thing we just
saw was one of them!
I can't tell you
how I know that,
but I'm positive I'm right...
and that woman's
eyes, those evil,
bloodthirsty eyes...
She was looking
straight at Naru!
What's the matter?
Your eyes are all red.
Our friend came
back to visit me.
Wait a second,
do you mean...
Turns out your
instinct was right...
She appeared at my
window last evening
I thought something worse might
happen if I looked away,
so we spent the entire
night staring at each other.
Why the hell
didn't you call me?!
Because I wanted to see
what would happen...
and I thought
it would be rude
to wake you up for nothing.
And what would you have done
if something bad had happened?
Well, obviously, if it
had I would have called...
but we just had a little
staring contest...
so stop worrying.
Then there's no way
it could be Kasai
I mean, for her to
cast a such big curse,
she'd have to have a lot
of that PK-whatever power,
wouldn't she?
It's PK-LT...
But you are right, if she
wanted to be able to affect
so many people
with this curse,
she would need to have
quite a lot of that power.
When we met her
the first time
she wasn't even able
to bend that spoon...
That's right...
And spirits appeared
to all of the victims
in every single incident
The Kasai theory
definitively doesn't account
for these apparitions.
Well, maybe she's
just off making
effigy dolls or something.
You mean she makes dolls
night after night
so she can go around
cursing everyone?!
I guess that's not
an impossible theory.
But whenever you use
straw effigy dolls
isn't it only supposed
to only hurt the person
where the nail is driven in?
She's right, and dolls
do not summon spirits.
Course not...
Moreover, they don't
possess the power
to have caused
repeated hauntings.
-Lin!
-Yes...
it's possible
that's the answer.
C'mon, fill us in.
I can't believe I didn't
think of it sooner...
Were dealing
with a zuzhou.
A zuzhou?!
There's an extremely powerful
hex at work in this school
to that's calling
down curses on people.
Are you serious?!
Okay, but what's
the connection
between the zuzhou
and these spirits?
This hex ,originally
derived from the Yin-yan Tao,
is cast by driving a
nail into a hitogata,
or straw effigy doll...
I'll explain this
so Mai can catch up.
In the Yin-yan Tao
there's a certain
method of cursing people
referred to as enmi.
It's a hex that uses
either a hitogata
or a possession of
the one being cursed,
and driving a nail into
the straw effigy doll
is one of the enmi arts.
The doll's function is to simply
convey the level of hatred
of the person
driving the nail...
the dolls themselves
can do no real harm.
But when the hexer, the
one performing the curse,
drives the nail
into the hitogata,
they call upon gods or spirits
to deliver a deathcurse.
Deathcurse?
The gods or spirits
accept the task,
and carry the curse to
the unlucky subject.
In other words,
the hexer actually contracts
these gods, spirits
and even demons
by performing the enmi arts.
So you're saying that
the cursed desk...
the hand that
attacked Mr. oshino...
And that woman that came
down from the ceiling...
Were all evil
spirits with curses?
Someone has cast multiple
enmi spells against people
at this school
and evil spirits are
appearing to those
who have been cursed.
The spirits aren't
powerful enough
to kill their targets
immediately
so they torment and lead
them to their deaths.
It's a very indirect
form of murder.
And if these attacks were
to happen frequently,
as they have at Yuasa...
It would definitely have a
negative effect on those people
who are easily influenced.
Yes... an extreme
example would be the girl
who believed she was
possessed by a fox.
This explains both the
incidents themselves
and why the entire school was
thrown into such a panic.
So who performed
the curses?
All the evidence
would seem to suggest
the hexer is Kasai.
Wait, hold on...
It has to be Kasai.
-You think so, too??
-Well, yeah...
look her abilities
were rejected
and in turn she was
made fun of and attacked
in front of the
whole school, right?
And even her teacher friend
has been put through
hell because of it.
There they go again.
It's kind of sick.
I don't understand
how Miss Ubusuna can stick
up for her like that.
They pushed
Kasai to the edge
so she called down a
deathcurse on them...
she's just making
good on her threat.
But it's not true!
Then explain why Mr. oshino,
who personally challenged
and laughed at her
in front of the entire school,
is now in the hospital?
I dunno, but...
What reason do you
have for believing
that she's not to blame?
I'm not sure but...
I do.
Yeah... it isn't
something I can explain,
I just know deep inside
that Kasai isn't the
person we're looking for.
She's not the one...
I know it!
Alright... I believe you.
You do?!
That's great but
someone could still die
if we don't hurry.
We have to act...
we can't leave the
zuzhou out there...
I'd like you all to
search for the hitogata...
Lin and I will go
looking for the culprit.
Uh, we're looking
for dolls?!
There are two ways to
break an enmi spell...
Turn the curse
back on the hexer
or burn the hitogata
being used.
The doll is usually
buried near the target...
That means if the
hexer is a student
or school faculty member,
it's most likely
around here somewhere.
'Somewhere'?!
Oh great, that
helps a lot...
what do you want us to do,
dig up the whole school?!
Well, the hexer
must have buried
my hitogata sometime
after Monday
when we started
investigating.
So that one should still
be fresh and easier to spot.
I guess but, c'mon
this school is huge!
Perhaps you'd
like to leave.
Alright!
Wait a minute, Naru...!you
can't just go in there,
the class is in
session right now!
Don't...
I guess they must've
switched rooms or something.
Naru, you really
shouldn't do that either!
Here it is.
That's the hitogata?!
They did a good
job on it...
But It doesn't seem to be made
for anyone specifically...
it's only intention
was to curse
whoever sat at this desk.
I think you're right.
The hitogata caused
whoever sat here to
have an accident...
Meaning the hurt students
weren't specifically targeted
so much as they
were just unlucky.
I bet we'll find another one
in the track
team's locker room
that's aimed at the
entire club...
rather than at
a single person.
hm, the floor
is concrete...
they're usually buried,
aren't they?
Usually Yes, but it's
quite possible
they've been hidden
in the ceiling.
I found it!
Good work, Mai.
Oh, no prob!
This one is
enmi as well...
A cursed desk and
the track team...
if we dig a little deeper
we're sure to find
the culprit soon.
Its Masako!
NO!
[Music]
Next time on Ghost Hunt,
'The After-School Hexer'
Part Three.
Is it just me
or is school more
dangerous these days?