Tell us what
it felt like.
It was like my arm was being
yanked around by the marker...
I honestly felt
that if I let go...
it would just fly
off on its own.
Hey boss... you sure do
seem incredibly calm.
Well, that's just because
I have nerves of steel.
Stop.
Rewind it to around
fifty-three seconds
and go frame by frame.
There wasn't anything on
it until it hit the floor.
Masako...
I'm sorry...
I don't feel very well...
Let's go to our room.
Miss Matsuzaki, would
you please go with them?
We should be okay
by ourselves.
No way!
Oh... Alright then.
Wow...
Naru's more
jumpy than usual.
[Music]
You smelled blood?
Yes, it was like my clothes
were all soaked with it...
the smell was so strong
I thought I was
going to be sick.
The same thing happened
after we first got here, right?
Yes, but this time
it got much worse
after all of those
rapping noises began.
Do you think it could be a
scent from the spirit...?
Like at Rokuryo
High School,
remember, there
was the classroom
that had that
horrible smell.
-What do you think, Mai...?
-Huh?
Are, you sensing
any spirits?
Well... I don't
know what you mean...
why would you be asking
me something like that?
Because during that
last case we were on,
it seems that you were
the only other person
who saw the same
apparition that I did.
What apparition...?
Oh... you mean Sakauchi?
Yeah, that was crazy...
I haven't been having any
of those dreams, though.
Well... you two seem
to be getting along.
You must be joking...
Clearly, someone like
me doesn't associate
with someone
like this.
Hey, what is that
supposed to mean?
Just how you are...
I didn't say
it's a bad thing.
You are an
awful person!
Maybe, but at
least I'm pretty
and unbelievably talented.
You're one of the meanest
girls I've ever known...
why do you hate me? !
You know, I'm
really not sure...
I guess it's just
because you're breathing.
I'll breathe on
you ya creep!
Oh... that's great, you
guys are really on your way
to being best friends.
Oh no, I'll never
be friends with her!
Hey, good morning, Lin!
Good morning, hello,
how are you today?
Are you absolutely sure none
of you have seen Suzuki?
What's the matter?
It seems that Suzuki
has gone missing.
Please... try to
calm down Ms. Igarashi.
When did you
last see her?
This morning...
I woke up once...
it was around
daybreak I think...
and Suzuki was
sleeping, right there.
Do you know what
time it was?
When did you get
up this morning?
Seven o'clock.
Okay, it's ten
o'clock now...
so we can say that
she's been missing
for the past three
hours at least.
Sorry to keep
you waiting.
I questioned the staff to
see if anyone might have
seen her sometime last
night or early this morning
but so far no
there's no news.
I just recently checked
the front door myself
and it was still
locked, so...
So we can probably assume
that she didn't go outside.
Oh no, Suzuki has
very bad eyesight...
I know for a fact she
wouldn't have gone anywhere
without her contacts.
Wait a sec...!
What if we asked Dr. Davis
to help us find her...
I mean, he was able to find
that billionaire's son
by using his
clairvoyance right?
Is that true?
Ms Igarashi, I just
heard what happened...
how terrible for
Miss Suzuki...
We'd be happy to help
in any way we can.
Oh, Thank you...
if I may...
I'd like to ask Dr. Davis
to attempt psychometry.
Maybe he can find her.
Perhaps he could use
this contact lens case
that she left behind...
if the doctor would at least
try I would be very grateful.
Of course yes...
I will ask him.
Dr. Davis...
I'm afraid he is unable
to see with this item.
But... why not?
Yeah, it's something that
belonged to her, right?!
The doctor is limited...
he can only utilize an object
that was with the person
at the time they
went missing.
Oh no...
So we should look around
to find something
she dropped since
this morning? !
This isn't my fault
little miss...
I unfortunately don't
make the rules...
Has anyone considered
that the séance yesterday
traumatized the girl and
she simply went home...?
Young people these days
just don't seem to have
-much staying power.
-What? !
That could be
a possibility...
I'll try calling
Suzuki at home...
Thanks so much.
Ms. Igarashi...
The rest of us will divide
up and help search for her.
Now let's see if Mr. Ohashi
can show you to the telephone.
Thank you.
But...
Suzuki hadn't
just gone home.
She could be
anywhere in here...
I mean, this house is
so gigantic and weird
that I can't help thinking
there are a bunch of places
we don't know about.
Well, a floor plan will go a
long way toward helping us out
so you guys
keep at it.
If it's so important
then why am I not
hearing you offer to grab a
tape measure and help out?
Because I'm exhausted
from walking around
this screwed up place
trying to sense spirits,
that's why...
Right, Masako?
Yes...
Although I have to say
you do tend to whine
and complain about it
a lot more than I do.
Oh shut it, you know
you're tired too!
So do you think she could
have been taken away somewhere?
By who?
I dunno...
maybe by a spirit who
believed that Suzuki
could help them
or something.
I hear ya...
she was the person who
actually experienced
the spirits
calling for help.
Or maybe...
She actually faked
everyone out
and wrote those
words on her own,
then ran off
because she was afraid
of being found out?
But what about the
one written in blood
and all the
knocking sounds?
Oh... yeah.
Hey you guys, the floor
seems to sink down here.
-A door?
-But...
Where's it go...?
There's one way
to find out.
What is this?
You found a
hidden space?
Yep!
And we ran across this while
we were checking it out.
Look at the tag, Naru.
"Miyama Charity
Hospital"...
the one that was founded by
the first head of the family.
That would mean
this lab coat
was in fact issued
by the hospital.
So... what would
that be doing here?
Hidden in a secret room?
I see something ...
Wow... that money sure
looks really old...
and I think I can see some
kind of writing on it.
Well Mai, what
does it say?
Yo... ge... ku... ki...
ta... sa... ni... ura...
ru... kyo... shi... mina...
ha... rai... sho?
What the hell
is that?
It doesn't make
any sense.
It's so dirty...
I can't read it all.
Why do you think someone
would write on money?
Maybe whoever it was didn't
have anything else to write on.
Let's keep
investigating...
But whatever you do...
make sure you always
stay together.
Well, here I am,
having to stay here
and keep watch with Lin...
He's been in such a lousy
mood since yesterday...
He hasn't said two words
to me this whole time.
I'm... gonna get some tea...
Do you want
any, Lin?
No, thank you.
Oh... okay...
So what do you think
happened to Suzuki?
Okay, why aren't you
talking to me, Lin...?
I really didn't mean to do
anything to offend you...
I was just surprised
that you were Chinese,
and I guess I must've said
it wrong or something.
Because I think
you're great,
and the last thing in the
world I'd ever want to do
is hurt your feelings.
I'm fine, I just...
I hate the Japanese.
Do you know about what
has happened historically
and what they did
to my country...?
You should pick up a book.
Not to be rude but I'm
not interested
in befriending Japanese...
especially those who
don't know their history.
My heart is
pounding so hard...
I don't know
what to do...
I usually feel this
way when I'm angry...
but this is different...
I feel... sad.
It's not like I'm
stupid about it.
I know Japan did some
terrible things...
but hating people now for
what happened then...
I dunno but it just
seems really wrong.
Just think, if everyone did
that then the whole world
would have to hate
each other forever
and it would
be so awful...
we're gonna have to learn
to forgive each other.
I can understand if
you don't like me
because I'm annoying
or something,
but I really wish
you wouldn't hate me
just because
I'm Japanese.
Uh... did I say
something funny?
Sorry, there was someone else
who said the same thing to me
a long time ago...
you just made me
remember that.
Oh... was it Naru?
Oh no...
When I told Naru
I'm pretty sure
his exact words were,
"That's stupid".
That sounds... like him.
I don't hate you,
Mai, and I'm sorry
for making you
think that I did...
it's just that my heritage
is very important to me
and I can't just get
rid of my feelings...
So...will you forgive me for
saying such hateful things?
Absolutely,
forgive me, too.
Hey, welcome
back guys!
Did you find anything?
What's that?
It's a ghost!
Hi, everyone!
Madoka, why in the world
did you show up here?
I wanted to tell
you what turned up
in my investigation.
But you know that it's
extremely dangerous here...
What if something
had happened to you?
I guess you'd have come
to rescue me, right?
I can't believe Naru's
actually taking that.
Okay, let's
start with Suzuki,
the girl you called me
about this morning...
I questioned all of the
bus and taxi companies
that operate in the area
and none of their drivers said
they saw or picked up any
woman fitting her description.
Moving on to the disappearances,
two months ago...
the first; was a boy who
apparently was here partying
with several friends.
They reported that
he staggered
out of the room at one
point and never came back.
A week later, an official
search was ordered.
The police came out
to comb the property,
and that's when a
twenty-one year old man
from the fire
brigade disappeared.
And as for the Miyamas...
well, I'll begin with
Kaneyuki Miyama...
The man was meticulous.
Listen to this... an
employee at his silk mill
had been embezzling
money from other workers
and was understandably fired.
But Kaneyuki also fired
the man's oldest son,
who worked in the mill,
as well as three other sons
who were on staff
at the hospital.
The house that they
all lived in,
as well as that of his
daughter and son-in-law,
were actually rented
to them by Kaneyuki,
and they were all evicted
from those properties.
-He threw them out?
-Uh-huh.
Apparently even the
embezzler's parents
were employed by Kaneyuki
on the grounds here
and he told them
to clear out, too.
Jeez, talk about
thorough...
Yeah...
It seems the man became
sort of famous for it.
Anyway, he wasn't a
very sociable guy
and always insisted
on hiring his maids
from outside of the area...
he was very adamant
about keeping people
away from this house...
Over time, the locals
began to suspect
something fishy must
be happening here.
His son, Hiroyuki, tried
to keep people away too,
and was known to say some
pretty strange things.
What kind of things?
Whenever anyone
would ask him
why he was constantly
adding on to the house,
the answer he
always gave was...
There are ghosts in there...!
I'm doing it to shut
the ghosts inside...
and keep them
from getting out!
Keep them from
getting out?!
You'll find everyone's
personal histories in here
nice and neat...
can I do anything
else for you?
Yes, I'd like you to investigate
Miyama Charity Hosptial.
You got it.
Bye!
I'm sorry I wasn't any
help to you this morning.
Oh please, that's all right, I
should have never been so rude.
I just hope we can find
Suzuki as soon as possible...
Goodnight, then.
Atsugi seems like
a really nice guy...
I wonder why he's working
with a man like Mr. Minami?
What's even more baffling is
why Naru would choose you
as his assistant.
Hey, what the heck
do you mean by that?!
Huh...? Where
did everyone go?
No, wait... you shouldn't
go over there...
Listen to me...
please come back!
If you go that way something
bad is going to happen!
-Yes?
-It's Minami...
I'm sorry
it's so late.
Have you by chance
seen Atsugi tonight?
First Suzuki
disappeared...
and now Atsugi's
gone, too.
I'm sorry to say that none
of the staff members
have any information
about Atsugi...
shouldn't we take this
opportunity to again
ask Dr. Davis to use
his abilities...?
And if the doctor is
unable to use clairvoyance
then perhaps,
someone else can.
Uh... yes...
But perhaps...
This is an
emergency, sir...!
Two people have
vanished in two days
and one of them was
your own assistant...!
Why wouldn't we ask
Dr Davis for help,
unless you've
been lying to us
about the identity of the
man you brought with you
to this house!
Is it true...?
could it be
that this man...
is just an imposter?
Well, I'm not going to
sit here and take this...
how dare you insult
not only myself
but the honorable
Professor Davis as well!
It's obvious now...
We're being forced to solve
this case all by ourselves...
please... come with me,
Professor.
Something is not
right with that guy.
We don't really
have any proof
that the man is
actually Dr. Davis.
You mean, Apart from
Mr. Minami's insistence.
Yeah, and he didn't use
his clairvoyance again.
It's been four days...
the case is at
a standstill...
and there's been no sign
of Suzuki or Atsugi.
I just can't get
used to this house.
Yeah... I mean, normally
you'd never think of
anyone going missing inside a
house, but in this place...
Hey, there's
a door here!
Fantastic... another
secret room?
Geez, it's dusty!
I wonder who
we have here?
It says "Meiji 32,
self-portrait, Urado".
Oh, really?
So who's Urado?
Since his self-portrait
was hanging there
I would guess he was likely
someone close to Mr. Miyama.
Should we ask Mr. Ohashi if
he knows anything about it?
What is it, Naru?
Urado... I think... yes.
Wait, I don't get it,
wouldn't somebody read
that as "Toura"?
Hold on a sec...
Didn't we said that this bill
would be from the Meiji era...?
And since they read opposite
of how we do it today...
it would really be
right-to-left...
so then...
the writing would actually
look something like this, right?
The first part would be...
"Everyone who has come
here is now dead"...
I think.
Dead?!
And I'm guessing that the last
part there is "Run away"...
Do you think this was supposed
to be a message to someone?
Well we can easily
assume that "Here"
would most likely
refer to this house.
Remember?
Madoka said Kaneyuki wouldn't
allow anyone to come here.
Maybe this Urado person
did something really bad
and Kaneyuki didn't want
anyone to find out.
That's a lot of
trouble to go through...
why not just expose him?
Maybe Urado was
holding him hostage...
and when he finally decided
to try to communicate
with someone on the outside
the only thing he had to use
was this bill.
In any case we've
learned some
very interesting
things today...
and once we use them...
Let's not forget we know
something else as well...
The spirits here spoke
quite clearly at the séance.
I am now certain that they were
the spirits of those people
who have died
in this house.
The people who
died here...?
But who did that hospital
coat belong to...?
Could it be that the
people who went missing...
Suzuki and Atsugi...
I can't move!
Why can't I talk?!
Ayako...! Masako... wake up!
What do I do...?!
No... stay away!
No, let me go...
Please...
let me go!
What room is this?
Someone's here.
No...! I've got to be having
one of those dreams again...
because if I'm not then...
It smells like blood.
Stop... I don't want to
go into that room...
No!
What is this?
Why am I wearing a kimono?
What are you doing to me?!
This is a dream...
I have to hurry
and wake up...
I don't want to die.
Somebody...
-Help!
-I don't want to die.
No!
[Music]
Next time
on Ghost Hunt,
'The Bloodstained
Labyrinth" Part Three.
Let's just hope
I make it out alive!