I'm Mai Taniyama,
a freshman in high school
and I work part-time
with a team of professional
ghost hunters.
It was one thing
when we found out
that the doll Minnie was
behind the poltergeist,
but everything changed
once Minnie tried to physically
harm little Ayami.
Naru did tons of research
on the previous
owners of the house
and found out that lots of
children around eight years old
who have lived
here have died,
one after the other.
Going off the idea
that the children's spirits
were trapped in the house
and possessing Minnie,
Naru called in John and
Masako as reinforcements.
And then...
Monk, I'd like you to try
cleansing the house again.
But once Monk started
his exorcism,
things took a turn
for the worst.
Tomiko...
my... child.
What am I looking at?
And who in the
world is Tomiko?
[Music]
Naumaku san manda
bazaradan sendamakaro
shata sowataya un
tarata, kan man.
Naumaku san manda
bodaran, on boron.
Monk, there's
something behind you!
What? There's nothing
in here Naru!
Damn... I guess
he can't see it.
Mai, wait!
Monk... Look out!
Go...! Right now!
But...
We can see the
ghost on camera.
Don't just stand
there, Mai!
Get out of here!
Come quick!
You're in danger!
No one can interfere with me.
Mai!
Naumaku san manda
bazaradan kan!!
-Mai! Are you okay...?
-Yeah.
Come on. Let's go.
It looks like the house
was built over this well.
It must be pretty old.
There's the spirit
of an OSHIMA here
She's lurking deep
down inside the well,
calling to the
children's spirits
and pretending to
be their mother...
The children only
want to return home,
but they're lost and
can't find their way out.
Is Minnie there too?
Minnie, who is actually
Yuki Tachibana,
acts as the ringleader
of the children,
but in reality, she is in
so much pain and sadness
that she just wants all
of this all to stop.
It appears to me that this
well bores deep into the earth.
And At the very bottom,
lie the spirits of the children,
trapped in the dark.
Who is this Tomiko?
It's Oshima's child.
She's looking
for her child.
Tomiko is her daughter.
That's why she's
gathering the children.
Now we're getting somewhere.
Naru?
I need to take
care of something.
Naru... don't leave yet!
Naru... Where are you going...?
Why does he do this
every time...?
It's starting to get old!
He does that so often
I just expect it now.
How about we work on
driving out the spirits
until he gets back?
You're right...
Okay guys...
-Who wants to go?
-Hmm?
Which of you two is up
to the challenge...?
I'm warning you it's
intense in there.
Fine, I guess I'll do it...
But If I go, one
of you brave men
will have to watch
Ayami for me.
-Of Course.
-Sure thing.
May the heart of this
house be cleansed
as thy interim dwelling,
and enshrine thyself in
this altar of peace.
Ayako is so lame.
The only reason I'm here
is because she was scared.
And she calls herself
a spiritualist?
I just felt a chill...
Where could it
have come from?
I summon the energy
of this world...
And of Emperor Yamato,
who reigns over the Land of
the Eight Grand Islands...
What did you stop for?
Take it easy.
What's wrong?
I just felt
someone touch me!
You need to stay focused...!
You're a professional, remember?
Mai... What's wrong?
I can feel a...
hand on my...
Help!
Mai!
I can't stop!
Help me!
Quick grab my hand!
MAI!!!
Where am I?
That's not Ayami...
Who is that?
No...
Get away from that man...
I don't know why but
that man is dangerous!
NO!
Stop!
Tomiko!
Tomiko! Tomiko!
Is that the girl's mother?
Tomiko!
NOOOO!
Don't...!
Naru?
Tomiko.
Don't do it!
Mai! Are you Hurt?
Ayako.
Oh, thank goodness
you're okay Mai, ...
Just sit tight. Lin's coming
right down to help you.
Oh yeah...
That's right...
I was dragged down
into the well.
Really...? A kidnapping?
That's right...
at 'least I think so.
It was a vision...
This man just strolls
up to the girl
and then walks
away with her...
so That's why I believe
her mother threw
herself down the well.
You have no experience
as a medium
so how could your dream
possibly hold any weight?
There!
That hurt!
Surprisingly enough...
I think she may have hit
the nail on the head.
Wait... So you agree with me?
I wouldn't go that far,
but it is a possibility.
I know that was
no ordinary dream.
It seemed so real.
Naru?
Now this is a dream
I've had before.
So Naru...
Ayami...
Do you really think
we can save her
before it's too late?
She'll be fine.
Really?
You're right.
As long as we do our best,
everything will work out.
Are you sure that's
a good idea, Naru?
He's back!
Lin. Play back everything
you've recorded thus far.
Right.
Hey Naru. You're back.
Yes, thank you, Mai.
I knew that already.
Why can't he ever act
like he does in my dreams?
What are...
Hey.
What do you mean, hey?
Aren't you two supposed
to be watching Ayami?
She could be in danger
right now for all you know!
Naru said there's no use
in guarding her anymore.
So we came back to help.
Wait... Are you positive
that she's okay?
She's fine...
Everything will
be over tonight.
Miss Hara... Can you see
what the spirits are doing?
They're in the
living room...
There's no indication they've
gone to the hotel yet.
Matsuzaki
Start making charms
that will stop any
spirits from passing.
I want the rest of you to post
them throughout the house.
We're going to raise a
kekkai barrier in here.
Care to fill us
in on the plan?
I'm planning on returning
Tomiko back to her mother.
Huh?
That's impossible, Naru.
Tomiko cannot be
returned physically.
Her mother will continue
to haunt this place
until we can at least create
the illusion of her return.
So we'll need substitute.
You don't mean
Ayami, do you?
The problem lies
with the woman...
If we leave here
without removing her,
we'll have failed.
But this woman
is dangerous...
She nearly killed
Mai an hour ago
when she pulled her
into the well...
I think at some point
we need to start
considering our own safety.
I guess...
but what about Ayami?
Come on guys.
I must say I'm disappointed
in all of you...
I expected much more.
If you can't even
think objectively,
then I don't need you.
But the risks are high.
If we screw this up
our spirits could be
trapped here as well.
Whether or not you
want to participate
is entirely up to you.
Mai, You're free
to leave as well.
Naru.
You poor thing, Mai...
He's quite a handful.
If Naru is prepared
to go that far
then there's at least
a chance of success.
Why is she so pro-Naru
all of a sudden?
I trust your judgment Masako
and if you think we
should then let's do it.
You sure?
Well at this point it's
the only option we have.
I agree. I think
it's a good plan.
If you all end up dead
I'll see to your funeral.
Well, how nice.
Just like Naru told us,
we began putting up charms
all throughout the house.
So... what exactly
is the purpose of putting
these charms everywhere?
It's simple...
To keep the spirits
from leaving the house.
Naru!
Be aware that we'll be
leaving the demongate open
to distribute the spirits.
Oh get off it...
Why does he have to
act like a bigshot?
'Cause he's Naru.
Uhh, did he say
Demon's Gate?
No Demongate...
The northeast quarter...
It's the easiest direction
for spirits to pass through.
Monk and Matsuzaki
guard the demongate...
And When the
spirits exit...
scatter them as
best you can.
So we'll be reducing the number
of spirits temporarily
to draw the woman out?
John I want you to
cover the living room
and do the same.
Piece of cake!
Wait, hold on a second.
Then Who's going to
conduct the exorcism?
You don't mean...
Our father,
who art in heaven.
Hallowed be thy name.
What's wrong?
Cleansings are addressed
to the spirit directly
to help them with issues they
had in their past lives...
Only a medium can
be successful at it.
Naru is no medium,
so he plans to
perform an exorcism.
What's the difference between
an exorcism and a cleansing?
In a cleansing you try
to persuade the spirits
to change their ways...
but in an exorcism
the goal is to destroy or
kill the spirit outright.
That's horrible.
I wish he wouldn't
exorcise her...
At least...
not in my presence.
Interesting...
To Masako, spirits and
humans are one in the same.
You okay?!
Yeah. I'm fine.
Something yanked
on my arm.
In the beginning
was the Word.
And the Word was with God.
Miss Hara... How 'bout now?
They're attempting
to escape...
Their numbers are
beginning to drop rapidly...
They're trying to get
out of the living room...
and they're crying.
Hey wait...
Why don't you go ahead
and cleanse the children's
spirits right now?
Impossible...
Not as long as the
woman's spirit is here.
What is it?
She's coming out.
Tomiko.
Those eyes.
Tomiko is not here!
These children do
not belong to you!
Please, set them free.
Can't you see the pain
they're suffering?
They just want to return
to their real mothers.
Let them go...!
John!
Naru...! Give me
another minute...!
Please, don't!
Naru wait!
Your child is right here...
look?
What is that?
Take the children you've
gathered with you...
and leave this place!
What a warm light.
It's so beautiful.
Look Mai... right there.
They're all gone now...
They've been cleansed.
And with that,
another case was solved.
You have no idea how
grateful I am for your help.
I just heard
from my brother
and he said he'll be
returning as soon as he can.
Oh, That's great news!
Are you sure it's safe...?
I mean you're sure
that you got rid of all
the ghosts in the house?
There's no need to worry.
Last one.
We're set to go.
Naru. What was that little
thing you gave the ghost?
It was a hitogata.
What is that?
It's the original form of
the straw effigy dolls...
It's made by carving a
piece of Paulownia wood
into the shape
of the person
you want to put a spell on.
You dummy ...
That's how you put
a curse on someone.
Spellcasting has both a
light and a dark side.
A light spell
helps the person
while a dark harms them.
Often the casting
has a combination
of light and dark sides.
That's right...
It's just like in
esoteric Buddhism,
where either approach can be
used to confound a sworn enemy.
The hitogata is simply a vessel
used to contain a spirit...
For example, let's say I
patterned an effigy after Mai.
If I were to
damage the hitogata,
Mai would be harmed as well.
That's how close the
effigy is to the real person.
So that one was...
Made for Tomiko.
Of course...
Since she thought she had
retrieved her daughter Tomiko,
she was cleansed because
her wish had been fulfilled.
I gotta to say I'm impressed
you made a successful
hitogata that quickly.
Is that why you
had left earlier?
The date of Tomiko's birth
and death were necessary
for the effigy
to be effective.
The woman was Oshima Hiro.
Tomiko was her
only child...
The girl had
disappeared one day
and her body surfaced
from the pond
about six months later.
A couple of
years after that,
Oshima's house
was demolished...
and the house before us
now was built in its place.
Tomiko...
Do we know if,
she was kidnapped?
Is that why the mother
threw herself down the well?
There was no mention
of a kidnapping...
The important thing is that
this house is free of spirits.
I wonder...
Were you planning
on a cleansing
from the very beginning, Naru?
I never would have pegged
him as an Onmyouji!
Onmyouji...?
Do you mean like
that Abe guy?
Fashioning a hitogata
after Tomiko
and cleansing the mother
is pretty complicated...
Only a pro can
pull that off.
It's amazing isn't it...?
With how young Naru is.
Amazing?
Well it's definitely cool.
-Hey Mai!
-Hey...! What's up Ayami?
So Do you think...
we'll see each
other again?
I'll tell you what.
If you ever need me,
just call.
-You promise?
-Promise.
At the end of the day,
I'm just happy that
Ayami is safe.
[Music]
Next time on Ghost Hunt,
the After School Hexer,
part one!
Aw Back to school, again?