I'm Mai Taniyama,
a freshman in high school.
I have what you would
call a weird job.
Wow! What a cool house!
That guy standing next
to me is Kazuya Shibuya .
He's my boss.
I'm sorry to drag you
out here like this.
It's quite a drive
from the city.
This is my
sister-in-law Kana...
and my niece Ayami.
My brother is on a business
trip overseas at the moment
so it's just us
three girls
in the house all
by ourselves.
Three days ago, that woman,
Noriko Morishita,
came by the office
I work out of
and hired us to
investigate her home.
There's something
strange about that house.
The furniture will
rattle all by itself...
I'll hear knocking on
the walls of rooms
when I'm the only one home.
And Doors will constantly
open and close
all by themselves.
As you can imagine,
we're pretty frightened.
I'd like to have a
word with your boss.
My name is Kazuya Shibuya
and I own the company.
Oh, I had...
It's not uncommon for
people to react like her
when you consider the
lead investigator
is only a teenager.
He's extremely
self-confident,
which lead to the
nickname I thought up.
Naru the Narcissist!
So Anyway...
What are we looking at...?
Do you really believe
we have a ghost?
We will explore all options
in our investigation.
I'm happy to say that I'm a
proud member of the team at...
Shibuya Psychic Research.
[Music]
Whenever we do on-site
investigations,
we always set up a base,
or headquarters.
This is the main
room we operate
out of while we
conduct experiments.
How's set up of all
the equipment looking?
All audio and video feeds
are transmitting clearly.
That's Lin,
Naru's assistant.
He's not a big talker
and he's definitely
not a fan of me,
so I try to
keep my distance.
I wonder if we're dealing
with a poltergeist.
Judging from
Noriko's description.
Ah, you're sounding less and
less like an amateur each day,
aren't ya kiddo?
Hey Monk!
Hey.
That's Hosho Takigawa.
He's a monk from Mt. Koya.
I see you're
overdoing it again
with all this
fancy equipment.
And that's Ayako Matsuzaki,
a self-styled shrine maiden.
Neither of them are
members of SPR,
but they'll help us on jobs
when their specific
skills are needed.
Let me see.
Clearly the work
of an earth spirit.
It's defiantly a human.
The evidence
speaks for itself.
Well listen to you.
Now Don't forget.
Nearly half of all
poltergeist cases
can be attributed to
human interaction...
Many of those cases
deal with women
under great deals of stress.
This case in particular
may have to do with the
woman of the house
not getting along with
her sister-in-law.
Like Noriko?
I'd buy it...
That Kana woman does seem
to be a bit unpleasant.
You're welcome.
It's amateurish at best.
In cases where a human is
to blame for a poltergeist,
the culprit is
usually a teenager...
or adolescent child.
Noriko is already
in her twenties.
So she doesn't meet
the age requirements.
But...! Now it is true that
there are cases of women
who are sensitive
to the paranormal,
so I will consider that
in my final decision.
Why you...
Excuse me! I'm still
learning my way, got it?!
Why does my boss have to be
such a jerk all the time?
Hi there Mai...
Perfect timing...
I'm taking up some
lunch to Ayami...
Would you Care to join me?
Oh That sounds great!
Ayami is such a cutie-pie.
If you had to say,
does she take more after
her father or her mother?
Hmm. Probably her mother.
Really? Because she doesn't
look like Kana at all.
Well that's because Kana
isn't Ayami's birth mother.
My brother had her
with his previous wife.
Oh I'm sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Ayami...? Lunch time...
Mai's here too.
Hey Ayami...
Hope you're hungry!
She's so cute!
Nice to meet you.
Oh, hello...
And you're...?
Minnie.
Ayami...
Your new book...
are you enjoying it?
What's wrong?
Why don't you have
some food... 'kay?
I'm not hungry.
I wonder what came
over her so suddenly.
Focus your eyes
on the light.
Naru's first experiment
was to see if the source of the
poltergeist was human or not
by using this
glowing red light.
Try to match your breathing
to the glow of the light...
Nice and slow.
It's said that in the case of
people causing a poltergeist
they use a
supernatural ability
they're unaware
of possessing...
So when a suggestion
is planted into
the sub-conscious.
Tonight, a vase will move.
A small glass
vase to be exact.
It will be sitting
on the table
that's in front
of you now.
If the person who receives
the suggestion is the culprit,
they will do what
Naru has told them.
That'll be all.
Please try to spend the
rest of your evening
as you would any
normal night.
Kana, the key?
Oh, right.
The suggestion worked.
As you can see,
everyone's eyes were
focused on the vase.
So if a human is the cause
of the poltergeists
in this house,
the vase will move.
And if it doesn't move,
then the cause is unknown.
Any movement?
Not yet.
Come quickly!
I came up here to
put Ayami to bed
when I found all the
furniture like this.
Everything is moved
away from the walls.
What's going on...?
I thought you people were
supposed to stop things
like this from happening!
Are you sure the little
girl didn't do this?
There's no way
she's that strong!
You're right...
The rug was moved as well.
Even I don't have
that kind of strength.
I agree...
If there is a human
capable of this...
I'd love to meet him.
I was merely throwing
the option out there.
It wasn't Ayami.
Aww... We believe you.
What's wrong?
This time everything
was upside down!
Even the carpet's
been flipped over.
Classic poltergeist
activity.
It's A simple
earth spirit...
I'll have it driven out of this
house by tomorrow morning...
You'll see. Night everyone.
Where does she get
her confidence?
What's up Naru?
You look like you're
on to something.
Care to share with
the rest of us?
Don't you think this
response is a little quick...?
Paranormal phenomena tend to
have an aversion to outsiders...
Usually any signs of
a haunting back off
in the first twenty four
hours of an investigation.
Really?
If you ever watch
those tv shows
that cover famous
haunted houses,
usually nothing substantial
ever happens on camera, right?
Normally the spirits
will shy away
from the visitor initially,
but that's not
the case here.
I think this is
full on... Hatred.
You thinking the
same thing I am?
Yeah...
The house is aware
of our presence,
and it's quickly
becoming angry with us,
so... if you couple that
with these increasingly brazen
attempts to scare us off...
We're dealing with a poltergeist
that means business.
We may have a hard
time with this one.
Naru declared that Ayami's
bedroom and the living room
were now off-limits
to everyone
until the completion
of the investigation.
Ayami was to stay in Noriko's
room from here on out.
The next morning, the
vase in the family room
had not moved an inch
from the night before.
Does that mean an actual
spirit is haunting this house?
I stand here today to
beseech the gods...
I call upon them to descend
from the heavens and join us
where no gods dwell to end
this ceaseless suffering.
I ask that my humble
plea may be heard
to reclaim peace
unto the spirits
trapped in this
haunted place.
Well... That should do it...
Sometimes I amaze
even myself.
Naru. Here's the
temperature rundown
for every room in the house.
Ayami's room is a few
degrees cooler than the rest.
Naru taught me that
whenever a spirit is present
the temperature drops.
The house itself looks to
be structurally sound...
all the floors are flat...
There's no sign of
subterranean water loss
so the ground is solid.
Do you think that there
really is a... ghost.
The chances of that
are increasing.
Seriously?
What the...
Kana!
The flames just started
shooting out of nowhere!
Just Get back...
Takigawa!
Naru...! Someone's out there!
Are you sure?
Yes...! Someone was looking
through the window!
A little kid.
Okay Minnie,
time for me to tuck you in.
Sweetie?
Ayami.
Were you just outside?
No. Mai saw someone looking
through the kitchen window...
Now I'm not angry,
I just want to know
if it was you.
I wasn't.
Are you telling the truth?
I am...
Ayami didn't do it!
What's happening?
Ayami didn't do it.
Stop it!!
Noriko!
Aunt Nori!
Oh no!
So what is that...?
Two huge failures
in a row?
I guess I'm just a useless
waste of space then.
Luckily, Noriko wasn't
hurt in the incident.
So yesterday...
What was that?
It seemed to react to
the little girl shouting.
And it could be tied to
the image of the child
you mentioned seeing
in the kitchen.
I believe that
Ayami's behind this.
I thought the
suggestion experiment
you conducted proved the
culprit wasn't human...
How much confidence do you
put in that test of yours?
One hundred percent.
Is it possible the
suggestion failed?
There's no way.
You know you've
been wrong before.
Kazuya.
The temperature in Ayami's
room is dropping again.
Lin... More sound.
That is intense.
There isn't even
anyone in that room.
Incredible.
What's that?
The temperature.
It's dropping
unbelievably fast...
Hold on... Then...
Then who could be responsible
for doing this?
It's not Ayami,
that's for sure...
No...
No human could
pull this off.
I take it Ayami likes
to keep to herself, huh?
Well normally she's a lot
more outgoing and cheerful
than how you've
been seeing her...
She's been acting strange
ever since her dad got
remarried a few weeks ago.
I see.
Ayami. It's time
for your snack.
It's nice to have
someone to play with...
Don't you think so?
I really wish you would
talk to me more...
Why don't you
have a cookie.
Don't you want one?
Fine.
Suit yourself.
It's okay sweetie.
Is it alright with you if your
Aunt Noriko had a cookie?
No!
Those cookies are no good!
Minnie told me so.
She said all the
snacks are poisoned!
Minnie told me my
new mom is a witch...
She said she made Dad her
servant with her magic...
She said Ayami and
Aunt Nori are in the way
so she's trying
to poison us.
This is getting weirder.
The doll told her all that?
Where am I...?
Oh this is Noriko's
guest room...
I was so tired I don't
even remember going to bed.
Naru?
What...? What's wrong?
What?
Naru?
Ayami's in grave danger.
She... She is...?
I don't understand.
How?
How is she in danger?
Naru...! What's going on...?
Please... Talk to me...
Is Ayami okay?
That was weird.
I don't believe myself!
Here I am dreaming
about Naru again...!
What's wrong with me?
Oh yeah... I forgot.
Minnie's the one that
told her that...?
So she's talking
with the doll?
Yeah.
Pretty creepy, huh?
It was definitely a dream.
The only time I see him
smile is in my imagination.
This is Ayami's doll, Minnie.
My brother bought it
for her as a present
right before they moved
into the house with me.
Did Ayami's behavior change
before she got the doll...?
Or after?
Umm, it was after.
Let go of her!
I'll save you Minnie!
Give her back!
Now Ayami...
I understand that you're
able to talk to Minnie.
Don't you ever
touch her again!
Ayami!
Ayami... I'm sorry...
I just need to borrow
Minnie for a little bit.
So that's Minnie, huh...?
I'm surprised the little
squirt let you take her.
Yeah, Well to be honest
we didn't get actually
get her permission.
She sure is creepy
looking, isn't she?
I guess.
Archaeologists believe that
dolls were originally
meant as vessels
for trapping
people's souls...
Being soulless and
empty on the inside,
a spirit could posses
them more easily.
So Naru, are we just gonna
watch this doll all night?
Hey... What's up?
Minnie.
No way... She was sitting
just a minute ago!
[Music]
Next time we continue
with part two of
"the Doll House!"
Is that not the
creepiest doll ever?