Help...
Someone...
please...
Help me...
Help...
help me, please...
I don't want to die...
Welcome, thank
you for coming.
Please call me Ohashi...
I've been given full
authority to handle this matter
on behalf of the client...
If you have any questions
or need to speak with him
I will be your
direct contact ...
May I ask who is
in charge here?
Yes of course, that
would be me sir,
my name is Kazuya Shibuya.
So it seems the rumors
of your young age
were in fact true,
Mr Shibuya.
Who have you brought
with you today?
They are accomplished
spiritualists
and friends of mine...
They have graciously
offered their expertise
on this case.
And... over here we
have my assistants.
Narumi Kazuo, sir.
There actually is a
reason for all of this...
[Music]
I've accepted a
new contract.
It's a very high
profile case...
The client has requested
that we exercise the
utmost confidentially,
if the media got involved
it would no doubt blow up
into a massive story...
I think the safest
bet would be
if we all worked
on this together.
Excuse me, but did you
speak with a Mr. Ohashi?
Why, did you get a
call from him, too?
Yes.
So tell us...
who are we talking about?
Mr. Ohashi is just
a representative...
The actual client
would be...
Are you serious?
Isn't that...
the ex-prime minister?!
Wow, that would be a
major story for the press.
Which is why we should
avoid attention
as much as possible.
And a good way to start
is by asking Yasu here
to stand in for me.
Uh... what are you
talking about?
So that's the reason
why you asked him
to come here today, Naru...
I thought it might be
so we could celebrate him
passing all of his exams.
Oh man, you got
into college?
Yeah, of course...
So do you think you'd
be willing to stand in
and take my place, Yasu?
Oh, yeah...!
You guys are great
and I'd be more than
happy to help out...
Plus I think I
owe you one...
I mean if it
weren't for you all
I'm pretty sure the
case at my school
never even would
have been solved.
Wait a second...
I understand why you prefer
to steer clear of the media...
but do you really think
this calls for a body double?
The client has
apparently been calling
in a number of
other psychics,
including some shady
bottom-feeders...
I'm sure it's no surprise
that I have no interest in
associating with those types.
Nice... so you're
pushing it off on Yasu
just because you
don't wanna do it?
If you have a
problem with that
no one is forcing
you to stay here.
Geez! You should talk to me
before you go running
at the mouth!
Uuum, excuse me miss - are
you looking for someone...
Here's a shocker - when you're
asking people for favors
there actually is an
appropriate way to do it.
I've said this before but no,
you never learn do you...
Please excuse him...
this little boy's still
learning his manners.
This... little boy...??!!
Madoka... would you mind having
a seat and being quiet...?
we're trying to work here.
And that's why communication
is so important!
Isn't she something.
Who is she again?
Of course...
My name is Madoka Mori.
Hi, um, how do
you know Naru?
Well, I guess you could
say I'm his teacher.
His Teacher?!
Yes, I'm the one who
taught Naru everything
he knows about
ghost hunting.
To be completely honest...
I'm the one who asked
Naru to take on this case
I know it's weird and
you don't know me...
but I really hope
you'll work with us.
Which brings
us up to now...
This house is so weird.
It's a little
more than "weird."
Hey have you guys ever
seen those paintings
that are like this?
I was thinking about that...
I wonder if the
builder was an artist.
Come in here, please.
What's that smell?
Is something wrong?
No, I'm fine.
What was that?
This house has
been unoccupied
for quite some time now...
Local teenagers...
took advantage by
sneaking in to explore
and scare each other.
However, two months
ago it was learned
that one of them...
went missing.
A young man from
the fire brigade
who was searching for the
missing boy also disappeared.
Shortly thereafter,
several people reported seeing
fox fires inside the house.
In fact, there are many
who would swear on
their very souls
that this house is haunted.
While the house
was being remodeled,
there were similar stories
of workers disappearing...
Of course, we don't want
anyone else to come to harm
and we'd like to try to control
any more negative rumors,
which is why you've
all been invited here.
Whoever exorcises the
house successfully...
may expect a very
substantial reward.
Interesting!
Also... if any of you decide
to withdraw from the case
I will understand...
if you would remain on the
premises until such time...
I would greatly
appreciate it.
Now, please allow me
to introduce everyone
who has so generously
agreed to join us today...
Ms. garashi, professor
at Otoha University,
and her assistant,
Naoko Suzuki.
Renowned medium
Masako Hara.
Reimei Minami, head of the
Minami Psychic Research Council,
and staff member
Hideo Atsugi.
Their mentor, from the English
Psychic Research Society...
Doctor Oliver Davis.
-Shut up, are you kidding?!
-Whoa...
Oh my gosh, who knew we
were going to be working
with the famous Oliver Davis
on this case...?!
Monk, isn't it cool?
Uh, Monk?
Look at him...
All star-struck
and freaking out.
I've gotta say...
I'm really surprised
that such an authority
on psychic research
would show up here.
I assure you we'll have no
problem handling your case!
After all, we have the
famous Dr. Davis with us...
and not to mention
the efforts
of all of these other talented
and fairly important people.
So who's this Davis guy...?
and why is he
such a big deal?
Because he's incredible,
that's why.
He's actually not involved
with the psychic power side
as much as he's done
a lot of really
fantastic spirit research.
But there was this one
time, a few years ago,
that he did this amazing
PK demonstration!
Was that the one where he
took the giant aluminum block
and slammed it into
the wall...?
I had to miss that one.
And there's also
that famous case
when Dr. Davis helped find
and rescue that American
billionaire's son
who'd been kidnapped.
Yeah, yeah
that kid had been buried alive
in the ground, right?!
That means Dr. avis
is clairvoyant, too!
Hey... isn't it sorta weird
that someone that
famous would be here
without more people making
a big fuss about it?
Honestly, his fan base
is pretty specialized.
I'm glad to see you're
all enjoying yourselves.
Hey, Naru...
where'd you run off to?
I decided to start
bringing in the equipment...
I mean, we were intending
to do some work here, right?
Oh my gosh I'm so sorry...
here, let me help...
No Mai... leave it there.
The equipment's way too
heavy for a woman to carry.
Oh... no...
I can do it.
You go ahead and
take a break.
Well, this is
very impressive.
Ah, Mr. hashi...
I hope you find this room
to be sufficient
for your needs.
Yes... thank you,
we're getting
settled in ...
If you don't mind,
may we take this opportunity
to ask a few questions?
Yasu's asking questions?
Of course, you're welcome
to ask me anything.
That's very kind of you...
Alright then, Narumi...
please proceed.
Yes sir.
Oh, I get it.
You said the house has been
unoccupied for some time...
would you mind telling us
who the previous tenant was?
The prime minister's
wife's grandfather...
and former family head.
He actually built this
house around Meiji 10.
But since that time
there have been numerous
renovations and add-ons.
In fact, up until the
last head of the family,
I believe additions
were made every year.
So it's unlikely
that much of the original
building still remains.
Tell us more
about the character
of this former
head of the family.
Well, his name was
Kaneyuki Miyama...
and he owned a lot of land
here in the Suwa region.
He ended up building
a silk mill here...
and was known for
his involvement
with various
charitable works,
even opening an orphanage
and a charity hospital.
Unfortunately, he lost
most of his ventures
when the market collapsed...
and the hospital and orphanage
had to be shut down...
He passed away...
shortly thereafter.
Mr. Ohashi, have you
ever witnessed anything
out of the ordinary
in this house?
I haven't.
Would it be at all possible
to interview those people
who were in the
house at the time
of the child's
disappearance?
Well, we'd prefer to keep
this as quiet as possible...
Do you have any idea as to
the source of the ghost stories?
No... but the last
head of the family
might have suspected
something.
His final words
were instructions...
to leave the
mansion alone...
he wanted it to
deteriorate over time.
His final words...
You wouldn't happen to have
a floor plan of the house?
No, unfortunately
there isn't one.
I see.
Excuse me, who is
this gentleman?
My name is Lin Koujo.
I would guess that
you're Chinese?
I'm originally
from Hong Kong.
Wow Lin, I had no idea
that you were from China!
So what?
Uh... so nothing!
If that's all I
should take my leave.
Yes sir, thanks very
much for your assistance.
Alright let's
start by taking
temperature readings
throughout the house.
And after the sun goes down
no one does anything
alone, agreed...?
Miss Matsuzaki, I want
you to make some charms.
Be sure to make
enough for each of us
and for all of the rooms.
Relax man...
don't you think you're
jumping the gun a little?
That sounds exactly like
what somebody would say
to excuse their
own laziness.
This is a mansion that's
been empty for a long time...
There are numerous stories,
and there's no floor plan...
Given what we know and
what we don't know...
it's only common
sense to be cautious.
Hey...! what's wrong?!
There's a foul
presence here...
and I think I smell blood.
I think...
I smell it, too.
Man, this is like a maze.
Dead end, ladies
and gentlemen.
He did say there were
a lot of additions
but seriously this
is kinda crazy...
Oh...
What is this?
I guess It's just
another weird room...
You don't think we might
actually discover the body
of anyone who went
missing do you?
If it's somewhere
we could find it
I'm sure the police would have
turned it up a long time ago.
-What the...
-What is it?!
Did you find a body?!
Not quite...
But... why would
there be another room
on the other side
of this window?
Well the shutters
look kinda new,
so I guess this is just
another one of the additions.
Just over 4 degrees.
Well, should
we keep moving?
Yeah...
which way did we
come in again?
This way.
Oh great...
uh hey, wouldn't
it be hilarious
if the three of us managed
to get lost in here?
A room inside a room...?
No way, this is totally
like we're in an RPG.
A dungeon maybe?
Well if this
were a dungeon,
there would be
something in here...
Oh that's too bad...
nothing's in there!
Hey you guys...
forget the dungeon...
have you heard of the
Winchester mansion?
Like... Winchester rifles?
That's right...
The inventor of the rifle
left a widow when he died...
For years she was constantly
putting additions on the house
to protect her from
curses and spirits...
She thought people killed
by her husband's guns
would come back
to haunt her.
It's supposed to be a
pretty complex house,
similar to this one.
You mean someone wanted the
house to end up this way?
Oh excuse us...
we didn't realize there
was anyone in here...
You're all with Shibuya
Psychic Research aren't you?
Who's that guy?
I think it's Minami -the
guy who brought Dr. Davis.
Ah, the eagerness
of youth...
I find it so
refreshing, really...
of course, when it comes
to psychic research...
It's all about experience
so I'll be very curious to
see how well you kids do.
Pardon me, I
realize I look young
but the truth
is I just turned
two hundred forty
nine this year.
I've got great genes -
everyone in my family
practically lives forever.
I don't really appreciate
being made fun of, kid.
Alright smart guy, then
tell me when you were born?
Well I was born
in Horeki .
You know, I think you young
kids today are just super...
but of course if I'd
talked to my elders
with the same sort of
disrespect that you've shown me
I'd have felt
it for a week.
Yeah... The times sure
were tough back then...
I'll never forget the
"Great Tenmei Famine" -
Man, Naru totally knew
what he was doing -
this kid is awesome!
Yeah, it's kinda
freaking me out a little.
And they scared me to death
with stories of the Onin War...
Oh... please wait!
I'm not done yet...!
Mr. Minami?
-Well done!
-Bravo!
-Good job!
-That was truly amazing.
Thanks but I really
feel a little guilty...
please forgive me for
being a jerk, to the jerk.
All of the temperature
readings we took
were on the low end.
I don't think we
should call it a day
until we've got the night-vision
cameras, thermography,
and condenser
microphones set up...
and remember to stick
together no matter what happens.
Tomorrow, I want us to measure
each room and the hallways
and we'll use those to
create a working floor plan.
So how about it, Lin...
do you feel like
drawing up a floor plan?
Alright everyone...
back to work.
Well... this won't be
over anytime soon...
Hey Mai... shouldn't you
call home or something?
Nah, it's okay.
Just let 'em know
where you are.
Well since I don't
have parents
there's not gonna
be anyone there.
What are you
talking about -
you're... an orphan?
Yeah.
My dad passed away
when I was little
so I don't remember
him much...
and my mom died when I
was in middle school.
Don't you have any
aunts or uncles?
Uh-uh... no one...
neither one of my parents
had brothers or sisters.
Then, who's been taking
care of you all this time?
Oh, well I had a teacher
that was really nice
and she let me come and stay
over at her house for awhile...
but now it's just me.
I'm all grown up!
My school is really
great to people
who're having hard times,
so my tuition is free...
between that and my job,
everything I need is
pretty much covered...
And, since I'm
supporting myself,
the school will let
me take off whenever!
I get it - if you wanna skip
you just say you gotta work.
Yep...! I can stay out
for as long as I want.
"No wonder you're stupid."
Oh wow...! you
sounded like Naru...
If life ever
gets you down
you just come cry
on Monk's shoulder.
Ew,quit it...! No, way...!
Let go, ya dirty old man!
Well you don't
have to be rude!
These cases
may be scary...
but I wish times like
this could last forever...
When we're all joking
around and laughing,
it makes me so happy...
it's the best
feeling ever.
Is something dripping?
Someone probably
left the faucet on...
No... it's off...
It smells like metal...
it was just a dream...
but it was so awful...
I feel a little sick...
This is so weird...
If you go by the outside
measurements it's a rectangle...
But when you actually look
at the room it's a square.
So if we measured correctly,
the thickness of the walls
would be three meters?
It is weird...
But maybe we just
got something wrong.
Excuse me... Mr. hibuya?
Uh, yes... I'm sorry -
what is it?
I think it would
be a good idea
to conduct a séance
here tonight.
And I'd like to invite everyone
in the mansion to participate,
if at all possible.
Hello... please come in.
it's Dr. Davis!
Try not to freak
out on him!
Hey... keep it down will ya?
Sorry about yesterday.
Ms. Egarashi...
can we add a little
light in here?
It's difficult to shoot
with the room this dark.
Oh... is that a regular video
camera you have there?
Yes, I use it often.
I see...
when you said you were going
to record this experience,
I assumed you had brought
a night-vision camera.
I beg your pardon?
I'm sorry, Mr. Minami,
there will be only a single
candle during the seance...
spirits do tend to
dislike the light.
Oh... I'm sure
it'll be fine...
Wow... how could he not know
something as basic as that?
I'm concerned, though...
Without a
specialized camera...
Wait a sec...
we have a night-vision
camera, right Lin?
Well then sir...
should I go and
get our camera?
Yes, please do, Narumi.
Oh, if you could please,
that would be wonderful...
Let us take a deep breath
and call out to the spirits...
Those living here
in this house.
To you who dwell
around us...
I welcome you to use
this woman's hand.
to speak your will to us.
Please, speak to us
and help us to understand
your wishes...
if you can hear my voice,
please, use this woman to
speak your will to us...
Masako?
What's happening up there?
Mr. Minami,
please sit down!
You must remain still!
Who are you?!
I know there's
someone here.
Naumaku san manda
bazaradan kan!
Are you alright?
Yes, ma'am.
It would appear that
you summoned a spirit.
It says, "help"
This one's the same.
This one, too.
Hey, this one's different.
Who wrote it?
I don't want to die...
[Music]
Next time on Ghost Hunt,
'The Bloodstained Labyrinth'
Part Two.
Until then...
don't turn out the lights.