Are you ready?!
Are you ready yet?!
Come on...
I'm right here...
I'm ready...
Come and find me.
Get your Christmas
cakes ... Right here.
They're really delicious!
Hey...! Naru. Lin.
Good morning!
What are you doing?
It's Christmas Eve silly,
and I think this room
is in dire need of
some festive color.
Take it down.
What...? I've spent the
last hour putting it up!
Take it down.
Come on.
Hey! Masako!
Oh... What a beautiful
Christmas tree!
It really looks
great Mai.
Hey! Hey guys!
Ooh you have a tree!
Nice job.
It really puts you in the
Christmas spirit, doesn't it?
You're a monk that
celebrates Christmas?
Look who's talking
Miss Priestess.
Why are you all here...?
There's no work
at the moment.
We're just spending some
time with our dearest friends...
After all it's
Christmas Eve.
What do you say we throw
a little office party?
If you're so desperate
to celebrate
then find yourself
a church...
I don't throw parties
in my place of business.
Let me guess. You've
come to join the party?
Uh...
no no...
Actually I came by for
something else entirely...
I was wondering if you'd
be interested in a case...
It's for my local parish.
A case...? On Christmas?
[Music]
Wow! Check this
place out you guys!
It's amazing!
Christmas at an actual
church...! How cool...!
This sure beats out
an office party!
We didn't come here
to goof around Mai.
I know we're here to
work. I'm just excited.
This is fantastic.
It just doesn't get
better than celebrating
Christmas at a church.
Yeah, we get it.
Look we have a job to do.
And that's why we're
here, to work...
Though you have to admit it is
tough working on a holiday.
That's true.
We're gonna have to try and
wrap this up quick today...
There's a party later on
and you will be there.
Great... Sounds like fun.
Ah Father Brown.
Gday Father
I appreciate your coming by.
Now Kazuya...
I'd like you to meet the
Pastor of the Church.
Father Tojo...
And Father this
is my associate.
He's the head of Shibuya
Psychic Research.
Kazuya Shibuya.
It is a pleasure
to meet you.
Wow!
So pretty.
You see that?
There's a kid for
about every country
in the world on
that playground.
Father Tojo helps run a day
care service out of the church
for expats that
work here in the city.
A majority of these
children are foreigners
whose parents are over
here on work visas...
The rest of the kids
are either orphans
or those awaiting placement
in a foster home...
But They really love it
here, as you can see.
That's no nice.
Wow! I've seen you on tv!
You're that psychic!
Oh... Hello children.
Come on!
Why don't you talk to
the spirits for us huh?
I wanna see a spirit!
Do it! Show us!
We want to see a ghost!
It's... not that easy kids...
Maybe some
other time okay?
Settle down, children.
Settle down...
I'm so sorry about that.
It's fine.
I think I'd be
worried if the kids
weren't so excited, ya know?
You have a point there.
While Father Tojo briefs us on
the details of the case...
I'll need the rest of you
to play babysitter
with the children
until we return.
Alright...! Who's
ready to have some fun
on the swing set
with Takigawa? !
Monk... You're just
riling them up.
Follow me!
There you go...
Wanna go higher?
Just hold on
tight now, okay...
Youre that psychic!
So... are spirits scary?
Show us one! Show us one!
I wanna see!
Well... Believe it or not it's
much harder than it looks.
Honey I don't think you'll
be seeing any ghosts today.
What do you know Grandma?
Oh... Isn't that sweet?
Nice pass there...
Mai...! Ball's
coming to you now!
Bring it on!
Here goes!
Whoops...
Sorry.
Now Gentlemen...
Every so often
unexplainable things
will happen here
at the church.
This morning one
of the children
was behaving erratically,
at which point I
telephoned father brown,
And he suggested that I
contact you right away.
You know the kids
from earlier...
the ones from
the daycare...?
Like clockwork every
couple of weeks
one of them will become
possessed by a spirit.
I've exorcised spirits
from them a number of times.
But you're saying
no matter what
the possessions reoccur.
That's right.
However the possessions
never seem to do
any permanent harm
to the child...
They just behave like a
completely different person...
and they're all
obsessed with hiding.
They're hiding?
Oh where could that
stupid ball have gone...?
It could be anywhere...
Oh wait...
There it is!
Alright.
Whichever child is possessed
will always play a game
we call stick.
It's called stick?
Excuse me. Are you lost?
Are you okay...? What're
you doing out here?
Wait! Come back here!
Hey wait up! Why
are you running?
I'm just trying to
help you...! Stop!
Hey kid...!
That's weird...
Where'd he go?
Oh ... Hey
There you are.
Please don't run! There's
nothing to be afraid of!
Stick is essentially
just hide-and-seek,
but instead of shouting
the kids will beat
a wooden stick
against something.
One hit means they're
not ready yet
and more than one hit means
they've found their
hiding place.
What is that sound?
Why is it so hard to tell
where it's coming from?
Uh... I'm afraid Thanat
is hiding again.
What's that noise?
That sound is
the stick...
The boy that was behaving
strangely this morning
must be in the
forest somewhere.
We should all split
up and find him.
What the... You hear that?
Is there something wrong?
That must be Thanat.
What is he doing?
He's been hiding in the
forest since this morning.
I just hope he's alright.
Hey where did you go? !
I can't find you? !
Where could he be?
I'm gonna find
you eventually!
So this is where
you've been.
Mai... are You okay?
Hey... Naru...
I found this boy
in the woods.
Wait a second.
Daddy it's you!
Huh?
What did he say?
He really likes Lin.
At least somebody does.
Thanat...
Come over here
for a second.
It appears as if he's
mistaking me for his father...
Would you mind
telling him the truth?
Well the funny
thing is,
you bear an uncanny
resemblance to Kenji's father.
Who's Kenji?
According to Father Tojo,
there used to be a boy
here named Kenji...
one day he disappeared.
Shortly after that,
the possessions
started occurring.
Hello... You must
have gotten a chill
while you were outside...
I've made some of my famous
hot tea for everyone...
Would you all
care for some?
Oh yeah that
sounds wonderful
Thanks alot.
Yes thank you.
Ahh, now that's good...
So Naru... Do we know
anything about this boy
that went missing?
Actually Father, didn't you
mention that this time of year
holds some significance
to the phenomenon?
Kenji first arrived to your
church around this same time.
That's right...
it was a week before the church
moved into this building
from another location
in the city.
You said that Kenji was
originally brought here
by his father...
but even though he
promised to return
for his boy the
following Christmas...
the man vanished
without at trace.
Why don't we head
inside, Kenji?
It was apparent from the
start that Kenji suffered
from a mental disorder...
which left him unable to
speak like a normal child.
That's terrible.
When that boy saw Lin
earlier he called him daddy...
Wouldn't that mean
Kenji is able to talk?
He must have had strong
feelings for his dad
to notice him through
another body.
I bet that's why he was
able to speak up
when he saw Lin...
It must have been overwhelming
after such a long time.
Although He may not have been
able to speak like the others...
he was happy... and playful...
all of the other kids took a
liking to him immediately.
They even crafted
playground games
to include Kenji...
such as the hide-and-seek
game called stick.
At that time, the parish
was in its infancy
and the building itself
under construction.
But children were so happy
to be getting a new home,
they just chose to play
around the construction.
They actually found it
to be quite exciting.
Hey...! Who wants to
play hide-and-seek?
I do! I wanna play!
Kenji, do you
wanna play too?
But... You never
say anything,
so if you can't shout
'I'm ready' or 'not yet'
then how are you
supposed to play?
He's right.
I know...! What if Kenji
could give us a signal
when he's ready or not
instead of saying it?
Good idea!
I found this stick for you to
signal us, okay Kenji...?
You just tap it...
Once for not yet and a
bunch when you're ready.
Ready yet?
Not yet!
Apparently Kenji was
very fond of this game...
and played it quite often.
Would you say
that's true?
Oh yes...
Kenji was known around
the playground
for being the
best at hiding...
The other kids
would call him
the Master of
Stick for that.
Even now I can still see
the big smile on his face
as he would step out from
wherever he was hiding...
so proud that no one
was able to find him.
Later, for his birthday,
Father Tojo gave him
a whistle on a string to
wear around his neck...
He then replaced the
stick for the whistle
while playing the game.
Right.
Now try to keep this
with you all the time.
Pay attention...
If you ever need something
you can blow the whistle
rather than using
your voice, 'kay?
Unfortunately, not
long afterwards,
Kenji went missing.
This was at a time when
the church's construction
was nearly complete...
and the children were
looking forward to having
their first Christmas
in their new house.
What...? Kenji's gone?
When did this happen?
Well We were all playing
stick at the new house
when it started
raining on us.
We said we were
going back in
but Kenji never came out
of his hiding place.
It's alright...
I want you kids to
stay right here...
I'll go outside and bring
Kenji back in, okay?
Kenji! Kenji!
Where are you? !
Hey Kenji...!
Can you hear me? !!
Father...
There's no sign
of him out back.
Oh no...
Where in the
world could he be?
Hey Father... .
Over here!
The scaffolding!
Don't tell me he's
trapped under there.
I'll get some more hands.
After four hours of
intense searching,
no one ever found a
trace of Kenji.
And then?
The next day...
The staff began a broader
search for Kenji...
and found a whistle,
similar to the one he wore,
next to a storage
shed behind the church.
They found it
behind the church?
There's an aqueduct that runs
east to west back there.
It's quite deep and at
the time they hadn't yet
erected the fence
that's there now.
So you believe he fell
into the aqueduct?
I do.
The police did an
extensive search between
the church and the river
that the aqueduct feeds into...
They never found one
piece of evidence.
So the police could
never find the body...
poor child,
that's horrible.
Were those sounds I
heard earlier today...
from Kenji...?
Is it possible
that he could...
still be playing
hide-and-go-seek?
Anything is possible Mai.
I wonder if he's out there
still beating his stick...
because he lost his
whistle so long ago...
as if he's begging to
be... found.
It doesn't sound like
there's any danger.
Huh?
But there is the
possibility
that this could escalate
into something bigger.
What exactly do you
mean by escalate...?
Are you saying this could maybe
turn into something worse?
I don't know... From what
I've heard so far...
this is an innocent haunting
because Kenji would
never do anything
to harm the people
he cares for.
Yeah but...
no matter how many
times I drive him out
he always comes back again...
Plus from what Father
Tojo has told us...
Lately...
Kenji's been appearing a
lot more frequently
than he used to which could
be a sign for the worst.
The possessions are...
changing him.
Really...? What
do you mean?
Well you hear
people say that the
"spirit of their
ancestors"
is haunting them, right?
But do you think a
spirit would knowingly do
something horrific
to their own family?
No.
Yet sometimes
that is the case.
My point is that dead people
who are left to wander...
tend to change over time.
Though change isn't
the right word.
Think of it as if they
absorb the thoughts
of those around them and are
altered in the process.
So wait, You're saying
spirits can be influenced
by the actions of humans?
That's one way
of putting it.
Otherwise they'd
become too attached
to something on earth...
and would just end
up embodying
the very thing
they've left behind.
That means...
even though Kenji was
good while he was alive...
he may not necessarily be
so nice in the afterlife.
That's pretty much it.
So what do we do now?
That's simple...
We'll just have to
start looking for him.
Now let's get to work.
It's so odd.
Well that's an
understatement.
You know... Lin actually
looks like he'd make
a pretty good dad.
You're filming?
Strange scenes like this need
to be immortalized on tape.
Usually, Kenji will
emerge from the child
after playing a game
of hide-and-seek.
Maybe he feels more secure
thinking his
father is around.
One thing's for sure.
Shooting video isn't
going to help...
So John... lets see if
you can drive him out.
Okay.
All of the curtains in
the room are closed.
-You ready John?
-Yes.
Our father who
art in heaven...
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come,
thy will be done,
on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day
our daily bread,
and forgive us
our trespasses.
As we forgive those who
trespass against us, and
I feel bad for Kenji...
he just looked so happy
thinking he was with his father.
And now he's about
to feel alone again.
Yeah... But for Kenji
to stay happy
Thanat has to stay possessed...
it's not fair to him.
Yeah I know but...
Amen.
May god have mercy
on your soul.
It's alright... He's
no longer possessed.
Father!
What is that?
Can you guys...
feel it?
Those are
knocking sounds.
Uh... Mai...?
Are you alright?
How do you feel Thanat?
Okay.
Hey... What happened
to me Father?
Mai... What
are... you doing?
What? No way...!
I think Kenji
just possessed Mai!
[Music]
Next time on Ghost Hunt.
Silent Christmas, Part 2.
Wait, what just
happened to me?