She came to see us on
a Sunday in November...
-Here you go.
-Oh...
thanks alot.
So you're saying...
your friend has been
acting strangely
ever since using a
Ouija board at school?
Yeah.
She'd jump up onto her
desk in the middle of class...
And in gym she was eating
sand from the sandbox.
I know it sounds crazy,
but I really think
she might be
possessed by a fox.
Can you help her?
[Music]
You should take your
friend to the hospital...
she needs a doctor.
But... Naru... wait!
[Music]
Why did you treat
her like that??
All I said was that it
sounded like her friend
needed a doctor's care.
You could have at
least been nice
and referred her
to someone else.
Knock-knock...
Hey Naru, whaddup?
Uh... who're you?
Man, lemme tell ya
coming to Shibuya
on a Sunday is crazy.
Mai...! be a sweetheart
and get me an iced coffee.
Uh... no way...
Is that monk in there?
What, the outfit...? I
had a live show today...
I gotta admit I love being
in front of a crowd...
playing in basement studios
isn't nearly as exciting.
Hey...! Does that
mean you used to be
in a rock band
or something?? !
Well, I didn't used to
be in rock band, Mai...
It's my main gig...
I play bass.
But, how can
you work at Mt. Koya
and be in a band are you
just a monk on the side?
Kinda...
The temple belongs
to my family,
and my dad really wanted
me to be a monk...
but when I couldn't bring
CDs and stuff up there,
I had to make a choice.
You know... I see a lot of
curses in rock n roll...
More than you'd imagine...
So whenever
something happens
and an exorcism is needed...
They call me since I'm
already in the biz...
See?
Uh-huh...
I get it.
Wow, I guess you really
never know about people.
Although in Monk's case
it was actually harder
to believe he was a
monk than a rocker.
How about you fill us
in on what business
you have here today?
Oh, right...
There really was a point
to my coming here,
I promise.
I was hoping you would let me
pick your brain a little.
There's a local high school
girl who follows our band...
after our last gig, she struck
up a conversation with me.
Is it true that
you do exorcisms?
Uh... well...
So after some initial
fan girl chatting,
she started telling me about a
certain desk at her school
that's apparently cursed.
Every single person
who's sat there
in the last three months has
been involved in an accident...
and not just that, but
the same type of accident.
They've all gotten their arms
caught in the door of a train...
and then been
dragged by it.
A total of people have sat in
that seat since September,
and all of them
have fallen victim.
One had only
minor injuries
but the rest were
seriously hurt.
The teacher of that class
was also affected -
he went on and on
about seeing ghosts
and then ended up
in the hospital.
He keeps coughing
up blood,
but they can't figure
out what's wrong
There's all sorts
of stories
about strange incidents
happening at that school...
I've even heard they think
someone there is possessed.
Wait, possessed?
It sounds crazy, but
I think she might be
possessed by a fox.
Hey Monk...
do you happen to
remember if the school
she was talking about
was Yuasa High School?
That's right...
How'd you know?
Hello...
hope I'm not intruding.
Hi...! um...
what can we do for you?
Well you see...
I'm hoping you
can help me.
Yuasa High School? !
We're grateful
for your time.
Mr. Yoshino is our
guidance counselor...
he'll give you a full
tour of the school.
Hi there...
it's nice to meet you.
As you requested, a conference
room has been cleared out
for you to set up in.
We've announced that
anyone who wants to
speak with you
should go there.
So, this is
home base, huh?
We should get the equipment
set up right away...
Lin?
-Right.
-Um... excuse me...
Are you the one
who's in charge here?
No sir...
You want him.
What's wrong?
Well... I...
Before the
students come in...
I'd like...
to tell you
about something.
Yes, of course...
Have a seat please.
You see, um...
at night I've been
hearing this...
knocking sound...
It wouldn't stop, so
finally I got up
and went to open
the curtain...
Since then I've barely
gotten a wink of sleep.
Hmmm... has anyone else in your
house heard the knocking?
Yes, but it doesn't
seem to bother them
as much as it does me.
I see.
Your name was Kiyomi...
Kiyomi Ito?
Yes.
When you came
to see us...
I believe you said
you thought
your friend was
possessed by a fox...
Is she here?
No sir...
she's at home.
And you also said
she that was jumping up
on desks and
eating sand?
There's other
stuff, too...
One time she dove into the
pool with her uniform on...
It was like forty
degrees that day.
Has your friend
ever hurt anybody?
Oh, no sir.
When she started
acting strangely,
why did you believe she might
be possessed by a fox?
Why didn't you think that
she might just be sick?
Because...
she actually said
'I am the white fox
of the harvest god'...
It all happened after
that darn Ouija board...
When everyone was
leaving she told us
that she thought
she was possessed.
I told her that
there was no way,
but she said she
felt really weird.
And then the next day she
started acting differently.
Where were you using
the Ouija board?
In classroom 1-3
Look the track team's locker
room is really creepy...
the lockers just fall
over by themselves
and our equipment
will move around.
At first we thought someone
was just playing a joke,
so some of us hid to try and
catch them in the act...
No one knows how it
happened exactly
but suddenly the shot-put
balls we'd put in a box
were lined up in the
middle of the floor.
Last month some friends
and I did a test of courage
in a storage room
in the gym, and
I've been seeing a
bunch of these
weird shadows ever since...
One of the other
girls even swears
she's seen ghosts coming
out of her desk, so...
During class?
Yeah...
Um... she said it was like she
all of a sudden couldn't move,
and it felt like someone
was touching her stomach.
And when she looked
down to see ...
She said it happened
all the time...
And her stomach just
wouldn't stop hurting...
She ended up having
to go to the hospital.
Is anybody in here?
Norio!
Ohmygosh you really came!
Hey...
Meet my friends...
That handsome devil
is Mr. hibuya,
the director of Shibuya
Psychic Research.
And his assistant,
Miss Taniyama.
Hi, my name is
Yuko Takahashi...
It's Nice to meet you!
Oh, same here...
Uh, "Norio"...?
What's that?
That's what they decided
to call me in the band...
See, my real name is
Hosho, right...?
-So we thought...
-So Getting back to the point.
I'm guessing that you're
one of the victims.
Were you involved
in an accident
after sitting at
a certain desk?
Uh, yes.
I was the second one
it happened to...
The train arrived
at my stop
and when the doors
opened I stepped out
and started to walk
away like normal.
Then it was like
someone grabbed my arm
and pulled me back, and
I got caught ...
I wasn't dragged very far but
my shoulder was dislocated
and my legs look
pretty bad.
Was there anyone
standing near the door?
Mm-mm, no one.
In fact I remember the
train was pretty much empty...
just a few people
were there.
Do you have any idea of
what the connection is
between that desk
and these accidents?
I don't, do you?
No
I'd really like
to see this desk.
Oh, sure, I can
take you to it.
It's back there.
Does anyone sit here now?
No one wants to, and the
girl that was sitting here
got hurt so badly she's
still in the hospital
And the desk has always
been in this position?
Uh-huh... Just like that
Oh...! hey, what's up!
What the heck is going
on at this school...?
I can't believe all the
craziness happening here...
who's gonna
exorcise it all...?
There's no way I
can do it alone.
Sorry Monk...
Wish I could help but
it's outta my league.
Something's not right here.
Huh?
Individually, these cases
are not a big deal...
but all together
they're abnormal...
Of course, this is assuming
that they are all true...
But with all of
these similarities...
there has got to be
something here causing it.
He's right - this goes
way beyond coincidence.
What exactly is
happening at this school?
With this many occurrences,
I think we need to
move quickly...
I propose we exorcise
anything we come across.
If that doesn't work,
we'll come back together
and try something else.
I'd like Miss Hara to take
a look around the school...
You should Start
with the desk,
and then when you're done
head over to the track
team's locker room.
Please, I'd be
more comfortable
if you'd just
call me Masako.
Is she flirting with him? !
Join her Miss
Matsuzaki...
Exorcise anything
you see fit.
Hold on...
Are you sure there's
nothing else
you'd like to say
to Masako...?
I ask because
it seems to me
that lately you've
been extra courteous
to our celebrity friend.
We can stand
around all day
chit chatting about
things that don't matter
but I'd much prefer to
see you in action...
Wouldn't you rather get
to work and impress us
than waste everyone
else's time?
Due to the number of
cases we don't have
enough equipment to
send with you...
so you'll have to rely
on your own instincts...
Monk and John
Same goes for you.
You got it.
Sure thing, no worries.
Lin and I will continue
the investigation.
Mai, you wait here for
everyone to report back.
-Sure
-Alright...
let's begin.
It's about the same
temperature outside.
And once again I'm
the one left behind.
What do I expect...
I can't do exorcisms
like the others...
man, if I could I'm
sure Naru would ...
Holy cow, you scared
the crap out of me!
Oh I'm sorry I
didn't mean to,
I just thought Norio
might be in here...
So What are you doing...?
Are you busy?
Nah not really.
Just kinda
holdin'down the fort.
Oh, I see...
So, how's the
exorcism going?
Well, we've really only
just gotten started...
but I don't think it's
going to be that easy...
there are just so
many cases here.
Yeah, I know... it
really makes you wonder
what's going on
at this school...
curses and ghosts and
supernatural powers...
like, where's the
UFO, you know?
Hold on a second!
supernatural powers?
Did you say
"Kasai Panic?"
Well... There's this rd year
girl named Chiaki Kasai
who could bend a spoon with
just the power of her mind.
It was just after
summer vacation...
suddenly everyone at
school knew her name,
and bending spoons and
other supernatural stuff
became a really big deal.
The school was divided
over the whole thing.
Some people believed in
it, while others didn't.
Then one day Kasai was called
up in front of everyone
during morning assembly...
If you really have
powers, prove it
by bending this
right here and now.
You can't can you?
Whoa, she bent it??
After that, things
got really bad.
A group of teachers started
to attack her credibility.
This is obviously
a trick...
you're just making
fools of us!
I guess that sent Kasai
over the edge,
because then she yelled
back at them...
I'll curse you to death!
And after that, all
of these crazy things
started happening
around school,
like with the desk and
the track locker room.
People started
getting frightened ...
they were saying it had to be
because of Kasai's curse.
I'm almost pretty sure
that's why she hasn't been
coming to class lately...
When she's at school
she's usually hiding out
in the biology
prep room.
I don't blame her...
Yes?
Excuse me...
We're looking for a
Miss Chiaki Kasai.
And may I ask what
this is regarding?
I'm here investigating with
Shibuya Psychic Research...
And I would very much like
to speak with Miss Kasai.
Oh right, um, what
was your name?
My name is
Kazuya Shibuya.
Ahhh...
yes, the principal said
there were going to be
some people coming
to investigate
all the strange things
happening around the school...
It's so good to
meet you both...
please come in, my
name is Kei Ubusuna
and I teach biology here.
Ubusuna...?
That's quite an
unusual name you have.
So you're looking
for Kasai...
I'm guessing you'd like to
ask her about the incident
-this past September?
-Leave me alone!
I have nothing to say!
Kasai I think you should
clear up any confusion
and tell these people
exactly what happened.
Why should I? !
So they can call
me a liar, too? !
But they investigate psychic
phenomena all of the time...
so they're not going
to immediately reject
or laugh at the
things you say.
O-kay... so whaddya
wanna know?
I've heard some very
interesting stories about you
Stories that connect
you to these events...
That you have powers...
The kind of powers that
bend spoons and keys at will.
Those aren't just stories
they're the truth...
I can bend them but I don't
expect you to believe me.
Why wouldn't I?
You're not the only one who
can bend a spoon, you know.
What? ! Can you??
I can...
But even if I couldn't
any psychic researcher
would believe in PK.
Then show me.
I guess I have no choice.
Over summer vacation I
was watching one of those
late night
shows, you know?
This one was about
spoon-bending...
So I got a spoon and
started trying it myself,
and eventually I
learned to do it...
I can't break them
like you, though.
That was in the summer?
But, you Can still
do it. Right ?
Of course!
Stop! Right now!
You were about to
bend the spoon
using the edge of the
chair, weren't you...?
You do realize that
if anyone caught you
doing that trick
they'd never
believe you again.
You're lying...!
I really can
bend a spoon!
Any researcher knows
that psychic abilities
can be affected by
outside sources
and are, therefore, unstable.
When you can't
do something,
it's okay to admit defeat.
The people who will
call you fake
never believe in
you in you anyway,
so don't worry
about what they think.
That's easy for
you to say...
but you don't have
to deal with
how mean people can be
if you can't do it.
Miss Kei was treated
horribly by the other teachers
just because she had
the nerve to defend me!
Oh, don't worry
about me...
please...
It's been incredibly
difficult to watch...
I felt so bad for how they
were acting toward her.
Then everyone in the
biology club quit.
Saying we must be doing
something crazy or evil...
I don't understand why
this is happening to me...
Is that why you
cursed them?
I'll curse you to death!!
Well, yeah...
I said that but c'mon,
it's not like I could really
do it, could I? !
Right?
Y'know, I actually kind
of feel sorry for Kasai...
All of this fear and
hatred over something
small like bending spoons.
Mai... I need to ask
a favor of you.
Did he say a favor??
I'd appreciate it
if you'd keep the
spoon-bending thing a
secret from the others...
especially Lin.
Oh this is totally
gonna kill me.
I wish I could
ask him why.
Sure, no prob...!
I won't tell...
I promise!
Thank you.
Oh my gosh!
This is Naru and I's
first private secret!
But that can't be true!
Well, it is.
I'm telling you there
are no spirits here.
I've looked all over
and if there were,
I would know by now.
Come on, there at least
has to be something
in that desk...
Don't forget about the
four accidents in a row!
There is some kind of deception
going on at this school.
Oh and I guess all
of the students
and teachers are in on it? !
You gotta be kiddin' me!
Relax mate. Easy.
You know, Masako's theory
may not be accurate.
Well I'm certain it's
more accurate than yours,
Miss Matsuaki.
In fact, MISS
Matsuzaki, I wonder
if anything you've said
has ever been accurate?
Hey, you may be
able to see 'em
but can you exorcize...
Lin... let's get back to work.
Of course.
Hey, whaddya say we go
take another look around?
I'm right behind you.
You may wanna look
more closely this time.
It won't matter,
I'll still be right.
I'm having déjà vu.
So Masako doesn't think
there are any spirits,.
If that's true then why are all
of these things happening?
Uh-oh, snap out of it!
Naru'll freak if he catches
me sleeping in here...
Naru?
Fox fires.
Fox fires?!
[Music]
Next time on Ghost Hunt
we continue File 3
- "The After-school
Hexer" Part 2.
I just hope
there's no homework!