Damn!
Whoa! It's up!
Nice follow-thru!
You have to ask the setter for
another chance, Asahi! You're the ace!
Shimada!
Sugaaaaaaaaaaaaa!
Over here!
Asahi!
Did you just hear that noise?! It was like blahw!
Nice one! You should be proud! Both of you!
Thanks a lot... uh great ball... Suga...
and Nishinoya's receive was perfect.
So... that's the ace.
Hey.
Hm?
I know you wanted to see the ace and everything...
But don't freak out!
What?! I-I'm not freaking out!
I may not be as tall or strong
as him, but I've got spirit!
Next ace... is me!
The average hand is approximately
3 quarters of an inch thick...
I have slightly smaller hands
than most people in my age group...
But that three-fourths of an inch
between the ball and the floor...
Makes all the difference in the world...
to keep the ace alive.
This is what happens when you skip club
for a month! You can't jump worth a crap!
I'm sorry.
Haha, don't you think that's a bit harsh?
Reunited!
So not only are we up against a veteran
team from the association but Asahi's with them?
We've sure got our work cut out for us now.
What are you going on about, Daichi?
You know you've got me on your side...
You've got me on your side!
Uh... What?
Hinata! Mind your own business! I was just about to be
a badass and then you popped up and ruined everything!
That was freakin' incredible! Nishinoya's like a pro!
If we can retrieve blocked balls,
then we'll be unstoppable for sure!
Don't bank on that... He's not
gonna be able to do it every time.
Huh?
The ball falls downward at a speed of 60 miles an hour.
And that's from just 6 to 8 feet away.
Nobody could save all of them. It's impossible.
Oh.
Listen...
The best thing we can do is get it into these boys'
heads that a blocked ball isn't the end of the world.
Just keep getting blocked and
I'll get every single one of 'em!
Huh?
Once you figure out that your teammates have
your back, Your frame of mind totally changes.
Go for it!
Ennoshita!
Cover it!
They could stand to work on their receives as a team.
Got it!
That setter's got a knack for gauging
distance from the point of impact.
If I remember right, he's a first-year.
Wonder which setter I'll use...
That's what I'm talkin' about!
Thanks!
It's all thanks to Kageyama's
sets... I can get past anybody now!
Oh wow, I guess he wasn't
kidding around when he told me that.
Dude, that was unbelievable! How'd
you do that?! I couldn't look away!
They didn't give each other any kind of signal...
How did they time it so well?
You!
What made you jump over there... huh, ginger?!
Huh?!
Uh... 'Cause it'll come to me wherever I am... uh, sir!
The shorty obviously jumped
without even looking for the ball.
Does that first-year setter automatically
adapt to everything the little guy does?
How's that kid so sure that the set is coming?
Who in their right mind goes full-swing on
something like that without even a glance.
What are you guys, a couple of weirdos?!
Weirdos?
Are we?
I dunno.
Wipe that smirk off your face, Tsukishima!
I have no what those two have going
on, but I'm not going to discourage it.
So... I was content to just hide in Kageyama's shadow...
It was... easier.
Man, that first-year setter's gotta be
some kinda mutant prodigy or something.
Okay!
In fact, he seems like he's got superhuman abilities.
Still...
Ooh! Straight spike!
And this is after he's been out
for a month, marvelous bastard!
You are way too excited.
That split-second timing between the toss and the spike...
It's the kind of thing that can only be accomplished after
you've been through a whole hell of a lot of training.
Yes!
A bond of trust like they have can't be built in a day.
We have a first-year setter with amazing talent...
And another pair with an incredible
connection with each other. We have weapons.
I'm free!
This ain't a bad team you've got here!
Why didn't you tell me, specs?
Yeah I've told you several times, actually.
But the ginger...
I don't understand why he's a middle blocker...
He's got pretty good quick attacks,
but can that peewee actually block?
He's staring at me...
Oh... that's right, I forgot!
This is Hinata's chance to go
head-to-head with the current ace.
Huh?
The thing is... Hinata enrolled at Karasuno
because he wants to be just like the tiny giant.
Yeah. That's right. That little guy was an ace too.
That's why he's always so fired
up... he's trying to be the same thing.
This'll be huge for him... A chance for
him to test his abilities against Asahi.
Heh, well isn't that special? Although
it's kinda like a kid against a grown man.
Parallel ball.
I can't believe I'm marking the ace right now.
The ace of Karasuno High School!
Get ready!
Nice receive!
It only took him a split-second to catch me!
I knew how high that kid could jump...
But it's amazing to see it at eye level. I
mean, how is something like that even possible?
He's great... and he's been out for a whole month!
You've been holding your hands in
the wrong position when you block...
This how you do it here! Like this!
Are you listening? Look at me!
Let's keep it up, you guys.
He was always covered in sweat
and looked like he was hurting...
But the tiny giant never stopped jumping.
I didn't really understand it at the time...
But I think that's what it means to be in a
position where your teammates completely depend on you.
Everybody on the team had faith
that he could score the point...
So they did everything they
could to get the ball over to him.
That must be what it's like to be Asahi too.
Hey.
The ace is awesome!
Even if they're blocking him, it doesn't matter
'cause he's got enough power to break right through 'em!
What?
Nothing.
Hm?
Forward!
Cover it!
Hey, left side!
If I was tall and powerful, I could be just like him...
Hinata, move closer to the back!
No! The tiny giant was amazing
without being tall! But still...
I wish...
Hinata!
Gahh!
Well, he's alive.
Are you okay?
You shouldn't feel bad, it's his
fault for spacing out like an idiot.
It's gonna be okay, specs.
Uh... sorry, guys... I'm okay.
Are you sure? Maybe you'd better sit out a bit-
I swear I'm okay! Don't worry about me. I just
didn't move out of the way fast enough, that's all.
I get hit in the face a lot.
Uh, that's not good...
Huh?
It's the middle of a game.
What could you possibly be spacing out about.
Oh crap. Kageyama's not yelling...
which means he's really mad.
This is just like that time I
hit him in the head with the ball.
I know what it is.
You wish you were the ace, don't you...
You don't want to just be the
team decoy... you think it's lame.
You want to be as big and as important as
Asahi so you can be the ace instead, am I right?
That's not how I feel!
Well... uh... maybe...
Now that you know we have an ace...
It's not just something you dream about... you're jealous!
Think about that garbage on your own time from now on!
Okay, so I'm jealous...
Is that so awful?
How could you understand how I
feel? You've always been really tall!
Look.
Heys, uh fellas!
It's time to close down the gym
for the night... put your stuff away.
I'm sorry, sir! Our game's not over yet.
Do you know what time it is?
Yes, I'll be sure to lock up.
It's my fault for holding up
the game. And now Kageyama's mad.
Don't doddle.
Thanks, sorry to bother you.
Sorry, Takeda! We'll hurry it up.
You tell 'em, Take!
Right... let's pick up where we left off!
Yes sir!
One more!
Let's go!
Hope you punks are ready!
Hey... based on what we've seen so far, it looks
like the high schoolers are in their best rotation now.
We better keep our eyes peeled
for the shorty's quick attack.
Yeah.
Listen.
Hm?
My next set... goes straight to this guy.
Block him with all you've got.
Yeah... I'm gonna send it to him...
just thought you should know that.
Oh yeah? You daring us?
Sure. Call it what you want... But it's going to Hinata.
Haaaa! You're funny, kid! That's really good!
Alright... thanks for the heads up.
You're welcome.
Is he crazy? The whole point of a quick attack is
the fact that your opponent's not expecting it...
So there's no way ginger can get through a head-on
block now... Not with all the cards on the table!
I agree.
His height already gives him a
disadvantage with blockers as it is.
What the heck is Kageyama's problem?
Why'd he have to give our plan away?
Those blockers are way too big for me to spike through!
All you are now... Is a clumsy little turd
who just happens to be fast and good at jumping.
Someone like you could never be the ace of this team.
Hey now.
That's not cool.
But...
With me around, you are the greatest!
What?
Look at Asahi. His spikes are forceful
enough to cut straight through a triple block.
Huh?! W-well not every time, but uh...
Whoa, calm it down, buddy!
You might not have what he does...
But how often do you really get
blocked? When you hit one of my sets?
Hm?
Go for it!
I got it!
Nice receive!
They're too tall...
Go around!
What other option do you have, you idiot?!
If you can't get through...
go around!
I hate being blocked.
I hate being pushed back!
I don't have a chance of winning
with these blockers in my way.
I can't break through them like the ace does.
But...
With me around...
you... are the greatest!
You might not be the ace of this team...
But with your speed and jumps... and my sets...
You can take on anybody!
The ace powers through for a
point, and you dodge for yours.
But a point is a point!
You don't need a crown with "ace" written on it!
You just need you to score all you can!
That's why our opponents will be marking you!
Your decoy skills will free up our other
spikers to score points too... Including the ace!
Right?!
Uh-huh!
Look this guy is right, you know!
Having you as a decoy could make a major
difference in our success rate every game!
It's an advantage.
So tell me, Hinata...
Do you still feel like the job of a decoy is useless?!
No.
Huh?!
Of course it isn't!
Good!
That last hit you did... It was great.
I'm sorry for interrupting the practice game, sir!
Oh... That's... uhh...
Yeah, sorry!
If it's okay with you...
Let's keep playing!
Alright! We're gonna catch right up!
Yeah.
Hey, specs.
Huh?
Anyway, just because you happened to nail it that time-
Those two there.
You mean Hinata and Kageyama?
Did they meet during middle school?
Or were the two of 'em close in
elementary school or something?
Huh? Oh not at all, actually the
two of them just met recently...
We had a lot of trouble with them at
first because they didn't get along.
Hm.
Um, why do you ask?
Whaddya know.
These high schoolers really know their stuff...
I think we're gonna have to kick it up a notch.
A jump float!
Hinata!
Alright, I'm open!
Uh?!
Face plant!
You are kind of a jerk.
Hmmm?
Hey... I've never seen a serve like that.
Didn't seem to have much momentum on it.
That's called a jump float serve.
Without any spin, it's got a shaky trajectory.
It could swerve or drop at any second.
Ah... It's like a knuckle ball... Interesting!
Uh Tadashi... they just got a point.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
One more!
Whoa!
Excellent!
That's four in a row.
Sweet!
Those two first years have a good combo worked out...
But the receivers do need some work...
Make sure to write that down.
Heh. You kids are all mine now!
Nice receive!
You're not gonna get away with it again, short pants!
Ha! Gotcha!
Uh-oh!
'Sup, scrubs?! Remember me?!
What?!
Nice save!
Suga!
Asahi!
Aw man! My bad, dude! They weren't
even trying to mark me either were they?!
Oh! No!
That was awesome though... You must've had
every set of eyes on you by the end of it...
Must say I'm a little jealous of you.
Keep it up next game!
Ah... um... Okay!
Man, that game made me feel like I was in school again!
Those were some good times right?
All the girls! All the drama...
"With me around, you're the greatest!"? You
kiddin? I wish I could say crap like that...
Man, high school was fun.
You kids really made us feel like some dinosaurs in there.
Uh... Sorry, sir.
Well anyway... you might not have
everything figured out just yet...
But once you do, I think you guys
are really going places. I mean it.
Thank you for coming!
Thank you!
Okay. Receiving... that's the biggest issue right now.
So we'll be working on that tomorrow!
Yes sir!
Thank you!
Now... don't forget to stretch.
Let's stretch out guys!
Yes sir!
Rotations! 1, 2, 3, 4...
Is their receiving really that awful?
You seem stressed out.
No... that's not what I'm worried about most.
I never really thought about it that hard when I
was up for selection during my time in high school...
But the guy doing the selecting
has his work cut out for him.
Let's put all this away!
Yes sir!
Yamaguchi, bring the balls over there...
Coming!
Asahi?
Hm?
Let's pick up the pace, everybody!
I may not be the ace...
but I am one of the guys who clears the way for the ace...
I'm a great decoy... The best!
Ah! But I can't really do that without Kageyama's sets...
So... what I'm saying is...
"I'll do my best" sounds kinda cheesy... But
"let's do our best" sounds even worse, so...
Hinata?
Hm?
That is... your name, right?
Listen, "ace" is just another name for a wing
spiker in left position... you do understand that, right?
Uh-huh.
When it comes to breaking through a triple block...
Or hitting the ball when the timing's tight...
those things are definitely the ace's job...
With your speed and jumps... and
my sets... you can take on anybody!
But still, to have a setter say something like that about
you... Well, that's pretty impressive in and of itself.
Huh?
A-anyway... I guess...
What I'm trying to say is... Whether
you're a decoy... Or you're the ace...
I'd say the coolest player is the one
causes the most panic for the opposing team.
Like, "Watch that mid-blocker, he's crazy!"
That kinda thing.
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
Let's do our best.
Will do!
Oh! I guess that all depends on whether or not
they let me back into the starting lineup, huh?
Man, for such a big guy... You really are a softy.
It's real good to see you back in action again, Suga.
Yeah, sorry I got all obsessive
and weird about everything.
I didn't say you did...
It's good to have you back too.
Aw yeah!
But try not to assault the vice
principal anymore... Got that?
And finally... I'm glad our soft-spoken wing
blocker is back from his little vacation... Right, Asahi?
Let's get everything squared away and call it a night!
Keep it up, guys!
Alright?
Yeah!
Almost time for training camp.
Ch-yeah, I can't wait to be under
the same roof with Kiyoko-Tanaka!
Noya!
Tanaka!
Noya! Noya!
Uh, what's happening?
Just ignore them...
Next Haikyu!! "The decision."