I am so sorry, Tanaka! I mean it.
I told you, it's okay... I'm worried
about you. Do you feel any better yet?
Yeah... I do now that I'm off the
bus and I've rested a little bit.
Sweet, I'm glad to hear that!
After all, whether we win or
lose today totally depends on you!
Huh?!
And let me hit everything unmarked
like you got to do in the 3-on-3, okay?
Tanaka! Don't pressure him!
What? I can't hear you.
I-I'll do the best I can, I swear!
Hurghhh, I'm going to the bathroom!
Comin' out both ends?! You're workin' overtime!
He's getting sick again? That is so
pathetic! I'm gonna teach him a lesson...
Hey what are you talking about?! You know
beating the little guy up isn't gonna do any good!
Well, it's worth a try!
Hold him back, Tanaka! Help me!
You got it!
Let go of me!
Hey, we're playing Karasuno today, right?
Doesn't that one guy go there?
Who?
The king of the court...
Didn't you guys go to middle school together?
Or something like that?
Right... Kageyama...
There's nothing special about that guy.
He had the best technique out of anybody on the team, but
the jerk couldn't act like a team player to save his life.
Too full of himself.
Yeah... well I'm wondering why he went to Karasuno High...
I mean they haven't had a great team in a long time.
All I know about them now is that they've
got some super hot babe for a team manager.
They have a girl?!
Yeah, she's got this sexy vibe about her.
No.
And one of their team members
looks like a juvenile delinquent...
The guy's even got a shaved bald head.
And it seems like he's pretty stupid too.
Hmmm?
Um... hello...
Don't mock my team, bro.
We'll have your heads.
Heh. Come on, Tanaka, there's no need to talk like that.
I mean look what you've done. The hotshots from Aoba
Johsai High School are practically shaking in their shoes.
You idiots really think we're afraid of you?!
Who is this beanpole? I didn't
know they had a player that tall.
Oh yeah, good thinkin'...
It'll hurt worse if we kick
your asses on the court instead.
Hey! Knock it off! I cannot take you anywhere!
Please excuse him!
Uh, it's fine.
Don't make that face at me!
So how ya been? Your majesty...
I bet you've already whipped your new
loyal subjects into shape. Haven'tcha?
Uh-huh.
Ow! What was that for?!
Yep, that's the king... as stuck up as ever.
Whoa... no way... this gym is huge... They're huge...
All together!
Thank you for having us!
Thank you!
Every single player on the Seijoh team has exceptional
offensive and defensive abilities individually.
Their guys are all good enough to
be the ace no matter where they go.
That's good, keep working on it!
And they're also famous for their power blocking guys.
I dunno what you two are so scared of. Hinata's
gonna take those losers by surprise and blow 'em away!
Plus... I know how much you suck so I'll
be there to cover for you the whole time!
Oh, but you're on your own
whenever you serve the ball, remember?
Try not to screw up Okie Dokie!
I'm just kiddin'! Fumblin' a
serve isn't all that bad my man!
Just let it roll off your back and keep slammin'.
Hm? Hey hang on.. Where'd he go?
The bathroom, I think.
Not again!
Ugh, I'm in trouble... ggh!
Man, those Karasuno guys sure are
arrogant. Who do they think they are?
Ugh, yeah. Huh?
Hey... he was next to Kageyama in that game last year.
I could never forget a guy whose head looks like an onion.
Hey... take it you're one of their first-years.
What's it to you?
So... how is king Kageyama?
Has he learned any manners? Or is
he still the same conceited jackass?
What are you, crazy?! "Conceited"
doesn't even come close to it!
It's like I'm a small, sad little peasant.
Putting up with the daily torture of
living in the land without fun or happiness!
Just 'cause he's kinda good, he
thinks he's the boss of everybody!
See what I mean?
He hates that guy!
I mean, I'll be the first to admit he's
good at receiving, blocking, and serving...
Oh yeah.. Real good!
And his sets are great too...
A pain in the ass...
Huh?
Are you sure?
Uh-huh.
Let me guess, you've never had to hit one of
Kageyama's crazy sets in a real game, have you?
They're terrible! It's literally impossible to hit one!
That bad, huh?
He's a selfish dictator.
What's the point of him being a setter if
he can't put the ball where anyone can hit it?
He doesn't belong in that position.
To him, a "teammate" is just a mindless
slave who does whatever he tells them.
Anyone he can't use... goes straight into the trash...
Buh-bye!
You wanna know if he's changed since middle school?
You just wait and see, onion-top!
What'd you say?!
Isn't that right, shorty?
Uh?
Anyone he can't use goes in the trash?
What happens if I screw up in front of him?
I have had enough of you!
I'll get swapped out!
I'm gonna be sick!
Yeah, this is gonna be a good game.
Hinata!
Don't let your jitters get
the best of you my man... relax.
Yes sir, I'll relax as hard as I can!
Hey Kiyoko, do you think you could
give him a few words of inspiration?
Hm?
Excuse me.
Huh?
Do your best.
Well, I killed Hinata... Sorry, guys.
Let the practice game between Karasuno
High and Aoba Johsai officially begin!
Thank you!
Is that short guy supposed to be their
middle blocker? That has to be a mistake right?
Is that really Kageyama over
there? Why's he with these guys?
C'mon, pull yourself together, Hinata.
Yes sir! I'll get it together right now!
Seriously... calm down!
Hey, Hinata! You know the plan right?
Do it exactly like the 3-on-3, okay?
Yeah, I understand!
You sure about that?
Do it, Matsukawa!
I got it! Right here!
You moron! What's with you?!
That obviously wasn't your ball!
I'm sorry!
Ennoshita, cover!
Tanaka!
On it!
Ah...
That's one point.
It's okay Hinata, just take a nice deep
breath and pay attention to your surroundings.
I'm sorry!
He's completely cracked under the pressure.
Oof!
Hinataaa!
Please stop stressing out, buddy.
Yeah! Thanks a lot pal!
It touched the net.
Karasuno's finally on the scoreboard.
Come oooon!
Quit being nervous or I will kill you!
Well... there's the great leader I
remember. That's not helping me calm down!
He hasn't changed a bit.
Alright! We're gonna take all those points back!
Next one to serve...
Oh no... Hinata's up to serve.
Talk about bad timing!
Just breathe, Hinata!
If I flub this serve, we automatically
lose a point and the set's over!
Dude, call me crazy, but I think
Hinata just stopped breathing. Is he okay?
How do you expect me to know that, huh?
Anyone he can't use... Goes
straight into the trash... buh-bye!
You can't mess this up. If you do, you'll get benched!
Just calm down... everything's
fine... everything's juuust...
Gah... crap, that was a terrible hit!
Gah!
Guah!
Ach!
Pffff... Damn, Kageyama...
That was perfect!
I sure hope you've got a couple
brain cells left over after all that!
Stop, you're only making it worse!
Knock it off, you two!
I'm so dead...
Ah... hold on, Kageyama...
D-don't hurt me!
L-let's talk about this!
W-wait a second!
N-no!
Look.
What could you possibly be freaking out about?
How tall those guys are? Your first practice game?
There can't be anything scarier than
hitting me in the head with the ball...
right?
No, that's my worst nightmare.
Well, in that case you've got
nothing left to be scared of anymore...
I mean, you've already done the
most terrifying thing you can do.
Which means... Might as well get over it
and get your head in the game, dumb-ass!
So I'm not in trouble then?!
No.. Who cares?
Gah! Well if I can get away with that,
I guess I can get away with anything!
Thanks for freaking me out, onionhead!
Hm?
Still, we did just lose the first set thanks to me.
Kageyama's not the only teammate
I should be worried about.
Sidebar, Hinata.
Listen up.
Yes?
Don't go thinkin' you have to be as good as these more
experienced guys already... That doesn't make any sense.
But I have to do things right... or else...
I'll get taken out.
And I want to play the whole game.
Look, kid... you're stupid if you
think that crap is gonna change my mind!
I know good and well what a klutz you are!
Daichi knows too and he still let you play!
Huh?
Forget about being swapped out!
You can worry about that when... uh...
When you do get swapped out, how about that?!
Huh?!
Do you think we should step in?
No, I think Tanaka can handle it.
See, here's the cool thing about volleyball.
Everybody you see on this side
of the net... is your ally, okay?!
So it's fine if you kinda suck.
Just do your thing, even if it messes
us up! We're here to back you up, bro!
We're a team! Us and you!
Now, who's your favorite upperclassman?!
It's you for sure!
Haha, call me Mr.Tanaka sir!
Tanaka really wants to be treated like an upperclassman.
Yeah... well it's still good to have him on the team.
Crap like that always sound best coming from
someone who's honest to a fault... Like he is.
What's up?
Eh, just a practice game.
Looks like they're starting the 2nd set.
Dude, you gotta teach me how to do
that back-of-the-head serve later!
Yeah, it's great. Could you teach it to me too?
You're up, Ennoshita!
It's just like the 3-on-3.
First, go to a spot where they don't have any blockers.
Then at your maximum speed, I want you
to jump and swing as hard as you can...
Be careful not to bump into
our other spikers though, okay?
Yeah I gotcha!
Kunimi!
You got cover?
Yeah!
Let's take it to the left!
No, right!
They can't do quick attacks. I'm sure
they'll shoot for an opening on the side.
Huh?
What in the hell?
Huh? I didn't touch it...
So they can do quick attacks?
Maybe it's a bluff.
Either way...
If you keep missing those, it's only a matter
of time before the king tears you a new one!
Hinata!
Here it comes.
Sorry 'bout that... That last
set... It was a bit too high.
He's sorry?
I guess so.
That's cool, I forgive you.
Owowowow! Stop giving me the iron claw, Kageyama!
Service!
Nice serve!
Hey, comin' atcha!
Got it!
They go the right and center.
Left side's waiting.
Who's the king gonna pick?
Okay, here goes!
Huh?
Woooo!!
Yes!
Nice one!
I see... It's that weird set-and-spike routine again.
Did you see that?!
He's fast!
Come over here, you two!
Uh?
Nice play!
Yeah!
Awesooome! That was so team-like!
Huh? What do you mean "like"? We are a team.
Yeah, you're totally right!
Nice one, first-year.
Thank you!
Quick-attacks? Really?
He seems a lot different since the first set ended.
That's right, start panicking. I want
you to be totally focused on Hinata.
Okay guys, Hinata's on track
now. Time for the counterattack.
Heh!
A chance ball!
I got it!
I know what to look out for
now. You're not foolin' me kid!
What did you say?!
You're mine now!
Eat this! You like that?!
Dammit, the shorty was a decoy.
Aw man I thought he was sending it to me!
How do you like me now?!
Huh?
Told you we'd show your asses up!
Uwah... I acted all tough and talked
smack 'cause I thought the ball was for me.
I feel dumb!
And there's nothing wrong with that...
You were convinced you were going to hit it..
So you convinced all of them too.
Does that work?
Apparently.
Dammit.
Relax, Kindaichi...
We're making all our attacks count
today. There's no need to let it get to you.
Right.
Whoa...
Even to the untrained eye, it's pretty obvious that
their blocks are being scattered all over the place.
Was Karasuno High ever this good before now?
Bleh!
Not again!
They make a lot of mistakes, though.
Over here!
Yes sir!
Something wrong, Hinata?
No...
It's just that the first time I played in a game, I felt
like it was up to me to carry the whole thing by myself.
But now, I'm surrounded by a team full of
players who are a lot better at the game than me.
I can depend on them.
All I gotta do is believe and jump!
I guess I never really had to worry about much else, huh?
Huh...
Hurry up.
He may not realize it yet. But that leap
of faith of his is one hell of a weapon.
Okay what's the deal?
That Kageyama guy isn't anything like you said he was.
Yeah, well I've never seen him like that either!
How was I supposed to know that there would
actually be a spiker on this planet who could hit
those ridiculous royal sets?!
That's not quite it.
From where I'm standing, their number 5
player hasn't been looking at the ball at all.
Wait what are you talking about, coach?
The best I can figure out is that
Kageyama is purposely aiming the ball
to match the downward swing of
the palm of the spiker's hand.
Is that even possible?
So Kageyama... changed his playing style?
I'll tell you one thing.
That number 5 of theirs must be pretty darn talented if he
can get a self-centered and arrogant player like Kageyama.
To adjust his habits like that.
The really incredible part of it is that number 5
apparently trusts in Kageyama's sets one hundred percent.
He simply believes the ball will come.
If they shake off your blocking, just
receive and keep the ball in the air!
You boys are our starting lineup.
Show 'em what you're made of!
Right!
Let's turn this game around!
Kageyama's really good...
I kind of wish we could've
recruited him back at Aoba-Johsai...
Didn't you try to get him here, sir?
Yeah...
But even if he had come to our school, despite all of
his technical ability, would he have made plays like that?
I don't think so.
Huh?
I think it's Karasuno - specifically that number
5 that made him into the player we are looking at now.
Hm?
Hey, time to start.
Chance ball!
Four-eyes!
Aw yeah!
Good one, Tsukki!
Nice, Tsukishima!
Your sets are so precise, it actually makes me nauseous.
What!
Tsukishima is being kinda rude about it,
But I understand where he's coming from...
Anytime he wants the ball to come his
way, it's already right there in front of him.
It's a little scary... But... It works.
We're in the middle of a game guys.
Can we maybe save this for later?
Your serve, Tanaka!
You got this!
Ah, I get it now.
The team rotates every time they
earn a point and get serving rights...
Which means Kageyama, Tsukishima, and
Ennoshita should all be playing forward now.
Right. So at this point, their positions are the
opposite of what they were when the game started.
Thanks to Hinata's decoy tactics, the
overall success rate of our attacks increases
whenever we have him in the front row...
Also, whenever the ball goes to Tsukishima...
His blocks are every bit as intimidating as Seijoh's are!
I'm sorry, is blocking your specialty too?
Just try and stay out of my way, would ya?
Watch your mouth...
Get too close and your skinny ass'll get blown away.
Uh.. Let's not fight, okay guys?
You're s'posed to fight the guys in blue! Blue!
Here comes the ball!
What are you so proud of? I was
the one who blocked it, you know.
Oh whatever, it hit my hand too!
Knock it off! Cut that crap out!
Heh, for once it's not me getting yelled at...
Wipe that grin off your stupid
face or I will wipe it off for you!
What did I just tell you?!
Crap...
This is too close.
Get it together, Kunimi, that won't happen if you cover!
I was right, that number 5 of theirs is unstoppable, huh?
I agree... combining him with
Kageyama is even more intimidating...
But it's not just them.
What Tanaka lacks in composure
he makes up for in power and guts.
Tsukishima's a smart blocker,
even if he's not too ambitious.
Their captain Sawamura neatly
covers the team's weak areas.
Over here!
Some of the team members are amateurs,
and their defense is full of holes...
But the offense is flexible enough
to make use of their greener players.
They really took us by surprise.
So this is Karasuno. A wild... disjointed...
Yeah!
Interesting team.
Whoa!
I can't believe they won the set!
Damn.
You lookin' good out there, Kageyama.
Thanks.
Time to take the final set... Right?
None of the guys on their team can
serve like Kageyama... It's an advantage.
Totally... it's been huge for us... Because
our receiving could use some work... Thank you.
Don't get comfortable.
Huh?
That setter of theirs... I don't
think he's... their starter...
Huh?
Hey... Oikawa's back. 'Bout time.
So that's not Seijoh's official setter?!
Who cares? I wanna know why this
joker walked in lookin' so smug.
Kageyama, what do you know?!
Well, you'll just have to find out next time.
What?
Next Haikyu!! "Versus the great king."