Oooh!
We have a banner?
You can do it.
What the hell?! Calm down already!
We can win!
The first round is all ours!
Yeah!
Huh?
Hey.
So... looks like it's time for-
Uh, don't say it.
Uh?
You were about to start talking about
something really sappy, weren't you?
Yeah, something about this being our last tournament...
Who wants to hear that crap?
Ah? Eh...
I guess this shall truly be our last tournament.
Yeah.
It's so crazy...
We've all been through so much together.
Uh...
That kind of talk makes me feel like
we're planning for it to be over. Stop it!
Aw come on, what's so bad about it?!
I had this whole big plan to
boost you guys' morale yesterday,
by getting all of the third-year players together
after practice for a quiet talk under the stars,
so we could get ready...
But then you guys just up and left!
That surprise from Kiyoko more
than doubled the team's morale though.
Well... Yeah... I guess that's true, but...
All we need to worry about today is winning
the first two rounds so we can make it to day two.
I don't want to talk like the year is finished.
Let's just play the game... and win it!
Don't sweat the other stuff.
Yeah.
We're counting on you, ace... Just... play hard.
Morning!
Daichi being nice is freaking me out.
Yeah, it doesn't suit him does it.
Oh I'm sorry, I can be mean if that works better.
Good morning!
Morning!
Ah?
Hey! Awhhhhh...
Good morning! We'll unlock the room for ya.
Time to go.
Yep!
What do you think Karasuno's like?
Hopefully... they're not a bunch of giants.
Eh, don't worry about it, man. I
heard they haven't been too hot recently.
Shiratorizawa's gonna clean house.
Hum?
Um nah, Aoba Johsai's a bigger threat this year.
Now that Oikawa's a third-year, they're
even tougher than they were before.
Plus, their first-years are improving really fast.
But, that's Seijoh for ya.
Eh... I dunno...
Y'think they can win the block against Date Tech?
All I know, is I'm glad they're not in block a.
Let's see... Who is in block a?
What does the Kanji say?
Karasuno?
Oh, yeah! They might have a shot.
Aren't they supposed to be tough?
Yeah, a few years ago, maybe... Now they
suck so bad they've even got a lame nickname.
Huh, oh really?
So, then, what are they called?
Uh, something about how they're fallen champions.
Oh! "The wingless crows."
Ah!
Eh, maybe you should keep it down.
What did you just say?! "Wingless crows"? Well-
Cut it out, now...
I'm really sorry.
Uh, it's cool.
Do I need to get you a leash?
No...
Uh er...
They're kinda scary.
That guy looks like a grown man.
Wait! Is that who I think it is?!
Yeah, that's Asahi!
Wait... What? Who's that?
You mean you really don't know?!
He made his goons beat up some guys from North High.
Let's teach these fools a lesson.
Oh no, a fight! Stay here!
I'll go call the authorities!
Then he got caught selling stuff on the street.
Fifty thousand.
Miss, did you drop your handkerchief?
I'm so sorry!
He got held back five years.
Dude, he's old!
Oh boy, here we go again, Daichi.
It's hard to avoid that with your looks.
Wh-what's the matter with the way I look?!
I'm a taller guy, so what's wrong with
me wanting to look all tough and wild?!
Okay, yeah, you see... Nobody who's
tough or wild would ever say that, dude.
What's the big deal, dude? Who cares how you look?
See, this is what wild looks like.
Um?
Hey, check that out.
I guess the banner really did the trick.
Do you really think so?
I mean, it did a lot more good than anything I said.
She is smokin'...
Hey, I dare you to talk to her.
Oh man, you think she could handle it.
Cut that out.
She just hit me... That was awesome...
Hey, see that short guy over there?
I think that's Nishinoya from Chidoriyama.
He won "best libero" back in middle school.
Whoa... really?
And that's not all. Y'see that guy there?
He's that scary-looking setter dude
that everyone's been talking about.
The king of the court from Kitagawa First!
But why Karasuno?
Beats me...
I heard he got a bad rep in middle
school though, so maybe that's why.
Okay, then who's the carrot top?
Is he some kind of living legend too?
Whoa!
Um... I don't think so...
He's weird.
Wow, there's so many people!
Hey, the summit!
That's exactly where I'm headed! Stay outta my way!
What's with you?! You can't say things
like that! I'm so sorry, he's a little off!
Okay...
Ah!
This place is huge!
It smells like air salonpas!
What are you talking about?
That is what makes a tournament
smell like a real tournament!
I know, right?!
Mm-hm...
They're here!
Whoa, they're tall!
Hm?
It's Date Tech!
Where are his eyebrows?!
Who the hell are y-, hum!
Hey! Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, dude!
Please don't do that!
I am so sorry about him, everybody!
Um, can I get a little help here!
Yeah, yeah, please excuse our giant friend here.
He has a way of automatically picking
out the ace on every team he sees.
Anyway...
Hope you're ready... 'Cause
you're about to lose miserably.
Why do you guys always have to be so rude?
That's not good sportsmanship at all!
Well that was something...
I wasn't really sure how to respond.
Yeah.
I'm impressed you were able to look him in the eye-
Ah!
Oh man... that was really scary.
How are you a badass on the
court but a wimp everywhere else?
Damn Noya, that was cold!
Sawamura.
Huh?
Been a while.
Oh, Ikejiri! Hey, uh... I'll catch you guys later!
Okay, see ya!
Long time, no see.
Yeah... you look bigger now.
Really? I'm the same height as before.
Uh, that's not what I meant.
So I'm fatter?!
No, not that.
His build is different, and he looks more intense.
I'm sure he's training harder too.
I saw you at the entrance a while ago...
But I guess I was too intimidated to say something to you.
Wait what, are you serious?
Well no, I understand. I guess some of our
guys don't look very approachable, do they?
Well it's just... they all seem
really tough... and so do you.
You think so?
The thing is, my school has kind of a small-time team.
Uh!
Listen uh-
Wait, forget I said that!
Look, it doesn't matter how big we are...
Or how big we used to be...
'Cause we're here now, so...
Fact is, we're gonna wipe the floor with you!
Ah uh...
I'm so nervous!
I know. Me too.
Was it just me, or were their spikes
really on point during practice before?
Yeah they did make the top 8 last year...
Well, maybe hopefully we won't get matched with them!
We should have showed up to morning practice more.
Remember... it doesn't matter how strong or
talented your opponent is. You won't win unless you try.
If you look back now... We had more than enough time.
We could have practiced a lot more than we did.
We didn't have our priorities straight.
Yeah well it's too late for that, Yui-
But none of that matters any more!
We've got 45 minutes 'til the starting whistle blows.
All we can do now is make sure we're properly warmed up,
then play to the best of our ability 'til the very end!
And maybe... we can win!
Gather 'round, everyone... Let's huddle!
You heard the captain, ladies!
What?
Karasunoooo... fight!
Yeah!
Hinata... you better not be about to puke again.
No! I-I'm mediating!
What is that supposed to mean?!
Um, I think he means "meditating".
Nah... looks like he might pee himself.
You must be freaked out over what happened with Date Tech.
I-I no-I'm not freaked out, I'm just finding my chi.
Your chi?!
Oh great...
He's losing it...
We're gonna have to do something fast.
Or else it'll be the Seijoh game all over again.
Wow, Asahi, you're just as much of a
coward, but you don't seem to be that nervous.
He just called me a coward?
Well I have a trick for getting rid of pre-game jitters.
Just think about something totally
awful that happened in your past...
The more terrifying the better.
And then you think, "this isn't the
worst thing there is, I can handle it."
Something in my past that was really scary.
Hmm... hmm... hmm...
Hm? Hinata?
Yup... I think I'll be okay.
Snap out of it, we need you!
If you had this amazing coping strategy, then why did you
get all bent out of shape last time we played Date Tech?
Listen Noya, that's the kind of thing you
think but don't actually say, understand?
Uh, well I really didn't have time to think of
anything scary that day. I couldn't concentrate,
and it takes a lot of effort to come up
with the mental image! You guys get that, right?
Lame excuse.
Everybody ready?
This is our first game... Now, let's go get warmed up.
Right!
It's finally happening!
Whoaaaaa!
This place... it's huge!
Could you pick your jaw up off the floor, please?
You're too serious!
At least I'm not having a freak-out!
H-hey, let me go, Kageyama!
Ready, boys? 'Bout time to get in a few practice reps!
Yes, sir!
Let's go get a closer look at 'em.
I want to see those two Karasuno
first-years do that quick attack of theirs.
Yeah.
Aoba Johsai's here.
Man, those guys are tall...
They look like they're pretty tough, too.
Well it depends. A big part of how good a
team is, is their setter... Wait, where is he?
Where'd Oikawa go?
Uhhh... He's uh...
Tell us. We don't have all day!
He got held up by some girls from other schools...
Iwaizumi.
Got it.
These are amazing! You really made them yourself?
Yeah, I stayed up really late last night baking!
Well that makes me feel really special. Thank you.
Ah! I-it was nothing!
Could I please take a quick photo with you, Oikawa?
You want a picture of me? Absolutely-ahhh!
Unbelievable! Not even the coach has ever hit me!
Sorry ladies, have to take a rain check on that photo.
Aww...
It's onion head!
What the hell's an onion head?
You're the only one it could be.
Huh?!
Yoo-hoo!
Ah.
Kageyama and small fry! How's that
cute little combo move comin' along?
Great king!
Would you please stop doing that?
So you got a libero. He wasn't
with you at the practice game.
I think that big guy's new, too.
Hey...
That coach... I don't think
I've ever seen him around before.
Ginger, move your ass!
Okay!
So they have new players and a new coach to boot...
Wonder if that means Karasuno's improved their game, any.
Well, today's the day.
I can't believe it...
Our team's about to play here... In this giant venue.
It's making me... nervous just
watching from the sidelines.
But that's why...
It's important to do everything
we can, to the best of our ability.
Yes.
And... go!
I'm ready!
Date Tech...
Asahi!
Hm!
Right here!
Listen I'm worried about Date Tech too...
But I won't be defeated...
Because my mind's on victory... and remember...
Got it!
We have to remain focused on the opponents in front of us.
Yeah.
Captains!
Thank you for the game.
Alright, you guys!
Line up!
Thank you for the game!
Go, go, Date Tech, Date Tech, here we go!
It's the first game of the season.
And that kinda pressure can make anybody
nervous enough to throw off their game.
So our job is to shake the
nerves off quicker than they do.
The best way to get in the
groove is to score the first point!
Sir!
I don't say this to flatter you guys. I really mean it.
You are all very talented.
We've got a great team!
Let's show this whole stadium...
These crows can still fly!
Whoa! Take's making a big speech!
I bet those jerks still call us by that dumb nickname...
Man, they don't know how wrong they are.
People call them "the wingless crows".
It's time to stand up and say...
That's not true anymore! The old warhorse is back!
Yes, sir!
Ah... Wait! Was that too cheesy?! I'll stop!
No, no, no! That was great!
Hey, what's an old warhorse?
I never understand what he says.
I think what Takeda was trying to say was
that we were known for being stronger in the past.
Can we just worry about today?!
Karasunooo, fight!
Fight!
Just get that first point, boys.
Don't lose your head... All
that practice is going to pay off.
And don't forget to watch those receives.
Yes, sir!
No way! That little number 10 is their middle-blocker?!
I bet he can't be any taller than 5 foot 5.
Why do they have those taller guys on the bench?
Hilarious... those guys look totally
confused... And well, I guess they should be.
The middle blocker position is usually all about height.
Is that short guy part of their starting lineup?
He's not a libero...
Laugh now, but you'll pay the price later.
Well, you would know, wouldn'tcha?
I am not letting him make a fool of me next time.
Here we go!
Your serve, Komaki!
Asahi!
Got it!
First shot... Where do I send it?
Who can intimidate the other team and boost our morale?
What is the best move to start the game?!
I know... perfect!
Awww yeahhhh!
Nice one-
Okay, you can stop now-
Shut up! Now!
Karasuno already got themselves a warning!
Wow, these guys are a freakin' joke.
Hey, don't sweat it! Switch gears and pay these guys back!
Yeah, take back that point!
Take it to 'em, Tanaka!
Pshhh, good luck, cue-ball!
Here!
Nice receive!
Ikejiri!
How did he even get to that ball?!
That libero's got reflexes!
Damn, it's too far from the setter!
Here, Asahi!
Alright, here comes the left! Triple up!
It's up to you, ace!
Damn, that's a grown-ass man!
I hear he's been held back 5 times!
He's gotta be at least 30!
That's crazy.
Try not to let it get to you, Asahi!
No way...
Did you see that momentum?
Uh-huh.
That's right, don't mess with our left side!
Oh, and... that's not the only
weapon we've got up our sleeves.
Don't you dare wimp out on me!
Same thing again, Tanaka!
I'm open!
You're all very talented... We've got a great team!
Let's show this whole stadium...
These crows can still fly!
He's flying.
Alright...
Prepare yourselves...
for the Karasuno warhorse!
It's finally time, guys!
Listen carefully, young one...
In Sendai, Miyagi prefecture...
When someone says "the old warhorse"...
They mean Karasuno!
Next Haikyu!! "Winner and loser."