One more time!
As soon as he hits the peak of his jump...
The ball needs to meet his palm!
Now I just take aim... And swing!
Damn. I sent it a little too high!
Thanks, captain!
Nice job covering Daichi!
It's in!
Front!
Nice one Inuoka!
Over here!
Here you go!
Ready to block, Hinata? One, two, three...
Gotcha!
Smooth cover, Kai!
Wow... both of these teams have got some
pretty diligent worker bees, don't they?
They're not flashy, but they
make themselves indispensable.
In the end, they can make or break a game.
Kenma! One more over here!
I don't care who says our offense is no
better than average... I'm the ace of Nekoma!
That's our point!
Dammit!
Look at that! Yamamoto's especially enthusiastic today!
I wonder if he's fired up because there's a
player on their side who reminds him of himself.
Or maybe he's inspired by that vicious
rivalry between Inuoka and that number 10?
What's wrong with Hinata and Kageyama?
Their attacks aren't lining up.
Because they're doing those crazy combo attacks
where Kageyama synchronizes with Hinata's movements...
But now they're trying to execute
normal quick attacks instead.
Hinata needs to work on his technique.
And the only way he can do that is
conditioning through repetition.
But if he gets the training and he learns when
to use both kinds of attacks, then eventually...
They won't be a demon and his iron club anymore.
They'll be a demon and a demon!
Serve's up!
Aw, crap! Should I hit it over or underhanded?
Ugh!
Noya, cover!
Aw yeah! The ace might come through in a pinch...
But he's not the only one! Leave it to me!
Hyaaaaa! Gah!
Whoa!
Those guys never stood a chance!
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeahhhh!
I'm not gonna get shut down either! I can do this!
Hinata...
Huh?
Kageyama said not to tense up, remember?
Keep your eyes open.
Y-yes, sir!
Fukunaga!
The buzzcut guy's moving this way! A quick attack!
Keep your eyes open.
What's number 7 doing?
Nice one-touch!
A chance ball!
Huh?
He's quick!
Nekoma's number 7's fast, too!
It's amazing to me how two opponents can
influence each other in moments like this.
Each one continually pushes
the other to new levels of power.
That makes them "worthy adversaries".
He made it through!
He did it!
Oh, heck yeah!
Grr... that was still too high.
One more!
Haaaaaaa!
Yeah!
Uh oh... If we're not careful, they might beat us to 20.
It's your serve, Inuoka!
Okay!
Huh?
So when lanky mcspikehead goes to the back
row, then rooster top comes to the front...
I liked playing with lanky, but...
This guy's kinda scary.
Inuoka's about 8 inches taller than you are
and you still gave him a run for his money...
Not too bad, small fry.
Ack!
Huh um.
Who you callin' small fry, small fry?!
C'mere.
Ah! Hey, lemme go!
We are going to do the usual move, now.
What? You mean the super hard-hitting one?
That's right.
Aw... can't we stick with the soft one?
I was just starting to get used to it...
Forget it.
We can't do that with him on the front row.
Why can't we?
Because I said, alright?! It's just a hunch.
Put it over!
Awesome! I never get tired of that feeling!
That was a smart choice just now.
Ha?
Hey, that's my bad, guys...
With that third-year middle blocker, I think
their special quick attack is more effective.
If they'd gone with a normal quick attack,
a skilled player like that would've
shut it down without batting an eye.
If you looked up "super", you would have a dictionary.
I bet you anything you'd see that kid's picture.
But that doesn't matter. We can still catch up.
Go for it, Hinata!
Nice receive!
Wow look at that... Everyone's all jumbled up!
Who's it gonna be?
They should leave it to their
most powerful attacker number 4!
Haaaaaa!
A back row attack!
The front three were a decoy!
They just shook off all our blockers!
That's a chance ball!
Who's gonna get it?
An a-quick!
Wow...
That was pretty quick, alright.
Would you look at that?
That attack has got first-rate stability.
Or maybe it just look stable compared to Hinata's moves.
Make it a good one!
Hah!
Ah jeez... Cover!
I'm open!
Asahi!
Who's gonna attack next?!
Another a-quick?!
He's not jumping!
What kind of move was that?
That's called a delayed spike...
You pretend that you're gonna jump for a quick.
It throws off the blocker's timing.
That kind of attack has been out of
popularity for a long time though...
I gotta admit I'm impressed they thought to
throw that one in right after their a-quick.
Not bad.
Nekoma made it to 20 points.
They're just 5 points away from taking it.
Son of a...
I've already used up both our timeouts and everything.
Is that sneaky bastard laughing at me?!
It's crazy.
Ever since their number 1 rotated to the front.
It would appear the proficiency of all
their attacks has been through the roof.
That's true... But look at it this way...
With half of our lineup being first-years,
you might consider us a level 1 team...
By that standard, Nekoma's a good 10 or 20 levels higher.
In other words...
They're a full-grown adult feline, and
we're a baby birdie fresh out of the nest.
Exactly. Good metaphor.
They've got a perfect balance of offense
and defense... There's no way we can compete.
At least not today. So... Guess that means...
All we can do is persist!
Hit 'em with our full power and don't let up!
So you want us to beat 'em into submission, boss?!
Wow, that really makes us sound like the bad guys.
Wahahaha! What's so bad about being the bad guys?!
We'll be just like the crows perched on the gates to hell.
Could you please stop that, coach, you're freaking me out!
Our attacks and receives may be
sloppy... But we're gonna make this happen!
Thes're the weapons we've got right
now, so use 'em the best you can!
Hit 'em with all the artillery we've got!
Hit 'em! Hit 'em... Hit 'em hard!
That was great! Nice block, Tsukishima!
Keep it up, Tsukki!
It's okay, Inuoka.
Sorry...
Karasuno catchin' up to 'em, now.
Yeah, it's pretty close. The mood
of the game has changed entirely.
Anybody gettin' scared, yet?
Nope!
Good to hear it... You just keep that ball in play.
Yes, sir!
Okay! Just one more point to tie!
Ah okay you guys keep it up!
Can't let 'em score any more.
Right!
Oh no!
This wasn't supposed to happen!
They've got match point!
One more point!
Yeah!
Dammit...
Look at 'em, they haven't even flinched!
I guess we're not much of a threat to them are we?
It's alright!
We're still sharp.
We can do this.
Aw yeah! We clawed our way up to a tie!
Don't get too excited, pal!
Grr... Things might get a little trickier
now that their number 3's in the front row.
Our crucial middle blockers
are working at a hundred percent.
Hinata's got the speeding finesse to
score points around their blocker...
And Asahi's our top player when it comes to offense.
With the two of them in the front row...
This is the perfect chance to turn this game around!
If we can get a point right now, then it's a deuce.
You're right...
Then they'd have to score another
point, giving us time to turn the tables!
It all depends on this ball!
Nice receive!
Hinata's quick attacks are still shaky. What do I do...?
Come on!
Aw, I thought we had it for sure!
Hold on...
Here it comes! It's a chance ball!
Agh! My bad, you guys!
Direct spike, Asahi!
No way!
Do it, Asahi!
Yah!
They got it again!
Oh no! It's Karasuno's chance ball again!
That's how it goes.
Huh?
You can make mistakes...
In fact, you can fail to make an attack at all...
But as long as that ball doesn't
hit the floor, you can't lose.
It's a chance ball!
Hinata's so amped right now...
It's just like when I first met him.
He's intense, larger-than-life...
There's nothing he wants more
than the ball out in front of him.
Well, here it comes!
That was it!
The truth is, it's not that
whoever has the best abilities, wins.
It's that whoever lets the ball
fall down on their side, loses.
And that... is what it means to keep the ball in play.
We win!
We didn't make any mistakes the whole time...
And we hit them with the best weapons we have.
But still... We couldn't beat 'em.
Those Nekoma kids have trained as
a team instead of as individuals.
They deserve this win.
One more time!
Another game!
Huh?
Please!
Sure! I was planning on it.
It wouldn't be a practice game if it
wasn't followed by a rematch or two.
Nice one!
Let's go!
One more!
Alright, now we've been thrashed without a doubt.
Yeah we should probably call it a day.
Look how tired they are.
One more match!
Again?! You haven't stopped moving since
you got here. Where'd you get all that energy?!
Give 'em a rest, ginger!
If they stay, they're gonna miss the last train!
Circle up!
Actually... your coach Ukai's grandfather
and I have been acquainted for a very long time.
We used to play practice games
with Karasuno every chance we got.
And it was always a pretty close contest back then too.
But then...
Retiring?
Yeah, I'm afraid old age is starting
to catch up with me. Sorry, my friend.
That's too bad...
But hey... either way, I'm sure we won't be
too hard up for opponents for practice games.
The thing about rivals is...
A good one is hard to find.
Poor old Ukai... after he retired, I heard that
he starting to have some serious health problems...
And I was certain Karasuno would
never make a comeback from that.
But you kids have got more potential
than I thought, especially with your offense.
That number 9 and number 10 combo is something else.
That attack's gonna be difficult to beat.
Those left players of yours
are a couple of powerhouses too.
It all comes down to how long you keep the ball in play.
Right!
You need a lot more practice working together
as a team, but you've all got outstanding promise.
With the appropriate training, you should
be able to improve by leaps and bounds.
Seeing that really does my old heart good.
I'm glad to have a worthy rival.
I'm sure we'll see you again at the nationals.
In that shining, sprawling gymnasium
packed with thousands of cheering spectators...
Amidst the whirl of excitement and intensity.
The ultimate trashcan showdown...
The real "cats versus crows" faceoff!
Yes, sir!
Alright! Let's get all this stuff put away!
Right!
You little turd!
Y-yeah, you are!
Come on, let's pick up the pace!
Hey!
Yeah? What the hell do you want, dirtbag?!
You lookin' to get yourself dealt
with?! Come on at me, city boy!
Actually... it's uh... The thing is...
Huh?
Your... your manager... Could you maybe, like...
Could you tell me what your manager's name is?
A-choo.
Grrr... you son of aaahh!
You stay away from her... She is
our manager! If you even look at her...
I'll yank that ugly lint brush right out of your skull!
Don't worry... I'm too much of a coward to talk to her.
Fukunaga, could you mop over there?
Got it.
Yaku, you mop, too.
Okay...
Kiyoko.
Huh!
Her name is Kiyoko Shimizu.
That's perfect! Her name means "clear spring water"!
Yeah, it really does suit her, doesn't it?
It took me a long time to work up the guts, too,
so I know how you feel, but...! Check this out...
You want her to flat-out ignore you...
It's awesome.
Hwaaaaaa!
No way, man! I don't think I can handle that!
You know something? You're not so bad, brother!
Huh? Yeah, same to you. I'm uh... Taketora Yamamoto.
And I'm Ryunosuke Tanaka.
Heh.
How long have you been playing volleyball? Who
taught you how to play? How long have you been a setter?
Did you come up with that feint yourself? Have
you been training? Have you ever hit a brick wall?
If so, what did you do about it?
He's growly and scary like a saber-tooth tiger!
That's who he meant.
That was incredible, Shoyo!
"Swoosh!" "Vroom!" "Pow!" Oh, I'm Inuoka, first-year!
And you're really tall, but you ran fast like "zoom!"
And then "kaboom!"
You were so cool when you were like "blam!"
So were you! It was like "sha-ping!"
Thanks! And I've never seen anybody "fwop!" Like that!
It wasn't like "fwop!" It was more like a "da-dooom"!
Do you... understand that?
Nah, they sound like a couple of toddlers.
But you know... maybe you should try goofing
off once in a while instead of acting all stoic.
That's not one of my strong suits.
You sound like an old man.
I-I'm so sorry! I should have been moving faster!
What are you apologizing for?
This was all my fault. Please forgive me!
Great, he's scaring the first years...
They can't see what a softie he is.
In a way, they uh... Kinda look
like father and son from here, huh?
More like a scared kid and his kidnapper.
Um... why is your libero staring at me?
Oh, sorry...
Maybe if you just try to avert
your eyes he'll leave you alone...
Hey! I thought your receives were really great!
Our team's ace is pretty strong...
And I've never seen anybody actually
retrieve spikes from him before.
Your team has killer receiving skills and a lot of
that is because you have so much talent as a libero!
So well done!
But I won't lose next time! Count on it!
Ah! Hey... Wait! Let him respond!
Um... sorry, he's kind of intense.
He's dangerous.
Huh?
He's got lots of skill as a libero too,
but he doesn't let himself get any rest.
He just keeps going, looking onward and upward.
So he's a threat.
Coach Nekomata!
Thank you for making such a long trip to play with us.
Not at all, it was my pleasure.
I'm sure it's hard to get someone to play
practice games with when you don't have connections.
You had my phone ringing off the hook!
And at one point you even threatened
to come irritate me in person!
I-I'm sorry!
Anyway... enthusiasm breeds more enthusiasm.
You don't have much experience, yet...
But keep your nose to the
grindstone, and the kids'll follow you.
Good work.
Thank you so much, sir!
I want to see you get it together, too, Keishin...
After all, we played three games
today and you didn't take a single set.
Then next time we play, I'll
kick your ass in every set, old man.
Ooooh? Is that so? Well, I think you're full of hot air.
P-please don't provoke him, coach...
It's his own fault he looks just like his gramps!
That makes no sense!
Ah uh hang on!
I thought you said you'd only
stay on as coach for the Nekoma game-
You expect me to take that lying down?!
Ah?
I'll get revenge in a big venue with a crowd watching!
We'll be reunited soon, comrade!
Okay... that's weird.
Yeah I know... Just don't look.
You won't win next time.
Oh really? Because I think I will.
Cut it out. You're being weird!
The next practice game isn't gonna go down like that!
Good, otherwise it's not much of a practice game, is it?!
Not them too!
Hey come on, really?!
Kenma!
Shoyo.
When I first met you on the street...
You said you didn't really
like volleyball that much, right?
Oh... yeah.
How about now? Didn't it feel good to win?
Eh... it was the same as always.
Next time...
I'll make you want to win really bad...
And then we'll win!
And then...
you'll say "Man, that was a blast! I hate losing!"
And the way you talk about the game'll change for good.
Huh...
Cool...
Well... I'll be waiting.
If that had been a real match...
Hum?
We'd have been done...
As soon as we lost that first game... that's it.
Yeah, I know.
It's good to know you've thought about it.
Huh?
We do have a real game coming up...
The Inter-High Preliminaries, remember?
Now let's hurry back home...
We need to do some serious
thinking about today's practice game.
Then we get back to work!
Yes, sir!
By the way, Kageyama, did you ask their setter
about that technique where he feints with his eyes?
No.
Awww...
Were you too shy to talk to him or what?
What did you say to me?!
Awoooo. Jeez it was just a question!
Next Haikyu!! "The tough opponents"!