When I started middle school, I met a great athlete.
Seeing him play made me think
middle school must be the big leagues.
But it wasn't middle school that was impressive.
No, it was him.
If I can surpass him...
I'll be the best setter in the prefecture!
Wow, check out Karasuno's setter.
Most first-years can't stand up to Oikawa can they?
Yeah, it's like clash of the Superstar Setters.
That was sweet! You're just as good as the Great King!
Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow!
I swear... Even if I face someone who's better overall...
I'm still the best setter.
Doesn't matter, you're up to serve now.
You'll be in the back...
So you can't do it again, right?
Setter dumps are illegal from there.
I know!
I'll do it when I'm up front again, alright?!
Serve it up, Kageyama!
Dammit!
That's out.
He put some real strength behind that.
Somebody sign him up for the baseball team.
Let it go!
I'm sorry!
Well then. Shall I show you boys how it's done?
Oooooooolé.
He hit it right to him!
Straight on... Nope, curve.
He just controlled an Oikawa serve!
That libero's incredible!
Aw... that's no fair!
How about that? He's got some skill.
How did he retrieve that?!
It's like it was nothing to him!
I know, right?
Bring it!
Number 10!
Yeah!
Did you see that? Over on the right?
Uh-huh. Reminds me of how Nekoma's
setter could throw people off with a look.
Those magical sets of his should be illegal... Am I right?
I'm kinda surprised Nishinoya
could save that one... Wait...
Unless you think maybe Oikawa sent the ball
that way by accident; Could that be what happened?
Nah... He meant it to be for Nishinoya.
If he hadn't been able to save that one, it would
have done some serious damage to our team's morale.
You got it!
I think that's probably what he was going for.
That was close... You really saved our asses, Nishinoya.
Hey uh I'm sorry... It's
just... they keep confusing me.
Well, Karasuno did a number on Date Tech, after all...
Just give it a few minutes or so.
It's not going to be much longer now.
Anyway, I pity you.
You were Kageyama's partner... Now he's gone
and replaced you. And with that little neophyte.
No, it's okay...
You bet it is...
So what if Kageyama saw you as... "just a
subpar servant"? That was back in middle school!
So what if we don't have a
legendary quick attack like theirs?
Let's show him he never should
have driven you away, Kindaichi.
You're clear to jump.
Um... Yes sir!
Alright, Tanaka!
Do your best!
Watari!
Okay!
Nice receive!
Center Ball!
An A-Quick!
Kin-Dai-Chi! Kin-Dai-Chi! Geeeeet thaaaaat point!
Am I crazy?
Because I think their Number 12 is jumping higher
than he did in the practice game. I mean, right?
Your serve, Iwa!
Sorry, cover!
I got it!
Give it here!
A-ha.
I need a time-out, sir.
Wait why is Seijoh calling a time out? This is weird.
Yeah, didn't seem like Karasuno
was about to take the momentum.
Okay... pay attention to his choice of words.
"Bring it.. And "Give me."
Are you serious? Did they already figure it out?
How'd they crack it so fast?
My first thought was, "Wow, that little guy
screams something every time he goes in to hit a set."
I just assumed he was an idiot.
But then I noticed, when they do that insane quick,
he'll say "bring it here" or "bring
it" something with the word "bring".
And for a normal quick...
He says "give it here" instead.
Yes.
However... he is their greatest decoy.
And this is his strength...
They want us to lock onto him...
So we're going to employ a strategy to counter that.
Whenever the shorty says "bring
it", we'll put one mark on him...
If he says "give me", we'll wait to
see where the ball goes before we jump.
Okay?
Sir!
One thing though... We called a time-out pretty
early in the game for seemingly no reason at all...
Won't they realize we're onto their game plan?
So let them realize it! That
can only benefit us in the end...
If those Karasuno clowns think we've got their number...
it's sure to make their poor setter lose his mind.
Hey! That dumbfounded look doesn't suit you, dude.
Nah, that's where you're wrong...
I see this fool make this face at school all the time.
Mostly when he can't make a decision
on what to get from the vending machine.
I-I don't do that!
Anyway, Noya... I can't believe you hit that serve!
Well, I had to deal with it back
in middle school. So I'm used to it.
It was a killer serve whenever it actually went through...
but the success rate was pretty
low, and it wasn't as controlled.
He must have really been working on it.
It takes quite a lot to stay in the
top 4... more than just great setters...
or only one player with some
above-average serving technique.
Don't let 'em off easy... Give 'em hell!
Yeah!
D'oh!
Did you just say "d'oh"?!
It happens; Just keep your head up!
Excellent, guys, let's set the trap...
I assume you know where you should be aiming, Kindaichi.
Yeah!
One point!
Behind any strong setup...
is a solid initial receive.
Kindaichi's serve!
That's bizarre...
It didn't seem to be a particularly
powerful serve that time, did it?
These are tricky.
Wait a second...
Are they shooting for when the
setter moves up from the back row?
That guy's not as good at serving as Oikawa,
so why's the other team having
such a hard time hitting the ball?
Ahem! Yeah, well, here's the thing, ladies.
When the setter is in the back row,
he can't get as close to the net as the
people in the front row until the serve goes up.
That's why he has to move very
quickly to get to the net side position
the second the other team puts the ball in the air.
There's a tiny delay in the
receive as the players intersect,
which makes it easy for mistakes to happen.
But as long as everyone knows where the
serve is headed... they can still get it done.
Nice receive!
Yeah!
Who knew this game could be so complicated?
Thanks, random old guy!
Wait what?! Aw man...
Heh.
Oikawa's in the front row now.
Watch number 3! We'll have to
look out for that setter dump.
Just serve!
Damn, this is a lot of pressure.
There's already a 4-point gap.
Like the coach was saying, these guys know what's
in our bag of tricks. We need to switch things up!
Nice receive!
Setter dump!
You shouldn't rush a setter dump,
you know... It's too easy to shut down.
Haaaaaaa... bam!
Yeah!
Woooo!
Just 4 more points to turn this around!
Yeah, yeah!
You are so positive!
And it's really kinda getting on my nerves.
Give it here!
We'll wait to see where the ball goes before we jump.
That's it!
Yes!
They figured it out...
Kageyama's serve!
You got this!
This time, I won't miss!
It's too far forward!
Good.. He adjusted for a softer serve!
Damn!
You don't honestly think I'll let you get away with that?
Kageyama made the first touch! Now he can't make the set!
Here!
No way!
He turned a tight spot into an opportunity...
The kid sure is cool under pressure.
He's not thinking like the other guys.
It's okay, guys!
Yeah, keep it up... uh-oh.
The next serve... is Oikawa.
Nothing shakes a team's confidence more
than when their big talker suddenly goes quiet.
Oooooooolé.
Shake it off! Get the next one!
The best way to build pressure is
ruining several serve-receives in a row.
First step is silencing that loud skinhead.
Then the ace.
Breaking the two left players
who are crucial to the attack...
will nullify the decoy's efforts.
That was quick! Why is Karasuno
already calling a time out?
They probably did it because
Seijoh has all the momentum...
And if they can't fix that soon,
they'll never be able to catch up.
They keep going after that same guy. Sucks to be him.
Look... Send the ball to the setter... And if
you can't do that... then at least keep it up high.
Yes, sir!
And you, Mr. Serious Pants.
Yeah that setter dump...
What the hell were you thinkin'?
I'm sorry... I snapped.
Okay, as long as you know...
But it's more than that, though.
It's good to show our opponents that we
have a variety of offensive techniques.
But once they're onto you,
it's easy for them to stop a dump.
You have to be extremely careful about how you time those.
Sir!
Listen, do not forget who the opponent is
here... It's Aoba-Johsai, not just Oikawa.
And you're not the only one fighting them. It's all of us.
Yes, sir.
Oikawa!
Let's go!
Oooooooolé.
There it goes!
You're doing fine! Just keep the ball in the air, Tanaka!
Uh-huh.
Tanaka!
Hey, cover!
Number 5!
Tanaka!
Time!
Right!
It's kinda early to use up both
of our time outs, don't you think?
Then again, we've gotta do something
to get the momentum on our side.
Yeah, that's the thing about volleyball...
Everything hinges on keeping the ball in play.
Nothing's worse than the guilt
from repeatedly screwing up.
Yeah...
And then they add insult to
injury by going after him like that.
Number 5 is having a rough day.
Maybe I should say something to him?
After all, Tanaka's always got an encouraging
word for me whenever I start to doubt myself...
Yeah, I will.
Hey...
I'm so stupid!
I'm sorry!
Tanaka! Some things you just can't help, okay?
That last set was ridiculous, AND they triple-blocked you!
I should've followed through...
Shut it! I didn't call for the ball!
I just... I lost my focus!
And I'll be kicking myself
like hell when the game is over!
I'm not gonna drag you guys down!
And I won't have you wasting your
time... crying over MY stupid mistakes!
I'll... do better.
Ha! The fact that you can say
that is good enough for me, buddy!
Uh.. Thanks.
Make sure to use both your arms and
your feet, or it'll bounce right off you.
You could stand to be more
like Tanaka; You know that, Asahi?
I'm doing my best here, okay?!
Huh... this is the second time I've noticed it.
Oikawa is looking really off.
Yeah, well I heard it's his little ritual
to keep himself from breaking concentration.
A lot of teams call time-outs just
to throw off their opponent's groove.
We'll see if it works.
Bring it on!
It's all you, Oikawa!
Man, he's really got his head in the game...
It's up to you guys to take control now.
Ooooooooolé!
If it hits the ground, we're dead!
Tanaka!
Crap!
Don't let it fall!
That's what I'm talking about!
And in the best possible spot.
Here!
Get it, Hanamaki!
Nice receive!
Someone cover!
Left, now!
Tanaka!
Tanaka makes his share of mistakes.
And he takes the bait every
time someone pushes his buttons...
But...
His power's second only to Asahi's...
and he's got the mental fortitude to keep trucking and
play his best, even when he's near his breaking point.
No doubt about it...
He could be an ace.
Whoa!
Looks like the bald kid's got it goin' on, now!
He pulled the rug right out from under 'em.
Yeaaaaaaah!
Not bad!
Well, that's alright; I suppose
I can let go of a point or two.
Whoo, that was the best look at a block I ever had!
I just mean... sometimes I can see the other team's block
in midair, clear as day, like it's in slo-mo.
With a bright ray of light shining through it.
That sounds so cool!
You'll see one day!
It's your serve, jackass!
Right!
Their flow's been broken.
And there's still time...
We can come back!
Nice one-touch!
Chance ball, baby! Woo!
Bring it here!
Gotcha!
He's too fast even when we expect him!
Look, you... Please don't tell me
you still can't beat that kid's sets.
Kageyama's? Of course I can't...
You really think I can do a pinpoint set like that?
Please don't be mad!
I may not have as much talent, but I'm more in tune
with my teammates' capabilities than he'll ever be.
So, I'm just as good a setter as he is.
It got past the block again.
Aw, don't look so shocked, little guy.
Striking right above the blockers is
what Kindaichi does best, after all.
Forward!
7 points. That's way too big a gap!
Bring it!
Wow, they're really bringing their
A-game today, aren't they? I'm impressed!
We do not need to deal with a double-block right now.
If we're not careful, they'll take back the momentum...
I have to shake one of those blockers.
During my second year of high school, I heard about
a middle schooler who was a legend in his own time.
"The King of the Court?"
I thought. "He must be wonderful at what he does."
But when I saw him play, I knew
the name meant something else.
He's got power, and talent, and he craves
victory more intensely than anyone I know.
All those qualities make up Tobio Kageyama's strengths.
But...
they're also his weaknesses.
No man is an island, little Tobio...
You may have been at this for two months now, but...
It takes longer than that to break a bad habit.
Nice kill, Hanamaki!
Yeah! Way to go!
Woo!
Hey, Hinata!
It's time to change it up... Do you remember the signals?
Remember? You mean we're gonna use
the signals that we talked about?!
Now that's a block!
Ah! It's mine!
One more time!
Y'know... I've been watching Karasuno's
attacks... I think they're gradually speeding up.
I don't like how fast this is going.
We don't have any time-outs left.
Slow it down, fellas! Stay cool out there!
That's not very wise of them...
They're so desperate to outrun our
blockers... they're valuing speed above all else.
But they're losing their accuracy.
Whether they realize it or not, as their speed
increases... the number of mistakes will increase as well.
You really are something, Tobio Kageyama.
No one but you could pull off
that combo move with the short kid...
But it's not all about him.
Don't you think your Number 3
would have what he needs to overcome
our blockers if you would only set
to him a little slower from now on?
Wouldn't it help if Four-Eyes actually
trusted your sets when he hit them?
Every spiker has his own unique quirks.
The player who can take those quirks
and use them to their potential is...
a true setter.
This is bad! The gap isn't shrinking!
I'll do whatever it takes to fix this!
Over the net! Push it back!
You know, Kageyama just doesn't
seem like himself anymore, does he?
Nice receive!
I won't lose this game! I refuse to!
I have to win and stay on the court!
Get ready!
Nice follow thru!
Chance ball!
Oikawa's got horse sense, and
he puts in a decent effort...
But compared to a wiz-kid like Kageyama
who's two years younger than he is...
He's got skill, but he's far from a genius.
Still, with the way things are currently, I can
confidently say that the more proficient setter...
is Oikawa.
A swap? Right now?
Man, that's brutal...
It's hard to keep your head up when
you have to leave the court like that.
How would you know, Shimada? You're a a benchwarmer.
Next Haikyu!! "The Talented Upperclassman."