K-Kageyama! What are you plotting?!
Must be something evil!
What's your problem?!
Yeah, he's not plotting anything!
I think this is just the first
time he's ever tried to smile!
You didn't mean that the way it sounded, right?
Oh, screw you, Hinata!
Our little grump is finally showing his feelings!
Time to change it up...
Do you remember the hand signals?
You ready?
Oh hey, did you hear about the signals from Sugawara?
Yeah, he told me.
All right!
Let's go all in!
You got it!
Let's go, go-go-go-go SeiJOH!
Go, go-go-go-go SeiJOH!
It's been pretty nerve-wracking huh?
Trust me, nobody knows that more than me.
What do you mean?
Up until last year's tournament, I
didn't get to play in many official games.
You know, because the third-year players
had all the seniority and everything...
And now when I have the seniority, Kageyama
actually has more court experience than I do.
And yet he still lets himself
get all worked up... So weird.
Well... looks like it's already his turn to serve.
You think he'll be able to hold his own?
Alright, Kageyama!
You got this, bro!
Kageyama looks happy, doesn't he?
Sure does.
Well, hopefully that'll be good for us.
What do you mean?
I've just been thinking...
every player seems to have the same sort of
pride when it comes to being put in a game.
Great players like him and average Joes too.
Kageyama! Don't stress, okay?
Oh... Nevermind... He's fine.
We just need one point!
Yeah!
Watari!
A service ace!
The libero messed it up!
Now they're tied!
Gotcha!
I'm sorry.
It's okay, just keep trying!
Up high!
Hm?
He wants a high 10!
We did it!
Wait, that's not the Kageyama I know.
Nope.
Someone cover!
They're scattered!
It's coming back!
It's a chance ball!
"Bring"?
Or "give"?
Which one?
He didn't say anything!
Man, I still can't believe how
crazy Karasuno's quick-attack is!
There we go! Finally turned it around!
Sugawara's nice...
He always compliments me when I do good things!
Hey, Hinata.
Proud... of you...
Thank you...?
Alright, Hinata's really in his element now! And
Kageyama looks just like a fish in water out there.
Well his name does mean flying fish...
Oh great.
Hey... let's all relax.
Don't panic and let yourselves
get thrown off like they did.
Once we gain back a point, we're golden.
Right!
Hey... you. Stop posing like that... It pisses me off.
You're not helping!
Got it!
Good one, Iwa!
Looks like Kageyama's gotten his rhythm back...
No, there's more to it than that.
I should have lined up a bit closer to the sideline.
Before, his focus was glued on our blockers... but
now he's paying a little more attention to his teammates.
Don't hold back now, boys...
If we don't take this set, we're screwed.
Turbo-charge that freak quick.
Have some o' this!
Nice receive!
Kageyama told Hinata that he's only
the greatest whenever he's around.
But...
it goes both ways.
Thanks to that combo attack...
they're both the greatest!
Sweet! Our guys made it to 20 points first!
This is the final stretch.
Alright, that's 20 points.
And now...
the real challenge is about to begin.
Hey, since when is this all
about Tsukishima versus Kageyama?!
C'mon, Hinata!
Here goes!
Look out!
Chance ball!
Kageyama!
Any thoughts Asahi?
A little higher maybe?
Sure!
Oh. Seijoh's finally calling time out.
You know, whenever number 10 goes
back and number 11 goes up front,
Karasuno doesn't do as many center attacks.
True... Though that might just be because
Kageyama doesn't like the tall angry fella.
They weren't communicating during
yesterday's game, and today isn't any better...
I think of all Karasuno's spikers, the beanpole is the
one Kageyama finds the most difficult to connect with.
Please remind me to never become friends with you, Oikawa.
Why is that?!
You point out people's weaknesses.
Oh gimme a break I'm just trying to strategize here!
I think he talks to all the spikers so he can get
a feel for their emotional state during the game...
Helps him decide how to set. Because everyone's different.
What?
I can't read this guy at all.
All I know is that looking at him pisses me off!
Kageyama.
Just start with a conversation...
Try to be more direct.
You need to communicate with him okay.
Okay.
Got it!
Nice receive!
They got it... Watch that counter!
Tsukishima seems to be having
trouble hitting the ball now.
They just caught up!
Ah crap, man, we're tied!
It's break time.
I know I need one!
Takeda!
Right!
So uh... do they need more attack power or what?
Karasuno's in kind of a tight spot
now that their number 10's not up front.
Hey, what's with you guys?! You need to relax!
You're all doing fine! So just chill out!
Okay...!
Hey.
Was that last set decent enough for you, punk?
Why do you sound like Tanaka all of a sudden?
What was that, punk?!
I hate your sets because it's like you're forcing
people to play it your way instead of their own.
Again with this, Tsukishima?
Come on, this isn't the time
to be bickering like little kids!
What are you saying?
I like to do things my way...
So please be consistent.
Um... what's wrong?
I think... whenever Kageyama sets an A-Quick for
Tsukishima, he's also signaling its hitting course.
A position near the setter means cross-court.
And away is turn-swing.
Obviously, Kageyama places the ball
wherever he thinks the spike should be going.
But Tsukishima probably has a hard time
hitting anything like that.
You're not the only one out there thinking, you know.
Whether it's about defense formation
or deciding what attacks to use,
everyone on the team is always thinking.
Hinata was able to figure out
how to do those quick attacks.
So even that poor dummy is out there using his brain...
Well maybe not that much.
Did you say "not much"?! I think all the time, jerk!
Now, now...
That's fair.
Wait, what did you just say? Are you sick?
Let's try it your way... Maybe it'll work out for us.
Tsukishima must not be used to dealing with that
kind of directness. He doesn't know how to take it.
Good job, Noya!
I like to do things my way...
So please be consistent.
Dammit!
Y'see that?! He hit the empty zone right behind the block!
That was kickass!
I'm actually kinda jealous!
I thought he was going to spike it at the last second.
He's almost got a glow about him
when he gets past the blockers, huh?
A glow?
Uh-huh, that's how Tsukki looks
when he's really into the game.
You've got a chance ball!
Another trick!
That was close!
Heads up! Chance ball!
That Number 11's got game.
I guess so...
But it looks like he's just trying to
avoid confrontation with Seijoh's high-block.
You're right, Karasuno keeps creating diversions.
Yeah well... He can't run from those blockers forever.
Yeah!
Nice, Matsu!
Dammit... they already took it back.
Center, 11!
Again? I'll get it this time!
Nice receive, Watari!
I've got it!
Center!
Good work, Tanaka!
Ah, dammit.
They better be careful right here.
This play will make or break it.
It's up to the ace.
Everyone on the team is always thinking.
Number 11 again!
No, wait! Don't move! Stay where you are!
Yeah!
AWW YEAH!
Tsukishima, you magnificent bastard!
Nice one!
Get out of my face.
We were anticipating a fakeout, so our
defense was too far forward... They got us.
Uh.. Gugu... gugu... good job...
Don't hurt yourself, Kageyama.
Wow... He actually complimented Tsukishima.
Kageyama is changing, no doubt about it.
What are you, emotionally constipated?!
Set point for Karasuno!
This is crazy.
One more point!
You can do it!
Not gonna happen!
I-wai-zu-mi! I-wai-zu-mi! Geeet thaaaat point!
It's alright! Look... the last point is no different
than all the others you've scored; You can win!
Well done!
Our last tournament.
The end of middle school.
Hey, you have a genuine smile for once.
What? My smiles are always honest and delightful!
If you have to say they are,
that means they're probably not.
I've never gotten one of these before...
so why wouldn't I be happy, huh?
Toru Oikawa laughs everything off... but
there was a time when he couldn't do that.
He had a sturdy build.
Plus he was smart and swift.
And he just kept getting better and
better, especially after middle school.
But still, there was always a
brick wall standing in his way.
Shiratorizawa, now known as the best in the prefecture,
had just brought in Ushiwaka, their new heavy.
Why can't I beat them?!
They cleaned the floor with us.
We didn't even win a set.
We wanted to keep climbing and reach new heights...
but we kept getting defeated until our third year...
And then...
I'm Tobio Kageyama from Akiyama Elementary School...
I've played this game for years... Nice to meet you.
A genius swooped in to take our place.
There was no mistaking his overwhelming talent.
Kageyama always looked so overjoyed
just to be playing volleyball.
His fire and his technical expertise
put him miles ahead of the rest of us.
He can play just about any position we need him to,
but he'll eventually be a setter.
Yeah.
After that, Oikawa started to
push himself harder than ever.
You're working way too hard!
Didn't the coach just say that yesterday?
You'll be useless to us if you get hurt!
Come on, it's time to call it a day!
He was completely losing his cool.
During a practice game, his constant combo
mistakes made it clear he was lacking composure.
Which led to...
Kageyama, you're in!
Sir!
Okay. Go in.
Forward!
Got it!
Nice cover!
Nice kill!
Serve's up!
Oikawa?
Can you maybe teach me how to serve?
Get away from me...
Go away...
Just go away!
Don't come any closer!
Get a hold of yourself, you dumb-ass!
Sorry...
Kageyama. We're all done for today.
O-Okay.
We swapped you out today because
you needed to cool your head.
Give yourself a little credit, alright?!
I can't do that!
Not if I'm not good enough to bring down Shiratorizawa!
If I want to win and go to Nationals,
I need to work as hard as I can!
All you ever say is "me, me, me"!
What, do you think you're the only person on this team?!
You listen to me, dumb-ass!
You'd better stop acting like your performance is the
only thing that matters or I'll headbutt you in the face!
You already did!
I'm sure none of us has what it
takes to defeat Ushiwaka one-on-one...
But still...
That's why there's 6 people on a volleyball court!
Who cares about that amazing first-year... or Ushiwaka?!
At the end of the day, the best team of 6 wins, dumb-ass!
The best group of 6 wins, huh?
Whoa... Sorry, I must have hit you too hard.
I can't even describe how I feel right now.
It's like I'm invincible.
Hey Iwa, is "dumb-ass" the only insult you know?
You want another headbutt to the face?
Perfect! One more point!
How about that? Oikawa seems to be over his funk now.
Good.
Hey, Oikawa... could you teach me how to serve-toss?
Yeah right, in your dreams, dummy!
Stop picking on the first-year, Oikawa.
In our last middle school tournament...
we won the first set against Shiratorizawa Middle School.
We ended up winning 2nd place to them.
Oikawa got the best setter award.
Second place... That means our
spikers gave it their very best.
Yeah, but it also means Ushiwaka's even better.
Damn it...
I'll beat him...
I swear I will!
I'll humiliate that whole team!
Yeah, same here!
And you too dummy!
I don't know what high school
you'll be at in a few years...
but I swear, as soon as I get a chance,
I'm kicking your ass, you hear me?!
Don't talk all big with a runny nose.
You need a tissue?
Shut up!
Let's go, go-go-go-go SeiJOH!
Go, go-go-go-go SeiJOH!
Let's go!
Serve!
Heads up!
Uh-oh, time for Oikawa's serve.
You're up against the guy who's second on your shit-list.
So make it count, alright?
Oh, I plan to.
Oooooooolè.
Yours!
There it goes!
Crap, it's heading right back to Seijoh!
If he'd messed up that serve, it would've
cost them the whole set! This guy's good!
It's a chance ball!
It came right back to the setter.
The quick attacks from the center
give them a higher success rate.
I knew it, that's exactly what I would do!
Oikawa's back's against the wall,
so I'm guessing his next move is...
send it to Iwa!
Yeah!
No way!
Karasuno just took back the set!
Dammit, I'll kill that little shit!
Chill out.
Hey, what's so funny, jerk?!
You wanna fight or somethin'?!
Violence doesn't look good on you, Iwa.
Relax. I only threaten you, and you know I won't hit you.
You know...
that last quick from the center
was one of our best attacks.
Yeah?
Yet Kageyama was able to stop it.
He predicted I would send it left.
Do you know what that means?
He wasn't behaving robotically like usual...
No, he noticed our weak spot near the end...
not to mention our unbreakable bond of trust.
We don't have that and you know it.
My point is, he just made a solid judgment call.
That other setter...
What did he teach our Tobio?
That little self-serving dictator is
on his way to becoming a real leader.
What is this feeling? I'm incredibly irritated, and yet...
Set 3! It's time to start!
Let's do this.
Time for the final set!
I'm fired up! This isn't like me at all.
Yeah, I'll say.
What about my icy-cool image?
Forget about your damn image!
Next Haikyu!! "The Play to Change The Flow."