Oooh yeah!
That's our dynamic duo!
Well... Good try, man!
Hang in there!
Hm... looks like they're not doing that quick attack.
The one where he closes his eyes.
They still need work...
But it looks to me as if they're able to
execute a normal quick attack now instead.
Hm?
It's sloppy, but at least they've
got control over the trajectory.
That's a big difference...
Those kids must have had quite a productive practice game.
They've learned their weapons, built them up, and figured
out how to use the right attack for the right situation.
Hmmm... well, how about that?
They used to rely on raw power to score their points.
Now they're getting smart.
One more!
Yeah, but they still make a lot of rookie mistakes.
Can't argue with that.
I'm sorry!
But receives are the one thing
you can't perfect overnight.
Your serve, Chaya!
One more!
Noya!
Yeah!
Are these guys actually about to win the set?
Yeah, that libero's not playing around, dude...
And not just that...
I think that guy with the stubble is
really helping support Kageyama's sets.
It's alright.
Yeah... let's just get ourselves a point.
Okay!
One more, guys!
Give us a good serve, Hinata!
Yes, sir!
We got this!
Yeah!
We did it!
It was our biggest tournament in middle school.
We won the first game by dumb luck.
But in the second round, we were up
against a team we knew we couldn't beat.
And just as we were giving up,
do you remember what you said?
They're middle schoolers just like we are...
There's no reason we can't win this!
We still have to try, okay?!
Wow, you just never give up, do you?
I can't give up now...
It's my last tournament.
They're just middle schoolers too, huh?
Yeah, good point!
And plus we just cleared our first round one!
He's right! Let's win our first round two!
Yeah!
Our spirits were high,
but obviously that wasn't
enough to make us suddenly improve.
I'm sorry...
No. We're gonna take the next point!
We lost that game, but we were expecting it...
So it didn't really get us down that much.
Actually, we were kind of relieved, because it meant,
we wouldn't have to do any more
intense training the next day.
But you... you were the only one who was upset by it...
I didn't understand why, but part of me was
a little jealous that you could feel that way.
Yes!
Um... are you okay?
Do it, Hinata!
It's all yours.
Hey, very nice receive, Tamagawa!
Come to the left, here!
Here, Ikejiri!
So much for the "wingless crows."
That's not what I was expecting at all.
They're on a different level!
Em...
Whenever there's a net between you, it
doesn't matter what anybody's ranking is anymore.
We can't win unless... we try.
Er...
Well, I just mean... it's like my friend used to say...
Time to go.
Yeah.
Jeez, I should've known it wouldn't
be as persuasive coming from me.
I totally blew it...
Man...
Kageyama's up!
He got an ace!
Looks like Karasuno's starting to get in
the groove after winning that first set, huh?
Got it!
Damn...
That's high!
We did it...
Come on. It's one point. Is it that big a deal?
Of course it is! This is the kind
of play that could change everything!
Maybe you're right.
You guys...
Can't win unless we try... you know?
And we're not giving up!
Even small-time teams know they need to stick to it.
Let's win this!
Yeah!
Look out!
Get it, Yui!
Right!
Let it go!
L, u, c, k, y! L, u, c, k, y, lucky!
Even if you're not confident that you can win...
And even if everyone around
you says that it's impossible...
No matter what...
"We can't allow ourselves to say 'never!'"
Heads up!
Let's go!
Get it!
We did it!
Don't let it get to you.
It's my fault we missed that, Yui.
Sorry! I just...
Can't stop messing us up!
Now's not the time for that stuff.
On your feet... It's not over!
Alright!
Match point, and it's in their favor...
It won't hurt Karasuno at all if they lose the next point.
But for us...
One more point.
This isn't over!
Bring it, Karasuno!
Sakurai!
Ikejiri!
We haven't lost yet!
This is not the end!
Oh here!
Yeah!
Damn you!
Next time... you're all mine!
Right! Take it back!
Yeah!
Whoa, they're taking this seriously.
No one else in this whole gymnasium is
concerned with us or sees us as a threat.
The only team playing us for keeps...
is them.
Get your head out of the clouds, dumbass! It's time to-
We won.
Hm?
Uh-huh...
So... that means we get to play again.
Yeah... that's how it works.
We won.
We won...
We won!
That means we can play some more volleyball!
We get to stay in the court for a little while longer!
That little guy's been dying to play a real game...
And now he's finally getting his first taste of victory.
Yeah.
What're they thinking?
Don't these amateurs know they have
another game to play this afternoon?
Hm?
Well... they were gonna win that game either way...
They should've saved up their energy for the next one-
I disagree.
They gave it their all...
But we didn't see that special quick attack, did we?
The other game's done too... And Date Tech dominated.
Ahhh... Karasuno versus Date Tech.
Now that's more interesting.
We should go... if we miss our next game, it won't matter.
Aw, don't cry! It's fine!
I'm sorry... they went after all my
serves. I gave them so many points...
The point is to keep the ball in play...
They were just better at that than us... so we lost.
It's not anyone's fault!
Captain... the teacher needs you.
Okay... I'll be right back.
Michimiya's really... strong.
She practiced the hardest...
But she doesn't seem all that upset.
She is.
Hm?
It's true. She just puts on a brave
face whenever she's in front of us.
It's almost time for the next game.
But I'm sure, as soon as she has a moment to herself,
it'll all hit her.
I didn't do too bad, really...
I didn't miss many practices.
After I saw the game on TV, I said I'd
be playing to represent Japan one day.
Even though I said it jokingly, part of me was serious.
But once I got into all that resistance
training, my enthusiasm fizzled out.
Is this it?
It's only June... How could it end so quickly?
If only... I'd worked just a little
harder to improve while I had the chance.
If only I'd pushed myself more during practice.
If only I'd been a better captain...
If only I'd wanted badly enough
to make one more receive...
If only... I'd made the time to run one more step...
Maybe I would have gotten to play
volleyball for just a little while longer.
Sawamura!
Ikejiri?
Listen to me... please keep winning! For my team, too!
Sure. We'll do our best!
To think, tens of thousands of players around the
country are ending their seasons early, just like we are.
To get to the nationals, you have to
win every single game in the preliminaries.
If this was a TV drama...
The guys going to nationals would be the main characters,
and our team would be extras or something.
But hey...
We still got to play.
At least we could still play...
Volleyball.
Karasuno was awesome.
Yeah, that short guy really surprised me!
No kidding.
Did you see those quick attacks he did? Impressive.
Wh-what?! Can't I just be happy about this?!
Nobody's ever made a big deal out of me like that before!
I haven't said a word, Hinata...
Ah...
In fact, I'm glad to see you getting some recognition.
The more the enemy teams pay
attention to you and feel intimidated...
The greater the damage you'll be able to do.
Uh... so I don't know what that means...
But your face says it's something evil.
That's right, Kageyama.
We're building a great reputation with everybody
out there talking about our little, red 10...
So we need Hinata to shine out there.
So bright, the other team's blockers are
gonna be too blinded to know what's goin' on.
Just so you know, we'll be using the same
starting lineup for round two as we did for round one.
The next game will be starting at 1:30...
Let's stay loose you guys.
Now go get yourselves a light lunch.
Don't fill up though.
Yes, sir!
Next is that "iron wall" school with "no brows", right?
Date Tech.
Yeah yeah, that's the one.
Listen...
I think the game back in March where Date
Tech beat us was the reason Asahi quit the club.
Ah! Really? You think that was it?
In one of our games... every single one
of Asahi's spikes was completely shut down.
They've got blockers...
And they can stop Asahi.
Sorry to interrupt.
Ah?
You guys got a minute?
Asahi.
We should go.
Listen to me, you guys. There's
something I want to address.
Date Tech is a very tough opponent...
I'm sure you know three months ago, that iron
wall block of theirs completely obliterated us.
But now we have our special decoy!
Ah!
You have blazed a trail so Hinata could succeed.
So... please blaze a trail for Asahi too!
Okay! Time to win round two!
Ooooh... Wuh?
Go, go, Date Tech, Date Tech, here we go!
Date Teeeeech... let's fight!
Yeah!
Run some laps!
Well, they've got the scare tactics down, don't they?
Date Tech really scares me...
That'd be like sharing the court with a bunch of monsters.
Seriously, man! Did you see that team they played against
in round one? Dude, I felt really bad for their spiker.
Yeah, no matter what they did,
Date Tech shut 'em right down.
Captains!
Thank you for the game.
Oh boy... I get the feeling this
entire gym wants Date Tech to win.
Looks like we're on the receiving side...
You ready, sir?
Yep.
Receiving drills! Let's go!
Sir!
Alright! Let's do this!
Right!
It's been three months since Date Tech destroyed us.
Our team's definitely getting better...
But I think the third-years might still
have the last defeat stuck in their minds.
And we can't let that linger. Best course of action
right now is to stop 'em from obsessing over Date Tech.
Rollinggggg...
Thundeeeeeer!
Again!
There ya go.
Nice! Killer receive, Noya! I mean,
that was perfect! Except for the name...
You wanna say that to me again, baldy?!
Ooh, teach me! Teach me the again too!
How was that different than the last one?
At least he got it.
You never quit, do you?
Tone it down, dude. Daichi might get mad again.
Alright listen here! You guys
have nothing to be afraid of at all!
Hm?
Focus on what's in front of you!
I promise I'll always have your back.
Whoa... he's amazing!
Pretty cool.
That's great! Everybody's acting
like their usual selves again!
Yeah.
He may be short, and his hair,
ridiculous... But he's reliable.
The libero's not just there for defense...
Another big part of his job is to
support the team from behind the scenes.
We've got ourselves a hell of a libero.
Line up!
Thank you for the game!
So, no-brows got in your way once before, Asahi?
Uh, yeah...
Shouldn't he be scared of you?
Yeah, you look so much older than he does.
Oh, come on!
Great job, guys...
Next Haikyu!! "The iron wall".