Hey, Karasuno's swapping setters.
Don't feel bad...
We just need to change up the rhythm.
I'm sorry.
I am worried about him.
But we can't have both of them losing their grip at once.
I already promised you that I'd be the one to beat you!
Hey, Hinata! He's gonna get ma...
Don't you dare lose to those guys first!
Well, I haven't lost yet, have I?
The game is still on.
He is gonna kill you!
I guess there was no need to panic.
Kageyama... I want you to stay ready.
Just take a few minutes to cool off.
Maybe you'll learn something from your upperclassman.
You!
And you!
Aw yeah!
I hope you're ready! We are getting this point!
Yeah!
What?
Kageyama, you're making that ugly face again.
It's my face, asshole!
You just look so tense... And you've been so quiet.
I'm sure you're just really deep
in thought about something, right?
But you're hard to read when you go all silent like that.
So you're saying I'm not talking to the team?
Yup, you've been quieter in this
game than in any game we've ever played.
It's weird!
Damn, have I gotten so bad that
this idiot gets to lecture me?
Hey... That setter Karasuno just put in... Number 2...?
Looks like he's a third-year!
What?!
I wonder why they would replace a guy like
that with a first-year in the starting lineup?!
Hey, Daichi! Why are you being so quiet today?
Huh?
We can't have our captain losin' his cool!
Oh, uh... sorry.
Nobody lectures Daichi!
'Cept for him.
Tsukishima, c'mere.
I'm not sure what Mr. Optimism is actually good at...
But from his warmup, it's clear that he's
meticulous and serious about what he does.
Look, Iwa...
Number 2's got a low block, so I want
you to aim for a straight-down where he is.
Sure.
Nice receive!
Tanaka!
Gotcha!
Iwa!
Okay... Straight down at the low blocker!
Rejected! Guess they must've
seen that straight-down coming.
Yeah! That was a really nifty trick!
Right before Seijoh spiked it,
they swapped their blocker positions.
That was great, Tsukishima! You pulled one over on them!
That.. Wasn't just me...
Y'see, I'm a low blocker...
So whenever we play a tough
team I'm always getting targeted.
And I figured they would be no exception.
It comes in pretty handy to have
someone as tall as you next to me!
Um... thanks, I guess...
Yikes.
Sorry about that.
Here we go!
Hinata, c'mere!
All you, Tsukki!
Here!
Nice receive!
Man, they're giving it right back to them!
Oh, a quick attack!
And an A-Quick!
Woohoo!
Hinata, that was freakin' great!
Yeah, well you guessed right, Sugawara!
Next time they're able to neatly send it back to the
setter, they'll probably do a quick attack in the center.
But I want you to move slowly
and delay your jump a little bit.
Y'got that!
It was frustrating to have to watch from the sidelines,
but I think being outside the game allowed
me to assess the situation more calmly.
I was able to see the game with new eyes.
So the time I spent not playing was useful too.
The energy on our side is really amping up now!
Yeah...
You're worried, aren't you?
Huh?
Because you benched Kageyama, right.
And he's so prideful...
Are you afraid that he'll get
all bent out of shape over it?
He'll be alright.
I think Kageyama's pride is the
main source of his power and talent.
That, and his undying determination to
be a better player, make him exceptional.
Give us one more, Tsukki!
One point to break it!
Yeah!
Okay, what attack are we doing next?
My technical skill's not as good as Kageyama's
is, so I can't always toss perfect sets...
but hand signals might help us
communicate our next move during a game.
When an outsider looks at Suga, they only see one thing.
A poor third-year who got replaced by a first-year.
He didn't use his code words!
Kageyama's out, so it can't be that insane quick attack!
Right, duh!
But what they don't know, is that Suga has spent
enough time on the sidelines to know exactly what to do...
He's just as much of an asset as Kageyama!
Gotcha!
When it comes to actual ability,
I pale in comparison to Kageyama,
but I've been watching this team a lot longer than he has.
I know I don't have what it takes to beat Seijoh...
but my friends are amazing at what they do!
This point will turn the tide!
Right!
Good effort, Hinata.
Hey, guys.
Serve's up!
One point!
Oh... great.
Oikawa's serve.
Bring it on!
Oooooooolé.
Leave it to me! I'll get it!
The old hubby-wife play.
It happens when two receivers get mixed up.
Sorry, I should've gone for it myself.
I was too close! It's cool!
Oooooooolé.
Front line!
Set point for Seijoh.
Damn... How many times has Oikawa
scored with that serve of his?!
If there was an ultimate play in volleyball,
it would be scoring all 25 points with nothing but serves.
The opponent never gets a chance to attack.
That's what service aces are all about.
I got it, it's miiine!
Okay!
Number 10 and Number 5 are after it...
No, it's a back attack!
Yeah, nice receive!
Hinata, right now, do a direct!
I've never done a direct attack...
What the hell was that?!
I-I'm sorry, okay?!
Hey, guys.
I think I just noticed something...
It kinda looks like Seijoh carries out their quick
attacks a little bit slower than we do... We should...
Delay it by just a hair...
and jump!
Get back!
No!
It's out?!
Son of a...
Switch sides. Let's go!
Come on, Hinata! We'll get it next time.
Okay!
Agh, that was too close! They figured out our timing!
All their players are starting
to look before they leap now...
including the short one, and he
tends to blindly rely on his instincts.
Here.
We'll go with the current lineup.
Sir!
Okay, our biggest obstacle is Oikawa's serve, obviously.
So we're gonna beef up our defense!
Karasuno's attacks are pretty wild.
Just when we got into the right mindset
to handle that crazy quick attack...
They decided they would try to throw us
off our game by attacking us like normal.
You're focusing way too much on Number 10.
Iwa! Don't think too hard; You'll run out of brain cells!
During the practice game, we were scrutinizing Kageyama.
I didn't realize they had another solid setter.
Listen.
Yeah?
Uh, Kindaichi... Um I mean... Onion Head.
Number 12's quick attack is a
little bit on the slow side...
I mean, don't you think?
You're right, it is!
It's like that guy watches the ball
forever before he actually goes in for the hit.
Sugawara's a control tower they're not familiar with...
That oughta throw these guys off.
He's different from Kageyama.
Yeah... I put him in hoping he'd bring
the other kids back to their senses...
but this works just as well.
We'll have to remember this
little strategy in the future too.
Kageyama.
Uh-huh.
Okay, so I understand since we're both setters,
we're kinda supposed to be competing
for the same position or whatever...
But I just want to play volleyball!
Uh, s-same here.
Now that I'm actually standing on the court,
I realize how tall the Aoba-Johsai guys are,
and how that makes me a walking target for their spikes...
It's kinda scary.
But y'know what... I know I'm okay, because...
Now I have you right there behind me.
That's reassuring.
The points we make while I'm on the court...
and the points we make with you on the court...
they're all points for Karasuno.
So I will give it my absolute best... and you give
it your best too... That is how we'll beat Seijoh.
Yeah.
Are you crying or something, Kageyama?
No I'm not, butt-wad!
Don't yell at me! I was just
concerned about you, that's all!
Worry about yourself and that
lame direct you just screwed up!
Sh-shut up! I've never done it before!
Well there's a whole lot more of those
to come when I get back in the game!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Suga! You don't have to get all
introspective and overthink this.
Uh, I won't.
We'll make a comeback in the second set.
The first step to achieving that...
is breaking Oikawa's serve.
Seijoh's rotation is the same as the first set,
but Karasuno moved theirs up a little bit.
Huh. Wonder why they did that?
Yes!
Alright!
Ha!
Nice, Tsukishima!
Uh, thanks.
Do that again, okay?
He's really nice... He always
compliments me when I do good, too!
That's great...
It is, but Sugawara doesn't do that
just for the sake of being friendly...
I think he talks to all the spikers so he can get
a feel for their emotional state during the game.
Helps him decide how to set. Because everyone's different.
Tsukishima, on the other hand, is a special case,
because unlike with the older players,
Sugawara doesn't know much about him.
Oh what's that face for?
It looks like you're thinking "Why should I be
concerned with how a jerk like Tsukishima feels?"
Uh-You don't know what I'm thinking about!
'Kay it's sort of like this...
You know how you adjust your
set if Hinata isn't able to hit it?
Yeah.. He'll just swing at nothing.
Well, my point is, our other
spikers have enough technical
prowess to hit the sets that
aren't tailored to their strengths.
So maybe this sounds sort of biased...
but you know, if you ask me... we
have some pretty advanced spikers.
Uh, yeah, I agree with that. Sure.
In that case...
Don't you think if they were all hitting at 100%,
they'd be able to compete with
most any blocker they were up against?
One point!
Looks like the Great King's up to serve.
Serve-receive W-Formation!
When Oikawa serves... We'll delegate
our defense to just a select few.
That serve of his is a serious threat...
so a moment's hesitation could be the end of us.
So, I say we tackle this using our two
outstanding receivers, Nishinoya and Daichi.
We've never done this formation in a game.
But I think you'll do fine.
We will!
Wow!
They have a different rotation this set...
I wonder why they moved it
slightly forward from the first one.
I'm assuming they lined it up like this
to match with Oikawa's serve.
Those serves cleaned the floor with us in set 1...
not to mention the 5 points we lost to service aces.
Until we can stand up to that
serve, we'll never beat Seijoh.
Here goes!
Ooooooooolé!
Daichi!
Yes!
Nice receive!
We really need to score a point to
break the cycle of Oikawa's serve.
If we can, it'll make a huge difference.
But it's gonna put a lot of pressure on one person.
I'll send it to the player who broke the flow in
the first set after Oikawa tried to bring him down.
That'll get him back on his feet.
Tanaka!
It's all up to you!
Yeah!
YEEEEEAAAAAH!
Who-ho-hoa!
That's the point breaker!
That was very impressive, captain.
Let's keep it up!
Tsukki!
But you know, if you ask me...
we have some pretty advanced spikers.
Don't you think if they were all hitting at 100%...
they'd be able to compete with
most any blocker they were up against?
Man, our morale is through the roof!
Seijoh's may have us beat in
experience and technical skill.
And it'll be a nightmare if they can pick up a solid lead.
But if we hang in there, we
should be able to take control!
Wow, it's anybody's game right now.
I guess... but their blockers are all over us.
Good job, Kindaichi! You're
figuring out all their patterns!
Uh, yes sir.
It's not that Mr. Sunshine and Rainbows is a bad setter.
His attacks are just so textbook and predictable...
He never rushes a setup either.
Listen, Karasuno may have a lot of offensive power,
but it's nothing we haven't seen before
from other teams we've played, right?
Now let's leave these losers in the dust.
Gotcha!
Y'know... At this point in the game...
I think Seijoh's got a good sense
of what our setter's gonna do next.
I think you're right.
Ooooooooolé!
Seijoh scores back-to-back.
Yeah, and the break is where
the flow really starts to move.
We need to crank things up!
Karasuno's been using their left players a lot
since they swapped out their setter, haven't they?
Well, that's because each of their lefts
is a force to be reckoned with... Still...
I'm sure they're easier to deal with than
that number 10's constant bobbing and weaving.
It's like there's a noose tightening around my neck.
And yet I feel so calm.
Impatience isn't clouding my judgment.
I guess because I have a clear goal right in front of me.
Yeah, let's get that point!
I used to think that if I got benched...
it meant I wasn't useful to the team anymore...
Honestly, that probably was the reason back then.
But...
Now I have you right there behind me.
That's reassuring.
Sugawara and I have different strengths,
but I think our goal is the same.
Left side!
Heads up!
Open!
All I want is to play volleyball!
I want to be in this game!
I want to stay longer... Just a little longer!
The intensity of the court...
Please... let me keep playing with my team!
The rush of adrenaline...
I don't want to leave!
I want to be out there fighting... and winning!
I want to make these sets myself!
I have to!
So...
So I will give it my absolute best...
and you give it your best, too...
and that...
That is how we're going to win this game!
Nice receive!
YES!
Awesome block!
Sorry Hinata...
That last quick attack took me longer than it should have.
Oh! No it's fine...
They're calling for Karasuno's number 9.
I guess they're switching setters.
My time's running out.
Suga.
Send me the next ball, okay? I'll make it count.
Right!
Serve's up!
Amazing.
I hate to admit it, but...
Well, when Hinata hits your sets...
somehow he looks completely different.
And... I'm sure you know this...
but everyone on our team is good at what they do.
Yeah.
So go wi...
Let's win.
Right!
Good job.
Well done.
Yeah, You kept it neck and neck against those guys.
That's because we're a great team.
Listen here, kid...
From here on in, I think we'll be pushing
this setter route as aggressively as we can.
Sure! Thank you, sir!
What was that?
Well, you are talking in his setter language.
That's probably music to his ears.
If everyone does their best to succeed,
then I'm confident we can beat Seijoh...
But...
to get the boost we need,
the best bet for Karasuno is to have its
greatest decoy working at 100% of his potential.
And the one to make that happen...
will be you... Kageyama.
Welcome back, Tobio!
Watch it, pretty boy.
Now, now, settle down.
We know you're not capable of anything serious.
Tsukishima, he's meaner than you! You gonna take that?!
It's not a competition, Hinata...
Next Haikyu!! "Evolution."