Check it out!
I've got the pairings for the
Inter-High preliminaries right here!
Cool!
Sweet!
So, who do we play first?
Let me see...
Tori... Torino?
Torino? That's in England!
Try Italy. And you're reading the Kanji wrong.
Whatever, dude.
Oh! Karasuno, I've heard of that school!
Uh... if I remember...
A lot of people call them like, the "wingless crows."
Wow, that's a messed-up nickname, right?
Their team used to be pretty good though, right?
I think so.
I think they went to nationals one time.
Yeah, well, but apparently they're
nothing to write home about these days.
Oh! Hey, are you thinking what I'm thinking?
We might actually win this game!
We'll get past the first round for once!
Not if you don't get off your butts and start practicing.
C-captain!
Now go run some laps!
Yes sir...
You know...
This guy I played volleyball with back in
middle school, ended up going to Karasuno High.
Oh yeah? Well, that ought to be an interesting reunion...
You know, I don't think we've ever played them before.
Yeah, that's right...
He said that he saw Karasuno play in the Spring Nationals
on TV and couldn't get the place out of his head...
But I'm sure living close to the school had
something to do with his decision too, though.
Wonder how he's doing?
Good old Daichi.
Don't just stand there, follow through!
Get it together!
I'm sorry!
Go after every ball...
As if it's the last the last piece of meat on earth!
Don't take a play off.
If you do, that'll be the one
you cry about after the game's done!
First of all, you guys did a great
job playing against Nekoma today.
Next order of business... The Inter-High
preliminaries start next month, June 2nd to be exact.
There's no regional prelim here,
so it's straight to prefectural.
Out of 60-some teams in the prefecture,
only one gets to advance to the nationals...
Lose one match and that's all she wrote.
If you want revenge against Nekoma,
you have to get number 1 in Miyagi.
Second place won't do.
Well, that's assuming they can prove themselves
as the greatest high school team in all of Tokyo.
I guarantee you they can do it, coach!
Yeah! They're gonna make it!
I want... to challenge Nekoma again.
One more time!
You're ain't done, ginger! On your feet!
Yes sir! Keep 'em coming!
Front!
Hiya!
Cover it!
Dude, that's nuts!
Ah?
It's like a whole page!
Right?!
Let me see.
Ah!
What are you guys so excited about?
Look.
That's Ushiwaka from Shiratorizawa Academy.
They named him one of the three
players to watch in this year's nationals.
That's the school Kageyama didn't get into!
Would you shut it?!
What are you two losers laughing at?!
So, who's Ushiwaka?
You seriously don't know who that is?
Of course not. He only cares about the tiny giant.
Ushiwaka is his nickname.
His real name is Wakatoshi Ushijima, and
he's the number one ace in the prefecture.
Yeah, just look at him. Now that is
what an ace is supposed to look like.
Whoa! H-hey why's everyone staring at me?!
Is Ushiwaka the reason you wanted
to go to Shiratorizawa Academy?
Let me guess, you wanted to march
right up to that legendary ace and go...
"Move it, you clumsy dumbass!" Like you tell Hinata!
Of course not!
So we can't play Nekoma... Unless we defeat them first?
Remember, boys...
Shiratorizawa's not the only good team.
They're the biggest threat based on last year though.
Thank you for stating the obvious...
But there's a whole lot more than just them.
Wakutani South has great defense and solidarity.
Date Tech's been called the "iron wall" because
their team has higher blocks than anyone else around.
They're big guys.
From what I understand, these guys beat us two to nothing
in the public prefectural tournament back in march.
Hm?
Wait a minute.
Why does that sound familiar?
In one of games... every single one
of Asahi's spikes was completely shut down.
Was that the game Sugawara was telling us about
before Asahi decided to come back to the team?
Date Tech's team has been top-four
material for a good long while, but...
Last year, they only ranked in the top 16 after
losing in round 3 to Shiratorizawa, who won first place.
That's why they're not seeded this year.
So depending on how the brackets are laid out, we
could end up having to face them in the first round.
The next team is... Oh that's right...
I heard you guys played a
practice game with them not long ago.
Ah!
Their captain possesses the most offensive power
on the team on top of being an excellent setter...
He might even be the top overall
player in the whole prefecture.
Aoba Johsai, led by Toru Oikawa.
Oh yeah, the great king!
Hur...
They ranked in last year's top four too.
Humph!
Now last but definitely not least...
Shiratorizawa, headed up by that famous ace, Ushiwaka.
That's the short version.
I'll give you more detailed info later.
Wow, coach Ukai's got his stuff together...
You two smartasses wanna pay attention or
you wanna share your thoughts with the class?
Anyway, those are the four teams
I think we need to look out for.
That said, if you spend too much time staring at
the top, you'll get the rug pulled out from under you.
Don't let yourselves make the mistake of thinking we're
the only team who's there to take the number one spot.
We're not.
Sure, we're going to be training our asses off,
but remember all those other teams
will be training their asses off too...
No matter who won last year and who
lost, everybody's aiming to win it all...
Never forget that.
One more thing.
Don't let those bastards call us
the "wingless crows" ever again!
Right!
You all are still in here?!
I'm so sorry I'm late, I-I got stuck in a meeting.
Anyway...
I've got the bracket for the preliminaries!
If our team and Date Tech both clear the first
round, we'll be up against them in round two.
We shouldn't get ahead of ourselves you guys.
Aoba Johsai's seeded in our block this year.
That's not good.
Ugh... come on!
I don't like those odds...
Hey!
Did you already forget what I told you?
If you focus on the top-
Yes, we know, sir.
Which school did you pick?
Karasuno.
Which one is that?
You know, the one from Sring Nationals.
Oh, nice.
So uh where are you headed?
I chose to go to Tokonami...
Sorry about that.
It's cool.
I dunno, dude...
I guess if I keep playing volleyball in high school...
You should!
Maybe we'll get to play against each other.
But, hey, make sure you're ready for my
team to wipe the floor with yours, alright?
Go on and try it.
C'mon, pick up the pace, dude, it's gettin' late!
We'll stay focused...
One game at a time!
Um, hey, Daichi!
Oh... hey there, Michimiya.
I just thought you might want a copy of the
program for the pep rally... Volleyball's 5th.
Thanks a lot.
So do you have a speech prepared for it?
Eh, not really.
I can't believe the Inter-High tourney is so close.
Am... I hear the boys are getting super psyched for that!
What was the name of that other school you
guys used to play practice games wi-, ooh Sorry.
Ah, Nekoma?
That's the one... I heard you played them again.
Yeah... So how's the girls' team? Being in separate
gyms keeps us pretty much out of touch with each other.
Eh... everything's about the same as always.
I can't get a lot of the girls
to come to morning practice...
So I guess I'm not much of a captain, huh?
Oh well, we'll probably lose in the first round anyway.
Oops.
Michimiya... you told me you were
going to win for sure this time.
Ah um...
Remember...?
It doesn't matter how strong or talented
your opponent is. You won't win unless you try.
O-oh, I'm sorry! I'm sure you didn't
come here for me to lecture you...
Sorry it's what I do.
Awhhhhh!
It's funny, that's exactly the same
lecture you gave me back in middle school.
I got my butt kicked in a pre-tournament practice game...
I was starting to give up on winning for real.
Even if you're not confident that you can win...
And even if everyone around
you says that it's impossible...
No matter what...
"Never say never... don't admit defeat 'til you've tried!"
Remember?
Sorry! I just have a habit of
chickening out right before a tournament!
I hate it!
I guess I shouldn't be telling you what to do.
Am?
But we are both captains... So I've always got
your back... Feel free to talk to me anytime, okay?
Oh!
You're so weird... ha!
Okay! I'm good!
See ya, Daichi. Thanks a lot!
Listen carefully... My special protégé...
I want to crush you fair and square at an
official game, where we both play the setter!
What's his deal?
Hell if I know.
Hey, Asahi!
Club! Time to go!
That was kinda rude.
Yeah, he's not a dumb dog.
You don't have to do that every time, Nishinoya...
I'm not gonna run away.
I understand everyone's got my back.
I will hold my head up high...
And show everyone that I'm Karasuno's ace!
Hinata!
Oh Sugawara.
Perfect timing... I have something for you.
I made copies for all the first-years.
Signals.
My technical skill's not as good as Kageyama's
is, so I can't always toss perfect sets...
but hand signals might help us
communicate our next move during a game.
It might take some time but it'll
probably help for you to memorize all these.
Are you kidding me?!
This is gonna be so awesome. I can't wait!
Great... I'm sure we'll have to work out
the kinks before we can use them in a game...
So let's practice as much as we can.
Sure! I promise I'll learn to hit any set!
Give me some time... I can master it!
We use a triple front decoy...
And a back attack.
Keishin? Did you get any more mirin in stock yet?
Be right with you-ahh...
Well don't just throw it on the floor, dear.
So uh what's the matter with you Tanaka?
The tournament's almost here.
Yeah?
And tournaments are supposed to be all dramatic
like we're marching into battle, you know what I mean?
Uhh... sure.
And the most important part of
that is having a cute girlfriend.
Isn't your big sports thing is tomorrow.
Yes, darling, it is.
Isn't this the one you've been practicing so hard for?
Yeah, baby, I can't thank you
enough for supporting my dream.
Oh, I don't mind at all!
Nothing makes me happier than watching you play, baby!
Do you mean it?
I really wanted to do something for you
before the game... So I... um... made you this.
Is that a good luck charm?
That's right... Do your best, okay?
See, I want to be more fired up about the game...
But first I need a girlfriend... one that's sexy!
Keep the crazy talk to a minimum or
I'll tell the coach to give me your spot.
Huh?!
Nice kill!
Excellent!
Hey man-bun.
Sir!
Would you say you're pretty decent at back attacks?
Ar...
Over here!
Um?
I want to try something.
So do boys think you can handle that?
Well first we need to find the right hitting height.
That looks tricky.
We'll do our best. Thank you for your advice, coach.
Hinata, keep diving in just like before!
Yes, sir!
Keep it up!
Right!
Asahi, would you mind practicing with me a little more?
You know... you're looking really tired lately, coach.
Come to think of it, I noticed you've been
showing up right when our practice starts every day.
Is everything going okay at your job?
Mhmm... up until recently the
store was all I had going on.
But now I've started tending crops in the early
morning hours, so I've had to work night shifts instead.
I've been thinking maybe it's about time I
stopped relying so much on my folks, you know?
Uh thank you so much! I owe you a nice bottle of sake!
Oh yeah?!
Wow, this is a lot of different
attack patterns to practice...
Are you planning to use all of them?
Well... that depends.
Hah?
It's important to make sure these guys
stay focused on the game in front of them.
That's not to say it's a bad idea to go ahead
and prepare ourselves for all the other games, too.
Don't tell 'em I said that.
Great job, Hinata! You did it!
That Hinata-Sugawara quick attack's looking good!
The way you did it that time felt perfect!
Sweet!
Hey Asahi! What did you think of that last one? Too high?
Too low? How was it? C'mon you can be honest with me!
Ew, it was fine... Mhm... Good-
Gr don't hold back! Whatever criticism
you have, I can handle it! Just tell me!
Uhhh, huh... Okay, then, maybe aim it a little higher?
You could try sending it a
little further from the net too.
Right, thank you! 10 more tries!
Not enough?
The tournament's almost here. There's
no time to start changing things up.
Don't forget the timing we practiced.
Right!
Oh, okay I get it. You want
to practice another pattern now.
Alright, let's go, it's getting late.
Yes, sir!
Haaaaa!
Hey Kiyoko. Daichi's gonna
treat us to some food after this.
I'm sorry... I have something else to do.
Oh, okay. See you.
Goodnight.
One for everybody.
Thank you.
You're the best, captain!
Yeah, thanks Daichi!
Everybody eat up so we can go home.
Hey Tsukishima, the captain bought
everybody a meat bun, you want one?
Sure, thank you.
Hey, did Tadashi leave already?
He said there was somewhere
he needed to go on the way home.
Um...
Uh sorry, we're actually closed for the day. Ah?
I'm Yamaguchi from the volleyball club.
Right! So that's where I know you from.
Look... the jump float serve...
Do you think you can teach me how to do it?
Oh, yeah...
I used it when we played each other, didn't I?
I would, but the prelims are
right around the corner aren't they?
If you're wanting to learn before
then, I don't think you have enough time.
You're probably right.
Odds are I won't get to play in the game, anyway.
First-years don't usually have a chance to
play if there are third-years on the team...
But still...
Despite all that... I never want to be
the only first-year on the bench again!
Hm...
I say we call it early and get some rest.
Right!
Okay... let's go home-
W-wait, don't leave yet!
We have one more comment. It's from Kiyoko.
Huh?
I'm not very... good with words...
So I kinda did something.
If you please, Takeda.
Of course.
Ah! Wait, sir... please, let me take that up there.
I got it.
What is that thing?
And, go!
Whoa!
We have a banner?
I found it while I was cleaning
up, so I thought I'd wash it.
Yeah! I'm fired up!
You're awesome, Kiyoko! Thanks for everything!
We're ready now! Let's win this thing!
Not yet...
Huh?
Listen guys...
I think there's more.
Huh?!
You...
Huh?
You can do it.
Uh...
Kiyoko! She's never done anything like this before!
I don't get it. Why are they so freaked out by this?
Most of the time, you can't shut them up.
What the hell?! Calm down already!
We can win! The first round is all ours!
Yeah!
I'm the first one here!
Hey, get back here, Kageyama!
You like that? I beat you this time.
Now the scores, 31 - 30 with one tie.
That's wrong.
Hell no, it's not! I'm ahead of you!
Yeah, you are... But that makes it 30 - 32.
Huh?
I lost to you this time last year, too.
You beat me bad.
You might be the king who rules the court for now...
But I'm gonna win!
One day I'll stay in the court longer than you!
Listen to me.
I'll beat you! If it takes 10
or even 20 more years, I will!
Wait a second... you think one
day, your dumb ass'll be on my level?
Hm?
Yeah... that's right!
Even the best in all of Japan? And the world?
The world?!
U-um... obviously!
And I told you, not to call me the king.
Let's go.
The real journey begins today.
Hm...
Yeah!
Ah... Tanaka, why are you still crying?
Kiyoko said it's okay to cry!
Yeah... but that was yesterday.
Dammit, don't make me relive it!
Ugh. You guys are pathetic.
Next Haikyu!! "We're back."