Hey... Welcome back, Oikawa.
How's that leg doing?
Never been better! Glad I can come back to practice now...
It was just a tiny sprain.
Listen, son... don't ever do that again!
They brought Kageyama like we asked them to, so
we can't just show up without our official setter...
That would make us look bad.
I'm sorry.
Careful, Oikawa! Please don't hurt yourself!
Hey, it might be because he's
got all the ladies' attention...
But I already hate this guy.
Yeah that's Seijoh's team captain.
Oikawa. A super offensive setter.
Top of his class in attacking and team play.
If he thinks this guy is good, then... hmm...
Yeah... and he's got a bad attitude too.
What? Is it worse than yours?!
Even worse than four-eyes.
That is bad!
Since you know him, I guess he
must've also gone to Kitagawa first, huh?
Yeah. He was my upperclassman.
If he's above the king, then he's...
the great king?!
Hey there! Long time no see, Kageyama!
How long has it been since I saw you? You've really grown!
How's it feel to be the king?
He's good... I learned everything I
know about serving and blocking from him.
Do not underestimate him.
He must've invented that killer serve.
Still... for now we should stay focused on the game...
We are gonna take that last set!
Y-yeah!
Tanaka, stop with the faces!
Now get over there and warm up! And be extra
thorough so you don't get yourself injured again!
Alright.
I'm gonna kill this guy!
Come on, when are they gonna let Oikawa play?
No he can't go in yet. If he doesn't warm
up first, he might hurt his beautiful body.
Oh nooo, that would be awful!
I know, right?
Comin' atcha!
One more point.
That's all we need.
We might just win against a top 4 team!
Don't start getting cocky yet!
Yes!
Nice, Kindaichi!
It's alright. Shake it off!
Uh-oh. Looks like we're in trouble.
You warmed up?
I'm ready anytime.
Just leave everything to me, okay?
Right.
Ahhh... it's the great king!
Cut that out!
Bleeehhhh!
Wait, are they swapping our setter out?
He's not the setter. He was filling in.
You're up, Oikawa!
Doesn't matter how powerful their attacks are.
If they never make a solid connection
with the ball... Then what's the point?
What?
Huh?
He's targeting Tsukishima!
Tsukki!
I just started watching, but looks like I was right.
Number 6... and number 5.
Uwah!
You two must be first-years. Your receives are terrible.
His momentum's even better than Kageyama's.
And he's got the control to
land the ball anywhere he chooses.
This guy's really good.
So that's Seijoh's captain.
Now... one more time.
Poor Tsukki!
Damn.
Don't worry about it, guys!
Tsukishima's a jerk and he gets on my
nerves... but for some reason... grrr...
Ah, just one more point to tie.
Hey, great king!
Why don't you aim for me?! I can take it! Just aim
the ball right at my head! Unless you're too scared!
Stop it, you're acting like a toddler!
Excuse me?!
This freakin' guy always knows what to
say to make me mad... but, but still...!
Listen up! The cool thing about volleyball
is... The cool thing about volleyball is...
Everybody you see on this side of
the net is your ally, okay Tsukishima?!
Wise words from a wise guy!
Okay... let's fall back as a group...
Tsukishima, you stay close to the sideline.
Right.
Now... let's go!
Oooh... the captain is the strongest
receiver, and now he's expanding his defense zone.
One more!
Still... it takes more than one
player to defend the whole court!
Argh!
How can he pinpoint someone who's so far away?!
But he's emphasizing control,
so the momentum should be slower!
It's up!
You're awesome, Tsukki!
Oh, you got it! Niiiiice!
I guess I made it too easy... oh well.
You guys did just gave us a little gift though.
Agh dammit!
Oh my... look at that delicious chance ball...
Don't mind if we do, thank you!
I got it!
Uh-oh, this rotation doesn't
give us enough blocking height...
Kindaichi!
Alright, I shook off all the blockers,
where'd the shorty come from?!
There it goes!
Nice one-touch, pal!
Chance ball!
Just wait, carrot-top, next time I'm gonna smack you down!
If you miss Hinata by even the smallest
instant, he'll be impossible to catch.
The only thing that can keep up with him...
is the ball!
What was that?
That guy moved across the court in a split second.
The ball flew straight into his hand like a magnet.
Aww yeah!
Line up!
Is there something wrong?
Incredible...
Oh yeah, that's right!
I guess this is the first time you've seen
Hinata and Kageyama's special attack in action...
It's pretty cool, huh? In fact,
it's so cool it kinda freaks me out!
Huh?
We're ready!
Ready!
You're supposed to give them some feedback.
Oh, sorry, I didn't know.
Lemme see...
Like I said... I don't know that
much about volleyball... but still!
I can tell something really
great is starting to take shape.
Huh?
We've just had some really
gifted first-years join the team...
And things didn't run so smoothly at first... but now...
I think I understand why! Even
if everyone doesn't always agree...
Whenever people are brought together...
It creates a chemical reaction.
Somewhere in the world, there's a fateful
encounter happening at this very moment.
It could be happening somewhere far
away in a completely different country...
Or on the other side of the globe.
Or maybe... it's on a small eastern
island... In a tiny northern town...
In an ordinary high school...
In a regular volleyball club.
I believe that encounter was made at Karasuno.
I don't have any proof yet...
But I can't ignore what I believe!
And before too long, this team
is going to become even stronger.
Uh...
I'm sorry! That was too weird, wasn't it?! I'll stop!
No no no, that was great, Takeda!
Thanks!
Thank you!
Uh... sure.
Kindaichi.
We cannot deal with Kageyama anymore, coach!
I know he's got amazing attack power and everything...
But he's obviously been holding the whole team back!
Seriously...
Better off without him.
Hey uh...
Don't even apologize to me!
And I'm not going to either!
Okay.
To me, you're always gonna be that
self-centered, pain-in-the-ass king of the court,
the number-one person on earth I want to defeat one day!
Fine.
So don't ruin that!
There's no need for the two of us to make
up... I mean we were never friends to start with!
Fine.
But next time we meet...
I will win!
Yeah well...
Time to go wash up, oh yeah!
You can call me Shoyo, future ace of Karasunooo-
whoa, it's about to go down! Are they gonna fight?
I should probably stay away from something like that...
Kindaichi.
The next time you and I meet...
We're gonna beat you again.
Hm? Hey, what was that all about?
He just... used the word "we".
Huh?
Are you crying?
Until now, it was always "I" this "me"
that. Like he was on a team by himself.
Agh... you idiotttt!
Have...
Have I already lost?
Ow! What was that for?!
Thank you for playing with us!
Takeda's right, but...
If we ever want to play and win a real game
against Seijoh with Oikawa in the setter position.
We're still missing a vital ingredient.
Wow.. Very well said captain.
That's surprisingly astute.
Look out it's the great king again!
What's your damage?
Gotta problem?
Wanna knuckle sandwich?!
Yeah, let's rumble!
Ah, come now, no need to get yourselves worked up.
But hey, short stuff.
That one-touch and broad jump
were great... you should be proud.
Huh? Oh...
Next time, we should try doing
things full-out from the start.
You haven't seen our real setup.
But don't worry... we'll be working
on perfecting our serves 'til then.
That's true, it'll be different.
Next time we'll be dealing with his serves the whole game.
That combination attack is pretty effective,
but you're going to run out of steam at some point.
You need to improve your receives.
After all, I'm not the only person who does power serves.
The Inter-High Tournaments are coming
up, and I want you to make the cut.
Listen carefully...
My special protege... I want
to crush you fair and square...
At an official game, where we both play the setter!
Yeah well... we can train to receive, fancy-pants!
Hey, let me go!
Just so you know, receives aren't
something you can master overnight.
I'm sure your captain can attest to that.
If we happen to meet again at the tournament...
I look forward to seeing all your improvement.
Look.. Do not let him get to you...
Antagonizing people is just one of
those things he likes to do, so...
He's right... we don't have a
whole lot of time until then...
But... luckily we have someone coming back soon.
Who's coming back?
Karasuno's... guardian.
Karasuno's... guardian?
Kageyama's getting really good, huh?
Yeah. He's a prodigy who's finally found himself
an outlet for his very specific set of abilities...
The average player's no match for him now.
Wait, are you saying you're not a match for him either?
Not for his sets... When it comes to that,
no one in the prefecture can out do Kageyama.
I'm every bit as good as him at spikes,
blocks and serves though... ow, what the-?!
You know damn well your sets are as good as his too!
That is why you're our setter!
Sorry... but it's the truth, okay?
Which is why we're going to sabotage their receiving...
Because no matter how perfectly they can catch a serve,
it's all for naught if it
doesn't make it back to the setter.
If we get matched with Karasuno in a real game...
We'll have to ruin all of their receives so
Kageyama never gets to make one of those flawless sets!
They can't just rely on just one person to win!
Ah, I'm already looking forward
to cheering them up after they lose!
What? Didn't you say you hated him for being a genius?
Not as much as I hate pretty-boys
like you who get all the girls!
Ow! Prejudice like that isn't very
becoming on you, my friend! Ow! Oww! Stop it!
Hey, cut that out or the coach's
gonna us one of his lectures again!
Good job, guys!
Now let's do a little light cleaning and call it a day!
Yes sir!
Watch it!
Thanks a bunch for setting everything up, Takeda.
Don't mention it. You guys did a great job!
I still can't believe we won against
a prestigious team like Aoba Johsai!
Yeah, but the fight is just beginning.
Huh?
I mean... thanks to that combo technique of ours...
We can put up a pretty good offense.
But if Hinata gets caught by blockers and
our receivers aren't up to par like today,
we won't have a strong enough defense.
And besides... we uh don't really have a coach... so uh...
When it comes to that kind of
advice... you're not all that much help.
You have a point.
Oh! That came out wrong!
I promise I wasn't saying you're not doing a good job!
I didn't take it that way...
Leave the coach problem to me. I have someone in mind.
Huh? Do you really? Who is it?
Well, it's someone I've tried and
failed to win over several times now...
but I'm sure I'll think of something.
Do you mind locking up when you guys are done today?
Yeah, sure.
Whoa, I think take's starting to take charge.
Mm-hm...
Hm? It's broken...
Hey, can I throw away this
mop? Someone might get a splinter.
Huh? No, it's fine! Just leave it!
I'm sure that it can be fixed somehow.
Huh?
Good night!
Night!
Meat buns?
Sorry boys, the soccer geeks just bought up all I had...
I know life is so unfair.
I'm hungry!
Yeah, where's your manager?!
I am the manager! Now get your
butts home and eat some real food!
Build up a little muscle!
Here.
Wow!
Thanks!
Now go eat your dinners.
Woohoo!
Ugh...
Sakanoshita.
Not givin' up, eh?
That was nuts.
I can't believe how good that guy's serves were...
It's a good thing he didn't show up until the final set.
Makes sense that he came from Kageyama's middle school.
Huh? Hang on.
Why'd you pick our school anyway, Kageyama?
Hm?
Shiratorizawa's got the best team in the
whole prefecture. Why didn't you just go there?
Shira-huh?
How have you never heard of Shiratorizawa?
Those guys have got unbelievable skills. They
rank in the top 8 in the whole country every year!
Whoaa!
Oh yeah, I didn't make it in there.
No way!
Well I didn't get a recommendation from them, so I
had to take the entrance exam and ended up failing it...
Their test is some pure nonsense.
Passing their exam is extremely hard...
I'd say almost impossible.
Aww... or maybe the king
doesn't have a head for academics.
Goodnight!
Tch!
Why did you pick Karasuno?
Let me guess, you want to be
like the tiny giant too don't'cha!
No, I picked this school because I heard
that coach Ukai might come out of retirement.
Ukai?
He's the best coach we've ever had! He made a
name for Karasuno by getting us to Spring Nationals!
Really?!
Yeah dude, some people even
call him the "crazy crow coach"...
You know, since our school name kinda means "crow".
Yeah, the second- and third-years got a
little bit of instruction from him last year...
But it was pretty basic and spartan.
Why are you jealous of that?
At one point they were planning
on formally reinstating him, but...
He collapsed?!
Sorry, but the school's not planning
on bringing him back anytime soon.
I don't care... no matter what school I go to...
I'm still going up against high school
students... And I'm still gonna win.
Look at this guy acting all
cool, you not foolin' anyone, buddy.
Pffff!
Don't be stupid!
I'm not trying to act cool at all! We did
beat one of the top 4 schools today, didn't we?!
That's true... two to one against Aoba Johsai High..
And thanks to my boy Hinata
here... I got to score one unmarked!
Sure thing my man!
So, you've made your debut now.
How did it feel?
On the other hand, you were losin' your
shit for the whole first set, remember?
Yeah, and you lost just as many points as
you scored, so don't go getting too cocky okay.
Come on why do you guys have to bait him like that?!
He's got a point though.
Huh?
Our team's still lacking. And in a lot of ways...
We might've won, but only just barely.
Okay, I'll practice myself crazy!
Whoa, whoa! Self-improvement is really important.
But... The main issue here is that
Karasuno still needs a few more players.
Huh?
Yeah, I would agree.
We need a natural libero... And also...
It would be really handy to have an ace
spiker who can handle a triple block too.
Hey! I can be the ace spiker!
You can't! You're supposed to be the decoy, remember?!
But you said our guardian would come back soon, right?
Yeah. Karasuno may not be the strongest
team, but we're not the weakest either.
Look, we used to have really skilled players..
But we failed to make sure
they trained their replacements.
Well now we've got players again...
Plus we've recruited a few first-year guys.
We just need to coordinate all our strengths.
Summer Inter-High Tourney.
The nationals aren't some unreachable goal...
If we work hard and play our cards
right, I'm positive we can get there!
Right, the Summer Inter-High Tourney, I know about that!
So...
The libero you said should be coming
back soon, where has he been all this time?
Uhh... yeah.. He's been serving a week of suspension,
plus he got banned from all club activities for a month.
Hm?
So is he some kind of troublemaker?!
Dude, no... he just gets carried away sometimes.
He's a stand-up guy though. Trust me on that.
If Tanaka thinks he gets carried
away, that's saying something.
And check this out.
He's known as the resident genius of the volleyball club.
But I guess now that we have smart-ass Kageyama on the
team, he won't get to keep that nickname anymore, will he?
Do us a favor once he's back...
Call him your "upperclassman".
He gets a stupid kick out of it like Tanaka does.
Hey, it's not stupid!
I can't wait to see what our team's guardian is like.
Get a move on!
Ah! Alright I'm coming!
I'm gonna hit it!
Agh!
Gwah!
Can't you stay out of my way for five minutes?!
I could've had that if not for you!
Yeah well I got it!
You didn't get anything! It's out of bounds!
Whatever.
Jeez.
This time for sure!
Huh?
He redirected its momentum and rotation,
sending it straight to the setter position.
A perfect receive.
Are you shorter than me?!
Who the heck is that?! He just swooped in out of nowhere!
That receive was so smooth and flawless!
I think I'm gonna cry!
Well, I guess I should introduce you guys.
Next Haikyu!! "The one they call The Ace."
I think I'm gonna cry!
Well, I guess I should introduce you guys.
Next Haikyu!! "The one they call the ace."