It's been three months since they defeated us.
The wall just fades away, and then the
view of the other side is totally clear!
In the past, I'd been able to
see the view he was talking about...
But when faced with that iron wall,
I couldn't picture anything beyond it.
I still wonder... what it must look like over there.
Rollinggggg...
Um...
Thundeeeeeeer!
Again!
Alright, listen here! You guys
have nothing to be afraid of at all!
Um?
Focus on what's in front of you!
I promise I'll always have your back.
Whoa... he's amazing!
Line up!
Thank you for the game!
Go, go, Date Tech, Date Tech, here we go!
Listen to me, boys.
So Karasuno surprised us with that quick attack...
But it was just the spiker's
height that threw us off, that's all.
Despite that incredible jumping power, at the end
of the day, all he did was a normal quick attack.
Don't lose sight of that.
Just don't let him or that ace
of theirs score a single point!
They know we're the iron wall...
So get out there... And remind them!
Yes sir!
From what they showed us in round one...
I'm thinking they'll come out
strong with their first serve...
They as notorious for their
serves as they are for their blocks.
Date Tech's strategy is to tank
their opponents' morale from the get-go.
So let's be sure to receive high
on the first one, you guys got that?
Right!
Oh, and... you know what to do, Don'cha?
Yeah.
Perfect... make me proud, team! Let's clear that wall!
Sir!
Karasunoooo... fight!
Fiiiight!
Hey, looks like Karasuno's
starting their ace in the back row.
Right, probably because that's the
strongest formation for receiving.
Date's in the same position as the first round.
You can do it!
Let's go!
Bring it on!
Do it, Kamasaki!
Serve's up!
Daichi!
Nice receive!
His form is flawless. He's able to mask
where he plans to send the set... but...
Sweet! Nice moves, Hinata!
Uh-oh! So they did block it! And here I
was thinking we had them a step behind.
Jumping after seeing the set.
That's called read-blocking, right?
Yeah.
The other schools we've dealt with used "commit blocks",
meaning they make the jump as soon as they
have a vague idea of where the set is headed.
But Date Tech prefers hardcore read-blocking, meaning
they don't jump until they can see the set in motion.
In other words...
it'll be almost impossible to fake them out.
That would put them a step behind to block it, but...
That number 7... he's so damn big and so fast...
He could close the gap, quick.
Wow, that's scary.
That read-blocking is gonna be a problem...
How do you think they're going to fight it?
Who knows?
After all, Karasuno hasn't even brought
out the big guns in this tournament yet.
Go for it, Kageyama!
Yeah, get the point!
Damn! It went straight to the libero!
That was a pretty impressive serve, there...
Now if he can just learn how to
control it, he'll be in business.
Whoa, he saved it!
Amazing!
Tanaka, cover it!
Gotcha!
Back here!
A back attack?!
There were barely any of those in the last game.
Hey, Asahi!
Man...
Oh, darn.
Don't let it get you down! Keep moving!
I'll get it next time! I'm so sorry.
Thanks, but I don't mind... I'll do better too.
C'mon, this is a sports tournament...
You should be at each other's throats!
What good do you think that would do, Futakuchi?
Ow!
A net touch, huh?
That was lucky!
I-it's fine! Don't sweat it!
They must be really happy that Date Tech hit
the net. Karasuno would have been in a lot of trouble.
They're not half bad, though...
Their blocks and their quick attacks
seem to work fairly well together.
They've got potential.
Nice receive!
I'm open!
Asahi!
Wait, I'm confused. Did we get a point for it being out?
Asahi, it's your serve!
Karasuno's doing a good job of keeping the lead.
But Date Tech's not giving them
enough room to make any spikes.
Well, not the kind of spikes they need, anyway.
Mm-hm.
So far, they've been able to narrowly
avoid Date's blocks, but if they slip up once,
they'll have the rug pulled out from under them.
Futakuchi!
Nice one, Hinata!
Seriously?
Chance ball!
In a fraction of a second, we take what
was almost their point and make it our own.
We break their spirits while boosting our own morale.
The perfect marriage of offense and defense.
That... is the block.
Nice block!
That was awesome, Aone!
Ahha!
Awggggh...
They are called the iron wall...
And he's part of the reason.
I was right.
This is bad.
Dangit!
Just shake it off and stay focused.
Huh?
Trust me... the next one's ours.
You think so?
Oh! You mean... time for whoosh?! And kaboom?!
It's been quite a while, hasn't it?
I'm gonna need your fastest
speed and your highest jump too.
And I'll bring the ball straight to you.
You can count on it.
Karasuno's probably going to use
that number 10 for their fastest attack.
Still, they won't be able to get around our iron wall.
So why aren't they acting the least bit nervous?
When we played against Nekoma...
Who can tell me why our special technique didn't work?
Ooh! 'Cause Inuoka's too awesome!
That's uh... not quite the answer I
was looking for, but you're not wrong.
It's because of their middle blocker...
He learned Hinata's movements.
Uh-huh... that's it.
That wasn't all though.
Nekoma had another star player that made
things complicated for us. What was his name?
The one with the two-toned hair.
Kenma!
Seriously dude, what do you have a cold or something?!
I'm fine Inuoka. Just leave me alone.
To tell you the truth, I didn't expect them
to come up with a countermeasure that quickly...
But once the word gets around, every team is gonna learn
how to adapt to that Hinata-Kageyama combo we've got.
Don't get me wrong... It's a deadly weapon, but
it's not invincible... The most important thing is...
Is how we use it.
Tanaka!
Got it!
Even flawless read-blocking is no
match for Hinata's breakneck speed!
That was intense!
Yeah!
There's that monster quick-attack.
That move is killer.
It's a game-changer... That's for sure.
Nothing pisses me off worse than a prodigy.
That was a crazy set...
It's like he sent the ball extra hard
just to get Aone out of the way or something.
It had to have been calculated.
The spiker hit it perfectly.
There's no way they planned to
do that. It must have been a fluke!
That kid...
Have you ever seen him before?
No sir... Well at least not from the
most recent middle-school tournament anyway.
Was it a fluke... or not?
It's all you, Tsukishima!
Yep.
Hey, your highness... How about a
little something a further from the net...
I'd like to stay clear of their blockers.
Sure, asshole.
Huh?
I said sure, okay?!
Look, I know it's not easy for you to take orders from us
peasant commoners, but I'm here to win if you don't mind.
What?!
Guys, knock it off, now's not really the time!
Looks like Kageyama finally
busted out that quick attack, huh?
Date Tech must be shaking in their shoes...
And for good reason, you won't find another
technique like that combo attack in the whole world.
It's something else, alright.
Great job, dumbass!
There's still plenty of things they
could stand to improve upon though.
I got you!
Show 'em what you got, man!
You see, that was just a normal set.
He must have been really lucky...
Or only number 10 can pull that move off.
Good job!
That was great, Tsukishima, keep it up!
Go, Tsukki!
Yeah! Time to take back what's ours!
Nice, Kamasaki!
Yeah, that was great!
I don't think so!
Yeah!
The point gap isn't changing.
That's true, but look at the rotation.
Karasuno number 10's back on the front row.
Oh great... him again.
Kageyama hasn't thrown any of those crazy
sets since his number 10 left the front...
And come to think of it, when I
saw him play back in middle school,
I seem to remember him repeatedly leaving Kitagawa's
spiker in the lurch with impossible balls just like that.
I know, and as soon as I saw him set before...
I was really afraid he had
gone back to his old bad habits.
But then...
Their number 10 hit it.
Almost like it was planned out.
Futakuchi!
That's how it's done!
Date Tech's pretty tenacious, aren't they?
Yeah, now that Karasuno's number
10's moved up to the front...
Date's best blocker number 7's up there too.
Unstoppable force meets immovable object.
They're probably thinking that superhuman
quick attack was just happenstance.
Let's go all in!
Right!
It's in! Forward!
He saved it! That's nuts!
But there's no way they can do a quick
from there. Where's he gonna send it?
That's right!
Excellent work, you two!
The kid did it again! The exact same
lightning-fast set but even farther back from the net!
You mean that wasn't... just a fluke?
Let's go!
Oh, wow. Date Tech just called for a time-out.
Dude, is that number 10 even human?
How is he able to hit all those sets?
Technically it's not the spiker who's so amazing.
It's the setter who lines up the
ball for him to hit it so perfectly.
Tch!
It's like watching a pair of fine-tuned robots...
We were mind-blown the first time, too.
If that quick attack is for real,
we won't be able to read-block it.
But if we don't counter somehow...
Then that'll be just as bad as throwing in the towel.
If it looks like number 10
might attack, don't mark the set.
Mark him. Stay one step ahead of his jump.
There's still the possibility that
it was just luck, so keep that in mind.
Don't concentrate too hard on it,
just stay cool and play it by ear.
Right!
I don't think I've ever seen anything like that before.
Do you think he's the only one that can do that move?
If that wasn't a fluke, then
they've gotta be some kind of monsters.
True, that quick attack was pretty terrifying...
But if we focus too hard on that, they're
just gonna sneak past us with a normal attack.
It's not that big a deal...
All we really have to do is stop their number 10.
You're way too chill, you know that?
Better than having no chill.
That's why you can't get a girlfriend.
What'd you say to me?!
Aone, you know what to do!
But still... if Date can stop
that number 10, they'll be golden.
Hm?
I mean, he's the only Karasuno guy who seems to be
untouchable when it comes to Date Tech's iron wall.
Yeah, I guess so.
Either way, we know we have our strategy planned out!
Yeah!
We've gotta do something about that number 10.
Number 10.
That's right, Kageyama...
We're building a reputation with
everybody talking about our little red 10...
So we need Hinata to shine bright out there.
Bring it on!
Jeez, you're slow! We almost missed the game!
Yeah well we actually had some customers for once!
Hurry, hurry!
Um?
Oh, good, we made it! The boys
are still playing round two!
Can't believe they're beating Date Tech!
Bring it here!
Huh?
Damn, that guy is really fast...
Whatever, we at least tried, right?
Huh? What was that?
So quick!
Those two are first-years, aren't they?
Did you guy see how high that little guy can jump?
What are you looking so smug for?
Great work, Hinata!
Who's that?
Right! Now do another quick attack just like that!
Make it count!
So Suga's not in the lineup?
Nishinoya!
Go!
Give it here!
Which one of them will it be?
He's jumping!
Ah, o-or not?!
That was a normal one.
So I guess they're setting at
different speeds for different situations.
You just think that because you haven't
seen these crazy first-years we got.
They still have a lot of work
to do, but if they keep trying,
I really believe Karasuno High's gonna
have the perfect volleyball team one day.
I get it.
Damn it. Who is that little guy?
Alright, alright!
Don't lose focus!
Remember, you're putting in
some good work out there too...
Their number 10 might have caught you off guard, but
you guys have outdone all kinds of spikers in the past...
Including Karasuno's ace!
And this time is no different!
Right!
Why do you keep saying "you guys"?
You're part of this team too, you know?!
Futakuchi...
And I always thought you were
just a dumb, bratty underclassman!
Wow, thanks a lot, pal.
Yeaaaahhh!
Nice kill, Aone!
Whoa, did that guy really just jump twice?!
Well, I guess when you're that enormous, even
a little jump can put your hand over the net.
Not only is he tall, he's got long
arms and broad shoulders to his advantage.
But there's even more to him than that.
He's calm enough not to get tunnel vision, plus
he's got the tenacity to stop the ball no matter what.
Those two traits combined, are
what make his blocks so incredible.
Check it out... Now that's a block.
Yeah, that kind of technique
can completely turn things around.
So if Karasuno doesn't score the next
point, then Date Tech will just ride the wave.
We'll stop this too!
Yeah!
Let's go! Keep your head in the game!
Come on!
Futakuchi! You got this!
Cover me!
Open!
All you!
Center!
Hinata!
Right!
Yeah!
Nishinoya!
Kageyama!
Here!
Three attackers up front... which one?!
Bring it here!
Number 10!
I have to create a path...
for the ace!
And then the view from the other side is totally clear!
Yeah...
I remember!
Ooooh yeaaaaah!
Hey, wasn't that...
The same pipe Nekoma did?!
Asahi!
You guys are great... I really mean it.
Thank you so much.
Are you kidding me? That was all you, dude!
Good job, Asahi!
Please blaze a trail for Asahi too!
Yes!
Hey, what's the matter?
Well, I... I wasn't the one who scored that last point.
I can't take the glory...
Number 10!
But still, it...
It felt really good.
Like I said, decoy... Your job is just as cool.
The greatest decoy...
I get it.
Alright... at this point, we've showed
'em every weapon we've got in our arsenal.
Now...
The real work begins.
It's changed.
What's changed, Aone?
Karasuno.
No kidding!
Now that they have that setter and the short
guy, it's hard to figure out where to block-
The manager's girly hairstyle.
Oh, that?
Our next Haikyu!! "Back protection".