You're not fast enough! Can't you jump any higher?!
More.. More.. More!
Why? Why didn't you jump?
'Cause we've had enough of your
crap... Mr. "king of the court."
Gah!
Tch!
Good morning, everybody.
Hello, there.
Hey look! It's that pretty girl!
You're looking as beautiful as ever, Kiyoko!
So do you think she's the team manager or something?
Ah yeah, ignoring me!
Alright, let's get started.
Huh?
I'll play on Tsukishima's team to make it three-on-three.
Huh?! Is that fair though?!
Don't worry, of course it is. Tanaka's
got a lot more attack power than me.
I won't go easy on you though.
Well, ahem... the buzzcut or the shorty,
who to crush... I mean, challenge first?
So hard to choose... But I do know
I'd like to save his highness for last.
Uh... Tsukki? They can hear you... be careful.
I know, genius, I want them to hear me... I
can't wait to watch the king fall apart out there.
Well now... you've got quite
a personality there, don't you?
It'll have to be a pretty great show to top watching
him get abandoned by all of his loyal subjects last year.
Hm?
Well, well!
Didja hear that, you guys? They're talking trash
now... That jerk had better.. Just.. Stepppp oooooff!
Or he's dead meat.
Blegh!
He just got it right past that giant first-year guy!
He's even stronger than usual!
Yyyeaaaaahhhh!
Put your shirt on!
Yeah, calm down!
Nobody wants to see that.
This is what happens when you get Tanaka too worked up.
Tch!
Heh, so little...
Front!
Got it!
Hey, I can do that too!
Hinata!
That's my set! This'll be my very
first spike in a high school game!
Hm?
I'm gonna score!
There's another wall in my way... a big.. Big wall.
You took me by surprise before...
you have a really nice jump there...
Now if only you were about a foot taller, you'd be
a real superstar. Better start taking your vitamins.
He's only one guy!
Whatever! One more!
I got this one for sure!
Blocked again.
How many times is that?
Tanaka's getting a lot through, though.
Nice one, Tsukki!
Nice block, Tsukishima!
Ah, man.
Thanks. Damn...
He's better than I thought.
You better snap out of it, buddy, or
you're going to keep getting blocked.
Why not give him one of your royal sets...
the kind that wipes out your opponents...
And your teammates at the same time!
Shut your mouth.
Your serve, Tadashi!
Agh!
Tch!
Uh... Oops... sorry, Tsukki.
Shake it off!
We don't need quick attacks.
Time to win.
Alright you got this! Do it!
I remember Kageyama's jump serve, it was pretty amazing.
I can score all the points we need!
Ha!
Tadashi!
Leave it to me!
Damn.
Nice toss, Tsukki!
You're doing great.
Steady receives like that are Daichi's specialty.
They've got mad defense.
Did you think I would be a weak spot?
I may not have as much raw talent as you, but I've
been training on receives for a lot longer than you have.
You won't break through that easily.
Wow, he sounds cool.
Your grace!
Shouldn't you be taking this seriously?
Dude, what's the matter with you?! Why do you keep
picking on the guy?! Chill out with the freakin' nickname!
What for? Do you even know why everybody
started calling him the king of the court?
I thought his enemies called him that...
Because he's really good player...
and well everybody was so afraid of him.
That's a commonly misunderstanding,
but it's just not true.
Huh?
Well, if the rumors are to be believed,
then his nickname king of the court...
was given to him by the other players of Kitagawa first...
Yeah, that's right, by his
own teammates... the truth is...
They were not paying him a
compliment, but calling him a tyrant.
I've been hearing about it for a long time...
but now that I've seen him play, I'm convinced...
He got benched at the finals because he
was a domineering, power-tripping dictator.
Hm?
Kita go! Kita go! Kita go! Kita go!
Alright!
They block so high!
I'll have to use a faster attack to shake them off.
Something they won't be able to get to in time.
Hey, it's okay.
I guess.
Move faster!
Tch!
Our serve!
Go right!
Nice!
Cut it out! Can't you set it like a normal
person? What's the point if we can't hit it?!
One more to go, you guys!
If I can't shake their blockers, we'll never win!
Is this the end? Is this how we're gonna lose?
No! I have to go to nationals!
If your sorry asses ever expect to win anything,
you'd better learn to adapt to the way I set!
Huh?
End of the first set.
Set point for the opponent. I set the ball up.
But no one was there to hit it.
We had messed up several combinations that day...
But that was not a mistake.
It was a rebellion.
They wanted to make it absolutely
clear that they were done with me.
Kageyama.
Huh?
It's time for you to go back to the bench.
That's why you won't try a quick attack.
You're still shaken up over what happened that day.
You know what, I've had enough of your smarmy ass-.
Tanaka.
Huh?
Well, why bother setting if
there's no one there to spike it?
You're right.
Hm?
The thought of nobody being there to back me up...
It terrifies me, alright?
Yeah, but that was back in middle school.
Your sets are gonna reach me... no question about it.
After that.. The only problem is
how to get it past this jerkhole!
You need to kick Tsukishima's ass, join
the volleyball club and become the setter,
just like we planned! Then you have to
send the ball to me! It's not that complicated!
Oh shut up... that over-the-top annoying
little attitude of yours... is disgusting.
Hm?
And enthusiasm won't make you any taller. If
you think trying hard is all it takes to succeed...
You're sorely mistaken.
I got this, to you!
Tanaka!
Give it to me now!
Give it back, give it back, give it back!
Who do I send it to?
Over here! I'm open!
I don't know that Hinata can beat this guy.
Tanaka!
Kageyama!
No one... was there.
I'm here!
Gah!
Arglgh!
That was close... Almost jumped
at nothing... But it's out.
What the hell was that for?!
The ball came right towards me!
I don't care about what happened in middle
school! I'm grateful for any set that comes my way!
I just want the ball! I'll jump
anywhere! I'll hit any ball! Believe me!
Give me a set... And I'll hit it!
Kageyama planned to send that to Tanaka, I know it.
But when he picked up on Hinata's voice and
movement, he tossed to him with perfect accuracy.
He might have a sharp tongue and a bad attitude...
But he really is something else.
You guys can do quick attacks and you didn't tell me?!
What's that?
That crazy-fast attack you just did!
Uh? Uh-uh... no... the only sets
I've ever hit were way up in the air.
You literally just did it!
Look, remember in middle school when that rookie setter
messed up that set and you hit it anyway? Like that!
Huh? But I don't even remember how I did it.
Whatever, I'll still hit any set
that comes at me! You just wait and see!
You've never done combos before,
so that's impossible for you.
Impossible?! Does he even hear himself right now?!
Don't be ridiculous! You don't
get to act like a wimp! Just stop it!
Ugh.
Uh...
Not very regal of you, sire.
You're gonna pay for that I promise you!
Look at that... getting all bent out of shape again.
You can't just bulldoze your way
through everything. You know that, right?
Not everyone's a good fit for every job, you know.
I mean, you're clearly not cut out to be a spiker.
You're right. In middle school...
Even now... no matter how much
I jump, I always get blocked.
Height is important for volleyball...
You can't always just jump real high
to make up for being short like me.
But still...
That never stopped me from wanting to be a spiker.
I don't care whether I'm cut out for it or not.
I'll do the best I can with what I've got and I'll win!
I'm on this court and I'm not going anywhere.
No.
I'm not leaving...
I want to stay on the court the longest!
Have you even listened to a word I've
said? It doesn't really work that way, shorty.
You can't substitute spirit for height.
Unless you want to be a libero, that is.
Give a set and I'll hit it!
I open up the wall and block the spiker.
That's the setter's job!
Whoa, what gives, Kageyama?!
Gah, let go! You're hurting me!
Hey man, could you chill?!
What the-gah!
Listen up. If you can't make the shot...
Then I want you to go around them and hit my
sets with all the power and agility you've got.
Huh?! That's how you explain quick attacks?!
Got it.
There is no way you got that!
We have to at least give it a try!
What's with you? Not 2 minutes ago
you were nothin' but doom and gloom.
I was not.
You lie!
Okay...
Serve it!
Ready to go!
He should have the speed and reflexes to hit a quick set.
Bring it on, Kageyama! Show me what you've got!
Go, Tsukki!
We haven't established any signals, so for now...
Got it, so he's gonna set it that way.
Nice!
That's weaker than Mrs. Yoshida's serve...
Once it comes my way, I'll just-ggh!
Ah...
Oh. Faster than I thought.
How'd you miss that! You have to-
Nice ball, your highness!
Nothing ever works out on the first try!
Hey, that's what losers say.
Hwph! Gaaah!
Gwah! I touched it that ti-oof!
You look like a fish!
I can't guess your timing at all.
You have lightning-fast reflexes! You
just need to give it more "pow!" More "oomph!"
Is it oomph or pow?! Make up your mind!
Don't get caught up in the terminology!
Kageyama.
Hm?
You need to make sure you don't let history repeat itself.
Uhh... what I mean is, uh...
He's got super fast reflexes and uh... He
can jump! He can learn how to quick attack!
That's not really what I'm getting at though...
I think I know how you guys can be more effective.
Hmmm?
Hinata doesn't really know what he's doing out there.
That's kinda harsh...
He doesn't have technique or experience like a lot
of the people you competed against in middle school.
But he's a rare asset.
Huh?! Really?! Aww come on, I'm
not like a genius or anything...
Who said that?
If I had your skill... I mean, think about it...
Maybe you should try adapting to more of Hinata's
characteristics instead of the other way around,
don't you see what I'm saying? Then...
Take it easy, Suga!
It's up to you to use his talents more effectively!
I'm a setter like you, so I was honestly
pretty freaked out when I saw you play last year.
You've got incredible talent and control over the ball...
But most of all, you're good at analyzing the opponent's
blocking moves and you make decisions on the fly.
I've got... none of those things.
Don't you say crap like that-
Hold on... just let him talk, okay?
You're good at what you do and
have almost too much determination...
But your ability to assess your
surroundings is your most important skill.
So pay closer attention to your allies!
Hm?
Hup!
Use his talents more effectively?!
The ball came right towards me!
Hm?
Listen...
Uh! Uh-huh?!
I'm jealous of your crazy reflexes, alright?
Huh?!
That's right... That's why you
piss me off. It's such a waste!
Huh?!
That said!
All I can do now is use your talent to the fullest!
What the?
You're gonna run at full speed... And
you're gonna jump as high as you can.
I'll deliver the ball to you!
What do you mean by... "Deliver the ball"?
All you have to do is jump at Max height and Max speed
wherever there's an opening.. And swing at full power.
Forget adjusting to the ball...
you don't even need to see the ball.
Huh?! How can I hit if I don't even see it?!
I don't know!
What?!
Just... try, okay?
Alright.
What are those two plotting over there? I mean,
no one wants to deal his majesty's selfish ways.
Exactly.
Hope they've got a plan...
Hinata's not gonna be able to adjust
to those tosses without some practice.
Let's go! One point!
He's in the zone.
See now.
Where are the blockers? Where's the ball?
Where's the spiker? What's his next move?
Where will he jump, and how high is he going to go?
Now! This position! This angle! This moment!
Yes!
Ah... whoa...
I... I touched the ball!
It wasn't that great...
Guys...
He just did that... With his eyes closed.
Huh?!
What?! No way!
From the moment his feet left the floor to the
second he swung his arm, Hinata's eyes were closed.
Kageyama just made a pinpoint toss into Hinata's
hand, but Hinata wasn't even looking at the ball!
I don't know how he did it, but his timing was perfect!
Huh?
That's awesome! You guys! I dunno what happened,
but I just hit something! Did you see that?! Huh?!
Hey! What'd you do?! Your eyes
weren't really shut, were they?!
Um, well you're the one who
told me not to look at the ball!
If I kept my eyes open, I knew I would look at it.
I wasn't telling you to...
But... but it worked, right? What's the big deal?
I know it worked... but what kind
of person acts totally on trust?!
I can't help it! Trust is the
only way I know how to do it!
What have you been wasting all
your time on for three years?!
His mobility and jumping power...
That was crazy! Nice one, dude!
My sets can enhance that!
Tanaka, if we can score with Hinata's spike, then our
marks'll scatter and make it easier for you to strike too.
Yeah!
Right on!
Look, I know we don't have any
special trust built up or anything...
Hm?
But I'll deliver the next ball to you. So jump, okay?
Here!
Sorry.
Hmm... I guess that first time was a fluke.
Yeah, but I can tell their
precision's already starting to improve.
Uh? You really think so?
Mm-hm.
That was a nice one, Hinata.
Man... Too far away from the net that time.
That hurt...
This really is tough...
Keeping up with everything that happens
on the court is exhausting... but...
It's fun!
What're you smiling about?! This is the
second time I've been smacked in the face!
I'm not buying it... that had to be a one-time
thing... why are they even still trying it?
Well guess what... Hinata's probably gonna jump
without looking at the ball about a million more times.
I'm starting to think you do this on purpose.
You're right though, it is pretty unbelievable...
You do know we have to win, right?
It's difficult to trust another person 100%.
Especially your sworn enemy.
Aw maaaan, it's not working... but...
I definitely felt it that one time...
I felt the heaviness of the core of the ball.
I really like that feeling.
Just one more try.
More carefully this time. A set that gives
the spiker the chance to use maximum force.
Got it! Here!
Nice receive!
Looks like he gave it to short-stack by mistake...
Let's just keep our eyes on the skinhead fella.
Hey Tadashi!
Oh!
The wall!
Listen up... if you can't make the shot...
Go around!
I'm shorter than the tall players.
So I need that extra inch, that extra second...
To reach the peak!
For this one single moment in time...
I'm at the highest point!
There's a big, tall wall in front of me, blocking my way.
I wonder what's waiting on the other
side? What's the view like over there?
It's something I'll never be able to see on my own.
It's the view...
from the summit.
Yes!
You can't just spike with your eyes closed! Who are you?!
I don't believe this.
This is getting kinda crazy, huh?
Send me the next one too, would ya?
Calm down!
Aww... anyway, next Haikyu:
"The first time jitters."