My first and last real game in middle
school... we got our butts kicked.
We lost to the king of the court, and I
swore I'd challenge him to a revenge match.
After all that happened, I
enrolled at Karasuno high school.
But now...
No... wait...
Why? What is this guy doing at Karasuno?
No... it's gotta be somebody else.
Why did you come to this tournament anyway?
Not giving up is a lot easier said than done!
I'm gonna be the one in the winner's court!
What did you waste your time on for three years, huh?!
Nope, it's him. That jerk really is here! Tobio Kageyama.
We met last year. I forgot your name.
M-My name's Shoyo Hinata, okay?!
But I'm sure you don't even remember who
I am. I mean, you destroyed us in one game!
I remember exactly who you are.
He's got amazing reflexes, he
can jump high, and he's fast.
But he doesn't use those
abilities to their full potential.
What's with the silent treatment?!
What, you wanna fight or something?!
Oh, don't be a dumbass!
Er...
Don't make fun of me!
I might've lost really bad the
first time we met... but never again!
Look! I came here to get my revenge and now I
find out you're gonna be on the same team as me?!
How am I supposed to kick your butt that way?!
There's tons of better schools you could have gone to!
Why'd you have to pick this one?
Why didn't you go to one of those instead?
I applied to the school with the best team...
But...
Didn't make it.
You didn't?
They rejected the king of the court?
Never call me that... ever!
Who knew the setter from Kitagawa
first would end up at our school?
He better not be too cocky. Or I'll have to pound him one.
Give it a rest, Tanaka... you
don't have to threaten everybody.
What are you gonna do about it,
huh? Yeah, that's what I thought.
Uh... hello.
Well, well, well... Now what do we have here-.
You Kageyama?
Yeah.
It's nice to meet you.
Pretty tall, aren'tcha?
First impressions are everything, Suga!
You're a third-year, so you have to establish dominance!
Stop it, Tanaka... you look stupid.
Kageyama's a little taller than them...
But wow, these high schoolers are all pretty huge!
I can't believe I'm really here! This'll be great!
Hey guys!
So how tall are you?
Uh..
Six feet.
Hey dudes?
Six feet?
Excuse me?
That's badass.
Hey!
Huh? Hey.. It's you!
You're the shorty!
Wait a minute... So the other applicant goes by
the name of Shoyo Hinata... I guess that's you?
It's just... kind of surprising, that's all...
But hey! You guys both chose Kurasuno!
Guess so...
Didn't mean to freak you out，
it's just you made a big impression last year.
Yeah, you were tiny and all over the
place, but you really had some spunk!
Wow, thanks a lot!
And not to mention that jump of yours.
It's too bad you haven't hit a growth spurt yet though.
I know! I may be small, but I've got talent!
I'll be karasuno's ace before you know it!
Hot damn! Already got your eyeballs on the
ace position, do ya? Somebody's got cajones.
Well, there's nothing wrong with
shooting for the stars, is there? Right?
Yeah! I'll do my best!
Okay then... Now that you've sworn to become the ace...
You'd better be prepared to back it up.
If you're not careful, you'll waste another three years.
Excuse me?
Was that really necessary, Kageyama?
I did everything I could!
I did!
Look... I've done a lot! Stop putting me down!
Relax, guys... you know you're not enemies anymore, right?
Volleyball supposed to bring people together-
I want you to play me right now!
Whoa, watch it, punk, don't you
know Daichi's talking to you?!
What are we gonna play?
Volleyball, what the heck else is there?!
How do you plan to play volleyball one-on-one?
Like, passes and stuff!
How does anybody win at that?
The kid's got a point!
What's all the noise in here?
Oh turds, VP...
Be quiet!
Why don't you be quiet!
Are you boys fighting in here?
No, we're just working hard as
always, vice principal, right?
We gotta watch ourselves around the vice
principal. That guy's always waiting for us to slip up!
Serve it to me! I can handle whatever you send!
Dude!
Listen, jerk... I only received
one serve from you last year...
Granted it was with my face.
But since then I've practiced with everyone I could!
I am not the same person I was!
Hmph.
Not the same person, huh?
Well, I've improved a bit in the last year too.
Alright, alright... that's enough smack-talk, you guys.
They're both first-years, aren't they?
Don't let him get to you. Remember everything
you learned from practicing with the ladies' team!
Get ready.
A jump serve?! That's new.
Not even I could catch that!
I never saw a serve like that from
any of the ladies I played with...
Pathetic. How's that different than last year?
One more try.
Okay... now cut it out.
I see the new recruits have no respect for their captain.
Nice reflexes!
He got right behind it, now he can control it.
If this keeps-.
Or not...
Oh man, that was a toupee?
You just now figured that out? I
noticed it at the entrance ceremony.
Dude! Shut up! It's not even that funny!
You shut up, Moron!
Captain... a word please?
Luckily, we're not in trouble.
He doesn't even want an apology.
But we have been sworn to secrecy.
And as for if you two...
If you'd handled the serve, it wouldn't
have happened in the first place!
You're the same klutz you were last year. I
can't believe I thought you'd be a challenge.
You don't know when to quit, do you?
Can it! There's something I want to tell you.
I don't know what your reasons were for
choosing to come to this high school...
But... I assume you came to win.
Yeah!
Yes, obviously.
Up until a few years ago, Karasuno's volleyball
team could compete with the best of them...
They even made it to nationals once.
But these days we're 8th in the prefecture.
Not terrible, but not good either.
And people talk. They call us...
The wingless crows.
I remember when Karasuno played in
the Spring High National Tournament...
I was a student at a nearby school who
just happened to be in the neighborhood.
Watching them fight those tough
opponents in that huge gym in Tokyo...
It gave me chills.
Let's go back.. One more time!
We're going to play on the
same court the tiny giant played!
The nationals, huh?
Plenty of high schools talk about making
it there one day... Doesn't mean they'll go.
Wha-?! You little...
I know what you mean. But I'm dead serious.
If we want to get there, we need to be a cohesive unit.
That means no more run-ins with the VP, for one thing.
It's not like I'm telling you to be
best friends or anything like that.
I know back in middle school you two might
have been adversaries on opposite sides of the net...
But let me be clear... you're on one side
now and you need to make peace with that.
Is that clear?
I don't care how good you are.
Or how determined you are to play hard.
Anyone who lets a petty rivalry get
in the way of the team's success...
Gets the boot!
You two are banned from participating in club activities
until you learn to think of yourselves as teammates!
Huh?!
"L-Learn to think of ourselves
as teammates"?! What's that mean?!
Beats me!
Please let me in, captain! Please
let me play volleyball with you!
I'll find a way to get along with Kageyama, I promise!
Come on, I'm really sorry! I'll do anything!
Are you sure this is wise?
I mean we need players. You can't build a team
by threatening people to cooperate. It takes time.
Yeah I know... but...
I apologize! I won't pick any more fights with him!
Please let me be on the team!
You mean that?
I can do it. I'll share the court with him if I have to...
But I still want to do it all myself...
Every spike, receive and set in the game.
What is wrong with you?!
I wasn't expecting you to be that honest with me...
Hey, well, it's good enough for now... but you know...
In volleyball, it's against the rules to
drop, carry, or touch the ball twice in a row...
In other words, this game is impossible to play alone.
So are you mean... Or just stupid?
Go right!
Tanaka, follow through with your block!
Sure thing, boss!
There's a court and a ball right
in front of me. It's such a tease.
Ugh! This is such a stupid waste
of time! I have to get back in there!
But we're not teammates yet, are we?
I have a lot of potential!
That should be more than enough
for them to let me join the team.
Spoken like a true ki... uh.. So what are you gonna do?
We'll challenge them to a two-on-two and
if we win then they have to let us join...
That way we can at least look like we're
working together as teammates... it's foolproof.
Y-You mean we have to beat them?! What if we lose?
We won't lose... I'll make sure.
Whoa, is he serious?! Does he even hear himself?!
You need to do the you best you can. No screw-ups.
Do not drag me down, understand?
Huh?! Don't talk to me like that! Who's ever
gonna listen to you if you treat them like trash?!
Then what's your plan?
Just sit here and watch through the window forever?
My first game... and my only game...
Was the time we played against you.
We never had enough players for tournaments
before that, and I had no place to play.
So I used to practice in the corner of the gym
or in an empty hallway, or wherever I could.
Really?
So when I got to play my first game...
And I stood in the middle of that huge gymnasium...
I felt like the main character
in a movie. It was like, "whoaaaa!"
"Whoa?"
I wanted to stay forever.
But only the strongest...
Get to stay on the court.
Anyway... they're not gonna let
one of us in without the other.
If I get to play volleyball...
Then nothing's too much to deal with.. Not even you!
If I try not to look at you.. I
don't have to see your dumb face!
Keep talking, short stack!
Excuse me.
I... need to get through.
Hey Kiyoko! Thanks for your hard work! Let me get that...
No, thanks. I can carry it myself.
Okay then... you look super gorgeous today.
Ohhh man, she's so pretty when she ignores me!
Good work, everybody!
You know what I bet those two
goofballs are thinking right now.
That if they can beat us, then
they'll make the team, right?
Yeah sure... but all they really have to do is cool off
and prove to everybody that they've learned their lesson.
Captain!
Huh!
We challenge you to a match!
If we win, you have to let us join!
Guys, I'm psychic!
Now!
We want to prove that we finally
understand how to play together as teammates!
How many times did you rehearse that?
This is gold! I could get used
to having these clowns on the team!
If you lose?
Then you get to choose the penalty!
Huh...
Club application form. Here's an idea...
We have two other first-years joining the club soon.
You'll play against them in a three-on-three match.
We do this game every year with our new club members
so we can get an idea of how they play.
But if it's gonna be three-on-three...
then whose going to be our third player?
Tanaka... you're with them...
make sure they behave, alright?
Aww man, why me?
Well you seem to like them.
Don't drag me into their mess!
That's too bad.
I was thinking you'd be the only one tough
enough to keep these delinquents in line.
Aww well, why the heck not? When you put it like that...
Just stick with me, little man!
Anyway, here's the penalty if you lose. For
the remainder of my time here at Karasuno...
Kageyama cannot be the setter.
Huh?
Is that the only penalty we have, sir?
If the setter is aggressive, self-centered,
and driven by his own ego... the team can't win.
What? I'm not saying I'll reject your application to join.
I'm sure you'll be well-suited to a different position.
No way, I'm a setter!
Then win the game.
You're the one who thought you
could win without help, right?
Hey, uh.. But what about me?!
We play on Saturday.
Come on! I'm over here too, you know?
Don't worry! Your cool upperclassman's
gonna show you the ro-waahh!
See ya!
Daichi... are you being a little too harsh?
He's right, boss, you're acting
a lot more strict than usual.
Yeah, is there some special reason you're doing this?
Dammit!
What's wrong? Are you mad because
you're the only one who gets penalized?
Even if you're not a setter, I bet you'd
figure out a different position just like that!
Plus... spikers are cooler than setters anyway!
They get to go up and slam the ball!
Shut up!
The setter is the team's control tower!
Plus, it's the position that
gets the most contact with the ball!
It's the greatest position there
is because you get to be the ruler!
Without a setter to toss the ball, there
wouldn't be any spikes for you to hit!
I know, but even though the setter has an important job,
you don't really stand out very much, do you?
I'm guessing you've never seen a major
volleyball tournament in person, have you?
No.
You can't tell by the angle they show on TV,
but pay attention to the end of the court...
From there, you can see how
fast the setter tosses the ball.
It flies straight across the court... woah!
The ball passes right in front of the face of
the other team's blockers... then!
Just when you start to think "no
way! He's never gonna hit that one!"
There's a spiker just waiting to strike...
and he smashes the ball in just in time!
Y-Yeah...
The spiker's job may be flashier... but...
The spiker can't get through without the setter
to get the opponent to block and break the wall!
It's the most important, cool, and
challenging position on the court, okay?!
Yeah sure, fine, I get it, you wanna be the setter.
Kageyama cannot be the setter.
Dammit! What's with that guy?!
All you have to do is win. You seemed pretty
confident when you challenged them to a match earlier.
He's right. Not that he'll be any help. I'll just
focus on setting up tosses for that creepy second-year.
Okay! We've got until Saturday
to work on your crappy receiving!
Crappy?! Uh, but we can't get into the gym...
Huh...
Ahem!
I forget... we start practice at 7 am tomorrow, don't we?
Uh, yeah...? Is that a problem?
Ah! Not at all... a-anyway, do you think the
vice principal's nappy rug made it out alive?
We're not supposed to talk about that...
Alright then.
5 am.
Don't be late.
I won't.
Ah, wait! Hang on, I forgot my bag!
Shoulda seen that coming.
It's locked.
Okay, let's go through the window.
Are you crazy?! We'd end up getting expelled!
Man, 5 am is too early...
Tanaka?!
You got 2 hours... and then beat it!
You're awesome!
Thank you!
Yeah, who's your hero, first-years? Call me sir Tanaka!
Sir Tanaka!
What was that?
Okay, punks, let's get crackin'!
He's right, boss, you're acting
a lot more strict than usual.
Yeah, is there some special reason you're doing this?
Well, sort of... you saw those
two play last year... think back.
Kageyama had exceptional talent for a middle schooler,
but now he's got almost nothing to show for it...
If nothing changes, that lone wolf personality
of his will hold him back in high school too.
I don't want him dragging this team
down... the big difference now is...
That he and Hinata are on the same team.
What, Hinata? Oh yeah, I guess he's
kind of a crazy ball of energy and agility.
Right, but he hasn't reached his potential.
He's got incredible speed and quick
reflexes, not to mention that jumping power...
But he never played with a real setter before.
Kageyama, on the other hand, wants a
spiker fast enough to hit the sets he makes.
Separately, their abilities are
limited. But put them together...
And let them work on some combinations...
Karasuno will have the perfect team!
It's gonna be fantastic.
Outta my way! I'm gonna be the first one on that court!
You can't be first if Tanaka's already in, dumb-ass!
Then why don't you let me go!?
We don't have time for this...
Sorry, boss, we've got a long
way to go on those combinations.
Wow, check it out!
You were just here yesterday.
This is the same gym where
the tiny giant used to practice.
Alright! Let's do this!
Leave it to you to ruin things from the start.
What?! You're the one who
thinks you can play without a team!
I'd rather go it alone than work with you!
Why are you so stubborn?!
Clock's ticking!
Less yapping, more practicing!
Right!
Next Haikyu, "the most powerful ally."