Come on! Gimme another one!
Alright, shut up, I get it! Ready?
Yeah!
Ah!
Gah! That felt so good!
And once I reach the top of my
jump, the ball hits my hand...
And when the weight of it... Sorta
leaves a sting in my palm... I love that!
Sweet! Those cats won't stand a
chance against our quick-attacks!
Huh? Cats? Are they playing against Nekoma?
We've got ourselves a practice
game... It's the last day of camp.
Aahh!
Hey what's your problem?! Don't run away from me!
I'm getting out of here. You scare me when you get mad!
Well it's not like I'm mad all the time!
We weren't expecting this... We know nothing about them...
And the rivalry feels like an old folktale...
I mean it was the generation before
us... so it was never really relevant to us.
But now... it's time to face off, crows versus cats!
It's so strange to think that we're about to
have our first rematch with Nekoma in years...
I gotta say I'm pretty psyched about it.
It's just Suga...
And well of course Nishinoya, too...
I can't face them.
You know what, Asahi...
You really are pretty timid,
especially for such a big guy!
And Nishinoya's the opposite of that.
And you could stand to be a lot less blunt...
Anyway, it'll be fine... Nobody else
on the team has a problem with it...
Unlike you, they're pretty open-minded.
Uh, Daichi? I thought I remembered you being nicer.
I'll be nicer when you stop being such a wuss.
I don't care so much about you skipping
out of club activities for a month,
and then feeling awkward about finally coming back.
Because if you still love volleyball...
That's reason enough to play.
Not just that...
But we've got this new kid whose dream is to be the ace.
Ah... hey!
On the banks of the Hirose ri-i-ver...
Memories afloat... On the stream...
Dancing lights... over the rapids-
Hey! What're you doing here?!
Uh I'm sorry! I was just seeing
if you had any customers...
Are you here to ask me to coach again?
Yes.
It's not that I don't still love to play.
I even put together a neighborhood team.
I can't be a coach 'cause I'd
drive myself crazy wanting to play.
Oh...
And besides... I can't go anywhere near that gym.
Ah! Uh... Did something tragic happen there?
Not in the least! All my best memories are there.
Then why can't you?
I don't care if it's totally
different or exactly the way I left it.
I can't go into that gym or the club room ever again.
The short time I spent there was so unique...
If I went back, it'd feel like opening a time capsule.
Oh, so it's a nostalgia thing... 'Kay I get it-
Shut up!
And anyway... it's still a 'no.'
Even if Nekoma High's on the schedule?
The last day of golden week. It's our
first time facing them in five years.
You have got to be kidding me.
Coach Nekomata... the man that your
grandfather used to be such good friends with...
He just came out of retirement. Once I
heard that... I asked them for a practice game.
Back when you were still in high school...
That was when Karasuno had the
strongest ties with them, right?
Yeah.
And by the way... Their current coach...
He is the same guy who played the
setter position about 7 or 8 years ago.
This is our last shot, Ukai.
I want to see you at nationals this year, alright?
Sure!
I'll be there!
That was back when you were active in the club...
So I was thinking... that maybe
you two might know each other.
Hey...
Hm?
Are you trying to mess with me?!
I'm sorry! I'm really sorry!
This is bullshit! You just came here to push my
buttons! Did you really think that would work?!
What time is practice today?
I said I... Huh?
You mean that...?
I'm not letting those pathetic underclassmen
embarrass our school in front of Nekoma.
Stay right here, I'll go get changed.
Okay! Great!
Hey ma, can you watch the store?
Yes!
Hey, uh, Tatsu? It's me.
Huh?
Hey... Noya?
Yeah?
What kinda training did you do while you were suspended?
Hm... I focused on blocked ball retrieval.
So the ball doesn't hit the floor after they block!
I haven't gotten it down perfect yet...
But if I manage to get really good at it...
Then you spikers won't have to
worry... and you can just spike.
Man... every time I see this guy, he's got more bruises.
Noya! How are you such a badass all the time?!
It's nothing to cry about!
Um excuse me!
Alright come over here, guys!
This is Ukai...
As of today, he'll be your coach! Say hello everyone!
Huh?
Whoa, are you serious?! We have a new coach?!
Just until after the Nekoma game.
Huh?
Hey wait... Isn't that the grumpy
guy who runs the Sakanoshita store?
He's coaching us?
He's actually used to go to this
school. He's the old coach Ukai's grandson.
Huh?!
But your store's called Sakanoshita, right?
You shoulda called it Ukai, dude! I mean, sir!
It's named for my mom's side of the family.
Anyway, let's not waste any more time!
I set you up a game for 6:30...
So c'mon let's see what you got.
Huh?!
They're gonna be here soon.
Who will?
Our friendly neighborhood association team.
Because if you still love volleyball,
that's reason enough to play.
Going in!
Okay!
Hup!
Coming your way!
Damn... He won't pick up.
I guess it was too short notice to
get 'em all together on a weekday.
Heads up!
Here.
Um... thanks I appreciate it.
What's up!
Hey.
Oh, man!
Takes me back!
Uh, hi?
We're the Neighborhood Club Team.
Let's do this!
Hey! Thanks for comin' out at the last minute!
The neighborhood association huh...
I was picturing a bunch of old guys.
Me too.
Alright! You boys ready to play or what?
Yeah! Here we go!
Hm? What's with you? You sick?
Oh... sorry... he's not ready to play yet.
Why not? Is he injured or something? What's wrong?
No, it's not really as straightforward as all that.
So he's not gonna participate then? Well whatever it is..
You can play with us if you want to... our libero's
been pretty tied up with a buncha work stuff.
Do... you want to?
Hm, we're still short a couple
guys. You have more members, don't you?
There's Asahi! Look!
Asahi! Hey!
Agh! It's that short guy again!
Hey, listen, I was just here to uhhh...
You gotta be kidding! Late on the coach's
first day?! What position do you play?!
Uh-wing spiker?
Whatever, I don't care, we need some more
players! Get your ass in here and warm up!
Chop chop, man-bun!
So we just need a setter... I would do it
myself, but I really should watch the game.
Hey, do me a favor and let me
borrow one of your setters, would ya?
Sugawara!
Listen you're not doing this for me, are you?
Because if the only way I can rise up the
ranks is at your expense... I'm not doing it.
You know what...
Whenever you joined the club... I knew
that I had to fight you for the setter spot...
But it was kinda... it was a relief.
The setter is the attack axis for the whole team.
A setter has to be composed and steadfast... but I...
I was too nervous to put the ball in the right spot.
After what happened to Asahi, I was so afraid that
my tosses would cause another spiker to get blocked...
So I was content to just hide in Kageyama's shadow.
It was... easier.
Just the thought of a spike getting
shut down like that terrifies me.
But... please let me... set for you one more time... okay?
I'm playing on their side... oh and...
Hm?
I am not losing.
And me neither.
Now give me some of your famous receives, okay?
Oh you know it.
Asahi decided to come... see?
Yeah well... is he gonna stay?
Thank you!
Looks pretty threatening standing over here.
Alright, kids... Don't poop your pants.
Let's see the ace in action!
Nice receive!
Hey, that was a great set there, buddy!
Really nice job!
Wow! Thank you so much!
Sugawara's killing it!
Well of course he is! Suga's
our official setter, after all!
He's so happy...
Hey, nice going, Suga!
Thanks... but I didn't do anything special.
It's only because they're adjusting
their whole dynamic to suit my play style...
These people are real vets of the game.
Yeah!
My setting still needs quite a bit of work.
Still... we have to start playing hardball...
And get a good handle on those fast attacks too...
If we don't, the game'll ride
on just one player like last time.
You know... you're actually kinda cool.
What? Really? Wow, coming from
you, that's kind of a huge compliment.
Huh? Why's that?
Well uh...
Suga, you've become much more of a leader than I remember.
And Nishinoya is as constant as ever.
And here I am, coming out of nowhere
and just drifting back onto the team...
I'm so pathetic...
But even so...
You can do it!
One more!
I really...
I really do love being here.
Whoa! That was nuts!
Haha! We did it! Hahaha!
He really got some air!
And that set was scary accurate.
That was excellent, you two!
Thanks to Kageyama's amazing
sets I can get past anybody now!
The wall just fades away, and then the
view of the other side is totally clear!
The view of the other side...
We're good!
One more try!
That's a bluff!
Good job, Noya!
Asahi!
Well they did flub that one...
But their libero's a superstar.
My bad! I'll get it next time!
Too bad their attacker's no good.
Blocked again... how many times
has that happened to me now?
I've asked for so many chances. I
promised I would make them count.
But then I was paralyzed by my fear...
And I didn't want to call for them anymore.
What's going on?
Asahi?
Suga, aim right!
D-Daichi!
Uwwwaaah!
Dammit!
I was worthless out there... I
couldn't save a single blocked ball!
Nishi! Why won't you blame me for this?!
I am the one who cost us the game!
Even if you could have saved one, it'd be
pointless because I couldn't make it count-
Asahi!
What exactly do you mean by pointless?
And while we're at it, why didn't
you call for the ball at the end?
Come on you were in the perfect position.
Hey! Just lay off him, Nishinoya!
It was my fault for sending him
too many sets in a row before that-
Even if you did Suga... it wouldn't have mattered anyway.
You never know until you hit
the damn thing! You know that!
The next spike might be the one to break through!
Hey!
Don't you ever give up on a ball...
not while I'm keeping it in for you!
Noya! Take it easy!
I am the libero!
I am the last defense! The team needs me!
But... I can't score us points.
And I can't even attack either... so...
I don't care how many spikes get
blocked... I'd never blame you for that.
But quit... and I'll never be able to forgive you!
A...
Asahi!
Wait, don't go!
Ah...
Tell me... why weren't you there yesterday?
Did you forget or something?
The Inter-High Tournament's coming up.
Yeah where's the fun in hitting
spikes that don't mean anything?
What am I saying? That's not how I feel.
You must be sick of retrieving
balls for no reason... aren't you?
Stop it. Nishinoya doesn't think that way either!
I know Suga feels guilty every time I get blocked-
Oh who gives a damn what anybody else thinks about it?!
What on earth is all the racket about out here?!
Stop shouting in the halls!
Asahi!
Young man-
Don't touch me!
Uh-oh, someone's in trouble.
Don't you want to make a spike that matters?!
Nice one, Hinata!
Thank you!
Hinata... It's your serve.
I was wrong.
Huh?
I know I got stopped by the wall...
But I want to... I want to
keep trying to break through it.
And that's all that matters.
Hm?
That was all I needed to hear from you, Asahi.
My job... is just to keep the ball in play.
Do your best, Hinata!
It's in!
Agh!
My bad! Cover me!
Hey, bun-head! Finish it off!
The sky belongs to the spikers.
I can't compete in their space.
Shut him down!
Yeah I don't take orders from you.
Come on, man, we're playin' for keeps!
But if I can just keep the ball up in the air...
I know I got stopped by the wall... But
I want to keep trying to break through it.
I know I can trust the ace to nail it.
Damn!
Whoa! It's up!
Nice follow-thru!
I focused on blocked ball retrieval, so the
ball doesn't hit the floor after they block!
Great job, Noya!
Even if the ball rebounds off the wall...
I will keep it in play!
So please... You have to ask the setter
for another chance, Asahi! You're the ace!
Cover me!
Right here!
Who do I send the ball to?
The left is open, so it's probably our best bet, but...
what if I cause Asahi to get blocked again?
Sugawara!
Keep throwing it to him... Until he scores!
Oh that's just cruel, your majesty.
Quiet!
When the chips are down and the
receives are all over the place,
you're supposed to trust the ace with the last ball.
I know that... but still...
I can't send Asahi a ball he's not
expecting and make him deal with a triple block.
A spiker can only go for a kill...
After a setter sends him the ball.
Please... let me set for you one more time, okay?
And the set only exists because
the libero kept the ball in play.
Don't ever give up on a ball...
Not while I'm keeping it in for you!
So when I go to do my job, I'm not alone.
Everyone else was doing theirs, but I... I...
It's impossible to win all by yourself.
I mean, come on. That is why they call you the ace!
Because if you still love volleyball...
You have to ask the setter for
another chance, Asahi! You're the ace!
I'm free!
Shimada!
Sugaaaaaaa!
Over here!
Right... our ace is waiting.
He wants me to send it his way.
I'll set high, not too far from the net.
Asahi's favorite toss, the one
I've given him so many times.
It's a simple one, but I'll send
it with as much accuracy as I can.
Why would you bother encouraging them to do that?
You know we have to block him.
Obviously, it's meaningless if we just let him through.
My team has my back.
And my setter knows exactly what works best for me.
Who could ask for more?
Somewhere along the way...
I let myself forget the most simple
and natural thing about this game.
That I'll never have to fight alone!
I will land this hit.
Because I'm the ace!
Tanaka, would you stop crying
and focus on blocking, please?
What?! I-I'm not crying, stupid! This is just...
Right, it's sweat, you've said that a thousand times.
It's just a runny nose.
Whatever. Next Haikyu!! "The dream".