I'll be seeing you at nationals this year.
Hmph! Yeah, that's what you say every year, Ukai.
Oh be quiet! This is going to be the one.
This oughta be good! The trashcan showdown,
cats versus crows! Can't wait to see it!
But that June at the Inter-High preliminaries, both
schools narrowly missed earning a ticket to nationals.
In march of the following year, Karasuno
High, representing Miyagi prefecture,
and Nekoma high, acting as
Tokyo's second representative school,
both appeared at the Spring
High School National Tournament.
Karasuno was defeated in the third game, and Nekoma made
it to the quarterfinals, before they were also eliminated.
After that, the two schools
held many, many practice games...
But both coaches eventually retired without
ever having faced each other in an official match.
These events led to the steady decline
of both teams over the years to come.
But now...
Gah!
Their fated rematch is about to start!
Kenma!
Huh?
Hey.
You're really on the Nekoma team?!
Uh-huh.
How come you didn't tell me that when we met?
Well, you... Didn't ask.
But when you left, you said "later", so
you must've known I was gonna be here, right?!
Uh, you had "Karasuno High School"
written on your t-shirt, so...
Well, well, well!
You know, that's our setter...
What's your business with him?
Calm down.
I... I'm sorry! Ah!
And what about you? Shorty's with us... so
what's your business with him, brush head?!
What's it to you, buddy?
You lookin' to rumble? Eh city boy?
Hm-um yeah you guys are about to rumble...
The game's just about to start.
And stop saying "city boy". Nobody says that.
Yamamoto please...
Could you stop picking fights all the time?
You're making a damn fool of yourself.
Yeah.. That's our team idiot...
You'll just have to excuse him.
Sorry about ours too...
He's embarrassing.
Girl... Hot...
Sweet! Easy on the eyes!
Love me a girl manager!
Yeah, Yakisoba!
Damn you, Karasuno!
Jeez, get it together, would you?!
Uh Hinata... How do you already know one of those guys?
Oh, I met him earlier while I was out...
I guess he's Nekoma's setter, that's all.
A setter...
I look forward to playing with you today.
And we're also looking forward to playing with you guys.
Whoa! Check this out!
What? It's just a gym.
Ah, so he's the shrewd type.
Man, 8 years, huh? Barely
recognized you with that haircut.
Yeah, well maybe you oughta try
something new once in a while, Naoi.
Ah, Keishin!
Hm?
Coach Nekomata! It's been a while.
I see you're still the spitting image
of your old grandfather, aren't you, boy?
I-I'm Ittetsu Takeda, sir! I spoke to you
on the phone. Thank you so much for your time.
Well, after all those dozens of phone calls, I
started feeling like I had to respond one way or another.
Ah, I'm sorry about that!
Aw, I'm just pullin' your leg, son!
We've already had ourselves several good
practice games over the past three days...
And I expect this one'll be interesting too.
Yes! Thank you, sir!
Oh, and it matters not to me that Ukai's not here...
We'll still destroy you.
We haven't been a team for very long...
We're still kind of finding our groove...
So we're not very coordinated.
On top of all that, this is our first
game using our new starting line-up...
We don't know anything about Nekoma as a team,
but whatever kind of wall we
find ourselves up against today...
We can rise above it!
We are plasma.
Let's make our motions fluid.
Keep the oxygen flowing so the
brain can work to its full potential!
Here we go!
Okay!
Kuroo... don't say that stuff... It's really embarrassing.
Aw, don't be like that! It adds to the mood.
It helps us get into the right mindset.
Guess you're outnumbered.
Sweet! Just in time!
Ah yes here we go again.
Cats versus crows!
Let the practice game between Nekoma
High and Karasuno High officially begin!
Thank you for the game!
You don't seem as nervous today.
Really?
Huh?
You're tiny!
Gah! Don't you mock me!
I'm not mocking you at all, dude!
Huh? Really?
Yup!
Tch!
He's as paranoid as always.
Hey Shoyo.
Huh?
Remember when I told you that I
think Nekoma's got a pretty good team?
Well, it's not because I'm good...
We all are.
Huh?
You can do it, Kenma!
Asahi!
I got it!
Agh, sorry, guys!
That's what happens when you skip for a month!
Uh, my bad!
Kageyama cover!
Got it!
Whoa, that was crazy fast! But how...?!
A quick-attack from that distance?!
How'd he do that? I mean the
kid didn't even open his eyes!
Heh heh!
That's amazing... You've got skill.
Good job, Hinata!
Thanks!
Let's do this thing!
Kuah!
Comin' atcha!
Eat this!
Yes, nice receive!
Another one!
Agh!
Well, nobody could've retrieved that, right?
You got this!
All yours!
Thanks!
Hey, nice work.
Oh, thanks Suga...
That libero of theirs isn't playing around.
Huh?
Even though he's never seen Asahi spike... he got to it.
Ah! Sorry!
Sorry, but could you hold this for me?
Uh-huh...
It's cool, guys!
Go for it, Noya!
Nishinoya sure moves around a lot, doesn't he?
Yes sir... the libero specializes in defense so
he'll come in and out several times during a game.
Our middle blockers, Hinata and Tsukishima, have to go
to the rear to serve, and then after the rally's done,
they switch out positions with Nishinoya.
Aw yeah, it's my turn!
Yeah!
'Kay guys, now bring it in.
Wow. That's a pretty early time-out don'tcha think.
Their spiker and libero are extremely talented.
But their setter is the most
outrageous player in the whole bunch.
That boy's a monster.
He's speed-setting straight to
the spiker's optimum strike point.
He could thread a needle with that control.
Well, not much you can do about a prodigy like that.
But... just because they have one genius on the team...
That doesn't necessarily mean they'll win.
If their team's offense is hinging on Hinata...
Then we should stop him first.
Who's Hinata?
It's Karasuno's number 10.
Right, he and number 9 make for a deadly combination.
A demon... and his iron club...
So our first step is taking the club away.
Alright! They're in top form!
I'm getting bad vibes from these guys.
Uh-hm?
For some reason I get the feeling
they're scrutinizing our every move.
No way!
It's okay, bro! You were pretty close!
Their number 7's got his eye on Hinata.
Nekoma decided to move their blockers to the side.
Mm-hm... an area block.
What the...
That kind of block isn't designed to track the ace.
Don't tell me...
They're trying to lead Hinata.
We have to confine Hinata to a smaller area.
From what I've seen so far...
I think he just charges straight to
wherever we don't have any blockers.
So if we block him on one side, he'll go the opposite way.
And then you just have to follow him.
You got it!
That combo move is scary...
I think anybody would be thrown
off guard the first time they see it.
But... just like when you can't beat a level in a game...
The more you try...
the better you get.
Okay, I just gotta follow number 10!
He got to it again?!
It's a quick attack!
Dammit...
Don't let it get to you!
A setter dump.
Hey... don't tense up.
They see your weaknesses.
Front!
Sorry Noya, can you cover it?
Sure thing!
Right side!
Huh? Why's he calling for a set?
Kageyama.. Heads up!
Hey! That one's called a straight hit!
It goes down the side! Be selective with your spikes!
His perfectionism really starting to piss me off. Heh...
You and me both.
Nice drop, Tsuki!
This guy thinks things through, and
he's in tune with his surroundings...
He's the complete opposite of Shoyo.
Let's go!
You got it?
You bet!
Nice receive!
Who do I send it to?
To the right?
Left.
So he was watching closely.
He's quick too.
That glance was just a decoy!
Kenma is not a fan of interacting with people...
But he eventually became so conscious of
their eyes that he turned it into an advantage.
His skills of prediction are razor-sharp.
He can tell a lot about his
opponents just by observing them.
But of course, that's not what makes
our team such a force to be reckoned with.
All my life... I've never had
any luck making friends for myself.
I don't have any interest in other people.
I'm always extremely aware of their eyes.
I did all I could not to stand out.
Since he was my age and lived
close by, Kuroo was my one friend.
I don't like sports very much, but
I've always played around with volleyball.
When we were in middle school, Kuroo
talked me into joining volleyball club...
It was okay, I guess.
I kept playing it when I got to high school...
Our school had a good team my first year...
But there were so many people, I
couldn't deal with being a part of it.
Hey first-year, clean up faster so we can go home!
There's nothing special about upperclassmen.
They were just born a year or two sooner...
So why do they act like they're better than everyone else?
You can't quit... Not only do you have
greater observational skills than us...
You're also a good strategist.
All the first- and second-years
already know how amazing you are...
This team's gonna go really far with your help.
He doesn't stand out.
Huh?
Even an amateur can tell that Kageyama's got a
certain intense greatness about him, you know?
I'm not saying Nekoma's setter isn't
doing amazing stuff out there, but...
you wouldn't know just by watching him.
Well yeah... That's because their receives are stable.
The most important component for a
diverse arsenal of attacks is solid receiving.
You want receives that land the
ball neatly above the setter's head.
The better they are, the more room the
setter has to put his abilities to work.
We've got Kageyama, holding this ragtag
group together with his overwhelming talent...
Whereas Nekoma's setter is supported by
the receiving skills of his entire team.
We are plasma...
Let's make our motions fluid...
Keep the oxygen flowing... So the
brain can work to its full potential!
One touch!
Nice cover, Yaku!
We don't need a superstar for the team ace.
All we have to do is keep racking up
points one by one, slowly but surely.
I'm really going for it on the
next spike, so give me a set, okay?
But that's really risky for us right now...
One mistake and we lose the set.
I know that!
Trust me!
Nice!
But it's just like when you
can't beat a level in a game...
The more you try...
the better you get.
Finally got you that time!
Alright!
Look... We can't get discouraged right now...
We can take the next set!
There's not a spike in the
world that can't be stopped, red...
You gotta stay focused.
We'll nail this one for sure!
Kick its ass!
Right!
Aw, not again.
Nice block, Inuoka!
Their number 7's no joke.
He's got Hinata's patterns figured out.
Nice cover, Daichi!
Left! Tanaka!
I can smell you wondering why I'm
not taking Hinata out of the game?
Nope.
If this was an official game, I probably would have...
But for now I'd rather give
him a chance to find a solution.
Of course, if this makes him lose his will
to fight, I'll take him out in a heartbeat.
He juked him!
Damnit!
So close!
He was completely shut down during his
first and only game in middle school...
And now he's no match for
Tsukishima's height in high school.
So he found a way to overcome those
setbacks and face even the tallest opponents...
But now, even when he uses his best attack...
All it takes is a single blocker to stop him!
He's staring straight into the "human wall".
The more it stops you, the more your heart breaks.
Huh?
He's smiling.
Hinata...
Somehow... That was different.
What?
It wasn't the same as the confusion I felt back then.
When I couldn't see past the blockers to
the other side and didn't know what to do.
It wasn't like that.
I can tell my opponent's having
trouble keeping up with me.
Before, all I felt was fear
and hate whenever I got blocked.
Now when a blocker stands in my way, it's just exciting!
With your amazing sets and a good strategy...
I think I can find a way to get past him.
All I want is...
One more set... How's that sound?
Yeah we'll see.
Let's go!
What?
His...
eyes were open...
Yeah, you're right.
Hey, what was that?
Hinata's been leaving it up to Kageyama...
Something must be wrong!
Hey, time out, time out!
I-it's not that I don't trust you
or anything, but... Uhh let's see...
Dude. What are you freaking out about?
Kageyama... from now on, I want you to
try sending slightly weaker sets to Hinata.
No more direct delivery.
So you want an indirect delivery?
A what?
Your sets are usually powerful
with a straight trajectory...
It needs to float a little bit.
I know it's kinda tricky to change it
on the spot though... Can you handle it?
I can do it.
So what's the purpose of floating the set?
I want to give Hinata some extra freedom in the air...
I noticed that he was trying to
dodge that blocker mid-jump just now.
Huh?
There's a technique for shaking off blockers.
It looked like that's what he was after.
Too bad it was a complete and utter failure.
Up 'til now, I could hit it without thinking at all...
It's so weird to be the one lining up the shot!
One more time-out!
Whoa whoa whoa... You gotta calm down, kid.
Yes, sir! I'm sorry, I just
keep screwing up over and over.
Hey, don't even worry about that!
Thanks to you, I always get to hit the ball unmarked!
There's nothin' wrong with lettin' me carry
the game every once in a while, right buddy?
Okay, but Asahi's getting more points than you.
Ah! That's beside the point! Who
asked you?! Ain't that right, Asahi?
Oh, yeah, it doesn't matter... We're
gonna win all of those points back.
But if you keep messing up, you're
probably still gonna get switched out.
Tsukishima!
If you're trying to learn something new, then you
should keep at it... You might jump all by yourself,
but we're all right here to back you up.
And besides, Mr. Ace here says he's
gonna win all of those points back for us.
Daichi! Don't put too much pressure on him.
What if he breaks into a million pieces?
That's right! This guy's fragile, you know!
Uhh... can we just get back to the game? Please.
Asahi!
Left!
Go!
That was great!
Aw, it's all he can do just to return the ball!
Is there any way we could make this go smoother?
Go for it!
Not even a pro can be expected
to get a play right the first time.
But every great accomplishment
begins with baby steps, you know?
You remember karasuno's tiny giant, don't you?
Sure, that's the ace Hinata wants to be like.
He lived up to the nickname... Only
stood at about five-foot-five or so...
And he kept getting blocked whenever he first started.
But by the second half of his second year, there
was nobody who could compete with him in midair combat.
He couldn't rise above the high blockers,
so he would aim for the gap instead.
Sometimes he would intentionally make
the ball ricochet off their fingertips.
And that's how he developed his own
personal style as a smaller player.
Well, that's what I understand
from what my grandpa anyway.
Former coach Ukai said that?
Yup, the one and only. And I still
remember his advice like it was yesterday too.
Man has no wings...
so he finds his own way to fly.
Aagh! That's an out!
Wow, Shoyo...
That was amazing!
Once more!
The small fry... Hinata, was it?
He was pretty good, even if that last one was out.
Oh no, he's nothing compared to that Inuoka
guy, even though he seemed kinda impressed by us.
Uh, you guys are creeping me out.
Next Haikyu!! "Worthy adversaries."