Dammit, stop dragging your feet!
What happened to those reflexes you had? Get it together!
All I've been doing is receives...
Kageyama, we're running out of time! I
wanna jump around! I wanna do some spikes!
Well that's too bad!
That's enough!
A word to the wise.
Daichi's a nice guy most of the time,
but you will not like him when he's mad. Trust me.
Yeah, we know.
If he were to find out we're practicing early...
I'm so dead.
Not that I'm afraid of him or anything! Of
course not. That would be ridiculously ridiculous!
Hm?
Anyway, it's probably for the best if we keep this
little practice session a secret between the three of us-
Aha! Just as I suspected!
Suga!
Hey.
How'd you know?!
Come on. Something was obviously up...
I mean, why else would you
offer to take the key to the gym
when you always show up to practice at the last minute?
Don't worry, I won't tell. Your secret's safe with me.
A clandestine crash course. That's pretty exciting.
Whoo, I'm on fire!
Hey, you're not paying attention.
Hey, I wanna hit too! Throw me a bone here, Kageyama!
You're all about your sets, aren'tcha?
Go ahead, send one over this way!
Come on, just one!
I don't think he wants to.
For practice!
Please?
No.
Aw man, don't be like that!
Yeah, dude, send him one!
Mmph!
Fwup! Ah.
I sent that one head-on...
You received to make a set and attack...
Don't run your mouth if you can't follow through.
I'll be sending all the sets to
Tanaka during the match on Saturday.
Leave all the attacking to him... You
just do your best to not get in my way.
Okay fine, then as soon as I get good enough at receives.
Will you at least throw a few sets to me too?
I'll set to whoever I have to to win.
It's just... I highly doubt
that person is going to be you.
Watch your mouth!
How's he ever gonna learn if you don't set to him?
It's almost 7. We should clean up.
Oh, crap! Hurry up! We can't leave any traces!
We need to find a mop!
Dammit!
Try this... drop your hips down a little bit lower
and hit the ball like you're trying to return it
to exactly where it came from.
Okay!
Here we go!
Ooh, nice one!
Hey, Hinata. How about I start setting
for you tomorrow morning? Would you like that?
What? You mean it?! Really?!
Well, I am Karasuno high's official setter, after all...
And you want to practice spikes, right?
Exactly! Spikes are my favorite thing to do!
When you hit the ball just right... it feels so cool!
I guess you really got a thing for spikes, don't you?
Yeah... when I was in middle school,
I could barely get teammates at all...
Much less a setter to toss practice balls with me.
I used to get my friend in basketball club to help me out.
Ah, oops, sorry, I hit it the wrong way again!
After I dropped out of the club, I would ask
the first-years, the setters from the girls' team.
And pretty much anybody who
didn't say no to practice with me.
I made a lot of friends along the way...
But none of those people could
ever become my real teammates.
That's why... I was so excited
to see who the setters were here.
You're an idiot.
And now, uh...
You're clumsy.
You know the rest.
Well like I said, I'm a setter too...
I'll toss you a few, okay?
That'd be nice, but...
If I were to say yes after telling you all that...
It kinda feels like... I would
be admitting that he beat me.
So why do you get so competitive
when it comes to Kageyama?
If you ask me, it's better to avoid
making enemies with guys like that.
That day at the tournament...
Kageyama was so good at everything he did.
And he was way taller than me... and stronger.
It just really bothered me to see
him standing in my way like that.
Yeah, I think I get it.
That's why I came to Karasuno...
Because I want to beat him!
Really? If he's the reason you came here...
Then is he whole the reason you
play volleyball in the first place?
Ah! Um, well...
Is he practicing during lunch?
I just think that if I can get strong
enough to finally win against Kageyama...
Then I will be able to stand up
to all kinds of tough opponents...
Cause I've never seen anyone play like him.
I don't ever want to lose again!
I see. So what you're saying is, if you had
to rank all the players in your own age group,
you'd give Kageyama the top
spot? That's quite an endorsement.
Well...
He doesn't want to admit it.
He's no longer your most powerful enemy...
Now, he's your most powerful ally.
I can do everything without your help.
Anyway, let's do some receives.
Sure!
Thanks for taking out the trash!
1, 2, 3, 4!
5, 6, 7, 8.
2, 2, 3, 4.
Legs! 1, 2, 3, 4.
5, 6, 7, 8.
2, 2, 3, 4.
Arms! 1, 2, 3, 4.
Let's go.
What?! Sorry, where are we going now?
Well it's not like we can play volleyball
here, can we? I found a practice spot.
Ah? Really?! Where is it?! Wow, great job, Kageyama!
Oh my god, you're so annoying!
What? What do ya mean?
You two look sleepier than usual.
Uh, really? Maybe I've been
studying too hard or something...
I've been studying hard too!
It doesn't sound very convincing when you say it!
Eat it!
Excuse us.
Oh.. Hey guys. These are the other new first-years.
Normally we'd wait 'til next week to start new
members, but since we have that match on Saturday,
We're making an exception and bringing them in now.
Nice to meet you!
Be aware of your feet and your hands!
Hey, I need you to focus!
I know, I know!
We're gonna win this match and get let into the gym!
And then we'll play for real!
Oh... right, I forgot. If we lose on
Saturday, you don't ever get to be the setter.
That's why I need you to focus!
Gaah!
I told you, you gotta ease up a
little when we're practicing outside!
If you could receive worth a damn, I wouldn't have to!
Pardon me... your majesty.
What?
Ah! Uh-oh.
Tch.
What's with him? He doesn't like being king of the court?
I think that's a pretty cool nickname.
Hey, I wonder if I'll get a
nickname too? Just like the tiny giant!
The wind of the... whirlwind!
No wait, that' too much wind.
The forest... no that's lame... The
shadowy, um... the north eastern... tornado?
Hey! Pull your head out!
So anyway, what do you think the
first-years we're gonna be up against are like?
They can't be tougher than the upperclassmen.
It makes no difference to me how skilled they
are... we'll defeat them no matter what they're like.
You're right. That's exactly what I was gonna say!
Tch.
Don't you "tch" me! One more time!
You've got to learn to stop receiving with your face!
I can't put my finger on it, but there's
something I don't like about those rookies.
But you never like anybody when
you first meet them, Tanaka...
It's you... you're just a paranoid guy.
I don't like your tone...
They're a bit further along than I expected they'd be...
You think Saturday's game will be okay?
Are you kiddin'? Of course it will!
They've got yours truly on their side!
Well, at least Kageyama's good.
You know, I think he's actually calmed down
a bit since middle school. That's positive.
What?! No way, he's a snotty little shit!
Well, he seemed to have absolute
confidence in himself back then...
Maybe over confident. He's a lot
less brazen now, don't you think?
Okay, but he's still a little shit.
Oh, right, my bad... Maybe you're
not the best person to ask about that.
Uh... hey... That's not cool...
Okay... one more try!
You ready?
Yeah!
Behind you!
Gotcha!
Are you guys seriously practicing out here?
You must be the first-years who
made all that trouble on the first day.
T-shirts, out here? Aren't you cold?
Whoa, they're tall!
Give it back! Hey!
Shouldn't you elementary schoolers be home at this hour?
Who are you supposed to be?!
I guess you're the other new first-year players.
Hm?
Quiet!
Interesting.
I'll do the talking!
Question.. How tall are you?
Hey!
Glad you asked! Tsukki here happens to be six-two!
He's almost six foot three!
Six foot two?!
What's the point of you bragging
about how tall I am, Tadashi?
You're right, sorry, Tsukki.
You're Kageyama from Kitagawa first, aren't you?
Tch.
A star player like you at a school like this...
So?
Look, pal!
Hm?
We're not gonna lose to you, do you understand me?!
Isn't that cute?
I didn't realize that little skirmish
actually meant something to you...
We couldn't care less about it.
Huh?
We're not concerned with winning or losing,
but if it's that important to you two...
Maybe... we'll just throw the game.
You mean whaaaat?!
Fine... I don't care if you throw
it or work yourselves to death...
Cause I'm still going to win on Saturday.
You mean "we" right?!
So confident! Well that's the king for you!
Hey... don't call me that.
Ha, I knew it.
Rumor has it you lose your cool every
time someone brings up your old nickname.
But who wouldn't want to be king of the
court? I mean it really suits you, right? Your highness?
Your funeral, dude.
What is your problem?
I saw you, you know? At the finals.
Hm?
I still can't believe your teammates put up with all those
selfish sets you used to toss up... I know I wouldn't. Oh!
So that's why you're here! I
bet they finally got sick of you.
Tsukki!
What the? I don't really
understand what's going on...
But it's not like him to not just
say anything back to these jerks!
Come on, Kageyama, get the last word
as you walk away like you always do!
We're leaving.
What?! Wait!
Running off? Guess the king's not a threat after all.
I hope his majesty puts up more of a fight on Saturday.
Would you just shut up about
the stupid king?! I'm here too!
You have no idea what I'm capable of!
Oh yeah?
What's that look for anyway, buddy?!
Are you trying to start something with me?!
There's no need to argue, alright?
Let's all just enjoy playing some volleyball together.
It's just a game, right?
What's that supposed to mean?!
Exactly what it sounds like. Bye.
Hey, not so fast!
You never told me who you are!
I'm Kei Tsukishima, Year 1 Class 4.
I'm Tadashi Yamaguchi.
As of today, we're officially your new teammates...
Even if doesn't feel like it... Anyway, I'm
looking forward to his majesty's royal sets.
See ya!
What is their deal? Those two are some major
league butt wads. We should show those pukes who's boss!
That goes without saying.
Hey, where're ya going?
Huh?
We still got some work to do, don't we?
Hey Tsukki, wait up! Is something wrong?
I hate guys like that... Always
trying a little bit too hard.
They're both a touch over-zealous for my taste.
Focus! You have to brace faster than that!
How late are they planning to practice?
I know!
Eh, who even knows with these two knuckleheads...
All I know is I'm sleepy.
Your majesty.
Quit it, Kageyama! It's too dark to
see out here. Don't hit it so hard!
Sorry.
He doesn't look sorry at all.
What's gotten into him all of a sudden?
He's been extra tense since we ran into that tall guy.
But I can't really spike if he won't send me anymore sets.
I guess I'll just do my best at
receiving until he decides to do one.
Hey! Try another one of those!
That's new. He couldn't handle
a ball at that speed before!
Okay! Now no holding back!
Fine by me!
Whoops, overslept!
I'm so late, I'm so late, the boss is gonna murder me!
Kiyoko made me breakfast, so I couldn't leave the house!
Yeah I wish... hm, huh?
Damn, how long have they been back and forth like that?
Well, I got here 15 minutes ago, so...
It's been non-stop?!
Wow.
He makes up for his bad technique
with raw athleticism, but...
Everybody has their limit!
Let's take a break for-uh?
Not yet!
No! It hasn't hit the floor!
Okay, fine!
That's brutal! Can he hit that?
Damn, force of habit.
Hinata's had amazing athletic ability since middle school.
Huh?
But... besides all of that... He's got this...
insane thirst for victory that keeps him going.
His weapon isn't physical prowess and it's
definitely not size... It's something else...
It's that every time the going gets tough... He has
just enough left in him to take it one step further!
He did it! Nice one, little man!
I'll set to whoever I have to to win...
It's just... I highly doubt
that person is going to be you.
I don't ever want to lose again!
But it's... not over yet.
Huh?
Here we go!
There it is! He finally set him one!
Too bad.
There's no way he's got enough
strength left to spike it down.
I gotta hand it to him, the kid can jump.
Can't believe he managed to hit that.
Check out the stupid look on his face.
So I guess getting a set must be
really important to the guy, huh?
Huh?
I made a lot of friends along the way... But none
of those people could ever become my real teammates.
I suppose getting tosses from the setter
was just something we've always taken for granted.
Hey.
Huh?
Tomorrow... we'll win.
But he's no longer your most powerful enemy...
Now he's my most powerful ally.
Hmph.
Yeah? Tell me something I don't know!
That's sick!
Tanaka, get some water! Oh god... and a bucket!
A-and some towels...
Quit running, you little moron!
Why are you dorks wasting precious energy right
before a game? You should take a breather, idiots.
Man... we tied...
I can'... let you.. Beat me...
Back atcha...
This guy really gets on my nerves...
He's gonna start sending the ball
my way now... Sets from a real setter!
You ready to win this or what?
We need to go and get set up.
Yeah.
Morning, my liege!
This time...
I'll break through any wall they put up!
Kageyama's such a whimp. He
didn't even stand up for himself.
Shut it, Tadashi.
Sorry.
It's time to see what
the king's made of. And the shorty too.
Grr! Next Haikyu! " The view from the summit!"