A perfect receive.
Is this who they meant?
Huh?
Uh? Are you shorter than me?
Hey! You had better watch what you say to me!
Whoa, I am so sorry!
Um anyway... I just wanted to know how tall you are.
I'm 5'2, that good enough for ya?!
He's barely in the 5-foot range!
Wha... what's with you?
Somebody to look down at... I haven't
had that feeling since middle school!
You freaking kidding me! You're not looking that far down!
Huh? Long time no see, Nishinoya!
Heey, how's it goin', Tanaka?
Nishinoya!
Yo!
Oh, that's right, you haven't met yet.
Nishinoya's a second-year.
Hey!
Cool, nice to meet you, first-years!
Hey, I got a question for the
angry-looking guy that just threw that serve!
Where did you come from?
Went to Kitagawa.
Seriously?! That's a great
school. No wonder you're so talented!
I played against those guys in
middle school and they beat us 2 to 1!
They had someone back then who
could serve even better than you!
Okay, looks like he still a chatterbox.
Um... anyway, so um where did you go to middle school?
Chidori-Yama!
Wow, they're pretty good too! Why'd you come here?
Is it... because you heard coach Ukai was coming back?
Not really... I wanted to come back here because...
Well...
Karasuno's school uniforms for
female students... are the hottest!
Hm?
But not just that! The girls
themselves aren't half bad either! Whoo!
But most of all... yeow!
Our uniforms are awesome too... And black!
My middle school had blazers, so
I've always like military style...
And they just have to be black!
I know what you mean brotha!
So the uniforms are perfecto...
All the ladies are beautiful...
And a short commute! It was a no-brainer!
Hm?!
Ah! Oh my god it's Kiyoko! Come to my arms, sweet mama!
So I guess hasn't changed all that much has he.
I know right... he can be pretty noisy.
But whenever he gets focused on the game...
Not so much.
So... where's Asahi? Is he back yet?
Ah...
Well, uh...
Ah?
Tch!
Damn coward!
Hey Noya! Show some respect for your upperclassman-
Oh shut up! He's a scared little crybaby and you know it!
If Asahi's not coming back then neither am I!
Hey! Noya, wait!
My job... is just to keep the ball in play.
The sky belongs to the spikers.
I can't compete in their space.
But if I can just keep the ball up in the
air... I know I can trust the ace to nail it.
No matter what happens, even if it bounces off
a wall of blockers, I won't let it hit the floor.
So don't change a thing.
Ask me for the ball just one more time... Ace!
Uh, hey!
Hm?
You're a libero... Um right, Nishiya?
You're on the defense.
It's Nishinoya... why do you think I'm a libero...
Because I'm short?
Huh?
Course not. You're good at receives.
Hm?
That's the right fit for the libero position because
solid receives are the backbone of the defense, right?
Look at you... you really know your stuff, huh?
The captain says you're the guardian
of Karasuno or something like that!
Huh?! Guardian, where'd that come from?!
I-It's not like I'm that big of a deal.
That's kind of embarrassing, actually...
He really said that?
Mm-hm, Mm-hm, Mm-hm!
Does he think giving me a badass
nickname is enough to make me come back?!
I mean, he's not wrong, but...
D-dammit, Daichi, that's not fair!
I... still really suck at receiving...
And it's kinda the most important part of the game.
Hm?
Could you teach me... Nishi...
I mean, mister upperclassman!
Uhhh...
Look.
After practice I'm gonna treat you to some ice cream!
Huh?
I'm your upperclassman.
And that's what upperclassmen do!
Does that mean...?
That doesn't mean I'm gonna come back to volleyball club.
I'm just gonna teach you how to do receives, that's all!
Thank you!
Okay, I'll show you again.
Hm?
Schwoom...
Swish...
And bam!
You got it?
Huh?
I told you...
People who act on instinct really
suck at putting stuff into words.
Oh I don't know...
I'm pretty sure I understood what he meant.
Yeah, that's 'cause you're the same way...
It's all sound effects, it's
like... "whamajam!" and "kablooey!"
Stuff, you're like a bunch of five-year-olds.
Huh?
A libero, huh?
That's an interesting position.
It is. The libero specializes in defense... A digger.
They're not allowed to make serves or spikes.
Instead, they maintain the rearguard position
and keep the ball from hitting the floor.
So I guess that's why you called
him the guardian... That's impressive!
If we can convince him to come back,
I think the team'll be in great shape.
He may be small, but he's got
a huge presence on the court.
Tsukki is...
What did I tell you?
I'd feel a lot safer with him on our side.
It's at least good to see Nishinoya
still hasn't lost his touch, isn't it?
I heard he trained through his entire suspension...
He was gettin' it on with the ladies' teams.
Hahaha! Just like Hinata!
Um hey, Nishinoya?
Huh?
Who's that Asahi guy you were talking about before?
Dude! That's the one thing you shouldn't say!
He's Karasuno's ace... Well, s'posta be.
The ace, huh?
So, we do have one.
What are you all speechless for?
That's what... I wanna become!
Huh?
Really? A shorty like you?
I like your style!
You wanna be the ace because it's flashy and cool, right?
Hell yeah, buddy! You can be
the ace if you set your mind to it!
To tell the truth, you're a lot more
promising than the guy we have! Haha...
Of course... everybody out there wishes they were the ace.
Yeah! That's 'cause the ace is the best!
I mean even the word "ace" is awesome, right!
"Setter" and "libero" sound
kinda plain and boring, you know?
Just let it go...
But still... there's one thing...
That the crowd loves even more than a great spike.
Make a wicked receive and they
go crazy for you every time!
This game is "tall beats all"...
So if you're a bit on the short side...
libero's one of the only options you got.
But I'll tell you one thing... I don't
play the position because of how tall I am.
Even if I was 6 feet tall... I'd
still be out there digging the ball out.
Not being able to spike or block doesn't mean anything...
In volleyball, you can never lose
unless the ball touches the floor.
And the only one who keeps it in the sky...
is me!
Whoa... amazing!
Ah-hey, cut it out! You're making it
all weird when you freak out like that!
Look I'll get you two ice
creams if you just chill, alright?!
Okay!
So, future ace, what's your specialty?
Huh?
Well uh, you said you were bad at
receiving... So, what's your thing?
Well, it's not... I-I'm uh...
Huh? Speak up.
A... decoy.
Why do you say it like it's something bad?
Well, next to "ace" and "guardian" and all
that stuff... Decoy sounds kinda stupid, right?
Who gives a damn what it sounds like?
Yeah, but...
If having you as a decoy makes
it so a spiker can score a point...
Then your job is important...
Just as important as theirs is!
Okay...
Now maybe all those powerful spikes
we hit'll finally earn us some points...
Since we've gotten ourselves a good decoy.
This Hinata-Kageyama combo should come in handy.
Mm-hm.
You do remember what Takeda told us, right...
I think things really are gonna be changing for us.
Let's just hope it's a good change.
True that.
I realize I'm asking a lot here.
Look, I'll be the first to admit that I
don't know what I'm doing and I need your help.
Those guys have so much potential.
Can't you find it in your heart to help them out? Please.
You don't know when they quit, do you, Takeda?
No sir... it's my only real strength.
Ask me all you want, and I'm still gonna tell you no.
My grandpa was the super famous coach, not me...
I told you, I'm not the coaching type.
Listen, specs, I understand you
need somebody, but it just ain't me.
Honestly... I think the name's all you're after.
There is some truth to that...
Coach Ukai was all we ever had...
And I don't know who else to ask...
But I am not the coach those guys
need... I can't even run a practice game.
And you think a brand-name coach is all it
takes to fix that little problem of yours?
All I ask... is you try.
Forget it.
I feel bad for you, pal, I really do...
But the last thing I need is a bunch of
pain-in-the-ass teenage athletes to look after, okay?
I'll try again soon.
Try again?!
What's it gonna take to get rid of you?!
I'm sorry to bother you, but...
If you would just come watch them play...
Then you'd see why it's so important.
Guh...
Yeah right! I mean it! You're not gonna change my mind!
Tch! Just go awaay... Agh, jeez!
Here goes.
Hey, Suga. Uh... it's been a while, hasn't it?
Asahi... we would really like
you to come back to the team.
Nishinoya just got back from suspension y'know.
Really? Well that's good to hear. It makes me feel a
lot better knowing you guys have him there to back you up.
That's how we feel about you!
When you call for the ball,
everyone knows they're in good hands!
Look I appreciate the thought... But if I were to join
the team, I would just hold you guys back like last time.
Hear me out.
We've got this amazing decoy, and as much as I
hate to say it, the new first-year setter's great too!
You wouldn't have to carry the
whole team on your own anymore!
We've got some new tactics now...
If we just had you and Nishinoya back...
Then maybe Karasuno could be unstoppable again!
Look we need our ace more than ever!
Things are just starting to get better-
Asahi!
Huh?
It's time for career counseling!
Sorry, I gotta go.
Huh...
You go in first...
You're the one who wanted to see the ace so bad, remember?
B... But I'm way too scared to
walk into a third-year classroom!
Please wait, Asahi!
Uh Asahi?
Uh? What's up?
Hey uh... What are you first-years doing over here?
Uh, well we uh...
Ah yes... Yes!
Thank you so much!
Oh no, pleasure's all mine! Yes... thank you!
Alright!
That'll be perfect! Finally... Things are about to change!
Anyway... these are the new guys, Hinata and Kageyama.
Ah... It's uh nice to meet you guys.
Hello!
Wow, is he taller than Tsukishima?
Four. Not the numbers we
wanted, but they're all promising.
Either way, he's huge. So this is Karasuno's ace.
Heh... is that right?
He seems nice though.
Good luck. Alright kid...
Are you gonna come play with us or what?
I want to be the ace one day.
I was hoping to see you in action!
Hey Asahi! The teacher's waiting for ya man!
Sorry... but I'm not the ace anymore alright?
So uh... did he get hurt or something?
Oh no... it's nothing like that at all.
To be honest with you...
It might just be that Asahi's lost his love for the game.
What?! But why?! He's so big
and tall and he gets to be the ace!
See... Asahi was Karasuno's biggest and strongest player.
Even in the trickiest situations,
he could always score a point.
That's why we all depended on him and
considered him the ace of the team...
But then...
Was it a bad game?
Huh?
In one of our games... every single one
of Asahi's spikes was completely shut down.
It was rough... and he's the type
who feels responsibility for everything.
What's wrong with you?
I don't think it's a good
enough reason to hate volleyball.
Well, I dunno... it could've been a number of things.
Yeah like what else?
Beats me. But hey...
We don't actually know for sure
that he hates volleyball, do we?
Ah? You're totally right!
Rolliiiing... thunder!
Huh...?
Uh... well okay then.
Come on, dude, it's just a rolling receive!
What are you yelling for?
Are you hearing yourself?
You better watch your mouth, you little
first-year brats, or you're gonna regret it!-
I'll make you do laps! No, push-ups!
You know what, whatever you hate the
most, I'm gonna make you do a thousand of!
That was awesome! Teach me the rolling thunder too!
Take five, guys! Guess what? Great news!
So, the golden week training camp.
We're all going this year, aren't we?
Training camp?
Yeah... all of us can surely benefit from the practice.
That's excellent... cause on the
last day of said training camp...
I've arranged us a practice gaaaame!
Whoaaa!
Wow, Take! You're really pulling your weight!
Who are we gonna be playing?
It's Nekoma High School... They're in Tokyo.
People describe them as...
Catlike.
Catlike?
Yeah, we actually know who those guys are...
Our old coach was rivals with their
coach. We used to play them all the time.
Oh...
Oh, that's right! They called it...
"Cats and birds!"... the famous trashcan showdown!
I can't believe people actually came to see that.
But wait... We haven't played
that school in a while... so why now?
It's simple... but I'll explain all the details later.
In short, I found out they were our adversary...
and then... I just had to stage a rematch.
If we go up against Nekoma High... he'll change his tune.
Ugh...
Great! Looking forward to it then!
Let's make this practice game count guys!
Right!
Tokyo, huh? Those little city boys...
They have no clue what they're in for!
Did you say "city boys"?
What's it to you, f-four-eyes?!
Hey Daichi.
Hm?
I'm sorry... but I can't go to the practice game.
What're you talking about?
Hey! I bet Tokyo schools are tough!
Kageyama's a great guy, and even though the other
first-years are kinda rough, they're a fun group.
I think with a little time...
This team'll be something special.
I want to play with you guys... But...
But if I played in the game...
And we were to actually win...
Then well it would be like saying that
we don't need Asahi and I... I just can't.
We've been teammates for so long.
I'm sorry if I'm being selfish.
Look I get it... but I still
want you to come to the camp okay.
Hm? You mean it?
Hey Noya! That thunder thing!
Will you show me how to do it?!
Well then?
Huh?
Have a good night!
See ya!
Ahhhh...
Do you think if Asahi came back,
everything would work out for us?
And what about Noya, huh?
I dunno.
I don't get it...
Sugawara said Asahi was the kind
of guy who feels responsible...
But I think he might feel bad too.
They both feel like what happened was their fault...
But it's not like they can win alone.
No way, you don't get to say that!
What happened to Kageyama's
favorite catchphrase, anyway huh?!
"Receives... And sets... And spikes... I'd rather
do everything in the whole game all by myself."
Would you just freakin' drop it!
"Look at me, I'm a dumb jerk..."
We're all on the same side...
So we should be acting like it.
Huh?
I just wish we got along better... don't you?
Em.
Yeah it's nice of you to think of me and everything.
And I can tell it's important to
you, but I'm not really interested okay?
Look! If you don't come back to volleyball
club, the upperclassmen are never gonna cheer up-
Do you ever shut up?
You two are funny. But, listen to me.
G-guh huh?
I'm sorry but...
I've just forgotten what it feels like... to send the ball
through a wall of blockers. It seems impossible to me now.
I just know I'd fail... Again.
Just thinking about it freaks me out
and it's just too much for me right now.
Well, this might sound cocky coming from a first-year...
But I still think it's important for me to say it.
Whatever it is you can tell me okay.
I know what you mean.
I'm short and I don't have great technique, so
the blockers used to stop me all the time... but...
Thanks to Kageyama's amazing
sets I can get past anybody now!
Hmm...
The wall just fades away... and then the
view of the other side is totally clear!
The view...
I think I understand what he's talking about.
And once I reach the top of my
jump, the ball hits my hand...
And when the weight of it,
sorta leaves a sting in my palm...
I love that!
I know that feeling too.
You know... I'm really jealous of you...
The way things are... I don't have the
height to clear a wall... Or the power...
But you've got both! Look I know you
might've had a rough time in the past...
But you scored a lot more times
than you got blocked, right?
I mean c'mon... that is why they call you the ace!
Oh? Let's head back, Hinata...
Hey... Dude we gotta go.
Hey uh...
Hm?
It's impossible to win all by yourself...
You need the help of your teammates.
I'm still getting used to that idea myself, so I
can't really talk, but it's true... see you around.
Ready to go?
Yeah, wanna get some food?
Ah? Uh...
Come on! Gimme another one!
Alright, shut up, I get it! Ready?
Yeah!
And once I reach the top of my
jump... The ball hits my hand...
And when the weight of it...
Sorta leaves a sting in my palm...
I love that!
I know...
I know what he means.
I hope Asahi comes back soon.
He's got chin stubble.
What?
Maybe if I could grow stubble
like that, I'd be more like an ace!
Do you think hair tonic would help?
Who cares, dumbass?!
Next time on Haikyu!! "A toss for the ace."