Kay! See ya later!
Bye Shoyo...
We play Nekoma in four days.
And I've got new allies!
That spiker... and that receiver are both on my side!
This'll be great!
I'd better hurry... It's time for training camp!
Ah-hahaaa!
Mister Hinata... need a bathroom break? You can go.
Everybody here?
Yes sir!
We've got four days until the
practice game against Nekoma,
and after that, it'll be time
for the Inter-High preliminaries.
Time is short... but we've
got a whole lot of stuff to fix.
If you sad sacks expect to win,
there's only one thing we can do.
Practice, practice, practice.
I want you to keep retrieving 'til you puke!
Right!
Well, that means Hinata's done his job.
Forward!
Hey! How many times are you gonna
let me score on you?! Get serious!
One more!
Get ready!
Nice receive!
Good job!
That's five for him...
Time to switch out.
Next!
I'm ready whenever you are!
Good. Alright now let's work on a few spikes!
Right!
Nice kill!
Way to go, guys!
Whoaaaa!
Yeaaah!
Those spikes are lookin' good, guys!
Huh?
Um... do you mind if I go next?
Oh! Sure!
Alright... let's pack it up guys.
Yes sir!
Uh? Wow! So this is training camp!
Is it really all that exciting?
Of course it is! I've never been to a training camp!
It's just a bunch of loud, disgusting
guys in your face all day every day...
What's so fun about that?
You take that back right now!
Yeah, any place within a quarter-mile radius of our
gorgeous Kiyoko is automatically pure and beautiful!
This air's as fresh as a morning in spring!
And if your senses are so dull you
can't smell it, I feel sorry for you!
Kiyoko lives right by here...
She goes home whenever the day's over.
Should I even ask what you're doing?
Take... we can't go on... Goodbye sweet world!
Ah?!
Ah?
Huh?
Thanks for the fooo-oood!
Does anybody want seconds?
Yes please, Kiyoko!
Wow.
Okay... the bath's open for the first-years now.
Hm?
What's wrong, Hinata?
Hey.
There's somebody here...
It's a stranger.
Whatever... don't be ridiculous.
We're the only ones here-
It's...
a child.
Nah... You're seeing things...
I'm sure you just walked past a
mirror and saw your reflection.
Yeah, you're right. That'd be silly... it's nothing.
Uh-huh. You've gotta be uh... Just imagining things...
Huh?
Uh what's with all the racket?
Daichi's gonna get angry y'know.
It's just Noya, you idiot.
Whoa... it is him! But he shrank...
Maybe the ghosts made him shorter!
Is that why you have spiky
hair, so you look tall?! Bahaha!
Dammit, Tanakaaa!
Don't make fun of me or I swear-
You should keep your voices down. Daichi might hear you-
Huh. Guys, it's just me, Asahi!
All of you, shut up! Shut up!
What are you, a windmill?
Move your hands and your feet!
Yes sir! One more!
Nice, Hinata!
That's his fifth one.
Good, that should be everybody.
Time to run some laps, guys!
Yes sir!
Pick up the pace dude.
They sure are full of energy.
They even practice during lunch.
Yeah, I noticed that too...
Kageyama gets started early doesn't he?
Right... and Hinata's been doing the same thing...
He said he needs to do that here since he's
not going over the mountains like he used to.
The mountains, huh?
That would explain all that stamina.
On a different note...
Are you having some trouble choosing the starters?
Well just the setter...
I'm stuck.
If we're talking raw power, it's gotta be Kageyama...
Now you've got Sugawara who's built up experience from
playing alongside the ace ever since his first year...
But still, Kageyama's got more than enough
talent right out of the gate to make up for all that.
Then again, Sugawara's been around for a while...
So he's probably already got the trust of his teammates.
But that's not really the heart of the issue, is it?
So could it be that...
You're having trouble deciding
because Sugawara's a third-year?
Your last year in high school is special.
I can see why you would want to take that into account.
Ah! I'm sorry! I think I'm overstepping...
No, you're probably right.
You know... when I was in high school, the only time I got
to be in the starting lineup was when the official setter
who was younger than me, got hurt.
Back then, I was just angry that I never
got the opportunity for three whole years...
But now... as a coach, even a temporary one...
I shouldn't be thinking like a player. It's not right.
Hinata! Stop yelling like a madman. You're
gonna need to save that energy for the game!
Whoa, where are you going?!
Huh?
Nobody's back there. Is this path... the wrong way?
A red uniform? What school is that from?
Hey, whatcha up to?
Well, it's just... Uh... I'm lost.
You're lost? Are you from out of town?
Mm-hm.
Is that a fun game?
Uh... not really...
I'm uh just trying to pass the time.
Oh...
Hey! Do you play too?!
Huh?
Those volleyball shoes!
In your bag!
Oh. Yeah.
Shoyo Hinata! So... What's your name?
Kozume.
Kozume? Is that your first name?
No, it's...
It's Kenma.
So are you... In high school?
Yeah.
What's your year? I'm a first-year!
Second.
Oh crap, so you're my upperclassman! I'm so sorry!
It's okay... after all... that age-based
hierarchy stuff that comes with sports... it's lame.
Oh... you think?
Uh, so, do you like volleyball?
Eh... it's fine... I can't say I really care.
I don't mind it or anything... But
I'm not big on getting all worn out.
But uh... my friend likes to play...
And he needs me... So I play too.
Oh. Well once you get used to it...
I'm sure you'll like volleyball too.
Whatever... I'm only playing it while I'm in high school.
Yeah, what position?
Uh...
I'm a setter.
Really?! You're a lot different than the setter we've got.
He's really growly and scary
like a saber-tooth tiger! Grr...
Oh.
I'm a middle blocker by the way!
Cool.
Oh... but you probably think that's a little weird...
Shorter guys don't usually play that position.
Nah, I don't think that's weird... not at all.
People say a lot of stuff about
me whenever I go to a game, too.
You know, things like, "I thought the setter was supposed
to be the team member with the strongest abilities...
So why did they ever pick this guy of all people?"
You see... I'm not all that much of an athletic person.
Oh... so does your school have
a good volleyball team or what?
Hmm... I don't know... Apparently it
used to be good and then it went downhill.
But as of recently...
I would say, it's pretty good.
Hang on... what school is-
Hey Kenma!
Ah.
Kuroo.
Gotta go.
Later... okay?
You shouldn't wander off.
Sorry.
You don't know your way around here.
Later?
Ah! Hey Hinata!
We were looking all over for you.
Sorry Suga! I didn't realize I went the wrong way.
You always give it your all, no
matter what kind of practice we're doing.
Yeah. But I've still got a really long way to go.
Huh?
There's a lot of things I need to improve on.
I mean, yeah, it kinda gets on my nerves that no one
sees me as anything but half of a pair with Kageyama...
But it's better than not playing at all, right?
I want to stay on the court the longest.
Huh?
So do I. All I want is to play volleyball...
That's why... I do whatever it takes to be my best.
C'mon... don't want to be late for lunch!
Yeah!
Wow... Nekoma's setter's not very tall.
Oh yeah... he sure does look pretty scrawny, doesn't he?
Maybe that's just the backup setter?
Beats me, I don't know a thing about these guys.
That short scrawny guy you
seem to be so concerned about...
Huh?
He just happens to be the
spine... the brain... and heart...
of our team.
Uh, coach?
Hm? What's up?
Us third-years... we don't get a next season.
That's why I want us to win as many games as we can...
So we get more chances to play.
Uh?
And if Kageyama has a better
likelihood of making that happen for us...
Well then I think you shouldn't hesitate to put him in.
Daichi and Asahi have been playing
together since their first year.
I want to stand on the court with
them. And the more plays the better.
It's okay if I only get to fill in, like if Kageyama gets
tired or something happens to put him out or whatever.
You might pity me for being set aside for a first year...
But as long as I keep having a
chance to play... that's fine.
Even if I don't get to be the official
setter, I'll never give up on volleyball...
I just want to be the best part of the team I can.
Mm.
Sorry...
If I'm overstepping my bounds.
Sugawara.
Huh?
I think I might've underestimated you.
Honestly, you're kinda freaking me out right now.
What?
I don't have any coaching experience...
But I swear I'll do whatever I can...
to keep you guys on the winning track.
Thank you, sir!
Sure.
Let's go for the win... I think we can do this.
Yeah.
Time to eat!
Jeez, slow it down... You're gonna get sick.
Ugh...
Don't stop eating! Force it down if you have to!
How can you get through the summer if you don't eat?!
You've got a big appetite today. Suga.
Yeah, maybe so...
Are you gonna eat that? I'll take it!
Gotta stay strong!
No! Tadashi needs to eat his own dinner!
Listen up.
Here's our starting order for Nekoma.
I know you haven't had much time to get acquainted...
So I don't expect any of you to be perfect.
Just because we've got a hotshot libero and our
ace just came back doesn't mean victory is a safe bet.
The winner keeps the ball in play.
So let's see how far this team can take it,
those damn pussycats are not gonna know what hit 'em!
Yeah!
Asahi!
Just forget about Suga...
Ennoshita's the guy you should
really be feeling sorry for here.
What? Me?!
He's a wing spiker just like you! It must suck to be him!
Hey um... Asahi?
Uh?
It's fine... I haven't always been devoted to the sport.
I ran away from the game once... I get it.
You just wait. He's gonna
become way stronger than you are.
He just needs time. Then he will have the
regular position! C'mon tell him, Ennoshita!
Please don't speak for me-uhh...
Oh wait, nevermind, he would actually have to
take over Tanaka's position first, wouldn't he?
So you're comin' after my spot, are ya?
I'd like to see you try, you little bastard!
Whoa! I didn't say it, Nishinoya did!
There we go... hey uh... Ennoshita?
Hm?
About what you said...
Oh... about how chose to leave the game?
You heard about the old coach Ukai
coming out of retirement last year, right?
Yeah.
It's a bit embarrassing for us to admit,
but a bunch of us had some trouble adjusting
to his, let's say "hardcore" training methods.
We'd been doing volleyball club just to have fun, and
then suddenly it was all about winning and nothing else.
We felt like our space had been
invaded, and it kinda scared us away.
But then we really missed playing volleyball...
And when we came back... Well
coach Ukai had already taken off.
The thing is... we're not as cool as you are.
But now that we're all here... We promise to
work just as hard as the rest of the team...
So let's do our best, okay?
Right!
Sir?
Hm? Oh, are they ready?
Yes... alterations are finished...
And they've been cleaned. Here you go.
Whoaaa!
Just like I saw on TV!
Oh?
Hey! Why's Noya the only one with an orange one?
Because I'm the star! Jeez,
shouldn't that be obvious by now?
The star? Cooooool!
The libero wears a different color Jersey because
he goes on and off of the court during a game,
so it makes it easier to keep track of him... dumbass.
I-I knew that! Everyone knows that! Uh?
Hey... his is one number higher than mine!
I knew you'd say that.
We're only first-years. You should
be happy we get uniforms at all.
Uh... I know that too!
Heh, that's funny...
I guess he doesn't remember the number.
He only saw him on TV one time.
Huh?
When the tiny giant played in the nationals, his number...
Was 10.
Wow, coach, did you plan this just for me?!
No, settle down, ginger.
It must be destiny!
Or a coincidence.
Aw, don't be jealous, okay?
Why would I be jealous of you?!
Here's the thing. When Hinata's hero, the tiny giant,
was on the team, Karasuno was the best it's ever been.
But in spite of that, we didn't
win against Nekoma even once.
It ended in a losing streak. So let's turn that around.
Yeah!
Alright! You better get your asses back to practice!
Yes sir!
I guess Nekoma must have a really good team.
So what all do you know about them?
I don't really have a clue what they're like these days...
But that team has always had some talented receivers.
They didn't have stand-out
players, but their defense was tight.
The opposite of us, I guess.
And that whole "cat" thing... It makes sense.
They're extremely agile.
What the heck?
No matter how many times I hit it, I
can't get it to fall into their court!
I don't understand...
They don't have any superstar guys on their team...
So what's their secret?
Here's the most important issue...
Do they or do they not have a female manager?
My Yakisoba bun is saying no!
Huh? But don't you want them to have one? I say yes.
Yeah, I agree.
You crazy?! We don't have a girl manager,
so I'm just gonna be pissed off if they do!
Huh?
Or what if it's worse? She
could be a girl and extremely hot!
I would never forgive those stupid jerks for that! Never!
You'll pay for having a babe for a manager, Karasuno!
Give it a rest, Yamamoto!
Hey! What's Kenma think?
Does it uh... Really even matter?
Humph... I knew you would say that.
But...
Humph?
I do kinda look forward to playing them...
You know, a little bit.
Huh?
Huh? Whoa! Since when are you looking forward
to anything, Mr. couldn't-care-less Kenma Kozume?!
If you're that fired up, maybe I
should make you do some extra reps.
N-no, that's okay...
Hey, Hinata... They said the
first-years can hit the bath now.
Seriously? Are you about to throw up again?
What?! Of course I'm not!
I was just thinking...
They're all preparing for the match...
Even if they're not playing.
The only reason the coach put me
in the game is because of your sets.
I hate to say this, but if not for
you, I probably wouldn't be in the lineup.
I'm going in first!
Hey!
You got a head start, you little cheater!
Even going to the bathroom's a
competition... Those guys're morons.
I'm getting tired just watching them.
Hey! Quit screwing around!
It's time for our game against Nekoma.
Great, I can't wait to play against the
school for guys with weird-shaped heads.
Haha! Did you see those clowns?
Yeah, well at least they're not very tall.
Neither are you, short stuff.
Next Haikyu!! "The cat and crow reunion."