Damn it. He's tough.
If I can slow him down,
One second's all I need.
Kirito!
If only I had my scope.
I get it now.
There are things I shouldn't forget,
What it means to kill,
The significance of taking a life,
And once I accept it,
maybe then I'll be able to find some closure.
That's how I see it.
Right now, Kirito's trying to get
that closure he was talking about.
He's confronting his demons from "SAO" By
taking on the person who represents them, Death Gun.
And the reason he can isn't 'cause he's strong.
It's 'cause he accepts what he did,
even though it still tears him up,
and he's still trying to move on despite it.
I gotta do something.
Think!
Kirito.
He's sweating so much. He'll dehydrate soon.
I wonder if we can get him to
log out or at least warn him.
No, he wouldn't hear us.
The dive blocks everything out.
The amusphere is designed with stuff like this in
mind, so it should shut off if he gets too dehydrated.
Okay, then. I guess we just have to wait.
Hey, mommy,
try holding daddy's hand.
He'll feel the warmth of your touch
and know you're here watching over him.
Since I can't touch anything in
your world, hold it for me, too.
I know he won't feel me there, but still.
No, that's not true.
I'm sure he'll feel your hand, too.
I know he will.
We'll cheer him on together.
Mommy.
Hang in there, Kirito.
Fight for what you believe in,
and I'll be right here by your side.
Wherever you go and whatever you do,
I'll always be with you.
He's right. I didn't want to know his name.
I didn't want anything to do with him.
But I should have known
I wouldn't be rid of him that easy.
I didn't forget.
I only pretended to.
But I was just fooling myself.
Red eyes.
I saw them in the briefing before the raid.
Black.
Red.
Xaxa.
Red‐eyed Xaxa,
That's you! That's your name!
Kirito!
Sinon's distracting him with her bullet line.
She's got him in her sights,
Using all her skill and spirit to keep it trained on him.
It's like a phantom bullet.
One last attack!
I can't waste this chance!
Fool.
It's not over yet.
You can't stop me.
He'll find you,
And he'll...
No, Xaxa, you're done,
and we'll find your partner, too.
He won't kill anyone anymore.
Laughing coffin's dead.
Kirito.
Daddy.
It's over.
Yeah.
I guess now.
We should probably get this tourney over with, huh?
Yeah, we should.
With Death Gun out of the picture,
I'm pretty sure the guy casing
out your apartment's taken off.
Hmm.
I don't think you'll be in any danger when you log out,
But you should call the cops when you do, just to be safe.
Okay, but what am I supposed to tell them?
Oh, yeah. Right.
The guy I work for is with the government.
I could ask him to send the cops to your place,
but how am I gonna get your info?
I can't really ask for it in here.
It's cool.
I'll tell you.
Huh? Are you sure?
My name is Shino, Shino Asada,
And I live at...
You're not gonna believe this,
But you're close to the place I'm diving from.
Yeah? Wow, no way.
How 'bout this?
After we log out, I could head over to you.
You would? Really?
Oh.
No, I'm good.
A friend of mine lives near
me, so I've got help if I need it.
Okay, but after I log out, I'll call the guy I work for.
And have him send the cops if you're cool with that.
Mm‐hmm. Sounds good.
But not good enough.
You just gonna log out without telling me your info?
Oh, right. Sorry.
My real name is Kazuto Kirigaya.
That's how you got "Kirito"? Seriously?
Talk about a lack of imagination.
Yeah, well, like you're one to talk.
Hmm?
All right, then.
If we're ever gonna log out of
this thing, we've gotta end BOB first.
So how do you wanna do this?
Want to have a duel like we did yesterday?
Hmm.
Look at yourself. You're all banged up.
There's no challenge in beating
someone who's already as thrashed as you.
Nah. I'll take you on at the next
BOB, but you better not leave me hanging.
Well, let's get this thing over with already.
How we gonna do that?
Unless one of our HPs drains out all
the way, there's not gonna be a winner.
I guess you didn't hear what happened in the first BOB.
There were two winners.
The player who should have
won let his guard down too soon,
So his opponent gave him what we call a souvenir grenade.
A souvenir grenade?
What the heck's that?
This.
Uh...
Death Gun had two victims this time.
That means he's got at least two others helping him.
What am I doing?
Asada? You there?
It's me, Asada.
Shinkawa.
I, uh, just wanted to congratulate you on your win.
I even brought some pastries.
And, hey, congrats.
You were so awesome, Asada.
I mean Sinon.
You did it.
You're the best gunner in "GGO" now.
I knew all along you could do it.
You deserve being number one more than anybody.
You showed them all what real strength's about.
You should be proud.
Thank you.
Um, Asada...
What's up?
You said... you said to wait.
Remember that?
What are you talking about?
Well, you told me to wait and,
if I did, then you'd be mine.
Huh?
I waited.
I waited for you.
What's gotten into you?
From now on, I'll always be with you.
You don't need him to protect you.
That's my job.
I'm gonna protect you now...
Forever.
Shinkawa!
I love you, Asada.
You're mine, my Asada,
My Sinon, mine.
Let go!
Huh?
Why'd you push me away like that?
You made a promise.
We both did.
Shinkawa.
Sh‐shinkawa.
Don't make any sudden moves, Asada.
The syringe I'm holding's got a drug in it
that'll paralyze your muscles in an instant.
Before you know it, your lungs will stop, then your heart.
Syringe?
Maybe by injecting some kind of drug or something.
That's one way.
Yeah, it is the family business.
I promised my dad I'd go to med school,
so it's a done deal. Stuck with it now.
This is crazy.
You're the other Death Gun?
Ooh, I'm impressed.
You figured out Death Gun's little secret.
It's true.
I'm Death Gun's partner in crime.
Up to now,
Before this year's BOB, anyway,
I was the one playing Sterben,
but today I insisted on being the one to do the job IRL.
Don't you see I had to be the one doing the
deed? I can't let some other guy touch you,
Even if that guy is my brother.
Your brother?
So then the player who belonged
to that murder guild in "SAO",
That was your older brother.
Forget about him.
It's just you and me now, Asada.
Stop.
It's not too late.
You don't have to do this.
What about cram school, huh?
You said you were gonna be a doctor.
Doctor?
You think I give a damn about that,
About my parents, those guys at school?
They're all assholes!
You know what would have made me happy?
To be the strongest player in "GGO",
But that piece of shit Zxe‐D lied
about AGI types being the strongest,
And I fell for it like an idiot!
You don't know.
"GGO" was everything to me,
And I gave everything up in the
real world for it, god damn it!
Y‐You killed Zxe‐D 'cause he lied?
Oh, come on.
He was the perfect victim.
We had to show the world Death
Gun was the strongest in "GGO",
In all the VRMMOs.
What better person to sacrifice than that dork?
And now that that's done,
I don't need this reality anymore.
Let's move on to the next one.
Come on, just you and me.
What are you saying?
We can go somewhere like "GGO".
Mm. No, someplace with a fantasy vibe instead.
As long as it's with you, I don't care.
We'll be reborn, be husband and wife.
We'll get a house. We'll go on quests together,
Oh, and have kids, too.
It'll be so much fun.
I know it will. Come with me.
Asada.
You're so beautiful.
You are.
More than anything, you're mine and no one else's.
I always loved you, Asada,
Always.
In school, when I heard about what
happened, when I heard what you did,
I could look all over and
never find another girl like you.
I mean, you shot a real bad guy
with a real gun and killed him!
How cool is that?
I told you, didn't I?
I said you had real power.
When I came up with the Death Gun legend,
I picked the type 54 as his gun 'cause of you.
That's how much I love you, Asada.
I love you so much,
More than anything.
No.
I don't want to see anything,
or feel anything anymore.
This isn't real.
It can't be.
Kirito.
You went to all that trouble to save me,
But it was all for nothing.
How 'bout this?
After we log out, I could head over to you.
If he comes over, he'll be in danger.
And I can't do anything about it.
That's not true.
Huh?
Up to this point, all we've been
doing was looking out for ourselves.
We certainly never fought for anyone else.
But now, even though it might be too late for us,
Let's go fight for someone else,
just this once, me and you.
Come on. Let's go.
I love you, Asada.
A‐Asada!
No.
Let go of me! No!
Asada. Asada.
Asada! Asada!
Asada!
Run, Sinon!
Kirito.
Next time: "One Little Step".