A type 54 Black Star.
It's the gun.
Why?
Why here?
Why does he have that gun?
What it means to be strong,
to be brave...
I thought somehow I could learn those things from Kirito.
I don't wanna die.
A grenade.
Kiri... to.
I'm slowing you down.
Just leave me.
Not the horse.
It can go fast,
but it's too hard to handle.
Sinon, get your rifle,
and blow that horse away.
Huh? What?
All right.
I'll try.
No. My finger.
I can't pull it.
I can't do it.
I can't pull the trigger.
Hang on tight.
It's no use.
We can still get away.
Stay sharp, damn it.
No.
He's catching up.
Hurry! Faster!
Please don't let him catch up to us.
Help me. I can't do this.
I don't wanna die!
Hey, Sinon, snap out of it!
Listen, he's catching up with us.
Pick up your gun, and shoot him!
No, I can't.
You don't have to hit him.
Just distract him.
I can't!
Don't make me. Don't make me.
Then get up here, and steer this thing.
Give me your gun, and I'll shoot him.
Hecate.
She's part of me.
I'm the only one who can use her.
I can't do it.
I can't shoot. I can't move my finger.
I can't. I can't fight anymore.
You can!
Everyone can fight if they want to.
It's your choice, so what'll it be?
Will you give up, or will you fight?
If it's my choice,
then I don't want to fight anymore.
I'm done.
I don't want to suffer anymore.
I thought I could get stronger playing this game,
but I was wrong.
I'll help you, but you have to try,
so come on. You can do this.
It's no good.
With all this shaking around, I can't lock on.
It's okay. The shaking's gonna stop in three,
two, one,
now!
How's he do it?
How can he be so calm now?
No, it's not that he's being calm.
He's giving it everything he's got.
When he fights, he goes all out every time,
no excuses.
That's it.
That's where he gets his strength.
I missed.
This isn't good.
We're like sitting ducks out here.
We need to find some cover.
Hey, I think I see a cave over there.
If we hide inside, we can avoid the sat scan.
Sounds good. Let's go.
This is perfect.
We can dodge the scan and rest up, too.
What happened back there?
It's like he just popped up out of nowhere.
We didn't see him on the scan.
That must mean he's got some kind of cloaking skill.
Is there a skill like that here, invisibility?
Yeah, there is. It's a skill
called meta‐material optical camouflage.
We're safe, for now anyway.
Even if he's invisible,
the sands are rough here.
We'll hear it crunching under his boots.
We'll see his footprints, too,
so he can't sneak up like he did before.
Roger that.
Well, I guess we'll keep our eyes and ears open.
Hey, Kirito,
do you think there's a chance Death
Gun was killed in that explosion?
No.
The second before that truck blew up,
I saw him jump off of that robot horse.
He might have gotten dinged up,
but I can't believe that blast killed him.
Oh.
When he had me in his sights back at
the stadium, I thought I was a goner.
How'd you know I was in trouble?
And how'd you get to me so fast from your position?
We were wrong about Jushi X being Death Gun.
I took one look, and I knew it wasn't.
It was pretty obvious, actually.
Obvious?
Yeah. I know a woman when I see one.
Oh.
The second I saw her,
I knew we overlooked something.
I didn't know what, though.
Oh, by the way,
even though her handle says Jushi,
she calls herself Musketeer X.
Anyway, after I took out Musketeer X,
I looked over to the south and
saw you lying there in the street.
I knew you were in trouble,
so I grabbed her rifle and grenades and charged in,
shooting and tossing bombs as fast as I could.
I can't believe I let my guard down like that.
Don't go beating yourself up over it.
I mean, look, it's not like I
knew he was hiding down there either,
and if our roles were flipped, you know what?
I would have been the one getting shot instead.
But that's okay, 'cause I know you
would have rescued me, too, wouldn't you?
I can't believe it.
My rival's trying to make me feel better.
He knows I'm weak, and here he is consoling me,
like I'm a kid or something.
I'm heading out for a bit.
You might as well kick back
here and rest up while you can.
I wish you could log out, but I know you can't,
not till the tourney's over, anyway.
Huh?
You're going after Death Gun, aren't you?
You think you can take him on alone?
Yeah. I have to.
He's tough, and he won't go down
without getting off a shot or two at me.
If it comes down to that, I don't know what I'll do.
I might bail.
I don't wanna leave you hanging like
that, so it's better if I face him alone.
Then you're scared of him, too?
Yeah, I am.
If it was the old me,
I would have jumped right in and fought
him, even if there was a chance I was gonna die,
but not anymore.
These days, there's things I have to protect.
I can't die.
I don't want to.
Things you have to protect?
Yeah, in the virtual world
and the real one, too.
Okay.
Then don't go after him. Just stay here, and keep low.
As long as BOB's going on, we can't log out,
but once the competition's whittled
down to us and one other player,
we can suicide out and let the other guy win.
That'll end the tournament.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, that's one way of doing it.
Thing is, it's not really a good option.
If we just sit here and wait for the tourney to end,
there's no telling how many
other players that guy's gonna kill.
Yeah.
You really are strong after all.
I'm not gonna hide either.
Huh?
I'm going outside and help you take that bastard out.
No, you're not. Haven't you been listening?
If he shoots you, there's a chance you'll die.
As a player, close combat's my specialty.
It's not yours.
You're in way more danger than me,
'cause he can be invisible if he wants.
He'll pop up next to you, and bang.
I don't care if I die.
I was scared out of my mind back at the stadium.
I was scared I was gonna die.
I was even weaker than I was five years ago,
like a screaming, crying little girl.
If that's how I'm gonna be for the rest of my life,
I'd rather be dead.
It's only natural to be afraid.
I don't know anyone who's not afraid of dying.
Yeah, well, I hate it.
I'm tired of being afraid.
I'm so tired.
Whatever.
I'm not asking to go with you.
I'll fight by myself.
You want to fight alone and die alone.
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah.
I was always supposed to die alone.
Let go.
I have to do this.
You got it all wrong.
There's no dying alone.
It's not that simple.
When you die, you leave a hole in all
the people whose lives you were part of,
and like it or not, you're part of mine now.
Yeah, well, I never asked to be a part of it.
Besides, my life's no one else's business but mine.
You're wrong.
We're involved in each other's lives now.
All right!
If that's how it is, then you can
protect me for the rest of my life!
You don't know anything,
and you can't do anything, so
don't go saying stuff like that!
This... this isn't your fight! It's mine!
Mine! You got that?!
Even if I lose, even if I die,
no one can blame me for what I did.
You want to help?
You gonna carry this burden with me?
Then what, huh?
You gonna hold my hands
even though they've got blood all over 'em?!
Murderer.
Murderer. Murderer.
You murderer!
You kill anyone today?
Eww. Don't touch me.
You'll get me all bloody.
Why don't you kill yourself?
Nyah, nyah!
Psycho!
I hate you!
I hate your guts!
I hate you.
Even though I hate your guts,
can I borrow your lap for a sec?
I...
I killed someone.
About five years ago,
in a small town up north,
this guy tried to Rob a post office.
The news said the robber died
'cause his gun went off accidentally.
But the truth is I was there.
I grabbed his gun and shot him dead.
How old were you?
11 years old.
And ever since then, whenever I see a
gun, I start throwing up, and then I pass out.
If I see a gun, I see the face of the
robber the way he looked right before he died.
And then I‐I get so scared.
Really?
Yeah, but in this world,
I don't have those problems,
and that got me thinking.
If I can become the strongest player in the game,
then I'll be strong IRL, too,
and maybe even forget what I did.
But just now...
I mean, when Death Gun had me pinned,
I was terrified.
And just like that,
I wasn't Sinon anymore.
I was the real me again.
I'm scared to die. I am.
Although, what's worse is living with this fear.
It's so painful, I'd rather be dead.
But I know if I run away from Death Gun and my past,
I'll end up weaker than before.
I will. I know it.
Yeah.
I get it.
I killed someone once, too.
What?
I mentioned it once,
'bout how I knew Death Gun.
We fought before when we were stuck in another game.
I'm sure you heard of it,
"Sword Art Online."
Oh, my god. I knew it.
Yeah, I'm a survivor of "SAO",
and so is Death Gun, and back then,
he was a red player in this guild.
They called themselves Laughing Coffin, PKers.
They had to be stopped,
so one day, a party was formed to
catch 'em and haul 'em off to prison.
I was in that party.
They found out about our plans, and they ambushed us,
and in the middle of the chaos, I
killed two of Laughing Coffin. I just...
Cut 'em down.
And over time,
I managed to force myself to forget what I did,
till yesterday,
when I ran into the guy calling himself Death Gun.
And there's no doubt he was with Laughing Coffin that day?
You're sure he was part of that ambush?
I am, about as sure as I'll ever be.
He's one of the players we took to prison that day.
That's why, no matter what,
I have to settle things with him in here
in this world.
Next time: "What It Means to Be Strong".