I'm ninety‐nine percent sure the Death Gun story's a hoax,
probably someone trolling.
You can't kill someone in the
real world from the virtual anymore.
I know that's impossible.
But there's still that one
percent chance it could be true.
That's why I'm here.
Link start!
It's a lot different than ALO.
Go figure. Killing people's the point in here.
All right, then.
Hmm?
Holy crap!
I wish I looked a little more soldierish.
Holy bazongers! That's the F‐1300 model, isn't it?!
That avatar's so rare, I've
only heard about them till now.
I want it.
I'll give you two mega‐credits for your account.
Come on, lady. What do you say?
L‐Lady?
Um, hate to break it you, guy,
but I'm a guy, too.
Holy crap!
Then that means you got the M‐9000 model!
I'll give you four, no, five for it.
Sell it to me. Come on. Sell it to me.
Sorry, but this isn't a default avatar.
It's a converted one.
I can't exchange it for cash.
Aww, that sucks.
Yeah, well, later.
Hey, if you ever change your mind, give me the first bid.
If I want to get Death Gun's attention,
I have to make a name for myself first.
Looking for some action? 'Cause here it is.
What? Are you too good for me?
I'm totally lost.
Some shortcut this turned out to be.
Uh, excuse me.
Can you tell me where...
Uh‐oh. She thinks I'm hitting on her.
Yeah? What?
Uh...
your first time in the game, huh?
I, um...
Oh, my god.
She thinks I'm a girl, too.
Where do you wanna go?
Uh...
I, uh...
Yes, it's my first time.
I'm looking for a place to buy a cheap gun.
Oh, and I also need to find out
where the governor's office is.
Oh. Sure.
I can show you.
It's not cool,
but I'll let her keep thinking I'm a girl for a while.
By the way,
why do you want to go to the governor's office?
Uh, I wanted to sign myself up for
an event called Bullet of Bullets.
BOB?
Okay, but you just started playing today, right?
Yes.
Yeah, I don't know.
Your stats may not be high enough for that.
Oh. Well, I converted,
so all my skills have been transferred from another game.
If you say so.
So, anyway, you picked a heck of a game to play.
It's all grimy and stinks of oil.
Mm, well, I've only played fantasy games up to now.
They're fun, but I thought I'd try a cyber‐game for once.
I was also interested in seeing
what gun battles were like.
Really?
It takes guts to want to start
with BOB Right off the bat like that.
Let's hook you up with a gun then.
I know this great market. It's down here.
Okay.
Wow. This place looks like it has everything.
Yeah, well, the two types of
weapons that are mostly used in GGO
are optical guns and live‐ammo guns.
Huh.
An optical gun's lighter and more
accurate, but it has its drawbacks.
If your opponent equips their defense
shield, it only does half the damage.
For a one‐on‐one tourney like BOB,
a live‐ammo gun's the best bet.
Oh. Okay.
All right, let's start with your stats, highest one first.
Um, I guess my strength is the highest,
and speed after that.
You're an Str‐Agi type, huh?
Okay, you've got two choices for your main weapon,
either a heavy assault rifle
or a large‐caliber machine gun.
Whichever one you choose, you're also
gonna need a handgun for a backup weapon.
Oh, wait a sec.
You said you just converted over, didn't you?
Do you have any credits?
Yeah, I should.
Let's see.
It says I have a thousand credits.
Everybody gets that when they start.
Oh.
Hmm. If that's all you have, the most
you can afford's gonna be a small ray gun.
And for a live‐ammo gun, a thousand
won't even get you a used revolver.
Listen, if you want,
I could loan you the money to buy a gun.
That's really sweet of you, but I couldn't. Uh, I know.
Does this game have anything in it where a
new player like me could go earn some money?
Well, I don't recommend them, but
there are casinos and gambling games,
like that one.
Hey, chicken, come on.
How do you play?
You enter through that gate and go
down the alley, dodging the NPC's bullets.
The idea is to get as close as
you can to him without getting shot.
If you can touch him,
you win all the cash everyone's sunk
into it since the last time it was beat.
All of it?!
Three hundred thou and change.
Now, that is a heck of a lot of money.
Well, no one's beaten it.
Once you get eight meters away from the gunslinger,
he switches to this wicked‐fast quick‐draw mode.
By the time you see the bullet lines, it's too late.
The bullet lines?
Look. Another sucker's stepping up to add to the jackpot.
Today's the day, man.
Yeah, you got this.
Here goes nothin'.
I'm gonna blast you from here to the moon, ya varmint.
Hurry up, and die already.
Watch me clear this beeyotch in nothing flat.
Jackpot's yours.
Yeah, you know it.
Why's he doing that?
Was that the bullet line?
Yep. It's a defensive system assist.
We all have it.
Except for a sniper's first shot,
bullet prediction lines always show
up in the target's field of vision.
I'll kill ya.
Whatever.
Run, man!
You so got this!
You loser.
Game over, hoss.
Well, that sucked.
That guy didn't have a chance.
See?
That alley is so narrow, you
can't move too far to either side,
and you're forced to charge the gunslinger straight on.
That's about as far as anyone's gotten.
Ah, I get it.
If I wait to see the bullet lines, it'll be too late.
Uh, hey, where are you going?
Ten creds says the newbie gets it out of the gate.
Whoa. That's the cutest target I ever seen.
Let's stick around and watch her get pwned.
I'll kill ya.
You loser.
You're kidding.
She passed the ten‐meter Mark.
That is one fast kid.
Die, you varmint.
I'll blast you to hell!
Looks like someone's out of bullets.
No!
Hey, chicken, come on.
What the hell was that?
Who is that kid?
Oh, my god.
I've never seen reflexes like that.
I mean, at the end,
you dodged his lasers from about two meters away.
At that range, the time between you seeing the
bullet lines and the shots fired... well, that's it.
There shouldn't have been any time between 'em.
Oh. Um...
Really?
Well, since it's a game of dodging bullets,
I just predicted the bullet lines.
You know, predict the predictions.
You‐You predicted the predictions?!
Huh?
I'm confused about the specs for this assault rifle.
I mean, this thing's ginormous, so why's the caliber
of the bullets it fires smaller than a submachine gun's?
I'm confused about how someone like you can
dodge bullets like a ghost and not know that.
You converted from another game.
What'd you play before this one?
Nothing special.
Just one of those typical fantasy games, is all.
Hmm.
Yeah, so you said.
Well, during the BOB Prelims,
I'll get an idea of what you can really do.
As for the assault rifle,
you want to know why it uses a small caliber?
Sure.
It all goes back to the M16 from the US.
They designed it for precision and penetrative power,
but using a fast, small‐caliber round.
You don't need to know that stuff, though.
Now that you've got three hundred K, you
can buy pretty much whatever gun you want.
It all comes down to what you want
and what you think'll work best for you.
What does work for me?
Hmm.
Hey, what are these?
Oh, those are photon swords.
Photon.
It's a beam of light
that's a wave and a particle.
Photon sword's the official name, but
people call 'em laser blades, beam sabers,
and something else I can't remember.
Oh, cool! You can use a sword here?
Yeah, if you want, but nobody really uses them.
Why don't they?
Well, I mean, because you can't use
it unless you're close to your target,
and if you're crazy enough to get that close,
you'll get shot full of holes.
So basically it's good as long as you get close enough.
Yeah, I guess, but even with your skill at dodging,
if there's a full‐auto gun firing at yo...
ugh.
Welcome, player.
Thank you.
Thank you for your purchase.
Have a nice day.
Oh, well.
I guess when it comes to combat,
everyone's got their own style.
The way I see it, if this place sells something,
it must be okay for battle, even this.
Whoa.
Huh.
She looks like she knows what she's doing.
Wow.
Those are your fantasy game skills?
Not bad.
I know a couple of moves.
This sure is light.
Huh?
Well, looks like you're dead
set on that for your main weapon,
but you should have a submachine gun
or a handgun in your inventory, too.
It'll distract your enemy so you can get closer.
Oh, okay.
How much do you have left?
About a hundred‐fifty K.
Whoa. Those photon thingies are expensive.
You got a hundred and fifty K, huh?
You still need to get protective gear,
some kind of weapon, and the ammo for it.
What's cheap, but good?
I'll trust your judgment with all that.
For BOB, a live‐ammo weapon's your best bet.
If I were you, I'd go for accuracy over stopping power.
Hmm.
Oh. You'll spend most of your credits on it,
but this one's good,
the FN five seven.
What's five seven?
The bullet caliber,
5.7 millimeters.
They're smaller than the nine‐mill
parabellum bullets, but they still pack a punch.
They're similar in shape to rifle bullets, so
they've got the edge in both precision and stopping power.
Huh.
Hey, are you even listening?
Huh? Oh, yeah.
I guess I'll buy that one then.
Is that it, or do I need anything else?
Yeah, you do. You're gonna need a holster,
some extra mags, some protective gear.
And you should also get yourself
a defense field and range time.
What's that?
You never fired a gun before, have you?
Uh‐uh, never.
Let's change that.
If you buy a gun from the shop,
you can test it here.
Know how to hold it?
I guess.
It's lighter than I thought.
That's 'cause that model's made of reinforced plastic.
The recoil isn't too bad on it.
Still, you should grip it with both
hands. And keep your left eye open.
Oh, okay.
So right now, you should be seeing a
green circle in your field of vision.
Is it supposed to be shrinking and expanding like that?
Yep.
It's called the bullet circle,
your offensive assist system.
Your bullets'll hit the target
at random inside the circle.
How do I boost my accuracy?
I guess the easiest way is to get closer to your target.
What else?
Try to stay calm.
The faster your heart beats,
the more the circle expands.
This is harder than I thought.
No way.
I missed?
What'd you expect?
It's your first time.
Thank you for going out of your way for me.
I really appreciate it.
Mm‐mmm. I was happy to help.
There aren't many girl players here.
I wasn't doing anything, so it was a good
way to kill some time before the prelims.
Wait. You're gonna compete in BOB, too?
Uh‐huh. I was on my way to sign up before...
Oh, my god.
They're closing soon.
Really? I'm so sorry.
It's my fault we're late.
No, it's mine for not keeping track of the time.
Whatever. Let's hurry.
We're never gonna make it.
Can't we just teleport over there?
I wish. That only happens when you
respawn at a revival point after you die.
And we can't suicide ourselves to get there
either, 'cause in town, our HP Never goes down.
The governor's office is at least three kilometers away.
It's gonna take us five minutes to
sign up, so we have to get there in three.
Don't close.
Don't close till we get there.
That's it.
Here we go.
Better hang on!
Wait a sec.
These are supposed to be ridiculously hard to drive.
I don't know anyone who can
handle 'em, so how come you can?
Oh, well, I used to play a lot
of racing games back in the day.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
This is great.
Go on. Punch it.
The faster, the better.
Okay.
Next time: "Guns and Swords".