Um, okay, everyone!
A toast to this gathering of friends, new and old.
To us!
With everyone here, we'd be an amazing party.
Yeah, we would. I know!
We should raid the boss on floor twenty‐three.
I'm down with that!
Then let's go get him!
Yeah!
You're goin' down!
Aww.
Crap.
Hmph.
Yeah!
Thank goodness. You made it.
About forty minutes ago, her
heart stopped, but only for a moment.
We got it going with defibrillation and meds,
but if it happens again...
Why now? Why is this happening?
She seemed fine!
I'm sorry.
The truth is, ever since January,
when you first came to visit her,
her condition's been touch and go,
and for these last three months, we've all been stunned
by how Yuuki's managed to hang in there.
She can't beat this, but she keeps fighting.
She keeps on fighting.
The fifteen years Yuuki's spent on
this planet have been one long battle.
The HIV's only part of it.
She's also been fighting the harsh
reality of her situation while in treatment.
There's no doubt the clinical trials with the
medicuboid caused her an unimaginable amount of pain,
and still somehow Yuuki keeps hanging on.
Well, anyway, we should let her get some rest now.
Come on, Yuuki.
You can't lose.
I mean, you're Zekken...
The ultimate swordswoman.
Take her hand.
It's okay. That's what she wants.
Doctor, can she use the medicuboid now?
But, well, wouldn't she want
to spend her last moments here?
No. She wants to go back one last time.
Please, doctor, let her use the medicuboid again.
Mm.
It's going to take about a minute to boot up.
Then what?
I'm going next door to log in with the Amusphere.
Wait for me, Yuuki. I'm coming.
Thanks, Asuna.
I'm glad I got to see you again,
'cause I got somethin' for you.
I can't believe I almost forgot about it.
Really? What is it you wanted to give me?
Oh, um, I still gotta make it.
Hang on a sec.
Yuuki!
That's weird.
I feel so weak all of a sudden.
I'm not in any pain or anything, though.
It's okay. You're just a little tired, is all.
You'll feel better if you rest.
Yeah, maybe.
Listen, Asuna, take this.
It's my original sword skill.
No, Yuuki, I couldn't.
Oh, come on. I want you to have it.
Open the window.
I gave it a cool name,
Mother's Rosario.
I‐It'll keep you safe when you need it.
Thank you, Yuuki.
I promise I'll take good care of it,
and someday, when I leave this world,
I'll make sure to pass it on to someone before I go.
Your sword'll live on until the end of time.
Thank you.
Aww, guys. Come on.
We talked about this.
You promised, no good‐byes.
Nah, you got it wrong.
We're all here to cheer you up.
When you get to the other side, wait for us, okay.
We won't take too long, promise.
What're you talking about?
If you get there too soon, I'll be pissed.
Tsk, tsk!
You know the deal.
You're hopeless without us,
so don't even try to argue!
Just sit tight, and wait...
for... for us.
Please, Nori, don't cry.
We promised we'd be strong.
I give up. You win.
I'll wait for you.
But take your time.
You got it?
Mm‐hmm.
Whoa.
Look at all those fairies.
I'm sorry.
I had to let them know.
I hope you're not mad at me.
Are you kidding?
Why would I be mad?
There's so many of 'em.
It's like a dream.
Why are they here?
Because of you.
You're the strongest, most powerful
swordswoman this world's ever seen.
There will never be anyone else like you again.
We can't let you go without saying good‐bye.
It's not right.
We're all praying for you,
that your next journey
will be to a place as wonderful as this.
I'm happy.
I'm so happy.
You know, this whole time, I thought if I was born to die,
what the heck was the point of me even being born?
I never made anything or gave anything to anyone.
All I did was waste drugs and hog that machine
and cause trouble for everyone.
If all I get to do is suffer and disappear in the end,
it'd be better to just disappear right now.
I used to always think,
why am I alive?
Why'd I stick around for this long?
But you know what?
After all this time, I think I know why now.
I might not have done much,
but I'm glad I got to live,
'cause after everything,
these last few moments, they're the best ever.
I'm surrounded by all my friends,
and I got to end my journey in the arms of someone I love.
Yuuki, I promise,
I will see you again someday,
in some other place, some other world.
I don't know how, but I'll find you,
and then we can sit and talk,
and you could tell me where you've been.
I gave this life everything I had.
I was alive.
I never made anything or gave anything to anyone.
You gave me something.
You carved it deep into my heart,
and it'll always be there.
Hello, Asuna.
How are you?
Wait. Is that you, Siune?
Yes, in the flesh.
It's nice to finally meet you in the real world.
I'm Shi‐Eun An.
Oh! I‐It's nice to see you, too.
I'm Asuna Yuuki.
Like meeting for the first time, huh?
No, it's okay.
Just this month, I got the all‐clear from
my doctor and was discharged from the hospital.
Then, you're doing better?
Yes.
The type of disease I have is
called acute lymphocytic leukemia,
and it was about three years ago when I developed it.
The side effects from the medicine were so horrible,
I wanted to die rather than keep suffering,
but whenever I saw Yuuki, I thought, "here's this kid,
and she's handling her situation
better than I'm handling mine."
Around February,
they started cutting back on the meds I was on.
I thought, "this is it,"
and I braced myself for the end.
And then a week ago,
the day after Yuuki died,
my doctor came in and said,
"congratulations. You're in complete remission."
Next thing I knew, I was being discharged.
I barely had a chance to process the news.
And the truth is, it still hasn't sunk in yet.
It's like I should feel awful.
It doesn't seem fair that I'm
still here and Yuuki's waiting.
Yuuki and Ran, Clovis and Merida,
we promised we'd stick together forever,
and I‐I'm here, and...
Shi‐Eun.
You know, our lives are like vessels,
and we carry the teachings of
the ones who've passed in them.
For the longest time, I was so scared,
scared of telling someone how I really
felt and scared of finding out how they felt.
But I learned from Yuuki that
that was no way for me to live.
If I didn't even try to reach out,
nothing would ever change.
She taught me how to be strong,
and I want to share that with others.
As long as I'm alive,
I'll pass on what I learned from her to everyone I meet,
and then someday, when I see her again,
I want to tell her about all the people she's helped.
That's how I'll pay her back.
Thank you, Asuna.
You know, we're all so grateful for what you've done.
I'd been so worried about Yuuki.
She was carrying a heavy burden
on those little shoulders of hers,
but then you showed up, and something in her changed.
When you were together,
Yuuki seemed like she was really having fun.
She was like a forgetful bird who remembered how to fly,
and she flew up and up, and now she's out of our reach.
Anyway, jun's also doing great.
The medication he's on seems to be working.
It's like... I don't know.
To me, it feels like Yuuki's telling all of us
it's still too soon to join her.
I guess that means it's going to be a while yet
before the sleeping knights get back together.
Just remember, next time, you're taking me in as a member,
and I don't want to hear any arguments.
Hey.
I hope we're not interrupting anything.
No. But wait.
Do you guys know each other?
Sort of.
He's trying to steal my ideas
about that communications pod I made.
No, he's lying.
I'm interested in its possibilities
in full‐dive medical tech,
so we've been e‐mailing back and forth.
That's great for both of you.
What about the medicuboid?
Are you going to phase it out,
or were the trials successful?
Glad you asked. They were extremely successful,
and now we have enough data to proceed to the next phase.
Soon, patients all over the country will have...
I am so sorry about that.
I can't believe I didn't say this first.
Ms. An, congratulations on your recovery.
I know Yuuki would be thrilled at the news, too.
Thank you for saying so,
and congratulations on the trials.
It's good to know what you learned
from Yuuki will be used to help others.
That makes me happy.
Me, too.
Yuuki was the first person to test the medicuboid,
and her name will always be remembered.
If she were here, she'd get an award for her help,
along with the benefactor who made it all possible.
Knowing Yuuki, she wouldn't be
too thrilled at getting an award.
She'd say, "what's the point
in having it if I can't eat it?"
Um, doctor, you just mentioned the
medicuboid had some kind of benefactor?
I thought you said the government was paying for it.
Oh, well, yes, they are,
but the initial designs were given
to us for free from someone else.
If I remember correctly,
I think her name was Dr. Rinko Koujiro.
W‐What's wrong, Kirito?
I‐I know her
How?
I met her once.
Yeah, in fact, she was taking care of
Heathcliff's body while he was diving.
She was his head researcher.
She helped him develop full‐dive technology.
You see? The medicuboid's design,
you know who invented it?
No way.
It was Kayaba.
Need any help unpacking all this stuff?
Sure, but only if you're not busy.
Seriously, ain't she cute?
Uh... Uh...
I got you a little gift.
No way. You shouldn't have.
Hey... You guys suck.
Are you having fun hanging out here with everyone?
Yes!
And the cherry blossoms are pretty.
Yeah, it's too bad they're almost gone.
Oh, please, there's plenty left, you spoilsport.
Anyway, we're here with Yui.
That's the important thing.
I still can't believe we made it happen that fast.
Thank you so much for this, daddy.
Yeah, Kirito, thank you.
Nah, if you want to thank someone,
thank Yuuki for helping me develop it.
Wow!
The real world and the virtual,
I thought the closer they came together,
the better the future would be.
Hm?
It's like the more the lines between these worlds blur,
the more everyone gets sucked into its darkness.
Yeah, but a lot of people have been helped by it, too.
If anything,
I wish I knew what Kayaba's master plan was.
I don't know. Maybe it's our job
as survivors of "SAO" To find out.
I think you're overthinking things.
Yeah, I guess.
Still, I wanna find out more than ever now.
Even after everything that's happened,
my curiosity's got me hooked.
Although, a part of me thinks I'm being played here.
That's kind of annoying.
Whatever.
I don't know what's gonna happen tomorrow.
All I know is I wanna be with you forever,
and I want you to be with me.
I'll stick by you, even if you
move halfway across the planet.
Who said anything about moving?
Don't forget to take me along.
Hey, lovebirds!
Quit makin' out! We wanna take a photo!
Get over here, guys! Today, guys!
Hurry up! Move it, dude!
Well, shall we?
Mm‐hmm.
Okay, daddy.