A‐Asada!
No.
Let go of me! No!
Asada. Asada.
Asada! Asada!
Asada!
Run, Sinon!
Kirito.
What the hell? Get off me!
Bastard! It's all your fault.
She's mine.
She's mine, damn it!
Stay away from her!
Kirito!
Kirito.
He got me.
It happened so fast.
Didn't even see the needle.
I know. I'm gonna take a look, okay?
Hang on.
I'm not gonna let you die like this.
Um, hey...
You got this weird thing on your chest.
Please tell me that's where he hit me with the needle.
It looks like it, I guess.
What is that thing, anyway?
It's one of the electrodes from
this heart monitor I was hooked up to.
Heart monitor?
Never mind.
You know, you scared the hell out of me.
I scared you?!
How do you think I feel?!
I thought you were gonna die just now, you dumb‐ass!
Hey! Easy!
Mm.
He's not dead, is he?
Nah, he's still got a pulse.
You're crazy,
but thank you for coming over.
No, thank you for clocking him when you did.
I'm sorry I couldn't get here sooner.
Uh, you okay?
Mm‐hmm.
I can't wait to see the look on her face.
Next time you wanna meet, be on time.
Seriously?
Girl, you been acting way too cocky lately.
She's right. We should teach you a lesson.
Nah, you guys. It's cool.
We're all friends here, right?
It's good to have friends.
They come in real handy,
especially when you need a loan.
Speaking of, I need 20K, buddy.
I told you before.
I'm not lending you guys any money.
You'll change your mind after I
show you what my brother gave me.
I doubt it.
Get this. He told me not to point
this at anyone, but what does he know?
I mean, you've seen one before,
so it doesn't bug you, right?
Or does it, Asada?
Get on your knees, and say you're sorry.
Waah!
Crap. It's not working.
Ow!
Government‐Issue M1911.
Your brother has good taste.
It's not really my style, though.
And for future reference,
it only fires when the safety's off.
Hey, whoa.
Your brother's right.
You shouldn't point this at people.
Here.
Oh, my god. Are you okay?
Come on. Get up, Endo.
See you around.
They say the first step's always the hardest.
Huh?
Hey, Asada, do you know that guy?
Is he your boyfriend?
Aww.
Really? When I said I'd meet you, I didn't
think you'd park yourself in front of my school.
Hmm?
Oh, what's up, Sinon?
Kyoji Shinkawa and his older
brother Shoichi were arrested.
During the interrogation,
it came out that another person was involved.
This third Death Gun, Atsushi Kanamoto,
is still out there,
but Kikuoka says they'll catch him soon enough.
They got the idea of creating the Death Gun character
when Shoichi got the invisibility cloak
through a real‐money trade.
Using the cloak and some binoculars,
Shoichi started stealing the
real‐world info of the other players.
Meanwhile, his little brother Kyoji was
having issues with his avatar, Spiegel.
These players who think it's
all about their Agility... Heh...
man, they're living in a dream.
Spiegel was an Agi‐type, which Zxe‐D used to recommend,
but Zxe‐D shifted his stats to a Str‐Vit combo,
and that pissed Kyoji off.
When Shoichi found out,
he gave Kyoji Zxe‐D's name and address IRL.
Then they started talking about how to kill him.
They say they weren't serious about it at first,
but day after day, the more they talked about it,
the more it seemed they could get away with it.
For their plan to work,
they needed two things from their dad's hospital,
a master key card used to open doors in emergencies
and a lethal drug for the deed.
They researched their victims carefully,
narrowing the list down to the ones who
lived alone in low‐security apartments.
Using the key card,
Shoichi broke into their first victim's place,
Shigemura, AKA Zxe‐D.
The brothers worked out the
exact time he was supposed to die,
when Kyoji logged in as his brother's avatar Sterben
and announced himself as Death Gun and shot Zxe‐D.
Their second victim, Usushio Tarako,
was killed the same way.
But instead of being scared of Death Gun,
the other players in "GGO"
treated it like some kind of joke.
Shoichi and his partners were furious,
so they decided to kill some players during the BOB Final.
They found three who met the same
criteria as Zxe‐D and Tarako...
Pale Rider, Garrett, and Sinon.
Killing three people was gonna make
things hard for just the two of them, though.
Yeah. To be in sync with Death Gun,
the person doing the real‐world killing had to
make sure they'd be at each target's house on time.
So they recruited that Kanamoto guy you told me about
to be the third Death Gun. Where'd they find him, though?
Simple. Kanamoto was an old friend of Shoichi's.
They were both part of Laughing Coffin in "SAO".
We found out his handle there was Johnny Black.
That sound familiar?
Yeah. He worked with Xaxa.
I think his weapon of choice was a poison knife.
They put Kanamoto on Pale Rider and Garrett,
'cause he lived nearby.
Sinon, on the other hand, was Kyoji's.
See, Shoichi was the one who usually did the killing,
but for this one job,
Kyoji insisted on being the one to do it.
Um... Hmm?
Is that what he wanted for real?
Did Shinka... I mean Kyoji say that?
No. His brother was the one who
gave us all the details of their plan.
Kyoji still refuses to talk.
He does, huh?
Speaking of,
we found out a little more about Shoichi.
Healthwise, he'd been sickly since childhood.
His father pretty much gave up on him, so he
decided early on to hand the hospital over to Kyoji.
Staying sharp, ma'am, locked and loaded.
Even so, the brothers seemed to be close growing up,
but then Shoichi got obsessed with MMORPGs, and
in 2022, he got trapped in "Sword Art Online."
After he got out,
Shoichi only spoke to Kyoji about it.
He bragged about how, in that world, he was
a real mass murderer and how he was feared.
In Kyoji's eyes, his big brother was a hero.
As for Shoichi, he's sticking with the story
that everything about the Death Gun concept,
including the murders, was just part of a game,
that his actions here,
like gathering intel on victims, prepping for the murders,
and committing them, were no different than in "SAO".
The dark side of VRMMOs,
that's what it is.
His reality got a lot less real.
Yeah. Good point.
And how are you handling yours?
I feel like I left a part of me back in "SAO",
so right now, there's less of
me here than there was before.
I don't know.
You don't know?
Do you wanna go back?
Seriously? How could you ask me that?
Um, wait a sec.
You're kind of contradicting
what you told me the other day.
What?
You said there's no such thing
as a virtual world, remember?
That, like, wherever you were, that's your reality.
Where I am right now, here,
this world is my reality.
And even if you told me this was a virtual
world, it would still be reality to me.
You see what I mean?
I guess.
Yeah, you're right.
I gotta hand it to you, Sinon.
What you said just now might be the only
good thing to come out of this nightmare.
Oh, put a sock in it.
Sorry, I'm with Kirito on this one.
Well, I told you pretty much all we've found out so far.
You have any questions before I go?
I do. Has there been any word on
what's gonna happen to Kyoji yet?
Based on his brother's confession and their behavior,
they'll most likely be sent to a medical detention center.
I doubt either one knows what reality is anymore.
No, I don't think that's true.
Hmm?
I don't know anything about Kyoji's brother.
I never met him.
But I've known Kyoji a long time, and,
well, I think his reality was "Gun Gale Online."
He had pretty much given up on this world.
There was nothing left for him other than "GGO",
so he made that his reality.
He'd spend hours in it grinding away,
boosting his XP, and trying to be the best.
I guess the stress got to be too much for him.
From playing a game?
I know you can lose track of time, but reality?
Sure. At some point, Kyoji just
swapped out one for the other,
his real life for his virtual one.
Okay, but why?
I don't know,
but I wish I did.
Kirito, why do you think he did it?
To get stronger.
You're right.
I guess I was the same way.
When it comes down to it, maybe
all us VRMMO players are the same.
All we want is to get stronger.
Mr. Kikuoka,
I'd like to go see him if that's all right.
There's so much I want to tell him,
like what we were just talking about
and other stuff I've been thinking, if it's okay.
Mm. You're a strong person to want to,
and I, for one, think it's a great idea.
He can't have visitors yet, but
when he can, I'll let you know.
Well, I have to get back to the office now.
Okay. Thanks for taking the time.
Yes, thank you for talking to us.
Don't even mention it.
You guys risked your lives,
and god knows how many you saved.
It's the least I could do.
Oh, by the way, Kirito,
Death Gun or Shoichi Shinkawa or Red‐Eyed Xaxa or whatever
you want to call him asked me to give you a message.
If you don't want to hear it,
say the word, and I'll tear it up.
I'll hear it.
You got it.
He wrote,
"if you think this is over, it's not.
You don't have what it takes to end this.
Sooner or later, you'll realize that.
It's showtime."
That's it.
Hey, uh, Sinon.
Hmm? What's up?
Are you free right now?
What do you mean, "free"?
Free for what?
So this is where you're taking me?
Yep. There's someone inside I want you to meet.
Well, it's about time.
You made us wait so darn long, I
went and had two slices of apple pie.
If I get fat, it's all your fault.
How's that my fault? Jeez.
Come on, Kirito.
Are you gonna introduce us or what?
Huh? Oh, right. Sorry.
This is Shino Asada, AKA Sinon,
"Gun Gale Online's" third super‐champ.
Oh, don't say that.
These are my friends from my time in "SAO",
Rika, AKA Liz, blacksmith and swindler.
Huh? What the hell'd you call me?
Hah!
And that's Asuna, the berserk healer,
real name Asuna Yuuki.
Uh, berserk?
Uh...
You wanna grab a seat and get something to drink?
That's what Ster... I mean Schterben means,
a term hospitals use for death.
What was he thinking giving his avatar a name like that?
If I were you, I wouldn't try to find some
deeper meaning in the name he gave his avatar.
A lot of times, it boils down to
whatever a player thinks sound cool.
Oh, that explains it.
This whole time, I thought you gave your
avatar your name 'cause you lacked imagination.
Zip it. Ahh.
I do so have imagination, lots of it.
Okay! Jeez.
Whatever.
So anyway, I'm super stoked you're here.
It's always cool to meet another girl VRMMO player.
You said it.
I hope we can be great friends, Asada.
Hmm.
Listen, Asada, Shino,
there's another reason for us
asking you to come here today.
What is it?
Sinon, I'm sorry to put you on the spot like this.
I, uh... I told Asuna and Liz about
what happened to you when you were younger.
I didn't have a choice. I needed their help.
Huh?
I'll explain.
We wanted to help you,
so we paid a visit to the town where you used to live.
How could you?
Why would you do that?
Wait, Sinon.
They found someone who wants to meet you.
I can't let you leave till you hear what they have to say.
It might hurt, and I'm sorry, but I can't
stand by if there's a chance what they say helps.
Who is this person?
What do they want to tell me?
Sorry. Do I know you?
Sachie Oosawa.
You're Shino Asada, aren't you?
I'd like to introduce you to my daughter.
Her name's Mizueh. She's four years old.
I don't know if you remember,
but I used to work at the post office.
I'm sorry.
This is really hard.
See, I...
I should have done this ages ago.
I'm so sorry it took this long.
I never apologized or thanked you for what you did.
I was pregnant with her the day
that man came in and tried to Rob us.
What you did, it wasn't just my life you saved.
You saved the life of my little girl, too.
Thank you so much.
If it weren't for you, she wouldn't be here.
I saved your daughter?
Sinon, time to let go.
You've been blaming yourself way too long,
beating yourself up over what happened.
I'm not saying you're wrong to do that, but...
It's just whatever guilt you feel about what you did,
you got a right to consider the lives you saved, too.
You got the right to think about
those people and forgive yourself.
That's it.
That's what I wanted you to know.
I made it for you.
Thank you for saving mommy
and for saving me.
We love you.
Next time: "Debriefing".