Asada!
Shino Asada!
All your favorites are in stock right now.
Move.
Go on. Quit draggin' your feet!
I need a favor.
We sorta went over‐time at Karaoke, and now
we don't have enough cash for the train home.
We're gonna need about ten.
We'll pay you back, though.
Ten thousand?
I don't have that much money on me.
Well, go withdraw it then.
No.
Huh?
You heard. I said no.
I'm not giving you guys any money.
You bitch.
We'll do this the hard way.
Get out of the way. I wanna go.
Bang.
Poor Asada.
Y'know my big brother?
Well, he's got a butt‐load of these model guns.
Wouldn't it be cool if I brought some to class?
I know you like guns,
especially pistols.
Uh‐oh. Someone's gonna hurl.
Remember when you blew chunks in class and fainted?
Oh, god, that stank like ass for days.
All you have to do is give us your
money, and we'll let you go home.
Don't ya wanna? I mean, you look like hell.
Officer!
A girl's getting mugged in the alley! Hurry!
Bitch!
Asada.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine, Shinkawa.
Thanks for that.
So I heard what happened the other day.
You went on quite the rampage.
Yeah, but for a strategy, it was a fail.
I mean, we started the op with
six and lost four by the end of it.
If that's the outcome of an ambush we set up,
it's not much of a win, y'know?
You were pretty rad, though.
Y'know that behemoth guy with the Minigun?
He was kind of a legend in the game, 'cause
he never bought it in a squad fight before.
Yeah?
I had no idea he was that good.
I never really saw his rankings in BOB.
His days were numbered.
I mean, no matter how powerful a Minigun is,
carrying five hundred rounds of a MMO
pushes you over the weight limit, so you can't run.
And since BOB's a solo encounter battle,
he was easy pickings for a sniper like you.
Still, with that gun, he's pretty much
invincible as long as he's with a good squad.
The Minigun should be banned.
If we're talking about banning weapons, don't
forget some people think my Hecate's a cheat, too.
As its owner, I have to admit
using it does have its own special problems.
Wish I had problems like that.
So what're your plans for the next BOB?
I'm definitely entering.
I did my homework and have most of the info
of the top twenty players from the last one,
and I've got my Hecate now.
With her in my hands, I'm sure I can ki...
I‐I mean crack the higher ranks.
If I can take out all my enemies
and prove I'm the strongest, I'll be free.
Man...
Asada, you're amazing.
Having that awesome gun is one thing,
but you were also smart enough to put your
points on strength stats so you could use it.
I'm the one who got you into GGO,
but I've been totally left behind.
That is so not true.
In the last qualifier,
you made it all the way to the semifinals, remember?
Eh. Whatever.
An AGI build only gets you so far in GGO.
A good gun helps, too.
I spent points on the wrong stat.
Don't get so down about that stuff.
Sign up for BOB, and see what happens.
Nah. No point.
I'd just die.
Oh. Hmm.
Hey, how're your studies coming along?
You still wanna be a doctor?
Yeah. It is the family business.
I promised my dad I'd go to med school,
so it's a done deal. Stuck with it now.
Well, what about cram school and the GED?
Are those going okay?
Oh, yeah. It's goin' great.
I'm maintaining the same rank I had when I was at school.
Stayin' sharp, ma'am. Locked and loaded.
Roger that.
The reason I asked, is 'cause
you're always online when I log on.
That's why I was a little worried.
If you're online that much, when do you study?
I do most of my studying during the day,
and I take lots of breaks, too.
You must be making tons of cash if
you're diving all the time like that.
I'm not making that much.
Solo hunting's impossible for AGI builds these days.
Oh. Well, you're doing great if you're
earning enough for the connection fee.
Uh‐oh, it's late.
Sorry. I have to get going now.
Oh. Okay. Hey, uh...
Are you still makin' dinner for yourself?
I'd love to try more of your cooking someday.
Huh? Oh, sure. Okay.
It's just I think I need to get better at it first.
Thanks for the tea.
And thanks... I mean, thank you for saving me.
You were pretty cool.
I wish I could always be there to protect you.
Hey, uh, if you want,
I can walk you home every day.
I mean, if you want.
Oh, no, no.
That's okay.
I'll be fine.
It's the only way I'll get stronger.
What a day.
I can do this.
I don't remember what dad looked like.
I remember hearing he died in a car accident, though,
sometime before I turned two.
After the accident, my mom and I left Tokyo.
We went to go live with her parents.
It was peaceful there for both of us.
Huh?
And then one day,
that peace was shattered.
Put the money in the bag, god damn it!
And don't hit the alarm, or else!
Mommy!
C'mon! Don't just stand there!
Start fillin' it up!
Let's go! Move it!
Okay, sure.
I told him not to! You heard me!
Let's go, bitch!
Fill it up, or you get it, too!
Gimme the money now, or I'm gonna kill her next!
I swear I'll do it!
You little...
Give it back, you brat! Let go!
Let go of my gun!
I look awful.
Somebody...
Anybody save me.
Wait! What?! Y‐You're kidding!
You're quitting ALO?!
N‐No! I'll just be gone for a couple of days.
I'll convert back after that.
But why?
Well, actually...
It's complicated.
There's this other virtual MMO that I need to check out.
"Need to," huh?
You've done this before and just used new accounts.
Why not for this one, too?
I mean, if you convert, your items will be reset.
Why would you want to do that?
Well, it's like a favor
for that guy from the government.
I guess if Mr. Kikuoka's asking you to, you can't say no.
I don't know what it is about that man,
but there's a part of me that
still has a hard time trusting him.
Yeah. I'm not too sure I can trust him, either.
Just get back as soon as you can.
This is our home,
and it's not the same without you.
Don't worry.
I'll be back in ALO before you know it.
I'll just dive into Gun Gale Online
for a couple days, see what's goin' on,
and that's that.
I'm ninety‐nine percent sure the Death Gun story's a hoax,
probably someone trolling.
You can't kill someone in the
real world from the virtual anymore.
I know that's impossible.
This is real power,
real strength!
Let your fear carve one name into your brains,
the name I share with this weapon,
Death Gun!
But there's still that one
percent chance it could be true.
That's why I'm here.
Hello. Anyone here?
Yep!
What's goin' on, Kirigaya?
Ms. Aki.
It's nice to see you again.
Whoa!
You finally got some meat on you.
You could use some filling out, though.
You sure you're eating right?
Yeah, I'm eating. I'm eating.
Wait a minute. What're you doing here?
Your friend in the suit and
glasses told me about your mission.
He said something about you going into a virtual
network and doing some reconnaissance or something.
I can't believe he'd ask you.
I mean, you've only been back for a year.
Anyway, he found out I was the
one who was in charge of your rehab,
so he asked me to keep an eye
on your monitors while you dive.
They took me off my normal shift and everything.
The head nurse wasn't happy, but what can she do about it?
If the government wants something, they're gonna get it.
Well, I guess you and me are back together again, huh?
Yeah. Thanks for being here.
Um, so it's just us today? No Kikuoka?
Mm‐hmm. He asked me to give you a message, though.
Email your reports to me at the usual address.
Your fee and expenses will be
paid when you finish the mission,
so please don't forget to send me an invoice.
PS: Just because you're alone with a pretty nurse,
you're still on the clock.
Try to keep those hormones of yours under control.
Uh, if it's okay,
I'd like to connect to the network now.
Yeah, sure. It's all set up.
Okay, hot stuff, strip!
Why?!
For the electrodes.
Oh, don't be shy.
I've seen all your goodies before.
Uh, actually, can I just take off my shirt?
Mm‐hmm.
There. You're good to go.
Well, here I go. Wish me luck.
I don't see this takin' me more than four or five hours.
You got it.
And don't you worry about your body while you're gone.
I'll keep a close eye on it.
Thanks. I feel better already.
Link start!
Yeah, I'm doing great.
I'm used to the school now,
and I've made some friends, too.
I'm fine, really.
I've only had a couple panic attacks. That's all.
Yeah, grandpa, I will.
Don't you catch any colds, either.
I'll come home for winter break.
Me, too. Bye.
Ever since that day,
whenever I see a gun, I freak out.
If I see a picture of one or see one on TV,
I'm guaranteed a panic attack.
I came to Tokyo for high school, thinking
if I got far enough away from home, it'd help,
but it didn't.
One day, Shinkawa told me about Gun Gale Online,
and I thought it could work as a kind of therapy for me.
And in a way, it worked.
As Sinon, when I'm holding a gun
or when someone's drawing down on me,
I can handle it.
I figure the stronger Sinon gets,
the stronger I'll get in the real world,
so I keep fighting with my Hecate Ⅱ,
hoping it'll help me kick this phobia.
Winning the next Bullet of Bullets will cure me.
I know it will.
It has to.
Link start.
Zxe‐D and Tarako haven't logged on for a while.
It's been, like, a month.
If anyone's got their contact info
in the real world, hook us up with it.
Dude, if no one's heard from 'em this long,
they're gone for good.
We know the date and time they
were shot by Death Gun, though,
so all we have to do is check if any
VRMMO players died around that time,
and we'll know what happened to 'em.
Yeah, but if they lived alone,
maybe no one's found their bodies yet.
We already asked the cops, but they're not talking.
We even sent emails to Zaskar about
'em, but all they sent back was the old,
"sorry, we never share our users' personal info" crap.
I hate to say it,
but the only way to be sure they were
killed is for one of us to sacrifice himself.
So tomorrow at 11:30 PM,
I'm gonna wait for Death Gun at the Glocken Central Bank,
and just so he knows it's me,
I'll have a red rose on my chest.
Shoot me, Death Gun! I dare you.
Ah, dude, you'll be a hero.
But you better post your real name
and address. Otherwise, what's the point?
Oh, do a public dive at an Internet cafe, man!
Do it!
Whatever.
Next time: "GGO".