So Death Gun was in Laughing Coffin,
And you guys fought before.
Kirito, I need to know something.
It's about the people you killed.
How did you get over what you did?
How are you not affected by it?
How are you so strong, you're not controlled by it?
I haven't gotten over it.
What?
Last night, I kept having nightmares
about the three guys I killed.
I hardly slept at all.
I saw their faces right before they vanished.
I heard their voices,
Their words.
I don't think I'm ever gonna forget 'em.
But then...
What am I supposed to do?
I... I can't...
It's okay.
I think that's probably how it should be.
I get it now.
There are things I shouldn't forget,
What it means to kill,
The significance of taking a life.
And once I accept it,
Maybe then I'll be able to find some closure.
That's how I see it.
Closure...
By accepting it?
Death Gun.
Hmm?
It's hard to believe that under
that cloak, there's a real‐live person.
Who just wants to kill.
Yeah.
And if I knew his handle in "SAO",
I'd be able to figure out his
name and address in the real world.
That's the reason why I logged into "GGO".
Oh.
Then maybe his reason for being here is
'cause he likes to PK Maybe he misses the rush
of doing it from "SAO" You think?
Nah, there's more to it than that.
He killed Zxe‐D and Tarako in
front of a bunch of witnesses.
It was the same with pale rider.
He always picks times when he's got the biggest audience.
And that sign of the cross he makes,
I bet he does it to freak out as many people as possible.
He wants you to believe he's got
the power to kill you from in the game,
But it's all a show.
If that's true, then how's he killing people?
It's not 'cause of brain damage from their headgear.
The authorities said that Zxe‐D
and Tarako died of heart failure.
Heart failure?
My god.
To be honest,
I have no idea how he killed 'em either.
But the thought of firing a gun in the
virtual world and stopping a player's heart,
There's no way that's possible.
Hang on a second.
Come to think of it...
What?
That was weird.
What was?
Back there in the ruins,
He had his handgun out for you,
but he switched to the rifle for me,
But he kills with the handgun.
He could have killed me with it, so why'd he switch?
Yeah. Good question.
Could it be that he didn't shoot me with it
'cause he couldn't shoot me with it?
The handgun,
can't use it, though.
The switch. The crossing himself thing.
Invisibility cloak.
Conditions, rules.
Here. I can't tell you how relieved
I am to hear you put it into words.
Knew it.
In‐game guns can't kill IRL.
Shooting someone from in here's not what does it.
It takes preparation.
Now you lost me.
The only way to make it look
like he's killing people in‐game.
Is by setting up for the murder in the real world first.
How would he set something like that up?
I mean, if you're right,
he'd have to get a player's
real‐life information to do it.
All that stuff's secure, though.
No. If someone's clever enough, they
can find out a player's address easy.
How?
The terminals at the governor's office.
You have to plug your real name
and address into 'em to compete.
It's an open space.
You don't have any privacy there.
No way. You saying he peeked over their shoulders
while they entered their info? That can't be it,
'cause you'd notice someone lurking next to you.
He could have used a scope or
some binoculars from across the room.
That's breaking etiquette.
He'd get his ass kicked out of the game for that.
Then how 'bout this?
Maybe Death Gun can, like, use his
cloak to turn invisible in town, too.
He'd be right there, and you wouldn't even know it.
But still, he can't do anything in the real world.
When he's logged in here, he's unconscious there.
Right.
Wait.
That's it. Yeah.
It's not just him.
Death Gun...
Has a partner!
Check it out.
One of them plays as the Death Gun avatar.
His job is to shoot the target.
At the same time, in the real world,
the second person in the target's apartment.
His job is take the player out.
Okay, but let's say they found out your address.
What about the other people living there?
And they'd need a key.
As far as Zxe‐D and Tarako go,
They lived alone,
And their apartments were in older buildings.
The e‐locks on their doors were probably first‐gen,
Not very secure.
Besides, they were both diving
in "GGO" During the break‐in,
so they were both unconscious and completely helpless.
They couldn't hear,
So the killer could take his time getting in.
But then you said the cause of death
for both was heart failure, right?
So how'd they stop someone's heart in a way
both the cops and the coroner couldn't figure out?
Maybe by injecting some kind of drug or something.
That's one way.
Okay, but someone should have found evidence of it,
A mark or something.
They didn't find the bodies for a while,
So they were pretty decomposed.
Besides, a hard‐core gamer can go
for days without eating or sleeping.
I doubt anyone would think it's weird if
someone died of a heart attack after that.
They're crazy.
Right?
I mean, why else would anyone do this?
Maybe, or maybe they do it
'cause red players are who they really are.
I mean, deep down, I think I'm really a swordsman.
When you put it that way, I can sort of understand.
There's times when I think I'm a real sniper, not a gamer.
Wait. Do you think the guy doing
the killing's a red player, too,
You know, like Death Gun?
Yeah. They were probably in Laughing Coffin together.
I'm still wondering how they coordinated the
killings between this world and the real one.
How are they so precise about it?
That's it.
That's what doing the sign of the cross is about.
It's not just for show.
It's also a great opportunity
to sneak a peek at his watch.
You're right.
Sinon...
Do you live alone?
Um, yeah.
But I'm sure I locked my door.
My building's got first‐gen
locks, but I've also got a chain.
I think I left the chain off tonight.
Oh, man.
Listen, you're not gonna like this.
When Death Gun was chasing us on that horse,
I wasn't the one he was shooting at.
And that could only mean they got their
next victim all set up and ready to go.
Okay.
Then who's next?
I got a feeling that right now in the real world,
Death Gun's partner's in your place.
He's watching the live stream,
Waiting for when you get shot by that gun.
It's just a hunch.
No.
No. No, not that.
Oh, god.
Calm down.
If you log out now, you'll be in danger.
Just calm down.
Go easy.
Until Death Gun shoots you,
The guy in your place isn't gonna do anything, okay?
That's the rule they set up for themselves.
But if you log out now and wake up with his partner there,
He'll kill you, so you have to calm down.
But... but...
I'm scared. I'm so scared.
Hmm?
Jeez, Chrysheight,
Took you long enough.
Sorry, guys. I booked it over here
as fast as I could from my save point.
If there were a speed limit in "ALO",
My license would have gotten suspended.
Huh?
What is going on?
I'd be happy to explain in detail, but
I should warn you it might take a while.
To tell the truth, I'm not 100% sure where to begin.
Oh, don't even.
Not to worry.
I know just where to start.
On November 9, in "Gun Gale Online,"
A player called Death Gun fired his
weapon at an avatar appearing on a monitor.
That same day in Nakano ward,
the player of that avatar mysteriously died.
Young lady, that was unbelievable.
Gathering all that information and connecting
it so quickly, you must be quite the researcher.
Have you ever thought about a career in the VR Section?
Whoa. You win.
I'm sorry. I'm not going to stonewall you, promise.
Just complimenting her, is all.
She's right, though. It's true.
Yo, Chrysheight or whatever,
I hear you're the one that hired
Kirito to dive into that game.
So let me get this straight. You got him to
convert over knowing a player got shot in‐game
And died IRL because of it?
Easy, Klein. I can explain.
That's not how the player died.
Then how?
It's not the Amusphere rig.
No matter what happens to you in‐game, it can't hurt you,
And it certainly can't stop a player's heart
when it's not even directly connected to it.
As a matter of fact, Kirito and I met last week to
talk about it and pretty much agreed it was impossible.
There's no way anyone can kill a person
in real life by shooting them in the game.
Okay, then, if what you say is true,
How come you had my brother dive into "GGO" For you, huh?
You had a hunch something was wrong.
Scratch that.
You know something's wrong.
That Death Gun guy's a part of it,
And I bet you sent my brother in to try to find him.
Chrysheight,
we figured it out.
Death Gun is an "SAO" Survivor just like us,
But unlike us, he was a red player who was
in a guild of killers called Laughing Coffin.
You sure he was with them?
Yes. None of us can remember his name, though.
Klein and I met him once.
When our group went to capture his.
Um, hey, Asuna, I get the feeling
Chrysheight knows more than he's letting on.
No offense, Chrysheight, but all we know is you
work for the government doing something with networks
and that you play "ALO".
As part of some kind of research you're doing on VRMMOs.
Only for the past year.
The job I had before was a little...
Different.
I used to be part of the task
force for the "SAO" incident.
But even though we were called a task force,
In the end, we were pretty ineffective.
Chrysheight, you're obviously well connected,
and with a little digging, you could find out
what the real‐life name and address of this Death Gun is.
Just make a list of the handles
of all the surviving Laughing Coffin members.
Then contact their ISPs,
Ask which one's playing "GGO" Now,
And trace their location.
No. Sorry, that's not possible.
The ISPs aren't going to give
out a player's real‐life info.
If all we have to go on are their handles.
Maybe if we ask the game's admins, they could help.
They might, but GGO's admins are in the US,
so it'll be a while before we got an answer.
I know my brother,
And right now, he's risking his life in that game,
Trying to find out who this person is.
When he came home last night,
he had this look on his face,
Like he'd seen a ghost.
He must have bumped into the
guy yesterday during the prelims.
I bet that's when he realized someone
from Laughing Coffin was in "GGO",
Someone who figured out how
to kill players for real again.
My brother went back to put an end to that nightmare,
to find out his name, and stop his PKing once and for all.
Darn it, Kirito.
You should have said something.
Why? Why do you always do this?
That damn idiot!
Why didn't he say anything?
I could be backing him up right now, all he had
to do was ask, and I would have converted over, too.
We all would have.
Don't you see? That's why he didn't tell us.
If he thought there was any
real danger in what he was doing,
there's no way he'd get us mixed up in it, too.
That's just how he is.
Yeah, you're right.
He always thinks of others before himself.
In fact, he's probably protecting someone right now,
and whoever that is, I bet it's
someone who doesn't like him much.
Okay, Chrysheight, where is Kirito diving from?
I know you know, so you better tell me now.
Mm...
That's confidential.
Eh, okay, okay. I'll tell you.
I set up the room myself, so he's safe.
Security's rock‐solid, and
the monitoring's top of the line.
I've got a trained professional
right by his side at all times,
and I guarantee that his body's in no danger whatsoever.
Where is he?!
A hospital.
It's in Ochanomizu in Chiyoda ward.
He's in Chiyoda?
Wait. Is that the same hospital
he was in during his rehabilitation?
Yes, that's the one.
I'm going over there. I want to see
him, and you can't do a thing about it.
Tell me you got a plan.
We're going to take out Death Gun.
Once we do,
His real world partner'll stand down.
Then he'll just leave your apartment.
Okay, but he's skilled,
Black Star or no Black Star.
You saw. He dodged Hecate's
bullet from just 100 meters away.
And besides, I can't hide in this cave forever, you know.
By now, the other players probably
figured out the two of us are in here.
We might as well be sitting ducks.
It's just a matter of time
before someone tosses a grenade in.
You're right.
We've been a team this whole time anyway, right?
Might as well finish it together.
Okay,
But there's still the risk he shoots you with that gun.
Oh, that thing.
It's just an old‐school single‐action sidearm.
He can fire it all he wants, but I got you there.
Just deflect the bullets with your sword.
Right, and I won't let a single one of 'em hit you.
I still don't feel good about you being out there, though.
I mean, Death Gun's dangerous, and
you shouldn't get too close to him.
Oh, come on.
Hang on. I'm totally cool with you fighting
with me, and I wouldn't have it any other way,
But, Sinon, you're a sniper, remember?
Isn't your specialty the long‐range attack?
Well, yeah. What about it?
Here's the plan.
On the next scan, I'm gonna
step outside so it picks me up.
That way, we'll get Death Gun to come to us.
He'll probably keep his distance and take cover.
Then he'll try to pick me off with his rifle.
When he shoots, we'll know where
he is, and then you take him out.
What do you think?
Are you cool with playing the decoy?
Mm‐hmm.
All right. We do it your way then.
Just be careful out there, 'cause
if he drops you with his first shot,
I'm gonna be pissed.
Heh. I'll keep that in mind.
Wait. I just remembered.
His rifle's got a silencer, and you
won't see the bullet line on the first shot.
Oh, I'll just predict the prediction,
You know, like a certain no‐good faker told...
Um, I think we should stop talking.
Uh...
Ugh. Oh, crap.
We should have been paying more attention.
What is it?
And will it kill us?
It's a live‐stream camera.
Usually they're only supposed to shadow.
Players on the battlefield.
I guess this one's in here now 'cause
there aren't many of us left out there.
Then do you...
Think it heard us?
Not a chance. For it to pick us up,
We'd have to be shouting at the top of our lungs.
Wave to the audience.
Unless you got someone back at home.
You don't want seeing this.
Uh, I, um...
Shouldn't you be worried who's watching?
I mean, since I sort of look like a girl,
they might, you know, think you're, you know.
I don't care. They can think what they want.
The guys in this game are dorks. If they think I'm gay,
at least they'll stop hitting on me every five seconds.
How much longer am I gonna have
to keep pretending to be a girl?
Oh, you poor baby.
You've been faking it like a champ since you
logged in. Another hour or two won't matter.
Thank god.
We better get ready.
We got two minutes before the next sat scan.
I'll set up here.
When you get outside, fire up your terminal,
and let me know when our boy's close.
Wait. Hold on.
Why? What's wrong?
It's too late to change the plan now.
No, I don't want to change anything.
It's something else.
I was just thinking about Death Gun's real handle here.
The only name you didn't recognize
who's still alive is Sterben.
Oh. Huh.
I guess that's him then.
I wonder why he gave himself that name, though.
If I get up close and personal,
I'll be sure to ask him for you.
Well, here goes nothing.
Be careful, okay?
Next time: "Bullet of a Phantom".