Kazuto!
Okay, what's with that goofy grin?
Well...
This morning, I just so happened
to see an interesting article.
And then I noticed that.
Oh.
Wow, what are the odds? Someone's got a similar handle.
Yeah, except this isn't similar.
It's exactly the same.
If you're gonna put it that way,
then, yeah, I guess.
Although that name's not really that unusual.
I mean, mine's an abbreviation.
Maybe the Kirito in GGO's name is Kiri...
Kirigamine. Yeah, Touguro Kirigamine or something.
Better eat up, or it's gonna get cold.
Who is he?
He's gotta be one of the survivors from "SAO".
And that's not all.
We must have fought at some point,
and I bet we were trying to kill each other.
Kazuto.
You're making that scary face again.
I hope it's not scarier than usual.
Look, I already know everything.
I know you converted Kirito from "ALO" to "GGO",
so just drop the act already, okay?
Come on.
Did you honestly think I wouldn't notice
when you suddenly vanished from my friend list?
I didn't think you checked that thing every five minutes.
I don't. I just knew.
Last night, I got this weird feeling and checked my list.
When I saw you weren't on it,
I headed over to your room and
was about to bust the door down.
I didn't, 'cause I knew it'd
piss you off something fierce.
I also knew you'd never quit "ALO" Without telling me.
I figured you must have a good reason, so I
called Asuna up to see if she knew anything.
You did?
Huh.
Sorry.
I hope I'm not calling you too late.
It's okay. I wasn't sleeping.
Besides, I...
Never mind.
Honestly. You started to say
something, so just go ahead and say it.
I guess...
I guess I was just thinking about how...
I'd like to hear your voice.
That wasn't so hard.
What's wrong?
Nothing's wrong. Long day.
Did something happen in the game you converted over to?
N‐Nothing happened.
It's just...
If the new job's overloading you, I could help.
Thanks for offering.
I got it, though.
Besides, if you converted over, you would get lonely.
Are you sure you're all right?
Yeah. I'll be back before you know it.
If you need me, call, okay?
Will do.
Good night.
I can't drag Asuna into this.
That guy's sure to show up in BOB's main tournament.
I have to end this.
This is my problem, not hers.
Kazuto.
Know what Asuna told me?
She said not to worry,
'cause once you tore up "GGO", you'd be back.
She didn't say it,
but I knew she was really worried about you.
That makes two of us.
Last night, you got home so
late, and when I saw your face,
I wanted to say something,
'cause you looked all freaked out.
I did? Sorry.
I hope you're not doing anything crazy,
because if you are,
I couldn't bear it if something happened to you.
I'm gonna be fine. I promise.
Tonight's the last night of GGO's
tourney, and after that, I'll be back
to "ALO" and here.
I'll be back, no matter what, so don't worry, okay?
'Kay.
Oh, I almost forgot.
What?
When I was talking to Asuna,
she just so happened to tell me that you're
gonna get a huge check from this new gig.
That's right, and when I get back,
I'll treat you to something cool.
Seriously? In that case,
there's this awesome new
nanocarbon shinai I've had my eye on.
Oh. Okay.
Sure. You got it.
That dumb‐ass.
He pisses me off.
I'm so mad, I could kill him.
Take it easy, Asada.
I know you're upset,
but it's weird to see you this worked up.
You saw him.
He's obnoxious, he's cocky, and he's a dirty liar.
He thinks he's such a big shot fighting
with a sword in "GGO" of all places.
He tricked me into thinking he was a
girl and had me take him to the gun market.
I even helped him pick out his gear.
He thinks I'm an idiot.
Oh, man!
Really pisses me off.
What's that look for?
Nothing. I mean, it's just that,
like, you're acting kind of strange.
I don't think you've ever talked
this much about someone else before.
You're kidding. Really?
Yeah. I mean, you don't usually let people get to you,
you know, like this.
I get like this when people push my buttons.
Yeah, I guess you do.
I know.
How 'bout we find a field in the game and ambush him?
Huh?
Yeah. I can lure him out, and then you can snipe him.
Although, if you want to get him back,
you probably want to take him head‐on.
Either way, I know I can find a couple
machine gunners to back you up if you want.
Thank you, but mm‐mm.
I had something else in mind.
It's like, yeah, he pisses me off,
but when he fights, at least he seems honorable about it.
Unless I beat him fair and square, it won't mean anything.
And in today's final, I'm gonna blow a hole through
that dumb avatar of his if it's the last thing I do.
Would you mind surrendering, then?
I'm not a big fan of slashing at girls.
Just you wait.
I swear I'm gonna pay you back
double for what you did to me.
What? What's wrong?
Nothing. It's just that...
You see what you're doing?
Huh?
Wow. I didn't even notice.
I guess it didn't bother me, 'cause I was so mad.
Oh.
Asada...
W‐Wait. What are you doing?
What's the matter?
I'm worried about you. That's what.
You're not acting like your usual self today.
Oh.
W‐What do you mean? How do I usually act?
As long as I've known you,
you've been cool, calm, and levelheaded.
Nothing gets to you.
You've got the same problems at school as me,
but you didn't run away like I did.
You're, like, really strong.
But I‐I'm not strong at all.
You know that.
I get freaked out whenever I see a gun.
But Sinon doesn't.
She's got that amazing rifle and knows how to use it.
If you ask me, that's who you really are,
and I know, one day,
you'll be like that in real life, too.
That's why when you go ballistic over that guy,
I start to worry.
When I see you lose it like that,
I want to help you.
I'd do anything to help you!
I remember...
I used to be normal once.
I laughed and cried just like anyone else.
I didn't become who I am now because I wanted to.
Asada.
I'm sorry.
I really appreciate you wanting to help me,
especially since you're the only one in the city
who really understands what I'm going through.
But I...
I'm just not ready to be anyone's girlfriend yet.
Besides, I can't really fix what's
bothering me unless I do it on my own.
I see.
Until then,
do you think you could wait for me?
Thank you.
With that name
and your sword skills,
are you the Real Deal or what?
Are you Kirito?
Are you Kirito?!
What's the matter, kiddo?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
Oh. N‐No.
It's nothing.
You got a super‐hot nurse sitting here, offering
free counseling, and you're gonna pass it up?
Come on. Tell me what's bothering you.
Well, since you put it that way,
I guess I don't really have a choice, do I?
Um...
Before you came to the rehab unit,
you were in trauma, right?
That I was.
I've got a personal question,
and if you don't want to answer, I totally understand.
Of all the patients you've cared for,
can you remember the ones who died?
Let's see.
I guess if I think about it,
I can recall their faces and names,
even patients I only spent an hour or so with in the OR.
Mm‐hmm. I remember.
Do you ever wish you could just forget about those people?
Hmm. That's a tough one.
Not sure if this is an answer, but it's the best I got.
I guess I think if something's meant to be forgotten,
a person'll end up forgetting it
without even thinking they want to.
That said,
the more a person wishes they could forget something,
the stronger the memory becomes,
till they can't stop thinking about it.
And if that's the case,
then maybe subconsciously, whatever the memory is,
it's something that shouldn't be forgotten.
Then if I forgot,
I must be a monster.
When I was stuck in "SAO,"
I took out...
no, I killed three people.
They were all red players,
so murder was their business,
and I could have overpowered
them instead of killing them, but...
I went ahead and killed them anyway.
I did it out of rage, hatred, revenge.
And over the past year,
I've totally forgotten all about those people.
Even as I sit here talking about it,
I can't remember what two of 'em
looked like or what their names were.
How's that possible?
If I can forget people I killed,
what's that say about me as a person?
I'm sorry, Kirigaya.
I guess I'm not the awesome counselor I thought I was.
I wish I could take away the burden you're carrying
or at least help share the load of it.
What do I know?
I've never even played "Sword Art Online."
When you say you killed someone,
I don't even know what that means,
but there's one thing I know.
When all's said and done,
the reason you did what you did
was to save someone else, wasn't it?
In the medical field,
sometimes we have to choose who to save.
It doesn't make the decision
to let someone die any easier,
but still, in a life‐or‐death situation,
everyone's got the right to
consider the people they can save
over those they can't,
even you.
Just think about the lives of all the people you saved,
and you'll make peace with your decision.
I don't know.
I want to believe you, but...
I can't. I killed people.
I killed 'em, and I can't even remember who they were!
Don't you get it?
It's like I don't even care that they're dead.
I don't deserve to find any peace!
If you didn't care about what you
did, you wouldn't be suffering like this.
Deep down, you remember.
And when the time's right,
it'll all come back to you.
When it does... and it will...
just make sure you remember
all the people who are alive today
because you were there to protect them.
If you need me, call, okay?
Um...
Thank you,
you know, for the pep talk.
Sure. Glad I could help.
I don't think anything'll happen till after 8:00.
I should be out by 10:00 at the latest.
Well, here I go.
Okeydoke.
Bon voyage, you super stud, you.
Link start.
Asada.
Okay.
I'm gonna fight hard,
and I will beat him.
Link start.
Incoming!
Oh, my gosh!
Klein, are you okay?
Come on, guys.
What are you waiting for, an invitation?
He's being extra manly today.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Hang on, Klein. We're coming.
Take your time, ladies.
Oh, crap!
Poison gas!
Hold your breath!
Asuna!
Hey, Asuna...
Need a hand here.
Alfheim to Asuna!
Soo filla hail oustroo.
I'm sorry, guys.
I didn't mean to space out like that.
Nah, it's all good.
No harm, no foul, right?
Yeah. Today's your boy's big day.
That's right, Kirito's tournament.
It's gonna start soon.
I don't know about you guys,
but I say we quit early
and get over to our room to watch it.
I say we use the cash we scored
today to buy beer and snacks.
Do you honestly think we're gonna
let you blow all our money on food?
Don't you worry, mommy.
Daddy's gonna win today. You'll see.
Sure he will.
No matter where he goes,
Kirito knows how to handle himself.
Hey, guys, we don't want to miss the first match.
So let's start heading over to Yggdrasil city.
Okay.
Huh?
Come on, folks. Place your bets.
Sinon!
Hey, Spiegel.
It's almost time.
I believe in you.
I know you're gonna win this thing.
Thanks.
So what are you gonna do?
Well, I thought I'd find a bar somewhere
and watch the feed from there.
Cool. I'll track you down after
this, and we can toast my victory
or cry in our beers.
Sinon...
I mean Asada...
Yeah? What's up?
I was wondering if you meant what you said earlier.
What did I say?
You asked me to wait for you, remember?
After you won this thing and conquered your fears, we...
then maybe we could go out and stuff.
What the...
you're bringing this up now?
It's just that...
I care about you so much, Asada.
Don't do this now.
I have to focus on the tournament.
I'm sorry, but I don't have a chance of
winning unless I put everything I've got into it.
Right.
I understand.
Even so, I believe in you,
and I'll wait till you're ready.
Okay.
Well, uh, I better go get ready now.
See ya.
I'll be rooting for you.
Good luck.
Whoa.
I won't lose today.
I won't either.
Next time: "Bullet of Bullets".