Hey, guys!
This is miss Asuna.
Miss Asuna, this is my guild, the Sleeping Knights!
My name's Jun.
What's up? How's it going?
H‐Hi, miss Asuna.
I‐I'm talken.
It's nice to meet you...
Ah!
You really need to get a grip
on those nerves, tal, seriously.
Every time you meet a girl,
you turn into a blubbering mess.
Anyway, my name's Nori.
Glad to meet ya.
My name is Siune.
It's wonderful to meet you,
and thank you so much for coming today.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name's Tecchi.
And...
I'm Yuuki, the leader of this guild, kinda, sorta.
Miss Asuna, don't laugh,
but see, we wanna be the only
guild to beat the boss on this floor,
and we want you to help us!
Huh?
Huh?!
That's very ambitious,
but a boss raid usually takes at least forty‐nine players.
That's seven parties with seven players apiece,
so no matter how skilled you are, with
just seven players, that's kind of...
well, to be perfectly honest, it's unrealistic.
Yeah, it sorta is, isn't it?
We tried taking on the bosses on
floor twenty‐five and six the same way.
Huh?! J‐Just you six?
Yup.
And if you ask me, we put up a pretty good fight, too,
but both times, this huge guild swooped in and
beat 'em before we could figure out our next move.
Why would you even risk it?
That's a story.
It goes back to when we met
in another game's net community.
We hit it off right away, and
we've been friends ever since.
But we only have until next spring to go
on quests together. Since our time's limited,
we wanted to make the most of it.
You see, come spring, we'll all be busy with other things,
so we decided that before we disbanded the guild,
we had to do something so amazing, so
unbelievable we'd remember it forever.
Mm‐hmm.
So that's why you want to do this boss raid.
Exactly! If we defeat a boss together, our names
will be inscribed on the monument of swordsmen,
you know, the one in the town of
beginnings, in the black iron palace.
I know it sounds silly
and maybe even a little vain,
but we really want to get our
names up on that wall, no matter what.
But getting them on there's the hard part.
Hmm?
If a boss is defeated by a party,
then all of its members will get
their names inscribed on the monument,
but if it's beaten by multiple parties working in tandem,
only the names of the party leaders get inscribed.
Oh.
That's the catch.
If we want the names of everyone in
the Sleeping Knights up on that wall,
we have to beat the boss together, just us, no one else,
so we talked it over and came up with a plan.
A party can have up to seven players Max,
therefore we decided to find someone as strong or
even stronger than our most powerful player, Yuuki,
and hope whoever we found accepted our invitation.
I get it. That's why you were dueling.
Well? What do you think about joining up with us?
We can't pay you very much, but
you're welcome to what we have.
Uh, oh, no, that's okay!
Boss raids cost a fortune as it is,
so you should use your money for that.
I'd feel horrible taking your money, really.
If you want, you could give me
whatever the boss drops, and I'll be fine.
Really?! Then you'll join our party?
Huh.
This is nothing like how the old Aincrad was,
and yet here I am thinking about
safety margins and the odds of winning,
having safe fights and certain victories.
There's more fun to games than that.
I bet Yuuki and her friends already know this
better than I do.
Okay, let's see how far we can go.
Yes! Awesome.
In the end, it's not about winning or losing.
It's having fu...
Thanks a bunch, miss Asuna!
Please,
I‐I'd prefer it if you just called me Asuna.
Then you can call me Yuuki.
That reminds me, Ms. Yuuki... sorry, Yuuki...
The duel was all about testing players, right?
Yup. Pretty much.
Then you must've gone up against a
ton of strong players before I showed up.
Do you remember ever fighting
a spriggan, dressed in black?
He would've been using a one‐handed sword.
Huh.
You know what? I do.
Man, he was pretty tough.
Then why didn't you ask him to help you out?
I don't know. He just wasn't right.
Well, why not?
He found out my secret.
I can't have that.
Okay, so for tomorrow,
how 'bout we meet back here at 1:00?
You got it! You got it!
Roger that. What they said.
And let's have fun.
Right!
Wh...
mom? What are you doing?!
Last month, when you were late for dinner,
I told you it better not happen again.
And here we are.
You're late because of that game,
so now you lose your privileges.
I just lost track of time.
That's my fault, and I'm sorry.
But you didn't have to go and
pull the plug on me like that.
You could've shaken me or even yelled in my ear.
I would've gotten an alert in‐game,
and then I could've logged out...
I tried that approach before.
It took you five minutes to snap out of it, remember?
Well, yeah.
I had to say good‐bye to everyone before I log...
Oh, don't give me that.
What you do in some stupid
virtual game does not take priority
over your commitments in the real world, ever.
I'm sorry.
I'll be more careful next time.
This will be your last warning.
If you break your word to me because of that thing again,
I'm confiscating it.
I have no idea what's going on in that head of yours.
You lost two years of your life
because of that... that infernal machine.
You could've died.
How can you even stand to look at it?
This isn't the Nervegear, mother.
It's dinnertime.
Get changed, and come downstairs.
I'm not hungry.
As you wish.
Hmm.
Sounds like a good lineup, right?
Huh? Asuna.
Uh, s‐so Yuuki, Jun, and Tecchi are up front.
Then talken and Nori are midrange,
and Siune, you're the backup? Right.
Then I guess, if you're covered,
maybe I should hang back as the rearguard.
Yeah, sorry. I feel bad you're not up
front when you're so good with a sword.
Oh, I don't mind at all.
I'm afraid I'm not much good as a tank.
And anyway, I'm curious to see whether
Jun and Tecchi can survive a proper beatdown.
Don't worry about us!
We can handle it.
I guess we'll see.
I hope.
All right, ready to go take a peek at that boss room?
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
What a team.
I wonder if they really need me after all.
I can't believe how quickly you
guys are clearing the labyrinth.
You're an amazing group of players.
It's the boss room! Come on!
Yuuki, hold it!
Eck, kaa‐rah, phim, fisckle,
bryotah, ryu‐gah, gardol.
Look!
W‐W‐Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hang on!
Hang on! We're not here to fight you!
Then lower your weapons now!
Get rid of it.
Keep your eye on them, and if
they make a move for their weapons,
hit 'em with an aqua bind spell.
You got it.
This is our first‐ever PVP in "ALO".
It's kind of thrilling.
If you're not PKers, then why were you hiding from us?
We were waiting for someone.
We were hiding, 'cause we didn't wanna get hit by a
mob before our friends got here. You know how it is.
All right, then.
We're here to take on the boss,
so if you're not ready to enter yet,
we'd like to take a crack at it first.
N‐No, that's cool.
We'll just hang here,
you know, till our buddies show up.
Oh, and, uh, watch your backs in there.
Good luck.
Oath, shaal, oh‐bis, glone, lopt!
Don't give those dudes a second thought.
Come on. Let's do this.
Hmm. Don't worry.
Let's just stick to the plan and have a look inside, okay?
Okay.
Instead of just scoping it out,
let's bust in there and trash the
boss. If you want to try, go for it.
Just make sure not to use any of your
expensive potions and stuff to recover.
Siune and I will support you with healing spells,
so fight hard, but try not to get too far in the red.
Ha! Right on, coach! Uhh!
Listen up.
If you die, don't respawn right away.
Just hang out, and study the boss' attack patterns.
Then let's meet back at the lombard save
point and talk about what we learned, okay?
Roger that!
Let's get him!
Right!
Jeez! We got our butts kicked!
What kinda attack was that?
That's gotta be against the rules!
That boss sure knows how to defend itself.
You think that's a random move,
using his arms to block?
And we fought so hard, too.
Hey! What's wrong?!
Hmm? Hmm?
Come here, you guys. Gather round.
Eh? Eh?
I know you're tired, but we need to talk.
Remember those three guys standing by the boss room?
Sure. Why?
They were scouts from a guild
that specializes in boss raids.
If another guild tries to hit that boss
room, their job is to sit back and watch.
The bosses you tried to raid on the
previous floor and the one before that,
I have a feeling they were there, too.
I had no idea they were even there.
They didn't get in our way or try to stop us, so
they're definitely spies. All they want is intel.
And when a small guild like the Sleeping
Knights comes along to take on a boss,
we're helping them figure out all
its attack patterns and weaknesses.
Wait a sec.
The door shut behind us when we were
inside, and they definitely didn't follow us,
so if they can't see us fighting the boss,
how are they gonna gather any intel on it?
Actually, they could see us fight.
Towards the end there, I looked over, and
I saw a tiny gray lizard near Jun's feet.
That's when I realized I let my guard down too soon.
It's a dark spell called peeping.
It binds a familiar to a player,
and the caster sees what it sees.
So what you're saying is after we got hammered
by the bosses on floors twenty‐five and six,
that other guild swooping in and beating 'em,
that wasn't a coincidence?
No, I'm afraid it wasn't.
You probably fought so hard, the
boss used every move it had against you,
and they saw it all.
That's how they beat the bosses so quickly.
They used us again.
Now they know everything about this boss, too.
They're probably in there taking it down.
Those dicks.
Damn it.
Easy, guys.
Don't count us out just yet.
But what can we do about it now?
Simple. It's 2:30 P.M. in the real world.
At this time of day and on such short notice,
it'll be hard to find enough people for a raid party.
By my estimate, it should take them at least an hour.
That's plenty of time for us.
So here's the deal. After this,
if we can get back to that room
in thirty minutes, we can take it.
Okay?
Yeah!
Last one there's a rotten egg!
Hey! Wait for us!
Slowpoke!
Crap! We're too late.
Don't worry.
They won't advance with only twenty players.
We should have enough time to give it
one more try before the rest show up.
You think?
Excuse me! Hm?
We'd like to try the boss before you do.
Could you guys let us by?
Sorry, doll‐face.
The boss room's off‐limits for now.
Wait. Off‐limits? What's that supposed to mean?
It means, in a couple minutes, the
rest of the guild's gonna roll up here.
We're just holding the room till they do.
If you want, you can wait over there.
And how long do you expect us to wait?
Um...
Another hour or so.
But we don't have that kind of time!
If you were going in right now,
well, that's a different story,
but you're not, so let us go in first.
Look, I don't make the rules.
I'm just a grunt here,
following orders like everyone else, okay?
You got a complaint,
go to the guild headquarters, and talk to them.
It's over in ygg city, so get...
Are you kidding? That's far away!
It'd take us at least an hour to get there!
Hey, big guy.
Hmm?
Just trying to figure things out here.
So no matter how nice we ask,
you're not gonna let us get by you.
Is that what you're saying?
Yeah, that's it.
That's pretty much what I'm saying.
Okay. If that's what you're saying...
You wanna fight?
Huh?
But, Yuuki, are you sure?
Asuna, sometimes you gotta fight to get your point across,
you know, like how dead serious you are about something.
Just saying.
Yup, that's pretty much how it is!
You guys.
These folks know exactly what I'm talking about.
They look like the serious types.
We could chop away all day, and they'd
defend this room to the last player.
Right, big guy?
Uh...
W‐We got orders to...
Come on, draw your sword.
Y‐You little punk.
I'm gonna make you pay for that.
Sometimes you gotta fight to get your point across.
Yeah...
She's right.
Hey, guys!
I should've dealt with this when I had the chance.
Sorry, Asuna.
My big mouth got you into this mess.
But it was totally worth it.
Know why? 'Cause just now,
I saw the best smile I've ever seen on you!
In that case,
I'll start pulling my weight.
We might not take down this boss,
but the next one,
I promise that one's ours!
Eh?
Heh. Some folks just don't know when to quit.
Sorry, guys.
Stand down.
You're not getting past me.
Next time: "The Monument of Swordsmen".