No, see, the way it's set now, the gyro's too sensitive.
If you want to prioritize the visual tracking,
you gotta give yourself a little
more room in these parameters.
Okay, but won't it lag like
crazy if she makes any sudden moves?
I guess you'll just have to trust that the
learning program and the optimizer can deal with it.
How much longer, guys?
Our lunch break's almost over.
Let's just save this as the
default setting and hope it works.
Hey, uh, Yuuki, can you hear okay?
Yup! I hear you loud and clear.
Good.
All right, I'm firing up the
lens now, so it might get bright.
Let me know when you can see
perfect, and I'll lock that setting in.
Fire away!
Hold it.
Okay, you're ready to go.
Last thing, I installed
stabilizers, but they're kinda janky.
Try not to make any sudden moves, 'Kay?
Thanks, Kirito!
Wow. Your school's ginormous.
I know, right?
I'm sorry I couldn't show you around first,
but the lunch break's almost
over, and we don't want to be late.
Nah, that's okay.
I'm just excited to check out your class.
Sweet. Then let's head to the faculty
room and introduce you to my teacher!
What's wrong?
It's the one part of school I don't miss,
going to the faculty room.
Heh. Don't worry.
The teachers here aren't your typical teachers.
They're cool.
Excuse me!
M‐me, too!
I just wanted to make sure it was still all right.
Sure. I'm fine with it.
And what's the name of the
student who'll be joining us today?
Oh, um, Yuuki, Yuuki Konno, sir.
Uh, okay.
Ms. Konno, you're welcome in my class anytime you want.
Although, we start Akutagawa's "a lorry" today.
Unless you stick with it to
the end, you won't get the point.
Yes, sir. Thank you very much.
Mm. Heh heh.
See you in class.
Hm? Uh...
Heh.
What's that, Ms. Yuuki?
Hey, how'd you know my name?
No, she was using my last name there.
Oh, right. Duh.
Guys, meet Yuuki Konno.
She's in the hospital right now and can't leave her room,
so instead, she'll be attending our class like this.
Nice to meet you!
I can only hang out for a little while, though.
Cool.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, there. My name's Kota.
Oh, hi. Hey. Nice to meet you, too.
Please stand.
Bow. Be seated.
All right then, class.
Please open your textbooks to page ninety‐seven.
We'll be reading "a lorry" by Ryunosuke Akutagawa.
Let's see. Who'll read it for us?
Yuuki Konno, would you do the honors?
Huh? Me?
Uh...
Problem?
No, sir. I can do it.
Yuuki, are you up for this?
I might not look it, but I have read before.
"When Ryohei was eight years old,
construction on the light railway
between Odawara and Atami began.
Every day, he would head to the
outskirts of town to watch the progress.
It wasn't the construction of
it that fascinated him so much.
It was the sight of the lorries
transporting the soil which drew him.
There were two laborers aboard the lorry
standing behind the soil they'd just loaded.
Since the lorry was headed down the mountain,
it didn't need anyone to push it.
So as the chassis swung
and the sleeves of the laborers' coats flapped
and the narrow rails bent under the strain,
Ryohei would gaze longingly at these sights
and wish he could be a laborer, too,
or at the very least,
be able to ride on it with them, if only once.
I loved listening to you read, Yuuki.
Hey, have you had a chance to tour the school?
If not, we could show you around.
T‐Take it easy, guys!
Hey, wanna go to a soccer match?
Thanks, guys! You're the best!
Now that was fun.
I know, right?
Thanks for making today happen, Asuna.
Really, I had a blast.
I'm never gonna forget today ever.
Well, of course you won't.
The teacher said you could come back again if you want.
Oh, modern Japanese is third period tomorrow.
You don't want to miss that.
Yeah.
'Kay, what's next?
Is there anything else you want to do or see?
Oh. Um...
I guess there is one place I'd like to go.
Where?
It's so pretty here, huh?
Just look at that sky.
Yeah.
Hey, are your folks cool with you staying out so late?
You've been hauling me around all day.
Don't you worry about it.
I sent them a text, and it's fine.
Well? Where do you want to go next, Yuuki?
Go left.
Hey, are we in Tsukimidai yet?
Yeah.
Next corner, there's a white house.
Can you stop there?
Yuuki, this is your house, huh?
Mm‐hmm.
I never thought I'd get the chance to see it again.
Thanks for bringing me out here and for everything.
Do you want to go inside?
Nah. This was enough.
Come on. Let's head back before your folks get worried.
No, it's okay. We can stay a little longer.
Me and my family,
we only got to live here a little over a year,
and the weird thing is I can remember every day so clear.
My sister and me used to play in the yard,
running around and around. We had barbecues,
and we even built these bookshelves with our dad.
Good times.
Lucky you.
Yeah. They're gonna tear it all down, though.
Really? Why?
My aunt wants to either put a convenience store here
or maybe sell it.
No way.
That's why I wanted to come here,
so I could see it one more time.
Well, I know how you can save it.
How?
You're fifteen now, aren't you?
When you turn sixteen,
find someone you love, and marry 'em!
That way, you'll have someone around who'll
keep this house from ever being torn down.
You got the craziest ideas!
I don't think there's anyone I wanna marry, though.
Oh, yeah? But you and jun make a cute couple.
God, no! That guy's so immature.
Let's see. Who should I marry?
Oh, I know!
You!
Huh?
The only thing is, if you marry me,
you'll have to be the wife.
I mean, the other way around,
my name'd be Yuuki Yuuki, and that'd be weird.
I can't imagine what my mom would say.
I know. I'm kidding.
'Sides, you already got someone lined up.
Oh, well, yeah. I guess.
Still, you should be careful.
I get the feeling he's not
living in the real world, either.
Not like me, but you know.
I can't thank you enough, Asuna.
Just to see my old house again,
you don't know how happy that makes me.
Back when we lived here,
I remember we'd go to church to pray and stuff,
and mom used to always say this to me and my sister,
"god would never put us through all this suffering
if he didn't think we could bear it."
It didn't make me feel any better, though.
Instead of quoting the Bible, what I really wanted
was for mom to talk to us like... well, like a mom.
But you know, after seeing our old house again,
I think I get it now.
The words didn't matter.
It was the feeling behind those words.
She was praying for me so I
wouldn't feel sorry for myself,
so I could be strong 'til the end,
and now I finally get it.
I'm the same.
See, I‐I haven't understood my mom, either.
I can't hear what she's really trying to tell me.
She can't seem to hear me.
Remember what you told me, that sometimes
you have to fight to get your point across?
How can I get to be strong like you?
Me?
Heh. I'm not strong. No way.
Oh, yes, you are!
You're not like me.
When you stand up to someone, you
don't flinch or let them intimidate you.
Nothing seems to scare you at all.
It's like second nature for you.
Mm, yeah, I don't know.
When I was living in the real world or...
you know what I mean...
most of the time, I was faking it.
Huh?
It's like I thought I had to act cheerful,
'cause I didn't wanna make my mom and dad feel sad for me.
Yuuki.
You wanna know what I think in the end?
So what if I'm just acting?
If I get to spend more time smiling,
even if it's fake, what's the big deal? Am I right?
I mean, it's not like I got a whole lot of time left,
and it'd be a shame to waste whatever
I do got by moping around all the time,
so now I say exactly what I feel to everyone,
and if they got a problem with that, who cares?
At least I spoke my mind
and maybe even got a little closer to 'em.
You're right.
That's the reason we're here today,
why we're so close after only a few days.
It's all 'cause of you.
Nope, that wasn't 'cause of me.
Huh?
It's 'cause even after I ran away from you,
you tracked me down.
Look, how 'bout you try talking
to your mom like you did to me?
If you try telling her how you feel,
maybe you'll get through to her.
Don't worry. You can do it.
You're way stronger than me, honest!
Yuuki.
You hit me with everything you had.
That's how I knew I could trust you with everything I had.
In the end, it worked out for both of us, didn't it?
Yes, it did.
Thank you so much, Yuuki.
If you try telling her how you feel,
maybe you'll get through to her.
Don't worry. I know you can do it.
Come in.
You're late again.
I'm sorry.
Well, if you're hungry,
you'll have to make do with whatever's in the fridge.
Oh, and don't forget, the deadline for
your transfer application is due tomorrow.
Make sure it's filled out by morning.
Actually, about that...
Hm?
We need to talk, mother.
Well, what is it?
I can't really explain it here.
Okay, then. Where shall we go?
The virtual world.
It'll only be for a little while,
and you're going to have to use this.
Don't be ridiculous!
If you can't tell me what this
is about like a normal person,
I don't want to hear it.
But you don't understand.
It's the only way I can explain!
It's just five minutes!
Mom, please!
There's no other way to tell you what
I'm thinking and how I'm feeling, honest!
I can't tell you any of that here!
Just this once.
Mom, all I want is for you to see my world!
Five minutes.
But no matter what you say,
I have no intention of allowing you to
attend that school again next year, understood?
Also once you're done, you will fill out that application.
Okay.
So how do I use that thing?
Just sit back and relax. Once I turn it on,
it'll automatically connect you
to my sub‐account in the game.
After you're in, wait for me.
I'm turning it on now.
Link start.
This is so bizarre.
Seeing a strange face mimic what I do is unsettling.
And this body, it's so light.
Oh, that's normal.
That particular avatar's weight
setting is about ninety pounds or so.
Feels lighter than your real body, huh?
That is so rude!
I do not appreciate what you're implying.
That's interesting.
Your face here looks just like your real one.
Well, yes.
Actually, I take it back. Your
real face is puffier than this one.
Oh, now who's being rude?
I look the same here as I do there.
Well, I'm here. Now what?
You don't have much time left.
Follow me, mom.
You see? It looks just like it.
I have no idea what you mean.
All I see is some old cedar gro...
Doesn't it bring back memories
of the house that grandma and grandpa had?
I really loved their place in Miyagi.
It was magical.
Remember that obon holiday when I was twelve?
You, dad, and Koichiro went to
the Yuuki family compound in Kyoto,
and I went to Miyagi by myself.
I remember.
When I got there,
I apologized to them that you couldn't be with us.
I felt bad you couldn't visit our ancestors' graves.
I wanted to, but that year,
the Yuukis were having an important memorial service.
No, mom, I'm not blaming you or anything.
In fact, you know what grandpa said?
He said not to fuss,
because he and grandma were so proud of you.
You left this village, went to university,
became a scholar, and got your work published.
It made him so happy to see you
make a name for yourself in the world.
And then he told me something I'll never forget,
that someday you might get tired from all
the hard work you do and need a break from it,
and if that day ever came,
he said he wanted to make sure the
house and the mountain were always there,
that he'd guard them to give you a
place to come home to if you needed it.
I didn't understand it then,
but now, after everything that's
happened to me, I think I finally do.
Life isn't just about doing
the things that make you happy.
It's also about finding a way to live
where the happiness of everyone
around you fulfills you, too.
Somehow, I want to figure out how to live
a life that makes everyone around me happy.
I want a life that lets me be there for the
people I care about when they need someone to lean on.
That's all I want.
Mother, I'll study and work hard,
but I want to keep going to the school that I love.
Mom.
What is this?
This is crazy. I'm not really crying.
Mom.
You can't hide it when you're sad in this world.
When you cry, you cry just like in real life.
Such an annoying world.
Morning, mom.
Morning.
Asuna, are you determined to live
the kind of selfless life you spoke of?
Mm‐hmm.
Fine. If that is what you want,
you'll have to be strong enough to carry that burden,
so make sure you go to college,
and for that, you'll have to get better
grades this trimester and next year.
Really?
Then I can stay?
That's up to you.
You'll have to prove yourself.
Do your best.
Thanks, mom. I will.
Thank you, Yuuki.
Here I go.
Next time: "Mother's Rosario".