Only three days left till the new year,
and I hope you're all enjoying your holiday.
Hey, were you up late again?
Yeah,
for a mechatronics project for school.
Mecha‐what? Sounds fun.
Kazuto.
You see this yet?
What the?!
The holy sword Excalibur has been found in "ALO"?!
Aw, man, that sucks.
I can't believe someone else beat us to it.
Read the article, doofus. It says it's been found, is all.
No one's actually got it yet.
Oh.
Yeah, you're right.
Don't scare me like that.
A couple months ago on the Arun plains,
Leafa, Yui, and me got swallowed
by a big‐ass monster worm.
It dropped us in an underground realm called Jotunheim.
We looked around for a bit and came
across this four‐armed humanoid monster.
It was fighting another monster that looked
like a cross between an elephant and a jellyfish.
Go figure. Leafa felt sorry for the
jelly‐phant thing and told me to go save it.
I lured four arms onto this frozen
lake, and it fell through the ice.
Then the jelly‐phant took care of it.
Leafa decided to call it Tonky,
and suddenly it transformed into an
even‐weirder‐looking thing with eight wings.
We hopped on its back, and it took us to a passageway
leading to the surface world.
On the way up was when we saw it, an upside‐down
pyramid hanging from the roots of the World Tree
and a long, golden sword shimmering inside.
Excalibur.
I was planning on going back for it someday, but now...
It'd be a nice break from all that
floor‐clearing you're doing in new Aincrad.
This article doesn't say anything about how they found it.
Players can't fly in Jotunheim, remember?
But that's the only way to spot Excalibur.
That thing's too high up to see.
Unless they rescued one of Tonky's friends,
hitched a ride, and triggered the quest flag.
If we could do it, so could someone else.
I guess that makes sense, although who'd trust a creepy...
Uh, I mean who'd trust such a unique
monster unless they had weird ta...
I mean a weirdly big heart.
Someone just like you, sis.
What are the odds?
He is not creepy. He's adorable.
Anyway, the whole point of showing
you that was to get you going.
It's only a matter of time before someone
grinds through that dungeon and gets the sword.
You're right. Clock's ticking.
So what are you gonna do about it?
Sugu, getting rare items isn't the point of it.
If that's all you play for, you're missing out.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
There's funner things to do than boosting stats.
I wasn't finished.
I think Tonky wanted us to find it,
and that's why he showed us where it was.
For some reason, he needs us to clear that
dungeon, so it's up to us to make his wish come true.
Tonky's our friend, and there's no
way I'm turning my back on a friend.
Mmm!
A minute ago, you called your friend creepy.
Mm.
I meant creepy cool.
Anyway, you in?
Sure. I don't have practice 'cause of the holidays.
Awesome.
Okay, we'll need seven others.
We don't want to overload Tonky.
For starters, we got you, me, and Asuna.
Then there's Klein, Liz, and Silica.
We need one more person.
Agil's gotta work tonight.
Chrysheight's not leveled up yet.
Recon's grinding in sylph territory.
Oh, I know.
Let's ask Sinon to come along.
Great idea, sis.
What'd you expect?
I'll message 'em right now,
except for Asuna. I'll leave that to you.
Okay.
I wish I could see Kirito again
before I go visit my grandparents.
H-Hi, Kirito.
Morning, Asuna.
Sorry to call so early.
We were planning on going on a quest
in "ALO" This afternoon. You want to go?
Yeah, I'll totally go. I'm free all day today.
Cool. I'll text you the time and place,
so keep an eye out for it.
You know I will.
See you in a little while, then.
Yes.
Hey, Klein,
do you get to take vacation for new year's?
Been on it since yesterday.
Even if I wanted to work... and I don't...
there's no shipments this time of year.
You know what my cheap‐ass boss said?
"Be thankful you got a job where you
get a whole week off for new year's,"
bragging about it like he was doing us a favor.
And speaking of favors,
if we do manage to snag Excalibur today,
how about doing me a solid and helping me
get my hands on the soul blade kaguzuchi?
Seriously?
That dungeon's like a frigging oven, man.
Yeah, well, I'm going to Jotunheim for you,
where it's colder than the ass‐end of an ice pop.
You know, I want something out of this, too,
the Shekhinah bow.
Uh, your avatar's two weeks old, and
already you're gunning for a legendary weapon?
Yeah, well, that bow Liz made me is great and all,
but I need something with a little more range.
Oh, yeah?
Then what the heck are you using a bow in "ALO" For?
Their range falls between spears and magic.
You're like the only player who wants to
use these things to snipe from 100 meters.
If I had my way, I'd want double that range at least.
We're back, guys.
Thanks for waiting.
We thought you were never coming back.
What's up? You get lost or something?
Not at all.
We were gathering information while we shopped.
We talked to a whole bunch of people, daddy,
and so far, not one player or
party has reached that dungeon yet.
Really?
Well, then how the heck do they know where Excalibur's at?
That's the thing, daddy.
No one really knows where it is.
Apparently they found a different
quest than the one Tonky showed us.
They met an NPC who told them if they finished
this other quest, they'd get Excalibur as the reward.
And from what we heard,
the quest they're going on isn't very pleasant.
Instead of a delivery quest or an escort quest,
it's a kill quest, just slaughtering monsters.
Everyone in Jotunheim is out there
right now killing as many as they can.
Yeah, that doesn't even sound close to being pleasant.
This whole thing sounds sketchy to me, guys.
Here's what we know.
There's a dungeon in the sky with
Excalibur locked up at the bottom of it.
To get to it, you gotta fight
your way through a bunch of monsters.
But now we got an NPC offering it up
as a kill‐quest reward? That's bizarre.
Now that you mention it,
The NPC's not showing anyone to the
dungeon, but that's where the sword is.
Well, I'm sure we'll find out why once we get there.
All righty.
Your weapons are all restored and ready for action.
Even though our party's full of hotness,
we're still a bunch of gear‐toting meatheads.
If you wanna switch it up, you
could always boost your magic.
Ha! Keep dreaming.
A real samurai, he wouldn't be caught dead using magic.
Code of honor.
Code of honor, huh?
Know what samurai's are classified as in RPGs?
They're both warriors and black‐magic users.
Please. I'd rather bust my sword and
quit being a samurai than use magic, doll.
I don't know, Klein. If I remember right,
didn't you use a flame‐sword skill the other day?
You know, when you activate it, you are using part magic.
No way. Really?
Yes, Klein. What Silica said is true.
Remember the may update?
It brought a whole bunch of new sword skills to "ALO".
Some are physical, and others are advanced,
like earth, water, fire, wind, dark, and divine,
all of which are magical attributes.
Fire's magical, too, huh?
Okay, ex‐samurai, you need help busting that sword?
Dude, back me up here.
Well, since you don't chant when using
sword skills, I guess it's not the same.
I'll let it slide this time. Heh.
I really appreciate you guys
helping me out on such short notice.
Seriously, you don't know how much this means to me.
All right, are you ready?
Yeah!
God.
How many steps does this thing have, anyway?
I know. I bet the tower on the dungeon floor
of new Aincrad doesn't even have as many as this.
Oh, come on. It's not that bad.
If we took the normal route to Jotunheim,
it'd take at least two hours.
This way, it's just five minutes.
Instead of complaining about the steps,
you should be thanking me for
showing you guys this rad shortcut.
Yeah, yeah. You're right.
It's still a pain in the butt.
I got your pain in the butt.
Why, you...
Dumb‐ass. Do that again, and you
get a fire arrow in your piehole.
Brother, you got balls of steel, no joke.
Freezing.
Wowsers.
Amazing.
Aren't you cold?
Oath, sharle, raise, vind, bard, harl‐ca, stoles.
Better?
I cast a freeze‐resistance spell over us.
Tonky, up here!
Jesus.
Take it easy, Klein.
He doesn't look it, but he's a vegetarian.
Well, not exactly.
When I brought him some fish from aboveground,
he scarfed it all down in one bite.
Uh‐oh.
What's he doing?
He's telling you to get on his back is all.
Dude, no way. No way in hell.
My grandpa's dying words were don't ride in
foreign cars or on flying cthulhu elephants.
Is he the same dead grandpa whose dried
figs we were eating at dicey's the other day?
Stop farting around, and get on.
If it eats me, man...
This is gonna be fun.
We're so dead.
Thanks a lot for doing this, Tonky.
All right, Tonky.
Everyone's onboard, so take us to that dungeon!
Wow. I wonder what would happen
if you fell from way up here?
The same thing that happened when
a certain someone decided to get
to the next level of Aincrad
by climbing the outer pillars.
So how 'bout it, wonder Klutz? Care to show the lady?
Nah. I think I'll pass.
But maybe one of our more catlike
friends would like to take a shot.
Nope, nope, nope, nope, nope.
Eh?
Yah‐hah!
Kazuto, get up here. Check it out.
My god. I‐I can't believe it.
They figured out how to make that monster fight for them.
No, there's gotta be another reason.
It's not possible to tame monsters in this game,
not even if you're a cait sith master tamer
with a full power boost and special equipment.
Then they're leeching off the monster?
No, wait. They're not leeching.
Piggybacking, yeah, that's it.
See, that group's got ol' four‐arms
there doing all the heavy lifting
and sniping at the jelly‐phant when they get an opening.
But is it that easy to control a monster's aggro?
It's ignoring everyone else.
How come they're not taking on that four‐armed dude?
Where's everyone going?
Hey, you guys, look.
What the hell's going on down there?
After what we just saw and how it went
down, it should be pretty obvious what it is.
I hate to say it, but we're looking
at that kill quest Asuna told us about.
Even though it's a quest, helping these four‐armed
freaks murder Tonky's friends is disgusting.
Hmm?
Damn, she's tall.
Greetings.
I am Urd, queen of the lake.
You have bonded with my kinsman, and I am grateful.
My two younger sisters and I have spoken at length,
and we have a request for you.
If you would be so kind,
we ask that you save our lands from the frost giants.
Daddy, she's an NPC.
There's something strange about her, though.
Her speech pattern doesn't follow the same
set response routines that a normal NPC's would.
Her core programming is connected to
the language engine module of the game.
What are you saying?
Is she some kind of A. I.?
Yes, daddy, she is.
In the past,
Jotunheim was similar to your Alfheim,
covered in lush greenery and beautiful lakes.
It basked in the blessings of Yggdrasil, the World Tree.
We, the hill giants,
lived in peace and Harmony
with our kinfolk, the creatures.
Far below the splendor of Jotunheim
is a realm of ice and snow known as Niflheim.
Thrymr, king of the frost giants, rules that land.
He shattered our peace by casting Excalibur,
the sword that slices through wood and iron,
into the well of Urd,
the heart of our land.
It severed the thickest roots of the World Tree.
In an instant, Jotunheim lost the
blessings it received from Yggdrasil.
I was right, Excalibur.
Under Thrymr's command,
the frost giants marched on
Jotunheim and overwhelmed our defenses.
Their fortresses and castles soon blighted our land,
and scores of my people were captured and imprisoned.
Once they seized control, they
built Thrymheim, their largest castle,
atop the mass of ice once known as the well of Urd.
During the chaos, my sisters and I
escaped to the bottom of a frozen lake.
However, we no longer have the power we once had.
The frost giants are not satisfied with their spoils.
They wish to annihilate our kin,
the creatures that populate our realm.
If they succeed, my powers will be extinguished,
and Thrymheim will rise to the next world,
your world, Alfheim.
Hold the phone.
You're telling us that once they're done
here, they're gonna go up and destroy Arun?
Yes, that is their intention.
King Thrymr will seal Alfheim in ice and continue on
until he reaches the top of Yggdrasil.
Once he reaches it, he will take
the golden apple growing there.
Thrymr and his generals have grown frustrated
by the time it is taking to wipe out my kinfolk,
so they have turned to your people, the faeries,
for assistance in their murderous plot.
Your kind hunts our kinfolk to extinction,
lured by the offer of Excalibur as a reward.
However, king Thrymr cannot bestow that sword unto others,
for if Excalibur ever leaves Thrymheim,
the blessings of Yggdrasil will return to this land,
and their castle will vanish as a mist upon a meadow.
But... but then...
What kind of quest is it when
the reward for it's a total lie?
How is he gonna get away with it?
Most likely, he will award the
Victor a sword called Caliburn,
whose appearance is identical to Excalibur.
But that's cheating.
If he's a king, doesn't he have a code of honor?
Unfortunately, cheating and falsehoods
are Thrymr's most powerful assets.
However, he has made one great mistake.
In his eagerness to slaughter my kin,
he has sent a number of his giants down from Thrymheim
to marshal your kind for battle.
At this moment, the defenses of his
castle are weaker than they have ever been.
There's our shot.
Once the stone in the amulet turns black,
it will mean all my kinfolk have been slain
and my powers have left me.
Good faeries, infiltrate Thrymheim,
remove Excalibur from its plinth,
and save my realm.
I am counting on you, good faeries.
This is turning into a bigger deal than we thought.
Is this still considered a quest?
'Cause it's kinda turned into something
way more epic than a plain old quest.
You heard her. She said if the
creatures in this world get killed off,
the frost giants'll take over the surface next.
Yeah, I know,
but I doubt the admins would let that happen
without some kind of update or warning or something.
I mean, normally,
they'd let players know a week ahead of time.
Whatever. We're gonna finish this quest for Tonky.
Right, Kazuto?
You know it.
We were gonna storm the castle and grab Excalibur anyway.
It'll be easy if the castle's defenses are down.
Helping Tonky and his friends out, that's a bonus.
Here we go, guys! Our last big quest of the year!
Let's spank this thing and score us a
spot on the front page of MMO tomorrow!
Yeah!
Don't you worry, Tonky.
We'll get your home back for you.
It'll be good as new. Promise.
Here we go.
Next time: "The King of the Giants".