With that name
and your sword skills,
are you the Real Deal or what?
If he knows me, I should know him.
That's it.
He's an "SAO" survivor.
Who is he,
and where did we meet in "SAO"?
Answer the question.
Or don't you understand?
No, I don't.
What do you mean by "Real Deal"?
Never mind.
Whether you're a fake using his name
or the real guy,
someday I'll kill you.
Laughing Coffin.
The emblem on his wrist belonged
to the murder guild from "SAO".
Laughing Coffin.
God knows how many players they killed in their time.
But they're not the only ones guilty of murder.
If the tip we got's good,
we should be near Laughing Coffin's base,
but before we charge in, let's keep one thing in mind.
Those guys are red players.
Once the battle starts, they're not gonna
think twice about killing any one of us,
so don't you hesitate.
You do, and you're dead.
We've got two things going for us, though.
We outnumber them, and we've got higher skill levels.
So who knows? Maybe they'll surrender peacefully.
Hell, a guy can dream, can't he?
Damn it.
Someone must have leaked our plans to these bastards!
They caught us off guard,
but we regrouped in time.
We can do this.
You're outnumbered.
Surrender now, or else.
Come on. Drop your sword.
Do it!
You can't take another hit!
Drop the sword now!
It turned into a blood‐soaked nightmare after that.
We won the battle,
but by the time it was over,
we'd lost ten of ours.
As for Laughing Coffin,
twenty of them refused to surrender and were killed.
Out of that twenty,
two lives were claimed by my sword.
That guy...
If he's one of the survivors from Laughing Coffin,
then he must have talked to me
at some point after that battle,
or maybe he's one of the two people I killed.
No, that's impossible.
That's crazy.
...the name I share with this weapon, Death Gun.
Oh, my god.
His voice was the same as Death Gun's.
Was that him?
Could he be Death Gun?
You look like you're about to lose it.
No, I'm okay.
Guess your first match was tougher than you thought.
You got back pretty early, though.
Not too shabby for a noob.
God, if you're like this after one
match, you'll never make it to the finals.
You better man up, guy.
Remember, we got things to settle.
Hey, let go!
What's wrong with you?
Are you oka...
That player got a death wish or what?
Hmm.
Wha?
Huh. I can't believe he keeps winning fighting like that.
His next match is in the semifinals.
Yours is, too, so get out there and rock.
Good luck.
Stinger is my target.
His main weapon is an FN‐SCAR carbine rifle.
As a sniper, if I let him get too close,
I'm done for.
But on this map,
if he wants to close in on me,
he's gonna have to go through there,
and that's where I'll take him out.
Damn him.
He wanted me to waste my first shot
to buy him time so he could advance.
Too bad for him,
'cause I know the path my first bullet took.
My second one'll be right on target.
You should have got out of the car, buddy.
If you did, you might have seen
the bullet line in time to dodge it.
He's gonna try and close in on me
using the shadows for cover.
My only chance is nailing him with the
first shot, before he figures out my location.
He won't even know what hit him.
What's my problem?
Why do I want to beat him so bad?
Is it 'cause he reminds me of me?
Does he think he can dodge my bullet at this range?
Does he even want to?
Don't...
don't screw with me!
Fight me.
Come on, fight!
Or maybe you think I'm not worth the effort.
You got it all wrong.
All I want is to compete in the final.
There's no reason to fight anymore.
Then go on and shoot yourself, and get it over with!
Or would that be a waste of ammo?
Or maybe you wanted me to shoot you 'cause
you thought it would even the score between us.
To you, it's just a game,
just one stupid match.
That's all it is to you, is that it, a game?
Well, just 'cause you feel that way doesn't mean I do!
But if we do meet in the final bracket of the prelims,
I'll be playing to win.
Oh. I get it.
All right, if we both make it, no holding back.
I'm sorry.
What I did was wrong.
Sure, it's a game.
It's only one match.
But still, that's why we have to give it all we got.
It's why we're here.
It's how we live, how we keep surviving.
If anyone should have known that, it's me.
Sinon, give me a chance to make it right with you.
Let me give you the fight I promised.
I swear, if you're messing with me...
You got any bullets left on you, or are you out?
Yeah, I got one.
Okay, then let's have a duel.
Here's the rules.
We'll stand ten meters apart,
you with your rifle, and me with my sword.
I'll toss this bullet up,
and when it hits the ground, we start.
What do you say?
Hang on.
If we're ten meters away from each other, it won't
give you enough time to see the bullet line and react,
and with my Hecate, I'll definitely hit you.
At that range, I can't miss.
You won't know for sure till you try.
Why's he acting so confident?
Does he have a plan or something?
Whatever it is, I'm ready for it.
Okay.
If that's how you want it, let's go.
I knew it.
He does have a plan.
'Kay. Get set.
No way.
That's impossible!
You knew where I was aiming.
But how? How'd you know I was going for your leg?
I knew, 'cause I could see your eye
through the lens of your scope.
That's how he predicted my bullet's path?
That's amazing.
That kind of power's way beyond any VR Game.
If you're so strong you can do that,
why'd you look so afraid before?
You're wrong. It's not strength.
All it is is a skill.
No, it's not.
Technique isn't enough to cut
a bullet from my Hecate in half.
You and I both know that.
It takes strength, and all I
want to know is how to get it.
It's what I... it's what I'm here to figure out.
Listen, could you shoot a player in here
if you knew, in the real world,
that player would die from it?
And what if you had to kill that player,
'cause if you didn't, you or
someone you love would die instead?
If you had that power,
could you still pull that trigger?
Does he know
about what happened to me that day?
Maybe something like that happened to him, too.
I can't go through that again.
So I'm not as strong as you think I am.
I don't know the names of the two...
no, three people I killed in that other game.
I have to live with it every single day.
And every day, I keep hoping I'll forget.
I'm fine.
Anyway, I guess this means I won the duel, doesn't it?
Huh? Oh. Yeah, I guess.
Well, would you mind surrendering then?
I'm not a big fan of slashing at girls.
Huh?
Next time, I'm not gonna lose.
See you in the finals.
And make sure you survive until you see me again.
Resign.
Huh?
Next time: "Crimson Memories".