What's wrong, Yui?
I have a feeling there's a lot
more at stake here than we think.
This will require some explaining.
While all VRMMOs originate from the seed program,
there's a difference between them and "Alfheim Online."
You see, a stripped‐down version of the
cardinal system runs the other active VRMMOs,
but the one that operates this game
is a copy of the full‐spec version
that ran "Sword Art Online."
Full‐spec version?
The original cardinal system had a feature
which could automatically generate quests.
It would log on to the net and search for
various legends and folklore from around the world.
Then it would take the stories it found, adapt the data,
and use it to generate an infinite number of quests.
How about this quest, then?
Is it autogenerated by cardinal, too?
After seeing how that NPC was acting just now,
I have a feeling it is.
If that is the case here, then no matter what you do,
this quest will end the same way the myth does.
Just now, I ran a quick check on my archives.
According to my data and taking into
account the norse mythology "ALO" is based on,
this quest must end in a final war event.
The frost giants from Jotunheim and Niflheim
aren't the only ones who want to attack Arun.
Below Niflheim is a fiery realm called Muspelheim,
where the flame giants live.
According to the myth,
they will attack the world tree and burn it to the ground.
Ragnarok, the twilight of the gods.
Uh‐uh. I don't buy it.
I can't believe this game system
would destroy its own maps on purpose.
It's gotta be a mistake.
I'm sorry, but there's no mistake about it.
The cardinal system has the authority
to destroy its maps if it wants.
I know this, because the original cardinal
system's last task was destroying Aincrad,
the floating castle of "Sword Art Online."
No way.
There goes my blacksmith's shop.
There go my chances of ever meeting my soul mate.
Even if this ragnarok thing happens and it all deletes,
can't the server be rolled back the way
it was from one of the backups it's made?
The system has an autobackup
feature, but those files won't help.
It only saves player data, not field
data, so you can't restore everything.
Oh, I got it!
I don't got it.
You can say that again.
Stop razzing me.
I was trying to call a GM to see if he knew about this.
It ain't happening now.
It's after hours.
Support's closed.
That figures.
It's Sunday morning just before new year's.
Kazuto,
we're running out of time.
Yeah.
Let's hurry and get to the last level.
Right!
Damn it.
Damn.
This isn't looking good.
The gold one's tough. Nothing we do is slowing him down.
Yeah.
This sucks. If we only had a mage
who can cast attack spells in our party.
That's hilarious coming from you.
It wouldn't help, anyway, 'cause the dude in the back
with the high resistance to magic would just move up.
Could this get any tougher?
Shockwave attack coming up in three,
two, one!
Soo filla hail‐agool oustool!
Plot subahl bahni!
Kirito!
We've only got about 2 1/2 minutes
before I'm out of MP!
'Kay.
Kazuto, more than 2/3 of this medallion's gone dark.
If we die now, we won't have time
to start over from the save point.
Thanks. Good to know.
Hey, guys,
there's one thing we haven't tried yet.
If we use sword skills with magic, we
might do some damage to this gold bastard.
It'll leave you wide open, though,
it's do‐or‐die time!
So what do you say we focus our attack and wipe him out?
Hell, yeah.
Just say the word, and his ass is grass.
Silica, time for your bubble spell.
Right!
Ready, and...
Hit it!
Pina, bubble breath attack!
Go!
Kirito!
We locked up!
This is it.
Yah!
Aww. We killed your pal.
Too bad, for you.
Okay, what the hell was that move you just pulled?
You don't want to know.
Oh, come on. That was totally a new skill.
Well, it's not really a skill.
It's skill connect.
Skill connect?
Remember the last update?
You know it brought a bunch
of sword skills to "ALO", right?
Well, even though we got those, we didn't get
unique skills like Dual‐Wielding or the Divine Blade.
Hang on a sec.
You were Dual‐Wielding just now.
Technically, that wasn't Dual‐Wielding.
Huh?
I was using one‐handed sword skills
with each hand and alternating between 'em.
If I'm lucky, I can keep it going
without any lag maybe three or four times.
Hmm. Eh?
No, it's nothing, Yui,
just deja vu, is all.
You're not off the hook either.
What the hell'd you do just now?
I don't think you want to know.
Oh, come on. I've never seen anything like that before.
It's an extra skill I picked up,
Dual‐Wielding.
Don't pop a blood vessel.
All right. We can't stand around chatting all day.
Leafa, how much time we got left?
Oh, right.
At the pace we're going, we
should have maybe another hour or so.
That's it?
Yui, do you know how big these
last couple of floors are gonna be?
Yes. The third floor is about 70% the size of the second,
and the fourth floor is pretty much just the boss room.
I figure the last boss fight
will take us 30 minutes to finish.
That means we only got about
30 minutes to get to his room.
That settles it.
The clock's ticking, and the king of giants is waiting.
Let's get the lead out and kick his giant ass.
Daddy!
You heard her. As soon as everyone's got their
HP and MP restored, we'll hit that third floor!
Right!
Hyah!
Come on, guys! The last boss is waiting!
Please, help me.
Let me out of here.
It's a trap.
It's so a trap.
Well, maybe it is.
Maybe it isn't.
What do you think, Yui?
She's an NPC. Her core programming is
connected to the language engine module,
just like Urd's,
although there is one difference between them.
This one has an HP gauge.
Yeah, that's a big red flag.
If she's got an HP gauge, we might have to fight her.
A trap. Totally a trap.
Obviously a trap.
It might be a trap. It might not. I don't know.
Either way, we can't afford to take the chance.
We can't waste any more time.
We gotta get to Thrymr asap.
Oh, right. Yeah.
We got a job to do.
Do not leave me, please.
I beg you.
Eh?
I know it's a trap.
I'm not stupid.
But even if it is a trap,
even if I know it's a trap,
I don't care!
I can't just turn my back on someone if they need help!
Even if... even if it means we fail the quest
and even if Arun gets destroyed,
if I got a chance to do some good for someone, I will,
'cause that's what being a samurai's all about!
Don't worry, Princess! I'm coming!
I'm free.
Thank you, faerie swordsman.
No worries.
Let me help you up.
No, I can manage it.
Whoa.
The way out's kind of far, dollface.
You gonna be okay to make it on your own?
Hmm?
I could,
but I'm afraid I cannot leave the castle just yet.
For, you see, I must first retrieve my
people's treasure, which king Thrymr stole.
If you would, faerie swordsman,
please let me accompany you to Thrymr's room.
This is beyond fishy, don't you think?
Uh‐huh.
Hey, uh, Kirito...
All right. I can't stand seeing you beg.
Since we only got a little further to go before the end
and seeing as how we don't know for sure it's a trap...
Yes!
You hear that?
You're coming with us, gorgeous.
We'll help you beat that jerk Thrymr.
We're in the same boat now, so let's get wet together.
Oh, thank you, faerie swordsman.
Delete Klein's last comment from your memory, Yui.
Huh?
Name's Klein.
Freyja.
Huh. She must be a mage.
Her MP's really high.
With the way they got this dungeon laid out,
the final boss room should be down those stairs.
Remember, he's the last boss, so he's
gonna be way stronger than the other ones.
When you hit him, hit fast, and hit hard.
Until we can figure out his attack patterns,
we'll be on the defensive,
so no one moves on him till I say.
One last thing. If you see
his Gauge drop to yellow or red,
his attack patterns are gonna
change big‐time, so watch out.
Mm.
This is it, guys.
Get in there, and give it all you got.
Right!
Seh‐aah, filla, skeana, haggle, hogg, margle, ill‐toh!
Oath, narza, fiyohl, leggin, tinarda, valindle, yotun!
She boosted our maximum HP
I didn't know a spell could do that.
Cha‐cha‐ching.
Wonder how much yuld's here?
Coochie‐coochie‐coo.
Who let the flies in?
Hmm?
The buzzing of their wings is so irritating.
Hmm.
I shall crush them all
before they annoy me any further.
Winged Alfheim insects.
Have you burrowed down here on
the whims of Urd, the trollop?
Wretches, how dare you enter here?
Did you think you could steal my treasure?
If you tell me where I can find that woman,
I shall give it all to you gladly.
Ha! You think a samurai gives a damn about gold?
Well, you can stick that treasure right up your ass.
Better yet, let me give you a hand.
Lady Freyja.
How good of you to grace us with your presence today.
I see you have left your cage. Shall I take it you
have come to your senses and agreed to become my wife?
She's supposed to marry you?
Yes, she is.
That is why she came to this castle.
Isn't that right, my dear?
However, the night before our wedding banquet,
I caught her sniffing around my treasure vault.
As punishment, I locked her in a cage of ice.
Hey, Kazuto... hmm?
I know this story.
I read it before, Thrmyr and Freyja,
a stolen treasure, and something else, too,
but what?
I will not become your wife.
These warriors and I are here to
put an end to your reign of evil.
Return my treasure immediately!
Yes, that's the spirit, my lovely.
I would expect nothing less from the woman whose
beauty and valor are known throughout the land.
And as they say, the more noble the
flower, the more satisfying it is to pluck.
After I've snuffed the life from these insects,
I shall shower you with extra affection.
You bastard.
Over my dead body!
I, Lord Klein, won't let you lay a finger on lady Freyja!
Listen to the angry little fly buzzing away.
Now, then, it is time I began
celebrating my conquest of Jotunheim.
I shall start by crushing the life from you.
Heh.
It's on!
Listen to Yui, guys!
Don't attack till she says!
You got it!
Next time: "Excaliber".