So Zekken shows up at 3:00 on this island on floor 24.
Mm‐hmm.
Then I'll see you guys there tomorrow at 2:30.
Okay.
You got it.
I can't wait.
This'll be so much fun.
Yeah, it will. Huh. Yeah!
The berserk healer's gonna get unleashed.
Oh?
Daddy, you have something on your face.
Huh? For real?
Yes. It's covered in ink.
You're kidding!
See you guys tomorrow.
Yeah! See ya! See ya!
Good night, Ms. Sada.
Thank you for coming.
I'm sorry you had to work so late.
Not at all, really.
Just doing my job, miss.
Do you know if my mother and brother are home yet?
Koichiro phoned to say he won't be in till late tonight,
and your mother is waiting in the dining room.
Oh. Thank you.
Have a good night, Ms. Sada.
You're late.
Next time, I want you here five minutes early.
Yes, ma'am.
It looks good.
I assume you were using that thing again?
Yes.
My friends and I were doing our homework together.
Unless you actually physically do
your homework, you won't learn a thing.
But we all live so far away from each other.
It's more convenient for us to meet in‐game.
It hardly qualifies as meeting if you're using that toy.
Besides, doing your homework is not a team activity.
If you're with your friends, you'll just fool around.
Asuna, you don't have time to play around anymore.
You're two years behind everyone else.
You should be studying as hard as you
can to make up for all that lost time.
But I am studying hard.
Didn't you see my grades for the second semester?
I left them on your desk.
Yes, I saw them,
but grades from a school like that are suspect, at best.
They're not suspect.
Yes, well, for your next trimester,
I've decided to hire you a tutor,
and not one of those virtual
ones everyone's going on about,
someone who'll come to the house.
But don't I get to have any say in it?
Have a look at this.
A transfer exam study guide?
I know someone on the board of directors there.
After some discussion, I convinced them to let
you take an exam to transfer into their senior class.
It's a proper high school, not some makeshift study hall.
And since it's credit‐based,
I'm sure you'll be able to
graduate after the first trimester.
If you do, you'll be back on track for college.
Wait! Hold on!
You can't just make a decision like this without me!
I‐I happen to like the school I'm in.
The teachers there are great.
I‐I can learn there just as much as anywhere!
I don't have to change schools!
I've done my research, you know, and believe me, that
place you're attending can hardly be called a school.
The curriculum is slapdash, and the classes are a joke.
Even the faculty's substandard.
They're a bunch of losers with
no real credentials to speak of.
Don't say that.
They claim they're helping the students
who fell behind because of that accident.
It's all a lie. They just want all the children
who've spent the last two years killing each other
in one convenient place so they can monitor them.
It's more like an asylum than a school.
Did you forget, mother?
I spent two years killing other kids, too.
All the friends you had back in junior high
are studying to get into college this year.
They're leaving you behind.
Doesn't that bother you?
Not at all. If it takes an extra year or
two, it won't make much of a difference.
Besides, I might not want to go to college.
Ridiculous. I won't entertain such talk.
You're far too gifted, and your father and I
have gone to great lengths to nurture your talents.
I hope you appreciate that.
I do, but shouldn't I get to have a say in my own future?
Sure, I might not know what kind of career I
want right now, but I'm close to finding out.
If I stay in my school for another
year, it will help me make that decision.
No matter how long you stay at a place
like that, it'll just limit your options.
Look, try to understand.
I don't want you to make a
wrong turn now and regret it later.
I just want you to have a good life and
find yourself a good career you can be proud of.
So that boy you forced me to meet on new year's day,
that was you trying to help me with my career?
You should've heard him.
He was talking like we were already engaged or something.
You're the one who's limiting my options,
not me and not my school!
Marriage is part of your career.
If you marry beneath you or marry
poor, I guarantee you'll regret it.
You won't have the means to pursue
whatever it is you really want to do.
That's why I think Yuuya would be an excellent choice.
His family owns a small regional bank.
Those are much more stable than some
mega‐bank run by a board of directors.
Your last choice wasn't very good.
Did you forget how he made me and
I don't know how many others suffer?
Nobuyuki Sugou nearly bankrupted rect.
He was your choice, mother.
Enough, young lady!
I don't want to hear about him in this house again.
And you're wrong. It wasn't
my choice. It was your father's.
He suggested that crook marry into this family.
He's never been a good judge of character.
But don't worry. Yuuya might lack
initiative, but he seems stable,
and stability is the cornerstone of marriage.
I don't care.
I have no intention to date or marry him.
I choose who I'll marry.
Fine. As long as the man you choose is
from a good family and is worthy of you.
However, a boy like that,
your little friend from school, is not worthy.
Y‐You had him investigated?
Of course I did. Try to understand. Your
father and I only want what's best for you in life.
You have the potential to do whatever you
want as long as you make the right choices.
I need time to think about transferring.
Keep in mind the deadline's next week.
Don't forget.
And after you fill out the form, make three
copies, and leave them in my office on my desk.
Mother...
What is it?
Even though they're gone, you're still
ashamed of grandma and grandpa, aren't you?
You're angry you weren't born
into a rich, important family.
Asuna, come back here right now!
Asuna!
Kirito.
Hey, about that questionnaire, have
you figured out what you wanna do yet?
I guess, if anything, I wanna go
from playing games to being a creator.
A creator? What, for games?
No, not for games.
I wanna make a human‐machine interface
to replace the full‐dive tech we use now.
I've been going to all these
tech forums to learn more about it,
but it's a heck of a lot of information to absorb.
I want to be with Kirito and go after the same dream,
but now...
You sure are strong,
way stronger than I am.
I'm not strong at all.
In that world, I was a warrior,
but here...
Lightning Flash Asuna of the
knights of the blood oath is gone.
In the real world, I don't have any real power.
Hey.
It's rare for you to be so punctual, don't ya think?
It happens sometimes.
Hey, you remember?
You know, that one day you came to my
place in Selmburg and I made you dinner?
Hate to say it, but my memory's
about as good as my punctuality.
What?!
Yeah. I remember that day like it was yesterday.
Really?
Of course. Let's see.
That's the day I got a super‐rare food item, right?
And you made an awesome stew out of it.
That was some tasty meat.
I'm never gonna forget that day.
You don't remember anything except that stupid dinner?!
It's almost time.
I better get over there.
Asuna, be careful with Zekken.
Huh?
Well, it's like...
Zekken's really strong. Just sayin'.
Don't you worry. Liz and the
others already told me everything.
Yup, they even told me about how you lost.
I still can't believe it.
Oh, by the way, Leafa said in the middle of
your duel with Zekken, you stopped fighting to talk.
What'd you talk about?
Well, actually, I asked a question.
What about?
I got a weird vibe, so I asked...
You're full‐time in this world, aren't you, Zekken?
And then, for an answer, I got a
sly grin and a mega‐fast attack.
I'd never seen anything move that fast.
What did you mean by "full time in this world"?
Is that the same thing as being a heavy user?
Uh‐uh. Zekken's way different than
your average, everyday hardcore gamer.
It felt like... like they were a sort of
product of the full‐dive environment itself.
I have no idea what you're talking about.
In a way, it's probably better you don't.
The best way to explain it is for you to experience it.
Every time we turn around,
you're always pawin' at each other.
Sorry to interrupt your little love‐fest, but
there's a duel that's supposed to be happenin'.
Yeah. Yeah.
I‐I know. I was on my way.
I yield! I quit, resign!
Ah, yeah! That's 67 wins in a row! Zekken's undefeated!
Hah!
'Scuse me. Liz...
What?
You didn't say Zekken's a girl!
I didn't? I could've sworn I did.
You didn't!
And you...
I have a feeling I know why you lost now.
Stare...
Mm‐mm. No, you're wrong.
I didn't go easy on her 'cause she's a girl!
I was goin' full‐out! I swear!
Halfway through our duel, anyway.
Whatever!
So, uh, is there anyone else
out there wanna take me on today?
You're up. Go on. Get 'er!
Wait. I gotta psych myself up first.
Oh, please! Once you cross swords with
her, believe me, you'll get psyched up.
Go on! Get in there!
Hey, what's up? You next?
Oh, uh, hi.
I‐I guess I am?
Awesome!
So, uh, does anything go in this duel?
Of course. You can use magic or items, whatever you want.
I'm only gonna use my sword, though.
Oh, wait. Almost forgot.
You wanna fight on the ground or in the air?
Is either okay?
Mm‐hmm.
Hmm.
Let's duel on the ground, then.
You got it.
Jumping's allowed, but no using your wings, okay?
"Yuuki".
Ho ho ho.
She is strong,
but if I gave up now,
I'd ruin my reputation as a swordswoman.
In that world, I was a warrior, but here...
Got her.
She saw my quadruple pain?
No way.
I won't lose!
Is this the 11‐hit combo,
her original sword skill?
If I'm going to lose,
it might as well be to something as awesome as that.
That was an awesome fight, girl!
You're definitely the one.
Uh, what?
Aren't we gonna finish the duel?
I totally seen enough to know you got what it takes,
but if you want, we can keep goin'.
Mm‐mm.
I been lookin' for someone who could go the distance.
At last, I found ya!
Hmm?
Whoa!
Mommy.
Asuna! Where ya goin'?!
Asuna!
Um...
I picked ya,
'cause you're the only one who can help us.
Help? With what?
Next time: "The Sleeping Knights".