That's Kirihito for you.
Always has a plan.
Here it is.
The Shibakiyama Stable!
Home of top-ranked pros
and renowned
for its intense practices!
My first stop in conquering
the pro sumo world.
Ready or not, here I come!
All right!
Keep things moving along!
[BOTH grunting]
[WRESTLERS grunting]
[SAKI]
They're so intense.
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
What're you waiting for? Push!
[SAKI] And Master Shibakiyama
is as sharp-eyed
and intimidating as ever.
Even after retirement.
What lovely form but remember
to keep your chin
a little bit lower
next time, okay?
[SAKI]
I didn't expect that.
I appreciate you coming
all this way
to watch our training, Saki.
My pleasure.
It's an honor to spend
the next two days
at your stable.
It's weird seeing the master
acting so upbeat.
Must be because
we've got company today.
Hah! That's for sure.
But I guess you didn't hear
there's another student
stopping by
to have a trial with us.
And apparently, he's some kind
of high school hotshot.
You think we should be worried?
[SHIBAKIYAMA groaning]
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
He should've arrived by now!
I can personally vouch
for his skill
and guarantee you
one day he'll be
the top-ranked sumo wrestler.
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
A sekitori in the making.
I want him for my stable.
[TERAHARA] Master.
He's coming this way.
Oh! It's about time!
♪
-Hmm?
-[growling]
I'm so sorry about being late!
I got turned around
on my way here.
Oh, and thanks again for
letting me train with you today.
♪
I get it. You're like
his assistant, right?
So, is Ushio waiting for you
to announce him?
[HINOMARU]
Huh? No.
I'm Hinomaru Ushio
from the Odachi High sumo club.
Do I know him?
No, there must be some mistake!
-No.
-But...
I mean, just how tall
are you, son?
Oh, 152 centimeters, sir.
You can barely even reach
the light switch!
Calm down.
[BOY] The master's spirit took
a total nosedive.
Can't blame him.
[BOY] Look.
The kid's already here.
Let's humor him.
Besides, it's just for one day.
[exhaling forcefully]
Hey, your footwork's not bad.
Ushio, was it?
You can call me Terahara.
I was a high school sumo
up until recently.
As your predecessor,
I'll be your sparring partner.
Don't hold back, all right?
Yes, sir.
[HINOMARU] I stretched, but
I'm still feeling kind of stiff.
Is it my nerves?
[WRESTLERS grunting]
[SAKI] The atmosphere's
definitely mellowed out
since Hinomaru showed up.
Everyone's way more relaxed.
[sighs] Geez, I know
we're just sparring,
but these guys could at least
set an example for the kid.
They're trying to put on
a show for him.
He's a fan of sumo after all.
Might as well let him have
some fun until he leaves.
[BOY 2] If you feel
warmed up enough,
then let's step inside the ring.
-Yes, sir.
-Actually, before you start,
you want to try your luck
at a little competition
-we're throwing?
-Hmm?
[BOY 2]
Every kid who shows up
to one of our practices
gets a shot.
We call it the "Shibakiyama
Knock 'em Out Challenge."
You push one of us
out of the ring,
guess what you
could take home with you.
That's right,
official stable merchandise!
Whoa!
You wanna show the kid
what you've got, Terahara?
Oh, yeah!
♪
[BOY laughs]
Talk about a size difference.
Just do the best you can, Ushio!
[TERAHARA]
Don't worry, kid.
You won't go home empty-handed.
I'll step out of the ring
after you've struggled a bit.
Hmm.
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
Tera.
I recommend
you take this seriously.
Right. Sir.
Here I come.
[straining]
[ALL gasp]
He's only a kid.
-[BOTH gasp]
-[TERAHARA straining]
-[HINOMARU yelling]
-[TERAHARA groans]
[HINOMARU]
Even though I'll never turn down
Shibakiyama Stable merch,
my sumo team needs me
to bring home
more than just souvenirs
from this trip.
♪
The thing I really want
is a full-blown
Shibakiyama session.
[chuckles]
♪
[KEI]
Hinomaru should be training
with top-notch sumo wrestlers
right about now.
Hard to believe.
At the Shibakiyama Stable,
that right?
Yeah. And speaking of which,
why'd you choose
that one, Coach?
Even among the pros,
they're renowned
for their training.
Before he retired,
the stable master was famous
for his tough practice sessions.
The man wasn't exactly blessed
with a godlike physique.
What he had
were fearsome attacks,
which earned him
the nickname "Firecracker."
In his prime, he even gave
Yamatokuni a run for his money.
Despite his small stature,
he fought head-on.
Additionally,
throughout his career,
the man never altered
his charge.
Remind you of anyone we know?
Yeah.
[KIRIHITO] I want to hear
what the master thinks
after watching Hinomaru fight.
And there's also
another sumo wrestler there
I'm hoping he'll get
the chance to meet.
[panting]
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
This stable has a reputation
for its intense training,
especially when I was
at the top of my game.
Even so, many complained
about the regimen and left.
Here I was thinking you were
like those other boys.
Head full of dreams
and a heart with zero ambition.
[HINOMARU grunts]
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
I admit, I misjudged you.
Accept my apologies,
Hinomaru Ushio.
The pro league won't permit
someone of your height.
Yet you're besting
sandanme-division wrestlers.
He's too much for you to handle?
Then stand back.
[HINOMARU grunts]
[SHIBAKIYAMA] Sometimes when
you grab a mawashi belt,
your technique shows cracks.
-A move, maybe?
-[HINOMARU panting]
No, I have
a more important question.
Let's go, one more time!
[SHIBAKIYAMA] What is that gleam
you have in your eyes?
Yeah! Bring it!
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
His enthusiasm is infectious.
It's completely shifted
the mood.
Impressive someone so young
is able to do that.
-[door opens]
-[wind gusting]
[gasps]
Mmm.
[SAENOYAMA]
Do you know who our guest is?
That's Hinomaru Ushio.
He's visiting
for a one-day trial.
[SAENOYAMA] I remember hearing
he was coming.
He's not half-bad.
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
Hey, Nori!
Quit crouching there
like a creeper.
Get your ass in here.
-[door creaks]
-[SAENOYAMA] Forgive me.
It sounded like you were having
such a productive session,
I didn't want to interrupt
and break the momentum.
Actually, to tell you the truth,
I couldn't tear my eyes away.
[SAKI]
Uh...
The ninth-ranked maegashira,
Saenoyama!
[ALL WRESTLERS]
Good morning, sekitori!
[SAKI] So far,
Ushio's been fighting trainees
from the makushita division
and below.
I-I mean, not to say
they're pushovers,
but they're second
and third-rate pros at best.
There are 700
elite sumo wrestlers,
but only 70
in the juryo division and above
are sekitoris
and can tie
their hair in an o-icho topknot.
Plus, only they're allowed
to wear a white mawashi belt
during practice.
If you wanted to meet
one of the best, Ushio,
here he is.
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
The boy created a mood
similar to a practice session
for a sekitori.
I wonder.
Now that an actual sekitori
is here,
will things get even more tense?
[SAKI]
Uhh...
[SAENOYAMA]
Good morning.
Thank you for your
assistance earlier.
[SAKI] No, thank you
for letting me attend.
[SAENOYAMA]
Good morning to you, Master.
-[SHIBAKIYAMA] Hmm.
-Sekitori!
It'd be an honor
to have a bout with you!
-[SAKI gasps]
-[SHIBAKIYAMA] Hmm.
Slow down.
He only just arrived
at practice, Ushio.
[SAENOYAMA]
You read my mind.
I'd also like to duel.
[BOY 3]
Huh! Sekitori?
It's uncommon,
but you've piqued my interest.
♪
[HINOMARU] Is this
the opportunity you were hoping
I'd get, Kirihito?
Even the weaker fighters
gave me a workout,
but let's be honest.
Kusanagi was on
a completely different level.
Ordinary opponents won't do.
I need to fight wrestlers
who will challenge me.
Like Saenoyama.
[SHIBAKIYAMA] I'll admit,
we underestimated you
when you first walked in.
-However...
-Now! Spirit!
[HINOMARU]
He's not moving.
[groans]
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
You made the same mistake, boy.
[HINOMARU]
I found it.
Nice. Can we go
another round?
This is what I came for.
[HINOMARU groans]
I'm not making any headway.
His legs are so flexible.
My attacks have
no effect on him.
Then in a flash, he turns
his body into a boulder.
[groans]
The might of a pro.
"You should be like water."
My master taught me that.
Your form must be
as agile as fluid
and strike
with torrential force.
Be like water, huh?
[SAENOYAMA]
Whereas your sumo is like fire,
continuously raging.
You could say it's heroic,
but you might
also call it sloppy.
Thank you very much.
I understand the range
of your abilities.
Sekitori, please, wait!
Any further bouts would be
a waste of both our time.
I've one duty, and that's
achieve the rank of yokozuna.
A glory my master was unable
to reach during his career.
[HINOMARU]
But I'm only here today.
Please, just one more bout!
[SAENOYAMA]
Haven't you had enough?
I am at a loss
as to what spurs you on.
Even if you can't best me,
you shouldn't feel ashamed.
I don't know a single person
here who'd dare call you weak.
I feel you'll be moderately
successful in high school sumo.
Being moderately successful
isn't good enough for me!
I intend to become a yokozuna,
same as you!
That's my reason
for not giving up!
♪
[SAENOYAMA]
Like me?
Your dream is born
of childish idealism.
Meanwhile, I speak
knowing full well
how long and arduous
the road actually is.
And you think we're the same?
♪
You requested one more bout.
Very well.
Maybe you think
you'll have a growth spurt
or your luck
will suddenly change.
But I'm warning you now.
Your words were an insult
to sumo wrestlers,
and I'll make you pay
dearly for it.
That expression.
He means business.
[HINOMARU]
Don't back down.
This is exactly why I'm here.
It's my last chance
of finding a way to evolve.
I need to do something different
with my charge.
Gotta be realistic.
I don't have the skill yet
to overpower a sekitori.
But I'm out of options.
I'll go low
and fast as possible!
He's in a spider stance.
Keep experimenting
till you find what works.
♪
Now! Spirit!
[SAENOYAMA yells]
[grunts]
[TERAHARA]
Oh, man!
Side slaps are banned
in amateur competitions.
♪
[SAENOYAMA]
Interesting.
He used his knees as a cushion
to absorb the impact.
[HINOMARU]
After all my previous bouts,
I don't have much strength left.
I've got to be like water.
Fluidity varies your rhythm
and dictates the tempo
in a bout.
But you forgot,
fire doesn't just rage.
It flickers and burns!
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
This is it.
This is what you came
to my stable to find.
[HINOMARU] Kirihito went
through the trouble
of finding me
a damn good sparring partner.
I can't waste this opportunity!
If I'm reaching the top,
it means devouring you!
[SAENOYAMA] Some
incredible force is erupting
from within him!
[roaring]
[BOTH yell]
-[thud]
-[BOTH gasp]
[ALL gasp]
[SAKI]
The sekitori pushed Ushio
to the ground first.
But look at his knee.
He still went down!
[panting]
[HINOMARU]
My body was moving on its own.
It wasn't the same
as what Kirihito did,
but it felt so natural.
It must've been some kind
of new technique.
I almost had it.
I was nearly there.
Damn. Damn!
[SAENOYAMA] As we agreed upon,
that's our final bout.
Thank you for sparring with me.
[SAENOYAMA] I expect to see you
here again tomorrow.
-[gasps]
-Your sumo intrigues me,
and I'd like to see a bit more
of what you can do.
I may not look it,
but I'm a real curious guy.
I'll be here!
Count on it!
So, did you have fun
at your remedial class?
Some punk called Gengoro
from Ishigami stopped by.
Gengoro?
-[cell phone buzzing]
-Hmm?
Hello?
Uh-huh. Wait.
You're staying?
[HINOMARU]
Saenoyama's already agreed
to spar with me more tomorrow.
So the master said it made sense
if I stayed overnight.
Think you'll learn it?
Your new move?
[HINOMARU] I'll let you know
when I see you.
-Later.
-[phone beeps]
Was that Hinomaru?
It was.
He's spending the night
at the stable.
Seems he's training tomorrow
as well.
Guess he made
a good first impression.
We have to work hard too.
Gotta help him carry the weight.
Good, 'cause that's
my specialty.
If you want to help,
don't fail any more tests.
I'm a C plus student now!
[KIRIHITO]
They may think you're cheating.
Authentic sumo stable
chankonabe stew!
Kid! You did good
out there today!
Thanks a lot, sir.
Grab a seat and pour a bowl.
The sekitori's
still eating though.
Today's an exception.
So chow down.
Yes, sir!
[SAKI chuckles]
The apprentices
usually eat last,
so you shouldn't feel bad.
I know, but...
It's still kinda awkward.
[SAENOYAMA] I understand
you're a national treasure,
Onimaru Kunitsuna.
Are you serious?
It's not that big of a deal.
Why are you being so modest?
I heard you held you own
against Kusanagi.
Wait a minute, who told you?
Please. I'm a high school
sumo club manager,
which means gossip
inevitably finds its way to me.
By Kusanagi,
you're referring to...
Sosuke Kuze,
a national treasure, yeah.
The son of Yamatokuni,
the former yokozuna.
A legend.
There's no way.
He's a popular topic
of discussion these days.
They say he's gonna shoot
through the ranks
if he turns pro.
So you are in the same
generation as he is, are ya?
Tough break, kiddo.
[SAENOYAMA]
Who was stronger?
Me or junior?
[gasps]
Well, all I know is I did a lot
better fighting against him
-than against you.
-[ALL laughing]
Yeah, sounds right.
Hey, I don't see
your chopsticks moving.
Stew's a three-bowl minimum.
[HINOMARU]
Y-yes, sir!
[BOY 4] And after
you've eaten your fill,
we snooze.
[snoring]
♪
We're off to buy groceries
for dinner.
[HINOMARU]
When you're an apprentice,
there's no shortage
of chores to do.
The thing is, it's a lot of fun.
I know it's not all
about cutting loose.
You're living to compete,
after all.
I bet each wrestler has
their own private doubts
and anxieties.
In fact, I'm sure of it.
For the longest time, I wanted
-to be a part of this...
-[BOY 5] Awesome.
[HINOMARU] A member
of the pro sumo world.
I'm not here to goof off.
Not when I haven't accomplished
anything yet.
But still, if only
for a short while,
let me soak up this feeling,
until I have to leave.
♪
[scraping]
[moans]
[scraping continues]
I didn't mean to wake you up.
Sorry about that.
I couldn't sleep
and decided to run drills.
I wanted to revisit
everything I felt today,
if that makes sense.
You're too excited to rest,
I get it.
I want to be a pro.
And spending the day here
only reinvigorated that desire.
[SAKI] On my days off,
I've been arranging to stay
at various sumo stables.
My brother wants to turn pro,
the same as you.
While he's busy practicing,
I've been scoping
them out for him.
Yeah?
[SAKI]
So, tell me the truth.
Who was stronger?
Saenoyama or Kuze?
Well, obviously,
the sekitori has more power
and better technique.
And even though I appreciate him
agreeing to spar with me,
truthfully,
if they were to fight each other
at this moment,
I couldn't say who would win.
Maybe Kuze is looming
in my mind after our bout.
I knew I wanted to fight someone
who'd be similar
in height and technique.
If I can't take on
a full-strength sekitori,
then I can never...
-[SHIBAKIYAMA] Now I understand.
-[switch clicks]
It seems this friend of yours
chose Saenoyama
as a stand-in for training
against Sosuke Kuze.
[HINOMARU]
Master. You're up!
After fighting with
the sekitori yesterday,
I imagine there's plenty
you want to work on.
So, we better start sparring
right away.
[HINOMARU]
Huh?
[crowd cheering]
[SHIBAKIYAMA] When everyone said
I was past my prime,
I defeated
the higher-ranked Yamatokuni.
I promise there's still one or
two lessons I could teach you.
What's the matter with you, son?
I don't take my shirt off
for just anybody, you know.
[HINOMARU]
I guess I'm confused
why you're invested
in my future.
I'd understand
if I was a sumo wrestler
destined to turn pro.
But I'm a... well...
[SHIBAKIYAMA] Chalk it up
to another habit of growing old.
But when I look at you,
I see myself.
In my youth,
I was called small. Helpless.
But I still fought with passion
to become a yokozuna.
I only made it
as high as sekiwake.
And though I was praised
for my accomplishment,
I never achieved
my actual dream.
I passed my ambition
onto Saenoyama
thinking height was
what held me back.
But after watching you,
I have one more dream left.
To see someone our size
become a yokozuna.
Realize that dream for me!
♪
That was a bit long-winded,
I admit,
but I'm saying I believe in you.
When you're ready
to turn pro, find me.
I'll be waiting for you, kid.
Sir!
What's Hinomaru doing up?
Aah! The master's awake too!
And practicing with him?
Looks like everybody's
too excited to sleep.
[TERAHARA]
Aw, screw it!
Let's start practice now!
[ALL STUDENTS cheering]
[SAKI] A high school student
getting the pros stoked.
Hinomaru Ushio, huh?
[SAKI]
Thank you for everything.
Man, that was so much fun.
And having someone around
to talk to
who was my own age
made things easier.
Thanks for coming.
It was good to meet
a fellow sumo enthusiast.
If both our schools win
enough bouts,
we'll see each other
at nationals.
Well, I can guarantee
I'll be there,
since I'm going to become
a high school yokozuna.
I certainly hope you do,
but since my brother's
also competing,
you may have to hold off on
your dream until the next year.
Wait.
You told me you were
a sumo manager
but never what
high school you go to.
Tottori Hakuro.
Tottori Hakuro?
You mean...
I'm Saki Tennoji.
Anyway. It was good
to meet you.
[gasps]
[HINOMARU]
The sister of Shido Tennoji,
the national champion!
[SAKI]
I thought Ishigami was sure
to be the winning team
from Chiba,
but I learned something new.
All right, Onimaru Kunitsuna
from Odachi High.
Guess I'll see you at the top.
I'll be waiting.
Tennoji, Kuze, and Sada
from Ishigami.
Before I meet them in the ring,
I need to perfect
my new technique,
so I can beat them all!
[laughs]
-Check it out, Yuma.
-So?
Don't act like it's a big deal.
They're for sale.
-[HINOMARU] What do you think?
-Hmm?
The only thing shirts do
is cover up sweet muscles.
-Aww!
-Oh. Hey.
A Shibakiyama T-shirt.
So cool.
I'd love one of those.
-[HINOMARU crying] Captain!
-Huh? Okay.