[BATO]
I have to grab his belt!
[YUMA]
Lower block.
Reverse strike.
Joint strikes.
Inside leg trip.
Partial Lunge
Castle Break Punch!
There's still fire in his eyes.
-No.
-[grunting]
[YUMA]
Trust the team. Trust them.
And never stop fighting.
You can do it, Yuma.
[YUMA] Keep hitting
till your arms fall off.
Hear me?
Put it all on the line!
Everything!
[grunting]
Keep striking, Yuma.
Take him down!
[grunts]
♪
[YUMA panting]
[REFEREE]
East side wins!
♪
They actually did it.
They came back from the brink.
[SADA]
That's two for Dachi.
They're tied.
[KANAMORI]
Which means the tournament's
going to the fifth bout.
[ANNOUNCER] Gojo wins by pushing
his opponent out of the ring.
-[panting]
-[CROWD cheering]
-[footsteps approaching]
-[gasps]
Hail the king of the ring!
The what?
You just took down
a would-be national treasure!
You're insane, dude.
You did it.
-[chuckles softly]
-[gasps]
♪
[YUMA]
Today, I feel one step closer
to earning forgiveness.
[BOTH]
Yeah!
[BOTH laugh]
[laughs]
[ALL crying]
♪
Gojo was amazing, wasn't he?
I wish we were down there,
so we could celebrate with them.
[REINA sobbing]
[REINA]
I'm so proud of you, Yuma.
But it's not over yet.
Thanks to my brother
and the rest of the team,
it's his turn.
Hinomaru gets a second chance.
[AUDIENCE applauding]
-Huh?
[groaning]
Bato.
He must be devastated.
You could see it
when he bested Gojo in strikes.
On paper, he was clearly
the stronger wrestler.
This was supposed to be
an easy win.
Stats don't determine who wins.
When it came time,
Gojo didn't hesitate
to use every ace
up his sleeve.
He caught Bato off-guard
over and over again.
And then there was
that final barrage.
He was putting
every ounce of energy he had
into those strikes.
But if you want
the basic reason Bato lost,
it's because this bout was
just a pit stop on his journey.
But to Gojo,
it meant everything.
I failed you, boss!
[TENNOJI] What's with
all the doom and gloom?
You're acting like
we've already lost the match.
If you've gotta
blame someone, blame me.
It's my fault for losing
to Kusanagi earlier.
[ALL gasp]
I could tell you were worried
about how I'd handle
being defeated.
But after seeing
how motivated you were
to give me a second chance,
I feel reinvigorated.
You all did great sumo
out there.
All of us?
What bouts were you watching?
I was a complete mess.
I saw you fight,
and, yeah, you may have lost,
but you made it look good.
I've caused you
the most trouble.
Haven't I, Aki?
[grunts]
[TENNOJI]
And why are you crying, Bato?
Knock it off.
This isn't the singles match,
so hold your head high
until all the bouts
are completed.
You belong to the legendary
Hakuro High sumo team.
Losing will never change that.
[gasps]
Sir!
Did you hear me?
I want all of you
to stop looking so miserable,
and get fired up
for the fifth bout!
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL]
Hakuro! Hakuro! Hakuro! Hakuro!
That's right.
They may have tied the score,
but Hakuro's captain is up next.
Despite losing to Kusanagi,
he's still acting
just like a yokozuna.
There are people
that'll see his display
and get the wrong idea.
That it's just empty bravado
or he's got an inflated ego.
-[CROWD] Hakuro! Hakuro!
-Let 'em.
He understands
his responsibility.
He's giving the crowd
what they wanna see.
[CROWD]
Hakuro! Hakuro!
Once he steps foot
inside the sumo ring
nothing will stand in his way.
And the intensity he kept
in check will be unleashed.
[TENNOJI]
I regret how I approached
my bout with Kusanagi.
I went in feeling
like I was the underdog.
No matter
what anyone else says,
I'm the greatest high school
sumo wrestler alive.
I'm the yokozuna.
And I won't lose again.
[ALL gasp]
[HINOMARU]
Don't hold back.
I came here
to defeat a yokozuna,
and that's what
I'm going to do!
♪
Listen, guys, thank you.
I'm only standing here now
because of your efforts.
No, not just my team's.
There are so many people
who helped me.
I'm indebted to them.
-In that case, you better win.
-Agreed.
Losing's not an option.
Ushio! Win this!
Yeah!
Someone who wants
to be a yokozuna
can't afford to lose twice.
But above all,
they worked hard
to give me a second chance,
and I'm not about to waste it!
[ANNOUNCER]
Fifth bout.
On the east side, Ushio.
On the west side, Tennoji.
Hinomaru lost to him
only a couple of days ago.
Could anything have drastically
changed in that amount of time?
You should know.
Sumo wrestlers
live in the moment,
and all they need
is a moment to transform.
[HINOMARU]
I can tell,
you're different
from the last time we fought.
[REFEREE]
Hands on the ground.
[HINOMARU] Which means
I'll have to transform myself!
That's way low.
He's almost at ground level.
[TENNOJI]
We're in the same boat here.
Each of us lost
an important bout.
Which is why I can't
take this one lightly.
I know your body is also
surging with this power.
The will to make a comeback.
[SAKI groans softly]
[shudders]
♪
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
[HINOMARU]
A forearm charge? Not this time!
-[gasps]
-Got it!
[HINOMARU]
Right arm lock?
Don't think so!
No stopping! Press forward!
Demon Wheel!
He knew.
[grunts]
[TENNOJI]
Left arm latch-on.
[REINA]
He's trapped!
[SAKI gasps]
He let go of his belt!
[HINOMARU]
Arm throw!
[TENNOJI] You think I didn't
research that move too?
Arm-lock twist down!
[HINOMARU] Well, do you know
about this one?!
Damn. They're fast.
Of course.
They understand more
about who they're facing now.
[HINOMARU]
Try this on for size!
Hinomaru idolized him
and crafted his style
of sumo after his.
[TENNOJI]
Show me something new.
Nothing gets past Tennoji.
He disarms his opponents
of every weapon they've got.
They're familiar with
each other's special moves.
Constantly reading
what the other's about to do
and canceling out the strategy.
At the rate's it's going,
it's obvious who'll win.
[laughs]
[gasps]
[SHIBAKIYAMA] He keeps getting
pushed further and further back.
When you factor in
the number of battles
each has fought
at the top level
and experience,
Hinomaru will be the first
to run out of moves.
Hang in there, kid.
[HINOMARU]
He's incredible.
I'm being eaten alive.
So this is the beast
Sosuke awakened.
Tennoji's true form.
[SHUNKAI]
Behold the shadow
that blots out
an opponent's light.
This is the dark carnage
of battle.
Hinomaru!
[HINOMARU]
Tennoji can even anticipate
his opponent's growth,
and then counter it.
If that's the case,
I've got one option.
I need to outperform
his expectations!
[TENNOJI]
What is this?
Your intensity, it's gone.
[REINA]
He's getting pummeled.
-Yeah!
-Go!
[SAKI] Ushio almost always
goes for an all-out offensive.
This isn't like him.
My brother's already countered
every one of his moves.
There's only a single way
he can win.
Grab his belt,
knock him off balance,
then use the Hundred-Thousand
Demon Takedown.
But the mawashi
is too low for him.
He can't reach it.
Then there's the low strike
Tennoji used against Kusanagi.
Good luck bypassing it
and getting close enough
to grab on with both hands.
[TENMA] The greatest weapon
you have is about to be stolen.
What now?
Will you let it swallow you up?
The darkness?
[TENNOJI]
No way.
[TENMA gasps]
Hey.
Why'd he pull back?
[TENNOJI] That was
a grave mistake, Hinomaru.
You just acknowledged
this is as far as you can go
fighting me head-on
with your physique.
The reason you made it here
is because
you never accepted that before.
You retreated like a coward.
It's unacceptable!
[KARIYA] Was Tennoji's intensity
too much for you?
You were supposed
to show me the path
I didn't have
the courage to take.
Why would you run away now?!
No. He isn't.
His heart's
still in the fight.
Hinomaru hasn't stopped
moving forward.
He only stepped back so he could
take a more powerful leap.
[HINOMARU]
I lost because I was weak.
I used my strength
but didn't realize
that wasn't enough.
Defeat taught me
something valuable.
That I didn't get to be
where I am by myself!
[gasps]
[REINA]
Isn't that...
[HINOMARU]
There's Yuma, raining strikes
on me every practice.
And, man, do they hurt!
A lunge punch?
[TENNOJI]
What was that?
A leap.
No. He bluffed.
[HINOMARU]
Then there's your reverse, Kei.
It nearly fools me every time,
even when I'm expecting it.
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
He's always practiced
varying up his attacks.
Mixing strong and weak moves.
But never like this.
Pulling back gave him more room
to launch an attack.
[grunts]
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
His head-on approach
is shining brighter than ever.
[SAKI] With such a wide variety
of attacks,
my brother can't predict
what'll come next.
[SHUNKAI] To him, his sumo
represents a way of life.
If he thought at any time
retreating was the answer,
the flame inside of him
would extinguish.
Sumo.
His way of life.
And his resolve.
Each one contributes
to the fire in his eye.
That demonic,
enduring determination!
[HINOMARU grunts]
Hundred-Thousand Demon Drop!
♪
[HINOMARU] I used to think
being fifth on the roster
meant never showing weakness
in front of my teammates.
That I needed to be strong
all the time.
To assume the role of leader,
because I was best suited.
And if I ever stopped
moving forward,
they wouldn't be able
to continue either.
That's what I thought.
And I was so wrong.
After I lost,
I could see it clearly.
My teammates marching forward,
steady and strong.
If you think
that's all I've got,
you haven't seen anything yet!
My body has the sumo
of my entire team inside of it.
Like Chihiro's freestyle!
[chuckles]
Backward hook body drop!
A falling technique!
[SHUNKAI] Throwing and pushing
side-to-side,
followed by a pullback and fall.
Even Tennoji couldn't
anticipate that.
Take him down!
Don't quit now!
[grunts]
[HINOMARU gasps]
Do you know why
out of all the schools
I chose Tottori Hakuro?
Every day I get
to face specialists
with a wide array of techniques,
which means I'm ready
for anything
an opponent can throw at me.
You're not the only person
who's stronger
because of his teammates.
[grunts]
[TENNOJI] So try outperforming
my expectations all you'd like.
It'll end the same way
every time.
Nobody compares to me!
My team has made me
the best sumo wrestler around!
[grunting]
[HINOMARU] You noticed something
about our first bout?
Yeah. I'm not certain
how useful it'll be,
but I compared it
to your other matches
and it stood out.
Take a look.
Right there.
[HINOMARU]
Can't get overwhelmed.
Keep on attacking.
Reverse Hundred Demon Takedown!
Keep it up.
Knock him off balance.
Don't stop till you win.
Hundred-Thousand Demon Takedown!
You did the Hundred-Thousand
Demon Drop,
after the push, which ended up
weakening the centrifugal force.
Meaning this move wasn't
executed at full-strength.
Basically, the more you're able
to shake him side-to-side--
It has more power.
Keep going.
Make Tennoji lose his footing!
Swirl around him
like an inferno!
Reverse Hundred-Thousand
Demon Drop!
♪
[REINA sighs]
Hori's something else.
What a manager.
What?
Technically we have
the same role,
but she always finds a way
to help you guys
be more successful.
I'm completely useless.
[HINOMARU chuckles]
[HINOMARU]
You're wrong about that.
[REINA]
What?
[gasps]
[TENNOJI grunting]
[HINOMARU]
See this technique?
Kirihito.
The Shibakiyama Stable guys.
The Masters, both of them.
My rivals.
My team.
You got this! Yeah!
[HINOMARU] And you, Reina.
You all helped me complete it.
Tennoji, you're godlike.
And I never could've
defeated you alone.
But we're not alone anymore.
Are we, Captain?
Let him have it, Ushio!
[HINOMARU]
Here's goes everything I've got!
Demon's Enduring Determination!
Hundred-Thousand Demon Drop!
Go!
Drop him!
[groans sharply]
[HINOMARU]
Something's wrong!
[TENNOJI grunts]
[HINOMARU] Even now,
with everything on the line,
you're smiling.
[TENNOJI]
Kusanagi already beat me.
Which means I'm no longer
a champion.
But still,
I am the captain of the greatest
high school sumo team.
I can't afford to be weak.
You won't stop me from smiling,
even when
I'm on the brink of death.
I'm taking my team to the top
no matter the price!
[SHUNKAI] He still had
enough strength to use a throw.
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
What sheer grit.
[groaning]
[HINOMARU]
Just as expected.
You're incredible.
[CHIZUKO]
His left arm's locked.
[KEI]
Is this it?
[REINA] Even if you've
reached your limit,
you still have
your greatest weapon.
Your determination.
It may look bad.
Doesn't matter.
You never bend!
That's your style of fighting.
Your Hinomaru Sumo!
[grunts]
[HINOMARU]
I'm glad I idolized you.
The reason I came this far
wasn't just my team.
There was something else.
I've been chasing
after a colossus,
and his name
is Shido Tennoji.
I don't know
if I've conquered that mountain.
It's very possible
you're still stronger than me.
But I'm okay with that.
Everyone got me here today.
This is it.
I have to come out victorious!
Even if it kills me!
[gasps]
[ALL cheering]
♪
[grunts]
[yelling]
Yeah!
[gasping]
[SHUNKAI] It's considered
bad form to shout
or do a victory pose
in the ring.
But this time,
an exception can be made.
This wasn't just any victory.
Not by a long shot.
[ANNOUNCER]
Odachi on the east side wins.
Three-two.
Did Dachi High really
just make it to the final round
in their first
national tournament?
They beat Tennoji
and took down the Hakuro team.
[TENNOJI panting]
[gasps]
Good work out there.
Let's go.
The third place spot's
calling our name.
Hmm.
Do me a favor, you idiots.
Don't put on a brave face.
Not for my sake.
When you're disappointed,
show it.
Etch it into your heart.
Because one day, that feeling
will become your strength.
[AUDIENCE applauding]
[TENNOJI]
I let you down, too.
I couldn't make you the manager
of the best team in Japan.
Stop worrying about me.
For once in your life,
try to focus
on your own feelings
for a change.
[TENNOJI]
My own feelings, huh?
Hinomaru struck a victory pose.
But that's fine.
After all, you beat me.
I'd be disappointed
if you didn't show any emotion.
The score is now one-all.
We'll have our decider
in the pro league.
You better win.
A lot of people
are rooting for you.
Don't let them down.
♪
[YOMODA sighs]
The crowd's still energized
over that last bout.
Hakuro High losing.
I mean, who could've
ever predicted that?
[laughs]
Doesn't matter.
It's over, move on.
If they want more,
then we'll happily give them
a battle the likes of which
they've never seen.
So without further delay,
gentlemen,
how about we show 'em
what the cream of Eiga High
has to offer up?
♪
See that?
Even when he's outside the ring,
he's intimidating.
That's because he doesn't
have any eyebrows.
-Says who?
-[REINA and CHIZUKO gasp]
Watch this. Ta-da.
-Uh...
They've been here
the whole time.
Well?
Yeah. Neat.