♪
[HINOMARU]
Don't move sideways!
Forward!
[BOTH grunt]
[CHIHIRO]
Another strike!
[HINOMARU] I can see
my goal in front of me!
An adversary, on the cusp
of turning yokozuna!
I'm willing to risk everything,
even my life, for victory!
Heads together.
Both hands on your belt.
I can see the end,
and this technique
will get me there!
[KUZE]
I see what you're doing,
and I won't give you
a chance to start.
This right overhand grip
was taught to me by my father.
It defines my destiny.
[HINOMARU]
Don't hesitate.
[KUZE]
Just one error.
[BOTH]
And I'll lose!
[CROWD cheering]
[grunts]
[straining]
They're equals.
Deadlock.
Neither can move.
[KUZE] My father
once told me something.
Yokozunas are solitary.
There's no one ahead of them.
No signs.
Nothing to serve as a guide.
[ANNOUNCER on TV]
And he's forced out!
The yokozuna has been defeated!
Kaoruyama scores a major upset
by forcing his opponent out!
He lost?
Your poor dad.
[KUZE] Whether he was
victorious or not,
he never showed emotion.
Still, I could sense
the bloodlust in him,
and it unnerved me.
I strove to be a good son.
So I'd never interfere
with his competitions.
As for sumo,
my father neither encouraged
nor discouraged me
from participating.
Perhaps I followed
in his footsteps
only as a means of showing
the respect I had for him.
I knew the path
wouldn't be easy.
Even when he was
bruised and beaten,
he continued fighting.
As the son of a yokozuna,
I knew people
treated me differently.
It was my duty to follow
in my father's footsteps.
To honor his name
and reach his title.
I had to transform,
to become stronger.
As I chased after my goal,
I never once viewed sumo
as something I should enjoy.
♪
You're stopping now?
[MAN 1] That boy puts
the others to shame.
Did you see how stoic he is?
[MAN 2] Must be
the yokozuna blood in him.
He's not the same
as the rest of us.
Makes me jealous.
[KUZE]
Right.
This must be the solitude
my father spoke of.
Which means I must be following
the right path.
Even if no one else understands,
even if I have to go it alone,
I'll seek what
my father attained.
A state of a yokozuna.
[YAMATOKUNI]
Those who run ahead of the pack
are solitary.
But look to your side.
There are others
running with you.
Rivals who share
the same determination.
Striving to reach
that same solitary state.
♪
[KUZE]
Ushio.
I'm grateful for you.
It was by my own will I decided
to fight you that day.
I could see your soul, burning,
screaming to make itself known.
At that moment,
we fought at full strength.
Just like now.
[KUZE'S MOTHER]
His face.
He's smiling.
[MAN 3] Excuse me, ma'am.
Are you all right?
Yes. I'm fine.
It would disrespectful
of me to look away.
After all, I've been the wife
of a yokozuna
for many years now.
As a mother, it's an honor to
see how much my son has grown.
[HINOMARU'S GRANDMOTHER]
Hinomaru! Don't back down!
Your mother's watching!
[straining]
Hinomaru can't afford
to just maintain his grip.
The difference in size
will wear him down first.
He's still tired
from the semifinal bout,
and there's his left arm.
The longer this goes on,
the less his chances of winning.
[HINOMARU]
Can I keep this up?
His power's incredible.
Hurts so much,
I can barely breathe.
I need to do something,
but what?
[groaning]
[HINOMARU'S MOTHER]
Why is it you're doing sumo?
[gasps]
[HINOMARU'S GRANDMOTHER]
Another loss, I'm afraid.
Such a shame.
He did so well
in elementary school.
[HINOMARU'S MOTHER]
It's because of his height.
Huh?
[HINOMARU'S MOTHER]
He's a good boy,
so he'll never even think it.
But his late father
and I are to blame.
We're the reason he's short.
I'm sorry I couldn't give you
a bigger body, my son.
♪
[HINOMARU]
Winning at sumo was a rush.
My mom was my biggest fan.
She loved seeing me win
more than I did.
She acted so brave
even when she was sick.
It made me want to please her
even more.
It's all for her.
Still is,
even though she's gone.
[HINOMARU'S MOTHER]
No.
Try to remember further back.
Why are you doing sumo,
Hinomaru?
[ANNOUNCER] Entering the
sumo ring from the east side:
Yokozuna Yamatokuni.
[CROWD]
Yokozuna!
Bet you want to be
just like Yamatokuni.
That's why everyone else
signed up.
We're learning sumo
so we can be as cool as him!
[HINOMARU]
That's not why I joined.
I want something different.
[BOTH straining]
Here it comes, Hinomaru!
[straining]
♪
[KUZE]
Great Serpent Cleaver!
♪
[grunts]
[HINOMARU grunts]
[gasps]
♪
[HINOMARU] There's no
one reason why I'm here.
That's not why I joined,
if you want to know.
After watching him,
I thought about how fun it'd be
to throw
a giant yokozuna like that.
My initial motivation,
the feeling of losing,
other's expectations,
the time with my teammates,
and for the memory of my mother!
He's on fire.
[HINOMARU]
The reason I'm here
is 'cause I love sumo!
Is Hinomaru actually smiling
during a bout?
♪
Hmm?
[grunting]
This is your shot, kid!
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
Close the gap!
When his upper body's extended,
come up from beneath!
[HINOMARU yelling]
[ALL]
Push him!
[gasps]
[HINOMARU grunting]
He's almost there!
[SHUNKAI]
It can only happen in a sport
with no weight class.
The smaller contender rises
and invigorates the crowd!
[grunts]
[SHIBAKIYAMA] He pulled back
right at the edge of the ring!
[YAMATOKUNI]
His spirit can't be contained
within such a small frame.
This national treasure,
he's the future of sumo.
But Sosuke is no different.
♪
[YAMATOKUNI]
Witnessing size, speed,
and unfathomable
physical strength
is a large part
of sumo's appeal.
That's a left underarm grip.
[KUZE] Think you've seen
everything? No.
The sumo my father and I share
is so much more.
And you're about to witness it!
[yelling]
True Great Serpent Cleaver!
[HINOMARU]
Reverse Hundred Demon Takedown!
They're throwing each other!
Hinomaru was ready for it.
[SHUNKAI]
He saw that coming.
[HINOMARU]
I figured you'd try to counter.
Only because I believe
in your strength!
[CROWD cheering]
[straining]
Hori.
-I owe you.
-Huh?
I realize if it weren't for you,
then I probably
wouldn't be here.
When it came to sumo,
I didn't know anything.
I made fun of the sport
because I didn't understand it.
But when I'm this close,
there's nothing else like it.
The sound those
carefully sculpted bodies make
every time they crash,
it's glorious.
In a single moment, they execute
countless maneuvers.
I used to think the belt thing
was embarrassing,
but I'm starting to appreciate
the aesthetic behind it.
The more I learn about sumo,
the more I learn about him.
Just how strong he is.
No matter how many times
he's knocked back,
he keeps pushing forward.
It entertains the crowds
and captures their hearts!
-It's love.
-[CHIZUKO gasps]
[grunts]
For his style.
It's love for Hinomaru's sumo.
[KUZE]
Is this it?
I'm losing?
♪
[KUZE]
I refuse to.
I need to stop him.
Shake him back and forth!
♪
[KUZE]
Am I'm actually fighting one?
A serious sumo bout!
♪
I feel so close to death,
it's exhilarating.
Finally, my limits
are being tested.
In order to beat him,
I have to transcend.
I can't simply imitate
my father anymore.
I have to surpass him!
I must surpass a god!
Don't fall!
Stay strong, bro!
[grunting]
[YAMATOKUNI] There's no
forethought behind his actions.
He has something that can't
be taught in a training hall.
This is pure instinct!
I get it.
So this is what it means
to drive each other higher.
[KUZE]
Pulling Body Slam!
God Body Hammer!
[gasps]
An illusion?
He only feels like a giant.
[HINOMARU]
I've had to worry more
and work harder
than everybody
because of how small I am.
I've lived, breathed,
and dreamt about this sport.
Thing is, because of my body,
I've been able to enjoy sumo
more than anyone.
Mom, thank you for it.
[grunts]
♪
[KIRIHITO]
His arm.
[YUMA]
He hit his limit?
[CHIHIRO]
Don't crap out now!
[KEI]
No. Not yet. Of all times.
[SHIBAKIYAMA] If this happens,
I'll never forgive
the gods of sumo!
[yelling]
[HINOMARU] This body's overcome
every obstacle
that stood in its way.
And I'm proud of it!
If the gods of sumo disagree,
I'll throw them down too!
Go, Ushio!
Take him out!
Right underarm throw!
Demon Wheel!
♪
Take him out, Ushio!
Let's do this!
[chuckles]
[HINOMARU]
The name's Hinomaru Ushio.
My dream is to become
a yokozuna,
but first I need to be
the best high school wrestler
there is.
[KUZE grunts]
[SOBBING softly]
-[REFEREE] East side wins!
-[cheering]
-[CROWD cheering]
-[whooping and laughter]
Listen to that
thunderous applause.
Yeah, but what's even
more beautiful
is the sight
of cascading cushions.
[REINA crying]
♪
[panting]
[YAMATOKUNI]
I'm glad it was him
who defeated my son.
I knew he would experience
defeat someday.
Now I can see what he'll do
the next time it happens,
and how he'll win instead.
♪
[CROWD applauding]
We can go.
♪
[applause continues]
You really did it, Hinomaru.
Wherever she is,
I'm sure your mother
can hear the applause.
[HINOMARU]
If I'd gone alone,
I never would've made it
to this point.
I've been blessed
with strong opponents
and mentors who tested me.
♪
And, of course,
I can't forget my teammates
and all of their support.
[HINOMARU MOTHER] When
your dream finally comes true,
I may not be there in person
to celebrate with you.
But I promise,
I'll be smiling down
on you from above.
My dream hasn't
come true yet, but...
[NARRATOR]
Sumo.
Since ancient times,
warriors clad in mawashi belts
have waged battles
within the ring.
[REFEREE]
Bow.
[NARRATOR] It is one
of the few combat sports
without weight classes.
Thus, student wrestlers who are
heavier and larger in stature
have a distinct advantage.
Among those giants,
there was one who desired
to become a yokozuna
more than anything.
Though his body was small,
it was sturdy.
And above all...
East side wins!
[CROWD cheers]
[NARRATOR]
...dignified.
[ANNOUNCER] That concludes
the team tournament.
Odachi High School wins,
three-two.
I just want to say,
I'm so proud
-of all of you!
-[HINOMARU] What?
[REINA] I'm only crying
‘cause you started it!
Yeah, but I stopped.
[REINA] Yuma, you're the best
in Japan too.
Thanks.
[OZEKI] This used to be
a one-man sumo club.
Now we're the top
high school team in Japan.
I...
[sobbing]
I just wanted...
Seriously,
I can't thank you guys enough!
[CHIHIRO chuckles]
[CHIZUKO]
That's right.
They won't compete
as a team ever again.
And now, we wait to see
if Hinomaru's going
to the All-Japan Championship.
Yep.
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
Nothing to worry about.
[KIRIHITO]
It's been decided?
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
He did his part.
No way they won't take him
after all that cheering.
-Right?
-Huh?
It's him!
Master Yamatokuni!
How long has it been?
Three years?
I'm honored
you remember me, sir.
"Practice for three years
from now."
Your words were an encouragement
and allowed me
to endure until today.
I'm in your debt.
-It should be me thanking you.
-[HINOMARU] Huh?
After watching your team,
I know the future of sumo's
in good hands.
The pro league is very fortunate
to have you aboard.
Here's a bit of advice
if you want
to maintain
the same diligence.
Go practice for three years
from now,
Hinomaru Ushio.
You better not tell me
you're staying at Eiga
because you lost
the team tournament.
Trust in us.
We'll win next year.
You've got to keep
moving forward.
[scoffs]
[KUZE]
I feel disappointed.
Huh?
It may be the only time
I get the opportunity
to experience
this kind of emotion.
To lose with teammates.
I'm glad I came to Eiga.
Yeah.
[ANNOUNCER] We're proud
to present this year's
National High School Sumo Team
Tournament champions.
From Chiba,
Odachi High School!
[CROWD cheering]
[OZEKI]
Everyone,
thank you for your support!
[CHIZUKO]
Ushio went on to compete
in the All-Japan Championships.
However, he lost
in the semifinal
and took third place.
His opponent, Tennoji,
was the champion,
earning the right to become
a fifteenth-ranked makushita.
Wish your arm was fully healed
for our bout,
but, hey, a win's a win.
The count's two to one now.
With me leading.
Get used to us trading victories
and losses from now on.
Don't forget, I'm a makushita.
Still though,
sandanme's not bad.
Congrats.
Glad to have you.
Same.
[CHIZUKO]
After the Inter-High concluded,
Kuze entered the pro league.
He joined in time to compete
in the tournament
that September.
While you're only a sandanme,
you don't have to worry
about size anymore.
The first step to attaining
your dream is done.
You're in
the professional league now.
Welcome.
Thank you, Master.
[CHIZUKO]
But...
Ushio could only earn
his spot for one year.
If he wanted to keep it,
he would be forced to drop
out of high school.
And by extension,
that meant saying farewell
to the Odachi High School
sumo club for good.
We're proud.
Ushio is a talented student
and athlete
who'll go far in life!
And his school will be cheering
him every step of the way.
[laughs]
I'll do my best.
[HINOMARU groans]
[SHIBAKIYAMA laughs]
Exhausted?
It's gonna take a while
before you settle
into the swing of things.
It'll be even more difficult
once you're in the pro league.
I know I don't need
to sugar-coat the truth,
but your height's
gonna make you stand out.
[HINOMARU] Yes, sir.
I'm on the same page.
I also realize the attention
can be fleeting.
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
Hmm.
Honestly, it's been like
a whirlwind up till today.
The captain and Yuma
are studying for exams,
and the others are off training
or busy living their lives.
It's a shame I wasn't able
to give them a proper goodbye.
I hope they understand.
Why am I worried?
I'll do well in the pro league.
That'll be my way
of showing them how I feel.
Just gotta grab my sandals.
Huh?
What you got there?
That a love letter?
The next best thing.
Excuse me!
I've gotta take care
of something!
♪
[panting]
Uh!
The captain's sumo ring!
It's been totally rebuilt!
[YUMA] Thanks to Ozeki's
step-by-step instructions.
Hmm?
[YUMA]
Still was a pain, though.
I never stopped feeling guilty
about it getting destroyed.
I'm glad it's finally back.
Before you go gallivanting off,
help me break it in.
-[KEI] Just to be sure...
-Huh?
[KEI]
...we're not training.
We're doing this for real.
[CHIHIRO]
You better believe it!
[KIRIHITO]
There's no point otherwise.
This is our farewell present.
Showing you the sumo club's
serious style you helped create.
Think you can handle it?
[chuckles]
You guys.
This entire team's crazy.
It's way too cold outside
for sumo.
[chuckles]
[HINOMARU]
Maybe for anyone else.
But we're not like everybody!
All right!
Who's ready to go first!