[YUMA]
Anyone seen Hinomaru?
[OZEKI]
Yeah.
The doc called him and the Coach
into the back office.
-It's pretty amazing.
-Hmm?
Us. Actually winning.
We did it.
We brought down Hakuro.
Dachi beat Hakuro!
The strongest club
in high school sumo!
[cheering]
You started off your fight
like a bad-ass!
Man, it got me so pumped up!
Just walking away
from that gorilla like that.
Stop it.
I lost my bout.
What about you, Kunisaki?
That makes two national
treasures you've conquered!
[CHIHIRO]
I know, right?
I've been on one hell
of a winning streak!
Not saying I'm even interested,
but what if they choose me
to go to the All-Japan?
I'm so good, I scare myself!
Not again!
Stupid nosebleeds.
-Here.
-Good timing!
Tsuruko with the save!
My name's Chizuko.
How are all you guys
joking around?
I put every ounce of energy
I had into that last bout.
You did great, by the way.
Even with all that pressure,
you took care of things.
Don't act like you weren't
partly to blame.
Huh?
[YUMA]
When you lost your match,
I thought my heart was gonna
burst out of my chest.
[OZEKI laughs]
It motivated you though.
[REINA]
I know I should be overjoyed
at what we've accomplished
and busy celebrating our victory
with the rest of the team.
But why do I feel so uneasy?
Yeah. We really did it.
Made it all the way
to the final
and achieved our biggest goal.
Giving Hinomaru a chance
to face Kuze in the ring.
It doesn't matter if we lose
as a team at this point.
As long as he can take
the fifth bout,
his dream of going pro
is still a possibility.
Hell, so what if we lose?
We're still silver.
Second place at our first
national tournament!
Sorry, second place?
We've already beat
the strongest team!
Eiga's gonna be a cake walk
compared to Hakuro!
What're you...
[REINA]
That's it.
I know what's wrong.
-They're slacking.
-[YUMA grunts]
Gah!
You're all acting like the
tournament's already finished!
Are you forgetting?
Hinomaru's got a lot
of battles left to fight!
So what's this talk about
how losing doesn't matter
or how easy
it will be to win?
You can't just sit back
and relax now!
Know why Hinomaru
defeated Tennoji?
Because he saw how hard
you guys fought for him!
That's where he gets
his strength!
And Kuze, he's an even
stronger opponent.
I'm not sure if even
Hinomaru can beat him.
So fight!
And don't settle!
Try your hardest to win,
if not for yourselves,
then for him!
[ALL groan]
Uh... Yeah.
I mean...
Why'd you open your mouth?
But obviously,
I'm not in the ring
and it's not my place
to criticize anyone.
So, um, good work
and I'm sorry for ranting.
-[OZEKI] No.
-Huh?
You were absolutely right
to speak up.
Thanks for telling them what
I should've said as captain.
It probably slipped our minds.
Ushio lost in
the individual tournament,
so even if he beats Kuze,
he may not get invited
to the All-Japan
National Championships.
We need to do all we can
to increase his chances,
even if it's only
by a small amount.
We'll make Dachi High
the top team in Japan!
And help Ushio become
the number one wrestler
from the best school
in the country!
It won't be just
for his sake, either.
I know, our team has
the potential
to be the best there is!
Win or lose,
this is our final match!
Guys.
Let's go and make
that dream real!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[HINOMARU]
Um, how much of that
did you hear?
Ha, ha, ha.
[HINOMARU] It's the last time
this team will fight together.
Know what I think?
We've got what it takes.
♪
We'll be the best in Japan!
Hands on the ground!
Spirit!
[BOTH grunting]
Pure railroad tracks.
That was quick.
These are the semis, right?
[sighs]
Pff!
[grunts]
The second bout
didn't last long either.
Same for the third.
And the fourth.
Four straight
railroad track wins.
No surprise.
They're huge.
♪
[gasps]
Aah!
-[REFEREE] Spirit!
-[KUZE growls]
[screams]
The bout is concluded!
[CROWD cheers]
He was so intimidated,
he retreated out of the ring.
The ol' stare-out.
Centuries ago, that used to be
the way you determined
the winner.
They were outmatched.
You can only pity them.
He's not even in the same realm
as high school sumo anymore.
♪
Well, if it isn't
this year's dark horse.
[OZEKI] Back when we trained
with them before,
we didn't stand a chance.
I had no idea we'd be fighting
their team in the final!
Meeting again face-to-face,
I'm reminded how huge they are.
It's been far too long, Chihiro.
Sorry I missed you
that one time we practiced.
But maybe your heart's more
into academics than sumo, huh?
Come on, I'm just messin'
with ya!
You and me,
we're all good, right?
I mean, you took up sumo.
Why else would you,
unless you looked up to me?
Me getting into sumo had zero
to do with you, got it?
My hate for you burns
like the sun.
And I'll keep hating you
until you die.
[OZEKI] Well, they seem
to know each other.
Maybe they're like friends?
-[DANIEL] Calm down, everyone.
-Huh?
There's no need for us
to be aggressive.
The way I see it, sumo is more
of a beautiful endeavor
and less of a fight.
Leon, you agree, right?
Dude, are you insane?
Sumo is nothing but fighting!
I swear, if you say beautiful
one more time!
Whatever our
personal philosophies are,
let's save it
for the bouts, cool?
[HYODO]
Just one last thing, Odachi.
Looks like you're one man short.
Can we expect to see that runt
Mitsuhashi in the final?
[SAWAI]
Fat chance of that happening.
The twig didn't know his limits
and got snapped.
He had it coming.
He needs to accept
the hard truth.
Sumo wrestlers have to be big,
heavy, and larger
than life itself.
You'll understand what I mean
soon enough
after we meet each other
inside the ring.
Hold on a minute.
Hmm?
Do you actually believe
what you just said?
After all, you've seen
what our number five can do.
♪
There's something you don't get.
Sumo doesn't boil down to size
and weight alone.
It's about spirit.
♪
You ought to save that line
for later.
Like maybe after you've beaten
our number five.
♪
We don't hold back.
It's to the death, then.
His victory in the individual
tournament was hard-fought.
True.
♪
Quite the high school yokozuna
this year.
A national treasure
who also happens
to be the son
of the famous Yamatokuni.
There's so much going for him,
he may be ready
to move straight
into the pro league.
In other words,
this bout coming up
will be Hinomaru's
final opportunity
to compete with him
at the high school level.
The individual tournament
is done.
However, the strongest
sumo wrestler
has yet to be determined.
We'll find that out
in the team tournament final.
In the fifth and last bout.
Isn't that right, Hinomaru?
[grunting]
It's about time.
Let's get going.
[HINOMARU]
Ready!
Best of luck out there,
you guys.
-Yeah!
-We've got this!
And remember to have fun...
Hinomaru.
Oops. Was that not
the right thing to say?
Sorry if I broke
your concentration.
Um. I meant,
"good luck, Shorty!"
[CROWD cheering in distance]
[HINOMARU]
"Have fun." Huh.
Will do!
♪
[ANNOUNCER]
The team tournament final.
On the east side,
Odachi High School.
[CROWD cheers]
♪
[ANNOUNCER]
On the west side,
Eiga University High School.
[CROWD cheers]
It really happened.
Dachi's in the final round.
Yeah, maybe, but strategically,
Eiga's definitely got
the advantage.
You aren't wrong.
You've got two teams.
One that sailed through the
semi-finals without a scratch
and one that got totally
pummeled in the last round.
Plus, they've revealed
all their secret weapons.
This match will come down
to one factor.
The most spirit.
That's why they're gonna try
to hit the ground running.
♪
Go out and get us our first win!
[ANNOUNCER]
On the east side, Kunisaki.
[CROWD cheers]
All those adoring fans.
Such a crowd pleaser.
Isn't that right, Chihiro?
[ANNOUNCER]
On the west side, Hyodo.
[CROWD cheers]
Well.
I suppose beating
two national treasures
should count for something.
And so soon after joining sumo.
I'm impressed.
-Doesn't matter though.
-Huh?
[HYODO]
Let's be real, here.
You think you're gonna outshine
your older brother?
Dream on.
You're seriously telling us
Hyodo's your older brother?
The folks went through the whole
divorce thing when I was five.
Hyodo went off
to live with our father.
I hated the guy, so I decided
to stay with my mother.
Now he's back in my life again.
That jerk.
[mocking laughter]
My only memories of him
are of a pre-teen bully.
No one else.
It's going to be me
who takes him on!
I've waited too long for this!
♪
Place your hands on the ground!
The two brothers are similar.
Both have latent sumo talents
on par with a national treasure.
But like I said,
only on par with.
There's something specific
keeping him
from joining their ranks.
Hey, bro, gotta say.
I'm a real huge fan
of that Mitsuhashi kid.
That move he pulled
in the semi-finals,
it took brass balls!
There's a reason
he hasn't earned a moniker?
Yeah.
A big one.
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
[ALL gasp]
What?
[KIRIHITO]
He's an idiot.
So, what d'ya think, Chihiro?
Bet you're impressed.
Go ahead.
Lose your cool and charge at me.
I'll leap outta the way.
[screams]
He just stood there,
what the hell?
Hyodo, you are king
of the idiots!
Whoa! Whoa! Hold on!
He's tricky.
To the point, he ends up digging
his own grave occasionally.
-But...
-You dick!
I said wait!
That's how he's able
to take down opponents!
Strength and unpredictability!
It'd do you good to listen to
your older brother for a change.
You paying attention?
[KIRIHITO] The only one who can
fight an idiot of his caliber...
[CHIHIRO]
Leap!
[KIRIHITO]
...is another idiot!
[ALL gasp]
What the hell kinda bout
is this?
[CHIHIRO] He's always stealing
the things I love
and ruining them for me!
Huh?
You're taking up boxing now?
Hey, the two of us
should have a match.
-[HYODO grunts]
-[CHIHIRO groans]
-[bell dings]
-Oh, is it over already?
[CHIHIRO] He bulldozes my world,
then waltzes off!
Not this time!
Dachi High's dream
is to be the best in Japan!
You won't take that away!
Good idea.
Think I'll jump too!
What the...
He's mocking me!
♪
If you're not gonna let me
grab your belt, then...
Flash Attack!
You like that, bro?
-Masato Hyodo?
-Huh?
Is there a problem, Kunisaki?
Um, no.
So what about him?
He's been wrestling two years,
but in that short amount of time
he's already earned
a spot as a regular
on the Eiga High team.
This is from
the spring tournament.
As you can see, his technique
is highly unpredictable.
He's got power, speed,
and killer instincts.
All his stats are first-class.
It's your second year, huh?
Well, this is only my first!
-[CHIHIRO groaning]
-[HYODO laughing]
[CHIHIRO] You'd always take up
whatever sport I was into.
Outdo me, then quit!
But this time, it's my turn!
I've only done this one year
and already beaten
two national treasures!
[HYODO]
Hey, you're not half bad!
Whoa! Can't see.
[HYODO]
Down you go!
Inner foot sweep!
Remember, those are
my techniques
you're representing out there.
You'd better do them justice,
Kunisaki!
[CHIHIRO]
Damn. Spider monkey!
A leg grab, huh?
No good!
Got ya!
Yaaah!
Grab some dirt!
You're insane!
This is serious!
Quit screwing around!
It looks to me like
you're losing your cool!
Chihiro!
[CHIHIRO]
An overarm throw?
Did you see that, Ref?
Running away?
[BOTH grunting]
A test of strength!
Can you call what they're doing
sumo anymore?
Incredible!
[KIRIHITO]
What's going on?
You need to relax!
If you just regain focus,
you can win this bout easily!
Why'd you go and pinch me,
you cheating cheater?
It just popped into my head
so I had to try it!
Damn it.
Be serious for once in your...
Holy crap.
[HINOMARU]
This Hyodo guy's something else.
You can tell
how much he loves sumo.
[CHIHIRO] With all
his stupid running around,
it was hard to notice,
but up close, it's clear.
The brother who always used
to get bored
and walk away
has been working out,
transforming his body
into a sumo wrestler!
[sighs]
[YOMODA] Watching Hyodo fight
is giving me a coronary.
He'll defeat someone
twice as strong,
and then turn around
and lose to an easy opponent.
Makes it difficult to predict
how many bouts
you're going to win
during a team match.
Still, the guy only took up sumo
two years ago.
Back in those days,
he'd join a club,
make a scene, get kicked out.
Rinse and repeat.
Until he found ours.
He challenged us to a fight and
was knocked flat on his back.
So this is sumo wrestling, huh?
It's my kind of sport.
He's an idiot,
don't get me wrong.
Thing is...
the guy's in love with it.
His passion is so intense,
it makes you want to back off...
and just let him do his thing.
[straining]
[HYODO]
Chihiro,
do you love sumo?
Don't laugh, but I know I do.
I finally found
what was missing.
That thing in life
that makes me proud of who I am.
What about you?
What's your reason
for joining the club?
[CHIHIRO] It was the day
I lost to Hinomaru.
I wanted to learn
how he managed to beat me.
But I've kept telling myself
it's like wrestling.
Just another step
on my journey to being
the top mixed martial arts
fighter in the world.
Who do I think I am
compared to Hinomaru?
Or any of the other
national treasures?
Chihiro...
I see you out there
overthinking things.
Trust your feelings.
Yeah!
[CHIHIRO]
Know what?
My answer's the same!
[KIRIHITO]
He's changing tactics!
He lowered his head
and is charging in!
[BOTH grunt]
[CHIHIRO]
I love sumo!
[KIRIHITO]
He doesn't have sharp footwork
or shift techniques
like Hinomaru.
It's just a matter
of time before...
[CHIHIRO]
That's right.
I've never worked
on my headbutting.
I sidelined it to focus
on winning!
But I had to try,
even if the odds were slim!
It was that or run away
from sumo!
[BOTH straining]
Guys, I'm sorry.
I could've sworn you wanted
to be the strongest!
Fight back, Kunisaki!
You're the best improviser!
And the strongest in sumo!
So don't lose this!
[CHIHIRO]
Supreme! Invincible!
And the strongest!
Clasped hand twist drop throw!
Neo Chihiro Special Number Two!
I was wondering when you
were gonna try that!
Sorry to break it to you,
but you're not the only one
who knows both wrestling
and sumo techniques!
[ALL gasp]
[REFEREE]
West side wins!
[CROWD cheering]
Tss!
Going with the headbutt put him
at a pretty severe disadvantage.
Yeah.
When you break the teams
down by physiques.
Between Dachi and Eiga,
there's no competition.
I get that, but still.
There wasn't a huge difference
in size during the first bout.
Actually, what impressed me
the most
was how Hyodo handled
that last throw.
-Those two are so similar.
-[HYODO panting]
Maybe they each understood
what the other was about.
Well, looks like
I bested you again,
little brother.
I don't think I hate anyone
more than you.
You always ate my food,
used my save data
to beat my video games.
Oh, and let's not forget
about taking my allowance.
But what pisses me off
the most...
Is having to admit that you're
actually pretty strong.
Huh?
I'm not sure what
you're talking about,
but that match we had
was kick-ass! Right?
Yeah, I guess so.
Oh, man.
That was a big loss.
Their team must be in shock
after that.
-No doubt.
-You really think so?
You could've won that bout
if you didn't get so worked up.
Yeah, my bad.
I'm counting on you
to make it up.
During our practice sessions,
there were only two
Dachi High members
I could never beat.
One was Hinomaru.
And the second was...
[KIRIHITO] I wasn't expecting
to start with a loss.
Looks like I've no choice
but to adapt.
[ANNOUNCER]
Second bout.
On the east side, Tsuji.
-Morning!
-[KUZE] Hmm?
You and me!
Arm wrestling! Now!
Yeah, I don't arm wrestle.
-What's up!
-[KUZE] Hmm?
Me, you, thumb wrestlin'!
I don't really
thumb wrestle either.
So what kinda wrestling
do you do?
Hmm?
♪
[grunts]
Why didn't you tell me you were
an expert at this game?
What is this?