Yuma.
You ready to go home?
-[grunts]
-[KIRIHITO] Too slow!
Keep pace with the goldfish
as it turns.
They've gone crazy.
-Two, one.
-[OZEKI/KEI grunting]
-Okay, stop.
-[BOTH groan]
[KIRIHITO]
Hold the water in your mouth.
Now, Spirit!
Are these drills
or some form of mental torture?
That's just great.
Oh, Yuma.
What have they done to you?
[YUMA grunting softly]
I give up.
Slapping the ping pong ball
does what?
Watch.
I'm keeping my back straight
and using my legs
to stabilize my strikes.
Apparently,
it'll prevent opponents
from knocking me
to the ground.
Who told you that?
No, wait, don't answer.
I already know. Him.
Why're you even taking orders
from that guy?
He makes you do
these insane exercises
while he just sits on his ass
the whole time and watches.
[YUMA]
Yeah.
I'm sure it probably
looks that way
-to an outsider.
-Huh?
To be honest,
I don't like him much either.
But it's for an entirely
different reason.
When we've got our backs turned,
he sticks his neck out for us.
But, hey.
I figure what he chooses
to do on his own time
is his own business.
And I don't listen to anyone
I don't agree with.
Thing is...
[CHIHIRO] If I'm gonna pull off
advanced techniques,
I gotta master my footwork.
Need to force my body
to remember,
this is a different beast
than the wrestling I'm used to.
Watch the fish bowl
and imagine it's the sumo ring!
[OZEKI] Holding a mouthful
of water trains me
to finish a match
as quickly as I can
while holding my breath.
When you break it down,
the exercise makes total sense.
Everybody's thinking
the exact same thing.
More than half the team's
never done sumo before.
If we did training like
other teams of wrestlers,
we'd have zero chance
of becoming the best in Japan.
That's why we're taking
this route.
The drills may look bizarre,
but they're designed to help us
shake off anxieties
and hang-ups.
We're learning the guy
never explains things,
but it's not important.
As long as we feel it's right.
For me, my body's
telling me one thing.
If I follow him, ultimately,
I'll become stronger.
And does he feel the same way?
[grunts]
No, no.
Your movements
are becoming too erratic.
I mean, even your captain's
beating him.
This is supposed
to make him less anxious?
It is.
Take a look at his face.
One more time!
There's something
that I read a while back,
about how the best instructors
are the ones who are able
to instill a sense
of confidence in their athletes.
If that's true...
then he's a first-class coach.
[purrs]
[KIRIHITO] Okay, everyone.
Gather 'round.
As you probably know, it won't
be long until the tournament.
So, on our upcoming day off,
we're going to train
at Ishigami High School
in the next town over.
You think we're ready for that?
About time I get to show off
my sick moves again!
I might actually be able
to win a bout
if I'm up against
a first year.
[KIRIHITO] Ishigami's one
of the top sumo schools.
They came in second place
at last year's Kanto tournament.
Expect even their
first years to be strong.
Also...
national treasure
Mikazuki Munechika goes there.
He's the middle school yokozuna.
[BOTH]
The middle school yokozuna?
So that's where he ended up!
Sounds like a good opportunity
to try my new and improved
Hundred Demon Takedown.
-Hold up.
-Huh.
-You're going somewhere
entirely different.
-Hmm.
If you want to perfect
your new technique
in time
for the competition,
then you're going to need
to square off
with a wide range
of difficult opponents.
With that in mind,
I want you to head
to this address.
Hmm.
[motorcycle engine revving]
[KEI gasps]
This is Ishigami High?
Not to freak you guys out
or anything,
but everybody says this is
the most dangerous high school
in the entire prefecture.
Great. We finally get
a day off from school
and this place is where
we decide to spend it?
You keep acting like you're
being forced to come along.
Um, hey. Where's Kunisaki?
I thought he wanted
to show off?
[KIRIHITO] That musclehead
failed his midterms, surprise,
so he's having to take
a remedial class.
That sucks for him.
He was so psyched about coming.
[MAN] The hell do you think
you're doin'?
This is our turf.
[ALL clamoring]
Yeah! Looks like
we got fresh meat!
[whimpering]
Ooh-ooh!
I must be at a barbeque,
'cause you're smokin'!
-Why don't you ditch
these losers?
-Just try it.
We'll get you a matching uniform
and everyth--
[screams]
I'm gonna assume you were
only trying to shake her hand.
Cause you wouldn't mess
with a young lady, right?
Wouldn't dream of it!
I was keeping these trespassers
off school property!
[KIRIHITO]
Actually, we're only interested
in meeting with the sumo club.
I swear I didn't know!
In that case,
let me be the first
to welcome you.
Let's clear a path
for them, boys!
So you're a club
from a different school?
You've even got the
stereotypical cute manager.
Whoa. There's no way in hell
I'd manage these losers.
[GIRL]
It's him! It's Sada!
You're right!
He's a total snack.
Sorry, I can't give
you guys the tour,
but the dojo's that way.
You can't miss it.
Gotta run!
Every school you go to,
there's the nice guys
and the crazies.
[grunting]
Oh, man.
Hey, Coach.
Is this some kind of drill?
They're doing tire flips.
Very nice.
One that size probably
weighs around
150 kilograms.
Just flipping it over gives
your whole body a workout.
[KEI]
Huh? A hundred-fifty?
But training wise,
you have other options.
You can hit them with hammers
or simply push one
along the ground.
These guys are serious.
[KIRIHITO]
Just so you know,
everyone you see
working out here
is only a first-year.
[KEI whimpers]
With bodies like those?
[OZEKI]
No. Don't get intimated.
[MAN] You!
Who're you with?
Only club members are allowed
in the training yard.
Pardon.
You're Kanomori,
the club captain, yes?
We're sorry for barging in.
Huh?
[KANAMORI]
Practice with us?
First you waltz
into our club uninvited,
then you expect to us
to have bouts with you?
[OZEKI] Wait, you didn't
tell them we were coming?
So,
what school are you from anyway?
We're from Odachi High.
Dachi High?
I heard Onimaru is
enrolled there,
and he got Kuze
back in the ring.
Did you bring him along?
[KIRIHITO] He had
some things to take care of
and couldn't make it.
-Huh?
-[BOTH groan]
[KANAMORI] What good's
it gonna do us to practice
with your second-tier wrestlers?
[chuckles]
You think Onimaru's the only one
worth watching on our team?
Hey. Maybe we should
just quit while we're ahead.
Let's go back.
Relax, captain.
I'll handle this.
I've got practice dealing
with the easy-to-provoke type.
[grunts]
[laughter]
[ALL gasp]
[grunts]
[KANAMORI]
That guy threw himself at a tire
that weighs
as much as any heavyweight
and managed to stop it dead
in its tracks.
[OZEKI]
For some reason, the impact
didn't knock me backwards.
Maybe all that seaweed
harvesting we've been doing
has increased
my core strength.
First-years!
I'm only gonna
tell you once, watch it!
[STUDENTS whimpering]
We're sorry!
Apologize to this guy, not me!
Oh, it's, you know,
not necessary.
[BOTH]
Please forgive us.
So what do you think
of our captain here?
I'd say Onimaru's not
the only wrestler on our team
you should be interested
in fighting.
Hmm.
Why don't we let them join in?
They bothered to come
all the way out here.
[scoffs]
Please,
like smooth talk
is going win me over.
But we do need to make up
for what happened.
Come on! Hurry up
before I change my mind.
[MAN]
So this is where he's at.
[chuckles]
Well, Onimaru.
It's time we met.
What a waste.
I wanted to bring the hurt
on somebody today.
Grades, what can you do?
Guess I'll just play
with the goldfish or something.
-Huh?
-[NISHIZATO] Hmm?
Kunisaki!
[CHIHIRO] Are you here
for the goldfish too?
[FUNAKI] You got a student
from another school
hanging around
inside your club room.
Oh, yeah?
[CHIHIRO] Guy thinks
he's the ultimate badass.
You gonna tell me
what you want, tough guy?
Huh?
What?
Wake up, crop circles!
You should've told me
you were asleep!
I looked like an idiot!
[ALL] Whoa.
Dude's got serious balls.
Oh. My bad.
I fell asleep.
I didn't know how long
I'd be waiting.
[CHIHIRO]
Ishi High?
[MAN]
Hey.
I bet you can help me.
Go and fetch Onimaru, would you?
Huh?
I hear he's not bad at sumo.
Oh, yeah.
I'm Gennosuke Araki, by the way.
So, guess you could say that
I'm here scouting out your club.
[CHIHIRO]
Scouting, huh?
I get it.
Drawn to a challenge.
Like a moth to match.
Wait. A flame?
You're in luck!
'Cause I'm him!
[ALL gasp]
You are?
That's perfect.
Man, and luck's
usually not on my side.
I didn't even have
to look that hard.
Wait, can't call myself lucky.
It's a long story.
Too complex for you.
But I wanna be the king
of mixed martial arts.
I was told Ishi High has
the strongest sumo club around,
so I jumped at the chance
to enroll there.
But then I heard about Onimaru
and how he went head-to-head
with Eiga High's
national treasure, Kusanagi.
Thought I'd come by
and size him up.
[CHIHIRO] Are people
really talking about that?
I was interested
in sparring with you,
but I'm wasting my time.
Do you even lift?
Obviously the stories I heard
about you were exaggerated.
Don't get me wrong. I'm not
calling you weak or anything.
But if you gave Kusanagi
a run for his money,
well, you must be the one
with all the luck.
Hey.
Good fortune can be
considered a skill
if you don't have any others.
Guess if I want to fight
someone worthy,
I'm gonna have to wait
for nationals to roll around.
Sorry for intrudin'.
[CHIHIRO laughing]
All right, then.
Don't believe your eyes.
But trust me when I say this.
If you came here
looking for a fight,
today is your lucky day.
Huh?
[grunting]
[grunts]
[straining]
Well then,
I think our team's warmed up
and ready to start sparring now.
Okay.
You'll be the first
one up, Gojo.
Yeah.
Then Mamiya will start for us.
-Get in there.
-[MAMIYA] Got it.
[KIRIHITO] Keiichi Mamiya,
second-year heavyweight.
One hundred eighty-two
centimeters tall.
Weight, 166 kilograms.
The real question is
how effective
are Gojo's karate slaps
going to be against him?
[YUMA]
He's a mountain.
And up close,
he's even more intimidating.
[MAN]
Spirit!
[YUMA]
There it is.
My slap actually
pushed him back.
[KIRIHITO]
Gojo.
A minute of your time?
During matches, you should avoid
grabbing your opponent's belt.
What are you talkin' about?
That's like
a fundamental of sumo.
Wrestling like everyone else
won't give you edge
you need to win, though.
What I'm saying is you have
to play to your strengths.
Karate?
[KIRIHITO]
Listen closely.
I want you to fight
to your heart's content.
[YUMA]
It's working.
Thanks to my training,
I can match my strikes
to my opponent's movements
and never miss.
Whoa!
Rough around the edges,
but his strikes have
a kind of raw energy to 'em.
Yeah. They're way too good
for someone
who's just starting out.
But still.
[MAMIYA]
I was going easy on you
'cause you were a beginner.
[YUMA]
This isn't good.
Once Mamiya grabs your belt,
it's pretty much over with.
[MAMIYA grunting]
No, Yuma!
Damn it!
[KIRIHITO]
He'll need more work
before that tactic is effective.
Club captain Kanamori,
vice-captain Sanada,
and this Mamiya guy?
Obviously, all three are going
to the tournament
and we'll have to fight
them down the road.
And there's him.
Ishi High has
that other fighter.
But who'll be
their fifth member?
Someone stronger?
[CHIHIRO]
A one-arm shoulder throw!
[ALL]
Whoa, he knows Judo?
If that's the way
you want to play it.
-[ARAKI] What?
-[CHIHIRO] Strongest!
[ARAKI]
A leg grab!
[ALL]
They're awesome.
[ARAKI]
Hang on a second.
Liar.
You're not Onimaru.
[CHIHIRO]
Oh. That was a test.
-You passed.
-Huh?
Your techniques are different.
And you're like twice as tall
as he's supposed to be.
You can't fool me!
[ALL]
Congratulations.
Figures.
Just when I thought
my luck was changing.
So, who are you, really?
I'm Chihiro Kunisaki.
Future number one
mixed martial artist
in the entire world.
What? MMA?
You're like me.
-Uh, you're like me, Gengoro.
-Who's "Gengoro"?
Using sumo to get better
at martial arts was all my idea!
Back up! It's Gennosuke!
-Who is?
-Me! I'm Araki Gennosuke!
[ALL] Oh. Gotcha.
They're both idiots.
[MAN] Hey!
What's going on here?
[MAN] So you're the punk
trespassing on school property!
-[MAN shouting]
-[ARAKI] Guess I should go.
We'll finish our bout
another day.
Trust me.
You know,
maybe it was luck
I met you after all, Chiharu.
It's Chihiro!
I'll show myself out.
Later.
[MAN continues shouting]
[CHIHIRO] Only one month
before the Inter High prelims.
I need more time.
If I'd studied,
I could be over at Ishigami
with the others
training right now.
I'm never failing
another test again.
Okay, captain.
Enter the ring.
Um, sure.
I'll give it my all.
[KANAMORI] He stopped
that tire single-handedly.
I'd have to guess he's the
strongest member they brought.
-In that case, I'll send out--
-Hey, sweet.
Looks like we're having
training bouts, huh?
You punk!
You think you can just
stroll into practice
whenever you want, huh?
I showed up, didn't I?
The guy from earlier.
He could've told us
he was in the club.
Come on, captain,
I wanna have a turn.
Put me in the ring
and let's see what happens.
You're late, then you
ask me for a favor?
The only thing you're doing
is groin stretches
for the next hour!
Ah!
But you know I have
trouble with those.
I'm begging you, captain.
Have a heart.
What's the harm in
letting him play this match?
Let's be honest here,
how often does he feel
like doing anything?
Don't keep motherin' him.
He's never gonna learn
at this rate.
Sanada, you big softie.
Seems they chose your opponent.
You got this one
in the bag, Ozeki.
That's Mizuki Sada.
Or rather Mikazuki Munechika.
-[REINA] Uh?
-[BOYS] Huh?
[OZEKI]
But he seems so easy-going.
How am I supposed to beat
a national treasure?
When it comes to a tournament,
we need to win three bouts
to defeat their school
and move on.
Now let's assume that
Hinomaru and Kunisaki win
their matches
without a problem.
That still means at least one
of you needs a victory.
or the path to nationals ends
right then and there.
I want to win, but how?
Remember during practice?
You were able to keep up
with Hinomaru, weren't you?
That wouldn't have happened
if you weren't getting better.
[OZEKI] Does Tsuji
really believe I can do this?
Hmm?
[chuckles]
[OZEKI]
He thinks he can mock me
cause he's
a national treasure?
I'll show him how hard
I've been training!
You're not getting
a hold of my belt.
Oh, man.
He's just toying with Ozeki.
You're bigger than he is,
so what're you waiting for?
Knock the living crap outta him!
[OZEKI]
I hear you.
But if I miss,
then it's over with!
Hey, wait, I know that guy.
We were on the same sumo team
in middle school,
but the dude never won
a single bout.
How pathetic.
I'm surprised
he hasn't quit already.
Jerks.
Just watch.
-[OZEKI grunting]
-[SADA laughing]
[OZEKI]
What was I thinking?
I don't even know how to win.
What am I supposed
to do to bring down
a national treasure?
Get your head in the game!
Remember your training
with Hinomaru!
[groans]
It's no use.
No matter
how many times we spar,
I'll never beat you.
We finally have enough members
to compete for real,
but I'm the captain,
and I'm holding everyone back.
[OZEKI groans]
Dude, what the--
[groans]
You asked for it, brother.
You want me to stop, then don't
sell yourself short anymore.
You've been doing stomps
for about five years now, right?
It clearly shows.
You've got a physique
anyone in sumo
would be proud of having.
You're stronger than you know.
[OZEKI]
If that's what Ushio believes,
I just need to grab his belt!
He recovered his stance
from that position?
[OZEKI]
I can do this!
[groaning]
What's that?
He's trapped in an arm hold.
It's a maneuver that immobilizes
an opponent's attack.
And given his abilities,
there's no doubt
it's extremely painful.
He's got Ozeki
right on the joint.
When he uses that technique,
nobody can grab
his mawashi belt.
His opponents can't even get
anywhere near it.
You know, you'd think
sooner or later,
people would realize there's
a reason it's so pristine.
[OZEKI groaning]
[SADA]
It was good try.
You almost got your hands on it.
[OZEKI]
This hurts so much.
I can't even breathe.
Push away from him, quick!
Man, props for not breakin' yet.
Because of our water training.
[OZEKI]
I don't want to lose.
I have keep fighting
and get stronger.
Otherwise, I can't go
to nationals with Ushio!
[OZEKI grunting]
You got this, captain!
Keep pushin' him outta the ring!
How long you
gonna mess around?
Finish it!
Know what?
You didn't do half bad.
Crescent Moon!
[groaning]
What kind of move was that?
He threw the captain
like it was no big deal.
Do me a favor.
Onimaru Kunitsuna.
Give him a message for me.
Just tell him
I'm looking forward
to facing him in the ring.
[HINOMARU]
That's Kirihito for you.
Always has a plan.
Home of top-ranked pros
and renowned for
its intense practices.
The Shibakiyama Stable.
[growling]
Where is he?
That jerk's always running late.
Some nerve.
Especially when we went
out of our way
to be friendly to him.
-[babbling, giggling]
-Huh?
Waah!
What's goin' on
with your face, captain?
-You havin' a conniption-fit?
-[ALL] Sada!
Why are you late?
[SADA laughing]
[cries loudly]
This is too good!