♪
[KIRIHITO]
These may be your friends now
but in an instant,
they could become
your greatest enemy.
Moving speech, but let's see
if you can back up your talk,
Onimaru Kunitsuna!
[SAKI] Excuse me.
Is this the Odachi High tent?
Uh...
[REINA] Yeah, but the team's
already gone over to the ring.
Oh, I missed them.
You wouldn't happen to be
their manager by any chance?
Huh? Who, me? No.
I mean, it'd be normal
to have a female manager
for a sport
like soccer or baseball,
but sumo club, come on!
I get it. In that case,
I must be abnormal.
[REINA]
Uh...
[ANNOUNCER]
Attention.
The individual bouts
are about to begin.
On the west side,
from Odachi High School, Ozeki.
[OZEKI]
The individual tournament.
Whoever makes it in the
top three goes to the finals.
When this is over,
Ushio needs to make the podium.
I was planning to sacrifice
my spot to help him out.
But if I go deep
into the tournament,
I might end up fighting him.
Focus, Captain!
-Uh...
-[REFEREE] Spirit!
[grunts]
Oh, no!
-I started too late!
-[yells]
[REFEREE]
West side wins!
[CROWD applauding]
That was close.
He almost got taken out.
It's a good thing the other guy
got excited and moved too soon.
Going off that match,
it's hard to believe
he defeated the vice-captain
from Ishi High.
[REINA]
Hmm.
Seems like his drive to fight
is centered
around helping his teammates.
I got a feeling
he's nice to a fault.
He was so concerned
with the group tournament,
seems he lost sight
of the individual contest.
-Huh.
-Well, whatever the case,
you can't make it to the finals
if you're unable
to face your friends.
[ANNOUNCER] On the east side,
from Odachi High, Ushio.
There's our champ!
No way Ushio can lose!
Now that Sada's out, he's got
this in the bag for sure.
I doubt he'll waltz through
this, given what happened.
-You talking about his arm?
-That's part of it, yeah.
But after making it
through today's gauntlet,
can he stay focused
through more bouts?
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
[body thuds]
[ALL gasp]
♪
It'd be a waste of time
to worry about him.
[TERAHARA] He looks ready
to chew up and spit out
anyone in his way,
teammate or not.
[gasps]
Do you guys think
when it's our turn,
he's gonna fight
that way against us?
It wasn't long ago
we were all working as one.
Now it's like we're enemies.
[CHIHIRO]
You don't stop being teammates.
A little conflict
can be healthy.
When you step inside the ring
to face off,
it's against someone
who has a dream just like you.
And they deserve
all that you've got
'cause they're your teammates.
If you want to call yourselves
sumo wrestlers,
then shouldn't you demand
the same respect?
I want to face him at his best.
And win.
♪
[ANNOUNCER]
On the west side,
from Odachi High School,
Kunisaki.
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
You're kidding me.
Look at his footwork.
That's Sada's.
First Quarter Moon!
-[grunts]
-[CROWD applauding]
♪
[BOTH gasp]
That copycat!
Hey, it's a good move.
[KANAMORI]
I'd get copying the Demon Wheel,
but this tournament
was the first time
he's ever seen
the First Quarter Moon.
♪
[KIRIHITO]
He picks up on techniques fast,
but his knack for combat
goes way beyond that.
With Hinomaru
at his current state,
there's a chance.
I never thanked you.
You're the reason
I joined the sumo club.
Now I've grown stronger
than I've ever imagined.
You're next on my list.
A stepping stone to becoming
the world's strongest fighter.
Yuma's bout is coming up next!
Take him out!
You got this, Yuma!
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
[ANNOUNCER]
Pushed out of bounds.
-Nice!
-Gojo, on the west side, wins.
Nice going out there, Gojo!
[YUMA]
Thanks.
I guess it's time, huh?
On the east side,
from Odachi High, Ushio.
On the west side,
from Odachi High, Kunisaki.
♪
Both of 'em are looking
dead serious.
It makes you wonder.
Just who are we supposed
to be cheering for?
[OZEKI] I don't think
there's anyone on the team
who can decide
which dream is worthier.
Ushio or Kunisaki's.
And if I keep winning my bouts,
I'll end up fighting
whoever wins this one.
Place your hands on the ground!
[CHIHIRO]
He's a different beast entirely
when you face him in the ring
for an official bout.
Onimaru Kunitsuna,
you're incredible.
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
Here we go!
That's my move!
The inner thigh counter!
[KANAMORI]
The First Quarter Moon Throw.
Now this.
He's got talent.
[grunting]
[grunts]
He threw an attack.
Up until this point,
he's only been using grabs!
There's no telling
what's gonna happen next!
Think he modeled that move
off your Canon Slap?
Mm-hmm.
[SAKI]
He's definitely got an appetite
for any moves
that'll help him win.
And with so many talented
wrestlers at today's tournament,
it's been like a buffet of
different powerhouse techniques
for Kunisaki.
[slaps landing]
[KIRIHITO]
The way he absorbs moves
and keeps changing his style,
it's completely different
from the way he trains.
But...
you need more, Kunisaki.
[OZEKI]
You won't beat Ushio like that!
[KANAMORI] He isn't just
imitating the moves,
so it's obvious he has skill.
Even so, his versions don't have
the same intensity
as the originals.
You can tell because
Onimaru's body has barely moved.
[OZEKI]
What would I do here?
How'd I take advantage
of Ushio's stature
without letting him grab
my mawashi belt?
I'd try...
-[thud]
-[ALL gasp]
You thief!
Whoa, Now he's using
a leg sweep?
And not just any sweep!
That's Yuma's special!
[CHIHIRO] All of these moves
have been a distraction
to keep my options open.
-My real attack...
-Uh!
[CHIHIRO]
...is this!
He's going for a tackle
from that position?
[KIRIHITO] Kunisaki's strong
and has good technique,
but his real weapon
is improvising.
[CHIHIRO]
Damn.
Looks like I'm not
the only one
who got a power boost
during this tournament!
[HINOMARU]
Chihiro.
I swear, every time
you exceed my expectations.
[CHIHIRO] You're not getting
both hands on my belt!
[HINOMARU] There's only one way
to counter your improvisation.
I have to be stronger than you!
Underarm throw,
thigh propping twist down!
Demon Storm Hand Sweep!
♪
[whimpers]
-[CROWD cheering]
-[KIRIHITO gasps]
Not bad.
How many techniques
does he have?
Yeah, right?
He saw Chiharu use it
in the team bouts
and turned it against him.
[CHIHIRO]
You know,
the most annoying part is
even though I lost,
I'm not the least bit
pissed off about it.
To be honest,
I'm more stoked than anything.
It means I've still got
a long way to go
before I'm
the strongest fighter.
♪
[OZEKI]
Well, that gave me goosebumps.
[SHIBAKIYAMA] If his mind wasn't
a mess already,
it probably is now.
Huh?
It's okay.
You're a sumo wrestler too.
You can respect him
outside the ring
and still be able to compete
with him once you step inside.
♪
[OZEKI]
I want to fight Ushio.
But that's not enough.
I want to win!
♪
[groaning]
[HINOMARU] Please don't give out
on me until this is over.
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
-He knew it was coming!
-It's over
[KEI grunting]
[CROWD applauding]
Looks like his first
official win will have to wait.
Nice fight, Mitsuhashi!
[KEI] Damn. I wanted
to win at least one
before we headed to the finals.
How can I win there
if I can't win in Chiba?
Do you still have confidence
in my coaching?
Have faith in me.
And I promise
you'll win at the finals.
[KEI]
You really have faith in me.
You're our instructor
and if you believe
I can actually win,
then I will follow you.
All the way to hell and back.
[CROWD cheering]
Whatever hang-ups
he might've had are gone now.
Yeah.
[KEI] Our captain put
his doubts behind him.
I gotta catch up to the rest
of the team by the finals.
West side wins!
[CROWD applauding]
[OZEKI]
There's no turning back.
[ANNOUNCER] We're moving on
to the fifth bout
of the individual tournament.
On the west side,
from Odachi High School, Ozeki.
On the east side,
from Odachi High school, Ushio.
[MAN 1]
A bout between the captain
and vice-captain
of the winning team?
This is gonna be insane!
So who're you cheering for,
Professor?
-It's Hinomaru, right?
-Huh?
Let's be real.
You enrolled at Dachi High
to help him win, didn't you?
So if the captain beats him,
then technically you failed.
I won't deny you have a point.
But as your coach,
I've watched you all shed blood,
sweat, and tears equally.
I wouldn't want the captain
to lose for the sake
of someone else.
However...
I want you to tell everyone
that my arm's
not as bad as it looks.
[KIRIHITO]
What?
I understand not wanting
other schools to know,
but hiding it
from your own team?
[HINOMARU]
Absolutely.
[KIRIHITO]
Wha...
[HINOMARU] You think
I'm gonna tell them
to go easy on me
'cause my elbow hurts?
[KIRIHITO]
That's not what I meant.
Why risk making it worse,
especially in a bout
with a teammate?
-[HINOMARU] Respect.
-Huh?
This tournament's important
to everyone here.
I won't hold anything back.
That's how I show respect
to my team.
♪
He never lets up.
Even against the captain
of his own team.
He kicked up the intensity,
if that's possible.
Yeah.
♪
[OZEKI]
Ushio,
I can never thank you enough
for what you've done for me.
It's because of you, my love
for sumo has grown ten-fold.
You opened my eyes...
to the joy
of having teammates...
and winning against opponents.
♪
But those feelings
don't belong here.
They're for outside the ring!
[CHIHIRO]
A spider stance.
How come he didn't use that
when we were fighting?
Because you're unpredictable,
so he wasn't sure
what you were going to do.
But against Ozeki,
he's expecting a tackle.
[OZEKI]
This is the last Inter High
I'm ever gonna have.
Which means
this will be my first
and only official bout
against Ushio!
Spirit now!
Bring it!
Holy...
He stopped Onimaru's charge
with his chest!
♪
[OZEKI] I've dealt with this
every day of practice!
You gotta do better!
An underarm grip!
Neither of his hands
can reach the mawashi belt!
Hinomaru grabbed him back!
[OZEKI] His grip isn't
as strong as usual.
I'm guessing his arm
must've gotten busted up
more than I originally thought.
[groans]
[BOTH straining]
[OZEKI] If we continue fighting
like this, his arm's gonna...
[HINOMARU]
What's wrong, Captain?
Thinking of going easy on me?
I'm warning you, if you do that,
we'll both be disappointed!
[HINOMARU straining]
He pushed him all the way
to the rope!
Act like this is your last bout!
That's right.
For Shinya Ozeki, there's never
gonna be another match
as important as the one
I'm fighting right now!
For me, this is the final!
My main event!
He pushed him backwards!
[REINA] Now shorty's about
to get knocked out!
[OZEKI]
He's pulling me down!
I won't let him!
Wait. A trap!
He switched to underarm!
[OZEKI]
Not today!
He's not thrusting
with his right arm.
Looks like Onimaru
injured it as well.
You knew his arm was screwed up.
So why didn't you say
anything, Prof?
If you had known,
would you have approached
the bout any differently?
You wanna know?
Just look at the captain.
[yelling]
This is getting intense.
It's like he's
a different person.
[HINOMARU grunts]
[CHIHIRO] The upper body
and cardio workouts
the professor puts us through
took our game
to a whole new level.
But paired with the captain's
lower body strength,
it's made him
a fearsome opponent.
-[slap lands]
-[CHIHIRO] Still.
-[yells]
-[grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[CHIHIRO] You really think
Hinomaru will let you win
just cause he's injured?
Yeah, right.
[OZEKI]
What do you think you're doing?
You're using your busted arm!
[HINOMARU] I can't complain
about this kind of pain.
Especially when
I'm battling you.
I had to fight alone
in middle school.
Against both myself and society.
I didn't accept any help,
or anyone's advice.
I thought no one
could understand
what I was going through,
and I was fine with that.
Until I saw that
homemade sumo ring.
Up until that point,
I refused to believe
there was someone out there
practicing in harsher conditions
than me.
For the first time in my life,
I felt like I had
a brother-in-arms.
[BOTH straining]
My elbow's killing me.
But so what?
I'm not going to give
my captain anything
except the best match
he's ever fought!
Demon Wheel!
♪
[OZEKI] Ushio's laying it all
on the line to win this fight.
Then why?
[straining]
Why haven't I
been doing the same?
[ALL gasp]
[OZEKI]
I can take it!
If this is battle of endurance,
I won't lose to him!
[straining]
[HINOMARU]
That's the spirit, Captain!
I don't see you any different
than Kuze or Sada.
Right now, you're my rival,
pure and simple!
[HINOMARU yells]
[OZEKI]
Your grip's not tight enough!
Hinomaru!
Uh-oh.
He's only gripping one layer
of the mawashi.
That'll make it harder
for him to apply force.
[BOTH grunting]
He's standing his ground
and trying to push Ozeki out.
[SADA]
If he could manage a throw,
he'd be in
a much better position.
That's what I'd do anyway.
[chuckles]
But backing off
isn't exactly Ushio's style.
Ozeki's standing up straighter.
That half-pint had
that much energy left to burn?
[OZEKI] He's going full power
and not holding anything back.
Which means
he's planning on using
everything he's got right here!
If I survive this,
he won't have any strength
left in him to fight!
[inhales deeply]
Endure it!
All I have to do is get
through this, and I'll win!
Um, sir.
I know this sounds crazy,
and maybe it's just me.
But it seems like
they're both having fun.
They are.
I can see it too.
When it comes to their strength,
they have a mutual admiration.
I'm a little envious.
What I wouldn't give
to have fought Hinomaru
head-to-head
in a serious bout like this.
[MAN] No matter
which of you wins,
this bout is legendary!
[MAN 2]
You're almost there, Ozeki!
♪
I keep forgetting
I have to breathe.
Both of you, tough it out.
[BATO scoffs]
♪
[grunting]
[growling]
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH gasp]
♪
[ALL gasp]
[straining]
Ah!
[ALL gasp]
[body thuds]
To everyone else, the ring
is just a rice-straw bale.
-But for sumo wrestlers...
-[panting]
...it's the size
of a fearsome mountain.
[ANNOUNCER]
Forced out of bounds.
Ushio, on the east side, wins.
[cheering]
Don't tell me that wasn't
an impressive battle.
Ozeki held his own admirably,
but in the end,
Onimaru's tenacity won out.
You know, you'll likely meet
in the final bout.
You scared?
Please.
Aww, man.
I wish my arm hadn't decided
to give out on me.
You better heal up quick.
I need to train ASAP.
Sada actually wants to train?
After the match we just watched,
I can see why.
[HINOMARU panting]
[OZEKI]
Man, I'm disappointed.
I wanted to win.
But in terms
of matches I've fought,
it was the best I ever had
and just the motivation I needed
to push me during the finals.
There's gonna be a ton of strong
opponents standing in your way,
but I know
you're gonna beat them all
and become
a high school yokozuna!
Correction.
Everybody knows you're going
to be a professional yokozuna!
[chuckles]
-Wait, what have I done?
-[HINOMARU] Huh?
Dude! Is your arm okay?
I got caught up in the moment
and completely forgot
about it getting
injured earlier!
[laughing]
As soon as he steps
out of the ring,
he's back to being a teddy bear.
[KIRIHITO]
Good luck, Hinomaru.
♪
[ANNOUNCER] We will now present
the tournament awards!
The champion,
from Odachi High School,
is Hinomaru Ushio.
In second place,
from Ishigami High School,
Kanamori.
In third place...
Congratulations, Ushio.
I'll be seeing you
at the finals.
[BATO scoffs]
Okay, everyone get close!
[KIRIHITO] Hinomaru,
I know this was just
a stop on the road for you,
but you can still
look happy about it.
Wha... I am.
[REINA]
Come on, guys. Smile!
-You too, shorty.
-Uh...
♪
[chuckles]
-[REINA] Say cheese!
-[camera shutter clicks]
♪
Interesting.
If they're holding the belt,
it's "forced out of bounds."
Thanks for clearing
that up for me!
I'm still a novice and don't
know a whole lot about sumo yet.
Plus the guys who tagged along
were no help,
so it's a relief
someone here's knowledgeable!
No problem!
I'm just happy you enjoyed
the tournament.
Hey. If you wanna
check it out,
I recorded Yuma's bout
on my phone earlier!
[REINA on phone]
Whoo! Go, Yuma!
Wipe the floor with him!
That's what I'm talking about!
[whooping]
Yep, totally normal.
[REINA shuddering]