♪
[sighs]
[HINOMARU] I feel funky whenever
I miss my morning workout.
[yawns]
[OZEKI]
Ushio!
[HINOMARU]
Hey, fellas!
Whoa. What's with the crowd?
-[OZEKI] Huh?
-[KEI] I'm not sure.
[BOY 1]
There they are, over there!
Our prelim champions!
[BOY 2]
You guys rocked it yesterday!
-[HINOMARU] Hmm?
-[KEI] Uh...
[ANNOUNCER] Would all
the members of the sumo club
please come on stage
at this time?
[cheering]
[GIRL 1] Kei!
Over here!
[BOY 3]
Yuma!
[BOY 4]
You the man, Hinomaru!
[BOY 5]
Hey, Ozeki!
[PRINCIPAL] That was
a magnificent performance
you gave, boys.
The way you fought out there!
I was so impressed!
Well, in that case,
could our club get
a budget increase?
[PRINCIPAL laughing]
You got it!
[YUMA]
Weird.
I get them wanting to celebrate
how great we did and all that,
but why're they making it sound
like they were there
during the tournament
watching us from the crowd?
Hmm?
I don't remember that
much cheering
come from the Dachi High side
of the arena.
Plus, the freaks are
more excited than they were
back when I won the national
wrestling championship.
Which, no offense,
pisses me off.
[meows]
[CHIHIRO]
Chanko!
I need fur therapy
for my anxiety!
-[CHANKO screeches]
-[CHIHIRO grunts]
Breaking news!
I've got the answer here!
Why everyone's bananas!
-What's that?
-Oh, yeah?
[CHIHIRO] That's a video
of yesterday's team finals.
It's being shared
all over social media.
It's gotten so popular, everyone
at school knows about us now.
-[KIRIHITO] Hmm?
-But who's the one
that posted it?
-Tsuji?
-I wish, but no.
Well, Reina?
Uh! Don't look at me!
[GIRL 2]
I'm sorry.
The video that was posted,
um, it was me.
[OZEKI]
Uh? Cool, but why?
You see...
it's just that I was so inspired
by the exploits
of our school's sumo team,
it felt like I needed to share
that feeling
with as many people
as I could.
Well, that explains that.
Thanks for supporting the club.
[gasps]
I wanted to ask you.
If you don't have one already,
I'd like to become
the sumo club's manager,
if that's okay.
Huh?
We got a lady manger?
-Hell yeah!
-Whoa.
Is that a serious offer?
Not only am I serious,
I've fallen in love with sumo.
I was just thinking how another
pair of hands would help out
around here
and then you show up.
Okay!
Freeze one sec!
Manager?
If you were so desperate
for one,
why didn't you ask
the obvious choice?
Uh...
because we were all convinced
you hated sumo, Reina.
[REINA]
Uh...
Ladies, instead of wasting time
splitting hairs,
why don't both of you
join the club?
[KIRIHITO] Now the student
council's in our corner.
Oh, no.
He's scheming again.
[YUMA]
Seriously?
-You wanted to be our manager?
-[REINA grunts]
Well... Uh...
Okay.
We're gonna start
with some light training
and then go celebrate
winning a tournament
and gaining new members!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[REINA]
Barbecue?
This is how you roll out
the red carpet
for the new girls?
Why couldn't we go somewhere
more upscale?
This is our victory celebration
after all,
and you only joined
the club today.
That reminds me,
I don't think we caught
your name at the dojo earlier.
Oh, that's right.
Chizuko Hori, a first-year.
Thank you for inviting me.
No sweat.
It's nice to have a girl onboard
to diffuse some
of this bro-energy.
Question. Whose bout
inspired you the most
during the tournament?
Whose bout?
No fair, man.
You're basically asking her
to pick someone who won.
[CHIHIRO] You got a problem
with that, babyface?
[KEI] Yeah, I do.
And the name's Kei!
[CHIHIRO] I'll ask you
to remember
my many genius moves
during that competition.
[REINA]
Wait just a minute.
Does she like...
[KIRIHITO]
Okay, Reina.
Introduce yourself.
[REINA gasps]
Who am I? Please!
Just two-time Miss Dachi High,
Student Council president,
the incomparable Reina Gojo!
Yeah, like this face
even requires an introduction.
Uh! Oh, uh, also,
my brother Yuma's been
training hard,
so I should
support him, yeah.
[HINOMARU]
Hmm?
Wait, you mean the two
of you are siblings?
I had no freakin' clue!
[REINA] All those headbutts
must've caught up with him.
By the way, what does
a club manager do?
They have several tasks.
In addition to the stuff the
captain and I have been doing,
they get everything ready
for the chankonabe stew.
Oh, chanko stew!
We couldn't make it before since
we didn't have the funds for it.
But is the principal really
going to raise our budget?
Um, hello, you guys, I'm
the student council president.
If your club needed more money,
you could've just come to me
and asked for it.
What?
You're the best, Reina!
That's a huge relief!
[REINA scoffs] Yeah.
I know I'm awesome.
Thanks for acknowledging it.
[KIRIHITO]
These two are so gullible.
Oh, right.
We're on a timer,
so let's continue
this discussion
after we finish eating.
What do you mean a timer?
[KIRIHITO] Two thousand yen
gets you ninety minutes.
At a buffet of over
a hundred dishes.
We're talking barbecue, sushi,
desserts as far
as the eye can see!
♪
[HINOMARU]
Why didn't you say so?
And it's all you can eat.
-Is that right?
-Yep!
Let's see who can eat
the most in one sitting!
Hah! You're speaking
my language!
Yeah.
I think I'm gonna stick
to this section.
[JIRO] High schoolers
on their way back from club?
To be young again!
All right, kids.
Prepare to satisfy
your appetites.
That's why I opened this
restaurant in the first place.
The joy of seeing patrons
leaving full and happy.
Let me clear away
those dirty plates for you.
[gasps]
Oh, sweet heavens!
The meat, it's glistening
to a golden brown!
There.
That looks about ready.
Let's see.
Oh!
It's better than being adored
by the entire school!
[JIRO] The ancient
all-you-can-eat masters said
a person's true colors
are revealed only at a buffet.
This boy's plates exude
a sensitivity and sincerity
one would never associate
with his brutish appearance!
Does he descend from royalty?
Behold, the greatest man
to have ever graced a buffet!
[KEI]
Patience.
Flip the meat when the edges
start to turn white.
Wait for the juice
to form on top.
Time for my special attack!
[grunts]
-Rib Tornado!
-[KEI screams]
Delicious!
What gives?
That was supposed to be mine!
Hmm?
Are you telling me
you weren't cooking it
for your best friend?
[screams]
Who let this beast
out of his cage?
He doesn't care anything
about presentation.
As long as the food reaches
his stomach, he's content.
[gulps, burps]
[JIRO] Rest in peace,
my poor sweet appetite.
No. I mustn't judge.
Everyone has a particular
way of eating.
[sizzling]
-[YUMA] Here, Hinomaru.
-Hmm?
You've gotta balance
that meat out with vegetables.
Right!
Thanks a bunch!
Save the chef routine
for home-ec, Gojo.
You're not gonna get
your money's worth
unless you scarf it down!
Huh?
[JIRO]
Your money's worth?
Well, young man,
I guess you're saving up
for a one-way ticket
straight to hell!
You must be tired
of chowing down on meat.
Growing boys should always have
a bowl of rice in one hand.
Thanks for looking out for us.
[JIRO] Oh and please have some
of our rich Jiro noodles
on the side.
I made them extra-large servings
just for you, so eat up!
Don't have to tell me twice.
Ramen's one of
the food groups, right?
[laughs]
Yes, you fools! Eat!
This is how I protect
the restaurant's meat supply!
I won't let you get
your money's worth so easily!
Even though this one could prove
to be trouble
with his ravenous appetite,
he's no threat without
the support of his friends.
Oh man, I've got
food triplets here.
Is that gut just for show,
how're you stuffed?
I'm actually not
that big of an eater.
I'm done.
For like the next couple days.
Me, too.
[JIRO]
Your fate is sealed, sir!
Good luck making up
the difference on your own!
Remember, the buffet
is a team battle!
Too bad your weak lineup wasn't
enough to see you to victory!
You'll never defeat
the mighty Mr. Stamina Jiro!
Master of the buffet!
Why is it you get paid
more than us, again?
Come on, it's too early
for you to be quitting.
Don't forget the reason
we came to a buffet.
This is a victory,
welcome party,
and training session
all rolled into one event.
Your assignment is to consume
twice the calories
a pro eats:
twenty-thousand.
What're you waiting for?
Wolf it down!
[JIRO]
Twenty-thousand?
In all seriousness though,
the captain's the only one
on the team
who weighs over
100 kilograms right now.
The rest of you need
to do your part
and pack on the weight.
[scoffs]
All right then, gentlemen.
[ALL WRESTLERS]
Eat everything in sight!
[eating noisily]
♪
[JIRO]
What is going on here?
If we leave anything
on our plates,
we have to pay a penalty
which comes out
of our team's pocket.
Mitsuhashi. You've got
your work cut out for you.
Thanks a lot, Satan!
Oh, god.
My nightmare is becoming
a reality!
♪
[groans]
No more meat.
I can't stomach another bite!
[JIRO] Excellent.
That's one victim down.
Looks like it's time
to move on to the sweets!
[JIRO]
He's got room for dessert?
This is impossible.
They were ready to collapse,
and now they've all grown
a second stomach!
I've gotten jaded.
It's been so long
since I had a worthy adversary.
Very well, my nemeses.
Hope you're ready
for the big guns!
You know some of us
have to work!
[CHIHIRO groans]
Reached my limit.
-Kill me.
-I'm gonna hurl.
If you blow chunks,
our sacrifice will have been
for nothing!
[YUMA]
Victory party?
This feels more like torture.
[growls]
There's no way around it!
Looks like we're gonna end up
paying the penalty fee.
[JIRO]
Success!
It appears the cheap carbs
I loaded them up with
are finally starting
to work their magic.
I must say, Jiro,
that was masterfully played.
What fee?
I haven't thrown in the towel!
-[meat sizzling]
-[OZEKI] Ushio!
[CHIHIRO] Look, I know
you wanna one-up me,
but this isn't
the way to do it, bro!
See, the trouble is,
I got a high metabolism.
Gotta keep eating
or the weight falls off.
But you're at your limit,
Hinomaru!
You don't have
to prove yourself!
[HINOMARU] The legendary
yokozuna Yamatokuni
forced himself
to get bigger
so he could compete
against foreign sumo wrestlers.
But the thing
that's equally important
is I won't allow myself
to leave food on my plate!
[gasps]
[HINOMARU] Because anyone
who wastes a single bite
isn't worthy
of becoming a yokozuna!
[JIRO]
Inhuman!
How can he fit all that food
into such a compact frame?
I must admit defeat.
Congratulations, you monsters.
You win.
[ALL cheering, chanting]
Eat! Eat! Eat! Eat! Eat!
[REINA]
What is even going on here?
-[CHIZUKO giggles]
-Uh...
He's so cool, don't you think?
Hmm.
[WOMAN]
Thank you for your business!
Before you go.
-[GROUP] Huh?
-May I have the honor of knowing
who did I serve tonight?
Uh, who, us?
We're members
of the Dachi High Sumo Club.
[laughs] Yes!
The sumo club, of course!
That explains everything.
Best of luck,
Dachi High Sumo Club!
[KIRIHITO]
Hmm?
Yeah. You too.
[KIRIHITO] Listen up,
yesterday's tournament showed us
what we each need to work on
before the finals in less
than two months.
Let's give it our all, guys!
[ALL]
Yeah!
♪
[CHIHIRO] Good food,
good service. Five stars!
[KEI]
How can you walk so fast?
I'm gonna puke.
[laughs]
Hold it in, Mitsuhashi!
[YUMA] What we each need
to work on, huh?
[KEI] I mean,
how're you feeling, Chizuko?
[REINA] Don't tell me this girl
actually finds that shrimp--
[REINA]
What do you want?
I think we need to talk.
About Yuma.
Uh?
That was one heck of a battle.
Good luck,
Dachi High sumo club.
And don't be afraid
to never come back.
♪
[BOTH grunting]
Up to this point, we been
focusing on individual training,
so now I'd like for us
to break off
and work in groups of two.
Training in pairs?
So, first up we have Gojo.
I'd like you to partner
with the captain.
[grunting]
Why us?
[KIRIHITO]
It's quite simple.
Since the captain's heavy,
practicing with him
should help you learn some ways
to avoid being grabbed.
Whereas you need to work on
grabbing your opponent, Captain.
Gojo likes to fight
at arm's length,
so it'll be
good training for you.
Mmm. I understand.
[KIRIHITO]
I'll work with Mitsuhashi
on improving his strength.
-Sir!
-[KIRIHITO] Next up,
-Kunisaki and Hinomaru.
-[BOTH chuckle]
[shuddering]
[KIRIHITO]
The point of this exercise
is to establish communication
with your partner.
So be observant and tell them
everything you notice.
[ALL]
Sir!
It's gonna be good to finally
get to know you, buddy.
Here, I'll start.
So, you got any brothers
or sisters?
Um, when he said "everything"
I think he meant sumo.
How long's that rod
been up your butt?
Well, looks like we're partners.
Let's work hard, all right?
Sure thing.
-[OZEKI straining]
-[YUMA grunts]
You need to start being more
forceful with your charge, Yuma.
[panting]
I heard the first-years
had something going on
and were gonna be late,
but what the heck's
keeping everyone else?
Did Kunisaki get
another detention?
[groans]
[REINA]
I'm their manager now.
But I'm too nervous
to go inside.
♪
[HINOMARU] Is it just me or is
Yuma not acting like himself?
[REINA]
Hmm?
During the individual contest,
he was lacking motivation.
Not that long ago,
Yuma was eager to fight me.
I think it's because
of the captain.
[gasps]
It doesn't make sense.
If they have bad blood,
then why'd he partner them up?
[YUMA]
Get to know each other?
Hah! I already know
what Ozeki thinks of me.
[BOTH straining]
Damn!
[OZEKI] What's up?
You not feeling well?
There's no power
in your thrusts.
[YUMA]
I'm fine.
It's nothing.
Don't give me that.
Tsuji said we had to open up
and communicate with each other.
And I just told you,
nothing's wrong!
[OZEKI] If that's the case,
then you need to hit me harder.
Otherwise, neither of us
will get anything out of this.
[YUMA growling]
I can't hit you harder!
[REINA groans]
Yeah, I'm done.
Uhh...
[YUMA] Like you said,
this is no way to practice.
I'll tell Coach
to get you a new partner.
[OZEKI gasps]
Okay, but why?
This is was a perfect chance
for us
to get to know each other, man.
If there's something you want
to say, please just say it.
♪
[YUMA]
This isn't your fault.
It's mine.
The whole damn thing's my fault.
What I did to you haunts me
every minute of the day.
When I cleaned the dojo
and bowed my head,
I thought that would be enough
to set things straight.
But it wasn't.
Now that I've experienced
the joy of winning at sumo,
I realize how much
I've taken from you.
There's only one thing I know.
I have no right to be here
practicing with you.
No right to enjoy sumo
as much as I do.
♪
For real?
That's what's been
bothering you all this time?
[gasps]
Well, to be honest,
I pretty much put
our entire past behind me
after you bowed your head
and asked to become
a member of the sumo club.
I mean, sure I was hesitant
at first
about being on the same team,
but I got over it
almost immediately.
As soon as you started,
it was obvious
how much you enjoyed sumo.
And watching
the whole transformation
from you hating on the sport
to becoming a fanboy
was sort of its own reward.
[gasps]
[OZEKI] Besides, if all that
stuff hadn't happened,
we might have never spoken
to each other.
And you wouldn't be here now.
If things had gone
a little differently,
there's a chance the club
might not have made it.
We used to be
completely ignored,
but now no one
can stop talking about us.
So if you look at it that way,
I'd say everything turned out
all right in the end. [chuckles]
♪
If you're really that worried
about making it up to me,
then how about
we make a deal?
All you have to do
is keep on enjoying sumo.
Sound good?
Do you think
you can handle that?
♪
-[HINOMARU laughs]
-[gasps]
Looks like it worked out.
The captain forgave Yuma
a long time ago.
Everything that happened
was all water under the bridge.
That's one of
his greatest strengths.
Ozeki's a nice dude,
but Yuma won't ever
take advantage of him.
And your brother's got
a serious side
that won't let him
open up easily.
Before finals,
I needed to be sure
he understood one thing.
There'll never be a time
he's not welcomed at our club.
-Huh?
-[KEI] Uh... Hinomaru!
Wait.
Do you mean you planned
this all along?
Hah! Who can say?
Hey.
Quit your slacking and get back
to training, you two!
Uhh! Ushio!
We weren't talking
about feelings!
[chuckles]
♪
Here's the truth.
I invited Yuma to join
not 'cause we were desperate
for members.
I figured he'd get a win
at the finals,
so if he joined,
he'd help the captain
and the rest
of the team out.
[chuckles]
Now, I want you to charge
at me using full force.
Right!
♪
[grunts]
He's always been
a sumo wrestler I've admired,
but now that I'm viewing him
as an opponent...
I'm getting chills.
I can't even picture
how I'm going to win.
Shido Tennoji.
The high school yokozuna.
[KIRIHITO]
We haven't figured out
a solid plan of attack yet.
[HINOMARU]
Well...
nothing I can do
except keep training.
[KIRIHITO]
Damn it!
Will that be enough to win?
[cell phone buzzing]
Hmm?
Huh? Hinomaru!
Wait up!
[HINOMARU]
Hmm?
[KIRIHITO]
Hey, Master!
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
Oh, is, uh, Hinomaru there?
I can hear you, sir.
[SHIBAKIYAMA] You don't sound
that happy about it.
Oh, we are.
It's just we were watching
videos of Tennoji, so...
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
That good, huh?
[HINOMARU gulps]
[SHIBAKIYAMA] I'm thinking
the Dachi High team
should come over
and train with us this weekend.
Wrestlers from another stable
are joining us
for a joint training session.
You'd also get a chance to fight
someone at the ozeki level.
A real life ozeki?
We're honored, but I thought
you were gearing up
for the July tournament.
We'd be a distraction
while you were preparing.
[SHIBAKIYAMA] If I thought that,
would I've mentioned it?
When an adult makes you an offer
at a time like this,
you should accept.
Yes, sir!
[KIRIHITO] But wait.
Isn't the July tournament in...
Now you're putting
the pieces together.
I'll see you when you
make it to Nagoya.
[indistinct chatter]
[REINA] I've been thinking,
it's pretty strange.
You wanting to be a manager
of a sumo club and all.
I don't see it that way.
I think it's a great idea.
Oh, all right.
So I guess you got excited
about it
after watching them
at prelims yesterday.
Way before, actually.
Huh?
[CHIZUKO] I've been interested
since that day
when I first saw him.
[inaudible]
[chuckles]
-[CHIZUKO giggles]
-Hmm?