You don't need to fight
in the team tournament.
[groans]
[OZEKI]
Just as I thought.
Were you planning
on telling us?
[HINOMARU] I'm perfectly fine!
This is nothing!
[OZEKI] Tsuji's calling
for a taxi to come pick you up.
Then you're going
to the hospital.
You're not done, Ushio.
Your dream of joining
the pro league isn't over.
Not as long as the team
tournament's still up for grabs.
♪
[knocking on door]
It's Shibakiyama!
Open up, Doc!
[knocking on door continues]
[DOCTOR]
I heard ya, I heard ya.
[door opens]
Keep it down, will ya,
Kaorucchi?
You wouldn't believe
the savage hangover I've got.
[HINOMARU]
Um, I'm not so sure about this.
[CROWD cheering]
♪
[KANAMORI]
That's impossible.
He pushed me out of the ring?
♪
It's not like he gave up
on using strikes.
Tenma's just been practicing,
and now he's a grappling master.
[CROWD applauding]
[ANNOUNCER] That concludes
today's individual bouts.
Team tournament
preliminary bouts
will begin now.
♪
[DOCTOR]
Uh, Hinomaru... Ushio.
Fifteen years of age.
[HINOMARU]
This dump's worse than my place.
Uh! 152 centimeters tall?
He's tiny!
Big deal.
I'm still gonna be a pro!
Come on, kid!
You know there's
a physical, right?
Get your head out of the clouds
and join reality.
I'm a busy man,
and look how sunny it is.
Shine on, Mr. Sun.
Shine on.
Blue seas,
white sandy beaches.
Tanned, taut bodies
in colorful bikinis.
Summer. And it's calling
my name.
Ignoring it would be criminal.
Hey, first impressions
aren't everything.
[DOCTOR]
Gotta go. Ciao.
Excuse me!
[DOCTOR]
Now what?
You don't get it!
My teammates are waiting
for me to get back!
♪
We must be a magnet
for bad luck.
I mean, drawing last year's
third-place team
in the first round?
Come on!
And three of the competitors
we'll be facing participated
in that tournament.
Huh?
[CHIZUKO]
That's not all.
Among the competitors is
national treasure Hikage Tenma.
♪
So what you're saying is,
we could be
seriously screwed here.
[ANNOUNCER] For the next match,
on the east side,
Odachi High School.
On the west side,
Kanazawa Kita High School.
[YUMA]
Okay, go get 'em!
[ANNOUNCER] First bout.
On the east side, Ozeki.
Yeah!
On the west side, Aizawa.
-Bring the pain, Captain!
-You got this!
That's Ryo Aizawa.
“Swift Foot Pull.”
Although not the biggest,
he's the captain
of the formidable
Kita High team.
He's deadly.
♪
[DOCTOR]
I'm not gettin' any younger.
I don't see the point
in wasting my time.
"Wasting"?
Your team's up against
Kanazawa Kita High
first round.
Just between us,
you don't actually expect them
to win, do you?
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
Hmm?
♪
[DOCTOR]
The kid went into standby.
Did you understand the question?
[HINOMARU]
Now that I think about it,
I guess there's a chance
they could lose.
What?
But the thought never crossed
my mind until just now.
Uh...
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
[grunts]
[panting]
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
[yelling]
[ALL yelling]
You know,
hearing I wasn't needed
at the team tournament
was a shock.
It made me nervous.
But after I listened
to the captain
and saw the look
the rest of the team
had in their eyes...
I suddenly felt relaxed
about the whole thing.
This isn't about them
needing my help
or how they can't win
without me.
I just need
to fight with them.
Right now,
that's all I want.
[sighs]
Well, let's see it.
[HINOMARU grunts]
If you care
about your career,
it'd be better for you
in the long run
to sit this one out.
Yep!
That's what a doctor
with any common sense
would tell ya!
Hmm?
I swear.
I wish I knew
where you got your moxie from.
How about sharing it
with the rest of us?
Listen, kid, I've treated a lot
of sumo wrestlers in my time.
Some of them were
too messed up
to even step foot
back inside the ring.
But that didn't stop them
from coming to see me.
Getting your arm back in shape
will be easier
than cutting a fart.
[HINOMARU] What is this?
A spaceship?
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
I never get over this room.
By the way, when are you
gonna bite the bullet
and invest in a new sign, Doc?
I like the sign.
It's got a certain charm.
This way.
Let's get that arm
working again.
That's surprising.
Ozeki's the last person
I could imagine
going full-on beast mode.
I guess
that settles it, then.
Beating you at the prelims
wasn't just a fluke.
And he's only gotten stronger
since then.
Here I was thinking
Onimaru's absence
would be weighing on him.
But apparently it only made him
more determined to win.
His expression and technique
were full of spirit.
There's a face that shouts
"I'm Dachi High's captain!"
By the way,
look who's up next.
-Your favorite fighter.
-Huh?
[ANNOUNCER] Second bout.
On the east side, Gojo.
-Go, Yuma!
-Hail the king!
[HINOMARU]
Before he joined the sumo club,
he used to be a delinquent.
Huh?
But...
he's different now.
Trust me.
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
[growling]
[YUMA]
Uh...
He was ready
for the two-handed strike!
That's Takumi Sera!
His strength is incredible!
He placed fourth
in the Ishikawa tournament.
[SERA]
Think I'm intimidated?
I withstand
Tenma's strikes every day!
[growling]
Bring it!
[HINOMARU]
Honestly,
when I first met him
during his kingpin days,
I thought the guy belonged
in an entirely different decade.
But after we fought
and he admitted defeat
by bowing his head,
I knew that he was okay.
Before you can improve,
you need humility.
Without it, the thought
of combining sumo and karate
would be completely crazy,
but he found a way
to marry the two.
We're expecting
great things out of him.
[groaning]
[SERA]
He's too fast!
[KANAMORI]
Rather than pushing back,
his opponent's ricocheting.
Each blow's hitting him in a
completely different direction.
Sera couldn't make a grab
against that karate-like
snapping even if he wanted to.
That was your mistake.
You shouldn't have
let him build momentum.
Wearing me down, huh?
Yeah, right.
I'm ending you right now!
♪
[YUMA] Trip and strike.
Castle Break Punch!
♪
[SERA grunts]
Yeah!
[CROWD cheering]
Yes!
-Yuma!
-[CHIZUKO giggles]
[HASHI/NISHIZATO]
Get 'em, boss!
That was awesome, Yuma!
[MAN 1] Looks like
Kita High's washed up.
[MAN 2] A powerhouse team?
Yeah, right!
Both teams wanted
to carve out an early lead.
Two wins in a row
is a huge deal!
They're in a solid spot
right now.
Yes, but this next bout
will be a problem.
Their third opponent's going
to be a much bigger challenge.
Literally.
[AIZAWA]
It's all up to you, Tenma.
[TENMA]
Hmm?
You don't need encouragement
from your sorry excuse
for a captain,
and I know a national treasure
can handle himself,
especially against an amateur.
But I want to say this
to you anyway.
Go out there and win!
Damn it!
I'm sorry, guys!
[groans]
What a bunch
of pathetic teammates.
Huh?
[TENMA] A national treasure
who fails to become
a high school yokozuna.
A renowned school
without a championship.
I don't know about you,
but I'm here to change all that.
Watch and learn.
Yone. Komori.
Prepare for your bouts.
You better be paying attention.
Ishigami won't win
the finals next year
if you don't come up with a plan
for how to defeat this guy.
Hey, Captain,
which one are you
talkin' about?
[ANNOUNCER]
Third bout.
On the east side, Kunisaki.
[DOCTOR] So your teammate's
a renowned wrestling champion?
Impressive.
But he's only been doing sumo
for a few months, right?
And he's fighting
someone like that?
[HINOMARU] I don't like
throwing the word around,
but, in his case,
I'll gladly make an exception,
'cause there's no other way
to describe him.
♪
The truth is...
[HINOMARU/SADA]
Chihiro Kunisaki...
is a genius.
♪
[CHIHIRO] He's got a 20
centimeter advantage over me.
This must be what Hinomaru
feels like all the time.
♪
[CHIHIRO chuckles]
[CROWD murmuring]
Hmm?
[CHIHIRO] All right,
Mr. National Treasure.
How you gonna attack?
At that distance,
he's a sitting duck
for one of the best strikers
in high school sumo.
Maybe he's planning on charging
and going in low.
[KANAMORI] Show me
what you're made of, Kunisaki.
Even Sada acknowledges
your talent.
I want to see what you can do
against an elite fighter.
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
[grunting]
[groaning]
[gasping]
Even charging full speed,
he wasn't quick enough!
Did you really think
you'd be safe
if you held back like that?
Nearly the entire sumo ring
is within his range.
His speed, power,
they're completely unmatched!
There's no better example
than his Flash Attack!
[CHIHIRO grunting]
Oh!
Kunisaki's getting destroyed!
He can't get in a single hit!
I guess he was nowhere
near ready
to take on
a national treasure.
[CHIHIRO] If I want
to become a better fighter,
my sumo needs a ton of work.
I realize I don't have
enough time
to get there on my own.
So here's the plan.
I'm gonna absorb
your sumo style
and then soar
straight to the top!
Uh...
[gasps]
Yes!
Was he holding back
all this time
so he could evaluate
Hikage's attack pattern?
He sure had to take
a pummeling to do it, though.
The best strikes
in high school sumo
turned out to be more brutal
than he was expecting.
Of course he had a rough time
seeing through them.
Wait just a minute.
Are you telling me
between the prelims and now,
he completely adopted
your style?
The longer you spend wrestling
with the guy,
the more he starts
to creep you out.
[CHIHIRO] I want more.
Show me more!
[SADA] He may lack experience
in the sumo ring,
but he makes up for it
with his powers of observation.
That's the secret
of how he's able
to absorb techniques
so quickly.
It kinda pisses me off.
Here I am, not making it
past the prelims.
But there are my moves.
It's like I'm fighting.
[TENMA]
Mikazuki Munechika?
[CHIHIRO]
So that was the heaviest blow
in all of high school sumo?
Well, if that's the case,
there's nothing left to fear!
He outmaneuvered
Odenta's strike!
♪
Huh?
An over-the-shoulder grab!
His reach is incredible!
But Kunisaki has
a stronger stance!
He can do it!
[TENMA] I can hear them
all laughing at me.
The expectations are high
since I'm a national treasure.
But here I am, losing to a guy
who was a plain wrestler
till a few months ago.
I've already told you,
I've got zero interest
in watching my brother compete.
He'll win,
but only by just enough.
And of course there's no way
he'll beat a yokozuna.
Hey!
We all know
the only thing he's focused on
is remaining an ozeki.
It's truly pathetic.
If he doesn't care about
moving up the chain,
he should just quit.
Damn. What was that for?
[MAN 3] You've got no idea
what you're talking about, kid.
I hear that BS all the time.
But I didn't think his own
brother would go repeating it.
[TENMA]
Huh?
[MAN 4]
I guarantee you,
he's got no chance
of winning this bout!
-[TENMA] Hmm?
-[MAN 4] Seriously.
I've totally given up
rooting for Daikeisho.
"Strongest Japanese
Sumo Wrestler" my ass.
Yeah. Bottom line,
he just isn't hungry enough,
so he's plateaued.
[TENMA]
What do they know?
If you really think
the ozeki view the arena
as some kind of
comfortable safe haven,
you better guess again.
Even more reason, then.
It'd be easier on him
if he quit!
[MAN 3]
I thought it was obvious.
Uh...
♪
[MAN 3]
He isn't broken yet.
Far from it.
♪
Have you ever wondered
why you've always thought
of him as weak?
Maybe you're projecting
your insecurities onto him.
Uh...
[MAN 3] You've been avoiding
looking at the ozeki
because you see
yourself in him.
You believe
he can't defeat a yokozuna
only because you were unable
to beat Tennoji.
Maybe if you took the time,
you could learn
a thing or two
from watching him.
Your brother's far stronger
than you think.
[CROWD cheering]
[TENMA]
If anyone's pathetic, it's me.
Onimaru had that
same look in his eye.
The look of someone
confronting a reality
that threatens to break them.
♪
All I did was get annoyed
and take it out on others.
The only loser here is me.
I want to be
a strong sumo wrestler,
just like my brother!
[TENMA straining]
[KIRIHITO]
An overarm throw!
And from that stance, too!
His reach is insane!
[CHIHIRO straining]
[straining]
-He's close!
-Come on!
[CHIHIRO] Dude's coming at me
stronger than before.
Guess that's why they call him
a national treasure!
I'm gonna eat you alive
and push past my limits!
A feint?
[TENMA]
High-Angle Head Chop!
Lightning!
[groaning]
[ALL gasp]
[SHUNKAI] So this is
Dachi High's Kunisaki.
I see.
His fighting instincts
are sharp.
But he's not ready
to beat Tenma Hikage.
Then again,
perhaps that's why
he challenged him.
Even in sumo,
there are wrestlers
who evolve rapidly
following an upset victory.
He's trying to break
out of his shell.
Fighting isn't enough for him.
Only an upset will free him!
Strongest!
[straining]
-Yes!
Tenma grabbed first!
♪
His right hand's inside
and his left is high!
The perfect grip!
Yeah, boy!
Get him, Tenma!
♪
[SADA]
I thought you were working
on a cross-grip sumo style.
So how come you're ignoring
the mawashi belt so much?
Heh. The thing that
scares me about you
is that I have no idea
what's going through your head.
[CHIHIRO]
All that technical junk,
thrust-and-punch,
cross-grip, blah, blah.
I can't beat specialists
like you
if I get caught up
worrying about specifics.
Huh?
You said you're scared
'cause you have no idea
what I'm thinking about, right?
Suits me just fine.
That's my style of choice.
I want to be unsettling!
[TENMA]
Huh? What's he doing?
And what's this dark aura?
♪
[CHIHIRO]
I want to be stronger!
Stronger!
And the only way...
that's gonna happen...
is by causing an upset!
-That move!
-Did he just...
[CHIHIRO]
Neo Chihiro Special Number One!
Shoot Down!
[gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[chuckles]
[BOTH gasp]
[ALL cheering]
[MAN 5]
He beat last year's bronze!
[MAN 6]
Dachi High's unstoppable!
[CROWD cheering]
[HINOMARU] People who let common
sense control their actions
place a wall between themselves
and national treasures.
They build them up as special.
An opponent they have absolutely
no chance of defeating.
But Chihiro
doesn't believe in walls.
Only distance.
That's why he can charge ahead
without any fear.
And the thing
about guys like him,
is that they're usually
the ones who cause an upset.
[ANNOUNCER] Uh, Kunisaki
on the east side wins
with, um,
a kimono-string drop.
A kimono what?
The hell is that?
Wait, so you executed
a technique
the pros rarely use
without even knowing
what it's called?
Unbelievable!
He was operating
on pure instinct!
You're a scary dude,
you know that?
Sure it may be a sumo technique,
but it goes completely
against traditional norms.
So in other words,
it fits Kunisaki to a T.
♪
My national treasure name?
Yeah, man.
If you beat one,
you gotta have a moniker.
That's how it goes.
Screw that.
Those are only for guys
who are interested
in becoming a yokozuna.
I want to be the best mixed
martial artist in the world,
and nothing's changing that.
Still, if I had to choose.
And it's not like I've been
thinking about it or anything.
My official title
is Chihiro Kunisaki.
The "National Treasure Eater!"
♪
[BOTH chuckle]
[ALL chuckle]
[OZEKI]
Ushio!
♪
[laughs]
National Treasures?
Yeah, I eat 'em!
Explains my name.
I'm "The Kid."
[ALL]
Huh?
You know, 'cause kids
are always hungry.
-Uh, sure.
-Yeah, no.
Uh...