-[WRESTLERS grunting]
-[punches thudding]
[KANO] What's my motivation
for the tournament?
[FEMALE REPORTER]
We'd love to hear what drives
the national treasure Okanehira,
Hakuro sumo club's number two.
I don't know if motivation
is the right word,
but there's one thing I hate.
Losing.
I remember standing
by my father's side,
watching as countless teams
had their dreams destroyed.
Sumo is a cruel sport.
Don't you agree?
[REPORTER]
Right.
[KANO] You can train hard
for three years of high school
and still be defeated.
All that work, for nothing.
I never want my team
to experience that feeling.
Let me make one thing clear.
The agony of defeat
is for our opponents only.
[YOMODA]
I wonder what Kano's odds are.
-What?
-Nothing.
Just doesn't seem
like he enjoys sumo.
Gah!
[YOMODA]
I mean, just look at Sosuke
and the other
national treasures.
The sport holds a special place
in their hearts.
But Kano's a totally
different breed.
Always talking about his father
and the team.
Everyone else, you know.
But what about himself?
♪
Guys like that
never reach the top,
whatever field they're in.
I'm not saying he's weak
or anything.
The guy's proven himself.
Maybe he's the exception
to the rule.
Who knows?
[SAWAI]
Kunisaki's similar.
A former wrestler who's been
setting the sumo ring ablaze.
[YOMODA] But in terms
of raw sumo ability,
Kano's far scarier.
There's no competition.
[KIRIHITO]
Two losses.
It's do or die.
With our backs against the wall,
Kunisaki can't afford
to take any risks.
It's all up to him.
♪
-[REFEREE] Spirit!
-[CHIHIRO grunts]
[MAN 1]
That was a sharp strike!
Kano opened
with his killer stance!
It's strong defensively
and a perfect set-up.
He absorbs his opponent's force
while leaving enough room
to execute a throw!
[KANO]
Where do you think you're going?
[BOTH grunt]
Seriously, don't you ever get
tired of devouring moves?
The National Treasure Eater's
using Odenta's Flash Attack!
[grunting]
[KANO]
Unreal.
Yeah! Now that's what
I'm talking about!
Don't stop!
[KANO]
What a maniac.
He's going hard on offense
even though losing means
they'll be eliminated.
Out of all the times
to hold back,
now's not one of them.
There's no question
you're strong.
You're a member of the top
high school sumo club in Japan.
Just one thing.
That makes your fear of losing
even greater.
-Keep it up, Kunisaki!
-[CHIHIRO] Call it reckless,
-I don't care.
-You can do this!
[CHIHIRO]
But you can't grow
if you don't defeat your fears.
He knows that better
than anyone.
Remember him?
You called him weak.
Said his efforts
were meaningless!
-I'll show you.
-[KANO grunts]
[CHIHIRO] Just how strong
people who don't know
their own limits can be!
-Kano can't react fast enough!
-[BATO] Hmph.
That's it, Kunisaki!
Yeah!
He copied that move.
So what gives?
Kano should be able to block it
since he's never lost to Odenta!
He's mimicking it,
but it's not an exact copy.
Their reach and build
are nothing alike.
But thanks to those differences,
it's faster and has a different
rhythm from the original.
The move's transformed
and become a Chihiro Special!
Get a grip!
His strikes may be faster,
but they're not as hard!
I can block them!
High-Angle Head Chop:
Lightning!
Great hit!
The second best at Hakuro High
is going down!
[grunts]
[KANO]
Is this the end?
[MAN 1]
That's two years in a row!
[MAN 2] Tennoji's high school
yokozuna again!
-[CROWD cheering]
-[panting]
[chuckles]
Different year, same result.
Does facing a teammate
make you lose intensity, Aki?
Huh?
[TENNOJI] Back in middle school,
you shined much brighter.
You've gotten used
to losing to me,
and your light's dimmed.
We're rivals, remember?
Fight harder.
[KANO]
Don't overestimate me.
We've trained side-by-side.
I already know the truth.
I have no hope of beating you.
You can laugh all you want.
I don't care.
Being second only to Shido...
-[yells]
-...fills me with more pride
than you can imagine!
[groans]
Watch out for the grab!
[KANO] I'm not losing
to anyone but Shido!
Not Kusanagi
and definitely not to you!
Being cornered
must've lit a fire in him.
[ENOKI]
Kano always tells people
he's only half
as talented as Shido.
But we know the truth.
He loves sumo as much as we do!
[BOTH straining]
[MAN 1]
He's got his belt!
That's not good!
Kunisaki can't pull away!
And his agility's useless
in close quarters!
[YUMA] He's gripping both sides
of the mawashi belt!
[KIRIHITO]]
This could be bad.
Even he doesn't have a technique
that can break him free!
[CHIHIRO] There aren't
any throws that'll get me
out of this mess.
Fine, then.
[CHIHIRO straining]
Guess I'll just bulldoze him
out of the ring!
Is he trying a...
Force-out?
[CHIHIRO]
You didn't trap me.
I'm the one who caught you!
Yeah, it's true
you're more experienced in sumo,
but when I'm inside
this ring.
I'm no longer a wrestler!
[CHIZUKO]
Prior to this match,
Kunisaki would've
thought of a way
to break his grip
and pull back.
But he's not
the same person anymore.
He's made significant progress
as a sumo wrestler.
And he's facing an equal.
It all comes down to this,
a battle of wills!
♪
[BOTH grunting]
[KANO]
Why isn't he stopping?
Instead of getting weaker,
he keeps adding more
and more pressure!
[CHIHIRO] I don't love
the front force-out.
It's got no style.
But when you did it,
it was anything but boring!
♪
And after seeing that look
in your eyes,
no way I'm going to whine about
style points and risk losing!
[ALL gasp]
[YOMODA]
You remember how a second ago
I was all for Kano losing.
-Huh?
-Scratch that.
I think I'm starting
to hate Kunisaki even more.
[CROWD cheering]
[REFEREE]
East side wins!
[ANNOUNCER] Kunisaki is
the winner by force-out!
[blows nose]
[CHIZUKO]
Not a very showy finish.
Your match might've been
what he needed
to keep his ego in check.
He and I started learning sumo
at the exact same time.
Look at him now.
He's just too cool.
[cheering]
Kano had no idea
what he was up against.
He misjudged his opponent
and was destroyed.
Duly noted.
He's a threat.
The guy just keeps
getting stronger.
[HYODO]
I don't believe my eyes.
Both Hakuro and Odachi
have female managers.
Somebody want to tell me
why we don't?
Uh, what about the match?
[HYODO laughs]
Kano lost because of Kano.
Chihiro came at him full force
instead of being clever,
while he hesitated.
To put it another way,
the opponent revealed
his weakness
and Chihiro saw
his chance to strike.
Brilliant move, which he got
from watching me, no doubt.
♪
I let you all down.
Bat will finish this.
♪
[SANADA]
Huh.
That's the Mongolian
exchange student.
The first-year,
Batmonkh Batbayar.
You can only field
one foreigner per tournament.
And the guy managed
to earn that spot
when he was fresh out
of middle school.
I'm picking up some
intense vibes from him.
Same here.
Dachi High's only hanging on
by a thread,
and look who's next up
on the roster for them.
He's never competed
under this kind of pressure.
-My dude, Kunisaki!
-Ha-ha!
Man! You really came through
for us there!
Yeah, 'course I did.
It's me.
Well, bud.
You're up now, so show us
what you can do.
Kick...
Yeah. Sure.
What was that?
[BOTH gasp]
Are you still alive?
[KANAMORI]
It's over.
Everything's riding on you, bro,
and this is when you choke?
You know what this match means,
don't you?
If you lose, it's all over
for Dachi High!
-[YUMA grunts]
-[CHIHIRO] We won't be
-the best in Japan!
-[YUMA grunts]
[CHIHIRO] And Hinomaru's chances
of making it
to the pro league are dead!
[grunts]
He's got enough stress.
Maybe we shouldn't add more.
Besides, he's only feeling
the crunch
because I lost my bout.
[YUMA]
What'd you say?
[MAN 2] Dachi's wrestler
looks frozen in place.
Yuma.
[ALL gasp]
♪
[YUMA]
That's right. Ozeki did lose.
He lost two years of his life
because of what I did.
Now everyone's dream,
and that shrimp's future,
it all depends on me.
Relax.
This isn't a reckoning.
It's an opportunity.
How so?
Hold on.
This is what
I've been waiting for.
My chance to help everyone.
Ozeki, Shorty, the sumo club.
I can make it all right.
And if the thought of that
makes me shake,
then I'll fight trembling
the whole time.
[takes long, deep breath]
[CROWD murmuring]
[exhales sharply]
I belong to the Dachi sumo club.
Time for me to carry
some of the weight.
Right.
You ought to do like that guy
and chill out, mom.
I am calm.
[TAKANI] He'll give it his all,
so don't look away.
You have to watch,
no matter what happens.
[BATO sighs]
How did I get stuck
fighting you?
Huh?
You should know up front
that I'm way stronger
than Kano.
I'm not here to play.
There are a lot of eyes
in the crowd
watching how I perform today.
Each stable can only have
one foreign fighter.
And with that kind
of limitation in place,
I've got to show 'em
that I'm better
than the rest
of the competition.
How am I supposed
to stand out against you?
Onimaru on the other hand,
there's a real challenge.
-You done?
-Hmm?
[YUMA]
I don't care why you're here.
You're just a roadblock
in my team's way!
And I'm gonna be the one
who tears you down!
Place your hands on the ground!
[ENOKI] Mongolian sumo
doesn't use a ring.
The match ends only when
a competitor falls.
Up close and personal
is Bat's specialty.
And Spikey here loses
in those types of situations.
We got lucky.
This bout's in our favor.
♪
[REINA]
You've got this.
I believe in you.
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
[YUMA grunting]
-[KIRIHITO] Ahh!
-Strikes!
[BATO]
You like that?
I hear this is what
you specialize in.
I'll beat you using strikes
and show your country
how much stronger I am than you!
♪
[YUMA] So you're as strong
as a national treasure?
Then there's no way
I should be able to beat you.
-[YUMA grunting]
-[BATO groans]
[YUMA] But it looks like
I don't have a choice!
Holy crap!
He's breaking out the karate!
Let him have it!
[YUMA]
I can't lose this match!
-[gasps]
-[YUMA] If I do,
he'll regret his own loss
the rest of his life!
I'll help make Dachi High
the best in Japan,
even if I have to lay down
my life doing it!
[BATO]
Looks like I underestimated you.
Good. At least crushing you
will be worth my time!
[BOTH grunting]
I thought Batbayar
was from Mongolia!
So what's with
the fighting style?
He's only using strikes!
Yuma has a chance of winning!
[BATO]
This guy packs a punch.
[YUMA] I know my strikes eclipse
Odenta's and Kunisaki's!
They're my path to victory!
[BATO] Unlike me,
you've never been an outsider
or had to fight
for a place at the table.
That's why you'll lose!
Say that again!
I dare you to repeat it!
[BATO]
As many times as you'd like.
You're weaker than me,
so I deserve your spot.
There's only room
for one foreigner on this team.
[TENNOJI]
That's enough, Bato.
Before focusing on strength,
start with basic manners.
Yeah, right.
I won't defer to someone
weaker than me
-just because they're older.
-[slaps hand]
The reason I came to your
country was to become a pro.
Unlike the rest of you,
I'm not here to play nice!
Why don't we have
a bout to find out
which of us is stronger?
And before we start,
I want to know what I get
after I'm finished with you.
I'll tell you once, Bat,
knock it off!
[TENNOJI]
So, mutual respect won't exist
until we meet each other
in the ring?
All right then.
Whenever you're ready,
I think you and I
should get better acquainted.
♪
[BATO straining]
[BATO]
He's crazy strong!
Am I losing? How?
Not to a Japanese student!
No!
I don't believe it!
This can't be happening!
If I lose, my dream's dead!
I'll never be a yokozuna!
[TENNOJI]
What a fool.
[bone cracks]
-[gasp]
-[body thuds to ground]
[BATO groans]
Act like a beast,
I'll treat you like one.
You went too far
when you'd already won.
Why were you so rough on him?
[TENNOJI]
Rough? Hardly.
He would've done
exactly the same to me
if the roles were reversed.
That's the battle he wanted.
It's not as if I could
let him win.
After all, we're both idiots
trying our hardest
to be yokozuna.
[gasps]
[chuckles]
There's extra space
in my dorm room.
I'll teach you everything
from basic manners
to how to scrub a toilet.
Sound good?
[BATO]
Did you really think
you could beat me with strikes?
Guess again!
Tennoji and my other teammates
are the only ones worthy
of being called sumo wrestlers!
I've sweat and bled beside them!
You're nothing!
[grunting]
Batbayar's got
the advantage now!
He's avoiding Gojo's impacts
while hitting back hard!
Yuma's getting more strikes in,
so what gives?
[TAKANI] His opponent has
better accuracy.
He keeps landing
critical hits to the torso.
[grunts]
Improved karate!
Winding Defense!
[HINOMARU]
He's still up.
Gojo should've had
the advantage!
[groans]
[KIRIHITO] But he was
completely outmatched!
[YUMA]
If he gets my belt, it's done.
[BATO]
How'd he do that?
My wrist was hidden from view
and he still managed to grab it!
That's impossible!
[TAKANI]
Yes!
Close range.
That's how sumo is fought.
So you won't have a full view
of your opponent.
With only limited information,
you must predict their moves
and react accordingly.
Even when blind.
♪
You trusted my instruction
and based your training on it.
You've always been
straight-forward.
That's your biggest strength!
♪
Reel-in lunge strike!
[BATO]
If that hits, I'm done!
He dodged it!
[BATO] So you were waiting for
me to grab your mawashi belt?
Too bad it didn't help!
You're wide open!
[YUMA gasps]
It's about time.
-Thank you very much.
-[BATO gasping]
This is what he was
really after?
Yes!
He faked only being good
at strikes.
And to sell the lie,
he kept something hidden,
his secret weapon!
Gojo's actually grappling!
Yuma!
Do it!
Go!
Three-Point Attack.
Deformed Triple Attack
Force-Out:
Call Out!
[HINOMARU]
The leg trip didn't work.
He still has two points
of contact left!
[BOTH straining]
[BATO]
I've got to applaud him.
He's not a national treasure,
but he's tough all the same.
Too bad that's not enough!
With just one hand?
[BATO]
I'm going to become a Yokozuna
and be better than Tennoji!
There's a reason
I always talk big.
So I have to live up
to my own hype!
If I don't win,
I can't stay in this country!
Double Kick. Wolf Fangs!
Hang in there, Yuma!
It didn't force him down!
[BATO]
I have to grab his belt!
[YUMA]
Lower block!
-Reverse strike!
-[groans]
-Joint strikes!
-[grunting]
Inside leg trip!
Here it comes!
The extreme form
of the unconventional Gojo!
Yuma! Do it now!
Partial Lunge.
Castle Break Punch!
♪
There's still fire in his eyes!
The surprise grapple
didn't work,
and neither did
the all-out strike combo!
♪
No.
[grunting]
[YUMA]
Trust the team. Trust them.
-And never stop fighting.
-[ALL chattering]
You can do it Yuma!
[YUMA]
It's working.
Don't stop!
Keep hitting till
your arms fall off!
Hear me?
Put it all on the line!
Everything!
Push him!
[TAKANI] He fights at his peak
when it's for someone else.
After everything, you still
can't forgive yourself.
I want to see
that seriousness rewarded.
We all do.
Keep striking, Yuma!
Take him down!
Win this.
If not for anyone else,
do it for yourself!
[sighs]
[grunting]
[panting]
[ALL]
Uh...
[TAKANI]
Know what I hate?
Stories about punks
seeing the light.
Because they always
end up making me cry.
♪
[REFEREE]
East side wins!
[cheering]
[whimpering]
[crying]
[ALL whimpering]
[TAKANI]
You better not end up like him.
He's such a pain.
[breathing deeply]
♪
You ever notice
how he deep fries chicken
whenever something's
weighing on his mind?
I wonder what happened now.
It's cool
if I sample one, right?
Oh! What'd you use
for the seasoning?
They're dipped in a corn soup
I'm trying out.
Fried chicken is life!
Mind if I try ten?
Those still need to be refried.
Duh!
Obviously, he's in a mood
because he lost to Bato today.
-Mm, mm.
-[SAKI] Mystery solved.
[TENNOJI humming]