[SHUNKAI]
Their second win.
Eiga's the first to catch
a glimpse of the finish.
They're close.
One more loss and Odachi's out.
[YAMATOKUNI] Do I hear a couple
of old-timers giving commentary?
Ah. Yamatokuni.
You made it.
This meeting's long overdue.
Greetings, Shunkai,
and Master Shibakiyama.
Is the Heisei era's
greatest yokozuna here
to watch his son
emerge victorious?
That's partly reason, yes.
But I also wanted
to see them in action.
After all, these young men
are the future of sumo.
[ANNOUNCER]
Fourth bout.
On the east side, Ozeki.
I'm ready.
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER]
On the west side, Daniel.
Let's go!
[MAN] We get to see
the blond sumo wrestler fight!
Daniel! You can do it!
[WOMAN]
Check out his cute smile!
What's the deal?
Everyone's losing their minds.
I believe it's partly because
there are so few Caucasians
who participate
in high school sumo.
But also, his performance
is a major factor.
While he may not have won
the individual tournament,
I heard he held
his own against Kuze.
Wait. What?
[CHIZUKO]
His physique is flawless.
Even the pros
are watching his progress.
He's similar to Bato.
There's no way for a foreigner
to achieve
a national treasure moniker,
even though his abilities
are basically
on the same level as one.
Here comes our secret weapon,
hailing from Europe.
I've nicknamed him
King Arthur's
legendary sword Excalibur!
You're the only one
who calls him that.
[TENMA]
As good as a national treasure.
He may be too much for Ozeki.
[HINOMARU]
Captain!
Remember to stay level-headed!
Hmm.
[CHIZUKO]
You know...
I've noticed
something interesting
during this tournament.
Ushio supports
each of his teammates
in the way they need
to be supported.
They're such
different people,
but he understands
them all so well.
[MAN]
Whoa! Standing side-by-side,
the European dude dwarfs him!
There's no point
comparing physiques.
That's irrelevant.
Sumo's about
something more: Spirit.
Before this match, you said so,
and I completely agree.
Your team may be small,
but their passion isn't.
Even though I'm a large dude,
I used to be weak.
Sumo, and moving here,
it's changed me.
Totally. I was weak, too.
Promise you won't laugh,
but I didn't win a single bout
until last year.
Dang.
That's seriously weak!
[OZEKI]
Yeah, thing is...
I'm not weak anymore.
Same goes for me.
In that sense, we have
something in common, don't we?
[chuckles]
Guess so.
He loved sumo so much,
he moved to a different
continent to gain experience.
I've heard its popularity
is catching on overseas.
But actually deciding
to pursue it,
that takes a huge amount
of courage.
♪
[DANIEL]
Looking at you, I can just tell.
You're into sumo as much as me.
And I bet I know
the reason you got stronger.
Because...
I was the same!
♪
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
-[REFEREE] Spirit!
-[grunts]
Slap strikes!
[OZEKI]
He wasn't kidding!
So, he's stronger now, huh?
Well, it's true.
Daniel used to be weak.
[grunts]
We had high hopes
for our exchange student,
but when he saw him wrestle,
it turned out he was just
some beefed-up sumo fanatic.
Sure, he had the advantage
of a huge frame.
But he didn't have any clue
how to use it.
A left-arm clamp.
Looks sorta familiar.
Almost exactly
like your technique.
[BOTH straining]
[OZEKI] All of us
discovered sumo the same way.
By watching
the legendary Yamatokuni
competing in the ring.
I wanted to be just like him,
even if it meant
traveling to a sumo club
in the next town
over to practice.
It didn't matter.
Was it the same for you?
Living on another continent,
trying to copy your hero?
I know you're doing
his signature move:
the left-arm clamp!
Don't think so!
I won't let you seal off my arm!
I doubt his intention
was mimicking me.
My guess is, he learned
from watching Sosuke.
Hold your ground!
Keep grinding it out
till you can grab him!
[OZEKI] I can do this.
In a battle of patience...
I can beat anyone!
[DANIEL]
Guy has mental strength.
He's got a bulletproof spirit.
The same as Onimaru's!
[OZEKI] It was Ushio
who opened my eyes.
He taught me
what makes sumo fun!
-[HINOMARU] Captain.
-Huh?
Go win.
[OZEKI]
Tasting victory has only proven
what I already knew.
I absolutely love this sport!
[YOMODA] I'm starting
to suspect these two
might have more in common
than I first thought.
They used to be weaklings
up until recently.
Then, someone new
entered their life.
A person who changed
them completely.
♪
They met their heroes.
-[MAN] Ozeki!
-[WOMAN] Daniel!
[OZEKI] Keep grinding it out.
Nice and steady.
[DANIEL] I need to get
my arm outside his!
Then I can overpower him,
like I was taught!
I came thousands of miles
to do what I love.
Thought I'd be become
a pro just like that.
Until I got a cold,
hard dose of reality.
I can't beat
a single wrestler!
But I'm larger
than everyone else here!
I was wrong.
Sumo isn't fun.
I spent a year
thinking that way.
Then I met him.
He was still in middle school
at the time
and was going to enroll
at Eiga High School
the following year.
But for some reason,
the club members
weren't exactly welcoming.
[WRESTLER 1] Rumor is he refuses
to contest actual bouts.
[WRESTLER 2] Seriously?
What's his deal?
Does he think
he's better than us?
[DANIEL] I didn't know
anything about him.
But after we fought,
something came over me
and I couldn't help
blurting out.
Y-Yamatokuni!
It was only later they told me
who his father was.
But instead of shocking me,
it made total sense.
I think your sumo's incredible.
Then again, I'm sure it's fun.
Especially when
you're so good at it.
Fighting and not caring
what anyone says must be great.
Uhh!
You've got it all wrong.
-I do care what people say.
-Huh?
I worry about what
they think of my sumo,
and if it lives up
to the Yamatokuni name or not.
I know that doubt
is like an anchor.
It shows how weak I am.
I need to focus solely
on what happens inside the ring
and tune out
what everyone else is saying.
To do otherwise is rude.
An insult to both
my opponent and the sport.
That's cool, but I mean,
you do enjoy it?
Uhh!
I can say I like sumo.
But as to whether or not
I actually enjoy doing it,
I'm not certain.
The thing is...
it's my reason for existing.
I've devoted my life to it.
♪
[DANIEL]
I felt like he was telling me
how naive I was being.
He had the mindset of someone
who was going to make sumo
his livelihood.
Because I was so weak, I decided
to train harder than him.
If he did three hundred stomps,
I'd do four hundred!
[grunts]
If that didn't make
a difference,
I'd know it was time to quit!
Daniel. Sosuke.
New ring assignment.
Starting today, you're both
practicing in the first-string.
[laughs]
And now, that initial love
I had for sumo's come back!
I live and breathe for it!
[MAN 1] He couldn't grab him,
so he switched to strikes!
[MAN 2]
Dude's a beast!
[WOMAN squeals]
[YOMODA]
His rapid improvement just shows
the universal truth about sumo:
it's all about your spirit.
Sosuke used to be
on the third string
and was treated like an outcast.
Out of all the club members,
Daniel was the only one
who kept challenging him.
Anyone who froze him out
didn't get very far.
But those who saw a chance
to spar with Sosuke
as a golden opportunity, well...
There's a reason
they're here at the finals.
[groans]
[straining]
[DANIEL] So, you get struck
harder than that every day?
Then show me
what you're made of!
Ozeki! Do it!
This is like a sneak preview
of Onimaru and Kusanagi's bout.
Looks like he has
no choice but to win.
[OZEKI] Ushio wants to be
the best sumo wrestler in Japan.
And his way forward
is through beating Kuze!
I can't afford to lose
to his protege!
Excellent! He's in position!
[DANIEL]
I can grab him!
Just wait for him
to push forward,
then go for the outside!
I know I'm weak.
The fear of losing is constant.
Ozeki, I hope
I passed some onto you.
This overwhelming dread!
[yells]
[[DANIEL]
I want to know!
Are you having fun yet?
Right overarm throw!
Great Serpent Cleaver!
[ALL gasp]
[OZEKI]
Daniel,
remember when you said
the two of us were similar?
You're completely wrong!
Your only goal seems
to be imitating Kuze.
But me and Ushio
are nothing like that!
♪
It may have only been once
out of the thousand times
we sparred,
but I actually managed
to beat Ushio.
I was so proud of myself,
I bought a little
celebratory cake.
The next day at school,
he was still pouting about it.
Which totally made my week.
♪
Because the thing is,
while we may be teammates...
[BOTH straining]
...we're also rivals!
[yelling]
[CHIHIRO]
Captain!
-[YUMA] You the man!
-[KIRIHITO] We're tied!
[cheering, screaming]
With a beltless arm throw,
East side, Ozeki wins!
[panting]
He needs a ton of work,
but he definitely could be
a national treasure.
You know what?
Ozeki won the battle
with patience
and deserves his moment.
[panting]
[OZEKI]
We're tied now, two-two.
I've done everything I can.
It's out of my hands.
Ushio, I leave the rest to you.
Win this!
[ANNOUNCER] Team tournament
final, bout five.
On the east side, Ushio.
On the west side, Kuze.
[MAN 1] Onimaru versus Kusanagi!
Finally!
[MAN 2]
Two national treasures,
slugging it out to decide
which team is the best.
A lot's riding on this bout.
This could be their chance.
The winner goes on
to the All-Japan
and has a clear path
to joining the pro-league.
Listen to the crowd cheer.
Everyone already recognizes
Onimaru's ability.
Even if he doesn't
make it this year,
it's only a matter of time
before he gets there.
-[SHUNKAI] You've got it wrong.
-Hmm?
His goal isn't just to be a pro.
The boy wants to be a yokozuna.
He doesn't have
an unlimited number of chances.
If he doesn't win today,
how does he expect
to make it a reality?
-[HINOMARU] Hey, guys.
-[ALL] Huh?
What do you think?
Sumo's pretty fun.
Yuma.
We could all see your steady,
earnest efforts to improve.
You kept the club
moving forward.
Chihiro. As an experienced
wrestling champion,
you instilled confidence
in the team.
Kirihito.
You put us on the right path
and kept us there.
Kei. We can't forget
your courage,
even in the face
of daunting odds.
Hori and Reina.
Thank you for being
incredible managers.
You supported us
all the way.
-Captain.
-Huh?
You kept the club alive
for three years
and united us despite
our different personalities.
We're a team 'cause of you.
Everyone.
I'm glad you joined
the sumo club.
And I hope it made
your lives better.
Thank you.
[chuckles]
-You're so dense.
-[ALL] Huh?
If anyone here should be
grateful, it's everyone else.
We all love doing sumo,
but we only learned that
'cause of you.
[ALL chuckle]
All right.
This is going to be
our final bout as a team.
Leave with no regrets!
Go out there and win!
[HINOMARU]
Yeah!
You still think
you have a chance at winning?
Look at him. The sumo gods
have found their vessel.
He's their walking embodiment.
[CROWD cheers]
There's no stopping him.
[KUZE] Again,
this feeling washes over me,
and I like it.
The silence swallows us
as if we're the only
two people in the world.
I can forget about
everything else except for sumo.
-[HINOMARU] Hey.
-Uh?
This doesn't get you pumped?
Me? I can't get enough.
[CROWD cheering, applauding]
[HINOMARU] That's one
of the reasons I came here.
I needed the sound
of applause again.
Louder. Let's hear it!
[applause continues]
Loud enough
to reach the heavens!
[KUZE]
I shouldn't be surprised.
That's how you live.
I've been waiting for this
a very long time.
That right? So have I.
We started our bout that day.
[HINOMARU]
And we end it now.
[BOTH yelling]
Yes.
And neither of us
will hold anything back.
[REINA] As soon as
he entered the ring,
his smile vanished.
[TENNOJI]
Their bout of destiny.
[SHUNKAI]
At last.
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
A spider stance.
He's flickering. Like fire.
[HINOMARU]
I spent years preparing...
for this day!
-That's it!
-He won the charge!
Yeah, Onimaru!
-Ushio!
-Come on!
♪
[HINOMARU] Every do-or-die
bout I survived,
the opponents I've devoured,
the confidence
I had to rebuild...
♪
...all of it fuels my inferno!
[SHIBAKIYAMA] He's loading up
and attacking head-on!
[HINOMARU] I learned
not to rush in without a plan!
Now I choose my target
and lock on to it!
[YOMODA]
That was a rising strike.
The same one Tennoji used!
[groans]
A direct hit!
Don't let Kuze outpace you!
Keep up with him!
[BOTH grunt]
[HINOMARU]
You're quick, but guess what?
I know someone faster!
[grunting]
[SHUNKAI]
Don't underestimate him
because of his reach.
Once he gets in range,
his strikes pack a savage punch.
Shorter arms mean
he can attack faster.
He even held off Odenta,
the best striker
in high school sumo.
[TENMA]
If he manages to catch you
while your guard's down,
you better brace yourself.
He hits harder than you'd think.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
What gives?
He's almost out!
[HINOMARU]
One thing's certain.
I never could've gotten
this far on my own!
Come on!
[HINOMARU]
My team,
they've always had my back!
Push him out!
Whatever fate threw
our way,
we overcame it
despite the odds!
[groans]
[KUZE]
You've truly become strong.
And in such
a short amount of time.
But so have I.
-I'll destroy you...
-[groans]
[KUZE] ...and then I can join
the pro league!
[HINOMARU] Not only are
his moves depleting my stamina,
they're also breaking my spirit.
If I make even
a single wrong move,
I'm dead.
[gasps]
[REINA]
Hinomaru!
[KIRIHITO] Kuze never rushes in
or takes risks!
His offense is impenetrable!
Don't hold still!
Switch sides to get him moving!
What is this rush?
Excitement or fear?
I can't tell.
♪
[YAMATOKUNI] Sosuke,
what makes a yokozuna?
One mistake during a bout,
and the result
could end up proving fatal.
But to err is a human quality.
None of us are exempt.
No matter how careful
we strive to be.
Do you understand, son?
To become a yokozuna, you must
be feared and respected.
It requires you to crush
everyone in your path.
To never show
the enemy mercy.
To achieve that...
you have to cease being human!
♪
So beautiful.
They're in
a different stratosphere.
Both of them!
[HINOMARU]
Don't move sideways! Forward!
[BOTH groan]
Why isn't it working?
Attacking head-on? Is he insane?
The guy's completely fearless!
[HINOMARU]
No, I'm scared.
Of Kuze, of sumo.
-Even so...
-[CHIHIRO] Another strike!
[HINOMARU]
...I'm too close.
I can see my goal
in front of me!
An adversary on the cusp
of turning yokozuna!
[yelling]
[HINOMARU]
I'm willing to risk everything,
even my life,
for victory!
He got in a third strike!
[KUZE] I knock him back
and he doesn't yield!
Figures. You'll never slow down.
That's not your style of sumo.
♪
His hands are inside!
Kusanagi's hands are outside.
They're both in range.
It's either one's game!
[CROWD cheering]
♪
[HINOMARU] Heads together.
Both hands on your belt.
I created this move for only
one purpose: defeating you!
Now, to keep shaking you
and never stop!
I can see the end,
and this technique
will get me there!
[KUZE]
I see what you're doing,
and I won't give you
a chance to start.
This right overhand grip
was taught to me by my father.
It defines my destiny.
-[HINOMARU] Don't hesitate.
-[KUZE] Just one error.
[HINOMARU/KUZE]
And I'll lose!
[REINA] To get better acquainted
with sumo, we gave it a whirl.
[screaming]
[REINA]
But someone didn't knock.
Talk about rude.
And ever since then, Hinomaru's
been acting way different.
-Um, so, you think that we--
-Hmm?
No. It's--
Never mind! Sorry!
What's gotten into him?
It's almost like he wants
to tell us something.
Oh no. You don't think
he secretly lusts after us
and now he wants us
to quit being managers
because we disrupt
his concentration?
I bet you anything that's it!
[REINA] Where the heck
did that come from?
All right, listen up.
If you've got something to say,
then come out and tell us!
I-- All right.
Reina, don't overstretch!
Okay! Perfect!
Good position, Hori!
She can't throw you now!
Yeah, I know
I was supposed
to forget that day,
but I just couldn't
get it outta my head!
So, what do ya say?
Are you two gonna
take up sumo for real?
[REINA]
Dream on.