♪
[HINOMARU]
The Hundred Thousand Demon Drop.
You'll make it a real weapon?
Well? Yes or no?
Do you want to train
under a former yokozuna or not?
Decide!
[HINOMARU chokes]
[HINOMARU] I'd be honored
to train with you!
♪
[MAN scoffs]
[MAN]
How long will you be in Nagoya?
-[HINOMARU] For one week.
-[MAN] All right.
Then the two of you
will be spending
that entire week here with me.
Huh?
I get why you want him here,
but why do I have to stay, too?
Before I take you on
as my apprentice,
there's one thing
you must promise me.
Both you and the young lady.
Uh...
You will do exactly what I say
and without complaint,
and you will never ask me
to explain myself.
Do we have a deal?
[CHIZUKO] Who's that man
who took Ushio and Reina away?
[SAENOYAMA]
Hmm?
Judging by your reaction
when he showed up,
I'm guessing he must be
somebody pretty important.
"Important's"
a serious understatement.
Can't say I'm surprised
Ushio didn't recognize him,
considering how much he's aged.
That man is a former yokozuna
by the name of Shunkai.
He was not only
a skilled wrestler
but also a great trainer.
Two of the athletes he coached
attained the rank of yokozuna.
[gasps]
He trained two yokozuna?
[SEKITORI A]
Well, I gotta say,
I didn't see that one coming.
From what I heard,
he quit the association
and walked away from sumo.
[SEKITORI B]
Think the kid'll be okay?
If the rumors about
the old man are true,
I wouldn't last three days.
[SEKITORI C]
Same here.
[TENMA]
Thanks for all your hard work.
[gasps]
Hey, look who finally showed up.
He's a lot different than that
half-pint national treasure.
[SAENOYAMA] This guy is even
taller than the sekitori.
One glance and you know
he's the real deal.
I appreciate the invitation.
Too bad for Ushio.
I see why he's in such
a rush to improve.
[CHIZUKO] But now he's training
with a former yokozuna.
Even the sekitori
were intimidated by him.
What terrifying trials
will he face?
[REINA panting]
No way we'll be able
to pull this off!
We don't have a choice now.
Our training's started,
and we gotta see it through!
Excuse me! Pardon me!
So sorry!
-Make some room!
-[REINA] Ridiculous!
What the hell kind
of training is this?
The first task
of your apprenticeship
is to go fetch us some food.
♪
[HINOMARU]
Huh?
I'm hungry for curry.
You have exactly thirty minutes
to serve up enough
for all three of us.
-[HINOMARU] Yes, sir!
-No way!
♪
You can't make curry
on that kind of budget.
And with a half-hour time limit?
He told us using our heads
was part of the training.
So there's gotta be a way.
♪
[SHUNKAI] You made me wait
that long for this garbage?
Yes. My apologies, sir.
[SHUNKAI] No toppings,
and you missed your deadline.
You'll have to do better
than that.
[REINA growls]
♪
[REINA] Walk his dog,
water his flowers,
do his damn laundry.
Where's the actual sumo?
We've been stuck doing chores
all day long!
Well, it's all part
of the training.
Still not done?
What have you been doing,
twiddling your thumbs?
[HINOMARU]
Uh, I'm sorry, Master!
[SHUNKAI]
Whatever.
Just get the area around
the sumo ring ready for use.
Huh?
What?
[SHUNKAI] Why are you looking
at me like that?
Don't you want to practice?
Yeah! Thank you, sir!
[REINA]
It's about time.
[door opens]
[MAN] Thank you
for all your hard work.
-[door closes]
-Hello.
Sorry for dragging you out here.
[gasps]
[HINOMARU]
Ganryu!
The fifth-ranked
west maegashira.
Your training partner for today.
Now show him your triple combo.
Yes, sir!
-[HINOMARU growling]
-[GANRYU grunts]
See?
Interesting move,
don't you think, sekitori?
[GANRYU]
Hmm.
[SHUNKAI]
Okay, little demon.
Sir?
[SHUNKAI] Use your triple combo
to win a bout.
You may not use
any other technique to win.
Uh.
Right.
[REINA]
That's all you've got?
No advice or anything?
[HINOMARU grunts]
[REINA] He knows
the element of surprise is gone
once the other guy's seen it.
This is no different from
the practice session earlier.
You've been at it
for fifteen minutes.
That's enough for today.
[groans]
What? It's over?
Damn it.
[REINA groans]
[KIRIHITO]
Here are your bags.
Well?
How's training going so far?
Like you can even
call it training!
The geezer is crazy.
He offered to help,
but all we've been doing
is menial labor.
I say we just call it quits
and head back
to the rest of the team.
This was only my first day.
I can't back out now.
If I gave up like that, I'd
leave with nothing but regrets.
♪
Keep an eye on him for me.
Huh? There's only
so much I can do.
[GANRYU] Master Shunkai
sure lived up to the rumors.
Don't know how he roped that kid
into training with him,
but I feel sorry
for the guy.
He's making him do
all these ridiculous things
just so he can enjoy
the spectacle.
[BOTH gasp]
Supposedly, he turned
two wrestlers into yokozuna,
but I'm betting it had more to
do with their natural ability.
I mean, there were plenty
of others he trained
who couldn't deal
with his stupid stunts
and abandoned ship.
[REINA] That's what
I've been trying to tell you.
[GANRYU]
Now there's this kid.
You'd think the poor sap
would've realized
what's going on.
And what's with that
technique of his?
We're not doing gymnastics here.
He's so desperate
it's laughable.
[GANRYU screams]
I'm sorry!
I shouldn't have spoken
that way about you, sir!
[SHUNKAI] I don't care
what you say about me.
But you'd better make sure
I don't catch you
laughing at that boy.
Because you two have been
blessed with larger frames,
you'll never understand.
Think about it.
There's only so much
the boy can do
with that small body of his.
He needs that technique.
Do you still think
this situation's funny?
He's giving his all.
Never laugh at that!
[REINA] Now he expects us
to make an eight-veggie stir fry
with 100 yen?
Yeah, right.
Not at these prices!
I wonder if this coin's
supposed to represent me
and the veggie stir-fry
is my goal:
learning how to wield
the Hundred Thousand Demon Drop.
-Like a riddle of some kind.
-Huh?
Well, whatever the case,
I'm gonna put my faith in him!
I've decided I'm seeing
this through,
even if he asks me
for the impossible!
Oh, come on!
Seems pretty plain to me.
That looks like
a three-veggie stir-fry.
What happened to the other five?
[HINOMARU] We failed.
I'm sorry, Master.
You should at least
try it, though.
It tastes a lot better
than the curry did.
[SHUNKAI] What makes you think
how it tastes is important?
[BOTH]
Huh?
What was the task again?
Produce an eight-veggie stir fry
with one hundred yen
in thirty minutes.
-You didn't do so.
-[HINOMARU groaning]
[HINOMARU grunting, straining]
I can tell something's
bothering you, young lady.
Uh. I don't know
what you're talking about.
Well, out with it.
Go on.
Is doing this stuff
really gonna help him?
I would think it would be
more effective
just to tell him what to do.
True, spelling it out
is the easy option.
And he'd even feel like
he understood, for a while.
But gaining knowledge in
that way is a fleeting triumph.
The significance of it
doesn't sink in.
[HINOMARU groaning]
I realize this seems like
a roundabout way
of doing things to you,
but thinking on your feet
and working toward an end goal
becomes a technique in itself
that allows you to survive.
♪
[HINOMARU grunts]
[panting]
[slaps landing]
[grunting]
Just one more bout, please,
Saenoyama, sir.
I think it's time for us
to take a breather
and get cleaned up a bit.
We're not the only people
who want to use the ring.
There's no point
worrying about the others.
It won't make us any stronger.
If that's the case,
there's someone else
you should probably ask.
He'd make
a better opponent for you.
Your brother,
the ozeki Daikeisho.
[TENMA]
I don't want to fight him.
[SAENOYAMA]
Why? Do you hate him?
[TENMA]
I wouldn't say that.
I have respect for him.
He hasn't ended a season
with a losing record yet.
He's a talented ozeki.
Still, he's reached
his professional limit.
The strength of the yokozuna
has broken him.
He knows everyone was expecting
him to reach the top,
but he's given up
on that dream.
I find it disgusting.
[SAENOYAMA sighs]
[TENMA]
That's where we differ.
I'll live up to any
and all expectations.
Is that right?
[TENMA]
I'll surpass Tennoji and Kuze.
My own brother, too.
I'll take his place
and be the strongest yokozuna.
What's that shrimp up to now?
Thought he'd back here,
annoying us.
Last I heard, he was still
training with Shunkai,
working around the clock
to improve
that technique
he was showing off.
Did he say Shunkai?
As in the former yokozuna?
You seem well-informed.
Tell me everything you know.
[REINA sighs]
Another day
of indentured servitude.
It's not all bad.
Check out this bath.
The yokozuna must be loaded.
So how come he's only able
to cough up
a hundred yen to buy food?
You'd think he could spend more.
[SHUNKAI]
That's quite the monologue.
[REINA gasps]
[REINA] You eavesdropping,
old pervert! Go away!
I live here, so I think I'll go
wherever I want, young lady.
I must say.
You're working
a great deal harder
than I expected you would.
Well, it's not as if I can just
give up and leave,
or he wouldn't be able
to practice with you anymore.
[SHUNKAI] You've taken
a real liking to him.
[REINA gasps]
What? Don't be stupid!
It's not like that at all!
[SHUNKAI]
Yes. I have, too.
His sumo style inspires people.
[REINA] Oh, he was
just talking about sumo.
I suspect you don't have
a natural affinity
for our sport, do you?
[REINA]
Well...
[SHUNKAI] Yet you want
to see him succeed in the ring.
No one can blame you.
Compared to other wrestlers,
his fighting style has
a certain simplistic charm to it
you just don't ever see
in professional sumo.
Watching him throw someone to
the ground who's twice his size,
that would get even
a dead man's blood pumping.
I think the reason we're both
so willing to help him
is because we're right
there beside him,
wanting the dream to be real.
Yeah, sure I want
to help him out and stuff,
but it's not like
I'm really contributing.
-[SHUNKAI] That isn't true.
-Huh?
[SHUNKAI]
You're here, aren't you?
♪
[SHUNKAI] Let's not mince words,
the kid's got a thick skull.
I thought the two of you would
complement each other nicely,
since you seem to have
a decent head on your shoulders.
That's why I asked you
to stay here in the first place.
Similar to how he's inspired
and influenced you,
I was hoping you'd be able
to rub off on him as well.
[REINA groans]
Don't tell me the master
sent you on an errand this late.
[HINOMARU] I was on the phone
with Kirihito.
Look at this!
To get ready for tomorrow,
I went out and picked up
every last sales flyer
I could get my hands on!
Oh, wow.
I usually just pull up deals
on my phone, like this.
[HINOMARU]
Whoa!
You mean there's
an easier way to do it?
You're incredible!
And you're outta touch.
It may come as shock to you,
but the world's a bigger place
than you think.
Also, you don't have
to use a pay phone.
I would've let you borrow mine.
What I'm saying is, you can
ask me for help, you know?
I mean, it's kinda my job.
Since I am your manager.
Huh? Whoa! Slow down!
Reina, you are a genius!
Yeah.
[SHUNKAI] Aren't you going
to help him today?
You have a hundred yen
and half an hour
to serve tempura over rice.
Nah. It seemed like
he was confident.
[SHUNKAI]
Huh?
[REINA]
[TENMA] Thank you
for all your hard work.
[SHUNKAI sighs]
Did you need something?
As a master, you've successfully
trained two yokozunas.
But perhaps more importantly,
you have the distinct honor
of being one yourself.
That's why
I sought you out, Shunkai.
To teach me.
[SHUNKAI]
Hmm?
Guess what! I...
Uh! Tenma Hikage!
What are you doing here?
Go away. This has nothing
to do with you, Onimaru.
Do you know this mountain?
He just stormed in!
We had an unofficial bout
the other day.
Hikage, sure.
I'm well aware of who you are.
You're the little brother of
the ozeki Daikeisho, aren't you?
Then you must already know
about my dubious reputation.
It appears that the closer
to the top a sumo is,
the more poisonous things
they have to say about me.
I don't give a crap
about rumors.
If I don't think your training
is worth my time,
there's a simple solution.
I'll pick up and leave.
[SHUNKAI growls]
Okay, hang on just a minute!
You want to train under him,
then take a number!
If he's smart, then he'll drop
this runty loser
and make me
his student instead.
-[REINA] What?
-[HINOMARU grunts]
[SHUNKAI]
Listen up, young man.
That's not how you go about
asking to become an apprentice.
Remember, I'm the one
who ultimately decides
if you're worth training or not.
[TENMA]
Obviously.
It's up to the apprentice
to win his master's favor.
I'll show you who's more
deserving of your instruction,
me or Onimaru.
♪
The only problem
we may have is this coward.
He might be too afraid
to accept my challenge.
[HINOMARU]
Ready when you are.
-[SHUNKAI] Not so fast!
-[REINA gasps]
Idiot. What are you doing?
I agree to take you in,
and this is how you repay me?
You haven't perfected
your triple combo technique!
Go ahead and accept
his challenge if you wish,
but be warned,
I'll kick you out!
-Then permit me to fight, sir.
-[SHUNKAI] Hmm?
[HINOMARU]
We were going to eventually.
I'll admit, when we had
our first bout,
I was intimidated by him,
but I need to bury the old me.
Just as I trusted
and followed you,
I'm asking you to place
your faith in me, Master.
♪
I'll win this
by using the
Hundred-Thousand Demon Drop!
♪
[chuckles]
[slaps belt]
[SHUNKAI]
Win me over, huh?
He's more than two meters tall.
Long arms, broad shoulders.
His torso's slightly compact.
Otherwise,
he's the perfect build.
He does evoke
a different kind of excitement
than the little demon.
[whispers]
Excuse me, Master.
If Hinomaru fights,
do we really have to leave?
[SHUNKAI] Don't ask me.
That's just something I made up.
Either way,
if you don't talk a big game,
you'll never get anywhere
near the level of yokozuna.
-Spirit!
-[HINOMARU grunts]
-[BOTH gasp]
-His power's incredible!
[TENMA] In this modern era
of sumo, size is everything.
You'll never have a career
in the ring!
[HINOMARU grunts]
[HINOMARU]
Taking a step back from sumo
has helped me notice
some things.
It's not just my right elbow.
Now that I'm well rested,
my whole body
is overflowing with power!
[HINOMARU yells]
[SHUNKAI] Despite the
little demon's physique,
his body has a rigidity to it.
He's full of surprises.
Nice! Get in close!
[TENMA] The last time,
I let you grab my belt
so I could see
your triple combo.
But I won't be toying
with you this time, Onimaru!
It takes real skill
to strike a target
that low and minuscule
with such intensity.
Hey now!
Forget landing the
Hundred-Thousand Demon Drop,
he's nowhere close
to grabbing his belt!
[TENMA]
So, you want to hit back?
Don't underestimate me!
[HINOMARU]
You're mistaken if you think
I'm some pushover, Odenta!
Don't forget.
I fought another
national treasure.
Mikazuki Munechika!
And grabbed
his untouchable belt!
He's got it!
[SHUNKAI]
Now, show it to me.
The answer you've come up with!
[TENMA] Our ridiculous
difference in height
allows him to execute
a shoulder throw
while holding my mawashi belt.
It's a fearsome technique.
But the third contact point
makes it a double-edged sword.
All I have to do
is avoid the leg sweep.
Your triple combo dies today!
I'll drive you into the ground!
-What?
-[BOTH gasp]
[TENMA]
The hell?
He lifted me up!
[HINOMARU]
Reverse Hundred Demon Throw!
[TENMA]
Damn you!
How dare you mock me!
[REINA gasps]
[HINOMARU]
Yeah.
Maybe I got cocky
'cause of the power
of the technique.
The Hundred-Thousand Demon Drop
is difficult,
but if I can pull it off, I win.
That way of thinking
made my sumo predictable.
That's right.
There are plenty of ways
to initiate the
Hundred-Thousand Demon Drop!
[HINOMARU roaring]
[TENMA]
I can't get out of this stance!
[SHUNKAI]
Before executing the technique,
first you must set up
your opponent.
Even when they know it's coming,
they can't counter it
if they're off-balance.
Now that you're seeing
the big picture...
there's no limit to the ways
you can initiate the move.
As the name suggests,
it becomes an army
of a hundred-thousand demons!
His sumo style inspires people.
Watching him throw someone
to the ground
who's twice his size
would get
a dead man's blood pumping!
[HINOMARU]
Hundred-Thousand Demon Drop!
-[TENMA groans]
-[HINOMARU grunts]
Truly splendid.
It appears you've discovered
the secret
-to unlocking your move.
-Yup.
And based on that, I suppose
you've finally managed
to solve the food riddle
as well.
[HINOMARU]
Yes, sir.
The challenge was to take
a hundred-yen
and come back
with tempura over rice.
You never said
that I had to make it.
All it took me
was one phone call.
Hello! Got your takeout
courtesy of Tenemon.
You wouldn't mind picking up
the tab, right, sir?
I've got only one thing to say
to you, little demon!
You've passed
with flying colors.
Well done, Hinomaru!
You know,
we've done your laundry,
so we might as well
welcome your guest.
[SHUNKAI] This is someone
who deserves the utmost respect.
-[REINA] Huh?
-[SHUNKAI] I'm amazed.
I didn't expect you to stick
with my old-fashioned
training methods.
It's only right that
I reward you for it.
I asked him to make
the trip out here
so Hinomaru can have one,
and only one, bout with him.
Oh, wow.
I mean,
even I know who that is.
Yes, a current yokozuna.
A man at the apex
of the professional sumo world.
Man, you didn't even last
five seconds.
The bout was over
before I had time
to process what was happening.
I can't remember anything I did
or how I ended up down here.
[HINOMARU laughs]
[REINA]
As long as you're happy, weirdo.
I mean, I just witnessed
the power of a yokozuna.
You know I feel sorta guilty.
I'm the only one having
these great experiences.
[REINA]
Huh?
[HINOMARU] I've practiced
with the Shibakiyama stable,
trained with a former yokozuna,
and just had a surprise bout
with a current one.
Being this blessed
scares me to death.
I can't help but feel
something bad's about to happen.
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
So he's blessed.
There's nothing wrong with that.
[SHUNKAI]
Hmm?
[SHIBAKIYAMA] Since he was
shortchanged in physique,
he can be rich
in circumstance instead.
♪
When you reflect
on all that's happened,
do you actually feel
like you've been blessed?
[HINOMARU] Uh...
Yes, sir. I do.
That's good to hear,
because I agree.
You're going to help me dream
a good dream.
Sir!
But this summer,
I'm focusing my energy
on one thing,
high school sumo!
Thanks a ton, Hori!
You're a lifesaver!
You don't mind if I take one?
By the way, you're rocking
that uniform today.
What do you wear
outside of school?
[WRESTLER]
And those glasses are the bomb.
[CHIZUKO]
Have I suddenly become popular?
Yeah, right.
Keep dreaming.