[NARRATOR]
Sumo.
Since ancient times,
warriors clad in mawashi belts
have waged battles
within the ring.
It is one of the few
combat sports
without weight classes.
Thus, student wrestlers
who are heavier
and larger in stature
have a distinct advantage
over the rest
of their competition.
Among them,
there are those
with the potential
to achieve the rank
of yokozuna.
These athletes receive
the name of a sword
from Japan's National Treasures
as their moniker.
[horn blaring]
[grunting]
[gasps for air]
Feels like I'm drowning
in shoulders here. Hmm?
-[MAN 1 moaning]
-[GIRL whimpering]
-[screams]
-So you like being handsy?
I'm thinking you and I
should have a little chat
at the next stop.
We're waiting, sicko.
Apologize to her.
MAN 1: The boy's lying!
Where's your proof?
[scoffs]
From where I was standing,
I could see you clear as day.
God is watching
and doesn't miss a thing.
Let me through, people!
About time you showed.
We got us a pervert.
[OFFICER] No kidding!
Where are your pants?
What're you talking about?
I meant the guy in the suit!
[OFFICER] Is this what kids
are into these days?
-Not wearing pants?
-You got the wrong idea!
I'm checking out a new school
and just wanted to make
a good first impression!
[grunts]
[BOY 1] I was hoping I could
join their morning practice,
but it's already past noon.
Getting off the train
a station too early
really turned me around.
And this map Kirihito drew me
isn't helping the situation.
[groans]
[bell tolling]
There we go!
Now, let's see.
The front gate's gotta be
around here somewhere.
[thudding in distance]
Huh?
[thudding gets louder]
[grunts]
[groans]
[panting]
[BOY 1]
Oh, awesome!
Looks like
I didn't miss practice!
You mind if I join in?
Uh... hold up.
Incredible!
I know I shouldn't
be surprised, but still!
They even have Sumo rings
built outside the dojo!
How ingenious.
The bale's a firehose
filled with dirt.
Yeah, the platform
is packed tight!
I'm sorry. Who are you?
Oh. Guess I forgot
to introduce myself.
I got carried away when I saw
someone in a mawashi belt.
Sorry. I'm a third-year
middle schooler.
I came to check out your school
because of its sumo club.
The name's Hinomaru Ushio.
Good to meet ya.
Before I can be a yokozuna,
the highest rank
in all of sumo,
first, I have to be the best
high school wrestler there is.
[BOY 2]
Did he say yokozuna?
What's your name?
Oh. I'm Ozeki
from the sumo club.
I would love to have a bout
against someone driven enough
to be practicing
during their lunch break.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What're you doing?
-Could you do me favor?
-Huh?
Hand me my bag.
I need my mawashi belt.
[OZEKI] Oh, sure.
Wait, you're changing out here?
[HINOMARU]
No one's looking.
[OZEKI]
One thing's obvious.
This dude's done
some major training.
But where'd he get
all those scars from?
If you're warmed up,
wanna start?
Uh, okay.
He's way intense about this.
All right.
[grunting]
What's wrong?
Is that all you got?
You wanna see
what I'm made of?
[grunting]
Ow, ow, ow.
Not bad.
You didn't do so bad yourself.
[OZEKI] You said your name
was Ushio, right?
I'm kinda surprised
I never heard of you
from any tournaments before.
Yeah. Well, that's a long story.
I haven't done much competing.
Just a few back when I was
in elementary school,
that's all.
Oh, gotcha.
[OZEKI] Kinda feel like
I shouldn't have brought it up.
[HINOMARU]
But that's the whole reason
I want to enroll at this school.
Sorry for missing
the morning practice
and making a bad
first impression.
Morning practice?
You mean you're actually
joining the sumo club?
Of course I am!
-You're for real?
-Yeah.
[giggles]
I can't believe it!
We've got a new club member!
It's not a big deal.
It's so totally a big deal!
-[laughing]
-Well, before you pass out,
how about you take me
to see the dojo?
-Uh...
-Huh?
Um, you see, the thing
about the dojo is.
He was gonna find out
sooner or later.
Looks like the rest
of the club's inside!
What's up?
-Huh?
-[OZEKI groans]
-Hmm?
I didn't say
it would be pretty.
Uh...
I remember hearing this school
had its share of delinquents.
[MAN 2] Who are you calling
a delinquent, short stack?
[MAN 3] Does he come
with batteries?
-[MAN 2] Ozeki!
-[screams]
Who gave you permission
to come wandering around here?
[OZEKI] N-No one!
I just, uh...
[MAN 3]
Quit stuttering and speak up!
-Pick that up.
-Huh?
A dojo is treated with respect.
Do not defile it.
Pick up that trash right now!
Hey, dude. A word?
Do you know who you're
talking to, shrimp?
Not at all. Do you?
[MAN 2 whimpering]
[chattering]
-[MAN 4] Let him go, man.
-[MAN 5] What're you doing?
[MAN 6] What're you mongrels
howling about?
Yuma's back!
And here I was thinking
somebody had stopped by
looking for a fight.
How about you tell me
what's going on, Ozeki.
We... I... uh...
It was this half-sized punk!
Just came in
and started a fight,
no warning or anything!
Say the word
and I'll just go ahead--
-[grunts]
-Huh?
Lesson one:
you're an easy target.
Hey, shrimp. Is everything
that idiot said true?
[HINOMARU]
Yeah, most of it.
I hope you know
what you're getting into.
[HINOMARU sighs]
I got an idea what you can do
with your free time.
-Yeah?
-How about all of you take up
sumo wrestling instead?
Tons of fun. Well?
-[chuckles]
-[ALL laughing]
Fat guys hugging
isn't our idea of fun.
-Looks like he wants to fight.
-Um, hey! Yeah!
So sorry!
He didn't mean any disrespect!
Right on cue.
Odachi's resident coward.
-Odachi?
-The kid's a middle schooler
thinking about joining
the sumo club next year.
-He said Odachi High.
-We need to go! Like now.
[HINOMARU] Doesn't he even know
what school he goes to?
So, Yuma. What now?
[OZEKI] I really embarrassed
myself back there, huh?
What's the deal?
Why're you letting them
walk all over you like that?
It's just the way things are.
No one can stand up to Yuma
even though
he's only a second year.
Hmm.
I suppose knowing karate
would stop a lot of people
from talking back.
Wow, you could tell?
Yeah, the guy actually won
the Kanto tournament
back when he was
in middle school.
If those weren't club members,
where is everyone?
Well, after you join,
that'll make
a grand total of two.
Uh... the Ishigama High School
sumo club only has one member?
Uh, no. But the Odachi
High School club does.
Uh...
[screaming]
I was at the wrong school
the entire time?
[OZEKI] I think most people
would've noticed.
And probably used
the front gate.
[HINOMARU]
This was all a mistake.
Makes sense. For real though.
I mean, why would someone with
actual talent wanna enroll here?
Sorry I didn't pick up
on it sooner.
It's not your fault.
You deserve better.
A hot shot like you oughta
be going to a powerhouse school.
[HINOMARU] I could say
the same thing about you.
-Huh?
-I could tell from our bout.
It's your legs.
Obviously, you've put
in the time training.
That sumo ring, you're the one
who built it, right?
Oh, yeah.
There's not a weed
or pebble visible.
And like I said before,
the dirt's packed nice
and tight.
[HINOMARU chuckles]
I knew it from
the moment I saw you.
You're a sumo maniac,
just like me!
As long as you keep up sumo,
I know we'll see each other
in a tournament.
I can't wait for that day.
[chuckling]
No way. How did I end up
back at Odachi High?
Ozeki even drew me a new map.
I'm a mess.
Not to mention
I kept getting distracted
and used up the entire day.
Well, whatever.
I'll just thank him
for the map and head home.
[HINOMARU]
What happened to your ring?
-[OZEKI] Ushio.
-It's destroyed!
There's nothing left!
Who did this?
Even the bale is in pieces.
Time to quit, huh?
I can't continue practicing sumo
at the school anymore.
I didn't care when they
called me lame or fatty
as long as I had this ring.
Some place of my own.
[voice breaking]
I really wanted to have
an official bout here one day.
Now it's gone.
They stole it.
Took it away from me!
Damn it!
[MEN laughing]
I tell you,
manual labor's sure tough.
Yeah, but it feels good
working up a sweat.
How would you guys know?
[HINOMARU]
Hey!
That bag weighs a ton.
The hell's in there?
Well! Don't you feel any remorse
for what you did?
-Remember, God is watching!
-[MEN grunting]
-What're you talking about?
-Don't play dumb!
Your thugs destroyed
the sumo ring!
Ahh. Now things
are making sense.
Guess the boys got carried away.
Then it sounds like
it's your problem, you jerk!
Of course! I take responsibility
for their actions.
So, what you gonna do about it?
I want a duel!
If I win,
you have to give up the dojo.
A duel, huh?
Okay, but if we're gonna
do this,
-you play by my rules.
-Deal!
Then it's settled.
Good. See you at the dojo.
Sure. I'll be there
after I change!
-[YUMA] Better not run.
-You wish!
-You're gonna fight him?
-He gave me no choice!
I'm gonna win that dojo back
for the sumo club!
It's between me and him.
You'll be fine.
That's not what
I'm worried about right now!
You don't know
what kinda trouble
you've gotten
yourself into, man!
-Huh?
-We're talking about Yuma!
Playing dirty is his specialty!
Trust me on this!
He's going to do
whatever it takes
to make sure
he wins the fight!
That's it? No problem.
After all,
I'm gonna be a yokozuna.
What's with you?
I'm saying
don't take this lightly!
Would you stop talking about
being a yokozuna for one second!
You're not even tall enough
to look the dude in the eyes!
I'm sure
you know already, but...
you have be at least
a 167 centimeters
to pass the medical exam
and become a sumo wrestler.
And you look
to be shy of 160.
I know you love the sport,
but you can't be a pro-wrestler.
Much less a yokozuna.
Look, I hate being the one
who says this,
but there are some things
in this world
you have no control over!
[WOMAN] I'm sorry I couldn't
give you a bigger body.
[OZEKI] Anyway, you should go
while you still have a chance!
Okay? I'll see ya.
Like that's gonna stop me!
-Hmm?
-Huh?
So, you didn't run.
Where's your pint-sized amigo?
He's not going to show up.
-[YUMA] What?
-I'm asking you.
Please, let it go
just this one time!
Do what? He's the one who wanted
to fight in the first place!
I know and I'm sorry!
But I'll do anything you want
to make it up to you!
What kind of crap
are you pulling?
It's an interesting proposition.
-It is?
-So if I have this straight,
you'll do whatever I ask?
Uh, yeah.
I want you to give up sumo.
It's my life.
[YUMA] I'm not sure
how you know each other,
but you came here
to protect him, right?
Then you better be prepared
to lose something
of value in exchange.
[HINOMARU] I knew it
from the moment I saw you.
You're a sumo maniac,
just like me!
-Okay.
-Hmm.
From this day forward.
I'll never...
-[screaming]
-Huh?
You shouldn't make promises
you can't keep.
Well, ready when you are.
Ushio?
What's going on
with his outfit?
[MEN laughing]
[MAN 7] Someone tell him
his butt's hanging out!
[MAN 8] Maybe he wants to make
it easier for Yuma to kick it!
What the hell?
I told you to escape, dude!
Like I would ever
run away from a fight.
I imagine some people
would have taken your advice
and left you to the wolves,
but they could
never become yokozuna.
You need to have three things.
A strong spirit,
technique, and body.
And unfortunately,
I'm on the short side.
So I can't very well let
my spirit be weak, can I?
Ozeki. Don't let anyone
make you quit sumo.
-[clapping]
-Huh.
The kid's a poet,
not a fighter.
I mean, did you hear
that speech?
Lovely. Now then,
why don't we see
if your spirit is as strong
as you say it is?
If I remember right,
you said the fight
would be played by my rules.
-Ten minutes.
-[knuckles crack]
You just stand there.
And if you endure my punches
that long without fighting back,
you'll be declared
the winner.
Or as we like to call it
the famous Odachi High
human sandbag!
[OZEKI] What kind
of insane fight is this?
-Let's get it over with.
-Eh?
You're not going to back down
after hearing the rules?
All right!
[grunts]
[winces]
Hey, you'd better be counting
those ten minutes.
Just who the hell are you?
I'm Hinomaru Ushio.
And my name will echo
through history on the day
I become a yokozuna!
Listen up, you punks.
If you think you can beat me,
bring it on!
[HINOMARU] Don't retreat.
Don't back down.
The ring is four
and a half meters across.
Nothing exists outside of it.
I'm taking this body
into fights where if one hand,
one knee touches
the ground, I lose!
If I can't win now,
then when will I?
Hey, there's something big
going down at the dojo.
You wanna go check it out?
[BOY 3]
The human sandbag again?
That's nothing new.
No, listen.
[BOY 3 gasps]
Are you serious?
[YUMA]
What's with you?
[grunting]
Break!
[groaning]
Damn you, kid!
What're you made of?
-[phone beeping]
-Uh?
-Time's up?
-That can't be right!
I even added five minutes
just to be safe!
-No way.
-[HINOMARU] Hey.
Maybe it's just me, but that
felt like more than ten.
[YUMA] What's it take
to knock you down?
That's a stupid question.
In sumo, you lose
if anything besides
your feet touches the ground.
I've worked hard
to make sure I never fall.
You didn't think
those weak punches of yours
were enough to put me down?
It's gotta be
some kind of trick!
No one messes with me!
Time's up, which means
I can fight back now.
Ahh!
I take it you've never
experienced sumo.
Ready for a taste?
-[yelling]
-Spirit.
[OZEKI]
Are you serious?
He just took down Yuma
with a single hit!
Hinomaru Ushio...
The two-time
elementary school champion?
He was so strong,
they gave him
the moniker of a demonic
national treasure.
Onimaru Kunitsuna!
-Uhh...
-[HINOMARU] So, Yuma,
-You appreciate sumo now?
-[YUMA groans]
We had a bet.
Take your flunkies and get lost.
You think
we're just gonna leave?
This isn't over until
you fight the rest of us!
What? You do know
what a duel is, right?
[MAN 8] There's no way
he can beat all of us!
-[ALL clamoring]
-[YUMA] All of you, shut up!
I had fifteen minutes,
and I couldn't drop him.
But he took me out in one hit.
I lost, and that's all
there is to it.
[YUMA]
Damn! How'd that shrimp beat me?
If you want the answer,
you should try the sport.
I'm gonna be
the best wrestler in Japan.
If you ever want a rematch,
I'll be happy to take you on!
Finally, a dojo.
It's like a dream!
[HINOMARU] Pinch yourself,
‘cause it's real.
Things should have
always been this way.
But still,
I can't believe
all this time you were Onimaru.
You told me there are
some things in the world
that can't be helped.
-Oh, yeah.
-This is what I'm going to do.
I'm going to win.
Then I'm going to win some more
until I'm the best high school
sumo wrestler there is.
That'll show everyone
it's not the size
of your body that counts.
And then...
I'll make
the professional sumo league
bow their heads to me!
You know what?
When you say it, I start
to think it might happen.
It's not something
I joke around about.
I'll see ya.
Please take one!
[MAN 9] Sign up right here
for the soccer club!
[MAN 10] Oh, so you're gonna
join the basketball club?
Smart choice!
-[BOTH grunt]
-Oh, sorry.
Didn't expect
to see you out here.
I don't get
why you even bother.
No one's gonna join
your sumo club.
I'm gonna prove you wrong!
I think.
Maybe they'll end up
being right.
No! This year
it's gonna be different!
[HINOMARU laughs]
That's right!
The dojo's in terrific shape.
Ushio, what are you
doing back here?
Well, there's not many
sumo maniacs like you around.
So I decided,
we're both gonna dominate
the competition this year.
You mean it?
You're joining the team?
I'll be counting
on you, Captain!
Yes! Great news!
You don't know how pumped
I am right now!
What do you say we celebrate
by having a match?
[OZEKI]
As captain, I totally agree!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[BOY 4] Really?
But he's so short.
[BOY 5]
I'm dead serious.
Not only that, he beat Yuma
before he enrolled.
Sounds like you got
a reputation.
[HINOMARU groans]
The boy from the train.