-[CROWD cheering]
-You guys.
It's far too early
to be shedding tears.
Yeah. It's not over yet.
Ushio. Go out there and win!
It's our turn to watch
all of your hard work pay off.
I'm ready.
[CROWD murmuring]
♪
[beeping]
Time for two national treasures
to go head-to-head.
All right, Bato, Enoki.
I want you to watch closely.
Sure. Not like
it matters though.
These guys might be
national treasures,
but they're not
in the same league
as Captain Tennoji.
[grunting]
-One match left.
-[grunting]
I can't see a thing!
Uh! This isn't a solution
to the problem, Daniel!
I'm only trying to get you
a better view.
I changed my mind!
[ANNOUNCER]
We'll begin the final bout
of the Inter High
Chiba Prefectural
team competition.
On the west side, Ushio.
♪
On the east side, Sada.
Our spot
in the final competition
is riding on this last bout.
How about you shut up, Araki?
Huh.
I'm sorry, Sada.
I didn't want to pile
this kind of pressure
on a first year.
Onimaru's strong.
However, you're
Ishigami High's ace.
Go show him what you can do.
Don't you worry about a thing.
I'll make sure our team makes it
to the national stage.
[SADA] I've always had
complete confidence
in my athletic abilities.
♪
[YOUNG SADA]
Hey. You know what?
I've never given sumo a go.
-You have got to be kidding me.
-[giggles]
Don't do it.
No one looks good
in a mawashi belt.
[HINOMARU yelling]
[WRESTLER grunts]
[CROWD cheering]
[SADA]
In other words,
if some guy wore
a mawashi belt
and actually rocked that look,
he'd be cool.
Maybe even the coolest athlete
that ever existed.
[SADA] Because you wear
nothing but a belt,
you can feel the intensity
coursing through your skin.
I took to sumo
way more than I expected.
I wanted to fight all-out
against an opponent
on the same level as me.
♪
One problem:
As I climbed the ranks
and became
a "middle school yokozuna,"
my equal wasn't in the ring.
♪
[CROWD murmuring]
You know what I heard?
This Sada guy's belt is spotless
because nobody's been able
to lay a finger on it.
[HASHI]
Seriously?
[FUNAKI] Have you seen anyone
in this tournament grab it?
[NISHIZATO] Whoa.
Does Hinomaru stand a chance?
Onimaru Kunitsuna
and Mikazuki Munechika.
A bout between
two national treasures.
♪
[muscles creaking]
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
[OZEKI]
The same charge.
[KANAMORI]
They're equals.
[grunts]
Why'd he use
a thrust and shove?
At that range,
Sada has a clear advantage.
[grunts]
[HINOMARU growls]
[HINOMARU] His arm holds could
be a real pain in the ass!
-In that case...
-[slaps landing]
...how do you like this?
His slaps just keep
getting faster!
His speed.
[SADA] I don't need
to block every strike.
Only some have
real weight behind them.
[HINOMARU grunting]
[SADA] You're mixing them in
with light attacks.
All that's left is
figuring out the pattern.
And only countering
the heavy hits!
-He blocked him!
-Watch out!
[HINOMARU grunts]
[yelling]
How's he going even
faster than before?
[SADA]
I can't tell which is which.
Every strike
has power behind it!
[yells]
Check it out.
-Sada's smiling.
-[chuckles]
[SADA] Now this is fun.
That feeling of uncertainty.
I've been waiting
for a fight like this!
Onimaru.
You wanted this too!
[HINOMARU] What the hell
are you grinning about?
I'm only going to smile...
once I've taken
your head for myself!
[SADA gasps]
[SADA grunts]
-He's got him by the arm!
-Wring that punk out!
[yells]
Now Sada's attacking!
Onimaru can't get close to him!
Those strikes are non-stop,
and sharp.
Each hit's targeted to keep
pushing him backwards.
[slaps landing]
[REINA] You were the one
who dragged Yuma
and the others
into this sport.
They're only here
because they believed in you.
You better win, Hinomaru!
♪
[HINOMARU grunts]
[SADA]
Crescent Moon!
[gasps]
[HINOMARU] I was wondering
when you were gonna do that!
Did he just step
into Sada's throw?
[ALL gasp]
You got him!
[HINOMARU]
Demon Wheel!
♪
He's really something.
When did Mikazuki stop
his throwing motion?
[breathing heavily]
[HINOMARU] While you're busy
catching your breath,
here's my second counterattack!
Demon Storm!
[SADA grunts]
He's still standing after that!
His Demon Wheel
didn't work either!
[HINOMARU] Like I thought
that'd be enough to win!
[HINOMARU grunting]
♪
[HINOMARU]
Hundred Demon Takedown!
[SADA]
Damn he's strong.
This is Onimaru Kunitsuna.
Even though he's the smallest
wrestler I've ever faced,
he stands taller
than any competitor I've fought.
I've been waiting for the day
I could face-off
with someone like him.
But are you satisfied
with just competing?
Of course I'm not!
-I only want one thing!
-[yelling]
Victory against the strongest!
You hear that? He's roaring.
-[grunts]
-[SADA] First Quarter Moon!
[OZEKI and KEI gasp]
[HINOMARU grunts]
[HINOMARU grunting]
[KEI gasps]
A throat hold!
Sada is being
unusually aggressive.
I've never seen that look
in his eyes before.
[SADA growling]
[HINOMARU grunting]
♪
He let go of him!
[HINOMARU grunts]
[CROWD murmuring]
They're so fast,
I can barely keep up.
They really did save
the best fight for last.
[grunts]
[HINOMARU gasps]
He used his hand
to counter the thrust!
And took all the force
out of the strike.
[muscles creaking]
Sada's signature
power arm grab.
This is bad.
Onimaru's locked in.
When's he gonna use
that new move?
Isn't this a perfect time
for his triple combo?
The new technique
isn't quite ready yet.
[KEI]
Huh?
We didn't have enough time
before the tournament.
[YUMA]
Without it in his arsenal,
can really he beat Sada?
Dude's got this.
If there's anything
that gets his blood pumping,
it's stacked odds!
[yells]
-[MAN] He grabbed both sides!
-[KIRIHITO] That's it.
Believe, Hinomaru.
You've trained like a madman,
chasing your dream
to be a pro yokozuna.
And that entire time,
your body's never betrayed you!
So believe in it!
[breathing heavily]
[HINOMARU]
The Hundred Demon Takedown
isn't enough for this guy!
If I don't beat him,
how can I become a yokozuna?
You wanna see a smile?
Wait till I win!
[YUMA gasps]
[SHIBAKIYAMA]
He cut him off!
[SADA] You're acting like
you actually expected to win.
But your fun stops here.
There's only room for one of us
to shine in this ring!
It's done.
[SADA]
Own Hand Pulling Overarm Throw!
Double Moon!
♪
[CROWD cheering]
[HINOMARU] The lingering feeling
of something
other than my feet
touching the ground.
And everyone looking down at me.
My feet are like weights.
They're dragging me deeper
into the sludge.
People came out
to cheer me on.
I didn't want them
to see me in that moment.
Mom...
how can you be proud of me?
Is this as far as I can go?
Is this all I'm capable of?
Stop making that face.
What do you think you're doing?
[HINOMARU]
I envy you.
Your height and strength.
Your talent.
If you end up going pro,
you'll go on to do great things.
Anyone can see you were destined
to become a yokozuna.
I guess... I wasn't.
[grunts]
[HINOMARU]
Like hell!
[ALL gasp]
[SADA gasps]
[creaking]
His arm!
Ah! It's going to break.
-[HINOMARU] Talent? Destiny?
-[grunts]
What a bunch of crap!
No one decides my future but me!
And I've already mapped it out!
-Watch!
-[yells]
[ALL gasp]
[OZEKI]
He broke loose!
[HINOMARU]
If this was a contest between
which of us
is more talented at sumo,
there's a chance
I'd lose to you.
But as far as this bout
is concerned,
-I know one thing.
-[BOTH yelling]
Victory will be mine!
-[ARAKI gasps]
-Sada!
[gasps]
-[OZEKI] Got it!
-[SADA] An underhand grip!
This isn't good!
Gotta cut him off!
No, not his elbow!
[SHIBAKIYAMA gasps]
[HINOMARU]
Optimal distance.
Right footwork.
Unbeatable form!
[ALL gasp]
[SADA grunts]
I'm not going to lose!
[KIRIHITO]
There's his new technique.
An attack
on three points at once!
[HINOMARU]
They're watching.
The sun overhead!
And my team!
They've seen your resolve!
♪
Your passion!
Your fight!
♪
[HINOMARU]
Now, the only thing left to show
is the road that lies ahead!
After I beat Sada!
After we beat Ishi High!
This final blow carries
our destiny on its shoulders!
Hundred-Thousand Demon Drop!
[wind whooshing]
[REFEREE]
West side wins!
♪
[GROUP cheering]
Ushio!
-[breathing heavily]
-[CROWD cheering]
You did it! You won!
-[cheering continues]
-[panting]
♪
[ANNOUNCER] The final result,
with a score of three-two,
the west side
are the winners.
Congratulations to the Chiba
Inter High prelim champions,
-Odachi High School!
-[KEI] Yeah!
[screaming]
What a bunch
of total bad-asses!
[NISHIZATO]
Yuma's going to the finals!
♪
[ALL laughing]
[chuckles]
♪
[REINA]
They're incredible. All of them.
[KIRIHITO]
Wait. Your arm!
How is it? Does it hurt to move?
Hmm?
[KIRIHITO]
Don't give me that!
You're too reckless!
You realize that
you could've dislocated it?
Man.
-[HINOMARU] Kirihito.
-Hmm.
You gotta learn to relax
once in a while.
Relax?
If you're going to be our coach,
you need to act more stoic.
[laughs]
Not like the professor here
was much help
during our final bouts.
He definitely struck
the biggest victory pose
out of all of us.
[growling]
Well, you could hardly expect me
to show no reaction.
In fact, I've got
the perfect analogy.
Hold up.
[KIRIHITO]
It felt like
I was a mother watching
my children performing
for the first time
in a school play.
Of course it was nail biting.
Gah!
[CHIHIRO]
Our mother?
[OZEKI] Yeah, I'm not sure
I completely get it.
-[CROWD cheering]
-Uh! Huh?
♪
I almost forgot, you guys.
But our team actually won.
I'm not gonna let
today's bouts be your last.
The five of us will breeze
through the prelims,
then to the finals.
And you're coming with us
all the way to the top!
-[OZEKI sniffling]
-[HINOMARU] Huh?
Next up, it's the finals!
Damn straight!
[CHIHIRO]
That last throw of his.
He realized in that moment
his arm couldn't handle
the weight,
so he used the force
of his whole body instead.
You don't practice
a stance like that.
It had to have been
pure instinct.
Savage, bro. Damn.
How strong are you plannin'
on getting?
[KEI] I wasn't able to win
a single bout today.
I didn't contribute
to the victory.
Not even in the least.
Uh?
The two of us might be
dead weight for the time being.
But we'll show 'em
what we got during the finals.
Right.
[SHIBAKIYAMA] Every bout
they fought was significant.
Even the ones that they lost.
When a teammate was defeated,
their feelings transferred
onto the next person.
And when it was
that wrestler's turn,
it supplied them
with the energy
they needed to win.
They may have gone in to face
their opponents as individuals,
but none of them
were truly alone.
[TERAHARA]
I know what you mean.
[SHIBAKIYAMA] If this
hadn't been a team competition,
there's no telling how the bouts
would've ultimately played out.
-One thing's for certain.
-[CROWD applauding]
No one would dare accuse
the other team of losing
because they fought
with any less passion.
[crying]
I still can't believe we won!
How are you managing to smile,
cry, and eat at the same time?
Hold up.
Where did Kunisaki go?
[OZEKI]
Your arm! I-Is it...
[HINOMARU]
Oh, yeah! Don't worry.
It's nothing serious.
I put ice on it just in case.
[tent flap rustles]
I'm certainly glad
it wasn't anything serious.
You're lucky.
[MAMIYA]
A partially dislocated shoulder.
There may also be
a hairline fracture.
[SADA]
A standard was expected of me,
and I'm sorry
I failed to meet it.
After being touted
as a national treasure
and the sumo team's ace,
I let you down.
It's my fault the third years'
summer is over with.
That the team's road
to the finals ended here.
And to apologize,
I'll give up--
So tell me,
Mr. National Treasure.
How do you feel?
Like a disappointment.
I'm pathetic.
♪
[KANAMORI] I've got a
selfish request to make of you.
[SADA gasps]
I want you to spend
the next two years
in the Ishi High sumo club.
[gasps]
So do I.
Once these two graduate,
we're going to need
someone like you
to make the team even stronger.
Mamiya.
And don't say
you gave it your all
when today was the first time
you ever tried being serious.
[KANAMORI chuckles]
You got that right.
[TEAM laughing]
Sada, your sumo journey,
it's just begun.
The team is in your hands.
[breathing shakily]
Yes, sir.
[ARAKI]
You're all insane.
How can you be talking
about the future already?
They kicked our asses!
If I hadn't lost,
we could've been champs!
It's all my fault!
That's what everyone's thinking!
So, just get this over
with and say it!
[crying]
-[SANADA] Araki.
-Huh?
You're the reason
we lost today.
[wails]
The fact you're smiling
while you're sad
makes it worse!
[SANADA laughs]
I'm holding back tears too.
Your drama queen act
is killing me.
[ALL laughing]
[SAKI] See? Aren't you glad
you made it?
I told you Hinomaru Ushio
was something special, didn't I?
Well, we've got
the match footage.
He doesn't stand a chance
against Tennoji,
but he'll still want to see it.
-Hmm?
I believe I'm the one
who should hand the footage
over to Captain Tennoji.
[scoffs]
No way. I'm the best choice.
Quit bein' a baby and give it!
[BATO]
What are you doing? Stop!
[BOTH grunting]
[BATO]
You're gonna break it!
[grunting continues]
[TERAHARA]
Saki!
[SAKI]
Master! Terahara!
[shushes]
You don't want to blow
my cover, do you?
Everyone knows who you are.
That's Master Shibakiyama.
Why are you dressed like that?
[DANIEL]
Hinomaru sure is a beast.
He's stronger
since he fought Sosuke.
And that's saying something.
[KARIYA scoffs]
He's not the only one
who's been getting stronger.
♪
[CHIHIRO]
I'm glad I came to Dachi High.
Not only did I find sumo,
I found my bros and won
a team competition with 'em.
Still, I've got one regret.
The guy I want
to fight the most
happens to be
on the same side as me.
[REINA]
Huh?
A new competition!
Starting now?
You're exhausted and you want
to fight one-on-one?
-Get real!
-I am worn out.
But I'm not joking around.
[OZEKI]
Think about it.
Sada's not competing.
With him out,
Ushio will sail
through
the individual tournament.
I feel kind of guilty,
but luck's on our side.
Ozeki's right!
Without any competition,
Hinomaru's sure to win!
Me? Win?
[chuckles]
You think?
[footsteps approaching]
I'm not so sure.
♪
Hmm?
Kunisaki?
[CHIHIRO]
I want your best.
This has to be a serious bout.
My dream of becoming
the strongest fighter
lies beyond your fallen body.
-[OZEKI] Dude. Same team!
-Absolutely.
I have zero intention of taking
the easy way to the top.
On that note...
I expect the same
from the rest of you.
The gate to the summit's
open to all.
As for me,
whatever you got,
I'm willing to take.
I want to win and be recognized
as the best there is.
♪
[KIRIHITO]
These may be your friends now,
but in an instant,
they could become
your greatest enemy.
Moving speech, but let's see
if you can back up your talk,
Onimaru Kunitsuna!
♪
It's been ages
since I signed my autograph.
[whispering]
Hey. Say "I love you, man."
Do it for me.
Right.
Unburden your feelings, bro.