[birds chirping]
[HINOMARU]
Thought I'd find you here.
Uh. Hey, Ushio.
[HINOMARU] There's not
a trace of the old ring
left behind, huh?
[OZEKI]
Yeah.
♪
The name's Hinomaru Ushio.
Before I can be
a yokozuna,
the highest rank
in all of sumo,
first, I have to be the best
high school wrestler there is.
Good times.
It feels so long ago.
Hard to imagine
it all started here.
Back in the days
when the sumo club
only had one member.
Now we've got six wanting
to be the best in Japan.
[OZEKI]
Honestly,
-I'm kinda scared.
-Hmm?
I'm a third year,
so if we lose today,
that's it for me.
I'm done.
But I don't want this to end.
I want to keep sumo wrestling
with everyone in the club.
♪
[OZEKI laughs]
Listen to me, whining again.
I must sound like
a pretty sad excuse
for an upperclassman.
[HINOMARU]
When the school made fun of you,
you could have walked away
and shut down the club.
If you hadn't been so committed
to keeping it alive,
none of us would be here now.
You're stronger
than you know, Ozeki.
The club only exists
for one reason.
You fought as hard as you could
to keep it around.
I'm not gonna let
today's bouts be your last.
We'll breeze through the prelims
on to nationals.
You're coming with us
to the top!
Right!
♪
[KANAMORI]
The pledge!
As their official spokesman,
I certify each
sumo wrestler here trains
to cultivate their spirit,
technique, and body.
The ring is four point
five-five meters in diameter!
Once inside, we will fight
to the best of our abilities!
Declared by me,
Tsuyoshi Kanamori!
We saved you a good seat, Reina!
[NISHIZATO]
Over here!
-[AUDIENCE applauding]
-Look at the turnout.
I didn't think the audience
would be so pumped.
[ANNOUNCER] At this time,
we'll begin the fifth match
in round one
of the tournament.
Yo! Up here, Hinomaru!
We came out to cheer you on!
Did you forget we're incognito?
So try blending in like me.
[TERAHARA] Your costume's
way louder than my yelling.
[ANNOUNCER] First in the ring,
on the west side,
from Odachi High School,
Ushio.
On the east side,
from Kashiwa Technical, Ito.
Odachi High School?
I've never heard of them.
Same, but the other one's
a real powerhouse
and has gone on
to nationals before.
[MAN 1]
Look at the size difference.
It's so one-sided.
[REINA grunts]
[REFEREE]
Hands on the ground!
Spirit!
His reaction time was too slow.
Not quite.
[grunts]
That kid.
-He's using Saenoyama's charge.
-Heh-heh.
[grunting]
[HINOMARU]
Arm grab underhand throw!
Demon Wheel Rear Attack!
[CROWD oohing]
-Down he goes!
-No contest!
Not bad.
He threw that guy around
like he weighed nothing at all!
[groans]
♪
[exhales]
One down.
And now that
Onimaru's given them
a taste of what he can do,
it's time for us
to do the same.
I think we ought to show
these schools
what Dachi High's capable of.
[OZEKI/CHIHIRO/YUMA/KEI]
Yes, sir!
Hold on a minute.
That short-ass kid.
I'm pretty sure
he's the same guy
who took on Yamatokuni's son.
Are you serious?
You wouldn't know by looking!
So we finally get to meet
Onimaru Kunitsuna.
Strength-wise,
he's not that bad.
Make sure you reach the finals.
'Cause I'll be waiting.
Where do you think you're going?
Oh, I've got a magazine
interview to do. Ciao!
Is it Jackass Monthly?
Hey, look who's fighting next.
[humming]
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
♪
[CHIHIRO] Chihiro Special,
number thirteen!
[grunting]
Interesting technique.
An outer thigh
propping twist down.
Told you.
Chiharu's moves are pretty dope.
Is this the same guy you ran
into while you were suspended?
[SANADA]
Great.
Our secret weapon's intro'd
himself to the competition.
[yelling]
-[grunting]
-Unleashing Chaotic Thrusts!
[gasps]
Those strikes are
lightning fast!
[WRESTLER] Screw this!
I'm backing off!
[KIRIHITO] It's one thing
to back off when you're winning,
quite another
when you're on defense.
[grunting]
That's my big brother!
[NISHIZATO/HASHI/FUNAKI]
Bow down and worship
the king of the sumo ring!
[KANAMORI]
Huh!
He's definitely improved
from the last time we saw him.
Odachi's stronger
than I thought they'd be.
And since they won
three bouts in a row,
they're in the second round.
Based on what we've seen so far,
the rest of the team
must be incredible!
[BOTH TOGETHER]
Or not?
[yelling]
[groans]
[BOTH]
Ugh!
You did fine.
Don't let it get to you.
Now I understand.
Dachi front-loaded
their roster
with the best wrestlers
they had.
-Huh?
-Don't believe me?
Check out their sorry excuse
for a captain.
Do you see
how freakin' terrified he is?
That guy's
a bully's wet dream.
Just shut up and watch.
It's these later bouts
that could prove
to be the most important ones.
[ARAKI]
Huh?
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
-Huh?
-Ha-ha!
[CROWD chattering excitedly]
[ARAKI]
He railroaded him.
♪
[CROWD cheering]
People can transform
if given the chance
and become something great.
And I know who gave him
that opportunity.
Dachi High's sixth member.
Kirihito Tsuji.
I think it's safe to assume
they're no longer
a one-man team.
Don't hold back against them.
See that?
-They're watching us closely.
-Yeah.
These jerk-offs
are probably realizing
they're in for a fight.
I've got no problem with that!
We'll see 'em
in the final round!
♪
Oh, hey, there you are!
Ushio.
[KIRIHITO]
Mizuki Sada.
Figured we'd run into
each other eventually.
Would've been better to meet
inside the ring first.
Geez. You make it sound like
we're about to get married.
Oh, about your semi-final match.
You better make it quick
so you can save
your strength for our fight.
Been looking forward to this,
haven't you?
You've no idea.
Middle school sumo
was a major bore
without an equal around
to keep my skills sharp.
I wanted to tell you something
before our bout,
Onimaru Kunitsuna.
How thankful I am
you made it this far.
You say that now,
Mikazuki Munechika,
but you'll regret it later.
You're blade's about
to get tarnished.
Sorry in advance.
[ANNOUNCER]
Match over.
Odachi High,
on the west side,
wins four to one.
Hell yeah!
Yes, we made it
to the last round!
Finals, here we come!
Sure, but that scrawny kid
could end up
being a big problem for them.
You could literally replace him
with anyone,
and they'd do better.
[REINA] He's weak but still
charges straight at them.
Don't you realize
you're not Hinomaru?
To be blunt, Ishigami's team
this year is strong.
Maybe the best one
they've ever had.
We could make a tactical call
and pair Mitsuhashi
against Sada.
Give him an easy win
while we focus
on the other bouts instead.
But still, they're
a nationally ranked opponent.
There's no such thing
as a perfect plan against them.
We'll need every win
we can get.
This is one pitstop
on our journey.
We'll face them head-on
and win!
Who'll be the best team
in Japan?
[ALL]
Odachi High!
[ANNOUNCER]
Onto the final round.
♪
[ANNOUNCER] On the west side,
Odachi High School.
First in the ring,
Kei Mitsuhashi.
Second, Chihiro Kunisaki.
Third, Yuma Gojo.
Fourth, Shinya Ozeki.
On the east side,
Ishigami High School.
First in the ring,
Keiichi Mamiya.
Second, Gennosuke Araki.
Third, Tsuyoshi Kanamori.
Fourth, Yuki Sanada.
And fifth, Hinomaru Ushio
versus Mizuki Sada.
[REFEREE]
Bow.
[ALL WRESTLERS]
Let's have a good match!
[ANNOUNCER] First in the ring,
on the west side,
-Mitsuhashi.
-I'm ready!
[ANNOUNCER]
On the east side, Mamiya.
So, uh, I'm no psychic,
but I know how
this is gonna end up.
[MAN 2] There's gotta be 100
kilo difference between them!
Somebody call an ambulance.
I'll say this at least.
It's kind of impressive
an amateur with his physique
can charge the way he does.
But two months training isn't
long enough to work a miracle.
Dachi is basically a team of
only four qualified wrestlers.
Goes without saying,
losing any bout at this stage
is a setback.
And yet,
Mitsuhashi's expression tells me
he hasn't thrown in the towel.
And based on the way
his teammates are behaving,
they're counting him
as their fifth member.
♪
[KEI grunting]
Once more.
[KIRIHITO]
No one can deny you've got guts.
Charging in head-first
like that.
If you've got something to say,
then let's hear it.
'Cause I guarantee
whatever it is,
it won't make me feel worse.
Your technique
has improved considerably.
However, you still
won't be ready in time
for the Inter High prelims.
[grunts]
[yelling]
-Um, hands on the ground.
-[KEI] Uh?
-Right!
-[chuckles]
Should I laugh or cry?
[MAMIYA] He must've
gotten that from Onimaru.
Planning on charging me head-on?
In a way, it's touching.
-[KANAMORI] Mamiya!
-Hmm?
[KIRIHITO]
It's time.
Show them how serious you are.
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
[MAMIYA]
He's gone!
Where'd he go?
♪
[REFEREE]
Spirit!
[MAMIYA]
He's gone!
Where'd he go?
♪
A leaping charge!
He didn't come up with that
at the last minute.
It requires practice.
[chuckles]
A change?
What kind?
Well, strategy wise, it's solid.
Thing is,
I know you.
And you respect
Hinomaru's approach.
What I'm suggesting
is entirely different.
There's no point doing sumo
if you feel like you have
to compromise your style.
And besides, you still
have two more years.
[KEI] Let me tell you
what I want.
I know Hinomaru's worked hard
to wrestle the way he does.
But could you imagine
if I waltzed into the ring,
tried to imitate him,
and then said,
"My bad.
I wonder how I lost."
No way.
And not during the finals
of a team tournament.
I can't wait
for the next two years!
You think I don't know
I'm a burden?
But Hinomaru and the captain
have always made me feel
like part of the team.
And Gojo and Kunisaki too.
They could've found anyone
stronger to take my place,
but they didn't.
So, please!
Show me the way, Coach!
Show me how I can win
for the team!
The only thing
that matters to me
is helping them out
when it counts!
Respect and how I want
to wrestle don't mean anything!
Huh.
♪
[KIRIHITO] If you had made
the transition earlier,
it's possible you would've
already scored some wins.
But then again, that wasn't
your end goal, was it?
There was a noble reason
you kept losing over and over.
When people see you,
they immediately suspect
you'll use a trick to win.
You played the honest clown,
and they lowered their guard.
You saved this move for when
it mattered the most.
To help us beat Ishi high!
Mitsuhashi!
Win it!
[ALL]
Push him out!
[grunting]
[KEI]
No way!
[CHIHIRO]
He's too fast!
[KIRIHITO]
He knew!
[KANAMORI]
I figured they had some scheme.
[MAMIYA]
If the captain hadn't warned me,
I'd be in trouble.
-[MAMIYA grunts]
-[KEI groans]
[KEI] Don't give up!
I've almost got it!
[MAMIYA grunts]
Damn it!
Honestly, what did you expect?
That's how it should
have played out.
Yeah, still.
The kid took on someone
three times his size!
[AUDIENCE applauding]
♪
[ARAKI] You're new to this
whole sports thing, aren't you?
Did you think you'd win
just 'cause your brain's
the biggest muscle you've got?
That's pretty arrogant
if you ask me.
[OZEKI]
Kunisaki!
♪
[KIRIHITO]
Nicely done!
After that, doesn't matter
how big your opponent is.
Push him out!
Just one problem.
You only get a few go's
before they catch on.
You're right.
That's why we're gonna
save it for Ishi High.
[CHIHIRO]
You actually think you've got
a chance against them?
[breathing heavily]
Hey, no worries.
It's not like anyone's
actually expecting you to win.
The captain and Gojo
are getting better every day.
We can rely on them.
Just treat your match like
it's an individual competition.
[KEI]
Sorry, Chihiro.
But I'm not going out there
just to make memories.
I'm on this team!
And when we promised
we'd be the best in Japan,
that includes me!
After I get a win
and help us go to nationals,
you'll thank me!
♪
[OZEKI]
Mitsuhashi!
Guys. I'm so sorry.
What're you talking about?
You did great out there!
[CHIHIRO]
You jumped way too far.
You got freaked out
and screwed up.
Even if he was expecting it,
you should have gotten yourself
in a better position.
Whoa. Too soon, Kunisaki.
What am I gonna do with you?
Well, you better make it up
to me during nationals.
[CHIHIRO]
Now I get it.
This is what makes it
a team competition.
Chiharu. What's up?
[CHIHIRO] This is
the first time I've ever wanted
to win for someone
other than myself.
We got a lot riding
on this second bout.
Damn straight.
A judo champ versus
a wrestling master!
A combat sports showdown!
All right, Gengoro,
it's time to settle the score.
My name's Gennosuke.
Whatever, at least
we're fighting.
Though I would've preferred
an individual competition.
I'm just preparing you
for Dachi's High's second loss.
You're toast, buddy.
'Cause all that pressure
to do well
for your team's
gonna screw up your game.
Meaning what?
I wanted a duel with you
free of distractions
so we could get
at the truth.
Who is the strongest?
This is a team competition.
But, come on.
It's just five individual bouts.
No point viewing it
any other way.
Yeah, I get the picture.
If something
doesn't make you stronger,
-you toss it in the trash.
-[ARAKI] Huh?
You don't have to worry.
Because I'm always
at my best, Mutsugoro.
Punk! I'll make you
remember my name!
♪
Spirit!
[MAN 3]
Huh?
[MAN 4]
How come they're not moving?
[AUDIENCE muttering]
[MAN 5] Do something,
for crying out loud!
[MAN 6] What is this?
Performance art!
The crowd's turning ugly.
A lot of the spectators here
are only interested
in watching wrestlers
fight each other.
But they don't realize these two
have honed their techniques
in extremely
separate disciplines.
Neither one wants to launch
into a reckless attack.
And both know they're
at their most vulnerable
when they get in close.
But I have a feeling
who'll make the first move.
[MAN 7]
Kunisaki on the offensive!
-A takedown!
-Good!
[KIRIHITO] Lower attacks
are harder to counter with judo!
[ARAKI]
So predictable.
Underestimate me, you'll lose.
Arguing which
fighting style's better
is a complete waste of time.
When I beat Chiharu,
it won't prove judo
somehow makes you
more powerful than wrestling.
If you're strong, you'll win
at everything you try.
But I can't think
about any of that now.
The cheers of the crowd,
their jeering,
the judo champion title,
the expectations
of the upperclassmen,
the days I spent training,
noise, all of it,
throw that garbage away!
The only thing that matters
is destroying
the opponent in front of you!
[CHIHIRO] He's countering
with an inner thigh throw!
-Kunisaki!
-Ah!
[CHIHIRO]
I know your type.
I used to be the same as you.
The old me was obsessed
with my own strength!
But not anymore.
♪
[ARAKI grunts]
[CHIHIRO]
My team's already under my skin.
And they're not going anywhere!
[FUNAKI]
He countered with a hip throw!
For the past month,
I've been doing foot exercises,
making my toes overpowered.
Now I can hold onto the ground!
I win!
♪
He did a front flip in midair!
It threw him off his balance!
Put pressure on him!
♪
[MAMIYA]
A sweeping grab!
[SANADA]
That's a judo sacrifice throw!
[CHIHIRO]
Crap!
He's using all his weight
to pull me down!
There's not a single
wrestling move
that'll get my ass
out of this one!
Look at his focus!
It's not human!
Meanwhile, my head's a mess!
This is make or break.
But here I am thinking about
everything except the contest!
My life's flashing
in front of my eyes.
Why am I thinking
about this junk?
Have I gotten weaker?
You're not done!
He's right!
I'm just getting started.
Even if my thoughts
are weighing me down.
I'll shoulder 'em
and use them grow.
To win!
Demon Wheel!
[ARAKI grunts]
♪
[chuckles]
We won!
♪
Oh, it's Mother's Day?
Can I help you?
Aah!
♪
Sorry! I think I wandered
into the wrong store!
[MAMIYA]
Looking for carnations?
Yeah.
♪
[KEI] Well, don't judge
a book by its cover.
Does he work there part-time?
What's his problem?
-[WOMAN] Keiichi!
-Hmm?
[WOMAN]
Dinner's ready!
Okay!
♪
[HINOMARU]
They had no way of knowing,
but soon they'd meet again.
This time, inside the sumo ring.