[humming]
[yelling]
And so, in the end, through his heroic efforts to capture the criminals, this iconic
symbol of peace, the Statue of Justice, was saved, thanks to Mr. Legend.
Ah, Legend was the coolest.
[alarm sounding]
Okay, off to work now!
[stumbling]
This is Hero TV breaking news! Masked thugs have highjacked armored truck in West Silver
and are on the run with over 3 million Stern Dollars.
Unbelievable! They took out a police cruiser!
It doesn't look like the authorities can stop these blood thirsty criminals.
And yet, there is still no sign of any heroes.
As you know, only one daring program brings you ongoing, up-to-the-second coverage of super-charged
heroes battling crime and natural disasters.
The only rescue entertainment show that ranks vigilantes by points, and at the end of
the season crowns the undisputed King of Heroes! You're watching HERO TV LIVE!
[honking]
And here comes our first hero!
It's the bourgeois, open flame broiled Fire Emblem!
Will he bring the heat for another arrest today?
A-camera, push in close!
I'm all over it.
He's gonna use his fireball attack!
What a merciless move!
The suspects are losing control of the vehicle!
And another hero is on the scene! The bold tank of the west coast: Rock Bison!
[grunting]
Rock Bison has been struggling in the rankings all season...
... it's good to see him back in the game!
[grunting]
Ah-ha! What? Hey!
Don't even think about it! Hold o-- come here!
It appears Rock Bison can't extract his horns!
Huh?
And now the villains have commandeered a taxi cab!
Oh, no!
[grunting] Come on!
[grunting]
Huh?!
[chuckling]
And who should drop in? The lightening bolt kung-fu master, Dragon Kid!
A sizzling double arrest!
[cheering]
They're out cold! Talk about a shocking victory! More points for Dragon Kid!
As usual, the hidden hero Origami Cyclone can be seen in the background.
And so... another crime prevented by--
Wait-- what's this? One of the robbers is still on the run!
[grunting] Get this train movin'!
This is terrible! According to new information,
the remaining suspect has taken control of a crowded monorail!
Oh, no!
Okay!
[screaming]
So, what now? We should probably pull out and not interfere.
Look! What's that?
Ugh. Great.
I don't believe my eyes. It's the crusher for justice, Wild Tiger!
I hope he's careful this time!
Cut to commercial. Tiger, you reading me?
We need you to hold for a thirty second commercial.
You gotta be kiddin' me.
[segway music]
Ahh!
I am not waiting for ads while people are in danger.
Hey, listen to me! If you do it my way, there will be more suspense!
Screw suspense!
A real hero... only cares about one thing...
... And that's keeping the peace!
Wild Roar!
Damn him. So stubborn.
Keep rolling!
Hold the phone! It appears Wild Tiger is activating his Hundred Power!
Which makes his physical abilities a hundred times stronger!
Go faster! I can't!
Incredible!
Let me outta here!
[grunting]
Give it up, scum bag! Huh?
You fool! He's below you!
Gah?! Where'd that come from?!
The suspect has escaped to a blimp!
Blazing into the fight, it's the wind master himself, Sky High!
That's right! This season's leader and reigning champ has come to save the day!
[cheering]
What a jerk. Showin' up after I've done all the dirty work.
[gasping and yelling]
[groaning]
[whimpering]
Don't try anything funny, or else!
You don't try anything funny, or else!
Sky High?! You're a dead man!
[gasping] Damn it!
Ah! The suspect's rocket has exploded! Oh, the humanity!
Ah!
Controlling the wind to save innocent lives! Just what we'd expect from Sky High!
Look out! The blimp is gonna crash into that building!
Dear me, the blimp's headed straight for that cruise ship!
[screaming]
[gasping] Seriously?!
You boys done foolin' around, yet?
Huh?
Every male fan knows the cold wind that just blew in...
Protecting the cruise ship with her freezing liquid gun,
it's the icy super star of the hero world, Blue Rose!
All right, get me a close up!
My ice is a little cold, but your crime has been completely put on hold!
Absolute perfection!
All she cares about is racking up points.
I caught the suspect, doesn't that count for anything?!
[gunshot] Huh?!
Huh?
[gasping]
You shot me?! [gasping for air]
I told you to stay out of it, man!
[groaning] What a day I'm having.
Wild Tiger took a bullet to the chest, but he's all right.
Huh?
[yelling]
Ew! Stop! [screaming]
It's her patented Cutie Escape!
She's just running away.
Wild Tiger leaps into action!
[grunting]
He ran out of time! Remember, Wild Tiger's Hundred Power only lasts five minutes.
[screaming]
Wild Tiger has lost his super powers! This could be curtains for our super hero!
What the--?
Who the hell are you supposed to be?
The guy who just saved your life.
Ah!
Oh, yeah.
It's... um... who is that?
Huh?!
Ah!
Our mystery man has apprehended the crook!
[grunting]
Heh.
Could this be the birth of a new superstar?
The season ends with the surprise victory by a mysterious new hero!
[cheering]
Hmmm...
Cut to a commercial!
Hurry, please.
I have to see you, now.
[alarms sounding]
All right! This is what I'm talkin' about!
Nex! Nex!
This Pepsi Nex...
...is refreshingly cold!
Having one in my hand... puts my heart on hold!
The great taste draws me in!
Pepsi...
Nex!
Ah!
♪♪
Hey, so, who's your sponsor, anyway?
Don't have one.
Wait, you're tellin' me you're a free agent? Why'd you stick your nose in this?
Come on, does it really matter? I made the arrest.
And showing your face... why would you take off your mask in public?
Are you crazy?
Huh?
It's a basic rule! A hero's secret identity has to remain a secret---
Secret, huh?
Uh...
Time's are changin', old man. Better keep up.
Old man?
This is it! The moment you've all been waiting for...
... we're about to reveal the winner of this season's Hero TV!
What were you thinking, Kotetsu?
I mean, bending the track? And did you have to smash the windows in the train like that?
Well...
Do you realize how much that's gonna cost?
Listen, I'm sorry.
You do understand who made you a hero, don't you, pal?
Hmm... my sponsors, sir!
Good answer. Now, get to that award ceremony.
Thanks, Ben.
Fire Emblem. Rock Bison. Dragon Kid. Origami Cyclone. Sky High. Blue Rose. Wild Tiger.
Which hero shined the brightest this season?
You're late.
So, when are they gonna announce the winner?
Right now.
All right.
We know it's not gonna be you.
Shut up.
[chuckling]
The points have been tallied and it's time to crown a new champion!
One of these fearless heroes is a heartbeat away from winning all the glory!
With an unprecidented 12,730 points, the King of Heroes is Sky High!
And now... your Champion!
I could not have done this without everyone's help. Thanks and thanks again!
Now, with an important message, here is the CEO of Apollon Media,
as well as the president of the OBC, give it up for Albert Maverick!
I'd like to take a moment to introduce someone very special to our viewers. Come on up.
This bright young man has just won the approval of the Justice Buearau.
So you'll all be seeing a lot more of him.
Please welcome the City of Sternbild's newest hero... Barnaby Brooks Jr.
[mocking] What a clown.
Be nice.
His super power may sound familiar to some of you.
When activated, this young man's physical strength is increased one hundred times.
But it only lasts him for five minutes. And yes, it's the exact same power as Wild Tiger.
However, he also has the power of youth.
Which is why I'm hopeful our new hero won't need to be rescued as often as someone else we know.
[chuckling]
As you know, individuals with super powers, known as N.E.X.T.,
began appearing 45 years ago due to some sort of mutation--
Hey! I'm out of here.
♪♪
Promise me, dear. You'll never stop being a hero.
I'm proud of you.
Well, I've managed to stay safe so far.
I feel it's all because of you.
...Tomoe.
Evening.
A veteran hero who made his debut 10 years ago.
He may be past his prime, but he is--ugh.
Huh?
Give me 10 Wild Tigers!
Whatever.
Hey, what's up?
Are you seriously ditching the after party?
Eh, those things are too stuffy for me.
There's tons of free food and all the suits are here.
Say hi for me, will ya?
Hello? Hello?!
Ah!
Hmm! Bison's got some junk in the trunk!
Stop, stop! Get off of me!
You got your screen time out there as usual. Keep it up, it's great exposure.
I won't let the sponsors down, sir! I mean, I hope not.
You're not listening. My catch phrase is stupid. Can't your company let me change it?
That domineering attitude of yours is why people love you. Why change what works?
I guess.
It's all about the fans. Thanks and thanks again!
Hello, Mr. Maverick!
Ah! I knew promoting you to producer was the right choice for Hero TV,
but I never expected you to pull in these ratings!
Well, when it comes to creating a spectical, I stop at nothing.
Hmmm.
Good evening, Mr. Brooks.
Mm?
Nice to meet you. I've been assigned to the Justice Bureau as of today.
My name, by the way, is Yuri Petrov.
Pleased to meet you. What can I do for you?
I just wanted you to know, we I very much look forward to your work.
Well, I'll try my best to meet your expectations.
That won't be too difficult. Follow your own code of justice.
I will.
Yeah, yeah, coming!
Yeeelllo?
Dad?
Honey! What's goin' on, Kaede?
Tomorrow's my recital. You didn't forget, did you?
Forget? I said I'd be there and I will! Ow!
You mean it? You're not gonna have to work like you usually do?
No way! Tomorrow, you're gonna be the cutest little girl on stage
and I'm gonna be the first one in line to watch you perform. I wouldn't miss it for the world!
You said that last time.
Eh. You know, you should say something when you take the phone, mom!
I saw you on TV, do you have to pay for all that?
Heh, heh, real funny mom.
All I'm saying is that you should really try to be more careful, dear.
I know, Mom. I will.
If something happens to you, I'll have to tell Kaede about your work as a superhero at your funeral.
Yeah, I know. Believe me... I know.
[opera music]
Ouroboros.
Huh?!
I'm sorry, Kotetsu.
Ben?!
A merger?
It was the only option. Ad revenue kept falling...
... and we were lucky to find a buyer willing to take on our debts.
Here.
Huh? Who's this Lloyds guy?
Your new employer.
Huh?
And I would suggest that you go and pay him a visit.
What? Hang on a second. What the hell is going on?
Starting this next season, only the 7 biggest corporations are going to be sponsoring heroes.
Hate to say it, but our company just dropped off the list.
So, you're gonna disappear? Just like that?
Hey, business is business.
Do all the other heroes know about this?
I'm the last to know.
Sorry, old pal.
So, you're Wild Tiger. And I see your real name here, but how do I pronounce it?
It's Kotetsu. Kotetsu Kaburagi.
Hmm...
Right. You'll be briefed on your new suit in the design department.
Oh, I hadn't planned on starting today.
Or you can just quit if you don't like it.
Heh. Today works.
Huh?! [alarm sounding]
The industrial district.
The Steel Hammer statue?
I thought it was just a symbolic piece of art.
So why is it moving?
I bet a N.E.X.T. is behind this.
All right, you'd better get going.
Huh?
This is a perfect chance to debut your new look.
I don't think I can do that... sir.
Really? And why is that?
It's just... I've worn the same suit my entire career.
Don't be nervous. The tech on this suit is far better than that old one that you're used to.
Yeah, that's not the issue here. That costume defines my life.
It's everything I am as a hero.
A symbol of hope and justice!
Just wear the thing or you're fired.
Yes, sir.
Actually, this thing is really cool.
There you are. Let's do this.
There is one other thing.
We've decided to partner you up with another hero.
Huh?
Apollon Media is going to sell it as the first ever super hero duo to take the stage.
Nobody asked me about that.
That's because you don't have a say in the matter.
[groaning]
Where's my teammate, anyway?
[screaming]
Damn, that hurt. Guess I can't take this guy alone.
What?! It's you?!
Hold on. They're pairing me with you, Rock Bison?!
Say what?!
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Apollon wants you to be my partner.
You gonna talk all day, old man? Or are we gonna get to work?
[grunting] No way!
Chaser change!
Double chaser!
Hey, how come I'm stuck in the side car?!
I think it suits you well.
Yeah, dream on.
Take it up with our sponsor.
[grunting]
I'll handle this area, you all go on ahead!
What are we gonna do, sit here and watch?
We don't wanna just rush in at the same time. We've got to time our entrance for maximum effect.
[sighing] What a clown.
Excuse me?
That's a brilliant idea. Why don't we wait until the whole city's destroyed?!
A real hero doesn't time his entrances!
Okay, show time!
We are ready to go live, everyone, so good luck!
In 3... 2...
Welcome, ladies and gentlemen, to 'Hero TV Live'!
Stern Bild's seven major companies now have exclusive rights over the Heroes!
As many of you are already aware, we're starting fresh under a new management system,
and we have great expectations! The question is, which Hero will win the honor of
becoming King this season?!
Okay, time to move.
You sure? Don't wanna touch up your makeup or--
Sorry!
Hey. What the---?
And look who's just arrived! Now, we can really get this party started!
My ice is a little cold, but your crime has been completely put on hold!
Blue Rose! That crime fighting hottie!
But hold onto your hats, it's not just her body that's naughty!
Yes! I made it into the shot!
This is ridiculous. That's not how-- huh?!
Hey! I thought we were a team!
I'll show you how to bring this thing down!
Yeah? Good luck with that.
I'm gonna have to drop a line on this little guy.
Huh? What's wrong with the damn thing?!
Whoooaa!
See? Watch and learn, kid. Hey! Where'd he go?!
Is that who I think it is?
Yes! It's our new fan favorite! Barnaby Brooks Jr.!
Heh.
Heh. Man, I hate that. Okay, big guy!
You're goin' down.
What the hell?
Gotcha.
Huh?
[screaming]
[struggling]
[grunting]
Great plan, worked out real well!
Well, maybe if you hadn't gotten in the way!
Oh, great.
[screaming]
I'm tellin' ya, I can't work with this guy!
Well, I must admit, your debut as a team was hardly a rousing success.
In fact, I thought we'd seen the last of you.
Uh...
It was just lucky for you that that thing ran out of gas.
It's a mystery why the rampaging statue suddenly stopped.
Or, why hours later, it remains frozen in position.
So, do we have any idea who's behind it or what they want?
Forget that, you've got bigger problems.
You don't seem to understand the situation you're in. You are yesterday's news.
Hey!
This offer to be Barnaby's sidekick is your last chance to stay relevant at all!
What?!
That's right. Sidekick. Backup. Second banana. And you're lucky to get it.
Sidekick to that showboat?! That guy's a costume clown!
Speaking of costumes, you've got some explaining to do.
Hm?
[whispering]
What's that?
Suit, eh-- huh?
[whispering]
Uh-huh, okay.
Well, it was my first time.
[whispering]
Hey, come on, that suit isn't that bad.
[groaning]
Okay, whoa, whoa! All right, that's enough! I get it, I get it!
Ugh, okay, okay, you proved your point.
Hehe!
Heh, what a weird little guy.
[whispering]
Yeah?
You mean this?
[whispering]
The current time is 3:28PM.
Is that the time?! Oh, man, I gotta go! I gotta go!
[whispering]
I swear I'm on my way, I'm just running a little late, that's all!
You said you'd be here at 3!
I know, honey, I'm sorry!
Are you even coming?
What?! Of course I am!
Yeah? When are you gonna be here?
Uh, well, umm--
Don't worry, Kaede, I'll be there.
When do you actually go on?
4?
Okay, plenty of time!
[alarm sounding]
Hang on a second, honey.
Calling Tiger and Barnaby. It's showtime! The statue has started moving again!
We need you suited up and on the scene right now!
[grunting] Kaede?
Oh no! I'm starting to get nervous!
Dad, you've gotta to hurry up and get over here! I mean it! You've gotta make it!
Huh? Oh, how long have you been waiting here?
Just 3 and a half minutes of my life that I'm never going to get back...
... but hey, don't worry about it.
Oh, boy. How'd I get stuck with you?
How will the heroes deal with this giant visitor from the Brox area?!
It's showtime! And Blue Rose is the first one to arrive on the scene!
All right, you hold it there, buddy!
And there she goes!
As you're about to discover, my ice is a little cold...!
...But your movements have been completely put on hold!
[screaming]
Her ice was not strong enough to stop him!
You're kidding, right?!
[screaming]
It walked right over her Cutie Escape!
If you're going to go and create such a mess...
...you should take some personal responsibility. The least you could've done was stop that thing.
Just shut up, willya!
It looks like the Heroes can't get around to stopping the statue,
because they're too busy saving the civilians!
Here come reinforcements!
Hurry, guys! Hurry up!
Okay, boss! We're ready!
Good, now go!
Firing in three... two... one...
Rock Bison is on his way!
Yes!
He's controlling his direction trajectory by using his shoulder drills!
This looks promising... just a bit outside.
[yelling]
That was a close call! And a close shave, now that I think about it!
Yeah.. Thanks.
[screaming]
Look out!
Hang on.
Huh?
Hmm...
[gasping]
What are you doing?
What do you think?
Just wait a minute.
That thing's got a little kid.
Or maybe it's the other way around.
What are you--? Get out of my way!
Look, maybe it's not the kid who needs saving. You see where I'm goin' with this?
No.
What if he's the N.E.X.T. controlling the statue?
Well, he's still in danger!
Maybe the kid's a N.E.X.T. with telekenetic powers!
Well, while you're thinkin' about it, I'm goin' in!
I wouldn't be so hasty. Remember what happened last time.
Hey, that was an accident.
You know? I'm beginning to seriously question your judgement.
I never liked this idea. If the sponsors weren't insisting on it, I'd quit this team right now.
That makes two of us.
Uh-oh.
[screaming]
Don't move or you're all dead!
[grunting]
One move and the kid gets it!
[screaming]
What do ya know?
With those powers of yours, you can save people.
Ohhhh.
After all, you saved me. That makes you a hero, too.
Heh-heh!
[grunting]
Have a nice nap, old man?
Funny. You gonna tell me what happened?
The statue grabbed us. And then he stopped again.
And you're just sittin' here? Why didn't you escape?
Well, I can't!
Huh?!
Without using my power, I mean.
Then use it, you idiot. What are you waiting for?!
We've only got 5 minutes. I wanna save it until I really need it.
Unbelieveable. Well, suit yourself, little bunny. I'm outta here!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold it.
What?!
What did you call me? Did you just call me Bunny?!
Yeah, why not? You got those long pink ears and you're always hoppin' around.
You're just like a cute little bunny!
I am not a bunny! My name is Barnaby!
I am not a bunny! I'm a Barnaby!
I don't talk like that!
Head's up, you two. We've got another statue heading on a rampage.
There's a giant stone lion headed toward the new Morgan District.
What?! That's where the ice rink is!
[screaming]
[grunting]
You mind getting me out, too?
Huh?
Well, I mean, you're all powered up and everything.
You're right. I am.
Daddy's coming, Kaede!
[screaming]
[gasping]
Hey, kid! Come on down from there.
Stay away!
[roaring]
Wait!
[grunting]
Hey, handsome! You look like you're in a bit of a bind! What's going on up there?
Yeah, do you think you can help me out of here?
Hmm...
I guess I have no choice. / I can't turn down a hot guy like you!
Thank you very much.
Hey!
Ohhh!
At least let me palm that little butt! Oh, you're such a tease!
[squealing]
Oh-oh, I can't get out of here! Darn!
[screaming]
[roaring]
Kaede! Honey, where are you!
Kaede!
Mom, what are you doing?!
Kotetsu, thank goodness!
It's Kaede! I can't find her!
I think she's still somewhere in this building!
Okay! I'll handle it from here! You get outside!
[grunting]
This way, folks!
Kaede!
Noooooo!
Kaede...
Thank you so much, mister!
[gasping] Huh?!
Now, you get on out of here.
I sure will!
Hey, um, thanks.
Huh? Thanks for what? I didn't save your life, did I?
No, but--
Help me! Help!
You okay, kid?
Stay out of my way.
Why are you doing this, kid?
He knows why. He and the others!
What do you mean?
My whole life, they've hated me and treated me like I was some kind of freak!
No, not your whole life. Just since you started to make things move.
Normal kinds can't do what you do, I mean, it freaks us out!
We don't hate you, we're scared of you!
I didn't ask to be given these powers, it's not my fault!
[roaring]
Slow down, kid. I know just how you feel.
No, you don't!
I do, 'cause it happened to me, too.
I was about your age when I found out I was a next.
Huh?!
My friends turned on me. Called me a freak. I hated them for that.
Most of all, I hated my powers.
Then a hero called Mr. Legend came along and told me something that changed my life.
With those powers of yours, you can save people.
My powers can't.
Why not?
Because they're not like a real hero's powers. All I can do is make stuff move.
Trust me, one day you will find the right use for them. I promise.
You mean it?
You could be one of the best.
Really?
Sure. Now, come on down and let's have the police call your parents.
What are you doing? If we don't arrest him, we don't score any points.
Oh, shut up, will ya?
Okay, kid. You wanna be a hero? This is your first step.
What do ya say? You gonna come down?
It's gonna be okay, Tony.
Watch out! The building's collapsing!
I'm on it!
Let's go!
[laughing]
Help me! Somebody!
I got it! Save your power.
Your powers are still re-charging, right? I should be able to use mine.. Right about now!
Damn! Losin' it!
Thanks, and thanks again.
Uh-oh.
What's wrong, Tiger?
I'm out of time.
Huh?!
My power's about to run out.
Well, we've gotta do something!
Hey, Tony!
Uh!
We can't hold it! It's gonna fall!
[screaming]
We need your help, Tony! We need you now!
I can't.
You can do it! I know you can!
I'm down to five seconds.
4... 3... 2...
This is terrible!
Excuse me. What are you doing?
Just watching to see how they handle this situation.
That's sick! What is the matter with you?!
Huh?
Heh!
[cheering]
Oh thank you! Thank you!
Hooray!
[cheering]
Unless I'm mistaken, you just saved the day, Tony. Do you know what that means?
It means you're a hero.
I'm a hero?
Huh?
Come on, you have plenty of power left.
Huh? Oh, well, what do you know about that?
[chuckling] Who'd have thought?
Come on, it's time to go home, Kaede.
Okay, let's go, Grandma.
I'm so glad you're safe. I was really worried.
I thought I made myself clear.
You're supposed to be Barnaby's backup, his second.
I know what you said... But in the heat of all the action, My body moved on its own.
You're unbelievable.
What were you thinking, leaving Barnaby behind like that?
I tried! But he said he didn't want to activate his powers, so what was I----
It's not his call! If he's not participating, you make him!
Okay...
Since he's still inexperienced as a Hero, it's your job to help, and give him guidance!
What?
Isn't it your duty as a veteran, to offer emotional support to the new recruits?
I guess...
If I can't rely on you for that, there's really no point in keeping you under our employment.
The only thing you have going for you, old-timer, is experience.
Try to think of something that will help.
You know, like trying to create a pleasant work environment for Barnaby?
Are you listening?!
Uh...! Yes, sir!
I get it.
The guy's a loose cannon. I don't think this team thing's gonna work.
On the contrary, it's working perfectly.
Yes, but--
The two of you have captured people's attention. Viewership is up whenever you're on.
Now's your chance to sell yourself.
There's a reason you revealed your true identity to the public.
You're not going to let all your careful preparations go to waste, are you, my boy?
No, sir.
And by continuing this work, you may find a clue to help uncover the meaning behind this symbol.
It may lead you to the truth about this person you're after.
[opera music]
Don't worry yourself, my boy.
We'll find your parents' killer someday. I'm sure of it.
[phone ringing]
Hey! Don't screen my calls!
Do me a favor, and don't waste my time.
Oh, man...!
Apparently, you're as unfriendly as ever, little Bunny!
I told you... Stop calling me that.
I have some good news. I've been thinking it over...
You'll have to excuse me.
Hey! Hear me out!
Want to go grab something to eat?
Is this the good news you couldn't wait to tell me? Sorry, but I have stuff to do.
Can't you spare a little time?
Not really.
But everyone is expecting us!
What?
Whoa.
So what do you think? I'm pretty cut, right?
Amazing! You're completely rock solid!
I had no idea. I've only seen you in your Hero suit!
I thought so! Come on, kid. Go ahead and hit me! Give me your best shot!
No thanks, I don't want to. It looks like it would really hurt!
Don't be shy!
This is really stupid.
Huh?
I mean, come on. Why in the world do we have to do have a welcoming party for the rookie?
Well, I I think it's a nice gesture!
Huh?
He acts aloof, but I think he really wants to get along with his fellow Heroes.
You have to admit, he's delightfully mysterious.. and quite good looking.
I wouldn't necessarily call him mysterious. I happen to know the guy.
As a matter of fact, he was a very popular figure.
And he was very well liked at the Hero Academy.
Unlike me, he was an excellent student, and everyone at the academy knew who he was.
Well I think it's fun! It's the first time I've ever come to something like this!
Actually, I'm kinda nervous!
You're not alone. This is the first time any of us have tried to get together outside of work.
Oh, wow, really?
It's a good opportunity. We can get to know each other a lot better.
Let's all have fun! Most importantly, let's enjoy!
Sounds good to me.
If the King of Heroes says so, count me in!
his is so annoying.
Sorry about that, guys!
You're late, Kotetsu.
I was busy makin' sure I look good for all of you.
Now why would you need to worry about that? It's Barnaby who's the guest of honor.
You're right!
Hm?
Mr. Wild. Why don't we start by re-introducing ourselves?
Yeah! That sounds good!
Mm-hmm! Hi there!
I'll start us off.
[applauding]
And a good evening to you, handsome. I go by the name 'Fire Emblem'.
My real name is Nathan Seymour. I may not look it, but my Helios Energy is my---
You own it, right?
Huh?
You don't need to explain it to me, I already know.
Oh. Really?
I see why you're a top student! You've done your homework! That's terrific!
Now, why don't we just move right along?
Good idea!
Don't bother with your spiel.
I've already done my research on you, too.
Oh. I see.
Hey! This guy's bein' a jerk!
Well, he's just socially awkward, I guess!
He's probably nervous.. ...being in front of the Heroes he looks up to.
I'll be leaving now.
W-why?!
Going through these introductions is just a big waste of time.
Now wait a second, Bunny...!
Oh great, well that does it!
Just who do you think you are? This is ridiculous.
The only reason we came here is because you said that you wanted to get to know us.
What?! I never said that. You're mistaken.
It was my understanding that this was oganized because you wanted to get to know me.
What the heck's going on here, Mr. Wild?
You're the one who set this up! You said handsome here wanted to meet us!
I was told you wanted to meet me.
Does it matter..? I mean, really?
Kotetsu!!
I thought it would be easier for Bunny to fit in.
You know, if he was closer with everyone?
So, does this mean you lied to us?
Sort of...
That's appalling.
Despicable!
Just a minute, everyone! I don't understand what's going on. What the heck is this all about?!
I'll explain it to you later!
Come on! Don't you think it's a great opportunity for us to get closer as a team?
Closer as a team? Are you stupid?!
We're all rivals! It's a competition!
S'cuse me, I'll be going now.
But... Bunny...!
What a drag this turned out to be!
I'm leaving.
Huh?
Hmpf!
Oh...
I need to tend to my shuriken.
I guess I'll go take John for a walk.
No! Wait a second! Huh?
Huh?
Wha---?
Hello, Heroes! Something big just happened in the Stern Medaille area!
A thief has stolen an item worth billions of Stern dollars! You need to head over there right now!
Help me, willya?! I'm afraid of the dark!
Ah, stop grabbing my butt!
Oh, good, I'm not so scared, now.
You're scarin' the hell out of me! I'm going on ahead!
Transporter! Meet me at the south end of the park, over on Ninth Avenue!
Cool...!
I wonder if my earlobes would stretch out if I tried to wear those.
Huh?
Uh, you wanna try them?
Uh-uh!
Excuse me. I don't understand. Why are you running?
It's faster than walking, isn't it?
That's not what I mean.! I thought you could control the wind. Why don't you just fly?
I can't!
I don't just jump into the air! In order to reach flight speed, I need a jet-pack!
You can't fly with just the use of your powers?
Right!
I just float!
Mr. Sky High!
Damn it! Today is turning out to be one crummy incident after another!
Oh yeah!
Ready!
Hah!
Ha!
The suspect is still on the run. He's now taken the Statue of Justice.
Huh? Wait a minute, isn't that...?!
That's right. It's a symbol of peace that Mr. Legend recovered from some criminals a long time ago.
It's a very high-profile piece. So this crook knew exactly what he was stealing.
Know what'll happen if he gets away with it? People will lose faith in their Heroes.
So make sure you bring it back. It's critical!
[humming]
[chuckling and humming]
Hold it right there!
I don't want to!
Fire!
Ha!
Come back!
Waaahooo!
The suspect has now evaded police and is on the run. We still don't see any heroes in pursuit.
Come on! What's taking them so long?
Here they come now!
Hold on, everybody! The new team of Tiger and Barnaby is on the scene!
Will their teamwork be effective enough to make an arrest?
So that's the theif, huh?
Please don't do anything funny, all right?
What are you talking about? Just hurry up and catch him, all right?
There's a construction barricade up ahead. We're gonna split up.
What?!
[yelling]
Whoa!
Too slow!
This is bad! She's after our points!
Blue Rose, Barnaby Brooks Jr., and Wild Tiger are all in hot pursuit of the suspect!
They're closing in, but the question is, who will reach the man first?!
Now is not the time to be having this little bike race, you guys!
Uh-oh!
Wait a minute!
Huh?
Ladies and gentlemen, the suspect is nowhere to be seen! Where in the world could he have possibly gone?!
Damn it, Tiger! It's your fault we lost him!
Hey...
Did you... see anybody come through here, lady?
[giggling]
Yahoo!
Hey, you! Come back!
What the heck?
[screaming]
Didn't think he'd escape into an amusement park!
Well... It will make it look more exciting for us.
[giggling]
Hmmm!
There's the suspect! And standing in his way is Rock Bison!
These points are mine!
And look! Dragon Kid is here, too!
I've got him!
Oh no, you don't!
Hmm...
Hhhhaaaa!
Huh?!
[struggling]
[chuckling] Buh-bye!
[groaning]
Sorry! Oh!
[screaming]
Look out!
Mikey!
Hurry! Get out of here!
Okay! Thank you so much!
It looked like they stopped him, so how did this happen?!
[chuckling] Hm?
And here comes our King of Heroes... Sky High!
Hm!
Stop where you are!
Hm! It's not polite to point!
Sky High!
Bye!
Wow! What happened here?!
Wahooo!
Huh?
You're not getting away!
Well...
Yes!
You're a thinker!
He truly is the King of Heroes! The wind seems to be blowing in his favor this season!
It's the end of the road for you! Now hand over the Statue of Justice!
If you want it that badly... then come and get it!
What?!
How did he get away?!
I think we should put an end to this chase now!
Really? Are you sure?
What if I don't agree?
My ice is a little bit cold... but your crime has been completely...
...put on hold!
Girl...! You are takin' too long!
Stop interfering!
This is ridiculous! If you have time to say all that, just put him on hold and be done with it!
Hey! Don't steal my points!
[screaming]
You're breaking the rules!
No I'm not! That's what you're doing!
My word! What in the world just happened?!
That's strange...
He shouldn't have been able to dodge that.
Look, daddy, it's Sky High!
The Heroes are stalled, and unable to apprehend the suspect!
[giggling]
Aha! There he is!
Not so fast, old man. You promised not to do anything funny.
Huh?
Can you define what you mean by funny?
You really are annoying.
Okay, smart guy, then what should we do? In case you haven't noticed, he's very quick!
No matter how fast he is, he can't escape from us if we activate our powers and
flank him from both sides at once.
Actually a good plan.
Does that mean you're on board?
This is the perfect chance to show people that Heroes can operate as a team.
I don't care what we do, so long as we arrest him.
Okay, you go around to the other side. I'll come at him from over here.
Right on.
[screaming]
Oop!
Time to give it up, pal!
They assigned me the rookie, huh?
It's not just the rookie, smart ass!
Now!
What the hell happened?!
Where did he go?!
That was a pretty good idea! But... I'm afraid it wasn't good enough to catch me!
Damn it!
Huh?
[chuckling]
[yelling]
Agnes. Barnaby's calling in.
What is it?
I have a request to make.
Listen, everyone. Barnaby has something to tell us. I'm opening up all channels.
Hi, this is Barnaby. I think I've figured out the suspect's power. It seems to be location switching.
What the heck is that?
Apparently, he can switch places with anyone in his line of sight.
So that's how he got away!
Listen to me. There's something I want all of you to do.
Tell me something. Why, exactly, should we listen to you?
Oh! I'm sorry!
What are you doing?!
Just watch.
[cackling]
We have to be very careful that we don't harm any civilians.
What the--- ?
Just to remind you, we're Heroes who protect people.
Attention visitors. There is a criminal with NEXT powers, loose in the park. Please follow our
staff member's directions, while we move you to a safe location.
Right this way, folks. Keep a single-file line, please.
I had you all wrong, buddy. It seems you do care about the people---
Don't get the wrong idea.
Eh?
I came up with this plan so HERO TV's image wouldn't get ruined. And besides, it will make
it more difficult for any of the other Heroes to interfere.
This gives us me the perfect chance to steal the glory.
Whaaat?! I don't get it. How can you be so petty?
You should be thanking me.
Because of this brilliant maneuver, you're gonna stand out.
Hey, hey. Don't pull me into your head trip.
One problem.. As of now, our power's have have completely run out.
So, we need to make a plan until we recover.
Hey, I've got an idea that's foolproof.
Forget about it.
Hey, listen to me!
I'm sure it's nothing workable.
You haven't even heard it yet!
And besides, whose plan was it that made us run out of power in the first place?
What?
Excuse me, but you agreed to it!
No, I didn't! I was planning to go 'Ka-Bang' and then 'Ka-Boom' on this bastard,
and take him out, right from the beginning!
That makes no sense.
I'm saying we should've just gone for it!
If that's the way your mind works, I don't really think your plan's gonna be all that good!
Well I'm not gonna waste my time on some plan made by an egghead like you!
[growling]
Hey!
Why are you two fighting in the middle of this?!
I've got information from the Justice Bureau!
The man you're chasing is named Robin Baxter. He's an internationally known criminal, and we have
case reports on his activities from many countries.
Amazingly, though, he's never been apprehended. He's gotten away every single time.
So quit your petty squabbling and focus on the job!
If you do that again, I'll take points away from you!
Yes, ma'am.
The Heroes are now calling on all citizens to evacuate the amusement park.
Really?
Hey, what's going on?!
Huh?
We paid a lot of money to come and enjoy this place!
What's the problem? Go catch the guy! Hm?
Hi, papa!
Get him!
Don't let him get away!
[gasping]
Hey, you all right?
I'm fine.
Jerkwad.
Whoa! Whoa!
Did you see that?!
Out of the way!
I got ya! Hey!
It looks like he's moving toward the exit! Let's head him off!
Huh? Hey, wait a minute, we're not done here yet!
[chuckling] I'm over here!
[laughing] Whooo!
[grunting]
Ooh! Now the one with the mohawk is chasing me!
What, did you prefer the little bunny instead?!
Waaaahaaa---
End of the line, pal!
Whew! I think I've burned enough calories for today...
Let's wrap this up, what do you say? There's nowhere to run.
What do you know, I'm being chased by a couple of fools!
Who are you calling a fool, ponytail?!
What the hell?!
You got a problem? Go ahead, do your little trick!
You can switch places with either one of us. We don't care.
[laughing]
Uh, wow.
You two boys really are fools!
Aren't you even gonna try to show off?
Huh?
Hey, Tiger and Barnaby! Showing the public how close you are to each
other, isn't going to help you catch the suspect!
[laughing]
Umm. Do you think you could let go of me now?
Oh, sure.
This was your whole plan?
Kinda. I thought he was gonna switch places wi--
Come on, who in their right mind would fall for such a childish trap!
Yeah...
This is going to make people change the channel.
Change the channel?! What do think this is all about? We're not out here just to appear on TV!
Yeah, yeah.
Is that all this means to you?!
What was that big act you put on at the plaza?!
We're supposed to be protecting people!
If you remember, you're the one who told me to put pressure on the perp!
What are you trying to say?!
Not too bright, are ya?!
They're at it again!
Robin Baxter has committed many crimes around the world, and is a dangerous character.
Even as I speak, the Heroes are in the process of closing off the amusement park,
to keep him from escaping.
As part of that process, we're seeing the park visitors being led to safety.
Skyyyyy High!
Oh-oh! Looks like we're being pushed out, as well!
Ladies and gentlemen, this area is currently closed due to an emergency. Visitors are
to follow orders and move to the exit gates immediately.
[giggling]
Everybody, stay where you are!
[gasping]
[chuckling]
So there you are!
What are you doing?
I'm trying to catch the guy!
Get as close as you can!
Everyone! Try to form a tight group!
What's happening here?
Well, you're not very bright, are you? We've completely shut this area off from the outside.
Why?
If we gather everyone here, he'll be trapped. He won't be able to
escape, no matter who he switches places with!
Heh!
Interesting maneuver. Maybe you're not as stupid as I thought.
All we have to do now is come up with a good way to catch him... you know?
Well, I'm sure you will. You guys are pretty smart.
Holding us like this makes no damn sense. I'm getting out of here.
What? Stop that man!
Heh!
[grunting]
Help me!
[gasping]
Thank you, so much! Goodbye!
Oh, no, he just went out there!
Damn it!
Well, so much for following orders.
We need to rescue that guy!
You can handle that job yourself. We need to catch the suspect.
Dad! Dad!
Wait a second...
Dad, hold on!
Don't move, son!
Ah!
[gasping]
Huh?
Whaat?
Daddy!
Sir... From now on, don't let go of your son.
Remember... You're his one and only father.
And because of that, you're irreplaceable.
I understand.
Nice work. So, I guess you like kids.
Huh?
Come on, you did all that for that little boy..
...Not to mention what you did earlier in the day.
I have to admit.. It's kind of unexpected.
I was just trying to do my job, that's all.
All right! The Heroes are moving toward the park attraction where Robin Baxter was last seen!
They usually have things pretty much under control. But this time around, the situation's
very fluid. They don't seem to have a handle on how to deal with this guy yet!
I have some bad news...
I found out the roller-coaster the suspect escaped to, stretches from the core
of the park to the upper areas of Stern Bild. The long vertical tunnel is split up into the Green
Zone, the Mirror Zone and the Sky Zone. We've closed off all the emergency exits from the ground to the upper areas,
but if he gets past the Sky Zone, he'll be able to access the entire town from the observation deck.
So if the suspect makes it all the way up there...
...he can switch places with anyone in the city.
Oh, no...!
There's no choice! You have to catch him before he has a chance to reach that observation deck!
If we don't, he's gonna get away scott-free with the Statue of Justice!
But as soon as we get near him, he'll just switch places again!
Maybe we should destroy the entire building, and be done with it!
I shudder to think how much we'd have to pay in damages.
He's a diabolical opponent, for sure.
Ahhhh!
The suspect has just passed the Green Zone, and entered the Mirror Zone!
What?! Already?!
Don''t pressure us so much! We're trying to come up with a plan, all right?
Damn it! Let's just go and confront the bastard!
I'm tired of this! I'll capture him, man to man!
'Cause that worked so well last time.
[growling]
Then you come with me! / I'll provide you with support!
To be honest, that worries me the most of anything.
What?! And here I was, about to offer to act as your decoy!
[gasping] That's it!
What do you mean? What's it?!
Don't follow me!
Excuse me? Are you nuts? We're supposed to be a team!
I swear. I will capture the suspect.
Hey! Are you just gonna let the rookie go off on his own?
[humming]
Everyone hurry! According to our sensors, Baxter's going to be leaving the Mirror Zone soon!
Hm?
Hmm...
It appears he's about to reach the observation deck!
What in the world is Barnaby doing?!
You've been giving us quite a difficult time!
It's over! We're going to take you into custody and put you away for a long time!
Hmpf!
I don''t think your team is capable of doing that!
We're about to prove you wrong.
Heh!
Huh? What the---?
What's the matter? Your goal is just up ahead...
[efforts]
[grunting]
Heh!
All power exhausted in thirty seconds.
Ahhhh!
Damn it! I can't see anything in here!
[screaming]
It's over, everyone.
I've captured Robin Baxter.
(Cheers
He's finally done it! The rookie Hero, Barnaby Brooks Jr., has put an end to the latest threat
to the population of this great city! He has also successfully returned the Statue of Justice to Stern Bild!
[cheering]
Showed that guy who's boss!
Wow, that was exciting!
Our numbers are skyrocketing!
Great! We need to showcase Barnaby!
Let's make a documentary!
Here's what we've been waiting for... The Heroes are now turning Robin Baxter over to the police!
This is your idea of justice?
[humming]
Huh?
Hey! Congratulations! You really came through! Great work, Li'l Bunny!
How many times must I tell you not to call me that?
Hey pal, are you really still in a bad mood?
Just get over it! Isn't it about time we put all this behind us?
Whoa! Why the look?
What, precisely, did you do today?
Huh?
I mean, you talked a big game. But in the end, all you really accomplished was getting in my way!
Is that how you really feel?!
Hm?
Good work out there!
Thanks.
Yeah, today was a real challenge, no doubt about that!
I wasn't talking to you, Wild Tiger. And you didn't do anything all that challenging, anyway.
What are you talking about? I did stuff!
That... was very impressive.
Keep that up and you'll do well!
Yes sir.
[groaning]
I'm just glad you're all right.
I'm fine, but it was so scary!
I'm sorry honey, I should've been there to protect you.
That's what a dad's for... right?!
Oh, I had plenty of protection, dad! This guy Barnaby saved me!
He's one of those heroes, you know? Oh, and you should see him. He's so cool!
And really cute. He's my new favorite hero on the show!
[groaning]
[whispering]
Thanks, I appreciate it.
It was... just instinct.
[whispering]
Huh?
I forgot that was running.
Man...
I've gotta say... You really surprised me yesterday.
Don't follow me!
I swear... I will capture the suspect.
Hey! Are you just gonna let the rookie go off on his own?
Let me tell you, I have no intention of following his orders!
If we don't jump in, Handsome's going to steal the best part!
Hey, wait a minute!
Huh?
Can we let him handle it this one time?
See... I kinda wasted three- and- a- half minutes of his life, so I owe him.
What are you talking about?
It makes no sense.
We don't have time for this!
Mr. Wild!
We've gotta move!
Do you have a reason why we should let Handsome do this on his own?
In fact, I do!
My gut... says so!
What?!
He may have a small-- Well, he may have a big problem with his personality...
...But right now...He's trying his very best to capture the suspect.
As his partner, I'll watch over him!
If something goes wrong.. I'll take responsibility! Alright?
Until then, let him carry out his plan.
Please don't do anything funny, all right?
You promised not to do anything funny...
It's over, everyone.
I've captured Robin Baxter.
[sighing]
To be honest, I was really nervous at the end of the operation. I said I would take
responsibility, but there was nothing I could really do!
Huh? [laughing]
Well.. In spite of everything, he was able to make the arrest.
So it looks like your faith in him was well-placed.
[screaming] Whoa! That was close!
The guy never learns.
So, I never got to sing during the broadcast.
Then I went and chipped a nail! By the time I got home, I was so annoyed, I couldn't sleep!
I kept eating ice cream all night!
Are you blaming me for that?
Of course not! It's your partner's fault!
Yeah, he went and grabbed all the glory for himself. Even if he is a competent Hero, he's never
gonna win any girls that way!
Well... He was quite popular at the Hero Academy.
As I recall, he even had a fan club.
Well, regardless. I guess all of that still remains to be seen.
In that case, maybe we should invite him out for another drink!
Huh?
Sure! That welcoming party? Was a total disaster!
So Wild Tiger says he's going to treat us to another round!
S'cuse me?!
Hey... We honored your request to stay out of his way.
Don't you at least owe us a drink for that?
It's nice you're not pushy about it!
I don't mind going, since he's treating us!
I'm in.
It would be rude to turn you down, since you're so determined!
Thanks, what a generous offer!
Wait a minute...!
Can we go someplace where I can get a bowl of miso soup?
Words beginning with CH.
Okay... chaps!
Hey! Race you to it!
Get out of my way!
[giggling] Hold on!
[giggling] Hurry, Tiger!
I know, Tomoe...
Don't worry...
I'll try my best... to find a way for us to work together.
Mom... Dad...
I made it. I finally became a Hero.
And I swear...
There'll come a day... when I'll solve your murders.
I hope it's soon. I must say, though, I'm a little concerned about my partner.
[phone ringing]
Hmph.
Hello?