[LAWLESS laughing]
[LILAC grunts]
Lila?
[TSUBAKI]
I found you, dear.
So you were the hostage.
Don't worry, I'm here now.
[MAHIRU]
Tsubaki?
[TSUBAKI] You must have been
so frightened all alone.
I'm sorry it took so long
for me to find you.
Now, give me that.
[MISONO] What's going on?
Why is Tsubaki already back?
[TSUBAKI]
Wow, you even defeated Higan.
It looks like Greed and his Eve
really went on a
rampage in here.
What a mess.
[TSUBAKI]
Oh. Hey, Big Brother Sloth.
I finally found it... Teacher.
No, Licht, stay back.
You can't take this guy on,
he's too powerful.
[LAWLESS] Dumb angel. Look at
you, you're hardly standing.
And my body feels so heavy.
We can't fight him.
Brother!
I'll take care of it.
[MISONO]
So that's our enemy.
Tsubaki.
[MISONO grunting]
[gasps]
He must know what
happened to Hugh, right?
Where they're hiding him.
Tetsu...
[MISONO]
Don't do anything crazy!
Where is he?
[TSUBAKI] Ah. The one who
fell for Berukia's move?
[TETSU growls]
[TSUBAKI] Anyone who gets
trapped in his magic box
is teleported into an identical
one I carry with me.
Don't you think
the Servamp of Pride
made a wonderful assistant
to my magician?
It's almost a shame we made
him disappear forever.
You didn't...
Hugh...
[MAHIRU] Tsubaki. Tell us.
What are you trying to do here?
[TSUBAKI laughs] Just what
I was put on Earth to do.
[gasps]
[TSUBAKI]
You see, my late teacher
wants me to clean up after him.
This is one messy world
that he left behind.
[MAHIRU]
Blood? No... Flowers...
[TSUBAKI] I'm an instrument.
I am a cleansing rain.
And as fate would have it,
I am the only person who
can destroy a Servamp.
I am Melancholy.
I'm here to break you.
Your contracts, your worthless
bonds with each other,
mean nothing to me.
Stop! Don't!
You bastard!
[LAWLESS gasps, screams]
[KURO, TSUBAKI grunt]
[TSUBAKI]
Get out of my way, Sleepy Ash.
It's time for me to
kill our brother.
To do that, I have
to cut off his head.
It has to drop like a
fading camellia flower.
[KURO grunts]
You sure are troublesome
for being the baby of the group.
[TSUBAKI laughs]
You mean you accept it?
You admit that I'm your little
brother? Part of the family?
[KURO] I don't think I
have much of a choice.
My creator is the only one
who could have made someone
as monstrous as you.
[TSUBAKI]
That's right. He was a genius.
I've been searching
for you a long time.
Ever since you
murdered my teacher.
[KURO growls]
[TSUBAKI]
You are the black lion
who murdered that man in
cold blood, aren't you?
Who took the life of
our creator? Our father?
[TSUBAKI]
Wonderful!
There's something I've
been dying to ask you.
Tell me, Sloth...
[KURO gasps]
[TSUBAKI]
...you were the only one
who could have heard my
teacher's last words.
What did he say before
you took his life away?
[KURO] I didn't exactly stop
to have a chat with him.
[TSUBAKI]
Is that so?
My teacher had not met
with any of my siblings
since I was born.
You were the were the last one
to see him. You, the black lion.
I can only imagine his surprise
at seeing you, Sleepy Ash.
And he said nothing?
Not a single word
escaped from his lips?
Ahh... Or is it just that
you refused to listen?
Well, I guess it doesn't
matter in the end.
Wait. Of course. That's right.
I was the only one
he had plans for.
The only one he
gave a mission to.
[KURO]
So what did he want you to do?
Why did he create you,
the eighth true vampire?
Oh, so now you want
to talk, is that it?!
[laughs] You should have
asked him yourself,
while you had the
chance, Brother.
[KURO growls]
Where are you, Hyde?!
[LICHT grunting]
[LICHT]
Stupid hedgehog.
Misono! Tetsu! Get out of here!
[MISONO grunting]
Shirota! What are you doing?
[coughs] Kuro...
[KURO]
I know I was wrong.
I realize that now,
after running from my
feelings for so long.
That's why I'm not running
away now. Or stepping back.
I'm facing you head on.
I'm going to settle this
with you right now.
We should be conversing
with words, not weapons.
Don't you think so?
That sounds nice, sure,
but I don't think you
and I are ever going to be
able to agree on anything.
Besides, didn't you
kill my teacher
without ever trying
to talk to him?
So why should we
have a family chat
before you try to
murder me, huh?
[KURO] Can't you see
I regret what I did?
[KURO groans]
So weak! [laughs]
You don't act like you
actually regret it!
If you really did,
you'd find some way to
repent for your sins.
[TSUBAKI]
Hey...
...just how connected are we
as long lost brothers, hm?
I wonder... Do we think alike?
Do we become happy in the same
way, worried in the same way,
angry in the same way?
What do you think, Brother?
If so, wouldn't we agree
about everything?
And yet here we are fighting.
Wouldn't it make things
so much easier?
That way I'd understand you and
you'd understand me, as one.
But that's not the case here.
I'm alone, and you
are, too, Brother.
There's a rift between us.
It's probably just
a misunderstanding.
People reject the things
they don't understand.
It's a mechanism we have to
protect our sense of purpose.
Doubting yourself can lead
to destruction, after all.
Here! See for yourself,
the destruction of the world!
[CROWD screaming]
[MOTHER]
It's gonna be okay.
[CROWD screaming]
[TSUBAKI laughing]
[KURO]
You monster...
[laughing continues]
[TSUBAKI] I don't think
there's anything left
for us to talk about. [laughs]
I don't really give a damn
what you want, Tsubaki.
[TSUBAKI]
Uh...?
I'll stop you even if it means
I have to destroy you.
[TSUBAKI laughs]
[TSUBAKI] That threat isn't
interesting at all, Brother.
[KURO growling]
[groans]
Dammit, there are still
important things
we have to talk about.
Like what happened that night.
And what you did to Greed.
I don't want to regret
things anymore.
[KURO panting]
[TSUBAKI] Tell me again, did
my teacher really not speak
about me at all before you
murdered him? Not a word?
[KURO]
Uh.
Why did he remain silent?
Why did he keep me a secret,
why didn't he tell anyone,
even my own family,
about my existence?
[KURO grunting]
[MAHIRU coughing]
[MIKUNI]
Hey, kid.
[MAHIRU]
Is that you, Mikuni?
[MIKUNI]
Tell me. Why didn't you run away
when you had the chance, huh?
Sometimes it's hard to tell if
you're brave or just stupid.
[panting]
I couldn't go. I have
to look out for Kuro.
[MIKUNI grunts]
I don't think this situation
calls for your help any longer.
It's a family matter. It won't
stop until one of them breaks.
[MAHIRU]
You're wrong!
Kuro's finally
facing everything.
Not just his brother,
but also his own past.
[MIKUNI] If he's taking
responsibility for that...
...then let him. That's
Sloth's problem, not yours.
No. If I'm useless, there's
no point being an Eve.
[MAHIRU]
I'm Kuro's partner.
[TSUBAKI laughs]
[KURO groaning]
Ah, look at us, Brother,
these are the games we could
have been playing all our lives.
[KURO groans]
Get away from him.
[TSUBAKI] You're spoiling
our family fun time.
[MAHIRU grunting]
[KURO]
Mahiru!
[TSUBAKI laughs]
[KURO yelling]
[roaring]
[TSUBAKI]
Not interesting at all.
Hurry up, you two!
This place is falling apart!
[TSUYUKI] Most potential
problems are easily avoided
if you're always prepared.
I had the building evacuated.
I had a feeling that having
you all in one place
would result in chaos.
You must be C3.
[TETSU grunting]
[C3 MEMBER 12A] We need to go.
Please, get inside.
[gasps] Hugh!
[roaring]
[SAKUYA panting]
[roars]
[TSUBAKI laughs] Is that
the best you can do, Brother?
I expected much more from you!
That's enough. [laughs]
Now you're going
to die by my hand.
Is this the same way that
you murdered my teacher?
[growling]
[MAHIRU]
Kuro! You can't do this!
Trust me. Kuro...
[MAHIRU gasping]
[SAKUYA grunts]
[gasps]
Sakuya?
[chuckles]
[SAKUYA] Don't ask me why.
I don't really get it, either.
But I felt like this was right.
Even though I'm
Tsubaki's subclass,
I ended up betraying him.
[SAKUYA groans]
I could never really...
choose a side.
I'm a real idiot, huh, Mahiru?
[MAHIRU cries]
[laughing]
[roars]
[MAHIRU]
Kuro! Don't do this!
[roars]
Kuro!
[gasps]
Huh? A key?
[TSUBAKI growls]
[MAHIRU]
Uh...?
[yelling]
[screaming, crying]
[TSUBAKI (FOX)] You see?
It's just as teacher said.
You're the very best.
Absolutely remarkable.
You have more power
than your seven big brothers
and sisters combined.
You are his greatest creation.
I wonder what they'll be like.
If they will welcome
me into the family.
[TSUBAKI (FOX)]
I don't know.
You do have the power
to kill them, after all.
I wonder if any of my
brothers and sisters
will come and see me.
[inaudible]
[TSUBAKI (FOX)] Hey.
Doesn't teacher have enough?
Aren't we enough for him?
[TSUBAKI]
The words of truth were lost
and the clouds broke
off into the sky.
[TSUBAKI (FOX)]
Why does he keep making Servamps
if he doesn't need any more?
[VILLAGERS screaming]
[TSUBAKI] Oh, in the
depths of shining April.
Gnashing. Burning.
Coming. Going.
Stop it! Please, no!
Don't kill him!
[TSUBAKI cries]
[TSUBAKI]
I am a single asura.
I will do what my teacher
put me on earth to do.
This is the reason
behind everything.
I will kill Big Brother for him.
[gasps]
[TSUBAKI] I am Melancholy.
I'm here to break you.
Your contracts, your worthless
bonds with each other,
mean nothing to me.
[MAHIRU]
Tsubaki.
[TSUBAKI] The farmer wearing
a straw coat who gazes at me.
Can you really see me?
In the depths of the blinding
sea of atmosphere,
the sorrow is deeper and bluer.
[MAHIRU grunts]
[MAHIRU gasping]
[TSUBAKI laughs] You're just
not interesting at all.
[MAHIRU]
Kuro!
[KURO]
Mahiru! Stand back!
[MAHIRU grunting]
[KURO] Dammit. People like you
are the most troublesome of all.
[MAHIRU]
"Someone." "Someone else."
People never want to do
anything themselves.
Because it's easier that way.
Because you don't have
to take responsibility.
But, the only reason
the world keeps going
is because someone
does show up to help.
Someone takes a stand.
I wanted to be that
"someone," too.
The "someone" we need
isn't me. Not quite.
It isn't him, either.
No... It's us.
[yells]
[TSUBAKI laughing]
[EVACUEES chattering]
[MISONO]
Uh? Ha!
Shirota!
[TSUBAKI sighs]
Uh?
[TSUBAKI]
Sakuya.
W... Will you listen
to my last request?
[SAKUYA]
Huh?
[TSUBAKI] Tell my subclasses to
forget about me and live freely,
however they choose.
This is a personal problem now.
Thank you.
I'll take it from here.
[MAHIRU] I'm Mahiru Shirota.
Sixteen years old.
I like to keep things simple,
and try to keep
life uncomplicated.
That's why I picked up a cat.
I didn't want to just
leave him there
and end up regretting it later.
That would be irritating.
[MAHIRU]
Hm?
[meows]
[MAHIRU]
Heh.
[gasps]
[MAHIRU] Hey, how about I
buy you some of that ramen
you like for dinner tonight.
You can share it with
your new feline friend.
[KURO]
What are you grinning about?
I can't face you like this.