[MISONO sighs]
I never would have
thought an outdoor bath
could be so nice,
but this is great.
I'm having one put in at
home as soon as I return.
[LILLY]
I meant to tell you.
Mahiru went out to do some
investigating earlier.
Gah! He's always
going off on his own!
[yells]
[LILLY]
Misono?
[MISONO] So Tsubaki's
plans were foiled again.
You idiot! Why do you
keep going after him alone?
You're lucky Lawless
was so strong.
Don't you know what
would have happened
if you'd walked into
that trap without help?!
I know, I'm sorry.
By the way, what
happened to your head?
That's none of your concern.
Misono's right; that
could've been really bad.
[MAHIRU] It's not like I went
there looking for a fight
or anything.
Regardless of
your poor judgment,
capturing one of Tsubaki's
subclasses is a big win.
[TETSU]
Yeah, way to go, Mahiru.
You got so much stuff
done while shorty here
was relaxing out
in the hot spring.
Don't call me that! You idiot!
I am not short!
You're just freakishly tall!
Have some respect!
Anyway, I'm not so
sure it's a good idea
to have this subclass roaming
around the inn so freely.
In fact, we should think
about restraining him
in some form or fashion.
Wait, but Lila's no trouble.
Oh, come on,
don't be so naive.
He might be pretending to be
weak so we let our guards down.
Maybe I am too trusting.
Heard that before.
I'm not saying you
shouldn't trust others.
But you should keep all
possibilities in mind.
[HUGH] Before we do anything,
we should get some info.
You'll be a good lad
and tell us where Tsubaki
and his men are hiding, right?
I mean, you don't have
much of a choice, really.
Take it down a notch,
Hugh. Okay?
I've been thinking
about all this.
[MISONO]
And...?
If Tsubaki finds out
that we have Lila,
then isn't it possible he might
come to us to save his subclass?
[MISONO]
Huh... You think?
For just one subclass?
Remember when we defeated
Berukia on the street?
Tsubaki showed up himself,
which was the first time
that I met him.
I'd thought he was there
because he had some business
with Kuro, but...
I think he actually might've
been there to make sure
Berukia was okay.
He cares.
[SAKUYA]
I can't betray him.
Tsubaki was the only one.
He reached out his hand to me.
[MAHIRU] If one of your
subclass children got taken,
wouldn't you go and
try to save them?
Well, yes, obviously I would.
But it's hard to believe
Tsubaki would do that.
But you have to admit
it's a possibility.
Right, Kuro?
Huh?
Kuro?
Wait up!
Hey. Is everything okay?
[MAHIRU]
Kuro's being weird.
He hasn't been himself since
Lawless brought up that stuff
from the past.
I wonder...
[MAHIRU]
What happened to you?
Who did you kill?
Why did you have to kill him?
Did you agree with
the majority vote?
--To be, or not to be?
--[MAHIRU] Should I ask him?
Or just leave him alone?
If we don't fix this rift,
Lawless will probably
never work with us.
And we need him.
Kuro!
What happened when you guys--?
[MAHIRU]
Never mind...
Let's go back.
Everyone's waiting.
[meows]
[MAHIRU] Lately, I've been
thinking a lot about
what it means to have resolve.
[overlapping voices]
Back then, though, I still
didn't know the meaning
of the word.
[MAHIRU] Um, I'm really
sorry about everything.
I guess we're all just a
little on edge, you know.
[MAHIRU]
Want some?
[LILAC]
Um, Mahiru?
Why are you going out of
your way to take care of me?
I'm your enemy.
And I'm just causing
you more trouble.
[MAHIRU]
Huh?
[LILAC] You even got
into a fight with Greed.
For me. To make sure
he didn't kill me.
Don't get me wrong,
I appreciate it.
But I don't know
how to thank you.
Or if I should.
[MAHIRU]
Well, you say you're my enemy,
but it's not like I want
to fight Tsubaki.
I just don't want
people to get hurt.
I mean, sure, there are
times when fighting's
the only option.
But us killing each other
isn't going to help anything.
[KURO]
What are you saying, Mahiru?
That sounds nice.
But in reality, you're wrong.
You sound like a child when you
say things like this, Mahiru.
[LILAC]
I don't want to fight, either.
I guess I could thank you
with some advice.
If and when you face Tsubaki,
make sure you
watch out for Higan.
He's the strongest
and most dangerous
of the subclasses.
Ruthless and powerful.
That's why he's Tsubaki's
number two man.
[MAHIRU]
Tsubaki's number two?
[MAHIRU groans]
It's way too early to be up.
After everything that
happened yesterday,
I guess I've got too much
on my mind to sleep in.
Plus now I've got this
dangerous guy Lila mentioned
to worry about.
At least we're getting
more people on our side.
[MAHIRU]
Kuro? Did you not sleep at all?
Hey.
[phone ringing]
[MAHIRU]
Hello?
[KRANTZ]
Good morning!
Sorry for calling so early.
This is Krantz, from yesterday.
Licht's manager?
I hate to bother you,
but do you have any idea
where Lawless is right now?
[LICHT] Dammit, where is
that rotten hedgehog?
He's not in your room, is he?
No, I haven't seen Lawless
since he walked out
of the venue last night.
Is something wrong?
[LICHT]
My body feels strange. Heavy.
It's a struggle just to walk.
Is this what that stupid
hedgehog was talking about?
You'll die if we stay
separated for 24 hours,
my angel of music,
so always keep me close!
[LICHT]
Why don't you shut up and die?
I'm gonna murder him
just as soon as I find him.
[HIGAN]
The man you search for...
...is so far beyond your reach,
it cannot be helped.
Uh, let's see...
You are the one
I'm looking for, right?
Licht, something?
[LICHT]
What the hell? Who are you?
[HIGAN]
Your little pet made a mistake.
He put Tsubaki
in a terrible mood.
And as a result... [chuckles]
...he sent me.
I'm the old man who's now
in charge of dragging you
through total hell.
My dear pianist,
your wings will be torn from
you, no fault of your own.
[LICHT] When I was a child,
I had many dreams.
I wanted people everywhere to
listen to me play the piano.
I wanted to fly and
to talk to animals.
[animal crying]
What's your problem?
Sounds like you want something.
Almost like you understand
what I'm saying.
Do you like music?
[LICHT] All those dreams
pretty much came true.
But now I have
a different dream.
And anything a man can
imagine is something
a man can make a reality.
White, white, black...
[LICHT]
Imagination is a weapon.
In fact,
it's the most powerful
thing in the world.
[LICHT]
White, black, white, black...
And red.
[HIGAN] Why go through
all this trouble, hmm?
You could give this
old man a break
and come quietly instead
of resisting the inevitable.
[LICHT]
You're outta your mind.
Tell me who you are!
Sure, kid, I'm... Hm?
Huh...
Where'd my lighter go?
Crap, don't tell
me I dropped it.
Hey, Licht, you don't
have a light, do you?
[LICHT]
I'd rather give you my foot!
Wow, youngsters nowadays
are so short-tempered.
It can't be helped.
Well, then. Back to it.
I guess I'll have to
hurt you some more.
[LICHT]
What is the hell is this?
The old man's got
some kind of fire power?
Hey, listen up, kid.
There's no way you
can win against me
if you're fighting alone.
Not without a shadow.
A shadow is necessary if
you want to see the light.
Otherwise, how do you
know it's there?
What? You're talking nonsense.
[HIGAN] Okay, then,
think of it this way.
Right now, your
shadow is beneath
Tsubaki's wooden
sandals, defeated.
I think Tsubaki
sent me a picture.
My phone...
Crap, did I drop that, too? Aww!
I don't give a damn about
that good-for-nothing hedgehog.
But still... I refuse
to allow you to beat me!
I can imagine myself winning,
so I'll make it happen.
[HIGAN]
Such a strong spirit.
How very unfortunate.
Well, if you choose to resist,
I suppose it can't be helped.
Let's dance, little musician.
What is that?! A pillar of fire?
[MAHIRU]
Somebody's fighting over there.
Kuro! Let's go!
[KURO] Maybe we should
think about this first.
[MAHIRU]
But Licht could be in trouble.
Shouldn't we get
that spoiled brat
and the hot springs
giant to go with us
so we have some backup?
There's no time!
Licht could be dead by then!
[KURO]
But alone--
You're just being lazy again!
No, that's not it,
I promise. You see, it's just--
[MAHIRU]
We're fine!
As long as you're
with me, we can do this!
But we have to hurry!
Let's go, Kuro!
Put him down! Right now!
Wait, I know you.
You're Sloth's Eve, right?
I said get your
hands off him!
Now, now, there's no
reason to get worked up.
Just look at him, he's enjoying
this little dance of ours.
[LICHT]
I'll kill you.
Who are you?
Lemme guess.
One of Tsubaki's subclasses?
You can call me Higan.
And yes, I'm one of
Tsubaki's charming friends.
Higan?
--Kuro! It's time to fight!
--Really?
This is so troublesome.
Ma... hiru...
Kuro! What's going on?
[MAHIRU]
What the...? Kuro?
What happened?
Are you...?
Hey, Kuro? Are you in there?
The Servamp of Sloth
turned into a little ball?
Interesting.
Weapon!
[LICHT]
I'm the one you're fighting.
So face me, old man.
[HIGAN] Your creation
skills are amazing.
And here I didn't take you
for the type who gets stronger
when protecting others.
Such an angry gaze.
It makes me want to draw.
Thanks a lot, kid.
You've inspired this old man.
[MAHIRU]
My body won't move.
I want to help,
but I'm just sitting here
and letting Licht protect me.
Why can't I fight?
I feel like I can hear
Licht speaking to me.
His words breaking through
the music and flames.
[LICHT] "Why the hell
did you come here?"
[MAHIRU]
It's no use!
I'm not strong enough!
Kuro's gone.
I don't have a weapon.
I can't do anything!
[LICHT] It's not about wanting
to do something that you can do.
It's about what you want to do.
[LICHT] It's not about
wanting to become someone.
It's about who
you want to become.
[HIGAN sighs]
How tiring.
You're really strong, kid.
[MAHIRU] I have to move--
to do something!
[HIGAN] But all's well
that ends well, I suppose,
and my objective's been met.
It just can't be helped.
[MAHIRU]
Move!
[MAHIRU] Stop!
You put him down right now!
It's fine to be brave,
but it's not always smart.
Tell your friends
that I said hello.
[MAHIRU] No way...
What did you do to me?
Who are you?
You wanna know who I am?
I am a simple artist.
[MAHIRU grunts]
[HIGAN] The man who draws
what Tsubaki wants to see.
[MISONO]
This is impossible.
You're saying this tiny black
ball is the Servamp of Sloth?
[LILLY]
It's true. I feel his presence.
[HUGH]
So do I.
[MAHIRU] That man took
Licht and I couldn't stop him.
Couldn't do anything.
Kuro was right after all.
I should have waited
for the rest of you guys.
Crap!
[MISONO] Don't beat yourself up;
we may still have a chance.
Look what I found.
I came across it
on our way here.
A cellphone?
Wait... Is that a Berukia charm?
Do you think this belongs to
one of Tsubaki's subclasses?
I do.
And that gives us a direct line
of communication with him.
We don't have to
sit around waiting
for his next move anymore.
[BERUKIA (RINGTONE)]
Someone's calling you!
[BERUKIA (RINGTONE) laughing]
Jackpot. We're in luck.
Yeah, but... What's with
this ringtone and wallpaper?
[TSUBAKI]
Ah, wonderful, hello.
Did you happen upon this phone?
What a relief.
I'm a family member of
the person who dropped it.
Thanks for picking it up.
[MAHIRU]
Tsubaki!
[TSUBAKI]
Higan.
Don't worry, it looks like
someone found it after all.
[HIGAN]
Oh, thank goodness.
[TSUBAKI] Well, aren't
you going to thank them?
[HIGAN]
I mean, I guess I should.
Want it back? Then how
about we set up a trade?
We want the Servamp.
And Eve too, you bastards!
[TSUBAKI laughing]
Not interesting at all.
I'm speaking to the Eve
of Lust, that right?
Don't you think you're
asking a bit much?
I mean, it is just a phone.
That's not all.
We also have one of your
subclasses in our possession.
I'd call that a
pretty good deal.
And another thing...
We want Greed and Licht
back unharmed.
[MAHIRU]
Misono!
You're the one
who said he cared.
We'll see if he really does
want his subclasses safe.
It's the only card
we have to play.
[TSUBAKI] Don't you have
anything interesting to say?
We'll plan the tradeoff
and call you back
from this phone later.
Interesting enough for you?
[TSUBAKI]
I see.
All right, fine, we won't
hurt them anymore.
But I think we'll still keep
them separated far apart
from each other.
[TSUBAKI]
Well, I'm going to sleep now,
so be a dear and don't call me
again until late afternoon,
all right?
Oh, one more thing.
Higan says the charm
on his phone is handmade,
so make sure you're careful
and don't break it.
[MISONO]
That's what you care about?!
It's safe.
Jeez, what a relief.
Higan!
Your mistake
deserves punishment!
Even death!
I'll never understand why
you're his number two.
If anyone, it should be me!
Ah. So you're back.
I thought I smelled
old man in here.
Hey. I can't help
the way I smell.
Well, now...
It seems our plans
have been rewritten.
What to do? What to do?
[LAWLESS]
Ouch.
And where am I?
What time it is it?
How long has it been?
I wonder if the angel died.
Life's but a walking shadow.
A poor player...
...that struts and frets
his hour upon the stage.
And then is heard no more.
No matter how much they
struggle in the light,
they all die without meaning.
Licht's piano
skills are amazing,
but pointless.
No matter who you are,
it's impossible to become
anything that lasts.
Human life is so meaningless.
[MISONO] They can't stay
separated very long.
So we have to act quickly.
If the Servamp
of Greed was taken
around midnight last night,
and they haven't been reunited,
then we don't have
much time to plan.
Licht's life is
in grave danger.
[MAHIRU]
You mean he could really die?
At midnight tonight?
What will you do?
Should we go invade immediately?
Are you completely clueless?
Where would we even invade?
[MAHIRU]
Then what?
[MISONO]
Shirota.
You can't be involved
in this rescue mission.
You don't know what
happened to your Servamp,
and you have no weapon. Correct?
We don't have time to look
into what happened to Sloth.
Lilly and I will do what we can
with Tetsu and Hugh by our side.
We only have 16 hours,
but we'll do our best
to save those two.
Let's get a plan together.
[MAHIRU] I can't believe I'm
useless at a time like this.
What am I doing?
I feel like I'm
running in circles.
[MAHIRU]
Kuro!
[MAHIRU] I thought that
by going to the park,
I'd be able to save Licht.
I thought I had enough
power on my own.
I thought I could
be Kuro's partner.
But all I really did was
expect him to fight for me
and take care of everything.
Even though he said
it was a pain.
I'm so stupid.
I haven't learned
anything at all!
Even after everything
that's happened to me!
Dammit!
I wanted to get stronger.
To protect people.
C'mon, Kuro.
What happened to you?
Where are you?
You dumb cat.
Kuro...
You know,
I wanted to be an adult
so I could have the ability
to face problems head on.
But I didn't face you
head on at all.
I pretended it didn't matter
what you were feeling.
I pretended to be kind,
but ignored you.
Thanks to you, I was able
to do a lot of things
I never would have
been able to alone.
But when it was my turn to help
you out when you needed it,
I totally failed.
[crying] I'm sorry!
Kuro, I'm sorry!
[MAHIRU crying]
[KURO]
I can't watch this.
[MAHIRU gasps]
Kuro?!
[KURO] Why are you making
so much noise out there?
[MAHIRU]
Huh? What happened to you?
I actually have no idea.
I can't get out, though.
Well, at least you're alive.
I was afraid I'd never
hear your voice again.
[KURO] Honestly,
I kinda like it in here.
[MAHIRU]
You can't stay in the ball!
There's gotta be a way out.
Because... I want to talk
to you man-to-man, Kuro.
[MAHIRU]
That's right. Think.
What do I want to become?
How will I do it?
I'll find a way to
get you back to normal.
Thinking simply. It has
to be me. I'm your Eve.
[KURO]
This is turning into a drag.
I'm having a perfectly nice time
rolling around in this thing.
The outside world
is too much of a pain.
Maybe this is a good thing.
I don't have to face it now.
[MAHIRU]
You're not staying in the ball!
[SHAMROCK] I must know!
Will our young master
show up again next time?
[HIGAN] It can't be
helped if he doesn't.