[MALE GUEST 9A]
Hey. What's going on?
[MALE GUEST 9B]
A blackout?
[MISONO] Dammit!
You're smarter than I thought.
And to think you saw
past my elevator shoes.
[SAKUYA]
That disguise sucks!
[MISONO]
This is bad.
What if Greed and his Eve
have already been moved?
No, they're still using
this hotel as their base.
They didn't expect us.
Sendagaya! I'm going down.
You take the stairs up.
Leave it to me!
[MISONO]
All right.
So it's up to Lilly
and me to stop this guy.
[laughing]
Here I am.
I wonder which one
of their group
they'll send to
say hello to me.
[TSUBAKI]
Huh...?
Look, I like a
good laugh as much
as the next vampire,
but this is a bit much.
[GILL] So you're the
one called Tsubaki!
What a harsh voice!
I didn't expect a cute whale
like you to sound so manly.
[GILL] I'm told that you've
taken our Servamp
and his Eve as your prisoners.
Oh, I see.
You're subclasses of Greed
here to save your master.
[GILL]
He may be a brat,
but he's still our boss.
If anyone is going to
punish that little monster,
we're the ones who
should get to do it.
He isn't yours to hurt.
We'll be taking him back now.
[TSUBAKI laughs]
Well, I was thinking
of settling this situation
by handing over the keys to
the rooms they're being held in.
[GILL]
The keys?
[TSUBAKI] Listen, it's really
hard to take you seriously
when you look so ridiculous.
I'm living up to
my end of the bargain.
Now where is my subclass?
[GILL]
He's here. But he's hidden.
You'll find him inside one
of these mascot costumes.
Inside one?
[GILL grunts]
[TSUBAKI]
What a clever ruse.
If I attack any
of you at random,
I risk hurting my own subclass.
Hmm, I wonder what I should do.
This is turning into
quite an annoying trade.
Hello...?
Someone's showing off.
Oh, I see.
This must be Alicein's
private property.
Honestly, I thought this
trap would be more elaborate.
Either you didn't have
enough time to plan,
or the person in charge
was just very unimaginative.
[TSUBAKI]
Not to worry.
As long as there's a
chance my subclass is here,
I'll play along.
I'm not skipping out on the fun.
But I must warn you
that I'm the type
who'll do anything
to win the game.
Are you certain
you're ready for this?
[TSUBAKI] Hmm...
The mascot costumes are thick,
so I can't tell if there's
one person inside or two.
[TSUBAKI] Playing hide-and-seek
with whales in the forest...
I actually kind of admire
how absurd this setup is.
[laughing maniacally]
Ah!
Not interesting at all.
Shall we continue?
It's always so sad if
one of the poor children
isn't found during a game
of hide-and-seek, isn't it?
So...
...let's play the game.
[MISONO]
Bottom floor.
Gill and the others can only
distract Tsubaki for so long.
We have to save Greed
and his Eve quickly.
[HUGH] According to the
information we've gathered,
it seems Tsubaki has
five main subclasses
who are all highly
skilled in battle.
[MISONO] The strongest
among them is named Higan.
He's the one who kidnapped
Licht in front of Mahiru.
Logically speaking,
if the Greed pair
is separated beyond
their distance limit,
then our enemy is most
likely guarding them
in two different teams.
Higan can probably
handle one hostage
while the other
four work together.
Heh. As long as we take
Tsubaki out of the picture,
Tetsu and I can easily
handle any subclasses.
So you say.
Hopefully we won't
have to find out.
[MISONO] In order to get
Greed and Licht back safely,
we'll have to stop any
subclasses we come across.
But my Lilly isn't
well suited for combat.
How many of Tsubaki's
subclasses are down here?
Who are we facing?
[MISONO]
Huh? No one?
What's going on?
[chainsaw revving]
[SAKUYA]
There a problem?
You look like you were
expecting someone, huh?
[LILLY]
Stand back, I'll handle this.
Something's off.
We're alone here.
I don't sense anyone else.
[MISONO]
What sort of trick is this?
[SAKUYA] Guess you made
a few miscalculations.
I bet you expected us
to separate the hostages
beyond their distance limit.
And that the subclasses
would be split up
into two teams to protect
the top and bottom floors.
Sound about right?
You really don't
understand Tsubaki at all.
He's not the kind of person who
wants to be on the defensive.
You could also say
he lacks subtlety.
He'd rather aim big.
[TSUBAKI] I think we'll still
keep them separated far apart
from each other.
[MISONO]
Crap.
He's been playing us
from the very beginning.
[SAKUYA] You thought you
had the upper hand here.
But, you see, our goal
was never to destroy Greed.
It was to use him as
bait to get to Pride.
So we can crush him.
[MISONO]
They tricked us.
Lawless and Licht must
both be on the top floor.
Dammit, I can't believe
I fell for this.
[BERUKIA] Huh? This guy's
seriously only 14?
[HIGAN chuckles] No one's more
surprised than this old man.
[SHAMROCK]
Higan!
Will you please
stop fooling around?
Yeah, all right.
I don't really wanna
fight against a kid,
but then I guess
it can't be helped.
So they're definitely
hiding Greed and his Eve
back there, right, Hugh?
Yes. This is quite the blockade.
Don't worry your
head about this, Tetsu.
[HUGH]
Pride's here!
And I'm gonna handle
these guys all by myself.
[LILLY]
Misono!
[MISONO] We have to
defeat him quickly
and get up to the top floor.
But how?
Winning's the easy part.
Listen, brother.
All you have to do is
make sure you're crueler
than your opponent is.
[MISONO]
I can't hold back.
I have to provoke my enemy
and catch him off guard.
Sakuya Watanuki.
Tell me something--
who are you right now?
I don't see the trusting
friend Shirota promised
to save anywhere.
[SAKUYA yelling]
[SAKUYA]
Shut up!
Don't say another word!
Mahiru doesn't understand!
He doesn't see the
point of this war.
The point?
[SAKUYA]
Tsubaki has very specific goals.
He's been searching for so long,
but he still doesn't
know what the key is.
It might be as
simple as revenge.
Or it could be
something more terrifying.
So then this isn't
about vampires.
Guess they were only
a means to an end.
[SAKUYA] The whole war is about
finding some kind of key.
That's why he's doing everything
in such a roundabout way.
[MISONO]
What is he looking for?
[SAKUYA]
It's...
[LICHT grunts]
Where am I?
No doubt this is that
rotten hedgehog's fault.
I'll kill him.
[LAWLESS]
Man. This is a bad sign.
I'm hallucinating.
It's like I can hear my
little angel's voice in here.
I wonder if that means
he's about to die.
I mean, who knows how long
we've been separated for.
Of course.
I shouldn't be surprised!
Even my gloomy musician
is going to die!
He'll never become
anything at all!
He's so arrogant!
"Because I'm an angel," he says.
Don't make me laugh!
Actually, it's not
funny at all, is it?
[LICHT]
Shut up, you stupid animal.
I am not going to die here.
Because I am an angel,
you got that?
[LAWLESS]
I hate hearing voices.
Y'know, it's a real pain that
our minds are connected
by our contract.
The last thing I need is
your delusional death throes.
[LICHT] It's not like I want
to hear your idiotic voice
in my thoughts, either.
Hold on. Are you really there,
or am I totally insane?
[LICHT] Could you be
any more annoying?
I don't believe it.
So you're actually next door?
They must have caught you
after me, didn't they, Licht?
So lame.
[LICHT]
Shut up before I kill you.
[LAWLESS]
Yeah. Whatever.
Say, Licht...
They hurt you, didn't they?
It's weird...
My wounds won't heal at all.
So Licht, what happens
if this is how you die?
I mean, it's true
you're a great pianist,
but there are plenty
other musicians out there
in the world.
No matter how
unique a person is,
their life doesn't
really matter.
[LICHT]
I'm the exception, dumbass.
No. There's no such thing.
There's nothing special
about you, Licht!
The audience will applaud and
cry no matter who's playing.
You're just another musician
to them, that's all.
Something about us is different.
Oh, yeah? What's that?
It's me.
What are you talking about?
[LICHT] What are you
running away from, Lawless?
You stupid angel!
You don't get it at all, do you?
You should know better than
to have hopes and dreams.
They're all so meaningless.
Shut your mouth!
You're the idiot with
no real motivation!
You're gonna die!
And your whole life will
have been for nothing!
You won't leave a mark
on this world!
No, I'll live! Just you watch!
Will you stop talking?!
No human life has any worth,
and there's nothing you
can do to change that.
Sorry, it's true.
Talk and talk and talk,
but you don't really
believe what you say at all.
Get over here!
[LAWLESS]
You really are stupid, Licht.
Don't you think if I had
the power to get out of here,
I would?
You think I like sitting
chained up...
[LICHT] What, nothing to say
when we're face to face?
Pull yourself together.
[MAHIRU]
Where am I?
A desert? Hello?
[MAHIRU]
Hey, I know you.
Hello.
Kuro doesn't want to
see you at the moment.
You're lying!
[bell jingling]
[MAHIRU]
I hear it.
[KURO] Look at the map.
There's nothing ahead!
Good morning! Good evening!
Good morning!
[MAHIRU yells]
[bell jingling]
[MAHIRU]
Down here?
But how do I
get below a desert?
[MAHIRU] I can't lose
sight of why I'm here.
I have to find Kuro so I can
make things right with him.
Face to face.
Honestly. We'll fix this.
[KRANTZ] You see, it isn't
talent that accomplishes things.
It's imagination and effort.
[LICHT] It's not about wanting
to do something that you can do.
It's about what you want to do.
[MAHIRU]
This is what I want.
I just have to
set my mind to it.
Let's see...
[MAHIRU]
Stairs... going underwater?
Well. Now you've found him.
[MAHIRU]
Kuro?
[LAWLESS] Ugh, this whole
thing is insufferable.
Oh, don't get so riled up.
A majority vote is the fairest
way to make this big decision.
So are we going to kill the
person that C3 wants us to,
or not?
We don't have to take
orders from this C3.
Why don't we just rip
the letter up and eat it?
[JEJE] That's your
solution to every problem.
Why are we even
having this conversation?
It's crazy to think we might
kill someone for those bastards.
But we all know how
dangerous this person is.
Maybe it would be better
if he were gone.
Look, I understand
the logic here,
but something doesn't feel
right about all of this.
It's insane to think
we'd kill him just because
some organization told us to.
After all, he is the person
who created we Servamps
in the first place.
[MAHIRU]
The person who created Servamps?
Are Kuro and the others
going to kill him?
That's right.
He created seven monsters
like us all by himself.
He's powerful.
The letter says
that C3 found him.
Or at least someone in
Japan fitting his genius
and description.
Now, which one of us
saw him most recently?
I believe it might
have been me.
Though, that was at least
a hundred years ago.
[HUGH] If it's true
and he is still alive,
then he's no longer human.
Not surprising.
No human could have the
amount of power that man has.
Huh?
You're saying it takes a
monster to make a monster, eh?
[JEJE] What if he made
more creatures like us?
What then?
The world would
look like a hellscape
with monsters everywhere.
[GLUTTONY]
Listen, you mumbling maniac!
He hasn't actually
done anything yet!
We have no reason to kill him.
[JEJE] But we could do it
now, before it's too late.
How about you, Sleepy Ash?
What say you?
[KURO]
He must die.
I'll do it myself.
[LAWLESS] You really
think you can kill him?
[laughs sarcastically]
The human who created you?
You spend too much
time asleep, brother.
It's made you weak in the head.
He's like a parent to us.
He's practically one of us!
Our creator!
We have a duty
to protect that man!
Aren't we of all people the ones
who should be standing
by his side right now?
You're firstborn! Shouldn't
you try to keep him safe?
He's family!
Don't you dare use that
word to talk about us.
[GLUTTONY]
Hey!
[KURO]
What are we, really?
Can you even say
that we were born?
No, we were.
You know...
I never thought the
creation of vampires
was a good thing.
Not once.
What? No...
You can't...
That man is...
He's still our...
Kuro, come back!
[MAHIRU]
Kuro!
These... must be his memories.
I'm seeing his past.
He went alone to meet
with the one who created
all the Servamps.
[MAN 9A]
Ah. It's been a long time.
I'm glad to see you well...
...Sleepy Ash.
[KURO]
Wow.
I can't believe he's
really still alive.
[KURO]
Think about it.
No, don't think.
[MAHIRU]
I can't hear.
What are they saying?
Kuro looks unsure.
But he's doing it anyway.
[KURO]
But I have to kill him.
[MAHIRU]
Kuro! Your eyes!
[MAHIRU yells]
[KURO]
Don't look! Don't look!
I don't want to disappoint you.
I want to become
a hero, too, Mahiru.
Kuro, stop it, please!
You must know that
this was the only way.
We did what we had to;
there's nothing to regret.
[JEJE] He's right; we just
played the cards we were dealt.
Don't look down.
We chose the best option.
Yes, I objected.
But I can still see
that his death
was the inevitable outcome.
I am not angry.
I have no right to be mad at
you, even though I disagreed.
[LAWLESS] Well, I'm not
gonna forgive what you did.
I'll never forget this!
[MAHIRU] This is where Kuro's
uncertainty and regret
come from.
I didn't understand
the resolve I needed
to face his past alongside him.
He needs help.
Kuro! You idiot!
I won't run away!
I'm here!
Because I'm determined
to get you back to normal!
Your past sins and
regrets don't matter;
only what you do now!
I didn't know the resolve I'd
need to face this kind of pain.
[MAHIRU yelling]
[KURO]
Hey, you.
What do you think is eternal
in this fleeting world?
All living beings die.
Things fall apart.
Feelings fade away.
There's only one true constant.
As long as you're human,
only one thing is eternal.
And that... is the sin of man.
[MAHIRU]
Where am I?
[KURO]
My goodness.
I'm honestly impressed you
made it this far in, Mahiru.
If you were smart,
then you'd leave him alone.
What are you? Really?
[KURO]
Hmm... hmm... hmm...
Well, if you're here,
why don't you pry open
one of Kuro's secrets?
You might learn a thing or two.
Hold on.
I can give you some tools.
You can break every one of
these tortured containers open.
Find out Kuro's deepest fears.
Everything he regrets in life!
[MAHIRU]
I don't need to.
Kuro. You're inside, aren't you?
All I want is for
him to let me in.
I don't need a weapon.
I just need to knock.
[knocking]
It's me! Hey!
[KURO]
Who are you?
I'm...
[MAHIRU]
Me?
Wait... Who am I again?
[MAHIRU]
It's me. Mahiru Shirota!
I came here so I could face you.
[KURO]
Mahiru.
I... No, but...
Why did I do
something like that?
We don't need any more
monsters in the world.
No. I had a choice.
Should I have
discussed things first?
Could I have done
something like that?
[MAHIRU] All this time you
regretted what happened. Alone.
[KURO]
I was right. I'm not wrong.
We don't need any more
monsters in the world.
I had to stop him there.
I was right.
And if I hadn't done it,
someone else would have.
No. Is that true?
Was the only choice
really to kill him?
If I was wrong,
then why did I do it?
Regret is so painful.
It's tearing me apart.
I'd rather never do
or feel anything again.
I won't make
any more decisions.
I'll only do what
others tell me to do.
That's all.
Did I do the right thing?
Someone, please tell me.
Tell me that I wasn't
wrong to kill him!
[crying]
Maybe you were wrong, Kuro!
But you already know that.
You're the only one who can
tell if you were wrong or right,
and I can hear you arguing
with yourself about it.
Listen to me! Kuro...
The reason you feel
this way is because
you're doubting your actions
all those years ago.
It takes courage to
accept you were wrong.
Because it means you
don't trust yourself.
But you can work through this.
You can move on!
[grunts]
If you regret it,
then you can't just sit here
moping around forever.
Kuro. Stand up.
You and me.
Let's face this together.
You're not alone. Got that?
You're such a pain.
I could just die.
[MAHIRU]
Mahiru Shirota. Age 16.
I like to keep things simple,
and try to keep
life uncomplicated.
That's why I picked up a cat.
[KURO]
Meow.
[MAHIRU]
I decided to name him Kuro.
And he can call out my
name whenever he needs me.
I'll be there!
[MISONO] Listen, idiot,
I'm older than you,
so you have to follow my order!
[snoring]
[TETSU]
He fell asleep.