[MAHIRU]
Dammit. Ah!
[KURO]
What's wrong?
[MAHIRU] I can't get this
stupid letter to open.
What's with this seal?
It's probably junk.
Y'think? Whatever.
[BERUKIA] You've been in such
a good mood lately, Tsu-Tsu.
[TSUBAKI laughs]
I guess that's true. Pon.
It's a blessed day when
we get to see you smile.
I wish it were more often,
young master.
[TSUBAKI]
Pon.
The young master
used my discarded tiles
to improve his game!
[TSUBAKI]
Stop it, Shamrock.
You know I hate it
when you call me that.
All right, here I go!
[OTOGIRI]
That's ron. I win.
You got cocky.
Your carelessness is a problem.
[BERUKIA]
You little witch!
You've been picking
on me this whole game!
[OTOGIRI] I'll take your
12,000 points now.
Hey, Sham.
How 'bout an update on
the mission I gave you?
Right!
You shouldn't be concerned.
Everything's in place.
It is just like you wanted,
young master.
[TSUBAKI] I told you to
stop calling me that.
More importantly,
young master...
About this liar...
It's only a matter of time
before he betrays you.
[TSUBAKI laughing]
That's not very
interesting, Shamrock.
The eve of the
festival is over.
The war is about to begin.
It's time we make things
much more interesting.
The fireworks. The vendors.
The crowds of
unsuspecting humans.
What are you waiting
for, Brother?!
Hurry up and take us
to the festival!
[laughing]
[coughing]
--Young master...
--Embarrassing.
[TSUBAKI]
Water.
[GIRL STUDENT 5A]
Aw, little Kuro!
Here, have some of this egg.
[GIRL STUDENT 5B]
Do you want a cookie?
Look at this cat.
This has to be the best
of his nine lives!
It's almost like he understands
what they're saying.
Maybe he's a genius.
[MAHIRU] It was the end of my
first year in high school.
Summer break started
the next day.
Hmm... What are you gonna
do if people find out
you're actually a vampire
and not a normal black cat?
[KURO] Hey, don't get
all mad just because
I'm popular with the ladies.
[MAHIRU]
I'm not getting mad!
What if one of them
turns out to be an enemy
trying to get close to you?
[KURO] How are you both
paranoid and too trusting?
Forget about it.
Just watch me roll around in
your hands and be cute instead.
[MAHIRU]
You're not helping!
This takes me back.
I came here with my uncle
when I was little.
Kuro?
What the--Where'd you go?!
How'd you manage to get
all that food so quickly?!
[KURO] Never underestimate
a hungry vampire.
[MAHIRU]
The fireworks will start soon.
[SHAMROCK]
Excuse me.
I found this case.
Someone must have lost it.
I'm in a bit of a hurry now.
Could you take it to the
lost and found for me?
I'm afraid I just
don't have time to.
Please make sure
you get it there
before the fireworks begin.
[MAHIRU]
Well...
I guess it's the
simplest thing to do.
I'll be right back, Kuro.
Oh, wow, it's
so crowded... Ah!
[TETSU]
Oh. Sorry.
No. It was my fault.
Thanks.
[MAHIRU]
So tall!
And what's with that giant box?
[TETSU]
I didn't see you.
I'm on the lookout
for someone else.
A friend?
Eh, someone
I got separated from.
Well, in that case,
you should just page them
over the intercom.
Simple.
That's a good idea.
How do I do that?
I'm heading to the lost
and found right now,
and they should
be able to help you.
Just come along with me.
Thanks a lot!
You're a big help.
The guy I'm looking for
is kind of odd,
so I'll notice if we
pass him on the way there.
Okay, works for me.
[MAHIRU]
The shape of that thing...
It looks like--
[MAHIRU]
Uh... So about that box.
Oh, this?
It's just a coffin, bro.
[MAHIRU]
And, uh...
Why do you have it, exactly?
[TETSU] Well like
I said, it's a coffin--
so obviously it's for
vampires to sleep in.
[MAHIRU]
Could it be...?
Is this guy another vampire?
If you live around here,
you probably know that--
[CROWD MAN 5A]
Holy crap! What was that?
An explosion?
[CROWD MAN 5B]
Whoa, what happened?
[CROWD WOMAN 5A]
Someone said a bag exploded.
[CROWD MAN 5C]
Yeah, it was a silver briefcase.
[SHAMROCK] Please make
sure you get it there
before the fireworks begin.
[MAHIRU] The fireworks start at
seven sharp, right?
Okay, calm down.
If this is a bomb,
I can call Kuro
and have him take it far away.
But what about this guy?
Is he in on it?
Is this a trap?
[KURO] How are you both
paranoid and too trusting?
Listen.
Would I be right in assuming
you're a good, rational person?
Hmm... I guess so.
[MAHIRU]
I may be too trusting,
but I'd rather give people
the benefit of the doubt.
If I get tricked,
I'll worry about it then.
Things are simpler that way.
Huh... That's a
smart way of thinking.
[CROWD screaming]
Kuro!
[KURO] You need to get it
away from people?
The sky'll do.
He's a Servamp.
[MAHIRU]
C'mon!
Throw it as hard as you can!
That's not gonna
be high enough!
If that thing falls back
down on us, we're dead!
[KURO]
Meh. This'll be fine.
These situations
always work out.
The bag'll explode in the
air while we watch.
[MAHIRU] No, it's already
coming back down!
[SHAMROCK]
Young master!
Are you seeing this?
It's finally beginning!
The curtain's rising
on our grand funeral!
[TSUBAKI laughs]
Now, now, troubled world.
Won't you come out and play?
[TETSU]
Got it.
[MAHIRU]
How's that gonna help?
Everything's fine now.
Just watch.
Absolutely nothing can
destroy this coffin of mine.
[MAHIRU]
Hot springs?
Okay... Just who in
the hell are you, man?
Tetsu Sendagaya.
You may know my family's
hot springs resort.
[MAHIRU]
Huh?
[HUGH]
You fool!
I can't believe you
blew up the coffin
even though I was... inside!
[TETSU]
Hugh? You were in there?
I've been looking
for you everywhere.
I thought you'd disappeared.
[MAHIRU]
Hugh?
[KURO]
Oh, long time no see.
This is the Servamp of Pride.
Old Child.
[MAHIRU]
A Servamp?!
[MISONO]
Yes.
I should be back
home by next week.
My injuries are mostly healed.
I'm just resting now.
No need for concern.
Thank you for calling.
I know you're very busy.
Bye, Father.
[LILLY] Make sure you're not
rushing yourself, Misono.
We'll have plenty of
opportunities to help Mahiru out
once you've fully recovered.
I promise.
Doudou told me earlier
that you-know-who is in town.
Makes me wonder what
he could be planning.
[TETSU] Okay, Hugh,
you've had some of my blood.
Have you recovered yet,
or do you need some more?
[HUGH]
I'm fine, of course.
Don't mistake me for
someone who's easily beaten.
I embody strength!
My name is Hugh
the Dark Algernon III,
and I am the
mightiest of Servamps,
the true form of Pride!
Quake in fear before me!
[MAHIRU] Um... Are you sure
you're completely recovered?
You fool! Weren't you
listening to me?
Or maybe terror is keeping
you from thinking straight
in the presence of
a ferocious vampire.
Yeah, so, uh...
I can call you "Hugh," then?
[HUGH]
You'll use my full name, human.
[KURO]
That's way too long.
[HUGH] Yes, it has been
a long time, Sleepy Ash.
While you were off
lazing around,
the world fell into
chaos thanks to him.
You mean Tsubaki?
[HUGH]
Before we get into all that,
why don't I tell you the
story of how I met up
with Tetsu here?
[MAHIRU]
Why would we care?
[HUGH] I had followed the scent
of some high-quality blood
to a hot springs inn, where I
intended to find a person
worthy of being Pride's Eve.
[TETSU] A customer?
We have some nice rooms vacant.
You'll find that they're
reasonably priced.
I can't stay in a room that
allows so much sunlight in!
[TETSU]
A vampire?
[HUGH]
Don't you know anything?!
[TETSU'S DAD]
What are you doing, Tetsu?
That room has our best view!
[whining]
[HUGH] Tetsu's young,
but he's got top-notch blood,
physical strength,
and common sense.
We were a perfect match.
[MAHIRU chuckles]
Young, huh?
I don't know if
I'd call him that.
Though I guess when
you're an ageless vampire,
all humans seem like kids.
[HUGH]
Tetsu is only 14 years old.
14 years old?
Gah! You're in middle school?!
Second year.
And here I was thinking
you were a college student!
[HUGH]
Observe!
This grand weapon proves just
how great his potential is
as an Eve!
[MAHIRU] This giant coffin
is your weapon?
Yeah, I don't know
how to get rid of it.
So I figured I could use it
for some free advertising.
[MAHIRU]
That's actually pretty smart.
Well, if the
customer's a vampire,
then it's my job as an innkeeper
to prepare a dark room for him.
That's just good business.
Tourist destinations don't
do well if there's fighting,
so I do everything I can to
keep the peace between humans
and vampires.
[HUGH]
No question about it.
This was the work
of Tsubaki's men.
[MAHIRU]
You know that for sure?
[HUGH] I have more subclasses
than any other Servamp
because I like to stay
well-informed about the world.
We were on high alert today
because of certain information
we had received earlier.
It would probably be best
for us to stay in contact
and help each other out.
We can face Tsubaki together.
Yeah!
This is such a to-do.
Be warned.
Tsubaki isn't the
only player here.
There are other enemies
that we must watch out for.
Great, even more work.
[MAHIRU] Misono, Tetsu, and
that traveling antique dealer.
Right, that makes four Eves.
I hope the other
Eves and Servamps
are willing to
work with us, too.
That could make
things a lot easier.
--[KURO yawns]
--How are you tired? Ah!
[KURO]
Mahiru?
Ha ha! Looks like I'm
gonna rake in some cash.
[MAHIRU]
Where am I?
Where's Kuro?
What's going on?
[TSUYUKI] Most potential
problems are easily avoided
if you're always prepared.
I'm sure you must be thirsty.
Help yourself.
I prepared this spread
especially for you.
If you'd like something else,
I can have other
options brought in.
No thanks. I'm okay.
Don't I... know you?
I'm Tsuyuki, and I work
for a group called C3.
We're a neutral party between
humans and vampires.
[MAHIRU]
Neutral party?
[TSUYUKI]
Yes.
I am your ally, Mahiru Shirota.
I apologize for the unusual
way we brought you here,
but it couldn't be helped.
There's an important question to
which we must have an answer.
Will you work with us?
Will you help us stop Tsubaki?
[MAHIRU]
Um... Hold on a sec.
This is all really sudden.
[TSUYUKI] One of C3's top
priorities is to create harmony
between vampires and humans.
To ensure peace.
As you can imagine,
Tsubaki's existence
is a threat to that mission.
In order to guarantee success,
we need all the power
we can get on our side.
That's why we've
brought you here today.
We'd like your Servamp
to work with us.
You should ask him
about our organization
the next time you see him.
I'm sure he knows all about us.
[MAHIRU]
Really?
[TSUYUKI] Our goals
are the same, Mahiru.
There's no reason to
refuse this partnership.
Sure, but...
I need to talk to Kuro about it.
And how could you be running
an organization like this
if you're a high school student?
[TSUYUKI]
I'm 22 years old. I'm an adult.
[MAHIRU]
But I ran into you at my school!
[TSUYUKI] I was only there
in order to come in contact
with you.
It was all part
of my preparation.
[MAHIRU] I thought he
was just a year above me.
When did I get so bad
at telling people's ages?
It's our responsibility
to capture Tsubaki
and get him off of the streets.
You see, he was once a
Servamp that C3 was using
in their research.
[MAHIRU]
What do you mean?
[TSUYUKI] It was before
I joined the organization,
so I wasn't actually involved.
I've only read about it
in the archives.
[MAHIRU] Wait, hold on,
back up a little bit.
So, Tsubaki used to be
part of C3 or something?
[TSUYUKI] I'll tell you all
the details once you commit
to working with us.
Again, there's no
reason to say "no."
[MAHIRU]
But--
[TSUYUKI]
Tsubaki's gotten out of control.
And we've taken too long
to prepare on offense.
We must band together to break
Tsubaki and his subclasses.
There is simply
no other way, Mahiru.
[MAHIRU]
Break them?
You mean murder them.
You want to kill them all.
Then sorry, I can't help you.
One of those subclasses
is my best friend!
And I promised
that I'd save him!
You're talking about Sakuya.
That correct?
[MAHIRU]
You... know?
Yes. In order to prepare
for our little meeting today,
I looked through the information
we had collected on you.
[MAHIRU]
What?
It's time to stop acting
like a spoiled child
and be mature about this.
Trust the adults
and the good people
working at C3
to improve society.
Your personal feelings
have no place in this matter.
[MAHIRU] What makes you
think you know what's best?
Sitting there drinking black
coffee and calling me a child
doesn't make you mature.
And if adults murder,
then I'll stay a kid who
likes chugging orange soda!
[TSUYUKI]
I see. And I understand.
You have the right to refuse us.
[MAHIRU]
Yeah, I do. See ya!
[TSUYUKI] However, there's a
total of 52 doors in this room,
and I'm afraid only one
of them leads outside.
[TSUYUKI] Please, feel free
to see yourself out.
I'd hurry up, though.
Or you'll never see Sloth again.
[KURO]
This is such a pain.
[KURO grunting]
[TSURUGI]
Whoops.
You're one slippery target, cat.
Sorry, Tsurugi, my coordinates
were a little bit off.
[TSURUGI] It's fine. You've been
out of the field for a while.
And you've gotten fat raising
that new kid of yours.
[JUNICHIRO] C'mon!
I barely gained any weight!
[YUMIKAGE]
Tsurugi!
Stop the useless
chatter and focus.
[chuckles]
Sure. Apologies, Yumi.
[KURO]
Oh, I get it. You're from C3.
[TSURUGI]
Tsurugi Kamiya. Age 26.
I'm the kinda scum who'd
kill his whole family
if the price was right.
Seriously, I'll lick
your boots right now
if you pay me to do it.
[YUMIKAGE]
Will you please shut up?
[TSURUGI]
Ha ha!
[YUMIKAGE sighs]
If you'd come when
you got that letter,
then we wouldn't have had to
go through all this trouble.
It's your own fault.
[MAHIRU]
What are you doing to Kuro?
Where is he?
Your Servamp's currently
with expert vampire hunters--
the most talented
team that C3 has.
I'm positive they're
getting Sloth some exercise.
Vampire hunters? Seriously?
[TSURUGI]
Do you really have to run away?
I should ask for a bonus on top
of my flat rate for this job.
Vampires have a different
name for the hunters.
[YUMIKAGE]
Go, earn your pay, Tsurugi!
[TSUYUKI] They call them
the mad dogs of C3.
[MAHIRU]
Kuro. I've got to get to him!
This way!
Welcome back, Mahiru.
At this rate, it will
probably take you all day
before you find your way out.
Do you know about
the maximum limit
between an Eve and Servamp?
If you stay apart from
each other for too long,
you'll start to
feel pretty sick.
Eventually, you'll die
from the separation.
[MAHIRU]
Huh?
I'll kill that lazy cat myself!
How could he forget to tell
me something so important?!
[TSUYUKI]
You only have two options here.
You can find the
way out yourself,
or you can agree
to work with us.
Why would I wanna
work with someone
who's putting me
through crap like this?!
[door slams]
Have teenagers always
been this childish?
Surely I was never like this.
You're just wasting your time
trying to get away from us.
I mean, we do have
your Eve in our care.
We've got the upper
hand right now.
[KURO]
Mahiru...
[TSUYUKI]
Now, then.
Are you ready to
act like an adult
and make the right decision?
Decision?
[MAHIRU]
All of this...
It's just to force me
to work with them.
They've prepared this elaborate
trap so I have no other choice.
I have to comply.
But is there really only
one way to get outta here?
Only one way to save Kuro?
[TSUYUKI] You must realize that
the only real option you have
is to listen to us.
To join our cause.
You don't have much of a choice.
You're actually right
about one thing.
My choice is simple!
The so-called adults may have
prepared a "correct" answer.
But I've got a better idea.
What, are you breakdancing?
[MAHIRU] Kuro and I will
decide what to do on our own!
[MAHIRU yelling]
[TSUYUKI]
Unfortunately, you found it.
Another way out.
Let me warn you about
something, Mahiru.
You trust that Servamp,
but you shouldn't.
He will be your downfall.
That thing is not your friend.
It's a vampire.
And all they do is suck
the lives out of people.
Every vampire must be broken.
Tsubaki is just the beginning.
You want them broken?
Why do you keep using that word?
Why do you wanna break them?
Maybe you've never seen a
vampire rolling on the floor
while playing video games
and eating potato chips.
Or a vampire who
apologizes for lying
while crying tears of regret.
Or a vampire who just
wants to be left alone.
But will still save the
life of a human he just met.
I've been around
many vampires lately,
and believe me,
not all of them are bad.
In fact, some of them
are new friends!
I don't really know what kind
of history C3 has with vampires,
or what you're trying to do.
But thinking simply, I want to
keep anyone from getting hurt.
Human or vampire.
[TSUYUKI]
There's someone I know.
His father was
murdered by vampires.
Even after ten years,
the pain hasn't gone away.
No. Never mind.
[KURO]
I don't wanna deal with this.
[MAHIRU]
Kuro!
[TSURUGI]
What should we do? Chase them?
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Yeah, understood.
[YUMIKAGE]
That's it, we're done here.
[TSURUGI] Aw, man,
I really thought we might
earn a bonus tonight.
[JUNICHIRO] Well,
at least none of us got hurt.
We should get some food.
[TSURUGI, YUMIKAGE]
One, two, three, not buying!
[JUNICHIRO] What?
I am not buying you guys dinner.
[MAHIRU]
Thinking in simple terms,
you don't have to have an
excuse to help other people.
But if you hate someone,
if you hurt another person,
you must have a reason.
I want to know.
Why did Tsubaki start this war?
[KURO] Don't act cool when you
can't even control your broom!
[MAHIRU] I thought I was
getting good at this!
[MAHIRU yelling]
[LAWLESS]
Oh Romeo, Romeo,
where for art thou, Romeo?
What odd twist of fate
has brought us together,
Big Brother?
And at a time
like this, no less.
[HUGH] If you need to relax,
you should really try out
a hot spring!
[TETSU]
Thanks for the plug, Hugh.