[MAHIRU] Maybe you need to
have your eyes checked out.
Get close.
Don't you see a little Kuro
rolling around inside?
[MISONO]
There's nothing in there.
Hey, stop tapping,
hot springs guy.
I'm a delicate ball; you should
be handling me with care.
Plus, it's annoying.
[MAHIRU]
Listen, he's talking now!
I don't hear anything. Sorry.
[MISONO]
You may be able to see him,
but to us, this is just
a solid black ball.
At least you can
still talk to him.
[TETSU]
Here's an idea.
We just break the
weird ball so Mister Sloth
is free to lie around and
complain in full size again.
Tetsu! We have to be
super careful about it
We don't know
what this thing is.
[TETSU]
Sure thing.
[MAHIRU]
Kuro, tell us if it hurts.
[KURO yelling]
[MAHIRU]
We haven't done anything yet!
All right, get ready.
[MAHIRU]
No! Tetsu, wait.
This isn't right.
It's not how we should be
going about getting Kuro back.
[TETSU]
Uh, are you sure?
Thanks, Mahiru.
[MAHIRU]
Thinking simply,
this is my responsibility.
I'll get him out.
Just sit back and watch, Kuro!
And here I thought you'd
come to your senses.
[KURO screaming]
[TETSU] Wow, I can't believe you
couldn't break the dang thing.
Uh, yeah. Do you think we're
going about this the wrong way?
Tetsu, you have some
visitors waiting for you
in the lobby.
It's about Licht.
He's gone missing.
[MAHIRU]
I'm so sorry!
I tried to save him,
but couldn't stop them
from kidnapping him.
In fact, he actually
protected me.
[KRANTZ]
They have Lawless, too.
This Tsubaki fellow must be
one immensely strong vampire.
I'm glad to see that you're
still safe, at least.
[MAHIRU]
But I should have done more!
You know, maybe
this is a good thing.
Being held captive may calm
those two down a little bit.
They've been getting far
too out of hand lately.
[MAHIRU]
What? Don't be ridiculous!
[MISONO] We'll figure out a way
to rescue the two of them
before midnight.
We have to.
Their safety is our priority.
We should avoid
conflict if we can.
Is this overgrown mascot
any good in a fight?
Yes, of course.
He's Lawless's subclass.
He can take care of himself.
[MISONO]
First things first.
We need to hide
Lilac from Tsubaki.
I wouldn't be surprised if he
tried to pull one over on us
and make off with our hostage.
[MAHIRU]
Hey, Misono.
We will let Lila go once we get
Lawless and Licht back, right?
That's the deal.
[MISONO] In a perfect world
we could rescue them
without giving up
our own hostage.
That way we could
use Lilac as bait,
or in future negotiations.
[MAHIRU]
That's really underhanded.
We're getting our friends back.
We should hold up our
end of the bargain.
Otherwise, we're the bad guys.
[MISONO groans]
Fine, fine, fine.
You're such a stubborn
bastard sometimes.
[LILAC]
Um... Mahiru.
Thank you. But...
Why are you doing this for me?
Why are you being so nice?
We talked about this.
It's not like I really
wanna fight Tsubaki.
I'd rather solve things
peacefully if we can.
What about you, Krantz?
Are you going to be okay
fighting against vampires
with us?
Oh, yes.
I have the perfect weapon.
Count me in.
[MAHIRU]
It's... a water gun?
--[KRANTZ] May I see your hand?
--I guess so.
See, it's not just
plain water in here.
This is harmless to humans,
but against vampires,
it's quite toxic.
[MAHIRU]
Hugh!
Oh, dear! I had no idea
he was a vampire.
[MAHIRU] Seriously?! He's
dressed like a mini Dracula!
[KRANTZ]
It's just holy water.
I can use it to knock out any
vampires who might attack me.
[HUGH yells]
What the hell
were you thinking?
I won't forget about this!
Oh I do apologize!
I keep this around for times
when Lawless gets unreasonable.
[MAHIRU] I didn't know
stuff like this existed.
Where did you even find it?
There's a traveling
antique dealer who sells
--this kind of thing.
--[MAHIRU] Antique dealer?
Yes. He's a peculiar
little fellow.
You know this guy?
[MAHIRU]
It's got to be him.
I guess I'll stop by his
shop and see what he has.
[MISONO]
That man is bad news.
Why do you--
[MISONO] He just is, all right?
Don't trust him.
But...!
Now, Misono,
it's not like we have much of
a choice at a time like this.
[MAHIRU] Plus, I might
be able to get him
and the Servamp of Envy
to help us out if I'm lucky.
[MISONO] I guess we'll
go our separate ways.
For the time being.
[MAHIRU]
Misono. Tetsu.
You guys be careful, okay?
Ha! You're the one who's
always getting into trouble.
We'll be fine.
This kind of reckless
mission is right up my alley.
[MISONO] What?
This mission is not reckless!
It's gonna be brilliant.
[TETSU] You know what?
I believe you.
I'm sure it'll be great.
[MAHIRU] Again, I'm really
sorry about Licht.
I wish I could've helped.
I was really impressed
by how talented he is
at being the Eve of Greed,
you know.
Licht would hate
to hear you say that.
He doesn't believe in talent.
Let me tell you about him.
Licht grew up in the
countryside of Vienna--
a pretty normal child
who liked climbing trees.
But he was a curious boy.
He chose to play the piano
completely on his own.
Day after day, he sat
at the bench practicing,
imagining a grand audience
weeping in response
to his music.
Then, when he was
seven years old,
there was a big competition.
His parents were both world-
travelling musicians themselves.
This would be the first
time they heard him play.
Licht was ecstatic,
but also nervous.
In fact, his hair
turned completely white
from the anxiety.
[KRANTZ] He was finally going
to make his dream a reality.
In front of his parents,
no less.
But his hair wasn't
the only issue.
His mind went blank
when he sat down.
However, his hard work
didn't betray him.
The audience said that
he played like an angel.
Even now, some of
Licht's hair is white.
It never regained
its original color.
You see, it isn't talent
that accomplishes things.
It's imagination and effort.
So you understand
what I'm saying, right?
You, too, can be a
world-famous pianist!
[MAHIRU] Uh, wait,
was this whole story
some kind of pitch?
[MAHIRU] I hope this
place is easy to find.
[KURO yawns]
I'm so sleepy from
all that sawing earlier.
Time to take a nap.
[MAHIRU]
Hey, Kuro. You awake?
Hello?
[MAHIRU gasps]
A fox?! What the hell?!
[TSUBAKI]
What a tease.
I was hoping I'd catch my
subclass here alone with you.
I know that voice!
[MAHIRU]
Kuro, hide!
[beeping noise]
There wasn't an explosion.
It wasn't real.
But that was Tsubaki. Right?
[KURO]
Hey, what's going on?
That was a really
bouncy wake-up call.
[MAHIRU]
Kuro! You okay?
[KURO yawns]
Yeah, of course I am.
I'm a vampire; I'm immortal.
You should worry about yourself.
You're way too killable.
[MAHIRU] It's hard to take you
seriously when you're so tiny.
But... I'm glad you're okay.
And that you still have
your sense of humor,
despite everything.
[MAHIRU]
Tsubaki's already on the move.
So we should be, too!
[TSUBAKI] Mahiru, the Eve of
Sloth, doesn't have the hostage.
What a pity.
Time to move on.
Now, who's next?
[laughing]
[JOHANN]
Welcome back, Miku-Miku.
I'm afraid I have some
bad news to report to you.
I accidentally broke something
that you treasure today.
I'm so sorry!
But honestly, it's your fault
for putting something
of such value
within my reaching,
knowing me like you do.
Really, it couldn't be helped!
It's not that bad.
Just missing a face.
But don't worry,
I melted the head down
and made it into a special
potion just for you.
Just think! This doll
you love so much
will forever be a part of you.
Doesn't that sound wonderful?
The two of you as one, and
you have me to thank for it.
[JOHANN]
Cheers!
[laughing]
Who are you?
[MAHIRU] This place looks
more like a convenience store
than an antique shop.
[MAHIRU]
So, the reason I'm here...
[JOHANN]
Mikuni isn't in right now.
Mikuni?
Uh... Right, so what
are you doing here?
Are you one of Mikuni's
employees or just a friend?
[JOHANN]
A friend? Of that guy?
I'd rather die.
What about you? Are you
one of Mikuni's servants?
I'm no servant!
I'm just an acquaintance of
his named Mahiru Shirota.
Haruka Satou,
that's a nice name.
[MAHIRU]
What?!
How did you manage
to get every syllable wrong?!
Mahiru Shirota, eh?
Welcome to...
my research laboratory!
Now, have a seat, Kakeru Yamada.
Mahiru Shirota!
[JOHANN] Why don't you let
the good doctor examine you
while you wait?
Have some, uh, tea.
Wait... what is this?
[JOHANN] Just a welcome
drink for the Eve of Sloth!
Cheers, Mitsuru Hanaoka!
Who the hell is that?
[JOHANN sighs] I guess I
should admit I'm not very good
at catching people's names.
There are more important
things to remember.
[MAHIRU] Hey, stop!
What are you doing to me?!
[JOHANN]
There, that should help.
Welcome, Mahiru Shirota!
[laughing]
[MAHIRU]
Uh, so, who are you again?
[JOHANN] I'm part scholar
and part researcher.
Vampires are my specialty.
Huh?
Johannes Mimir Faustus, here.
That's technically my name.
The letters that denote
my individuality.
But you can call me
Doctor, or Hans.
Johannes, Faust, or Mimir.
Whatever you like, really.
--The more important thing--
--[MIKUNI] Johann!
Welcome back, Miku-Miku!
I told you not to come
here without asking!
And where, exactly, did my
dear Violeta's head go, huh?
[MAHIRU]
Uh, hi?
[MIKUNI]
Oh, hi, Mahiru.
Do you have some
business at my store?
Um, well... maybe.
Miku, is it?
[MIKUNI] Oh, that's right,
I never told you my name.
I'm Mikuni Alicein.
Nice to see you.
Thanks so much for looking
out for my little brother.
You're... Misono's big brother?!
That can't be right!
[MISONO] He just is,
all right? Don't trust him.
But why didn't Misono
say anything?
Is there bad blood
between you two?
Enough chit-chat!
I want to touch
this vampire of yours.
He's a cat, right?
The Servamp of Sloth!
So where is he? Where are you
hiding him, this powerful beast?
Don't be shy, bring him on out!
No way!
[MAHIRU] I'm trying to find a
way to get him back to normal.
[JOHANN] Ah, a problem
in need of examination!
Cheers to the unexpected!
Oh, if only we could
freeze in this moment.
It's just so beautiful,
I think that I might cry.
[JOHANN] Thank you for
bringing this oddity!
Now, into my laboratory!
[MAHIRU]
Ow...
What? I didn't break
the glass or anything.
Must be some kinda
revolving door.
Man, that's weird.
[JOHANN] It's time for
some fun experiments
with the good doctor.
Are you excited?
[MISONO] I had Doudou
examine this photo we found
on Higan's phone.
He thinks he's
traced its origin.
[DOUDOU]
There's no mistake about it.
It's definitely the Tokyo
Opera Hall in the background.
Got it?
There's only one place where
that could have been taken,
considering the angle
in the picture.
[MISONO]
They're in one of the top floors
of the Tokyo World Tree Hotel.
That's their base.
[TETSU]
Nice!
[MISONO]
The hotel has 45 floors,
plus five more underground.
Taking advantage
of that much height,
an Eve and a Servamp
could be separated
beyond their distance limit.
I see.
[KRANTZ]
Okay.
So Licht and Lawless
should be on the top
and bottom floors of the hotel.
Tsubaki's guarding them,
and he has help.
Higan, his strongest subclass,
is probably also keeping
an eye on those two.
He's dangerous.
[TETSU] You know,
you're really good at this.
You shouldn't be so
impressed by common sense.
After analyzing the facts,
this seems like the
most likely setup.
[TETSU]
All right.
I'm gonna get some rest, then.
[MISONO]
You're leaving it to us?
[TETSU] Just tell me
what you want me to do
once you figure it out.
Don't worry, I'm good
at this kinda thing.
[HUGH] Yes, it's a smart idea
to recover as much stamina
as possible before we begin.
Idiots. Don't you want a say?
Your lives are gonna be
on the line too, you know.
Don't you care?
I do.
But I also trust that
you'll do what's best.
Well, after a vote
of confidence like that,
we'd better make a good plan.
Like I wouldn't
do that to begin with.
The first thing we need
to do is to scout the hotel
from the inside.
But that could be a problem.
The subclasses definitely
know our faces by now.
You're right.
We need someone who can
slip past them unrecognized.
[JOHANN]
165.2 centimeters.
You're kinda short, you know.
What's the point of all
these measurements, huh?
Quiet down.
--I'll need some hair.
--[MAHIRU] Ouch!
[JOHANN]
Any history of chronic illness?
[MAHIRU]
I'm fine!
Kuro's the one you're supposed
to be looking at, not me.
I want--
What do you plan
to do if you manage
to get Sloth back to normal?
Are you going
to go after Tsubaki?
Do you have some kind
of plan to stop him?
You are aware that
vampires are immortal.
But do you really know
how to break them?
Break them?
What are you talking about?
Wait, I get it.
Are you saying you know
a way to kill vampires?
You're horribly uninformed.
As an Eve, you should really
know how these things work.
Vampires are essentially
immortal, true.
But subclasses can be broken if
a Servamp drinks their blood.
You could call it
a form of cannibalism.
There's also a way
to break a Servamp.
Using their name and their item,
the two things that connect
an Eve and a Servamp together.
You gave Sloth
an object and a name
to make a contract,
and that's his weakness.
Huh? No, I didn't
give him anything.
Crap! Yeah, I did!
His little cat bell!
I didn't think anything of it!
[MIKUNI] Servamps are sins,
and Eves their salvation.
In order to break
their connection,
you must destroy the item
an Eve gave to his Servamp.
Do that, and the
Servamp... well...
[MAHIRU]
This is good to know,
but all I want to do right now
is get Kuro back to normal.
[JOHANN] There's no known
method for doing so.
Servamps cause all sorts
of unexplained phenomena.
But I never thought
I'd get to witness
something like this up close.
Tell me, Doctor,
you're not an Eve
or a subclass, right?
So why do you research vampires?
Maybe I just enjoy
a good challenge.
I'm on a boat, rowing
against the current.
Always fighting to get upstream.
If you truly want knowledge,
you have to seek it out with
every ounce of your will.
Stop to rest and
you'll fall behind.
Humans have no time
to catch their breath.
There's only one way to get
whatever you yearn for.
Nothing begins without action.
If you do nothing, then
you're sure to gain nothing!
Satisfaction is stagnation,
which is death.
I want to know, see, and feel.
To experience and understand!
To learn everything!
This monster is amazing,
but we know next to
nothing about him!
He has such incredible strength.
He's won every battle
he's ever fought!
The ultimate soldier!
And now there's a
war between vampires?
Perhaps I should thank
the Servamp of Melancholy
for allowing me to see
something so fascinating.
In every era, wars have
forced us towards progress.
I want Sloth to revert back
so he can use his powers
to do just that.
Sure, but... it's not
that I want his power.
I want to learn from Kuro and
become the kind of person
who can face him as an equal.
[JOHANN] I have no interest in
such sentimental motivations.
Here, have some tea.
Thank you.
I don't know any
foolproof way
of getting him out of there.
But there is a radical solution
that I think's is worth trying.
[MAHIRU gasps]
[JOHANN] Of course, what I'm
proposing is a human Eve
entering the mind of
a Servamp and interacting
with him directly.
Taking unnecessary
risks as usual, I see.
[MAHIRU]
What... did I just drink?
[JOHANN] Luckily,
I've already concocted a way
to get into a Servamp's mind.
[laughs]
I can't believe I'm
getting to test it on
the eldest brother, Sloth!
Good luck to you,
Mahiru Shirota.
How about a poem as you depart?
[MIKUNI]
The Cat and the Unicorn
were fighting without the crown.
The Cat beat the Unicorn.
All about the town.
Some gave them no flower,
and sent them out of town.
They've hidden
my poor subclass.
[SHAMROCK]
Who are you talking about?
Their hostage.
I watched Lust and Pride
and couldn't find
a sign of him anywhere.
[phone ringing]
Well, it is about time
they called me back!
[TSUBAKI]
Ah, yes, hello?
Uh-huh, it's me. Oh?
That's it.
They've called for me.
I'm off now.
[SHAMROCK] It must be
a trap, young master.
Don't trust them!
We should be the
ones to go instead.
[TSUBAKI] It's not that I don't
have faith in all of you.
Quite the opposite.
I'm going because I know you
can hold down the fort here.
Surely you understand
how much I believe in you.
No matter who
deceives me in life,
I will never betray any of you.
[SUBCLASS 8A]
He's outside!
I've got a visual; he's out!
That's excellent news.
[SUBCLASS 8A] He left
the roof and heading west.
I'm sending a photo now.
Right. That means it's
time for us to move.
[LILLY]
Um, Misono?
Is this some kind
of cosplay, or...?
They're disguises!
Disguises are a must during
infiltration missions.
I've increased my height
by 15 centimeters.
No one will recognize me!
[laughs]
[LILLY] That's wonderful,
but don't trip, please.
[KRANTZ]
Excuse me.
Are there any rooms available
on your highest floor here?
Let me check for you.
Just one moment please!
[KRANTZ]
Arigato! Tokyo is amazin'!
Shibuya, Harajuku, let's see...
[MISONO] He's kind of overdoing
it with this tourist bit.
[DESK CLERK 8A]
I am very sorry, sir,
but we currently have
long-term guests
occupying floors 43 and above.
[KRANTZ] I asked about
the basement, too.
Seems they only use the
first four floors for parking.
The fifth must be where
they're keeping him.
I guess that would
make the most sense.
Bastards.
[KRANTZ] I got a room
on the 41st floor.
This cardkey will let
you take the elevator
above the 40th floor.
Take it.
You stay here
and be on the lookout
for anything suspicious
in the lobby.
Okay, Sendagaya.
I'll take the elevator
as we discussed.
Stand by for my signal.
[TETSU]
Got it.
[MISONO]
Our goal isn't to defeat him.
If we can rescue them and escape
before Tsubaki comes back,
then we'll be successful.
[MISONO]
Sakuya Watanuki?
Does he know?
Or is he just in the elevator
going back to home base?
Oh, did you think
we were going up?
I hate being a liar.
But I don't have
much of a choice.
The words "I believe
in you" are a burden.
No... They're some
kind of spell.
And once you hear them,
you're cursed.
You have to be loyal
to whoever said them.
You thought you pushed
the button for the 41st floor.
But shouldn't that button
be towards the top?
So why did you hit
the one so far down?
You should check again.
[MISONO]
Whoa! The button order flipped!
[SAKUYA]
You look confused.
This is why I hate lying.
I really wish...
I didn't have to lie again!
[JOHANN]
Let me borrow this doll.
I promise I won't hurt her.
[MIKUNI]
Don't touch my Abel, pervert!
Get away!