[KURO]
Help... Help...
I'm drowning... I'm drowning...
What should we do, Kuro?
We're being overwhelmed
by Mahiru's emotions.
Fear. Regret. Rejection.
If Mahiru hadn't taken you home,
he would never have felt
these things so strongly.
Wherever you go, you always
bring misfortune with you.
What a pain.
Kuro! Ah...
What are you...?
[retching]
[MAHIRU]
Kuro?
[OTOGIRI]
This is unexpected.
A surprise. That's a problem.
What should we do now, Tsubaki?
I guess he changed his mind.
That's a problem.
[growling]
Kuro, what the hell
is going on?!
What is that thing?!
[MAHIRU] This is bad.
I feel like... I'm drowning.
[SAKUYA]
Mahiru!
Here!
[MAHIRU]
Sakuya!
[OTOGIRI, BERUKIA]
Bad form.
You're trying to
save your enemy.
And that's a problem.
Shut up! C'mon, Mahiru.
You have to order your
Servamp to kill me now!
It's what I wanted!
It's the reason I lied
to you and brought you here!
[MAHIRU]
Kuro?
[MIKUNI]
Go on, Jeje. Get on with it.
[SAKUYA]
Who's that?
[OTOGIRI] Looks like we're
outnumbered. That's a problem.
Time to go home.
Yeah, okay.
Thanks for saving me,
but you could've been gentler.
Sakuya!
So you don't really
want to kill me?
It was a trick?
[MAHIRU]
Where'd he go?
What the crap?!
Is the arrogant brat dead?
Hi, Doudou.
Misono's... injured.
[LILLY]
Thank goodness you're here.
He needs a doctor.
Misono?
Are you okay, Mahiru?
Yeah, I'm fine;
just take care of him.
Don't worry 'bout me.
He's hurt. And it's my fault.
[MIKUNI] There's no reason
for you to feel responsible
for what happened.
I'll say one thing:
you have excellent timing.
Well, you-know-who
contacted me,
so I knew exactly where to go.
Of course. I see.
[MIKUNI] A person must
take full responsibility
for their own actions.
No matter what.
I'm sure Misono knew exactly
what he was getting into
whenever he chose
to get involved.
Nice to meet you, young man.
Beside me is the
Servamp of Envy.
His name's Doubt Doubt.
You might've guessed--
I'm his Eve.
Just a simple antique dealer
traveling across the world.
Won't you please
hold me, Mahiru?
Uh, wait, how do you
know my name?
Huh? No, don't be afraid, Abel.
It's all right.
This young man is not our enemy.
You're safe.
Huh? You think children
nowadays are too violent?
[laughs]
Don't worry so much,
Abel, my darling.
[MAHIRU] Why is everyone
I meet a weirdo?
[MIKUNI]
What's with that look?!
Don't stare at her with
such lust in your eyes.
Pervert! She'd just a doll!
What are you talking about?!
Whoa!
[JEJE]
Enough talk.
Time for you to
keep your promise.
[MIKUNI]
Huh? And what was that?
[JEJE] You promised that
if I followed your orders,
you'd let me drink your blood.
Huh? Sorry, I can't hear you!
[MIKUNI laughs]
Jeje, stop,
you're being mean!
Sorry we had to take
him down so brutally.
I wish we could have
destroyed Tsubaki's subclass
before he managed to escape.
You heard him;
that's what he wanted.
Well, at least now you know
you don't have the stomach
for something like that.
Though, you did come close.
I imagine it would
be pretty traumatizing
to kill your best friend,
even if he was asking you to.
Y'know, Mahiru...
I can teach you how to
nullify a Servamp contract
if you're interested.
You can?
I mean, it's none
of my business, I know.
But I figured you might be
regretting your choices.
You never thought things
would turn out this way, right?
Contracts like this
can be scary.
If you lose control and
start to fear your power,
then your Servamp won't
hesitate to gobble you up whole.
So just let me know
if you're interested.
I can help you go back to
being a normal student.
[MAHIRU]
Wait!
Just who are you?
What were you even doing here?
I thought I told you.
I'm just a traveling
antique dealer!
Isn't that right, Abel?
[laughing]
Mahiru.
Shouldn't you be getting
ready for school?
[MAHIRU]
How are your injuries doing?
I'm all healed up now.
I am a vampire, after all.
[MAHIRU]
Yup.
You are, in fact, a vampire.
Do you regret taking me in?
Is that what this is all about?
[MAHIRU]
Shut up.
[KURO]
Of course you do.
[MAHIRU]
I don't regret taking you in.
I just don't know what
I'm supposed to do now.
What's the point of this power?
I thought that if I had it,
I could help others.
But so far, it seems like the
only thing I've managed to do
is hurt people.
[LITTLE GIRL 4A]
That was really yummy!
[MOM 4A]
C'mon, dear.
[WORKER 3A]
Have a seat!
Who do we have here?
What an unexpected surprise.
Do you come here often?
Big sushi fan?
Don't look so glum.
Here, can I interest you
in a little salmon roe?
It's eggcellent.
[laughing]
[sighs]
Not interesting at all.
Sakuya... How did he
become your subclass?
Poor boy.
You really are clueless,
aren't you?
But if you want to know,
I'll tell you the whole
boring story, I guess.
[TSUBAKI]
Sakuya was the child of liars--
born into a town of liars.
The first person to tell
him a lie was none other
than his big sister.
Sakuya...
Father's coming home tonight,
so do me a favor, okay?
Promise me that
whatever happens,
you won't come out of your room.
[SAKUYA]
What about you, Sis?
[SAKUYA'S SISTER] Don't worry
about me. I'll be fine.
Everything will work out.
[SAKUYA'S SISTER]
How much do you get if I die?
Enough?
Make sure Sakuya's okay.
[SAKUYA'S FATHER] Sure thing.
I'll look out for him.
[SAKUYA gasps]
[TSUBAKI] Sakuya's father told
him to tell the police
that his sister
fell off the balcony
while they were playing around.
That it was all just
a tragic accident.
He said that if he didn't
go along with the story,
the same thing
would happen to him.
"You don't want
your sister's death
to have been in vain,
right?" he asked.
And so Sakuya lied
for the very first time.
And his family received a
huge life insurance payout.
The neighbors all knew
something bad was going on
in Sakuya's home,
but no one said anything.
They didn't want
to get involved.
They lied.
In a way, they helped
cover up his sister's death.
It was really no
surprise to anyone
when 6 years later,
Sakuya found himself doomed
to follow the same
path as his sister.
I've come to help.
[TSUBAKI] Here's something
you may not know.
Subclasses are created
when a dying human
drinks a Servamp's blood.
And subclasses have to obey
the Servamps who made them.
They make such good servants.
[laughs]
I can tell by the
look on your face
you didn't know any of this.
Some best friend you are.
[laughing]
[TSUBAKI sighs]
Not interesting at all.
Check please, sir!
[TSUBAKI] I'll leave before Big
Brother gets scary again.
He's in your backpack, right?
I could feel his murderous
aura from here.
Unfortunately, I just don't
much feel like playing today.
Ta-ta.
[MAHIRU]
Tsubaki, wait!
Where's Sakuya?
You have to... give him back.
Why can't I move?
It's my fault.
If only I'd tried to
understand Sakuya better,
I should have been
honest with him.
I was just trying to
keep him out of all this.
That's why I lied.
[TORU]
So you got into a fight?
Go on. You can choose whatever
you want off the belt.
[MAHIRU]
You aren't mad at me?
[TORU]
You know, Mahiru,
being a good friend to someone
is actually pretty simple.
You just need
the resolve to say,
"I am your friend
no matter what."
And, "I believe in you."
"I care."
That's all.
[TORU]
It's okay to make mistakes.
I've made plenty of them.
But you shouldn't
have any regrets.
You also have to learn
what's good for you
isn't always good for others.
People are different.
It's just the way it is.
But we can still lean on
each other in times of need.
That's what makes humanity work.
We get through life together.
We look out for one another.
[MAHIRU]
I'm sorry, Sakuya.
After all that time together,
now I can hardly remember
what your smile looked like.
[MAHIRU]
Yeah. I understand.
You don't need
to apologize, Uncle.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Talk to you later.
[SAKUYA] S'up, Mahiru!
Was that your uncle?
Is he not coming to the
parent-teacher meeting?
[MAHIRU]
No.
[SAKUYA] Well, I just told the
teacher that I'd be coming alone
because I don't
have any parents.
My grades are awesome, so it's
kind of a waste of time anyways.
I'd rather be hanging
out or something.
[MAHIRU]
Sure, you would.
[SAKUYA]
Aw, don't look so sad!
Wait, I've got a brilliant idea.
Why don't we have our meeting
with the teacher together?
[MAHIRU]
I don't think they'll let us.
[SAKUYA] Ha. You do realize none
of this really matters, right?
Come on, let's see
a smile, Mahiru!
Cheer up.
I'm here for you.
--[MAHIRU yells]
--[TSUYUKI] Ouch.
Ah! Ow... Sorry 'bout that.
Are you okay?
[TSUYUKI]
Yeah, I'm perfectly fine.
Most potential problems
are easily avoided
if you're always prepared.
[KOYUKI]
Oh! Mahiru's here.
[RYUSEI]
Thank goodness!
We were wondering what
we'd do if you weren't here
to help with the festival.
Where's Sakuya?
[KOYUKI]
Hm? Sakuya?
[MAHIRU]
No way.
Are everyone's
memories gone now?
Don't you remember him?
Huh? Of course. How could
we forget a dude like that?
But Sakuya transferred
schools. Last week.
[KOYUKI] It's too bad he had to
leave right before the festival.
He was so excited about it.
But now he'll miss it.
[BOY STUDENT 4A] I dunno,
maybe he'll show up anyway.
I'll text him after school.
[MAHIRU]
He left his name behind.
Part of their memories.
But why?
[RYUSEI] It's, uh... kinda weird
thinking about Sakuya.
For me, at least.
It's like there's
a blank space.
I mean, I can remember
what he was like.
But I just can't
picture his face.
There's just nothing there
when I try to remember.
[MAHIRU]
Sakuya, is this what you wanted?
You're a coward.
[RYUSEI] Do you think
I'll recognize him
if he shows tomorrow?
Don't worry. I definitely will.
[LILLY]
Misono.
Looks like Mahiru texted you.
He says he wants
to come and visit.
[MISONO]
Tell him I'm dead.
[LILLY] How about I send him a
map to the hospital instead, hm?
--[laughing]
--[MISONO] You bastard! Ugh!
You're my Servamp, Lilly.
You can't just ignore my orders!
And since when do you
know how to work my phone?
[MISONO]
My injuries weren't that bad.
Tell him I'll get
back to him later.
[LILLY]
Consider it done.
[MISONO]
I made such a big entrance.
But I couldn't
protect my friend.
How am I supposed
to face him now?
[MISONO] Lilly, I...
I want to become stronger.
[KOYUKI]
Hi everyone!
We're with class 1-6!
Please stop by our café,
and I guarantee that
you'll have a good time!
[SAKUYA]
Ow! What the heck?
[MAHIRU]
Sakuya!
[MAHIRU] Come back here!
We gotta talk!
Talk?!
What? Are you out
of your damn mind?
I tried to kill you.
And your friend, too.
Did you forget?
You are such a liar!
You reached your hand out to me!
You were trying to save my life!
Plus, I heard that Misono's
injuries weren't that bad!
But you should still
apologize to him!
[SAKUYA]
Like hell I will!
Listen.
I'm your enemy now, Mahiru.
[MAHIRU]
No, you're not!
You're my friend.
[SAKUYA]
How can you still say that?
We were never really
childhood friends!
Those are just fake
memories I gave you!
[SAKUYA] We've only known
each other for one year.
That's all.
And I was lying to you
the whole time.
Right to your face.
Don't you get it?
Even if that is the truth,
it was a fun year!
Just come back!
[SAKUYA]
No. I can't be with you.
Not anymore.
I am not human.
I'm different from
everyone else at school.
So... different.
[yell]
Fly!
I don't care if you're a
human or a vampire, okay?
This may all be new to me.
But I've still got the power to
grab your outstretched hand.
[BOTH yelling]
[SAKUYA]
So, the weapon lets you fly.
That's cool.
[MAHIRU]
This was kinda my first try.
But I figured, a black cat
and a broom, right?
It seemed pretty obvious.
It had to work.
Seriously, Mahiru?
[chuckles]
You're a mess.
[laughing]
[crying]
[SAKUYA] I... wanted more
chances to laugh like this.
But I think this is it,
you know?
When I met Tsubaki,
I was in such a bad place.
I lied to them.
And that means
I helped kill my sister.
If only I'd been the
one who died instead.
[TSUBAKI] You did
absolutely nothing wrong.
Don't think that way;
it's not your fault.
[TSUBAKI] You've been
through so much pain.
[SAKUYA crying]
[TSUBAKI]
It's all right.
When this is all over,
I promise I'll be there
to lend a hand.
[SAKUYA]
He didn't lie to me.
He kept his word.
I have come to help.
[SAKUYA]
Tsubaki was the only one.
He reached out his hand to me.
Tsubaki saved me.
[MAHIRU] It's almost like...
they're the same.
[SAKUYA]
I can't betray him.
If he tells me to kill,
then I'll just have to--
[MAHIRU]
No!
I'll stop Tsubaki.
Thinking simply...
Kuro and I are the only ones
who can take him down.
You don't just have
Tsubaki right now, Sakuya.
You've got me and
everyone else, too!
You aren't alone!
I'm here for you.
[SAKUYA] Mahiru, please
don't lie to me anymore.
[MAHIRU]
I won't!
[SAKUYA] I really do
want to believe you.
Thank you.
What you've said--
I needed that.
But I still can't
be with you right now.
I hope you understand.
I'll fix this!
[MAHIRU]
Kuro...
I want to stop Tsubaki.
This time, I'm serious.
To do that, well,
you're gonna have to
help me get stronger.
[KURO]
You're such a pain.
[SAKUYA]
I'm a child of liars
who was born in
a town of liars.
This is my truth.
A year ago,
I snuck into a
random middle school.
Just to kill a little time.
But when I saw that simple,
outstretched hand,
something happened.
I thought, "Hey, I want
to get to know this guy."
Mahiru.
Thanks for finding me that day.
Thanks for reaching out
your hand to me, my friend.
[SAKUYA] Now, I wonder how
much of the next episode
is a lie, hmm?
[TSUBAKI]
Not interesting at all.