[gasps]
How did I get in my room?
Was all that a bad dream?
Hey, put me down, will ya?
I am having the best dream
adventure and finally found it.
My prize... ultimate pillow.
So soft!
That sounds like the
dumbest adventure.
Wait, if you're talking,
then it wasn't a dream.
[MAHIRU panting]
Ryusei!
Oh. Hey, Mahiru.
Sakuya! Is Ryusei okay?
No.
[MAHIRU gasps]
[RYUSEI]
Look alive!
[RYUSEI] That's the kinda
tape you needed, right?
[MAHIRU]
Ryusei!
Huh?
Hey. So you decided
to come after all.
Why'd you scare me
like that, Sakuya?
[SAKUYA] It was a joke;
you seemed so serious!
I thought I'd play along
and maybe make something up.
[yells]
Anyway, how's your
neck doing, Ryusei?
--Does it hurt much?
--Eh. It's not that bad.
I was lucky the car
barely hit me.
The accident could've
been a lot worse.
A car accident?
[KOYUKI]
But still, it was pretty scary.
What are you guys talking about?
That's not what happened!
[KOYUKI] Huh? Some kind of
vampire street performer?
You sound like Sakuya.
Are you gonna start telling
stories all the time, too?
It's not like you were even
out there with us yesterday
to see how things went down.
We don't have time
to play around.
There's still a ton of stuff
to do for the school festival.
[MAHIRU]
Something's wrong.
They don't remember
I was with them,
or that we were attacked.
It's like their minds
have been wiped.
But that wouldn't explain
their new memories.
Ugh! This just
doesn't make any sense!
[KURO]
Hey!
[BERUKIA] I keep getting
cat hair in my mouth!
What the hell?
When'd you get in here?
I am so very hungry!
Please just let me have
a little bit of blood!
Pretty please!
Keep it down and
tell me why everyone
is being so weird.
It's like yesterday
didn't even happen!
[GIRL 2A]
What's with that boy?
[GIRL 2B]
Is he yelling at a doll?
[BERUKIA]
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
What are you doing,
you stupid little brat?
I hope Tsubaki murders you soon!
[MAHIRU] Who is this Tsubaki
guy he keeps talking about?
You're sure that name
doesn't ring a bell?
[KURO] No, and I can't
imagine who'd want to hurt
a cute, loveable cat
like yours truly.
Stop pretending you're
some kinda harmless kitten
and not a vampire.
[KURO]
Meow.
[MAHIRU] Let's think
about it in simple terms.
This Tsubaki person
is obviously our enemy.
If we don't do
something about him,
he might send more vampires
to attack you... and me.
[MAHIRU] Huh?
Sunshine while it's raining?
[MAHIRU]
What is this?!
[TSUBAKI]
Hey, you.
Why don't you tell me a story?
Something good.
I want to know about
the most interesting thing
that's happened to you.
[BERUKIA] Tell him how your kitty
turned out to be a vampire!
Or maybe how you used
him to try and murder
a brilliant street magician
who was just putting on
a good show!
I have a feeling this
is gonna be a real pain.
Wait--So is he...
a vampire, too?
[TSUBAKI laughing]
I'm already bored.
What, are you
trying to hide, now?
Wait--Do you know
this guy or something?
Not a clue.
But he's got a real
crazy look in his eyes.
[TSUBAKI]
Wonderful.
I've been looking
for this fiend.
Thanks for picking
him up for me.
Ugh, it was so cramped in there.
You're very late,
my precious Tsu-Tsu.
Precious... Tsu-Tsu?
[BERUKIA]
But you did come for me.
I'll forgive you, Tsu-Tsu.
[MAHIRU]
Tsubaki... It must be him!
That was fast. Why's he here?
This might not be the
best time to ask questions.
We should get out
of here while we can.
[TSUBAKI] Yes.
I am the one called Tsubaki.
So what?
I'm the one who's chosen to
challenge the both of you.
So what?
And I'm also the one
who wants to massacre
lots and lots of
vampires and humans.
So what?
I'm feeling a bit bored
and depressed today.
You know what would help,
Sleepy Ash of Sloth?
You could tell me a
really interesting story.
If you don't,
I'll have no choice--
we'll just have to go to war.
Huh? What are you
even talking about?
[TSUBAKI]
Come on, big brother.
Wait, what?
You're Kuro's... little brother?
No, he must be off his rocker.
I've never met him before.
[TSUBAKI laughing]
Terrible! Heartbreaking!
So you don't know
who I am, either?
None of my Servamp
siblings know I existed!
Can you imagine?
[laughing]
Say...
Do you know how many
Servamps there are, kid?
There's seven of us.
Sure. It's seven.
Sleepy Ash of Sloth.
Old Child of Pride.
Doubt Doubt of Envy.
The Mother of Wrath.
Lawless of Greed.
World End of Gluttony.
And of course,
All of Love of Lust.
You might think that these seven
are the only true
vampires in the world.
But there's actually
one more in the family.
I'm the Servamp of Melancholy.
The eighth true
vampire in our line.
My nickname is "Who is Coming."
And I'm the youngest
of the Servamps.
Kuro, you have so many siblings.
Is it 'cause you're a cat?
No. And besides, I'm the
only cat of the litter.
[TSUBAKI chuckles]
[TSUBAKI]
He's right.
This is what I
can transform into.
Hey, get off me if you're
gonna chase each other!
So, you're a dog, huh?
Don't insult me
by calling me that.
My form is a fox.
[TSUBAKI laughing]
Not interesting at all.
Tsu-Tsu.
These two idiots kept me from
murdering all those people
like you ordered me to.
They ruined everything.
Tsubaki.
Why do you want to
kill so many people?
Oh, you want a motive?
Maybe it's just that I'm
not so fond of humans.
You understand, right?
You attacked this vampire
because you didn't like him.
It's the same thing.
Tell me...
Do you know how many people
died in this town yesterday?
No idea, right?
Then does it really matter
how many of them we killed?
Does it make a difference?
No, I think not.
Are you crazy?!
Of course it matters!
Why hurt innocent people
when they haven't
done anything to you?!
[TSUBAKI]
That's just it.
They'd all be much
more interesting
if they could only realize
they're an integral part
of my big plans for the future.
Especially you...
...my dear brother,
little Sleepy Ash.
[TSUBAKI]
Hey, don't just lie there.
Now that we're together,
why don't we play?
[TSUBAKI] All of you
have forgotten about me.
No... you want to forget.
I won't let you.
I want us to reunite
in a great big party.
Why don't you call the
rest of our siblings here
for me, brother?
My teacher would be
so happy if we could all
gather together in one place.
Then I could make this
world--regret everything--
its entire worthless existence!
[MAHIRU]
Kuro! Drink my blood!
[KURO]
No thanks.
I'm still really
sore from yesterday.
[MAHIRU]
You're so lazy!
[KURO coughs]
Don't!
[MAHIRU]
I don't get it.
You want to start a war? Why?
Kuro!
[TSUBAKI]
Because it would be interesting.
I don't really care
who lives or dies.
The only thing
that matters to me
is that it's
entertaining to witness.
[MAHIRU]
What's with this guy?
He's talking crazy!
He's completely out of his mind!
[TSUBAKI] A kid like you
has no idea how I feel.
Not just you, nobody gets me.
No one in the world truly
understands how I yearn.
[MAHIRU]
This... sounds kind of familiar.
Back then...
[MAHIRU]
Mom.
[TORU]
You sure you're ready?
You can take a few
more days off, y'know.
No, I'm okay, Uncle. I'll go.
It'll be fine.
Mahiru? How are you feeling?
You know you can talk
to me about anything, right?
--[MAHIRU] Koyuki.
--Hey!
Let's go play some soccer!
I've been working on some
cool new moves for us.
[MAHIRU]
Ryusei.
Thanks, you guys. Really.
But I'm gonna head home now.
I've got stuff to do.
Huh?
What?
[RYUSEI]
Well, let's play tomorrow, then!
[TORU]
Mahiru?
Come here, kid.
What's the matter?
Did something bad
happen at school today?
[MAHIRU]
No. Nothing.
Everyone was super nice.
They asked me to play with them.
But... I just didn't feel
like doing anything.
I don't know why.
I want you to think about
what you're feeling right now.
If you can't understand
your own emotions,
you'll never be able
to connect with others
who are trying to reach
out and be there for you.
Try giving a name
to whatever it is
that's in your heart right now.
Even if it's sadness,
you have to feel that emotion.
That's the only way
you'll overcome it
and be able to
let other others in.
You'll never be able
to face anyone else
until you face yourself.
And you have to be honest
to understand that.
Nothing's interesting
to you because you aren't
facing your feelings honestly.
It's no wonder you're so bored.
You feel like no one
understands you,
but you don't even
understand yourself.
So how is anyone else supposed
to care about what you want?
[TSUBAKI]
Huh?
[laughing]
[TSUBAKI]
Maybe you're right.
But that just makes me want
to start a war even more!
Fighting is a method
of communication.
Look at it that way.
No! You're wrong!
I won't let you do this.
I'll stop you before
you can kill anyone else.
I'll use everything
I've learned about Servamps
in the last day.
If I name you and
make you drink my blood,
then you'll have
to obey me, right?
That's how it works.
So I challenge you
to face me head on!
But first I'll give
you a new name.
Really?
But what if someone murders you
before you're able to do that?
Mahiru! Watch out!
[TSUBAKI]
Where'd they disappear to?
And just when things
were getting good.
[BERUKIA] Are you just gonna
let them get away like that,
Tsu-Tsu?
[TSUBAKI] Don't worry.
We'll have plenty of fun
with them later.
I already have a name,
right, Teacher? Tsubaki.
[TSUBAKI]
They're not interesting at all.
Gah! What happened?
And where are we?
[sighs]
Somebody must've saved us.
Probably another Servamp.
[MAHIRU]
One of your siblings? Really?
Yeah, if I had to guess.
[YULEE, MARIE]
Mahiru Shirota.
Please follow us.
All of Love is summoning
you now--Come!
--Who, me?
--[YULEE, MARIE] Please.
[KURO] What a drag.
I think I'll sit this one out.
[MISONO] I know it's out
of the ordinary,
but I must insist
you come with me.
And I won't accept any
answer other than "yes."
--[YULEE] Kitty.
--[MARIE] Kitty.
[MAHIRU] So are you the one
that they call All of Love?
[MISONO]
I'm not.
My name is Misono Alicein.
[MAHIRU]
Misono Alicein?
I'm the Eve for All of Love.
The seventh Servamp.
[MAHIRU]
Eve?
[MISONO] That's a master
who's contracted a Servamp.
Oh, so we're the same.
I'm an Eve, too!
[MAHIRU]
Huh. I wonder who his Eve is.
[MISONO]
That's my place ahead.
[MAHIRU] Holy crap!
This place is gigantic.
[MISONO sighs]
I'm tired. Let's rest a bit.
[MAHIRU] It's only been 5
minutes since we got out
of the car and you
have to sit?!
And where did that
chair even come from?!
[LILLY laughing]
Unfortunately,
Misono has something
of a weak constitution,
my dear Mahiru.
What are you looking at?
Gah! Lilly, I keep telling
you not to land in my hair!
[MAHIRU]
A butterfly?
Nice to meet you.
Please let me know if there's
anything that you desire.
Put your clothes back on!
What? I was just trying to
make a good first impression.
Allow me to introduce this
stripping perv, All of Love.
The Servamp of Lust.
My Eve has given me
the name of Snowlily.
But please, feel free to
call me whatever you'd like.
Stop that!
[KURO] You haven't changed
at all, have you?
It's very nice to
see you, too, brother.
Now please, come inside.
[MAHIRU]
Get off of me.
[LILLY] I am the one who helped
you out behind the scenes
with that horrible
magician business.
[MAHIRU] He's the one
that made everyone forget.
Oh, thank you!
It's nice to meet
someone on our side.
There are so many things
I want to ask you guys.
[LILLY] Before we get
to your questions,
there's something
we have to ask you.
I didn't help you out just
because I was feeling kind,
unfortunately.
Here, Lilly.
[MISONO]
Mahiru, you bastard.
I hear you didn't launch
a single attack
when you faced Tsubaki today.
Misono...
You know about Tsubaki, t--
[MISONO] You haven't earned
the right to say my name.
How pathetic.
You don't understand
what it means
to be a Servamp's master at all.
Mahiru Shirota.
You must become my servant.
I'll give the orders now.
And you'll tell Sloth
what I want him to do.
I'm afraid you don't
have a choice.
You must say "yes."
I really would like
to resolve this peacefully
if it's at all possible.
You'll be a good boy and
play along nicely, now,
won't you?
Things are turning
into a mess again.
You can't just
order us around!
I only came here
to get some answers!
You're not very quick
on the uptake, are you?
Ugh, This is why I hate
working with commoners.
What?
Look, you're obviously rich,
but do you really have to act
like such an
arrogant jerk to us?
How do you expect me to
trust you after you showed up
outta nowhere and
demanded that we obey you?
Peasant! How dare you
talk to me that way?
[MAHIRU]
That's it, Kuro, we're leaving!
[MAHIRU] And here I thought we'd
found an ally in this fight.
Dammit.
[MISONO sighs]
Idiot.
Well, Misono.
What shall we do now?
[MAHIRU] Man. This place
is like one big maze.
[KURO] Yeah, this definitely
isn't the way out.
[whispering]
[MAHIRU]
Who are they?
[MAHIRU] Children?
And why are there so many?
They can't all be
Lilly's kids, can they?
I know he's Lust,
but that is nuts!
No, no--Certainly not.
All those cute kiddos
are just my subclass.
Your subclass?
[LILLY] Subclasses are
lower-level vampires
that have been
created by a Servamp.
Our servants.
They follow the orders of
the vampire who created them.
[MAHIRU] So those kids
are vampires, too.
[LILLY] Tsubaki's minions have
started killing subclasses
like these children.
They seem to be
his first targets.
We know of two who were
murdered this week alone.
Possibly more.
[MISONO] Do you know how
to play chess, Mahiru?
[MAHIRU]
I guess. Why?
[MISONO]
As the game goes on,
the number of pieces on the
board gets smaller and smaller.
But as long as your
king survives, you win.
It's unfair.
And it's not how battles should
be fought in the real world,
either, understand?
I don't want to hide on some
throne and be protected.
That's why I need all the
power I can get on my side.
I need so much more
than I have--[grunts]
Tell me, what do you plan
on doing with your strength?
There's a single Eve for every
Servamp, and you're one of them.
So what's driving you?
Can you use Sloth's powers
to achieve your goals?
No way!
He just attacked my friend!
[YULEE, MARIE]
Mahiru Shirota.
You'll help this lonesome
king, won't you? Please?
[MAHIRU]
You know... I get it.
Simply speaking, you're just
trying to protect people.
I don't think you have
to do all this alone.
Wouldn't it help if
others were by your side?
You need allies.
Misono...
Kuro and I will help you.
Only not as your servants,
but as your friends.
Hey, don't drag me into this.
Okay I guess.
If you won't be a servant--then
we can try things out this way.
It's not that a big difference.
[LILLY chuckles]
What do you think you're
laughing at, Lilly?!
Come back here!
By the way, Mahiru...
Since you're new to this,
you don't have a
weapon yet, do you?
--[MAHIRU] Weapon?
--[MISONO] Of course!
You don't plan on fighting
vampires empty-handed.
An Eve has the ability
to wield a custom weapon
created from
their Servamp's power.
[MAHIRU]
What? Seriously?
What a novice.
I suppose I'll have to teach
you everything, won't I?
Yeah. Please do!
You'll be like my mentor.
[MAHIRU] That day I found
someone who'd fight by my side.
A great ally.
[SAKUYA]
Mahiru?
So you decided to
keep the cat after all.
Uh--Yeah.
Better watch out, then--
you know black cats
are really bad luck.
[MAHIRU]
Oh don't worry.
He's just a normal cat.
Okay, fine, if you say so.
[MAHIRU] Ooh! I think I'm
gonna buy this wristband.
[SAKUYA]
What?
[MAHIRU] Remember?
I lost mine somewhere.
No, you can't do that,
because, you see...
Aw, jeez! Here!
[MAHIRU]
Uh...
For me?
After you told me
you lost yours, I saw this.
I figured I'd go
ahead and buy it.
I was gonna give it
to you later.
Sakuya.
I know it's kinda weird,
but don't make a big deal of it.
I won't, but thank you, Sakuya.
[SAKUYA]
I feel dumb now.
I didn't say stop.
[growling noise]
[SAKUYA]
What's wrong?
[MAHIRU]
Oh, it's nothing.
[SAKUYA] Sure you didn't
see something strange?
Maybe those rumors are true!
[MAHIRU]
Hey, Sakuya.
This is out of nowhere,
but tell me if anything strange
happens to you, okay?
I'll take care of it for you.
[SAKUYA] So you're some
kinda vampire slayer now?
Hey, Mahiru.
You've kind of been
acting super weird lately.
Did something happen to you?
You wouldn't hide
anything from me, right?
Because we're friends.
That means you're supposed
to be able to trust me.
[MAHIRU]
Nothing's going on with me!
[laughs nervously]
[MAHIRU]
Sorry to frighten you, Sakuya.
But I'll be fine.
[SAKUYA]
See you later!
I know I was lying when I said
Kuro is just a normal cat.
But what was I supposed to say?
[KURO yawns]
In that moment I was happy
about how things were going.
I now controlled a power
that could keep people safe.
But...
[MONSTER screeches]
[MAHIRU] ...things don't
always turn out how you think
they will.
[TSUBAKI laughing]
Not intwesting at ahl.
[BERUKIA]
He bit his tongue!