[LAWLESS]
Piano recital, huh?
[ACTRESS 10A]
Yeah, I have to.
It'll be worth it for dinner
with my boyfriend after, though.
Shouldn't you be focusing
on your next role?
Learning your lines?
Lately, your acting
has been a little... off.
[ACTRESS 10A]
Don't worry about my career.
[LAWLESS]
You were such a great actress--
enchanting the silver screen
with moving performances.
I expected more from you.
[LAWLESS]
Crap, I'm late.
Oh, well.
It looks like he's about to
begin the second piece.
[piano music]
[piano continues]
[LAWLESS]
Jekylland Licht Todoroki.
Everyone who hears him
play says he's unique--
an angel whose music
moves audiences to tears.
You're the next one.
[ACTRESS 10A]
Are you coming to dinner, too?
I can call ahead and get
a seat for you in the corner.
Nah. You have fun on your date.
[ACTRESS 10A] Don't tell me
you've got another weird
part-time job.
Whatever, just don't
go too far away.
[LAWLESS]
Be careful.
I'd hate for something
to happen to you.
Goodbye.
[LICHT] What, nothing to say
when we're face to face?
Pull yourself together.
I've been thinking...
I don't care whether
you're immortal or not.
It's my duty as an angel
to kill you here and now.
Any last words for me, Lawless?
[LAWLESS laughs]
Yeah, yeah, yeah. All right.
That's the kind of
crazy talk I'd expect
from someone like you.
A self-proclaimed angel
wants me dead.
When really you
should be buried here
before you screw
anything else up!
[LAWLESS]
My gloomy angel.
I don't know what makes you
think you're so damn important.
Haven't I made it
clear that your life
is just as insignificant as
all the others in this world?
[LICHT] Don't pretend
that I'm not special.
[LAWLESS]
Jekylland Licht Todoroki.
I'll prove how meaningless
your life is by killing you.
You're the one
who's going to die.
You bastard.
What is that?
The building's shaking.
Huh? Sounds like something
bad is happening next door.
[LAWLESS] What the hell
is wrong with me?
My body feels so heavy.
And my wounds are
healing really slowly.
But if I'm in this bad a shape,
he must be much worse.
After all, he's only human.
Let's get this
over with already.
How do you like being
crushed beneath my boot,
Hedgehog?
[LAWLESS]
What was that?
Are you okay, my angel?
Why are you getting up?
You'll die if we keep fighting.
Just give up already.
[LAWLESS laughs]
Okay. That's enough.
How about we just decide
to agree to disagree, huh?
To be honest,
I'm over this fight.
You really are amazing, Licht.
Set your mind to it
and you can do anything.
[LICHT laughs]
[LAWLESS]
Wait, what's so funny?
[LICHT]
Agree to disagree?
You're a coward.
That's just something
people say when they're wrong.
You don't even
have the motivation
to fight for yourself.
Listen, angel babes,
I'm just trying to teach you
something about real life here.
You and me and everyone else
are just anonymous parts
of a faceless mob.
[LICHT]
Anonymous?
Everyone in the world
is their own person.
Well, actually, no,
that's not true.
You're not a real
person, hedgehog.
You strut around the stage,
but the only things you spout
are tired old lines.
You don't even have a real name.
I'll teach you one lesson
before I end you.
You're defined by what you want
and how hard you work
toward getting it.
Your dream...
That's what creates character.
It's what really makes a person,
or even a vampire, unique.
You want nothing,
and you have no ambition.
You can't call any
life "meaningless."
Not unless you're doing
something with your own,
you idiot.
The one and only
Servamp of Greed?
What a joke.
You don't have a single desire.
You may think you're special.
But you're the worst of all.
If anyone is worthless,
it's you!
[LAWLESS]
Shut your mouth!
You know nothing
about me, dammit!
[LAWLESS]
Ophelia!
C'mon, where'd you run off to?
[OPHELIA]
Stop!
Huh?
[OPHELIA]
Now take two big steps back.
[LAWLESS]
Um...
[LAWLESS grunts]
[groaning]
Nice catch.
[GIRL 10A]
Look, there's the princess!
[PUCK] How'd it go?
Were you able to get anything?
[OPHELIA] Yes, the biggest
fruit on the tree.
Here you go.
That's amazing!
Thank you so much!
[LAWLESS]
Ophelia!
[laughs] You're right. I didn't
thank you for breaking my fall.
[LAWLESS]
What are you doing out here?
[OPHELIA] Puck is going
to have a baby sister soon.
We're gathering
fruit to celebrate.
[OPHELIA]
This makes me so happy.
[LAWLESS]
Huh?
We're growing.
Every day my country
gets bigger and stronger.
Yeah. Sure.
By the way, it feels
like you've gotten
a little heavier, Ophelia.
[OPHELIA laughs]
I'm just getting older.
All of us have to
grow up sometime, right?
Yeah, I know.
[OPHELIA]
A marriage has been arranged.
I don't know why you look
so surprised about that.
It's to the neighboring
country's prince.
The whole thing's
kind of sudden, I know.
But the fighting at our borders
can no longer be contained.
If I don't do something
to stop it soon,
we'll have a full-blown
war on our hands.
Marriage is the best way
to form a lasting alliance
and resolve this.
Let's run away.
It's crazy to marry
for that reason.
Run away with me.
We can have real freedom,
just the two of us, Ophelia.
I'm afraid freedom
isn't what I desire.
Okay, then tell me what
it is you actually want!
I'll do whatever it takes
to make sure you get it.
Come on, there has
to be something else
that you yearn for.
[OPHELIA]
Well, there is something, yes.
Perfect!
Let's go out and get it.
[OPHELIA] I want for our two
countries to live in harmony.
[OPHELIA] I will become
a symbol of peace--
the tie that binds
two peoples together.
That's my deepest wish.
Do you understand now?
[OPHELIA] I'll be moving
to the new country.
That means we're going to have
to hide our true relationship.
I'm sure no one
will ask questions
if I take you
as my pet hedgehog.
Still, it's going to be
difficult... for us both.
[HIGH OFFICIAL 10A]
A bloody vampire?
[SOLDIER 10A]
He's a monster!
[LAWLESS]
She got her peace.
The two countries were
tied together as one
by their marriage.
Things were good for a while.
But it didn't last.
The thing she wanted more than
anything eventually evaporated.
[RETAINER 10A]
But we agreed to an alliance!
[RETAINER 10B] Maybe they sent
the princess here as a trick!
To get us to let our guard down.
[RETAINER 10C] At this rate,
our own people
might turn against us!
[RETAINER 10D]
We have to kill the princess!
[RETAINER 10E]
Yes! Make an example of her!
[LAWLESS]
Ophelia! We have to go.
This is our only
chance to escape.
[OPHELIA]
I won't run away.
I'm staying here.
[LAWLESS]
What are you saying?
You'll be killed!
Even the king has
refused to spare your life.
Nothing can stop this. Let's go!
Will you please listen
to me for once in your life?!
We have to run!
I'll protect you!
[OPHELIA laughs]
[LAWLESS]
What could possibly be funny?
This isn't the first time you've
asked me to leave with you.
[LAWLESS] We don't have
time for this. Let's go.
I told you I didn't
care about freedom.
My life isn't that
important, either.
Didn't you listen?
The only thing that I want
is peace, and nothing else.
I want both these countries
I've grown to love
to live together in harmony.
My desire has gotten so strong.
I'm not sure that
it has any limits.
It's almost funny.
I guess I'm a fitting
Eve for Greed after all.
[LAWLESS]
Ophelia. You can't.
Because I...
I want peace.
With every fiber of my being.
I want to embody it wholly.
Wait and see.
I will make peace a reality.
This is just who I am.
It's not something that
you can change about me.
[OPHELIA]
Please don't cry, you fool.
It's so undignified
for a true vampire.
You're right, I'm a vampire.
And I'm not acting like
I should right now.
I could just...
murder everyone else.
I could kill anyone
trying to hurt you.
The whole country.
But you won't.
You won't take what
I want away from me.
Because you want me
to have my heart's desire.
You're wrong.
How can I just sit back
and do nothing?
[OPHELIA]
I'm sorry. Please forgive me.
Oh, Lawless. Thank you.
You're my Romeo.
[CROWD MAN 10A]
How terrible.
[CROWD WOMAN 10A] To think
they'd execute the princess...
It doesn't matter
how much time goes by.
This day will be remembered.
In countries not
yet established.
In cities where
they speak languages
we've never heard before.
Because this is the final
sacrifice for the sake of peace.
People of both nations,
hear my words.
I am not being executed because
I had no other choice.
I came here of my own volition.
That's because I love peace
more than I love my own life.
It's the only thing
that matters.
I stand here ready
to give myself up for peace.
For your future.
So if I am one who
is worthy of your love,
if you feel pity for me,
if you lament over my death...
After I'm gone,
please do me this favor.
Together as one people,
plant olive trees of peace.
I love you all.
So very dearly.
[LAWLESS]
Ophelia!
[BOY 10A]
This way! Hurry up!
[GIRL 10B]
What is it?
[BOY 10A]
It's really cool, I swear!
It's should be over here
by the statue of peace.
[GIRL 10B]
I don't see anything.
[BOY 10A]
Weird, it's always here.
There it is!
[GIRL 10B]
Wow! So cute!
[BOY 10A] Grandpa Puck told me
this little guy has been around
for a really long time.
He said that it
protects the statue.
[LAWLESS] You got what you
wanted in the end, Ophelia.
You really did
make peace a reality.
Even so, I find
no happiness in that.
[HUGH] This is why I warned
you to never fall in love.
[LAWLESS]
Old Child.
Have you come here
to laugh at me?
[HUGH] There's an
urgent matter at hand.
All seven siblings must
discuss this issue together.
[LAWLESS]
Okay, and what are we deciding?
You know what, never mind.
Do whatever you want.
[HUGH] Sleepy Ash wants
to hear everyone's opinions
on the subject.
[LAWLESS] These are the first
words I've heard from you
in so long!
I didn't expect you of
all people would suggest
that we murder
the man who made us.
He's the one person
who can create Servamps,
and you want to kill him?!
What are you thinking?
Do you just hate him,
or do you think this death
is really a good thing?
Tell me.
Do you think one death can
really create lasting peace?
What if you're wrong about that?
[KURO]
You don't understand anything.
I'm not doing this
because I hate him.
[LAWLESS laughs]
Well, then, why are you?
Are you just that delusional?
Or do you think this
is a noble sacrifice?
Could you really be
that stupid, brother?
This is... wrong.
Don't act like some kind
of tragic hero, dammit!
Who am I talking about?
[LAWLESS] An incredible
person is going to die.
[GLUTTONY]
Yeah.
[LAWLESS]
Someone who's important to us--
that all of us should care
about and try to protect.
[GLUTTONY]
I know.
[LAWLESS]
Especially our oldest brother.
I didn't understand at the time
why our brother Sloth
would say he would
take care of things himself.
I still don't know what's right,
or what I should've done.
Not that our actions
really matter.
When I returned
to your country later,
peace had disappeared
completely.
The two lands you brought
together were in ruins.
Destroyed.
Utterly annihilated by
a neighboring country.
[LAWLESS] I wonder what
you're a symbol of now.
[LAWLESS]
Everything is fine.
Ophelia... I'm not sad.
I finally get it.
It's not just you.
No one's life has any
meaning in the end.
Nothing lasts forever.
[LAWLESS (SONG)]
♪ She is dead and gone, lady, ♪
[LAWLESS] Your life wasn't the
only one without consequence.
[LAWLESS (SONG)]
♪ Lord! ♪
♪ We know what we-- ♪
[LAWLESS] Everything in the
world is completely meaningless.
♪ Sweets to sweet!
Farewell! ♪
[grunts]
[LAWLESS]
We're all just actors here,
putting on a worthless show.
[LAWLESS]
Bravo! Bravo! How wonderful!
[blows nose]
It made me weep!
You know it's a
truly moving story
when you can't help
but cry your eyes out!
You really are pathetic,
you rotten hedgehog.
Shut up.
Hey, wait, you
actually recognized me?
[LICHT]
Immediately.
But I stand by what I said.
The only one
worth nothing is you.
[LAWLESS]
Wait, what are you doing?
You just can't leave this place.
[LICHT]
It's my turn.
Now take your seat.
[LICHT] Even an idiot
like you can listen.
So be my audience of one.
Um, hey, I have a question.
Why do you play the piano?
[piano scales]
[LICHT]
I made a promise to a friend.
And I eventually
decided that I'd keep it.
I'll do anything
I can to fulfill it.
I can see them. In my head.
Everyone in the world
being moved to tears
by my performance.
I can hear it, too.
The sound of their
tears dripping down
onto their applauding hands.
That's what you're missing.
[LAWLESS]
Imagination?
And an achievable
dream created by it.
[LAWLESS]
Hey.
I don't want to hear
any sad songs right now.
Make this a happy place?
I can't decide if this
place is happy or sad.
Feel however you want.
That's up to you.
[playing "Fur Elise"]
[LAWLESS]
This is "Fur Elise."
Did you know it was supposed to
be "Therese" instead of "Elise,"
but Beethoven had
bad handwriting?
It's kind of a famous story.
He wrote her this love song even
though they couldn't be together
because of their
separate classes.
That's the popular
interpretation at least, but...
[LAWLESS]
Licht...
I don't like this song.
It's far too tragic.
[LICHT]
It's not the song that's tragic.
[LAWLESS]
Then... why am I crying?
Is it me?
Am I the one... who's sad?
[LAWLESS]
I... I... I am...
[LICHT]
You are a young boy.
You are an old woman.
You are flowers.
You are space.
You are me and
in turn I am you.
[LAWLESS]
Right.
Actually...
I could have become
anything I wanted to.
[LICHT]
Start now.
Imagine what you've
always wanted.
[LAWLESS]
I know who I am.
I'm the one who never
wanted to let go of your hand.
I'm the one who
wanted to keep you safe.
I'm the one who wanted
to protect what you wanted
to protect.
I'm the one who
wanted to tell you
that I was...
in love with you, Ophelia.
Why didn't I?
Why didn't I try
to become anything?
[LICHT] To be "Lawless"
is to do whatever you want.
You don't live up to your name.
[LAWLESS] I shouldn't have
ever let go of your hand,
no matter what.
There must have been
some way for us to both
have gotten what we
wanted at the same time.
So why couldn't I
imagine it and create it?
Come on! Step forward!
Come on! Want something!
I... I don't want
this overbearing human
to die in a place like this.
I want to ask Brother why
he really killed that person.
I want to tell him that I still
regret that I didn't stop him--
that I don't forgive
him for what he did.
I want to look him in the eye
and tell him how
I really feel about it.
[LAWLESS]
Ophelia...
Wherever you may be sleeping,
I want to show you
that I... I... I...
[LAWLESS]
I loved Ophelia.
I won't give up
on anything else.
No rules or people
will hold me down.
...with all their quantity
of love make up my sum!
Lawless of Greed!
Reach out your hand
and grab your dream!
Want it! Want it! Want it!
[LICHT]
Want it... Hyde.
[HIGAN]
Oh, wow.
You guys made it
out on your own.
I'm sorry, Licht.
But it looks like this
old man is gonna have to
beat you to shreds
one more time.
Who is this walking corpse?
Whoever he is, Licht's
enemy is my enemy too, so--
[LICHT]
Can it, hedgehog.
[LAWLESS]
Ah, come on, just say it!
[LICHT]
It's because...
[LAWLESS, LICHT]
I'm an angel!