[MISONO] I'm absolutely
astounded by your laziness.
You haven't even given
your Eve a weapon yet.
You live up to your title,
Sloth boy.
Hey, that's right.
Why haven't you given me
some kinda weapon yet?
What's the point in doing
something so troublesome?
Wouldn't you two rather
just look at how cute I am?
[MAHIRU, MISONO]
You're not that cute!
I have a lot to learn.
I barely know anything
about vampires
or what I should
be doing as an Eve.
But I do know that there are
people I want to keep safe.
I can't sit back and do nothing
if vampires are
attacking humans.
Do you really think
you need a weapon?
If it gives me the
power to protect others,
yeah, of course!
[KURO]
Then close your eyes.
[MAHIRU] Wait a second...
what's about to happen?
Aren't you gonna
explain things first?
[MAHIRU gasps]
[KURO]
Well happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday.
You're inside of Kuro now.
Come on, follow me.
You're here for
something, right?
Your very own birthday present.
Uh, my birthday's a ways off.
Oh, wait. Are you
talking about a weapon?
Who are you?
[KURO]
I'm another part of Kuro.
I'm in charge of his power.
Now it's time for you
to choose your fate.
Unwrap whichever one you like.
[MAHIRU]
Out of all those?
[KURO]
Yes. Happy birthday, Mahiru.
Pick a box and obtain
your very own power.
You can't return it
once it's been opened.
But you will become a stronger
person who can protect others.
[KURO] Choose carefully,
but confidently.
The ending will be the same
no matter what you select.
Though there are many possible
routes for you to take.
What's important is
that your choice reflects
who you are inside.
Well, in that case, I'll take
the simplest looking one.
[LILLY chuckles]
[KURO]
Well, you picked a broom.
[MISONO] Hmph. A fitting
weapon for a commoner.
[KURO]
Now that I think about it,
you tried to attack me
with a mop
the first time you
saw me in this form.
What's the deal?
Do you have a weird thing
about using cleaning supplies
as weapons?
No, of course not.
Like a tattoo. What the hell?
[MAHIRU] I don't get how
this thing is a weapon.
How will I be able
to fight with it?
Now. Fate is finally in motion.
[TSUBAKI] You can't put
a plate back on the belt
once you've touched it, Berukia.
[BERUKIA]
What, seriously?
This stupid place
has too many rules.
More importantly, Tsu-Tsu,
isn't that joker a little late?
How long are we
gonna have to wait?
Look. Not very long at all.
[MALE WORKER 3A]
Hi. Sit anywhe--
[CROWD gasping]
[TSUBAKI] Looks like
someone's in a bad mood.
[CUSTOMER 3A]
Let's get outta here!
[CUSTOMER 3B]
Wait for me!
[SAKUYA]
Tsubaki. You called?
Why don't you explain
what you're holding first?
[SAKUYA] I'm pretty sure
this guy was following me
around earlier.
He might be
someone's subclass.
[SAKUYA]
Who knows?
Aren't you afraid
someone from school
might see your current state?
It'd be pretty obvious
that you're a vampire.
Right? Sakuya?
That doesn't matter
to me anymore.
They're liars. That's just
something I just can't stand.
[MAHIRU growls]
And now I awaken my power!
[yells]
[MAHIRU]
Why isn't anything happening?!
You need to be able to
pull that weapon out at will
before you can start
learning how to fight.
Hey, Kuro, is there, like,
a trick to this or what?
I'm busy. Don't talk to
me until you can summon it.
[MAHIRU]
Ugh!
Mahiru, dear, why don't
you try focusing on exactly why
you wanted this power
to begin with.
Let that thought guide you.
But how will that help?
[MISONO]
Your Servamp lacks motivation
because you lack resolve.
The two are tied together.
[MAHIRU] If Kuro acts based
on how I'm feeling,
does that mean Lilly
keeps trying to strip
because you secretly want to?!
No, it's because he's
a damn pervert!
[MAHIRU] Focus on why
I want power. Okay.
Because I want
to protect others.
Everyone I possibly can.
Especially my friends.
They've basically been family
to me since I was little.
Since I don't have parents,
I probably value my
friends more than most.
[MAHIRU] Hey, I should
introduce you to them, Misono!
There's Ryusei, and Koyuki.
But Sakuya has to be the first.
He's my oldest friend!
[MISONO]
You can't.
You'd just be getting
your friends involved.
And besides, Tsubaki
is the only reason
we're connected to each
other in the first place.
[MAHIRU]
That's not true.
There's no reason
we can't all get along.
My old friends
and my new friend.
I want to keep everyone
important to me safe--
My friends and family.
No matter what we face,
we'll take them down!
Right? Kuro?
Don't know why you're
asking me; you're in charge.
I'll do what you say.
Kill or protect whoever
you order me to.
That's the job of a Servamp.
Oh, come on, Kuro.
Don't you even care a little?
[MAHIRU]
Huh? What was that?
Ah, It must have been...
[MISONO snoring]
[MAHIRU]
Misono?
I didn't realize it was so late.
He falls asleep
at nine on the dot.
[MAHIRU]
Like a little kid?
[LILLY] Why don't we
pick this up tomorrow?
[MAHIRU]
Yeah, that sounds good.
Thanks for all
the help and advice.
Both of you.
[LILLY]
Our pleasure.
[MAHIRU]
Huh? Sakuya's out again today?
I know. It's weird for him to
miss so many classes in a row.
[RYUSEI] Maybe he caught some
kinda cold and is stuck in bed.
I did call him yesterday,
but no one answered
the phone at his place.
I wanted him to
try on this uniform.
[KOYUKI]
Is that a butler costume?
[RYUSEI]
Whoa, did you make that?
You're so crafty, Mahiru.
This is gonna kill it
at the festival!
Sakuya will flip
out when he sees it.
Hopefully.
I think later I'll stop
by his house after school.
[MALE WORKER 3B]
Thanks! Come back soon!
[KURO]
Are there chips?
[MAHIRU]
Bad cat!
This stuff is for Sakuya.
Sakuya's the clown who's
always telling stories
and has weird hair, right?
I don't think he'd get along
with that stuck-up brat.
[MAHIRU]
"Stuck-up brat"?
You mean Misono?
[MAHIRU] Something seemed up
with Sakuya last time I saw him.
I should've spent more
time trying to figure out
what was wrong.
But since we were kids,
everything's just been
a big joke to him.
[KURO]
You were childhood friends?
Yeah, we've been friends
since elementary school.
Or wait, was it middle school?
[KURO]
Oi?
[MAHIRU] Sakuya lost both
his parents, just like I did.
[MAHIRU]
How did they die again?
I should know this.
And where does Sakuya live?
I don't--
Why can't I think
of his address?
I've been to his place
a million times.
When was I there last?
What am I saying?
He's been my best friend
since we were kids!
After all those years...
Wait, was he my friend...?
[KURO]
Are you okay?
My head's suddenly killing me.
We were inseparable.
[MAHIRU]
This "Sakuya"...
Who is he again?
[SAKUYA]
Hi, Mahiru.
[MAHIRU gasps]
[MAHIRU]
Oh. Sakuya.
[SAKUYA] Just loitering in the
middle of the sidewalk, huh?
What are you doing here?!
You haven't been to school or
picked up your phone in days!
I've been worried.
[SAKUYA]
So, the thing is...
Remember how I said
there were vampires
stalking around here at night?
Well... I was kind
of attacked by one.
Someone rescued me from it.
But I've been too scared to
leave my house since then.
Now... just how much of
that story do you think
I was making up, eh?
I knew you were joking.
Have some food.
I'm betting you
haven't had dinner.
Y'know, you could really
stand to be more serious.
[WOMAN 3A screams]
[MAHIRU]
What's that?
--[SAKUYA] Mahiru! This way!
--[MAHIRU] Wait, what?
Where are you taking me? Sakuya!
[SAKUYA]
Just follow me.
I'm your best friend, right?
You know what that means.
I won't betray you.
That's not what friends do.
[MAHIRU]
Where are we?
[SAKUYA]
Be honest with me, Mahiru.
Do you trust me?
If you really trusted me,
then you wouldn't lie to me.
Not ever.
[MAHIRU]
You're being weird, Sakuya.
What are you trying to say? Huh?
[SAKUYA] There's something
I have to know.
[SAKUYA] How much of our
relationship is a lie?
Or was our entire
friendship a sham?
[MAHIRU grunts]
What the crap is going on?!
--Kuro!
--[BERUKIA laughs]
[BERUKIA]
Now, let's hear some applause!
The skewering spectacular
is about to begin!
[MAHIRU]
Him again?
[SAKUYA]
Mahiru. I warned you, didn't I?
That there are
vampires around here.
[MAHIRU gasps]
I told you so, so, so
many times to be careful!
Mahiru. Your friend...
He's Tsubaki's subclass!
[MAHIRU]
Sakuya?
Mahiru.
Do you ever get the feeling
that the entire world,
everything you know,
was created five minutes ago?
You probably
think that's crazy.
After all, you have
memories of the past.
But what if those
are fake memories
that were recently
implanted in your brain?
What if I've only been your
best friend for five minutes?
Can you prove something
like that is impossible?
Can you prove that
anything actually existed
more than five minutes ago?
[MAHIRU]
What's he talking about?
[SAKUYA] What did I say
to you when your mom died?
Do you remember, Mahiru?
Was I... even there?
[MAHIRU]
Hold on.
Why isn't Sakuya in any of
my memories from the past?
[SAKUYA]
What do you think?
Just how many of your memories
of us are actually lies,
my friend?
[MAHIRU]
No, Kuro!
He slashed Kuro.
But he was going after me.
Sakuya is killing people!
What is going on?
You're making it up!
You're not actually
a vampire, right?!
Oh, you'd love it if that
were a lie, wouldn't you?
If vampires didn't exist
and I wasn't one of them,
you could chalk this up
as some kinda trick.
People always want
to believe the lie
that's most convenient for them.
Vampires take advantage of that
and use it to hypnotize humans.
[MAHIRU]
I know how it feels.
My parents are gone, too.
Come over for dinner sometime
so we don't have to eat alone.
[SAKUYA]
You were easy to fool.
You wanted to connect
with someone so badly.
Mahiru, why did you
have to get involved?
If you hadn't
picked up that cat...
If you hadn't lied to me
and said it was normal...
Then I might still be
standing by your side.
Right now.
We could've woken tomorrow,
still best friends.
Things could have kept
going on like they were.
Why does the world fall
apart around you so often?
It's not fair.
[MAHIRU]
I didn't mean to lie!
I just didn't want my friends to
get wrapped up with vampires!
I wanted to keep you safe;
to protect all of you guys!
Shut up!
You're still lying to me,
which means you
really don't trust me!
If I was actually
your best friend,
then you would've told me
the truth no matter what!
Don't you dare say you were
lying to me to keep me safe!
I was!
[SAKUYA] You know...I hate
liars more than anything.
Once someone lies to you,
you lose all trust.
You can't believe a word
that they say ever again.
Do you know how this feels?
It's like my entire
body's being torn apart.
That's what happens when your
best friend lies to your face.
And that's not all!
I'm not stupid.
I knew the words coming out
of your mouth were lies!
But I just stood there
pretending it was okay.
I didn't say anything,
which means you made a liar
out of me, too, Mahiru!
[MAHIRU]
Kuro...
Come on.
We can fix this somehow.
The two of us will work together
again and make things right.
[MAHIRU]
We... have to stop him.
--[MAHIRU] Kuro!
--[KURO] There's no point.
[MAHIRU]
Huh?!
Drinking your blood isn't
gonna help anything.
Not when you're like this.
[MAHIRU]
What?
[KURO] That stuck-up brat
explained it to you, didn't he?
We're linked.
The reason I'm so lazy is
because you lack certainty.
A Servamp is powered
by the resolve
flowing through
the veins of its Eve.
That means my power is
only equal to the strength
of your will.
[KURO] You don't have
any resolve right now.
I can't tell if you want
me to protect your friend
or to kill him.
[MAHIRU]
What am I thinking?
What am I trying to do?
Who do I protect?
[MAHIRU grunts]
[BERUKIA]
What the...?
[MAHIRU]
Misono?
Stand back, Mahiru Shirota.
I'll take care of this.
Hold on a second!
You can't!
That's my friend Sakuya!
Right.
I'm his very best friend
in the whole world.
So what are you going
to do with me, huh?
This guy is one
of your friends?
What a pity.
We won't get along, vampire.
[SAKUYA chuckles]
I'm not very good at fighting,
but I'll do my best.
If it brings you pleasure.
[BERUKIA growls]
Not a very good plan.
Do you really think you
can take me down alone?
That's pretty damn cocky of you,
you rich little punk.
Tell me when and why you first
got close to Mahiru Shirota.
What were your motives?
Huh? You're talking like some
kind of jealous boyfriend
who's been cheated on.
Why do you care so
much about Mahiru?
Didn't you just meet
him like, yesterday?
It doesn't matter when we met.
It matters what he said.
Shirota called me his friend!
[SAKUYA]
His friend, huh?
You child! You really believed
such an obvious con?
There's not a lie in the
world that's more overused
than friendship!
You're stupider than I thought.
You can't even tell when
someone is just saying
what you want
to hear to be polite!
What are you doing now?
What's a kid like you
gonna do against me?
This is so easy;
you're a lonely Eve
who's about to be
knocked off the board.
Separating from your Servamp
was an idiotic mistake.
Ah. Some applause, please.
Prepare to be amazed
by the duke of skewering!
Berukia...
and his magic murder box!
No one leaves the box alive!
Now, now, now, let's impale the
boy with the stupid cowlick!
Lilly only left my side because
he had a good reason to.
Watch closely, Shirota.
This is one way
I can use my power.
If an enemy target comes
in between Lilly and I,
this weapon activates.
[MISONO, LILLY]
Good night. And sweet dreams.
Huh?! What the hell
is this thing?
You're kidding me!
Misono's weapon... is a chair?
[LILLY]
Nighty night, now.
One down.
[MAHIRU yells]
[MAHIRU] It looked like you
chopped his head off.
[LILLY] My power only
destroys the mind, not the body.
To be honest with you,
I'm out of practice,
but it's good to know that
we can still put up a fight.
Misono really wanted to
show off for you, Mahiru.
[MISONO]
Be quiet, Lilly!
It's unfortunate.
Shirota told me
how excited he was
to introduce his friends to me.
He wanted you to be first.
He really wanted
to introduce us?
I see.
I wish we could
have stayed friends.
Even if it was only for
just another week or two.
I was actually pretty pumped
to go to the school festival
that was coming up.
If only things had
turned out differently.
Who knows.
Misono Alicein... You and I
might even have been friends.
Misono! Do not let
him distract you.
[SAKUYA]
Mahiru.
I wonder what your new
friend's intentions are.
Sounds to me like
he wants us to fight.
Is that it?
[LILLY]
Misono! What are you doing?
Where'd he go?
[LILLY gasps]
Hi, there.
I'm the grand duke
of skewering, Berukia.
Looks like something's
wrong with your leg.
Those strings...
Who's moving you?
[LILLY gasps]
Misono!
[SAKUYA] So just how much
of what I said earlier
do you think was a lie, Mahiru?
Does it mean I'm a liar
if I failed to mention
we're not alone?
[LILLY]
So there's someone else here--
pulling the strings.
It's so difficult to impersonate
the strange way Berukia talks.
It's a problem.
Sakuya! Why are you
doing this to us?
What the heck happened to you?
I thought maybe the three
of us could all be friends.
Why ruin that?
You can stop this!
[MISONO]
Shirota...
Did I do something out of line?
I just wanted to
protect my new friend.
It wasn't out of line.
You were only trying
to do something noble.
Dammit!
You have no idea, Mahiru.
No idea how your supposed best
friend felt this whole time.
Hanging out on the
way home from school...
The more fun I had
with you guys,
the drier my throat would get.
[MAHIRU]
Sakuya...
It'd get so bad that I'd
think about killing someone.
I guess it's just
to be expected.
That's just the way I'm wired.
Vampires exist to
hurt people. Humans.
[MAHIRU]
No...
You can't just say that;
it's not an excuse!
[grunts]
But it's true, Mahiru.
Honestly, the guilt feels
pretty damn good, too.
It's all part of
being a vampire.
The reward for my thirst.
Now, listen.
If you're going to try and kill
me, be serious about it.
Otherwise, I might attack
your new friend again.
And this time he'll die.
You're a liar.
Would you really do to him
what he did to you?
You won't betray him.
[MAHIRU]
Sakuya!
[KURO]
Keep quiet, Mahiru.
You can't fight him
in the state that you're in.
Wait, what about your wounds?
I'm better. So...
It'd be smart
for us to run now.
No way, Kuro. I'll--
[KURO]
We have to go.
We can't run!
Misono is hurt! Look at him!
[KURO] Do you really want
to use your power like this?
You haven't done anything
you'll regret yet.
You can still walk away from
here with a clear conscience.
I can't just sit back
and do nothing!
You're not listening, Mahiru.
What I mean is that you're
unsure of yourself right now.
Sakuya!
Good. You're doing the
right thing, Mahiru.
Liars all deserve to be killed.
It's raining even
though the moon is out.
But I thought you weren't going
to be joining us here today.
And why not, Otogiri?
I want in on the fun.
It's a problem.
So, Mahiru Shirota.
I want to see the true
shape of your despair.
It would be interesting
if you became the key.
[KURO]
Please.
Don't lose sight of yourself.
Don't be swayed.
[MAHIRU]
I hit him. I hit Sakuya.
[KURO]
Don't get swallowed.
[MAHIRU] I don't feel like
I'm the one swinging.
It's like I'm being
swung around.
[SAKUYA]
It won't stop bleeding.
Is it because of that broom?
What do ya know?
Maybe you will
be able to kill me.
[MAHIRU]
Wait a second.
What does he mean by that?
I'm not gonna kill Sakuya!
[KURO]
No. Don't go down that path.
You can't, Mahiru.
You won't be able to stay human!
[MAHIRU]
I don't want to kill anyone.
Especially not him.
We were friends.
This isn't the power
that I asked for!
[MAHIRU]
I can't do this.
I wanted to protect people!
[SAKUYA]
Hey, Mahiru?
You won't believe this, but I
actually had a secret plan.
It was for me,
someone who doesn't age,
to be best friends with you guys
and have the best three years of
high school anyone's ever had.
[KURO]
Mahiru!
[SAKUYA] And then quietly
disappear so you could
continue on with your lives.
That was my big hope
for a happy future.
[LILLY] I'll bring you
pleasure next week.
See you then.
[MISONO]
Put your clothes back on!