[NARRATOR] Gimlet, the new
weapon of the People of Metus,
(and a delish gin cocktail
flavored with lime and syrup),
plowed through the Union
Fleet's defensive lines--
steadily expanding the war zone.
Mm, who's thirsty?
Meanwhile, the Tiramisu was
positioned near Jupiter
when it received an SOS signal
from a broken-down
civilian transport.
The battleship agreed to take on
the transport's passengers
temporarily. Long enough
to ferry them to safety in
the neutral country of Europa.
[SUBARU]
My new power is awesome.
[SUBARU] It's like lifting
weights with my mind.
[NARRATOR] Indeed, Subaru's
concentration in battle
was approaching
superhuman levels,
and he was quite pleased.
You sure are good at that.
We were just admiring your
wonderful driving skills.
But you're civilian people!
[NARRATOR] His concentration was
so strong that he didn't notice
two of the stranded civilians
looking for adventure
had hitched a ride
in his cockpit.
[SUBARU]
How'd they get in here?!
Okay, everyone pause.
Why are you in my cockpit?
[PAC2-AR] They came in while you
were having a pooper party
in the little spaceman's room.
Don't you judge me!
And why the hell
didn't you stop them?
[PAC2-AR] Kick out a sweet
granny and her grandson?
Who hurt you?
Do you get to drive this
spaceship every day?
Why don't you be a dear
and let this sweet boy
take it for a spin?
[SUBARU]
Uh!
[GRANDMOTHER]
Look at all those asteroids!
I know he would love to do
a few laps around those!
And I bet you're
the perfect mentor!
It doesn't work like that!
No to asteroid laps!
[SUBARU]
You don't "drive" a spacecraft.
Animals.
I'm sorry, I just wanted
to see the boy smile.
His parents divorced.
His mom's on Earth and his
father works long hours
on Europa. It breaks my heart.
And here we go
with the guilt trip.
I guess he can sit in
the seat for a few minutes.
[GRANDSON]
Sweet!
[SUBARU] You know what'll
make it really fun
is if you don't touch anything.
'Kay!
Aww, the little guy gets me!
What happens if you
press this button?
Then you waste ammo!
That's the head volley cannon!
He's having so much fun
with that cannon!
Let him enjoy himself
and I'll give you
this yummy dried persimmon
for your tum-tum!
[SUBARU]
I don't need that!
Gramma, I'm bored again.
What's this thing do?
Nothing!
It transforms the ship using a
secret code only adults know!
Don't touch!
[GRANDMOTHER] Teach him well
and let him lead the way.
[SUBARU]
It requires a sequence!
This is why we can't
have nice things!
Sounds like a party up there.
[SUBARU] Stop! I'm using
my serious voice!
Don't piss me off, kid!
[NARRATOR] Although he didn't
know it at the time,
Subaru changed a life that day.
The boy you see here went on to
become a seasoned Union warrior
known as "The Dancing
Grim Reaper."
Their security's still
a tragic mess.
I can't believe they let a
bunch of civilians aboard
without even questioning them.
I'm all good if they want
to make it easy on us.
[ISUZU] Look at these beautiful
anti-mobile weapon bombs.
Hello, my precious.
These have the
power and precision
to destroy the new Durandal
without harming anything
else in its path.
[MAYBACH]
I know. Look at this.
You, uh, interrupted me.
Do you see the potential mess
I'm holding in my
hand right now?
[NARRATOR] Isuzu and
Maybach used the civilians
as cover to sneak
aboard the Tiramisu .
This is double-sided tape, bro.
That's how they expect
us to attach it.
Double-frickin-sided tape.
You're kidding.
[NARRATOR] Never trust
double-sided tape, kids. Never.
That's not possible!
Bombs always come with magnets!
Everyone knows that!
Read the box!
You better not have thrown
it away! Did you? Hey!
[MAYBACH] No, Drama Pants,
it's right here,
and this is the one
for the detonator.
You can't just tape a bomb.
There's gotta be a hook thingy
or a mount or something.
No universe exists where
an object this heavy
stays in place with tape.
Plus, how janky does that look?
Uh...
You did not just tell me
to go buy batteries!
[sighs] Well, I'm over it.
Do you want to reschedule?
[MAYBACH]
No, stupid.
Look.
This bomb is designed
with a switch on it
that lets you set it off
even without a detonator.
We'd just have to GTFO.
I could do that.
[MAYBACH]
Finally, let's get the one
that's already open
in the Durandal.
You came through just
when I needed you most.
But how annoying was that?
I'm gonna write to the
company and complain!
You should.
I think feedback
will really help,
and consumers need to know.
[ISUZU grunting]
[footsteps]
[phone buzzes]
Screw you and your passive-
aggressive emoticon! Uh?
Loud noises.
Is it sortie time again?
No!
What the hell are you
doing in there, Subaru?
[SUBARU] It's my Durandal,
what's your excuse?
[ISUZU]
Uh!
Aww, not on my favorite suit!
[ISUZU grunts]
It's all messy.
Whose hair is that?
Now it's not gonna
stick to anything!
It's your fault!
None of this would've happened
if you weren't such a
cockpit-whipped titty-baby!
Hey there, Pee-Pants!
[SUBARU, ISUZU shouting]
[LIGIER]
Who is that?
[SUBARU, ISUZU shouting]
[gasps] Bastard.
Yo, Honor Roll! Step away
from Powder Puff!
[gasps] No wait! Don't shoot!
[gunshot]
[SUBARU]
Neo Universe Sense!
You need to move,
Subaru Ichinose.
[NARRATOR]
When Subaru was little,
he was always told he didn't
look very much like his brother.
But in this moment,
he felt as though he was
looking in a mirror.
[ISUZU gasping]
No.
Subaru!
[VULGAR]
Listen, Pee Pants,
I'm gonna give you
an official moniker.
[SUBARU]
You mean a real one?
Like "Grim Reaper," or "Golden
Finger" or "Dark Crimson Wave?"
[VULGAR] Nah. I was thinkin'
"Steel Virgin." Ha, ha!
Get it? Like "still a
virgin," but "Steel"?
[SUBARU]
Why are you so mean to me?
[VULGAR]
Shut up.