[NARRATOR] As if pulled by
gravity's irresistible force,
the Hekatonkheires was heading
straight toward Earth.
Subaru and friends were
looking rather desperate
as they waged a battle against
its destructive might.
That's cute. Like I'm gonna let
that purple scrod
rocket hit Earth.
Couldn't have come at a
better time, if you ask me.
I've been needing
a nice Earth vacay.
Can you move any faster?!
Yeah. Calm down.
And what about you, Beyond?
What?! As if!
Don't question
the speed of a god!
You wouldn't know fast
if it donkey-punched you!
Yeah, nice try.
The Hekatonkheires
can never be stopped!
[OPERATOR 12A]
All units are maxed out!
[VULGAR grunts]
Lieutenant?
Don't look at me!
Focus on your fight!
Yeah, but...
What did I say?
No buts or asses!
We're all putting our
lives on the line, here!
[ISUZU]
Ooh! We've got ourselves a hero!
Huh?
I'm right behind you--
all the way.
Heh. Not the first time
ya said that.
[MAYBACH]
Sorry to interrupt.
Can you stop flirting
and help us fight?
[LIGIER]
Seriously!
[BEYOND] Heh. You're all making
this such a pain in my ass.
All lower forms of life should
give it up and go take a nap.
Get out of my way and leave
protecting planets to the gods!
[NARRATOR] In the midst of this
battle for the fate of Earth,
the melodrama level in this
show was at a record high.
Meanwhile...
Subaru had found what appeared
to be a controller of sorts.
It even came with a manual.
[PAC2-AR] What is that thing?
It looks vintage.
It's a controller for
the enemy mech.
[PAC2-AR] Ooo, Scandalous!
Should we tell the others?
You think we're all trying
to die out here, Pee Pants?
We'll do whatever we can
to protect our planet.
I mean, we gotta
at least try, right?
[BEYOND] I'm saying
something inspirational!
I love video games!
[SUBARU]
Forget it! I can't tell them!
They've invested so much time
and anxiety in this battle.
I can't say, "hey guys, I think
we just have to push one
of these gray buttons!'
I know what I'll do.
I can move it a
little bit at a time.
That way no one will
get butt-hurt about it.
There we go. Slowly.
Oh, there she is.
Sorry to wake ya, princess
Right. Yes, sir! Look at that!
Captain! The bulbus purple
chode-thing is changing course!
[VENTURI]
Mm?
[CADILLAC] This makes no sense.
What the hell's happening?
[LAMBDA] It looks like we're
veering off course.
Excuse you?
Attention, all units.
The enemy's course has begun
to shift slightly.
Keep fighting.
Everything from here
on out is in your hands.
Guess that means we can
hit the bars soon, right?
Uh, not yet. We're staying in
it until this job is complete!
He can't just bail.
We gotta beat his ass!
The time has come to
showcase our wisdom.
That which was given
to the People of Metus!
Too bad no one ever asked me.
I'd never allow some
stupid plan to destroy Earth.
I need less chitty-chat
and more assy-smack!
Let's show this thing
what we are made of!
[ALL]
Yeah!
What's wrong with you, Lambda?!
Correct the course!
[LAMBDA]
Uhm. I can't.
All right fine, I'll just
have to fly it manually.
[gasps] Feels like
something's sticking.
[PAC2-AR]
Did you make messy again?
BT-dubs I read the instructions,
and I found out something
very interesting.
Turns out, someone
doodled a cheat code!
No way? For real?
It's worth more than my life.
We have to save our
Earth, no matter what!
Is now the right time
to tell you I love you?
Our names will go down
in history for this!
Protecting the Earth
is a god's duty!
I'm counting on you
brave men and women!
[SUBARU grunts]
[NARRATOR] This situation and
the moods of those involved...
Over it.
[NARRATOR] ...were starting
to get on Subaru's nerves.
[SUBARU]
Enter the self-destruct command!
[CADILLAC]
Impossible!
Why isn't anything
working right?
[LAMBDA] Well, Mister, it
appears that someone used
the external controller to enter
the self-destruct command.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?!
[LAMBDA]
Because! You just asked me now.
[OPERATOR 12A] It's no longer
heading toward Earth!
[OPERATORS cheering]
[beeping]
Yeah, but who's to say
it won't try again later?
So, what now? You gotta plan?
[PAC2-AR]
Attention, please!
I did a little research.
If you aim right here
you can trigger a secondary
explosion and destroy it!
All right! Let's turn this
robot-trash into shrapnel!
I'm a god.
Have I said that already?
I can't stress it enough!
Let's go!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[VULGAR yelling]
[BEYOND yells]
[LIGIER yells]
Universe, go!
All right. It ends now!
[PAC2-AR] O-M-G. Are you
really okay with this?
Be real.
Yeah.
I'm not gonna be the animal
that crushes their dreams.
[NARRATOR] The experiences
of Subaru's past year
had brought about
change, growth,
and an overdue social awareness.
I guess it's all over now.
--[rustling]
--Hm?
Oh, Shelby. I'm sorry.
Tell me, where did I go wrong?
[LAMBDA]
It's okay, Mister.
There are as many women as
there are stars in the sky.
Really? What would
a kid like you know?
Here's the thing.
Shelby wasn't just
another star in the sky.
She was a star that
was created just for me.
Look! A shooting star!
[grunts]
[NARRATOR]
Cadillac ended up missing
his appointed court
mediation that day.
And later found himself
slapped with a lawsuit.
Don't get used to it.
It was a one-time thing.
Okay, that's fine.
Good. I'm working
toward revolution.
I swear, if you even think
of getting in my way...
Yeah, I get it.
But, um. Don't expect me
to just take your crap.
[NARRATOR]
And with that, the two brothers
went their separate
ways once again.
Space Age 0157.
Ace pilot Subaru Ichinose
of the Earth Union,
and Isuzu Ichinose of
the People of Metus...
[gasps]
Oh no! My eye thingy's gone!
Again?
He always forgets this thing.