[KOENIG]
Hey. Let's be honest, guys.
Do you think your lives
are on the right track?
You ever feel like something's
a little lacking?
Want that to change, you've
gotta take action, like me.
[SUBARU] Ensign Koenig
seems kinda different.
[KOENIG] All you gotta do
is listen, no pressure.
Now, I wouldn't tell
just anyone about this.
But you guys are my
comrades-in-arms,
and I wouldn't feel right
if I didn't share this
life-changing secret.
[SUBARU]
What's he talking about?
[KOENIG] We're all just
lowly soldiers here.
Never know when
death might claim us.
Don't know about you guys,
but I'm a person first
and a soldier second.
I mean, just think about it:
why shouldn't we be able to do
what we want and live our
best lives, you know?
Well, yeah, sounds great, but...
That's easy for you to say,
but I don't exactly have time
to "live my best life."
[SUBARU] And "doing what you
want" can be expensive, too.
You're absolutely right!
Living the life you deserve and
finding the kind of happiness
we all crave takes a
real time investment.
And I think we all know that
it doesn't come cheap, either.
What if we said there
was a way to eliminate
those pesky worries
about time and money,
would you want to hear it?
I'm betting so.
Hold on, is there a way?
One look at me and the ensign
should answer that
question for you.
[SUBARU]
Now I'm curious.
The paychecks we bring in
aren't too bad for pilots,
but we're sick to
death of the job.
And who knows when that might
literally be true, am I right?
[MEN laughing]
[MAN 17D]
Truth, man.
[NARRATOR] Subaru found
himself irresistibly drawn
to Koenig's promises
of wealth and happiness.
[KOENIG] The fact is, friends
allowing the Earth Union
to use us as pawns and
throw our lives away
in their war is
pretty damn pathetic
[SUBARU]
Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
[KOENIG]
Gotcha!
And we aren't the only ones
who think that way, either.
Right, Subaru?
Uh?
[MAN 17A]
Is that true, Lieutenant?
[SUBORDINATE 17A] Do you want
to talk about it, Subaru?
Sometimes I don't feel like I'm
in control of my own destiny.
Like all I'm doing is carrying
out someone else's orders.
Hey, you do more than that.
You're always saving our asses.
And you might be an incredibly
awkward, antisocial spaz
who's got an unhealthy
obsession with his cockpit,
but that's kind of your charm.
The Tiramisu wouldn't
be the same
without you and the Durandal.
We should all count ourselves
lucky that you're here.
He is right.
This job's really rough.
But I'm grateful that I met you,
Lieutenant Ichinose.
[SUBARU]
Grateful?
[MAN 17B]
Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
[SUBARU] These guys are
actually good people.
Have I been distancing myself
for no reason all this time?
Let's go, Subaru.
I'll teach you the secret to
controlling your own destiny.
[MEN laughing]
[NARRATOR] That's right:
they were all shills.
[SUBARU]
UHK. Isn't this
the Space Broadcasting
Corporation building?
[KOENIG] Yep. And the place
we're headed is nearby.
Doesn't get much more
legit than this, right?
[SUBARU]
Yeah. Totally legit.
[KOENIG] Trust me, Subaru,
you're in good hands.
Since this is your first time,
I'd like to demonstrate
some of the various products
that are available.
I get to try out all this stuff?
[KOENIG] Exactly. If you don't
know it's high-quality,
you can't recommend
it to others, right?
If we know our products
and can stand by them 100%,
then more people will join our
ranks and spread the word,
which benefits everybody.
Take this hand cream,
for example.
It's easy to mistake for
something sold in stores,
but it's actually a smash-hit
product of ours.
It's made entirely of
natural ingredients--
none of that artificial junk you
see so much of these days.
Well? Do you feel
the difference?
Yeah, totally. It's awesome.
I mean, I've never used hand
cream before, but still.
[SUBARU] This is the purest air
ever to caress my cheek!
That little baby's our top
seller in the Mars region.
A bit pricey,
but worth every cent.
[SUBARU] It's a completely
different color!
This cleaner's another of our
popular all-natural products.
And, hey, if you get thirsty...
[SUBARU]
No way!
So I just need to recommend
these amazing products
and get people to buy them?
I dunno, it seems practically
criminal for me to keep
a life-altering secret
like this to myself!
Lieutenant Leroy!
Whoa, you look rough.
[SUBARU] Listen, Lieutenant!
These pills are amazing!
They promote health and beauty--
I'm not interested.
No, wait, come back!
[SUBARU]
Vulgar. Hey, Vulgar! Vulgar!
What the heck's
gotten into Subaru?
Oh hey, Romeo! Perfect timing!
See this?
It's an organic pilot suit made
entirely of natural materials!
There's capsaicin infused
in the fabric,
which helps to
induce perspiration!
It'll make your skin as
soft as a baby's...
[ROMEO]
Something's very wrong here.
Wait. Is this one of those scams
they've been warning
people about?
You should come to
our next orientation!
[ROMEO]
Lieutenant!
[SUBARU]
Are you in?
If you bring a friend along with
you, the prices go way down.
Please, just listen to me.
I am honored to work with
you as your subordinate,
but I am not your friend, sir!
Uh?
[ROMEO]
It would be presumptuous
to consider myself
Subaru's friend.
But I'm sure that there are
people who can help you.
Who can steer you from this
dark path. Your real friends.
Uh. My... real... friends...?
[SUBARU] There's no one.
I don't have any friends!
[KOENIG] Come to think of it,
he's always alone.
[SUBARU gasping]
[KOENIG] It was cruel of me to
do this to you. You're free now.
[SUBARU cries]
I'm sorry.
[NARRATOR]
After coming to his senses,
Subaru decided to avoid
all human contact.
Friendless and alone,
he withdrew
even more deeply into the
sanctuary of his cockpit.