The buildings around
here look so similar,
it's starting to bum me out.
Shall I tear them to the ground
and rebuild this city
to more my liking?
Huh?
[BEYOND]
Hold on. Wasn't I just here?
[NARRATOR] On his first
authorized excursion outside
the safety of the lab, Beyond
visited a convenience store,
and got lost on the way home in
the maze of identical buildings.
[BEYOND laughs]
How fascinating.
So this is what it
means to be "lost."
They must've given me
such a haphazard map
so I could have
this novel experience.
[BEYOND]
Hm? What's this line for?
Ah, this must be the
infamous Ramen Saburo.
[BEYOND]
Oh, goodie!
I've been simply
dying to try it.
[NARRATOR] Beyond spent
a disproportionate amount
of his time reading
local restaurant reviews
on obnoxious foodie websites.
We'll see if this plebian
fare is suitable
for the palate of a god.
Hm?
[BEYOND] "Black oolong tea."
Heh, heh. Excellent.
[laughing] Perfect
beverage for a being
who drowns all around
him in blackest darkness.
[thud]
[EMPLOYEE A]
Welcome!
[BEYOND]
Another line? Ugh. Lame.
[EMPLOYEE A] Please buy a ticket
before you get back in line.
[BEYOND]
Ah, yes, I did read that Saburo
uses the ticket system.
[laughs] As if such
a feeble little trap
could trip up someone
with my divine abilities.
[BEYOND]
"Small"? I think not.
There's nothing
"small" about me.
For real?
Obviously a newbie.
Maybe he can't read?
[NARRATOR] Maybach was out
for a nice solo lunch,
so when he saw an acquaintance,
he scrupulously avoided
making eye contact.
[MAYBACH]
This is no place for a novice.
And he's making the same
mistake as Captain Suzie!
[BEYOND] Seems like a
typical ramen shop to me.
I see the water is self-service.
[BEYOND] They even make
their customers clean up?
Such arrogance!
And yet, he did it
without complaint.
Is that an indicator of
just how good this ramen is?
Here's my ticket.
[BEYOND laughing]
[BEYOND] Well, balls! I totally
forgot to present mine.
And now,
time to chant the
sacred incantation.
Bestow upon me a Large Veggie
Spicy Garlic Fat Mashi Mashi!
[MAYBACH grunts]
[NARRATOR] Maybach felt
every bit of embarrassment
that Beyond was too
oblivious to feel.
[MAYBACH]
Guess I shouldn't be surprised.
The dude is a clone of
Captain Suzie's little bro.
I'll take a Large Veggie
Spicy Garlic Fat Mashi Mashi.
[MAYBACH] They're screwin'
up in all the same ways!
Say how many noodles
and how al dente.
[BEYOND]
Huh?
Say how many
noodles and how al dente.
[BEYOND]
Uh, um... Uh, regular?
Okay, but... You sure
you want a large?
That's a lot. Can you finish it?
Uh. Heh, heh!
Do they not teach you
simpletons a god's stomach
is a black hole made
to devour anything?
Fine, don't say I
didn't warn you.
[BEYOND]
Hm?
Spicy!
Ugh. Yuck!
[EMPLOYEE A]
Sir?
Your order?
[BEYOND]
Uh... I...
[BEYOND] Do I do the toppings
incantation now?
Well, I'll, um, have...
[BEYOND] Bad time for
performance anxiety!
--[EMPLOYEE A] Sir.
--[BEYOND] Uh?
Were you still wanting to
order the large veggie
spicy garlic fat mashi mashi
like you said before?
Um, actually,
I'll just take a...
...regular.
[EMPLOYEE A grunts]
Uh?
[BEYOND] Huh? What the hell
is "regular" about this?
There are so many veggies
I can't see the noodles.
And what is that supposed to be?
Chashu? It's more than half fat!
[MAYBACH] Can't blame him
for gettin' the yips.
It's pretty daunting
for a Saburo virgin.
Even I worry about whether I can
finish, and I order the small!
Light on the noodles. Al dente.
[BEYOND] Maybe it's easier
to eat than it looks.
There was a woman
here, after all.
[MAYBACH] Oh, no!
He's making a rookie mistake!
Universe... Sense!
[BEYOND gasps]
[MAYBACH]
Listen to me, Beyond,
because I'm only
gonna say this once.
[BEYOND]
You!
[MAYBACH]
Don't start with the veggies.
Start with the noodles that
are absorbing the soup.
[BEYOND]
What? The noodles?
[gasps]
[EMPLOYEE A]
Here you go. One small ramen.
[BEYOND]
Uh.
Very interesting.
I believe I understand now.
Thank you for your assistance,
bulbus, hairy man.
[BEYOND]
This is good!
[MAYBACH] That's right.
Don't stop or your done for!
You just gotta keep eating!
[EMPLOYEE A]
Thank you, sir.
[BEYOND]
I've barely even made a dent.
You don't have to finish
all of it, you know.
No. I can finish a
single bowl of ramen.
I'm a damn god!
You really don't have
to prove anything.
[BEYOND gasping]
That's right, get outta
here, ya damn newbie.
[BEYOND cries]
[NARRATOR] At the first ramen
shop he had ever visited,
Beyond learned just how
harsh our society can be.
[BEYOND]
They don't know. I'm a god!
[ISUZU humming]
My god!
Who made messy? Seriously! Gah!
[NARRATOR]
And was forced to suffer alone,
haunted by a garlic stench that
lingered well into the next day.
[ISUZU]
That smell! Bleh!