[SUBARU] I must've been
out for a long time.
[SUBARU groans]
[SUBARU]
What's going on?
And why does it feel like
someone's staring at me?
[MAYBACH]
Captain Suzie.
Present.
Looks like Subaru B's awake.
He's what?
His Universe values
are off the charts.
I think it's safe to say he's
got the Neo Universe sense.
The mechanics finally finished
up the Hades Durandal,
and said he basically
ship-jacked them.
And now is on his way to Europa.
Guess he wants to
kill his original,
and that means your bro, bro.
Place is about to turn into a
warzone, know what I'm sayin'?
Indeed.
[SUBARU grunts]
[VULGAR]
There she is!
Hey. You're up.
Ahh! Please stop!
Who is inside my mind and
how do I get them out?!
You will now call me Beyond.
I am the copy human who was
born as a reflection of you.
And now he's... inside me?
[SUBARU B] I'm on my way to take
over your mecha and your life.
Go ahead and start saying
goodbye to your existence.
You're the buffed-out,
half-naked me.
[SUBARU B]
And don't even try to run away.
We're connected,
as one, you see.
Oh, could you make that half
fries and half onion rings?
Good idea.
[SUBARU B]
No need to be fri--
Huh?! No, don't change the size!
Just half fries, half rings!
[SUBARU gasps]
[SUBARU B]
Yes, I still want the drink!
But change it to something
exciting, like a melon juice.
[NARRATOR] Chasing after
Subaru is no easy task.
And I'm actually
in a hurry here.
How long do you think
it's gonna be?
If you make me wait too long---
[FAST FOOD WORKER 7A]
Thank you for your order!
Please proceed to
the next window!
[NARRATOR] So Beyond decided to
treat himself to a burger...?
[FAST FOOD WORKER 7A]
Your total today is 7.60!
The enemy's gonna
be here any minute.
I'll get you to the Neo Durandal
so you can escape ASAP.
You can hide from him,
but I won't.
[gasps]
You better go.
He's too strong for you.
What'd you say? Nice nightgown.
Hm?!
[VULGAR] Man, I hate it when he
makes those crazy-warrior eyes.
All right, fine.
But at least let me help
you to the roof, Mee-Maw.
Can I get fries after?
It's huge.
[SUBARU B laughs]
That's what she said.
Neo Durandal. Let's go!
This is neutral territory.
So, don't drag them into this!
[NARRATOR] And so began a
high-level exchange of thoughts
between two beings with
Neo Universe sense.
Mr. Weird Nipples thinks he
can tell me what to do?
Well that pisses me right off!
[NARRATOR] Subaru had to
cover his nipples--
even as an astral projection, he
was self-conscious about them.
[SUBARU screams]
[SUBARU B]
It's like being forced to stare
at all the flaws
I try to conceal.
You are everything
I hate about myself!
It'd be best for you
to just go away!
[HONAMARU EMPLOYEE 7A]
Order up!
Huge bowl of
cold noodles for ya!
[NARRATOR] Though Subaru and his
shiny-yet-angsty copy Beyond
were in the midst of some
heated mortal combat.
[HONAMARU EMPLOYEE 7A]
One magical medium kamatama !
[NARRATOR] They took a
break to enjoy the skills
of a topless astral Udon server.
They marveled at his work ethic
and joyful multitasking.
[BOTH gasp]
[SUBARU screams]
Hey! What's the
point of all this?
Why are you hating on me?
[SUBARU B]
You want a "point"?
I'm doing this
because I want to.
I know that you sense it, too.
We live in a world of endless
drudgery and annoyances.
Every day we breathe is for
some pain in the ass mission
we didn't choose for ourselves.
You have to change yourself,
or change someone else.
You must follow the rules.
You must make them up.
Why do we do any
of these things?!
When they're such
a pain in the ass?
Pain in the ass!
Pain in the ass...!
Even when you're
a god like me,
life is one blistered
pain in the ass.
And that's why I'm
going to end this world...
[SUBARU]
Man, this guy's lost it.
[SUBARU B]
...and I'll start with you!
Are you ready to begin?
Buckle up,
we're going for a ride.
[NARRATOR] It could have been
the perfect button
to that rollercoaster
of a monologue.
Why'd I have to lock the door?
[NARRATOR] But because
of some newb mistake,
Beyond was unable to burst
through the door to his cockpit.
Did you just lock
the door on yourself?
Shut up! That's not how
you speak to a god!
You shouldn't assume I
don't know what's going on.
I might've planned it.
Remember the last time you
doubted me and then almost died?
[SUBARU grunts]
[SUBARU B]
Oh. Look what I found!
[SUBARU]
Why would he call a locksmith
if he meant to
lock himself out?!
[SUBARU B] Right. As soon
as possible, please.
You got it. We're pretty close,
so we should be there very soon.
Kids.
[NARRATOR] Beyond did, indeed,
contact the closest locksmith.
Their office was located in
the Hades Durandal's knee.
[sighs]
--[LOCKSMITH 7A] Hello?
--[SUBARU B gasps]
[LOCKSMITH 7A] Are you the one
who called about the door?
Yeah. You guys are fast.
[LOCKSMITH 7A] Well, our office
is just a few doors down.
So, which one is being stubborn?
[SUBARU B grunts]
That'll do it.
Well, you definitely
locked yourself out.
You've also got a wad
of gum stuck in the hole.
Huh?
[LOCKSMITH 7A] It's probably
those Europa kids.
They're big fans of
this stupid prank.
[SUBARU B] They just go around
putting gum in holes?
Yeah. What are they
supposed to do--read?
Looks like you're gonna
need a new door buddy.
Are you serious?
[LOCKSMITH 7A]
It's gonna be great.
Why don't you head back
to Metus for a bit?
We can get you to the cockpit
through our office.
[SUBARU B growls]
Don't you dare judge me!
Virgin-boy!
[SUBARU gasps]
Could you bring us down
a little faster?
Sure thing.
[NARRATOR] Beyond retreated
to Metus temporarily
while his door was
being replaced.
While Subaru believed he endured
the biggest "WTF"
moment of his life.
He called me a virgin out loud.
[SUBARU] Maybach's nips are
always so on point these days.
[MAYBACH]
Um. I can hear you, you freak.
[SUBARU]
Aw, crap!
I forgot my thoughts
are audible now!
I'm so sorry!
[MAYBACH] And yesterday
you thought they looked
like bird beaks. Rude.
[SUBARU] That wasn't me!
I thought acorns!