[NARRATOR] After a hard-fought
battle on Europa,
Vulgar was promoted
to Lieutenant,
and Subaru was promoted
from Ensign to LTJG.
[PAC2-AR] Congratulations!
This is a huge deal!
[SUBARU]
Meh, ranks don't mean that much.
Besides... I suck.
I didn't do anything.
Not even tell him what
a whack job he was.
[SUBARU grunts] I shouldn't
even be a pilot--
much less a Lieutenant.
[PAC2-AR] Well, you're a Junior
Lieutenant, but you earned it!
Oh, that reminds me.
The first mission given to the
LTJG is the ship newsletter page
and I'm pretty sure
it's due today.
[SUBARU]
Yeah, yeah. I know.
[PAC2-AR] I'm so excited to see
what topic you cho-- Uh!
[NARRATOR] Subaru had begun
to doubt himself as a pilot.
He felt a comic
with no real point
would be appropriate
and symbolic.
Kinda like this show...
Reading it was so torturous
that even PAC2-AR,
Subaru's loyal supporter,
couldn't read it
without shuddering.
Done-zo.
Could you scan that and
send it off for me please?
[PAC2-AR]
Okay.
[NARRATOR]
However,
Subaru's "Floating Boy
Zero George" comic
was a hit with the crew.
Turns out the stress of war
slows the mind down just enough.
[CREWMEMBER 8A]
Hey, there's Mr. Funny Britches.
--[SUBARU] Huh?
--Love your comic!
I'm obsessed!
You're so talented!
You better not die before
you finish the series, man!
[SUBARU gasps]
[SUBARU]
No way. Do I have talent?
[NARRATOR]
Thought Subaru.
And so he drew and drew
and drew some more!
He even started writing real
storylines--with plots.
Before he knew it, his cockpit
had become his studio.
Look who's here.
You takin' a day off
from sorties?
Where the hell have you been?
Uh, no. At the supply vessel.
Are you kidding?!
This is all because princess
needs his snacks?
Look, no one likes that
mecha on steroids, all right?
But a battleship isn't
the place to have
your little slumber parties!
I'm not gonna do
your job for you!
And neither is anyone
else on this ship!
Got that... Junior Lieutenant?
[SUBARU]
Uh...
Oh, you think I can't do more
than one job at a time?!
Whatever, just leave me alone!
Run to mommy!
[SUBARU] He may have a
higher rank than I do,
but that doesn't
give him any right
to take away a man's dreams!
[NARRATOR] Subaru headed
straight to a manga publisher
on a nearby planet
to submit his manuscript...
unsolicited.
[EDITOR 8A]
There he is!
Your manuscript was a trip.
I thought it was
another space fantasy,
but then I was like, "oh,
this is some serious drama."
That's why I'm writing as
Hoshigahara, it's serious.
[EDITOR 8A]
And that spazzy one!
He cracks me up!
Every time he says this,
I die. I absolutely die!
Thank you so much, sir.
[EDITOR 8A]
But it's not enough.
I need more than a catchphrase
with some "feeling"
moments, ya know?
Your world design isn't
fully flushed out.
And where are
the hot chicks? Seriously.
I need a clear target audience,
and you're not givin' it to me.
[gasps]
Mr. Hoshino, your resume
says you're a pilot, so--
Hoshigahara.
[EDITOR 8A]
Tomato, tomata.
Point is, isn't being a pilot
a "cool" job? You know...
[NARRATOR]
After his dreams were crushed,
and his eyes became those
of a dried-out fish,
Subaru found release by
destroying 20 enemy craft
on his way back to base.
It's close-quarters combat now.
Big girl time.
That's probably the only way
to subdue them
without casualties.
[VULGAR]
Yeah, so don't mess yourself.
[SUBARU] No matter how
much experience I have
with close quarters,
I'd still rather not fight
outside my cockpit.
[gasps]
[SUBARU grunts]
I swear, if you got hit--
[SUBARU]
I didn't! Shut up!
[VULGAR]
We're goin' on my signal!
Roger that!
[SUBARU]
Mother of pearl!
Those jerks ripped my suit!
Great, the needle's missing.
Ready, Powder Puff?
[SUBARU]
No! How am I gonna do this?
[VULGAR]
Three! Two!
[SUBARU]
Just hold on! BRB!
[VULGAR]
Are you kidding?!
You can't leave!
I didn't give the order!
I'm coming back, just chill!
[SUBARU]
All right, Subaru.
Make it quick!
[NARRATOR] He put the battle
on pause while he fled
to a pilot suit store
on the nearest planet.
[SUBARU] Literally anything
in my size will work.
Please say they have my size!
[SUBARU]
Uh?
[ROBOT EMPLOYEE]
Welcome, sir.
If you tell me what you need,
I can help you find it.
I just need a new top.
But I need it right away.
Think you can you help me?
[ROBOT EMPLOYEE] Absolutely.
We got this one in yesterday.
Its blend of fabrics that
gives a lot of movement...
I don't need it to move,
I just need it to fit!
Hurry, throw it on!
[ROBOT EMPLOYEE]
You got it!
[SUBARU gasps]
For real?
I didn't mean literally.
[ROBOT EMPLOYEE] Looser tops
are so hot this season.
Everyone who's anyone is
wearing it loose, amiright?
[SUBARU]
That slimy sack of tin.
He's just saying
that so I'll buy it!
It doesn't even match my pants!
[SUBARU]
Be honest!
Which one of these
would best match my top?
Crap! It has to match
or I'll look like a tool,
but thinking of Vulgar
snarling while waiting
gives me tummy knots.
[ROBOT EMPLOYEE]
Ohh, excellent choice!
I have both pairs at home
and I love them!
[SUBARU gasps]
[ROBOT EMPLOYEE] We call
those a "closet convenience,"
because they're so convenient
to have in your closet--
they go with everything!
[SUBARU] You don't wear pants,
you're not even a real boy!
Look, I need a suit! Now!
My comrade's waiting for me!
[NARRATOR] Hold on a second,
did he say "comrade"?
Was that a mistake...?
I-I'm staying out of it.
[SUBARU] Nah, I'm using
this dressing room!
[ROBOT EMPLOYEE]
Ooh...
--So, what do you think?
--[SUBARU] What the...?!
Go away! I didn't say
you could come in!
What are you staring at?!
[NARRATOR] The machine
at the store couldn't read
Subaru's membership QR code.
His items were packed
with excessive care,
and time continued
to waste away.
[SUBARU] You're like a
mechanical slug, I swear.
Here, it's fine. I'll carry
it myself, thank you!
[SUBARU grunting]
[SUBARU]
Great, what now?
[ROBOT EMPLOYEE] Allow me to
carry this to the exit for you.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Vulgar
gave up on waiting for Subaru.
And managed things on his own.
[VULGAR] All right, Pee Pants,
I've got a new nickname for ya.
[SUBARU]
Good. Just remember,
it needs to be cool and
have a space-like vibe.
[VULGAR]
You got it, Princess.
How about "Our Little
Space Slugger"?
[SUBARU]
What? I'm not freakin' nine!