[phone vibrates]
[SUBARU]
Dad?
That isn't like him.
[yawns]
[ISUZU] The old man?
I'll just ignore it.
We're gonna get in there
and cut off their supplies
to the front lines. Things are
gonna go "boom," people.
Our missions are never easy,
and this one's no different.
So grab those nuts
and get ready to man up.
Ensign Aixam, you and I will
take a team and infiltrate
the Union base, then stand
by at these locations.
Captain Suzie,
you'll plant time bombs
on their underground
energy pipes.
That's the "boom" part
I was talkin' about.
The rest of us will
create a diversion
to buy time while you escape.
Get in. get out--
quick, like lightning.
Got it? Hello?
Come on, We're in a freakin'
meeting here, Suzie.
If you're gonna dick
around on your phone,
at least have the
decency to hide it.
[MAYBACH] I've sent the field
data to each of your devices,
so take a sec to confirm
you received them.
[phone vibrating]
[MAYBACH] Check the video files
to make sure you can play them.
If you can't, then
obviously you're an idiot
who doesn't know how
to operate a smartphone.
[ISUZU growls]
[STICKER VOICE]
Arf! Gotcha!
[gasps]
Now, moving on.
[ISUZU]
Damn you, you old bitch.
[STICKER VOICE]
Arf! Gotcha,
If you're gonna send a sticker,
pick one that's not some
freaky unicorn dog.
[ISUZU] Both of you, talk about
this stuff in a different chat!
The notifications
are driving me crazy,
and you're draining my battery.
Man, Isuzu types really fast.
Mad skills.
[STICKER VOICE]
Arf! Gotcha.
[sighs]
[ISUZU]
All right, it's time.
[ISUZU] Maybach, how will we be
communicating in the field?
We're just gonna use our phones.
Less chance of making mistakes
if we've got devices
we know well.
Understood. Let's get this
show on the road, then.
Yes sir.
[MAYBACH]
I'm in position. Standing by.
[ISUZU]
Done.
I've placed the bombs. All hands
begin diversionary tactics.
What now?
[SUBARU]
The hell?!
What are you doing, Isuzu?
Bomb jokes aren't funny.
Totally not cool.
[ISUZU] Balls! I accidentally
sent that to Subaru instead.
[STICKER VOICE]
Arf! Just kidding.
[ISUZU]
He fell for it!
[ISUZU] Damn it! I still
had the group chat open!
[ISUZU]
Not good!
I have to do something!
[STICKER VOICE]
Arf! Gotcha!
What the--?!
You traitor!
Ha, got it! How long's
that thing been up there?
I think somethin' went wrong.
Union troops are pouring
in all over the damn place.
We gotta get out of here. Now!
[ISUZU]
Idiots! I want a new family!
The way they came out
of nowhere like that,
it was like they knew exactly
what we were up to.
I hate to say it, but I think we
may have a spy in our midst.
Captain Suzie?
[ISUZU] The op failed thanks
to your meddling, Dad.
You better make this up to me!
[SOICHIRO] A parent's gotta
stop his son from villainy!
[ISUZU]
Oh, now you're a parent?
[MAYBACH]
My superior officer is the leak?
[NARRATOR] Maybach decided to
pretend he'd never seen Isuzu's
messages and that the whole
thing had never happened.
[sighs] What ev's.
[STICKER VOICE]
Arf! Bye-bye!