[ROMEO grunting]
[NARRATOR] After Cadillac's
public address,
fighting between the Earth Union
and the People of Metus
grew fiercer each day.
What's happening?!
Your piloting sucks.
You're way too stiff.
[ROMEO]
Right! Okay!
[ROMEO] I messed up and
now Subaru's mad at me.
Balls.
Get it together.
It's my job to support him!
Their stronghold's over there.
We're gonna end this
with the Durandal Riser.
No time for a dry run.
Can you handle it?
Yes, sir. I can.
On it!
[NARRATOR] While battling the
new "People of Metus" weapons,
the Earth Union
had launched a plan
to strengthen the Neo Durandal.
Lieutenant!
Get ready!
[NARRATOR] With the D Riser
as its support mecha,
the Neo Durandal gained
new capabilities.
[ROMEO] All right, time for
some "awesome sauce"!
I'll whip this D into
Subaru's wings!
[NARRATOR]
But his "D," as the kids say,
looked more like a
random protrusion
than a pair of wings.
I guess where I go when
we combine is already set.
That's good to know.
[ROMEO] Hey Lieutenant,
do you actually need me here
or are you good?
No one told me it would look
like this when we transform.
[SUBARU] Like what?
A huge space robo dong?
Listen, If you're wienering out,
can you transfer flight
control to me?
Um, well, I...
[ROMEO]
What do I do?
Leave? Or stay?
[ROMEO gasping]
[ROMEO]
What's wrong with me?!
I need to watch
and learn from him!
It's the only way I'll
become a first-rate pilot!
Screw that! I'm seein'
this through to the end!
[SUBARU]
Atta girl!
Preparing to fire
the Mega-Photon Canon.
I'll count down from three
and we'll pull our triggers
at the same time!
Roger that!
[SUBARU] The Durandal
will handle piloting
and attitude control.
You adjust the coordinates!
[ROMEO]
Yes, sir!
[SUBARU]
Here we go!
[ROMEO]
Please let me hit the mark.
Shut up. Mother says
to be confident!
And go!
[ROMEO]
Uh?
What? "Go"?
He never said there was a "go"!
I thought we pulled after "one"!
[NARRATOR] While they did
manage to fire the cannon.
The shot was completely
off due to bad timing
and some early triggering.
If I had a nickel...
[SUBARU]
C'mon! You had one job!
--[sizzling]
--[gasps]
Hot! My ass feels like it's
being flambéed by a demon!
What the hell?!
Why is my ass so damn hot?
[beeps]
My biscuits! They're burning!
[BOTH]
This sucks!
[NARRATOR]
While those two were pondering
the temperature of their asses,
Isuzu received a new model
of his personal mecha,
the Kerukeion Two.
I hope you're ready,
Captain Suzie!
It's finally done.
Very good work, Axium.
Let's go check this beast out.
[ISUZU] I can do it by myself,
you know.
[MAYBACH]
And I believe in you,
but just think how cool
I'll make you look
[ISUZU]
Fine. Whatevs.
Oh come on! You too?
Hey, don't freak out. I was
just keepin' it warm for ya.
[ISUZU]
While plugged in?
Well, what do you think of it?
Aw man, if I called it awesome,
it wouldn't be enough.
[MAYBACH]
One machine,
controlled by three minds,
plugged into headless devices.
Sounds like some kind of
mythical, three-headed dragon.
This whole cockpit's
like one bad-A monster
with zero blind spots.
I guess we are, too.
Now that we've got these
sweet, sweet implants.
[MAYBACH groaning]
That right there is
what's frickin up!
It like, takes all of your fear
and evaporates it right
before a battle.
You feel so invincible.
Know what I mean?
[MAYBACH]
Uh. Since when is he quiet?
[gasps]
[MAYBACH] Oh man,
he's not even plugged in!
Is he using his device to
hang his damn receipts?!
[MAYBACH]
Uh. Captain Suzie?
What are you doing?
Please, no.
What the-- Dude!
You didn't have
the implant surgery?!
I'm freakin' out!
Please don't.
I wasn't feeling it.
[MAYBACH gasping]
[ISUZU] Just looking at
the clinic reading materials
made my nads go turtle on me.
I'm sorry, okay?
Yeah. Sorry doesn't
really solve this.
Hey. What's goin' on, bros?
This nipple-baby got
scared of some pictures
and didn't get a plug-in.
Are you serious right now?!
Look. I didn't just
get scared, you guys.
I also find it extremely unfair
that our insurance
won't cover it.
Can you actually hear
yourself right now?
I think I might have to puke.
For real.
We all knew about the insurance
issue from the start.
Yeah, but you probably
didn't read that nightmare.
It didn't bother you you
can't roll on your back
for three days after?
Aixam and I both slept
on our stomachs
and lived to tell about it!
The only reason we synced
like this in the first place
is because you
aren't Universing!
Uh?
Fine! You're right,
and I'm wrong!
Gimme it! You're right!
I should just stab myself!
Who cares if it kills me?!
Is this what you want?
As long as you're happy!
No, wait!
Don't, you're
our captain, Suzie!
Let go!
[ISUZU]
Get off me!
[beeping]
[ALL gasping]
[ALL]
That was close!
[ALL laughing]
[NARRATOR] It was the Kerukeion
Two's Hyper Mega firing
that brought everyone back
to their senses that day.
[MAYBACH]
Captain Suzie, take this.
I got it from that
Flamingo bakery.
Their bread always sells
out way before noon.
I'll stab it on here so
you don't hurt yourself.
Are you sure?
Totally! I mean, it's in a bag
so we can still eat it later.
Wow. Feels nice.
[MAYBACH]
That makes me happy.
[AIXAM]
We ready to take off?
[NARRATOR] The drama, tantrums,
and uncomfortable laughter
was part of what Isuzu's unit
had experienced daily.
The team motto has become,
"it's just the way he is."
All right. Let's go!
[AIXAM, MAYBACH]
Yes, sir!
[SUBARU]
Hurry Romeo, time's almost up!
[ROMEO]
I know! I just...
I can't do it!
[SUBARU]
Hey. I believe in you.
[ROMEO]
You do?
[SUBARU]
Sure. Say it, "I know I can."
[ROMEO]
Okay. I know I can.
I know I can...
[ROMEO, SUBARU]
...I can flip this pancake!