[BEYOND growling]
Situation normal.
Isn't that right?
Heh. Oh, yeah? Come with me.
There's something
I'd like to show you.
What's the point of
bringing me here?
Are we having a picnic?
You really didn't think
this through.
I could drown this place
in a sea of blood.
It'd be adorable to watch you
try that while we're here.
Mythologia...
It's said that the discovery
of this monolith was
the birth of
the People of Metus.
I believe the text
we see here is
the last of Grand Mars's wisdom.
Huh?
If the Isuzu Squad can
finish deciphering it,
we'll be able to revolutionize
the entire universe.
[BEYOND]
Huh?
It's a glorious plan.
I'll start a revolution and
change Metus from the ground up.
[BEYOND laughing]
That was a joke, right?
Uh, no. This is why
we've been researching you
and others who have it.
Artificial Universe Sense.
I'm getting hangry.
Let's discuss details
over nom noms.
There's this cute
revolving sushi bar
over there I want you to try.
[NARRATOR]
Why am I never invited to sushi?
[BEYOND]
I've heard of these before.
You grab the sushi
before it glides away!
[BEYOND laughing]
[BEYOND]
That sounds fun!
Usually they're so--
Oh. I almost fell for it.
They're trying to trap me
with good times
and sushi fellowshipping.
Too bad, so sad.
They better not take forever
to seat us, I swear.
[MAYBACH]
I'll take care of it.
[BEYOND] Even monkeys could
come up with a better plan.
[BEYOND]
That's fine.
We can pretend you're
clever for the moment.
You guys!
I'm in a good mood today--
so all your sushi's on me!
[NARRATOR] To Maybach,
the only thing worse than
a "performance announcement"
in restaurants
was the birthday sombrero.
[BEYOND]
There it goes.
It really is revolving.
I'm impressed that
this brilliance
--was created by humans.
--[ISUZU slurping]
[gasps]
[BEYOND] There's more
than just sushi here!
[BEYOND laughing]
[BEYOND]
Human greed knows no bounds,
even when it comes to noodles.
Uh?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What is this machine
of magic and wonder?
That was a tiny sushi train!
Oh, revolving sushi place,
I think I'm starting to
have feelings for you.
You're my emotional
support animal.
That's what you want me
to say, isn't it?
[ALL]
Hm?
[ISUZU] Let's continue our
discussion from earlier.
Using the knowledge we're
gathering from the monolith,
we'll develop new and
improved mobile suits.
The new system will turn
each of the pilot's cells
into its own control device. Uh?
[ISUZU]
Rude! He's not even listening!
He cares more about his pickled
ginger than the new suits!
[ISUZU]
Uh?!
Why's he taking
the fish off the rice?
And dipping it in... Ah!
My eye thingy is not your
personal sushi bath!
[BEYOND groans]
You eat that rice like an adult!
Don't be a bitch!
[ALL gasp]
That thing only comes on
if there's an emergency.
[ISUZU]
Cadillac?
What's so huge he needed to make
a universe-wide broadcast?
We'll see. But it can't
be good, boss.
Never is.
[METUS CITIZENS cheering]
[CADILLAC]
People of Metus!
The Chosen People!
Do you remember
a time when you witnessed
the flames of revolution rising?
I know I haven't! Not yet!
I will see them for the first
time today along with you!
[METUS CITIZENS cheering]
Because of the
Mythologia monument,
I have been granted
ultimate wisdom!
No way! Who told
king farts about it?
[CADILLAC] This wisdom
has given me the power
to free you all from the
needless bloodshed of war!
Mark my words, I will end it!
And it will be us.
Our people will break
the chain of sorrow!
Sanguis! Os! Metus!
[METUS CITIZENS]
Sanguis! Os! Metus! Sanguis...
[NARRATOR]
And now, a momentary pause
and deep breath as we
dive a little deeper
into the character of
Commander Cadillac.
[DRIVER 10A]
Where do I go now, sir?
Sir! Sir!
Huh? Let's see.
Turn right at the cram school
with the yellow sign.
Just up there.
[DRIVER 10A]
One right turn, coming up!
[CADILLAC]
Shelby? I'm home!
Let's finish our discussion
from this morning!
Welcome home, sir,
the lady has gone out.
She's attending her class
reunion this evening.
Didn't she just have a class
reunion yesterday?
What's the point of graduating
if she won't leave?
Something's seriously
wrong with her! Huh?
She left that book
for you and said
she's enjoyed it for
the last several days
and highly recommends
you read it.
[CADILLAC]
Hmph.
[toots]
[CADILLAC]
Not again!
She knows surprising me
gives me the toot scoots!
I think I'd like to have
dinner now, Everett.
Absolutely, sir.
I'll have something delivered.
I don't want delivery.
I think I'll cook tonight.
It'll be a nice distraction.
Where are those boiled
greens from yesterday?
[EVERETT]
I'm sorry, sir.
The only food we have
in the refrigerator
is some pears I peeled earlier.
That's hardly a dinner.
I see. So this is what
my life has come to.
I've been pared down to pears.
Hmph. Everett, I'm going out.
Enjoy your evening, sir.
[CADILLAC] I'd like ten of
the scratch-off tickets, please.
They're all scratch-off tickets.
Better split it
with me if you win.
[CADILLAC]
You and my wife both, huh.
[CADILLAC] Ugh!  I don't have
anything to scratch these with!
[CADILLAC]
Omega Universe Sense, engage!
Huh?
Only 500 yen? But I still won.
[NARRATOR]
They say on a calm night,
you can still hear the Commander
scratching his... tickets?
[BEYOND]
Subaru!
I am the darkness that will
extinguish your light.
[SUBARU]
Shut up!
[BEYOND laughing]
I will not!
I am the jumbo and
you are the shrimp!
I'm big and you are small!
[SUBARU]
Seriously?
Jumbo and shrimp are
an oxymoron, like you!