[PAC2-AR]
Subaru! Hey, Subaru!
[VULGAR]
Move your ass, Princess.
We're goin' to the Ashigara!
[LIGIER] Yeah, we can
head there together.
I can't just leave in the middle
of Durandal's
maintenance routine.
I'll meet you there later.
But you don't want to
miss out on all the fun!
Yeah, jeez. Is it hard to hear
with your head up your ass?
[SUBARU sighs]
Uh.
Hold on. What's this?
[SUBARU gasps]
[SUBARU]
It's looks like... a bouquet?
[NARRATOR] That's right.
Today, September 2nd,
was ace pilot Subaru
Ichinose's 20th birthday.
[SUBARU]
Those sneaky sneak-faces!
That's why they wanted me to
come with them to the Ashigara.
They usually know
to give me my space,
so obviously this is
for a special occasion.
[NARRATOR] The Ashigara was a
supply vessel-slash-party barge
equipped with restaurants
and event spaces.
[SUBARU] And... done. I've
finished my maintenance,
so I guess I'll just be heading
over to the Ashigara now.
[SUBARU] They've clearly
calculated the perfect degree
of surprise-i-tude.
This way, it's still exciting,
but I won't get all freaked out
when they spring the trap.
Those guys are the best!
[bell chimes]
[CLERK 14A]
Be right with you!
[SUBARU]
This is the perfect spot.
I'll just stand here,
casually reading a comic,
and wait for them to see me.
[SUBARU]
No one's come to get me.
It's mean to keep me
in suspense for so long.
I wonder what's wrong.
Maybe they set aside a special
first legal drink and Vulgar
chugged it himself then started
hitting on women and got
punched in the face then
passed out in his own sick.
That's it. I'm going
to go check on them.
[SUBARU]
I didn't see them anywhere.
What's going on?
Was I totally off-base?
[music plays]
[VULGAR]
5... 6... 7... 8...
Yeah.
[music continues]
[SUBARU]
I know what this is!
One of those flash-mob things!
[SUBARU] They choreographed
a dance number just for me!
Wait...
[LIGIER chattering]
[SUBARU]
Huh? Huh?!
Huh...?!
If this is my birthday surprise
then why isn't anybody
looking at me?!
[ALL]
Way to go!
Congrats on your marriage!
Thanks so much!
What a great surprise!
You sons a bitches!
That was great! Thanks, guys.
[PAC2-AR] Here's to a long
and happy life together!
Hip-hip-hooray!
It really worked?
You were surprised?
[AVANTI]
Are you kidding? Totally!
[SUBARU] I was surprised
the surprise wasn't for me.
[PAC2-AR] I'm so proud of
everybody coming together
to make this a success!
Almost the entire crew
is here to celebrate.
[SUBARU]
No one told me.
[gasps]
[SUBARU]
Okay. Some couple got married,
and that's relevant to me how?
[SUBARU]
That email!
How was I supposed to know
it was something important?
[CREW chattering]
[PAC2-AR] Their happiness
is contagious, isn't it?
[SUBARU]
♪ Happy birthday to me ♪
♪ Happy birthday dear ♪
♪ Lieutenant Junior Grade
Subaru Ichinose ♪
[SUBARU]
Why am I even here?
Why was I born in
the first place?
Nobody seems to care.
It's like they don't
even need me.
[beeping]
[SUBARU]
Uh. An enemy attack? Now?
Subaru Ichinose,
sortieing in the Durandal!
[SUBARU]
How did so many of them get here
without anyone noticing?
They're all too busy with
their dumb surprise party.
No one even noticed
it was my birthday!
I deserve a celebration, too!
[SUBARU yells]
[SUBARU]
I should've known.
They don't care about me!
You're my only friend, Durandal.
That's it!
[MECHS]
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Subaru ♪
[DURANDAL] Let's hear it
for Subaru, everyone.
Aw, you shouldn't have!
[DURANDAL]
Go on. Blow out the candles.
Yeah!
[inhales, exhales]
God bless us, everyone.
[NARRATOR] Subaru turned 20
and earned his big-boy pants.
But with them came the
knowledge that adulthood
was a bleak and lonely time.
And that the only people
you can count on
to give a crap
about your birthday
are the dysfunctional
weirdos you call family.