[OPERATOR 4A] The mobile suit
squad has been wiped out!
But how?
There was only one unit!
So that's what Metus is
swingin' around these days.
What the hell's wrong
with you, Subaru?
Get back here.
[CALLAWAY]
Mr. Isuzu?
For some reason,
I knew you'd be here.
Good for you.
You know I don't approve
of entering enemy territory
during a test flight.
Yes, I'm sorry.
But... I wasn't
afraid of injuries.
I figured if I could at
least make you smile,
it would be worth it.
[ISUZU] Yeah, because I love
pilots with death wishes.
Whatevs.
Can't copy those with artificial
Universe Sense, anyway.
Uh. Sorry.
I'm not mad at you, okay?
A drink for the lady, please.
[BARTENDER 4A]
You got it, boss.
[cocktail shaker rattles]
Ever had a gimlet?
It matches the color
of your eyes perfectly.
Oh, how fancy!
You should name your mecha that.
In commemoration of
your premier battle.
That's a good idea.
[ISUZU]
Take Subaru B.
His senses haven't
fully developed yet.
He was put on
the field too soon.
I won't make that
mistake again with you.
I feel confident that
you're ready to fight.
And I'm glad you're safe.
Thank you, sir.
[CALLAWAY] You saw something
in me when I was nothing.
You're the one who
brought me this far,
and for that, I will
always be grateful.
Ready to close out, boss?
[NARRATOR]
After he returned from Earth...
[ISUZU]
Yes, I think so.
And we'll be paying separately.
[NARRATOR]
Isuzu learned to budget
even when it made
things awkward.
[CALLAWAY]
Seriously...?
[ISUZU]
I'll take a receipt for mine.
[CALLAWAY] I just came in to
report on my battle results.
He's the one who
ordered the damn drink.
[CALLAWAY gasps]
[CALLAWAY] I thought only
children had Velcro wallets?
I always pictured Mr. Isuzu
with a classic, crocodile skin
billfold, but maybe this one
holds sentimental value
from his childhood?
[BARTENDER 4A]
All right, miss, here you go.
[CALLAWAY]
It was just one drink.
It can't be more than--
[BARTENDER 4A]
One gimlet plus nuts... 1580.
[CALLAWAY]
What nuts?!
I didn't even eat any nuts!
[ISUZU] Go ahead and put
all the points on this card.
[CALLAWAY]
He's stealing the points?
[CALLAWAY groaning]
[CALLAWAY]
I'm fine. I won't hate Mr. Isuzu
over a drink and some
nuts I didn't even want!
It's fine!
[CALLAWAY grunts]
I didn't realize she was
such a lightweight.
What happened?
Well, look who's sober.
Where are we?
[ISUZU] The Kerukeionm,
where it's awesome!
Rest here as long as you need.
You brought me
to your cockpit?
[stomach growls]
[ISUZU]
I heard that.
You shouldn't be drinking
on an empty stomach.
I guess I should've
asked if you'd eaten.
Here. These are good.
[CALLAWAY]
He cares!
Oh. Wait.
[NARRATOR] It was December
of Space Age 0157.
Is it cool if I grab
the sticker from it first?
[NARRATOR] And Isuzu was
still a miserly tool.
I think I just need three more.
You send in the points and
they give you one of those
cute bunny plates.
Oh, yeah?
How fun for you...
[NARRATOR]
'Twas the night before Subaru
was launched back into space.
A small assist bot was stirring,
from a decision she'd made.
She left a note and
said her goodbyes.
It would be hard to depart
from the hero's side.
And scene.
[PAC2-AR]
Please take care, Mr. Subaru.
Since you've found
newer equipment,
there's no connecter
I can interface with.
I'm just an obsolete
robot to you now.
[PAC2-AR] But I've always
wondered what it would be like
to sit here and yank
on this lever thingie!
[NARRATOR]
In case there was any question,
PAC2-AR's mentality was like
that of an eight-year-old child.
[PAC2-AR]
Check me out sortieing in
the Neo Durandal like a beast!
Boop, beep, boink, beep!
[PAC2-AR laughs]
Huh? Uh-oh, did I
turn something on?
[PAC2-AR gasping]
Welcome and Greetings
from Lexus2000,
the Neo Durandal's AI.
[PAC2-AR]
I didn't mean to wake you up.
It's all right.
But you do not appear
to be Subaru Ichinose.
In which case, I hope
you don't mind,
but I'd like to air
a few complaints.
[PAC2-AR] Sure. Let's talk
about your feelings.
[LEXUS2000]
It's Subaru.
Once he realized I was
his personal mecha,
he started slapping
me with stickers.
And well, I don't like it.
[PAC2-AR]
Huh. Sounds like he was sharing
his playful side with you.
C'mon, Lex, an advanced
program such as yourself
doesn't let stuff like
that get to him, right?
Why not, I'm an AI?
Any entity capable of
thought can become upset.
We're programmed...
[PAC2-AR] Wow, so if great AIs
with majestic character design
can have problems,
then I'm doin' all right.
Ah... It feels like
my battery's dyi--
[SUBARU]
Wakey-Wakey!
Can't waste the day
in sleep mode.
[PAC2-AR]
Subaru...?
--[SUBARU] Hm?
--[PAC2-AR gasps]
[SUBARU]
Uh?
[PAC2-AR]
Where's Lex?!
I don't know what that means.
Is that someone from Dream Town?
[PAC2-AR]
Oh. Maybe it was?
I forgot about that. Subaru, I--
[SUBARU] And what's with
the dramatic break-up note?
I don't care if you can't
connect well with the interface.
Who'll be my lil cockpit
buddy if you go?
[PAC2-AR]
You really mean that?
Subaru.
I need your help, not
as a pilot, but as a...
...as an Ichinose,
please bring that
powder puff back home.
Already on it, Papa.
[NARRATOR]
In December of Space Age 0157,
Subaru and PAC2-AR made
their return to space.
[SOICHIRO]
Hmm, there it is again.
This song keeps getting
stuck in my head.
[SUBARU]
The Durandal song?
Yeah, I'll be step touch and
snappin' to it in my head
even when the captain
is yelling at me.
[SOICHIRO]
It's only the best song ever.
[SUBARU]
Oh, it's like a one hit wonder!