Jadeite!
You have already failed
twice. There will be
consequences.
I'm very sorry.
Well the monsters
you create are just
clay dolls, aren't they?
[gasp]
Of course they're
going to be weak.
Queen Beryl, please
allow me, Nephrite,
your loyal general,
to succeed where
Jadeite has failed.
I can gather even more
energy for our Great
Ruler, and do it
more efficiently.
And I'll get my hands
on the Legendary Silver
Crystal.
You can be certain of it.
Certain? Are you sure?
What if those Sailor
Guardians show up
again?
Zoisite...
For all we know, they
may be after the Legendary
Silver Crystal as well.
Queen Beryl, if I may be
so bold as to ask, what
exactly is this Legendary
Silver Crystal?
Why is it so important?
The Legendary Silver
Crystal is a stone that is
the source of all energy.
I have been told it has
unfathomable, limitless
power. And that the one
who wields it will
become the ruler of
the entire universe!
[gasps]
But for now, do
not worry about
it.
Our priority is to rid
ourselves of those
who would interfere.
I will give you one last
chance, Jadeite.
Yes, my queen.
I will go myself and
eliminate the Sailor
Guardians.
No matter what.
It's coming. Something's
coming. I can sense it.
Something evil is
about to unleash
chaos on our world.
Today was fun, Rei!
Can I come back
again tomorrow?
Sure. Get home safe
now, Mii. Be careful.
I will! Bye!
Have you guys heard the
latest rumor? About
the Demon Bus?
Yeah! I heard it's
the bus that runs
through Sendaizaka!
Demon Bus?
What's that?
How could you not know?
They say the bus that
goes through Sendaizkaue
at 6:00 PM sharp is cursed!
Anyone riding it
disappears never
to return!
They say the bus
driver is Death
himself.
And the final
destination is
Hell!
Knock it off, guys!
You're scaring me.
Wow, kids really do
love to gossip,
don't they.
Hey, Usagi. Wake up!
[tired groans]
C'mon. Get up. We're
supposed to go meet
Ami after school.
But I'm so sleepy...
Even if we're
meeting at the
arcade?
At the arcade?
Okay!
I still can't wrap
my head around it.
Usagi and I are both
real Sailor Guardians?
Well it's still
brand new to you.
I'm sure you'll
get used to it soon.
Luna, what happens
now? What do we do
next?
We have two missions,
to find and protect our
Princess as well as the
Legendary Silver Crystal.
Alright! I beat
level two!
So that's our mission?
Find a Princess and
a Crystal?
You're going to cram
school again?
Do you have to? It's
no fun without you!
Why don't you come
with me then?
Uh...
If you do, you might
get to catch a glimpse
of a really pretty girl.
Huh?
I see her a lot when
I take this bus.
Really? What does
she look like?
Well, she wears a
uniform from the
T.A. Girls' Academy.
"The 66 via Sendaizaka"
Does that mean it's the
Demon Bus?
[nervous laugh]
Couldn't be.
[gasp]
Oh...
What was that?
So pretty...
Usagi, don't stare at
her like that! It's
rude!
Wait! I'm getting off
here too! Bye, Ami!
See ya!
Huh?
Okay...
What are you
doing Usagi?
Did you get off here
just to chase after
that girl?
She's so beautiful!
And I've got nothing
else to do.
Oh, no! Luna, I've
lost her! It's
all your fault!
Well... She could have
gone into this shrine.
Really? You
think so?
I sense an evil aura.
Could it be a ghost?
No demon or spectre is
going to haunt this
sacred shrine.
Not while I'm here!
[screaming]
Evil spirit, be gone!
Ugh...
Agh!
Hunh? The girl
from the bus?
Um, Miss Usagi, is it?
I'm so sorry.
I sensed an evil aura
I thought was coming
from you.
An evil aura?
That's weird. But who
cares? She's beautiful
and a shrine maiden!
So cool!
Still it's strange.
Phobos and Deimos don't
usually attack regular
people unless they've
been provoked.
[giggle]
Did they feel it too?
Is there something
more to this girl?
Can I help you?
Oh Rei! It's Mii!
She's gone missing!
[gasp]
She didn't come home?
You know this has always been
a dangerous neighborhood.
And lately everyone's been
talking about some kind
of demon bus too.
[laughing]
Though that's not to
say you and this
shrine are dangerous.
I think we
should go.
Oh. Alright then.
I'm telling you that
girl is not normal.
They say she can sense
the supernatural!
Hm?
So, um, this little
girl, Mii, is she
your friend?
Yes. She likes to play
here after school sometimes
while she waits for the
bus to take her home.
The bus?
Do you mean-?
Sendaizkaue has five
hills. Their slopes
intersect near here.
There's an urban legend
about a mysterious sixth
hill, that's invisible.
Huh?
They say it's a gateway,
and that's the reason why
the Demon Bus supposedly
vanishes there.
[gasp]
Do you know what
they say when
someone disappears?
Hm?
They call it being
Spirited away...
Oh...
Did you guys
see the news?
A first year student has
been missing for four days!
Yeah!
You know it's
the Demon Bus!
Has to be! It's
so scary!
Do you really believe
it? That this is all
because of some bus?
Well the kids are
missing. So something's
going on.
Spirited away, huh?
[giggling]
I'm wearing mine too!
How cute! We're
matching!
Hey Luna, let's go
see Rei again. I wanna
go ask her something.
Sounds good. I was
just thinking about
her.
Huh?
Rei's a beautiful and
very mysterious girl.
She has a regal face,
and spiritual powers.
I think perhaps she
could be our missing
princess.
[gasp]
Oh wow!
She's definitely
pretty enough!
Then again, she could
be something else.
[sigh]
How many cram schools
does Ami have to go to?
She really should be
here. What if something
happens?
Don't worry, Usagi.
You can stay in touch
with her by using your
communicator.
Huh? You mean this?
Isn't it just a
regular old watch?
Meow! Meow! Meow!
[meowing]
Luna? What's
the matter?
[frantically meowing]
Why're you talking
to yourself?
Agh! It's you again!
We seem to bump into
each other a lot.
There's no need
to scream.
Uh... Are you in
junior high, too?
No! I'm a high
school student!
Mamoru Chiba, Moto-
Azabu Private High
School?
Hm...
Um... Have you heard
of the Demon Bus?
Yes I have.
Supposed to be this
bus line, right?
Huh?
Agh!
Meow!
My heart! It's
beating so fast
again!
Please Rei, use your
spiritual powers to
find my daughter.
I beg of you!
I'm so sorry, but my
powers don't work like
that. I can't just
meditate and tell
you where Mii is.
[gasps]
I think it's best
left to the police.
Her child is missing!
You're supposed to be
psychic! Why don't
you help her?
Maybe you had something to
do with Mii's disappearance!
And this is all your fault!
Hey, wait a minute!
How dare you accuse
Rei! She's a beautiful
girl, both inside and out!
Huh?!
Miss Usagi...
Rei would never do such
a thing! How could you
even think that?!
Where have the
children gone, then?
Do you know?
Uh! Well yeah, that's
a good question...
What are you trying to
say? Are you involved
in this too?
What? No! I-I just...
I-I don't have anything
to do with it!
All of you please...
Just leave now!
Ever since I was a small
child, my spiritual powers
have made me an outcast.
And there were some
who even called me
a freak.
Why was I born this way?
I don't understand.
Oh Rei...
Everything will be
okay. I'll help you
find Mii!
Thank you, Usagi.
But you should stay
away from me and not
come here anymore.
There's nothing we
can do. We should go.
I need to concentrate.
What's going on here?
I know something's about
to happen. But what?
[gasp]
Who is that?
Usagi's in danger!
Hmph!
[gasp]
You're the one...
Oh no! It's Rei!
Do you think that
could be the Demon
Bus? Agh!
What's happening to it?!
[gasp]
I gotta go save Rei!
Moon Power!
Why did you change into
a flight attendant? How's
that gonna help?
It's my duty to ensure
the safety and comfort
of all the passengers,
no matter what!
Agh!
[gasps]
[meowing]
Interesting...
She definitely
transformed.
Who is that girl?
Ami, can you hear me?
Usagi is in trouble!
What?!
You should have just
killed them, Jadeite.
Hello, Nephrite. There's
a good reason to keep them
alive.
Living hostages are
better for luring out
the Sailor Guardians.
[whining]
Where am I? I'm scared.
And Luna and Tuxedo Mask
can't save me this time.
[crying]
[sobbing]
Somebody help me!
Oh! The communicator!
Luna!
Help! Where am I?
Well Luna? Can you
track her location?
[frustrated groan]
I need a stronger
signal. This one's
too weak.
Wait, what if she
transformed into Sailor
Moon? Would that help?
Uh... Yeah.
And once we know
where Usagi is, can
we teleport there?
Yes!
Come help me! Please!
Usagi, transform now!
Huh? Okay!
Moon Prism Power
Make Up!
Mercury Power
So beautiful...
I'm strangely attracted
to her, like we've met
somewhere before.
Get away from
her! Right now!
You!
I am the Pretty
Guardian!
Who fights for love
and for justice! I
am Sailor Moon!
And now in the name of
the Moon, I'll punish
you!
I am the Pretty Guardian,
who fights for love and
for intelligence!
I am Sailor Mercury!
Douse yourself in
water and repent!
Here at last. I've
been waiting.
Release Rei and the
others you took right
now!
Mr. Uh...
whoever you are!
My name is Jadeite. I'm
one of the Four Kings
of the Dark Kingdom!
Agh!
Mercury Aqua Mist!
Save Rei and the others!
Okay!
Huh? When did it
get so cold?
Is that the best you
Sailor Guardians can
do? Pitiful.
Against me, you
don't stand a
chance!
[screaming]
I will freeze you, and
make you bow down before
our Great Ruler!
No!
Was all this just a
trap to get us here
and take us prisoner?
Usagi? Is that you?
What's going on here?
No, Rei! It's not
me! I'm not Usagi!
Ah...
Why are you
fighting him?
Well I kinda have to
because I'm a Sailor
Guardian. And normal
people can't exactly
fight evil like this!
Ya know, 'cause power
and like responsibility...
Usagi and that other
girl have powers too?
Are they like me?
[screaming]
[gasp]
Stop! Don't get in
my way! Let go!
I won't!
Hmph! I wouldn't do
that if I were you.
You're only human.
No! I'm more
than that!
[gasp]
I'm not an
ordinary human.
I'm special and I won't
let you hurt anyone else.
Anymore!
[groaning]
[gasp]
There is is...
That vision?
There's no doubt
about it now! Rei,
catch!
Huh?
Hold that pen and yell,
"Mars Power Make Up"!
You have to hurry!
[affirmative grunt]
[giggle]
I understand now. It's
up to me. I know what
I have to do.
Mars Power
Make Up!
I am the Pretty Guardian,
who fights for love and
for passion.
I am Sailor Mars.
In the name of Mars,
I'll chastise you!
Amazing!
[giggle]
I knew it, Rei! You
had to be! You are one
of the Sailor Guardians!
You're Sailor Mars!
Watch out!
Is that why I was
born this way? With
these powers?
Was it all so I
could help Usagi?
As a Sailor Guardian?
Usagi!
Okay!
Moon Tiara Boomerang!
Agh!
Now Sailor Mars!
Finish him off!
An evil being who
abducts innocent
children...
Must not be allowed to
exist in this world.
Evil Spirit,
be gone!
You'll pay for
this, Sailor Mars!
Hello, Mii.
Rei!
Huh? How did...
I get here.
The Sailor Guardians
came. They saved you
and brought you back.
Huh...
Mii!
Mommy!
Mii! Thank goodness!
I was so worried!
There are three Sailor
Guardians now that you're
with us, Rei.
Yeah!
I'm so glad that we
found you, Sailor Mars.
We're glad you could
join us. We've been
needing someone like you.
[happy laugh]
Another Guardian,
found. Now let's do the
same for our Princess
and the Legendary
Silver Crystal, too.
Yeah! Let's find them.
I know we can do it!
Can you tell us
what's in the box?
[news reporter chatter]
Usagi! They're gonna
display the royal treasure
of "D" at the Masquerade Ball!
A Masquerade Ball!
Usagi, you're
missing the
point!
A romantic dance
with Tuxedo Mask!
[giggling]
It could be the Legendary
Silver Crystal we're
looking for!
Moon Power! Change
me into a princess!
Are you listening
to me?!
Act Four, "Masquerade
Dance Party."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.