[snicker]
Usako...
No!
Sailor Moon...
Hunh? Where am I?
Mamo?
[gasp]
Chibi-Usa?
Wait!
Where are you going? Come
back! Don't leave me here!
[gasp]
[groaning]
My head is throbbing. What
happened? I can't remember...
[gasp]
Why am I dressed like this?
My brooch!
[sigh of relief]
What... is this place?
That image...
Is that me?
No. It's Neo Queen Serenity.
Admiring my hologram?
Stunning, isn't it.
These are my private
chambers in Black Moon
Castle on the
planet Nemesis.
Welcome, Sailor Moon...
Or should I say the future
Neo Queen Serenity.
That gown appears
to suit you...
I am Prince Dimande of the
Black Moon. Please...
Relax and make yourself
comfortable.
[grunting]
My body just
moved on its own!
I unleashed the full
force of my Evil
Sight's power upon you.
And yet you have already
regained consciousness.
The power of the Legendary
Silver Crystal is strong
with you indeed.
Tell me why you launched an
attack on Crystal Tokyo!
"Why"?
I wanted to prove that the
Legendary Silver Crystal is
not the only invincible
power in the universe.
And I succeeded.
Deluded by the fantasies of
eternal life and limitless
power, the people of
Earth had become
lazy and decadent.
They disgusted us.
Don't like the world?
Then why not remake it?
If you wish to have power
and truly change this
planet, go to Nemesis.
Obtain the Malefic Black
Crystal and anything you
want can be yours.
Nemesis: the untouchable
planet. As long as I control
the supreme power of its
Malefic Black Crystal,
any world in any dimension
is mine for the taking!
Against that awesome power,
the Legendary Silver Crystal
is but a mere stone.
The strong shall
inherit the Earth.
This revolting, utopian world
should never have existed!
Let us send an army into the
past, back to a time before
the Moon Kingdom took over!
History, shall be re-forged,
and the Black Moon will
claim the future!
[horrified gasps]
So that is our grand plan.
Operation Re-play: the
rewriting of history.
Rewrite history!?
Eternal youth and
everlasting peace are
fantasies. Immortality is
against nature. That which
is born is meant to die.
Altering history will
create a proper future.
You're completely insane!
Hmph.
[screaming]
[crying]
Stop crying,
you little brat!
Small Lady!?
I never dreamed I
would actually see her.
Yet the all-powerful
goddess, always kept
behind palace walls, is
right in front of me.
And she is the most
beautiful thing I
have ever seen.
But her eyes are
cold and she looks
on me with disdain.
To her, I am less than
human, merely an
enemy to be dealt with.
[gasp]
Surrender! You are
now under my control!
It was such awesome and
terrifying power...
I saw, for the first
time, what the Legendary
Silver Crystal
was capable of.
Since that day, I have not
been able to forget the look
in those eyes.
I needed to see her again.
I wished to make her
grovel before me.
I had to have her... by
any means necessary.
And now you
are finally mine.
Yes. That's the
look I remember.
The beautiful ruler, of
the beautiful planet.
Neo Queen...
Serenity...
[gasp] No!
Moon Crystal Power!
Make up!
[gasp]
I can't transform!?
[chuckling] This planet is
made entirely of Malefic
Black Crystal, which absorbs
and nullifies all other
energies, even the
power of the Legendary
Silver Crystal.
No...
Feel free to move about
the castle as you wish.
Think about this as your
home from now on. You will
be remaining here as my
permanent guest. [laughing]
The Black Moon... They're not
human. They're demons!
Nemesis...
Once again, it has
vanished from orbit.
King Endymion, if Sailor
Moon and the others are
really on that dark
planet, then we have
to rescue them as
soon as possible!
Yes, I know.
But we have to find Nemesis
before we canget near it.
What we need is the
Legendary Silver Crystal.
It alone can help
us save our friends.
But the only two people
who can use it aren't here.
Without Neo Queen
Serenity or Sailor
Moon, there's no way.
Hmm... [gasp]
Chibi-Usa...
What about Chibi-Usa? As Neo
Queen Serenity's daughter,
she should be able to use
the Silver Crystal too.
She is the heir of Silver
Millennium, isn't she?
She is of royal blood,
but Small Lady does
not have any power.
[gasp]
How old do you think she
is? Six, seven maybe?
She is in fact nine
hundred years old.
Nine hundred years old?!
One day she just stopped
growing, and has been like
that ever since.
She has no power,
and she cannot
transform.
Poor thing.
What if she never transforms
or learns to use the
Crystal? Will she
still take the throne?
Yes, but I believe one
day she will awaken.
She will grow up. It is her
destiny to protect this
world like her mother has.
King Endymion, is there
anything else you know
about the Black Moon?
You said the group had a
history of causing trouble.
How did it all start?
There was an incident
several centuries ago.
Crystal Tokyo had become
the most beautiful place
on Earth, a city of
peace and tranquility.
Then a mad tyrant appeared,
bent on inciting havoc and
destruction. His
name was Phantom.
Up to that point, Neo Queen
Serenity had watched over
Crystal Tokyo quietly.
But when the city was
threatened, she intervened
and fought to protect it.
Phantom was captured
and banished to Nemesis.
All access to the
planet was cut off.
Time passed. Harmony
returned. People forgot what
had happened. And
all was quiet...
Until a new group of
radicals showed up out of
nowhere, demanding
death to all the people
of the Moon Kingdom. Like
Phantom, they had dark
crescent marks on
their foreheads.
So I'm assuming these
radicals are the Black Moon?
Is that right?
Do you think they
could possibly be
descendants of Phantom?
I have no idea. But
whether they are or not is
immaterial. I refuse to let
them cause any more harm.
I swear, I will save you...
Hold on, Usako...
[gasp] Mamo?
Mamo, Venus, Luna...
I'm scared...
I'm all alone, and
I can't transform.
But the worst part is-
Someone other than Mamo
kissed me...
Oh Mamo...
I said such awful things
to you. I wish I hadn't.
I'm so sorry...
And now I might not ever see you
again, and you'll never know!
Always remember, my dear
Serenity, The Legendary
Silver Crystal
follows your heart.
Is there doubt in my heart?
Is that why I
can't use my power?
Every time Mamo paid more
attention to Chibi-Usa, I
felt insecure. I didn't have
faith in him, because I'd
lost confidence in myself.
I forgot that love cannot
live where there is no
trust. But I do love
Mamo, and we both want
to protect Chibi-Usa...
Sailor Moon! You're
my only hope!
I'm from the future!
30th-century Earth!
And I need you!
No. I won't lose hope.
I am the future queen:
Neo Queen Serenity.
I swore I would
protect my friends and
everyone else on Earth!
I am loved.
I'm not alone.
Believe in yourself, Usagi.
You can do this.
You have to.
First things first, you
need to rescue the other
Guardians. You know
they're somewhere
nearby. You can feel it!
Mars, Mercury, Jupiter!
Wherever you are,
I will find you!
What happened?
We're in our school clothes.
Something broke our
transformation.
What is this place?
Where are we?
My muscles are stiff. How
long have we been here?
So strange. I could swear I
heard Usagi's voice in my
head a moment ago.
You aren't the
only one, Mako.
We should transform. Then
we'll figure things out.
Jupiter Star Power!
Mars Star Power!
Mercury Star Power!
Make up!
We can't transform!
What's going on?
I can't breathe...
[gasping]
All my strength... is
being sucked out of me.
Sailor Moon!
[gasp]
Mars, Mercury, Jupiter!?
[evil laugh] Now that
I have the future Neo
Queen Serenity in my
clutches, I have no
more need of these three.
Leave them in
the Dark Chamber.
They can die and rot
for all I care.
Sailor Moon...
I don't know, Luna P.
Is that girl
really my Mommy?
That's the invincible
Sailor Moon?
But she's a crybaby and she
messes up all the time and
everyone's always
yelling at her...
Huh... Just like me.
The legendary guardian,
Sailor Moon, is invincible.
Nothing can defeat her.
How come?
She has a strong heart and
true friends by her side.
Those things give her
unbeatable power.
I may be her daughter...
But, I'm powerless...
I'm not brave, and I don't
have any friends...
Hey, shrimp! Why don't
you ever get bigger?
You can't be
queen someday!
You don't even
look like her!
I bet you're not
the real princess!
[laughing]
[crying]
Small Lady...
You know, when she was
younger, the queen
was quite the
crybaby too.
Really?
Mm-hm. You're more like
her than you realize.
She named you Small
Lady because it was her
wish that one day you
might become a fine
young lady, fit to
take her place.
That didn't make sense.
I'm not like Mommy.
And I can't grow up.
So I'll never be a lady.
Mommy's so beautiful
and perfect.
I could never
be like her.
And Daddy loves her
more than anything
else in the world.
[mean laughing]
A real princess of Silver
Millennium would be able to
use the Silver Crystal!
If you are the queen's
daughter, prove it!
Use your power on
us! I dare ya!
There it is. The Legendary
Silver Crystal.
Small Lady?
Small Lady, are
you in here?
[gasp] The Legendary
Silver Crystal is gone!
Small Lady!
What was that? Mommy?
Mommy! Where are you!?
[gasp]
It's all my fault...
[crying]
If I hadn't taken the
Legendary Silver Crystal...
None of this would
have ever happened!
Abra-cadabra. Poof!
Pluto...
Once I ran away from the
mean kids and ended
up in a hallway in the
back of the palace,
where no one was
supposed to go.
That's when I found
the forbidden door.
Hello, Small Lady. I am
honored to meet you.
[gasp] You know who I am?
Only members of the Silver
Millennium family are
allowed to come here.
And you bear a strong
resemblance to other
members of the royal house.
Who are you? How
do you know that?
You may call me Sailor
Pluto. I am the keeper of
the Door of Space and Time.
So, they said you don't look
anything like the queen did
they? Well they're
wrong. You're
her spitting image.
Huh?
No one besides Daddy
had ever said anything
like that to me before.
Listen, Small Lady...
Huh?
If ever you feel sad,
just cast this spell,
Abra-cadabra!
Abra-cadabra?
It will raise your spirits
and make you feel better.
Abra-cadabra...
Poof!
Ahh!
Is that a magical
staff, Pluto?
You mean my Garnet Rod?
Yes. It is quite
magical indeed.
My mommy has something like
that called the Moon Rod.
She uses it to control the
Legendary Silver Crystal,
and make miracles happen!
As her daughter,
one day that will be
your responsibility.
[gasp]
Yeah. Maybe.
Hey Pluto, can I come
and see you again?
Of course. I will be right
here waiting for you.
Always.
Pluto...
My one and only
true friend...
Maybe if I see her,
I'll feel better.
Hey Pluto! [giggle]
Huh?
Daddy?
I thought for certain
she would be here.
My King, Small Lady has a
far better head on her
shoulders than any of us
give her credit for.
[gasp] Pluto...
She is the princess, not a
helpless infant. Besides,
Luna P is with her.
You're right, Pluto. But the
enemy has Sailor Moon and
we must remain vigilant.
Please do whatever you
can to aid Sailor Venus
and Tuxedo Mask.
I'm counting on you, Pluto.
Yes, of course,
my King. I will.
I've never seen her look
like that. She was so happy.
Not like the Pluto I know.
She's lonely and kinda sad.
And I'm the only one that
can make her smile...
I will always be here,
waiting for you to return.
I'm not the only one
she was waiting for.
I'm not special
to her either.
A Space-Time Key?
This is the one Small Lady
took to go to the past!
Without a key she
could get lost in time!
Small Lady!
Where are you?!
I've been walking
for a while now.
I wonder where I am.
It's dark and cold here.
It's not like the space-time
portal I usually go through...
[gasp]
Something's not right.
I should go back.
[gasp]
My key is gone!
Lost are we?
[gasp]
I'm impressed you were able
to make it all the way out
here. Poor little Rabbit.
No one to love you.
Nowhere to go.
[gasp] Who are you?
Your fears betray you. I see
the darkness in your heart.
You could not have come to
this forsaken place unless
you had decided to give
up, to walk away from
everything you know and
everyone you care about.
You thought you were
wandering aimlessly, but you
were searching for me
without realizing it.
Someone who wants you.
Someone who needs you.
Come... Come with me...
Sailor Pluto, where's
Chibi-Usa?
Something has happened
to her, I can feel it!
Something so terrible,
it disrupted the space-
time continuum!
Chibi-Usa! Where are you?
Can you hear me?!
Please, Usako, lend
me your strength...
Help me find Chibi-Usa!
Act.22: Hidden
Agenda, Nemesis.
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.