[building roar]
What can I do to help?!
[gasp] Mamo!
It's Tuxedo Mask!
The barrier is failing! You have
to act fast! Otherwise, the
enemey is going to invade
the Earth!
[roaring]
You must transform into Super
Sailor Moon!
Moon Chalice...
...come into my grasp!
Sailor Moon.
She is so strong. Someday, I
hope...
...that I can be strong, as
well,...
...just like her!
[gasp]
Is that another...Moon Chalice?!
Her deep desire to be strong has
triggered a new awakening.
Sailor Chibi Moon, are you
ready?
Hm.
Moon Crisis Make Up!
[laugh]
She has now become...
...Super Sailor Chibi Moon!
Hm.
[growling roar]
Let's go, Super Sailor Chibi
Moon!
Hm!...Super Sailor Moon!
It's time to combine our powers!
[growling roar]
Rainbow...Double
Moon...Heartache!
[groan]
[wail]
[grunts]
[grunt] This distortion of
space...[grunt]
[gasp] That must mean...
(Setsuna)...Master Pharaoh 90 is
coming!
[roaring]
[yelling]
Act.37 Infinity 11 Infinite ‐
Judgement ‐
[growling roar]
We need more power! Enough to
blast her into tiny pieces!
Hm!
[yelling]
[howling]
[roar]
[yowl]
(Master Pharaoh 90) Hmm...
[gasp]
Come, Mistress 9. I've been
waiting for this moment!
Yes, Master. Of course. Let us
become one!
[gasps]
[moan]
[laughing]
[buzz]
She disappeared...
What the‐?
(Master Pharaoh 90) Mmm...
Power...I'm overflowing with
power!
[gasp]
Master Pharaoh 90 must
have absorbed Mistress 9 and all
her energy!
At the rate he's growing, he
could soon engulf the entire
Earth!
C'mon, guys! We've got to stop
him from getting any bigger! We
must protect the world!
Hm.
Venus...Wink Chain Sword!
Mars...Snake Fire!
Jupiter Coconut...Cyclone!
Mercury Aqua Mirage!
Tuxedo...La...
Smoking Bomber!
Ready? Super Sailor Chibi Moon?
Yeah!
Rainbow...Double
Moon...Heartache!
It's the end for you, Master
Pharaoh 90!
[yells]
[grunts]
[yelling]
(Luna) They're winning!
(Artemis) No, look!
[laughing]
So this is the energy of the
ones that are protected by their
Guardian Planets?
[gasp]
I'm out of power...
[swoon]
[gasps]
(Usagi) Chibi Moon!
[gasp]
[grunt]
(Master Pharaoh 90) What intense
power! This energy is absolutely
magnificent!
Oh, no!
[grunt, thud]
No! Venus!
Jupiter!
[groan]
Hang in there!
[groans]
[gasp]
Get up!
[chuckling]
[gasp]
Wait, is Master Pharoh 90
getting even bigger? Are our
attacks just making things
worse?
(Master Pharaoh 90) [grunt] I
can't move.
Is this a barrier?
We are not letting you out of
Sankakusu...
...Master Pharaoh 90!
The three of us will stop you
from invading Earth!
[chuckling] Try as hard as you
want; it's already too late!
[grunts]
It won't hold much longer.
Uranus, Neptune, Pluto!
[scoff] I will crush every last
one of you!
[grunts]
No! He broke through the
barrier!
[grunting] Damn! Is this it?!
[panting]
[gasps]
[gasp]
What is that?
Is that...?
...The Tau Star System?
[laughing]
Yes! My forgotten home from
faraway...The Tau Star System!
(Master Pharaoh 90) Behold! I am
about to engulf this planet, and
make it one with myself!
[maniacal laughing]
(Usagi) This black lava, which
reeks of death, is covering the
Earth's surface...
We have to stop him, or else
he'll take over the whole world!
[frustrated breath] But how? We
already hit him with everything
we've got.
[gasp]
This can't be the end.
[groan]
Damn it!
What now?
Chibi Moon! Chibi Moon
[gasping]
They've all reached their limit.
None of them have any strength
left.
[exhale...gasps]
[gasps]
A light?
[gasp]
What is this repulsive light?!
The glow of the moon...
[inhale]
It feels so warm.
(Usagi) Just like Mamo...and my
friends, who are always there
for me.
(Usagi) You have all watched
over and supported me,...ever
since my previous life.
Hotaru isn't gone at all!
[gasps]
(Chibi‐Usa)
She's alive in our hearts!
Here in our hearts...
[sighs]
So she's still here.
She'll always be with us.
(Usagi) Now it's my turn. This
time, I'll be the one...who will
protect all of you!
I still have power.
The power I have from my
friends is still with me, which
means, I'm the last chance we've
got.
I'm the only one left
who can fight...
Just me and the power of
the Legendary Silver Crystal...!
Now, Moon Chalice,...
...come into my grasp!
Lend me your power!
O' Legendary Moon Chalice,
filled with the last of all nine
Sailor Guardians' power!
Usa! What are you doing?
Hm!
Usa!
[gasp]
Sailor Moon...
(Usagi) I will stop him...
...by releasing the power of the
Moon Chalice and the Legendary
Silver Crystal from inside his
body!
(Usagi) I will stop him...
...by releasing the power of the
Moon Chalice and the Legendary
Silver Crystal from inside his
body!
No dont! Usa!
[gasp] Sailor Moon...!
Where did she just go?!
[grunt] Super Sailor Moon!
[growl]
[grunt]
She vanished.
Are you sure?‐Did she really
disappear?
No way!
[grunt]
Usagi, come in!
[gasp]
[exhale]
(Artemis) Sailor Moon's
signal,...it's gone!
[shaky breaths...sniffle] Usa...
(Mamoru) I let you die alone,
right in front of me...
I didn't protect you.
[gulp...shaky breaths]
Sailor Moon...Mommy!
[grunt] No...
Not this...It can't be!
Hey...
Huh?
I never did tell you my name,
did I?
(Usagi) You don't have to.
[gasp]
(Usagi) I already know it's
Haruka Tenoh.
Turns out you're famous. You
both are, you and Michiru.
I know who you are. I figured it
out. I could sense it in the
wind.
(Haruka) I just...All I wanted
to do was protect her, with my
own hands.
That's the only thing...I ever
wanted.
[choking cry] How could we
allow this...
[gulp] Sailor Moon...
[deep breaths]
[small sobs, gasp]
[deep breaths, gasp]
[deep breaths...gasp]
(Haruka) The Talismans...
[gasp]
(Michiru)...they're
resonating!
(Master Pharaoh 90) What is this
light emanating from my body?
[building roar]
[grunts]
[grunt] Now what?
[gasps]
[gasps] Oh no!
It can't be...
I am an emissary from the abyss
of death.
Protected by Saturn, the Outer
Planet of Destruction.‐The
Guardian of Silence.
I am Sailor Saturn.
[deep breathing]
Sailor Saturn?
Again she has awakened...
[gasps]
She's here...
[deep breaths]
We failed...
[deep breaths, gasp]
So then, is this the end?
From where I stand, it doesn't
feel like much time has passed
since the last crisis, which
triggered my previous awakening.
[sigh] It seems as though I
remain the uninvited guest.
The gradual overlap of
coincidences, has caused a
dangerous aberration in the
course of events.
As a result, history itself has
been slightly altered.
[grunt]
[scream]
I can't...move. [long howling]
(Sailor Saturn) What happened in
Mugenzu was supposed to be
Hotaru's end. She should have
found eternal rest.
Instead, she was forced to live
an inconceivable life as a
cyborg.
It was a huge shock to her
body...
It also caused a considerable
disturbance to my soul, which
should have stayed asleep.
Professor Tomoe's twisted heart
is what attracted these alien
beings to this world.
This eventually led to our
survival inside a vesselized
body.
Alas, it could not be helped.
There's a reason why we were all
drawn to this place, and why a
gateway from another world
opened up here.
This is the chosen land.
The path we are on was
predestined long ago ‐ the path
of destruction.
And now that I have awakened...
[yowl]
I must fulfill that destiny, and
swing this Silence Glaive.
That glaive is the scythe of the
Goddess of Death!
All she has to do is swing
and it's total annihilation.
Dammit! I refuse to let this be
our fate! Not again!
(Chibi‐Moon) No...Does this
mean...there's no future?
[gasp] No, Saturn! Don't do it!
Death Reborn Revolution!
(Master Pharaoh 90) [groaning]
My power...It's being
sucked out of me!
[grunts]
[groan] This massive negative
aura...
It's the same dormant power,
which surrounded the Omega Area!
I now see that power has
awakened as the light that
brings destruction!
It was you!
[bellowing]
She pulled him off the planet's
surface. What frightening power!
Abominable existence! You
Invader!
I condemn you...
...and Earth, to total
annihilation!
[yell]
This is the end. We can't stop
it!
(Mamoru) She's about to swing
her Silence Glaive,...
...which will destroy the alien
and the world along with it!
[gasps]
[whimpering] Sailor Moon!
Sailor Saturn has finally
awakened.
And she has swung her Silence
Glaive.
Next time, "Act.38 Infinity 12
Infinite ‐ Journey ‐."
The moonlight is a messenger of
love.