Hmm...
I see what
you're talking about, Meioh.
The data readings from
this area are abnormal.
But, to call it a
"spatial distortion"?
An assumption like that
is somewhat farfetched,
don't you think?
Yes, you're right.
I wonder why thinking
of it like that would
even occur to me?
Can we come in?
Sure, Reika.
You're working late?
Why don't you take a break
and come get dinner with us?
I'd love to, but I already
ate with my professor.
Aw, darn.
Wow!
Look at all these plants!
Mako would be so
excited to see this place.
Mm... "Mako"?
Who Motoki?!
She's a kid from Juban
Middle School who
comes to the arcade.
And, she's really into plants.
That's all.
Uh huh...
Whatever.
Sorry you can't join us.
Next time?
Sure.
So?
Whadya think of Setsuna?
She's pretty, isn't she?
Yeah.
She looks like a real
intellectual beauty.
Do you know anything
about the research
she's assisting with?
If I remember right, that
professor has published some
of his anti‐gravity studies
in the scientific journal
"Physical Review Letters."
Hmm...
I don't know any details
beyond what she said,
but she talked about getting
some strange readings from
the area around Sankakusu,
so she and the professor are
conducting some
studies there.
Hey, that gives me an idea.
Why don't we go have
dinner in Sankakusu?
There are lots of fancy
restaurants we haven't
tried, yet, in all
those new buildings.
[gasp]
Is something wrong?
I'm fine, but let's
go somewhere else.
I mean, just look at
the sky over there.
It's so dark and creepy.
[chuckle]
They're just
storm clouds, Reika.
Uhgh... Pathetic.
This one turned out to
be a defect as well.
Professor?
We must go.
It's almost time
to make contact.
The light of our
sacred life‐source,
the Taoiron
Crystal, grows weaker.
This is unacceptable.
Apologies,
Master Pharaoh 90.
I promise to deliver
you an abundance of
human hosts very soon.
And what of the
Vessilization?
Where do we stand?
Using human bodies that have
had their Hosts extracted,
we continue our attempts
to implant the eggs.
But, we have yet to come
across other specimens as
perfect as ourselves.
The anomalies are
slowing us down.
Those Sailor Guardians...
The ones protected by
their Guardian Planets...
And, that Sailor Moon
who possesses a light so
powerful, it can wipe out
a Daimon in an instant.
Its radiance is like
the Taioron Crystal,
our very source of life!
But, it is not alone.
I see an ominous
light hidden near it;
one that will
bring destruction...
And the time of its
awakening is at hand!
An ominous light that
will bring destruction.
Does he mean the
three Talismans?
Eliminate the destruction
advancing toward us!
And, obtain the light
which Sailor Moon possesses!
We need its infinite power
as soon as possible for our
grand resurrection!
We shall bring destruction
not only on the Sailor
Guardians, but
on all humanity.
We will turn the Earth into
our second mother planet.
Sir!
Well, then, those Sailor
Guardians certainly seem to
have put him in a good mood.
You summoned me,
Magus Kaolinite?
How may I be of service?
Our Master requires a
massive amount of Hosts and
I need you to gather them.
As Tellu, Level 404 of the
Witches 5 and Ruru Teruno,
prefect of Mugen
Physical Education,
as well as its
botanical garden...
I will bring in Hosts
of the highest quality.
[classroom chatter]
Okay, class!
As you can tell
by the blackboard,
this week's assignment is
to give someone a gift.
I would like everyone to
give the clay projects they
made to someone special.
That person can
be your mother,
your father, or
even your best friend.
The point is to let them know
how much you appreciate them.
Who are you
giving yours to, Momo?
I'm gonna give
mine to my mom.
Her birthday's coming
up so it's perfect!
Here. This is for you.
A Sailor Moon pencil holder!
Wow, Kyusuke!
That's really good!
How come you're
giving it to me?
Huh?! Well 'cause, you're my...
Well you're a girl I really
like hanging out with, okay?!
It's a token of
our friendship.
It's a token...
Of friendship?
Then, I think I'll
give mine to Hotaru.
Hotaru?
Yeah.
She's this girl,
who's really pretty,
and also kinda mysterious.
Look, it's that
sixth‐grader, Tomoe.
She's leaving early again?
I heard she's not well.
She wears tights and
long sleeves all year long.
She's always so gloomy.
Everybody knows
she's a weirdo!
Well, yeah, she is the
daughter of an eccentric
professor, after all.
Does she even
have any friends?
[chuckle] Oops!
Didn't see you there.
I shoulda watched my step.
Need help
picking up your stuff?
[giggling]
[gasp]
Uh...
What the heck?
Creepy...
[sigh]
Hey there!
You look kinda down.
What's wrong?
Well, I wanna see
Haruka and Michiru again.
[gasp]
They're Sailor
Guardians, just like we are.
And, they've
been helping us,
so why do we have to
keep acting like we're on
different sides?
I wanna meet with them
face‐to‐face and talk it out.
I have to get to
a club meeting.
So do I.
You're both
gonna abandon me?!
Things'll work out the
way they're meant to.
Have faith.
You should focus more
on your own life and
worry less about them.
Hey, shouldn't you be
taking a make‐up exam, now?
You're right, I
should get going.
You're a wonder
with plants, Mako.
Ever since you
joined our Club,
the greenhouses are
full of new species.
And it seems like the
flowers are always in bloom.
Really?
Yeah, totally!
Do you happen to
have a favorite flower?
The Camellia.
The Sasanqua Camellia.
Even now, it still
makes me think of him.
Mako...
Hey! I've been
meaning to ask you.
Have you heard about
a houseplant called a "Tellun"?
A "Tellun"?
No. I haven't.
It's low maintenance because
it doesn't need to be watered.
It takes moisture
right outta the air.
It's really popular, right now.
The Mugen Botanical Garden
is selling tons of 'em.
The Death Busters are
nesting inside Mugen
Academy, just as we thought.
Which means there's
a good chance the
school is their hideout.
Uh‐huh!
Let's move in
before things get worse.
Uh‐huh!
The energy readings we've
been getting from Mugenzu
are highly unusual,
especially near the Academy.
Professor Tomoe, huh?
Something about his
face looks suspicious,
if you ask me.
And, it says here
he has a daughter, too.
"Hotaru Tomoe".
The same Hotaru we met?!
It's that new plant.
That must mean these are from
the Mugen Botanical Garden.
Interested?
You're lucky I still
have some in stock.
They're so easy
to take care of,
everyone seems to want one.
Mako, you really do have a
thing for plants, don't you?
Yeah, I'm kinda
curious about this one.
It's new.
"Tellun" Bred by Ruru Teruno,
of Mugen Academy.
I'm home!
Huh?
Where are you
going, Chibi‐Usa?
To Hotaru's place.
[gasp]
Wait! I'm going with you!
Okay...
Hello?
Chibi‐Usa!
What are you doing?!
We can't just
let ourselves in.
There was no intercom.
So it's not my fault.
What are you two
doing in this laboratory?
You know you're trespassing.
Yeah... Well, you see...
The thing is...
‐We just‐
‐It's okay, Kaori.
These two are my guests.
Hotaru!
This way.
So, what brings
you here today?
I wanted you to have this.
What?!
You're just givng
it away like that?!
But Mamo and I worked hard
to make that Holy Grail for you!
Well, My teacher told me
to give it to someone very
special as a present.
So, I thought I'd
give it to you,
Hotaru, as a token
of our friendship.
[gasp]
Oh...
Is that right?
Not that I care, but are
you sure you don't
wanna give it to Mamo?
I can't give it to Mamo.
The both of you
helped me make it.
If I only gave it to him,
that wouldn't be fair to you.
Chibi‐Usa.
I'm very sorry, but I
can't accept this gift.
People who love you worked
hard to help make it for you.
So, I really think it's
something you should
share with them.
But, thank you
for thinking of me.
Her eyes are so
dark and deep,
they could pull
you right in...
It's like they
know everything.
What's wrong?
Um, where's the‐‐?
Down at the end of the hall.
I'll be right back.
Wow.
That was embarrassing.
[chuckle]
[gasp]
Hotaru?
Are you okay?
Just touching your amulet makes
me feel better, Chibi‐Usa.
All my pain disappears.
Really?
The power inside of
it, does it have a name?
It's the
Legendary Silver Crystal.
The Legendary
Silver Crystal...
[gasp]
Hotaru?
What was that?
For a moment, I craved to
have Chibi‐Usa's amulet.
But why?
It felt as if there was
somebody else inside of me...
The Legendary
Silver Crystal?
[sigh]
So Mugen Academy is
right behind this lab, huh.
I wonder if this place
does experiments on animals,
like the lab Ami
saw at the school?
Exactly what kind of
research are they doing?
Hello there.
Can I help you?
I, uh‐ drank too
much tea with Hotaru.
And I‐I have a
really small bladder,
so I had to go
to the bathroom.
‐A‐and then I just‐
‐I see...
So you're a friend
of my daughter's.
Hotaru.
It's time for your
health check‐up.
We, uh, should be
getting home anyway.
Bye!
See ya, Hotaru.
Bye‐Bye!
So that guy is
Professor Tomoe?
His hand was as hard and
cold as a block of ice.
When he first
touched my shoulder,
I didn't think he was human.
Chibi‐Usa?
It can't be her.
There's no way she'd
be walking around here.
Whoa!
Guess it's been a while
since I've been here.
Did you get
even more plants?
I did.
But most of them
aren't doing too well.
Probably because
of all the rain.
Would you like some tea?
Sure, thanks!
I feel sleepy all of a sudden.
[yawn] Me, too.
I smell
something nice, but...
Mako...
Mako!
The flowers are blooming.
Who's there?
Is that you, Nichogi?
Mako!
Wake up!
Oh, it's just you, Minako.
Mako, take a
look over there!
It's budding?
After only one day?!
Not that.
Look at all the other plants!
They've all
withered and died?!
Mako?
What the hell?
Hmm...
So this is how the three
areas that form Mugenzu
all connect, huh?
Tenohzu, Kaiohzu.
That's strange.
They're the same as Haruka
and Michiru's last names.
Usagi!
Hey guys.
What's up?
Something wrong?
Mugen Garden is our enemy!
Are you sure?
[gasp]
Haruka!
Michiru!
Don't go!
Usagi!
Why are you
running away, Haruka?
What is it?
Are you trying to avoid us?
They live in
the Minato ward.
So close, and
yet I never knew!
Haruka...
You're a Sailor
Guardian like I am.
I don't know why we
can't fight together.
Why won't you say anything?
Usagi.
We can't let the enemy
hurt more innocent people.
That's our mission, so that's
what we have to focus on.
Come on.
It's like a jungle in here.
Look over there!
Everyone's unconscious!
I know that scent...
[gasp]
I was right!
Tellun!
[gasp]
Oh no!
My strength is
draining out of me!
[chuckle]
What marvelous
life energies!
And to think the mighty
Sailor Guardians just walked
into my trap of
their own accord!
Lucky me!
[chuckle]
These Tellun
plants are a part of me.
They are such
beautiful flowers.
And they thrive
on life force.
The blossoms in here are
filled with human energy,
concentrated souls,
otherwise called Hosts.
And, they are
all for my Master.
Once I've
offered them to him,
he'll make me a
Magus like Kaolinite!
I can sense it.
Someone is suffering.
Someone who is
very close to us.
‐Could it be...
‐...an ally?
I can't breathe...
And I can feel the
life draining out of me.
Is this how I will die?
No!
I cannot die, yet.
I must remember the
reason I was born.
And the reason I was reborn!
Awaken...
The time has come.
What was that?
Something's just
been awakened!
Ready girls?
Let's do this!
Moon Cosmic Power...
Mercury Planet Power...
Mars Planet Power...
Jupiter Planet Power...
Venus Planet Power...
Moon Prism Power...
Make Up!
I am the Pretty Guardian who
fights for love and for justice.
I am Sailor Moon!
And now, in the
name of the Moon,
I'll punish you!
So you've
revealed yourselves.
Allow me to do the same.
I am called Tellu.
Know what my level is?
404.
That's very high, high
enough to take your Hosts
and the rest of
your other powers, too.
Mars Snake Fire!
Venus Wink Chain Sword!
Mercury Aqua Mirage!
Mandragora Buster!
Jupiter Coconut Cyclone!
Neo Queen Serenity!
Lend me your strength!
Lend your power to
my Heart Moon Rod!
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
[giggling]
Such brilliant power!
No way!
Sailor Moon!
Mommy, give me power, too!
I want to be able to
help Sailor Moon
and fight by her side!
Please!
Luna P?
Is this a new Moon Rod?
One just for me?
Pink Sugar Heart Attack!
[snicker]
[yell]
[gasp]
[scream]
[attacking yell]
Chibi Moon!
No!
Dead Scream.
[death scream]
That voice and
that attack...
You're Sailor Pluto!
What's going on?!
Next time, "Act.32
Infinity 6 Three Guardians."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.