There is soon to be an
awakening...
I see a light. A light that
will bring destruction to
the Omega Area, our
sacred ground.
And I see other lights.
The lights of planets.
The shining radiance of...
Guardian Planets.
This Omega Area overflows
with power: a power that
reminds me of our old world.
The massive aura of that
energy is like a beacon.
The powerful are
drawn to it.
I sense a light similar to
that of the Taioron Crystal:
the source of our
existence and from
which our life force
flows. It attracts me.
Regardless, this sacred
ground now belongs to us!
From here, we shall build
ourselves a new world!
I will not tolerate
any interference.
Remove these
anomalies immediately!
Of course, without
hesitation. Thy will shall
be done, Master Pharaoh 90.
As for the light that
brings destruction,
make sure it stays asleep!
Awaken...
The time has come...
For the light guided
by the three Talismans.
Let the destruction begin!
[gasp]
What was that?
What a strange dream.
[gasp]
The flames jumped...
Was that an oracle
from the fire?
What was it trying to tell me?
Where am I? It feels
so warm and bright.
What's that sound? [gasp]
Those are bells!
Are they wedding
bells? Are Mamo and I
finally getting married?
[alarm clock]
Usagi! Time to get
up. It's past 8.
[gasp]
[panic wail] Why didn't you
wake me sooner, Mom?
[sigh] That girl. Just
when she was getting
better, it's the same
old routine.
When you're right, you're
right, Mommy Ikuko.
Usagi just keeps getting
older, but won't grow up.
And now onto our
other top story.
We're receiving reports of
a bizarre incident that
happened yesterday in
the Minato Ward.
Several students from the
Mugen Academy private school
were attacked by a strange
creature, which has
yet to be identified.
Though authorities won't
confirm, eyewitnesses are
claiming the attacker
was a fellow student,
who had suddenly
turned into a monster.
Officials will only say
they're investigating the
matter as a case of
possible atavism.
What's "atavism"?
I've never heard that word.
You know how humans evolved
from apes? Atavism is like
an evolutionary throwback.
A return to a more
primitive state.
Oh...
But I doubt that's what
really happened.
Seems far‐fetched.
Humans devolving into
monsters?
If true, that's very scary.
I'm off to school! Bye!
[gasp] I should go, too!
Bye Daddy Kenji! See
you when I get back!
Bye Chibi‐Usa.
Have a good day!
I'm sorry, Mamo!
You're late again, Usa. I
was just about to leave
without you.
[gasp]
Don't be angry. Sorry
I kept you waiting.
Starting tomorrow, I
promise I'll be on
time from now on.
Okay? So smile, and give
me my morning kiss.
Ma‐mo!
[growling]
Good morning, Master Mamoru.
You look well today.
Hi, Diana. Good
morning to you, too.
Oh yeah. Usagi, I
brought your lunch.
You left it at home.
You need to get up earlier.
And stop skipping breakfast.
It's not good for you.
A well‐balanced breakfast
is the most important
part of the day.
You tell her, Chibi‐Usa.
[chuckle]
Little brat! Stop ruining
my romantic moment!
Even though she annoys me,
I actually like Chibi‐Usa.
She's me and Mamo's
daughter from the future.
Her home is in the 30th
century, but she came back
to the past to train as
a Sailor Guardian.
So right now, she's living
with me and my family.
Oh! It's my friends
from school!
I'm gonna walk
with them. Bye!
Not long ago, we fought a
fierce battle against the
Black Moon to save
Earth's future.
But now that seems like
a distant memory.
Things are back to normal.
It's peaceful again. And
everyone's living their
regular lives.
Awaken. Let the
destruction begin!
Is something wrong?
No. Nothing to worry about.
Sometimes I'm happy but
then I'll be hit by
a wave of anxiety. It's
like a roller coaster.
The moments when
everything's okay are rare
and precious. I know
they won't last forever.
But what can I do? That's
my fate. No matter what
happens, I'll get through
it. Because it's
my responsibility. Because I
have a mission to fulfill.
Come in, Kaiohmaru.
Oh, there you are!
We should head out to pick
him up soon, or we'll be
late for school.
The seas are going
to be rough today.
Haruka, I thought
I told you.
Don't floor it on
the straightaway.
But she rides so
smooth, coach!
Let me get her up to speed.
Not a chance! We're still
just breaking her in.
We agreed you'd stay
under 5000 RPMs.
You wanna wreck
before the race?!
Wow. He's certainly
popular. Who is he?
What? Have you been
living under a rock?
That's Haruka Tenoh. The
most talented young driver
to hit the Japanese
circuit in years!
But his sweetest ride
doesn't have wheels.
Those "birds" up there are
Tenohmaru and Kaiohmaru.
They belong to
him and his girlfriend.
They go to school in those?!
What a life.
Where have you been,
Michiru? You're late.
The wind is restless today.
Look. Isn't that Michiru
Kaioh, the famous violinist?
So the rumors about her
dating Haruka Tenoh were true?!
No way!
I hate to admit it,
but they really do
make a perfect couple.
I guess. And they do go to
the same school.
You know, the one that
was in the news.
Oh! I didn't realize they
went to Mugen Academy.
Finally!
Hi, Motoki! Hi, everyone!
Hey, Usagi. Hi, Naru.
Come on in.
You're late, as usual!
But I don't mind. I was able
to finish an entire book
while I waited for you.
[giggle]
This is Ami Mizuno. She's a
genius with an IQ of 300,
and a heart as big
as her brain.
I knew you'd be the last one
to get here. Pigs will fly
before Usagi's on time.
That's mean, Rei! You
don't have to rub it in!
This is Rei Hino. She's a
beautiful shrine maiden with
amazing spiritual powers.
Hey! 'Bout time, Usagi.
Where ya been?
This is Minako Aino. Long
before the rest of us
awakened as Sailor
Guardians, she was
fighting evil as Sailor V.
Hurry up! Get over here!
You absolutely have
to try this new game!
This is Makoto Kino. She's
strong, but also a "girly
girl" with many talents.
She's a great cook and
has a green thumb too!
We were all friends in a
past life, and fate brought
us together again as
Sailor Guardians.
As long as we're a team,
there isn't anything we
can't overcome.
What is "Battle Lap"? Is it
new racing game or something?
Yup! It's so realistic
you feel like you're
right on the track!
Here's your helmet.
Just step on the clutch,
and start the engine.
The engine noise is so loud!
And I can feel the vibration!
You wanna change gears
quickly. Keep shifting and
go straight to fifth.
[nervous groans]
This is scary! It's like
I'm driving a real race car!
Push harder on your
throttle. Increase the RPM.
Huh? Who's that?
Holy cow!
You were a lap behind a
minute ago, but now you're
neck and neck!
Whoa. That's unreal!
Take a look at his time!
He handles those turns like
a real race car driver!
I can't see. How
fast is he going?
400 kilometers per hour?!
[gasp] Usagi, look
out for the wall!
Huh? [scream]
Are you okay?
This game feels real even
when you crash...
That speed. Did you realize
how fast you were going?
It didn't feel fast at all.
I could hardly sense
anything with the helmet on.
Really?
If that's true you should
try out the track sometime.
You might have a hidden
talent for racing.
[chuckle]
[gasp]
Oh, I'm sorry.
Your eyes...
Their color has a
certain air of nobility.
You may have been a
prince in a past life.
That's an odd thing to say
to a guy you don't know.
This mirror, it reflects
one's previous lives.
Well, I gotta go.
Let's race sometime.
See ya, Bun‐head.
He is so cool!
Apologies. Forget
what I just said.
I didn't mean
anything by it.
Have a good day.
You seem to have made
a new friend in there.
Jealous?
Don't be ridiculous.
That bun‐head girl. She
seemed so innocent and
naiïve. I thought
it was cute.
I'm in love...
Yeah, I haven't crushed on
anybody this hard in a while.
Hey, that cool guy!
Huh?
I think he was someone
famous. I know I've seen his
face before. You may have
just met a celebrity!
I've seen that uniform.
Oh. That's right! It's the
one from Mugen Academy.
Mugen Academy!
Mugen Academy?
What? You've never
heard of it?
The Tokyo Bay Land
Reclamation Project
recently developed several
large tracts for
commercial use. The biggest
one is Sankakusu, home to
the Mugen District and its
new private school.
Umino! Where did
you come from?!
Soon after the Academy
opened, its prestige went
through the roof! Tons
of famous actors
and musicians study there.
They have Olympic athletes
too. It's like a whole
school full of the best
and the brightest!
Wow, Minako. You're
well‐informed.
I heard they have a massive
concert hall their students
get to use. So there
are some really
big, super‐hot teen
sensations that perform
there all the time!
Oh! You could meet
celebrities just by going to
school. I'd transfer there
tomorrow if I could.
You're so star‐struck.
A school for the best and
brightest In other words, a
school Usagi couldn't get
into in a million years.
[groan]
Shush, Rei. That's true,
but don't say it.
And there's the death blow.
Thanks, Ami...
Look! There he is!
I knew I'd seen
him somewhere.
I just couldn't remember.
His name is Haruka Tenoh.
He's Japan's newest
racing prodigy!
Cool...
So he's an actual race
car driver? Wow.
No wonder he's so good.
[fangirling scream]
Do you think he hangs around
Juban Shopping District?
Maybe we can see him again.
[laughing]
Hey look! They go
to Mugen Academy, too.
I'm super jealous. Their
uniform's are so cute!
Yeah!
[gasp]
[roar]
[growling roar]
I'll get Naru and Umino to
safety. You be careful!
Don't worry. I will!
Ready. Let's transform!
Right!
Moon Cosmic Power Make Up!
Mercury Planet Power
Make Up!
Mars Planet Power Make Up!
Jupiter Planet Power
Make Up!
Venus Planet Power Make Up!
I am the Pretty Guardian who
fights for love and for justice.
I am Sailor Moon!
And now, in the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
Protected by Mercury,
the Planet of water,
Guardian of Wisdom.
I am Sailor Mercury!
Douse yourself in water,
and repent!
Protected by Mars,
the Planet of Fire,
Guardian of War.
I am Sailor Mars!
In the name of Mars,
I'll chastise you!
Protected by Jupiter, the
Planet of Thunder,
Guardian of Protection.
I am Sailor Jupiter!
I'll fill you with regret,
it'll leave you numb!
Protected by Venus, the
Planet of Beauty,
Guardian of Love.
I am Sailor Venus!
In the name of Venus, I will
punish you with love!
[grunts]
What is it?
Is it an atavism?
Whatever it is, there's a
girl trapped inside!
Stand back. I'll free her.
Evil Spirit, be gone!
It's okay. We got this.
Ready, Jupiter?
[affirmative grunt]
Venus Wink Chain Sword!
Jupiter Coconut Cyclone!
[roaring]
What just happened?
She needs medical
attention! Call for help!
Yeah. Okay!
Someone's watching us...
Is it another enemy?
Something wrong?
No. Everything's fine.
My brooch lit up and
started making sounds
right before that girl
turned into a monster.
Was the Legendary Silver
Crystal trying to warn me?
Look at those features...
It's an atavism.
Are you positive?
All of you watched the
news this morning, right?
Did you see the story
about the students
who were attacked, allegedly
by some kind of monster?
Luna, weren't the students
in that story from Mugen
Academy too?
Mmhm.
A new enemy? So soon?
Mugen Academy and
de‐evolution...
Smells fishy if you ask me.
Then we agree. We'll
investigate Mugen Academy
as soon as possible.
[affirmative grunts]
Let's go.
To Mugen Academy.
Yikes! It's another atavism!
Well I don't care! Anything
that tries to disturb love
and justice will
answer to me!
Next time, "Act.27 Infinity
1 Premonition, Part 2."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.