Where am I?
Is this the
Moon Castle?
[gasp]
Is that-?!
Wait!
Tuxedo Mask!
I know it's you
Tuxedo Mask.
Please Mamo, just
say something.
Usagi...
Usagi!
That doesn't sound
like him?
Usagi!
Agh!
Darn it. It's only
you, Luna.
Only me?! Well 'good
morning' to you too!
I didn't mean it like that.
You just woke me right when
my dream was getting good.
Tuxedo Mask's, I
mean, Mamo's watch...
It stopped again, after
we came back from the
Moon.
Does that mean
something? Is he safe?
Fine. Ignore me then.
Huh?
It's not like I'm
important or anything.
Oh Luna...
You know I love you.
Are you sure you're
okay, Usagi?
It looked like you were
having a nightmare.
Aww. Really? Well,
don't worry, Luna.
I'm fine now.
There ya go. I'm
gonna change for
school.
Usagi...
So much has happened.
And now all these memories
from the past are flooding
back too. I know it hasn't
been easy. Yet you
put on a brave face.
Okay, I'm good to go.
Hey Usagi, remember you
can talk to me about
anything okay?
Don't forget. We're
partners. We're in
this together.
Yeah. I know
we are.
But I'm alright.
Really.
The Legendary
Silver Crystal...
On the Moon, Queen
Serenity said its power
comes from my heart.
If that's true, then I
can't keep being so sad.
If I want the Silver
Crystal's light to
come back, then I
have to be strong.
I'll be at the command
center if you need me,
Usagi.
Sure. Let me know if
anything happens, okay?
[gasp]
Huh?
It moved?!
Huh?!
From behind, he almost
looks like... But, no.
It couldn't be...
Still... why did the watch
start ticking again?
Hey, there!
Are you the new part-
timer my uncle sent?
Oh! You're that high
school kid who was with
Usagi the other day, right?
Usagi...
Endo, why don't you
go on in. I'll just
be a sec.
Sure.
Huh?
What happened? What
am I doing in front
of the arcade?
Wait Endo! Where
are you going?
That guy who just left
isn't Endo anymore. I am
your best friend now.
Understand?
Yes. You're Endo.
Hey Motoki! Are
you here?
Hey Reika!
I'm over here!
Your book came. So I
thought I'd drop it
off.
Oh thanks.
Oh? Is this the new
guy you're training?
What are you
talking about?
It's Endo. He's been
my best friend for
years.
Uh, that's Endo?
That's for geology class.
We have to write a term
paper on it.
Are you interested
in precious stones?
Jadeite, Nephrite,
Kunzite, Zoisite...
Wow. You know your
minerals pretty well.
Just those four.
They're special to
me.
Oh my goodness!
Ami's place is
incredible!
[giggling]
Everything is so
shiny and clean!
[gasp]
There's even marble
in the lobby!
Quiet! Please lower
your voice, Usagi.
You're embarrassing us.
And why did you insist
on bringing so many
snacks?
We can't possibly
eat them all.
Ah, come on! We're having
a slumber party, right?
So we're supposed to
stuff our faces!
Usagi! We're not here
for a party. Ami wants
to have a meeting.
[giggling]
Can't we do both?
Uh. Hey guys? Can I
ask you something?
Do I look too suspicious
carrying this sword around?
I don't want to get
stopped by security.
Uh, yeah you
look suspicious!
Come on!
This is a diamond. The
hardest natural substance
on Earth. Even its name
comes from the Greek
word for "unbreakable".
Okay, Minako, now I
want you to hit it
with the stone sword.
Sure!
[gasps]
Oh no, Minako!
You broke it!
What do I do? I didn't
mean to! I'm so sorry
Ami!
Don't worry about it,
Minako. This is what
I thought would happen.
But it didn't
just break.
It's the hardest stone
on Earth and it shattered
into little pieces.
Both the sword and the rock
fragment we brought back
from the Moon are composed
of very strong elements
not found here.
I still don't know
what they are exactly.
But they're toxic.
They're toxic?
But didn't Queen Serenity
say it was a sacred sword?
That is a legendary sacred
sword, intended to protect
the princess...
Yes, but I suspect that
the sword and possibly
the entire Moon
Kingdom was turned
into this toxic stone.
The Moon Castle... I can
still picture it. So
beautiful.
It gleamed like crystal.
Even the moon itself
was brighter then. It's
so desolate now.
Ami are you trying to
tell us that the enemy
turned our kingdom
into a dead planet?
Possibly.
Aww. Look at Usagi.
Let's let her sleep
for a while.
Something like this happened
to me once before.
I woke up at sunset
in someone else's bed.
Only then, I was
with Mamo...
So strange... Why
did I come here?
And why is my
heart racing?
Huh?
[gasp]
Oh! Hey there Usagi!
I don't believe it!
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Mamo? Is that you?
Usagi, this is my
best friend Endo.
He just started working
here part time. Come say hi!
Huh?
Furuhata and I go
to the same college.
You're not Mamo,
are you.
Sailor Moon wears buns
like these in her hair
too.
I guess it's popular look.
That voice though...
And it feels so much
like him.
So I heard you're very
good at the Sailor V game.
Perhaps you could
give me a lesson.
I'm not really that
good, but I'll give
it a try.
Something's not right.
He's that same guy
from this morning!
Ami, are you all
there? It's urgent.
We're here. Is
something wrong?
Mamoru Chiba?!
Impossible. The Dark
Kingdom kidnapped him.
They wouldn't
just let him go.
But the face...
It must be him.
Look closer, at his
eyes. They're different!
Something doesn't
feel right.
That's not Mamoru Chiba.
We need to go warn Usagi.
Oh no...
Usagi, wait!
Are you going to the
arcade to see him
again?
That guy is not
Mamoru Chiba.
I know. You don't
need to tell me that.
Then why are you going?
Just leave me alone!
I know what I'm doing!
Usagi!
I did it again. My concern's
just making things worse
for her.
You lied to me before. You
are good at this game.
It's like you know
everything about Sailor V.
Yeah, she's really
strong and loyal, too.
It sounds like you've
actually met her.
Believe it or not, I
once saw Sailor V
myself.
Really?
Yeah. I saw her fighting
some bad guys once. She
seemed pretty cool.
I know right? You can
count on her.
She's a lot more responsible
than me for sure.
You mean more than
Sailor Moon.
You wear your hair
just like she does.
Makes you seem a lot
like Sailor Moon to me.
I wonder where she is.
I haven't heard much
about her lately.
Perhaps she's at a
secret command center?
[gasp]
Command Center?
I, uh... have
to go home now.
Usagi...
Your bag.
Come back tomorrow.
Let's you and I get
better acquainted.
I want to know everything
about you, Usagi.
Goodbye!
The mind control
didn't work.
Oh my gosh! Oh my gosh!
Oh my gosh! I almost
told him all my secrets!
Usagi...
No. It's Usako. Please
Mamo... Call me Usako
again.
She doesn't look
okay. I'm worried.
Yeah. Me too.
Seriously?! Motoki's
with him again?!
What makes him so special?
He's just the new guy.
Mako, did you hear
that? Let's talk
to her.
Yeah.
Um, excuse me...
You were talking about
Furu just now. Are you
a friend of his?
You heard that? Oh!
I'm so embarrassed!
You wouldn't happen to
also know his friend
Endo, would you?
Because he looks an
awful lot like someone our
friend's been looking for.
Well I know Motoki. He and
I go to college together.
But I only met that guy
with him recently.
There was an Endo that he
used to hang out with a
lot but that was a
different person.
A skinny guy,
who wore glasses.
I haven't really
seen him lately.
That guy supposedly
goes to our college
too.
But I've never seen him
there and my friends
haven't either.
Hm?
I'll get into the command
center. One way or another.
Mind if I interrupt
your game?
What exactly are
you playing at
with Usagi?
Hmph!
What happened Mako?
We got your call and
raced here as fast
as we could.
What's the emergency?
Usagi. Thank goodness
you're here.
Stay away from that
new guy at the arcade!
So you confronted him?
Did you find out what
he wants?
Looks like he is our
enemy! He's after the
Legendary Silver Crystal.
You still have it,
don't you Usagi?
It's safe?
But, he can't be bad.
Because...
He never touched the
Crystal. It's still
around my neck.
The alarm's going off?
Is there an intruder?
Impossible! We're the
only ones who can enter.
The command center's shielded.
Usagi! Look out!
Mako?!
Oo. So close.
That girl is useless!
Tuxedo Mask!
So the entrance to your
secret Command Center
was right under the
Sailor V game!
But because of its
powerful shield, we
couldn't detect it.
Luckily we didn't
have to.
I hypnotized that pathetic
girl easily. She led us
right here.
That can't be right.
It's impossible!
Enough! Time
to transform!
Venus Power
Make Up!
Mercury Power
Mars Power
Make Up!
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
beauty!
I am Sailor Venus!
In the name of Venus,
I will punish you!
With the
power of love!
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
intelligence!
I am Sailor Mercury!
Douse yourself in
water and repent!
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for passion!
I am Sailor Mars!
In the name of Mars,
I'll chastise you!
[attack yell]
Venus!
I must have the
Crystal! Give
it to me!
Usagi!
That's no way to treat
a girl! Time for some
tough love!
Venus Love Me Chain!
[screaming]
Agh! No you don't!
Agh!
He's too powerful!
He's going to destroy the
whole command center!
[gasp]
The Silver Crystal!
Mercury Aqua Mist!
[scream]
[evil chuckling]
At last! I have it!
The Silver Crystal
is mine!
Not so fast!
[grunting]
You underestimate me!
[scream]
Why...
Why is everyone
fighting Tuxedo
Mask?
Usagi!
You have to fight him!
Hurry! What are you
waiting for?!
[gasp]
[evil laughter]
Fight?
Fight Tuxedo Mask? This
isn't real. It can't
be happening!
He was kidnapped!
Listen to me, he's
not who you think
he is.
That's not the real
Tuxedo Mask! He's
a fake!
Now Princess, take my
hand and come with me!
Take his hand...
Snap out of it, Usagi!
That's not the man you
love!
I'm sorry. I know I've
let you down before. But
please!
You have to believe me!
I'm your partner, Usagi. I
know who your true love is.
That man is an impostor and
I will not let him hurt you!
[gasp]
Get off me filthy beast!
[screaming]
Luna!
Hang on, Luna!
Hmph! As if a pathetic
little cat could hurt me!
Luna was right! You're
not Tuxedo Mask!
You're not the
man I love!
Moon Prism Power
Make Up!
Luna. Please open
your eyes, Luna.
I'm so sorry.
I love you.
What the-?
Sailor Moon!
Quickly!
If you hurry, you can
heal everyone with
the Moon Stick!
Moon Healing Escalation!
You are an impostor!
You are my enemy!
You hurt Luna! And you
hurt my other friends
too!
I will never
forgive you!
[chuckling]
[gasp]
No! Not her again!
You have done well,
Tuxedo Mask.
Now that I have obtained
the Legendary Silver
Crystal,
We can dispose
of these girls.
Sailor Guardians, your
secret command center
will be your grave!
But why? What did
we do to you?
[snickering]
No matter what life we
meet in, it seems you are
always a weak little girl.
She couldn't be...
Allow me to introduce
myself. I am Queen Beryl,
ruler of the Dark Kingdom.
Unlike the last time we
met, there won't be
any survivors.
Does she really not
remember me?
Then again, I'm a very
different person now.
Poor little Princess
Serenity, you missed
your beloved Endymion,
didn't you?
Well now he's going
to kill you.
Did you say,
Endymion?
You're lying.
The man I'm looking
at, is really Mamo?
Mamo! Do I really
have to fight you?!
No! I can't do it!
But... what choice
do I have?
If this is our destiny,
the reason we were reborn,
then so be it!
Act. 12 Enemy
Queen Metalia
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.