Tuxedo Mask!
Open your eyes!
Someone...
Is calling to me.
Long hair...
That shimmers
like moonlight...
The one who calls out
to me in my dreams...
It is you?
Sailor Moon?
You're sad. A face such
as yours should never
be sad.
Why are you crying?
Wait! Something like
this has happened
before...
Endymion!
Please don't leave
me, Endymion!
Endymion!
Endymion? That's...
my name?
I was reborn here on
Earth as Mamoru Chiba.
I remember now...
I came back...
to be with you
again...
I found you...
Serenity.
My love...
Hmph!
[gasp]
[screaming]
Sailor Moon!
The crescent
moon symbol!
[gasp]
Something's happening
to Sailor Moon!
Her body is
changing!
Usagi... she's...
Is that Usagi?
No. That's Princess
Serenity...
[gasp]
His broken watch, it's
ticking again... running
backwards.
Like it's turning
back time.
To the memories I
lost... that are
starting to return.
Unhappy memories.
[screaming]
[gasp]
It's all coming
back to me.
I remember now.
You are my one
true love, Endymion.
Long ago I saw a planet full
of hope and possibilities. Like
your eyes, it was a deep and
captivating blue that
mesmerized me.
So I secretly left the
Moon and came to visit.
And then I saw you,
Endymion, the Earth's
prince and heir...
You were so handsome.
With such charm and
strength. I came to this
planet many times just to
catch a glimpse of you.
Then one day...
You saw me.
And before we knew it,
we were falling in love.
Endymion, this has to
stop. We mustn't see
each other anymore.
Why?
People from the Earth
and people from the
Moon are not allowed
to be together.
It's forbidden. It's
the will of the gods.
We shouldn't, we
mustn't fall in love.
But it was too late...
Come on, men! Let's
conquer the Moon
Kingdom!
The Legendary Silver
Crystal will be ours!
Stop this! I am your
prince! Cease this
warfare!
Endymion?! Have you
turned against us?!
This is all her fault!
[gasp]
I will destroy you!
[screaming]
Endymion! No!
Please, say something!
Open your eyes!
We were reborn. Did we
find each other just
to be separated again?
Fate cannot
be that cruel.
I never got to tell you,
how I really feel about
you.
I love you! You're my
one and only true love!
Tuxedo Mask!
[crying]
[grunting]
So bright!
And powerful!
We can't get
anywhere near
them!
Usagi's tear crystalized!
It's gleaming!
It's too bright!
I can't see a
thing!
That brilliant,
white light...
Could it be...
I didn't think that the
seal would be broken
for a long time.
But there it is...
The Legendary
Silver Crystal!
Oh yes! What extraordinary
power! I can feel its energy
flowing through me! It can be
none other than the
Legendary Silver
Crystal!
Finally, the real
Crystal has appeared
at last!
A ball of light split
off from the Crystal.
And now it's going
into Tuxedo Mask!
The light...
it disappeared.
Queen Beryl,
you're here.
Now, Kunzite!
Hurry!
Seize the Legendary
Silver Crystal for
the glory of the
Dark Kingdom!
At once!
[grunting]
Wait Kunzite!
Don't do this!
Get out of my way!
Supreme Thunder!
Mercury Aqua Mist!
What?!
Evil Spirit, be gone!
[screaming]
Well, I'll just have
to destroy you myself!
[screaming]
Sailor Moon,
are you okay?
[gasp]
Where is Tuxedo Mask?
[snickering]
[evil laughter]
Tuxedo Mask!
Can't we save
him for her?!
We can't! We have to
protect the princess!
Looks like I'll be leaving
with the Crystal and Tuxedo
Mask!
Please, Sailor
Moon, stay back!
Let go!
I'm done with you
Sailor Guardians!
Please! Please
don't take him!
[crying]
No! Please just
let him go!
[crying]
Please, I beg
of you!
Don't go!
Mamo!
[crying]
Sailor Moon...
I mean, Serenity,
my Princess...
Has your memory
come back?
So you remember now that
I, Sailor Venus,
am true leader of
the Sailor Guardians.
And how we four were
assigned to protect
you.
Do you recall our kingdom,
Silver Millennium? The glory
that it once was?
[sigh]
Yes, I remember.
So the Moon Kingdom's
real Princess isn't
Minako?
It's actually Usagi?
I'm so sorry we had
to deceive you all,
but it was necessary
to protect both the
Princess and the
Legendary Silver
Crystal.
Then what's the
whole story?
Please tell us what
happened in the past.
Mhm. Back in ancient times,
the Earth was one big
country, a kingdom
unto itself.
The Moon was a separate
realm, distinct from
its close neighbor.
All of you served the Princess
as Sailor Guardians. You were
her bodyguards, her protectors.
Then came that
terrible day...
The Earth went to war with
the Moon and everything
changed.
That's right...
In our past lives
we were fighting.
As Guardians, we were
ready to lay down our
lives for the Princess.
Indeed. But while you were
busy trying to repel wave
after wave of Earth soldiers,
Endymion, the Earth's prince
and sole heir, fought to
make peace.
Sadly one of his own people
turned on him, and struck
him down.
Are you saying that
prince was Tuxedo
Mask?
Yes, that is correct.
The boy, Mamoru Chiba,
is Prince Endymion
reincarnate.
The terrible tragedy that
befell the Moon never should
have happened, but our enemy
brainwashed the people of
Earth and drove them to
attack us. Still, the Moon
Kingdom fought back and
managed to seal the
evil away.
So this is history
repeating itself.
It's so awful. Why is
this happening again?
That woman! She must
have broken the seal
and freed the evil!
Who are you talking
about?
Do you mean that woman
who took Tuxedo Mask?
Did you recognize
her? Who is she?
Oh Minako! Tell me that
you know where she's
taken Mamo!
Please! I need
to find him!
I'm sorry. I don't
know. Please calm
down, Princess.
Stop calling me that!
I'm not a princess!
I'm Usagi Tsukino!
I'm not royalty! I'm
just a normal girl in
middle school!
I'm just a girl in
love with a boy.
The only thing
I want is Mamo!
[crying]
It's still hard
to believe...
This was my tear but it's
also the Legendary
Silver Crystal we've
been looking for.
It's not your tear. It's
your strong love for
Endymion that manifested in
this world as the Crystal.
Endymion.
[gasp]
Mamo! No...
Ah! Princess!
Princess! Are
you all right?
What happened?
She fainted! It was
all too much!
Princess? Princess?!
Have you found the
Legendary Silver
Crystal yet?
No, my Queen. And we've
searched his entire body.
I don't understand. With
my own eyes, I witnessed
the radiant light
of the Crystal!
I saw it get drawn
into his body!
Damn! Find it! Whatever
it takes! But until you
do keep him alive.
Yes, my Queen.
Who's he? I feel like
I've seen him before.
I agree with you.
He looks familiar.
It's like I knew him
from somewhere a long
time ago.
Endymion!
[gasp]
Endy-
Agh!
So what do you
think, Kunzite?
Uh, no. He doesn't
look familiar to me.
Let's focus. The only
thing that matters is
finding the Legendary
Silver Crystal for
our Great Ruler,
nothing else!
Without the Legendary
Silver Crystal you are
of no use to me!
[screaming]
Noo!
How many nightmares
has it been?
How many more times
will I wake up crying?
[crying]
After the Moon Kingdom fell,
Artemis and I were placed in
suspended animation.
And part of my memory
was sealed away.
I slept for a
long time.
But then I woke up
and met you, Usagi.
Only I didn't trust
you enough...
And I ended up putting
you through so much
pain and suffering.
I failed you.
I'm sorry.
Come on, Luna. You
gotta get up. Let's
go see Usagi.
But Artemis...
We want to see her.
We need her with us.
Usagi is the heart
of this team.
If she isn't happy
and smiling then
neither are we.
You feel it too.
You're her partner.
Yeah. You're right.
Thanks so much for
stopping by.
I'm sure she'll be happy to
see you. Please come in.
How is she doing?
Is she feeling better?
I'm not sure.
She hasn't come out
of her room for quite
a while.
Hey Usagi? It's
Luna. Everyone's
here to see you?
We came to check
on you. Can we
come in?
Give me a sec.
Sure.
Okay!
[gasp]
[gasps]
Um, hi...
everyone.
Usagi?
What happened
to your hair?
Okay, I finished
cutting.
This one's too small, I
think we can wrap around
one more time.
Whadya think?
Like it?
Mm hmm...
I think this is how
it was before, right?
When did your
hair get so long.
Ever since that day, it
just started growing
really fast.
Back when you were the
Princess you would always
let your hair grow long.
Now that your memory's
back, your body's
just changing back
a little too.
Don't worry about it.
My body's changing? Does
that mean I'm turning
into the princess?
Then who am I now?
It's like I've
stopped being me.
Usagi? Is this the
crystal on the
table, here?
Yeah.
But it hasn't been
glowing lately.
Now it just looks
like an ordinary
piece of cut glass.
Not like that day with
him, when it shone as
bright as the sun.
That day...
[gasp]
Tuxedo mask! What's
happening to him?!
Where is he?!
It'll be okay.
No! We have to rescue
him! If we don't hurry
he'll be-
I... Mamo!
Please don't cry!
I'm sure he's fine!
I just can't take it!
I'm so scared! He's
gone!
And I don't know
what to do.
Come on, Usagi! Don't
lose hope! Pull yourself
together now!
The Usagi I know is
stronger than that!
You really think,
that I'm strong?
Back in the Moon Kingdom
whenever we were sad,
Princess Serenity was
always there to cheer
us up with her sweet
smile.
Just like you've
always done for me.
I can't Ami! I'm
not the Princess!
That's right.
You're not.
You're Usagi
Tsukino.
And you don't have
to follow anyone
else's destiny
but your own.
Even so, you've been
reborn now for a reason.
And we don't care why
or what your fate is
now.
We'll help you
no matter what.
Yes, that's right. We'll
be with you, come what
may.
Thank you.
[crying]
Usagi.
Thank you, guys. I
don't know what I'd
do without you!
But I still don't know
how to save Mamo!
[crying]
I think we should
go to the Moon.
Hnh?
The Dark Kingdom's location,
who our evil enemy really is,
and everything you wanted to
know about the Silver Crystal...
All the information...
All the answers are
there, on the Moon.
The moon?
The Moon, our former home.
Where Silver Millennium
once stood.
I was happy there.
Surrounded by my
dearest friends.
And then I found my
one true love...
Such precious moments.
I treasured them all!
I lost that happiness once,
I won't let it be stolen
from me again!
Never again! I will
not be a tragic
princess!
All right!
Let's go!
Let's find out what
secrets the Moon holds!
[determined grunts]
This is the Moon?
It's so dark.
And there's no sound at
all here. It feels so
strange.
What are those ruins?
Silver Millennium. This
is where are kingdom
once existed.
[gasp] Luna?
Who is that?
Act. 10- Moon
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.