No!
Sailor Mars!
What are you doing here?
Answer me, Chibi-Usa!
So that's Chibi-Usa?
Have you been spying on
us this whole time?
You know something about
this, don't you?!
Was this your plan? Are you
with those kidnappers?!
[gasp]
Usagi, don't!
Luna? Why are you
defending her?!
You need to calm down.
She's getting away!
Listen to me!
The Silver Crystal?
Go easy on her. She's just a
child. If you're too harsh
she won't tell us anything.
But she's...
Welcome home, sweetheart.
Oh? Isn't Chibi-Usa
with you?
I don't know where she
is! And I don't care!
How could I yell at a child
like that? I'm such an awful
person...
[doorbell ringing]
Usako?
Sorry to bother you
but I need your help.
She must have wandered
around for hours before
she ended up at that park.
I think she was
afraid to go home.
Maybe it's best that she
stays here tonight. Usako
seemed really upset.
Usagi didn't mean it. Deep
down, she understands.
And Chibi-Usa...
she's just scared.
I think she may have been
through some kind of trauma.
She doesn't trust us because
she doesn't know us.
But once she does, I'm
sure she'll open up.
She's not a threat.
She's just a little girl.
Mommy? Mommy,
where are you?
If something should ever
happen to me, it will all be
up to you...
The legendary Guardian,
Sailor Moon, is invincible.
Nothing can defeat her.
Daddy! Mommy!
[crying]
Please do not cry, milady.
Huh?
My magical rose has
begun to wilt.
Only the smile of a fair
maiden can revive it. Here.
Will you help it
bloom again?
Thank you. I am Tuxedo
Mask, at your service.
And my name is Luna.
Did you have a bad
dream, little one?
Pretty good, right? I
should be a professional
ventriloquist.
[gasp] Wait a sec!
I have a toy that I can make
talk, too! This is my Luna P
ball.
But I just call it Luna P.
"Luna P"?
Small Lady.
Small Lady!
Huh? Who is "Small Lady"?
That's my name.
Mommy gave it to me.
So, we've got Small
Lady and Luna P.
Huh?
Oh, is that your house key?
This key is very important.
I need it to get home.
Is home far away?
[sigh]
Lay down. Time for Small
Lady to get some sleep.
Hey, do you know if Sailor
Moon is really strong?
Invincible.
I wonder if she could
save my mommy.
Aww.
Poor thing. Chibi-Usa's just
a lost little girl who
misses her mom and dad.
Did she say who they were
or where she was from?
She didn't say anything
else. That's all Mamoru was
able to get out of her.
Ah. But if he's making
progress, we should probably
just leave her to him for now.
We've got bigger worries.
Like the Black Moon...
What's that? Are you playing
chess against the computer?
Um... yeah.
Really? Is chess as
difficult as they say it is?
It certainly looks confusing.
[chuckle] It's actually not.
Chess is a game of
cause and effect. You make
a move and your opponent
makes a counter move.
Once you figure out
their strategy, you can
anticipate what they are
going to do next.
And our enemy? What are
they going to do next?
I'm not sure. I don't know
who they are, or what
they're after.
But there's one thing
about this new enemy of
which I am certain...
They aren't coming.
They're already here.
[gasp]
[stunned gasp]
Chibi-Usa... You stayed
with Mamo last night?
And Luna, too?
Oh there you are!
Thank goodness you're home!
I was so worried about you,
my little Chibi-Usa!
Are you hungry at all?
How about I fix
you some nice--
[awkward groan]
Were you able to calm
down last night?
Chibi-Usa has something
around her neck that looks
just like the "Legendary
Silver Crystal."
I know. I saw it, too. And
there's a strange key on the
chain with it.
She told me the reason she
came here was to ask Sailor
Moon for help.
She thinks you are the only
one who can save her mom.
Let's just give it a bit
more time, 'kay?
[sigh]
Cheer up, Usako. Please.
No matter how many times I
stare at the Malefic Black
Crystal reactor, the
immensity of its power
never ceases to amaze me.
Prince Demande!
You needn't worry, brother.
As per your instructions, I
have been using the energy
of the "Malefic Black
Crystal" to produce Droid
soldiers and send them en
masse to Earth.
Those simple automatons are
little more than puppets,
until your alchemy
breathes life into them.
Excellent work.
Brother, I understand
you've captured Sailor Mars.
Yes.
But that was a rather
aggressive move, don't
you think?
What is it you're planning?
Are you questioning my
orders, Saphir?
My plans are my own.
I'm sure he wasn't
questioning anything.
Saphir's a good little
soldier. Always faithful.
As am I, my Prince. I will
obey your every command.
Rubeus, where is
Sailor Mars now?
She's locked away in
the Dark Chamber, right
where I left her.
Her will is quite strong. I
wasn't able to break her.
She wouldn't give up any
information about "The
Legendary Silver Crystal."
Wiseman...
Do as you will, my Prince.
But it may be worthwhile to
keep her. She can still be
put to good use.
Then I shall keep Sailor
Mars alive for the time
being.
Prince Demande!
May I have a turn?
As third eldest of the
Spectre Sisters, I,
Berthier, wish to serve you.
And how do you
propose to do that?
I'd like to take on the
Sailor Guardians with power
of water. I feel the
presence of the "Rabbit"
close to her.
The "Legendary Silver Crystal"
may be nearby too.
Go.
Code 002. Operation
"Re-move."
There is an active piece in
play that needs to be
cleared from the board.
Aww man. No water again?!
These sinks are always
breaking. It's such a pain!
There's the ones in
the locker room?
But those are so far away.
I wonder what the problem
is. Could there be something
wrong with the pipes?
Listen to the water. Hear
its ripples. Feel its flow.
[gasp]
This main's busted. We're
lucky the school didn't
flood!
Thanks, Miss Mizuno! I don't
know how you knew it was
broken, but I'll get
this fixed right away!
[nervous laugh]
Not bad.
[gasp]
But water divining
without a rod or pendulum
is practically heresy.
Don't you know that?
[gasp]
Who was that? Another enemy?
The latest threat from the
Black Moon?
No. I shouldn't assume the
worst. I'm just a bit on
edge.
But our friend is missing.
We need to be vigilant.
Rei... I hope you are alright.
Hi, Ami!
Hi, Naru?!
Usagi was feeling a little
down, so I thought we'd
swim!
[grumbling in water]
I didn't know you belonged
to this health club!
Um... Well, my father's the one
who's the member. I just
come here once in a while.
What does your father
do for a living, Ami?
He's a Japanese-style
artist.
You mean, like a painter?
How cool!
I don't see him much. He
and my mom are divorced.
But back when I was little,
my father taught me a lot.
Swimming and playing chess,
they still calm me down and
help me stay focused.
Aww. That's nice.
Is this your first
visit to Japan?
Yes. I'm so excited to
participate in the World
Chess Championship.
Now, Miss Berthier, in
addition to being the third
best professional chess
player in the world, I
understand you're
also one of this planet's
foremost expert dowsers.
Tell us a bit about that.
Dowsing is an
ancient science that
many people nowadays
have never heard of.
Or if they have, they
know only of using a
divining rod to find water.
But I've perfected my
pendulum technique so that
I can find anything.
And does dowsing in any way
enhance your chess game?
Yes. I use my pendulum in
every match. Its swings show
me where to move my pieces.
Fascinating!
Before we went on air
you mentioned there
was a specific player
you wanted to face?
Yes.
Junior Chess Champion,
Ami Mizuno.
[gasps]
Ami, if you're watching, I'd
like to challenge you to an
individual match.
Thank you for accepting my
challenge. I've been wanting
to meet you.
You have? Why me?
Call it a professional
interest.
Are you as proficient at
dowsing as they said on TV?
Could you even find
a missing person?
Why don't you try
it yourself?
It uses the same skills
finding water does...
Sailor Mercury.
Let's make a bet. The victor
can have whatever she wants.
May the best woman win.
Sailor Mars...
If you win the game, I'll
give her back to you.
And if you should win...
...what is it that
you want from me?
The "Rabbit."
That brat's around
here somewhere. I can
sense her nearby.
By "Rabbit" do you
mean... who I think?
[evil chuckling]
So The Black Moon is
after Chibi-Usa. But why?
Who is she to them?
My dowsing pendulum is made
from the "Malefic Black
Crystal"...
It can tell me anything...
even the thoughts in your
head.
Yes... You're
afraid Mercury.
You're afraid to lose Mars.
It reminds you of when you
lost someone long ago.
I need to focus. I
can't let her get to me.
You're alone. And Deep down
you know that's never going
to change.
It's inevitable. No matter
how much you love the people
you care about, someday
they're going to leave you.
[gasp]
Poor little Sailor Mercury.
Fate was not kind to you in
the past and I'm afraid
the future does not look good.
Your worst fears are going
to be realized... over
and over again.
You're going to lose this
game, Sailor Mercury. You're
going to lose everything!
Your precious friends, your
family, even your life as a
Sailor Guardian!
[gasp]
[snicker]
[chuckle]
Ami!
You can do it, Ami!
Shh!
Miss! You need to be quiet!
We're so sorry! She
won't do it again!
If she continues to
interrupt the match,
I'm going to have to
ask you to leave!
I promise! She'll be
quiet from now on!
What's the matter with you?
Thank you!
What happened? I had her
right where I wanted her!
You're right,
Miss Berthier.
I am alone in this world...
And there will come a day,
when I have to say goodbye
to the people I love.
But, I'm not going
to feel sad.
Because there have been
many happy moments in my
life and no one can take
those away from me!
So even if I lose
those I love!
As long as I hold those
precious memories close
to my heart...
I'm never alone!
[gasp]
Huh?
Checkmate.
[cheering]
Did she win?
Yay! Way to go Ami!
How could I lose?
It's not possible!
There! Now give
back Sailor Mars!
You won the match,
but not the game!
[gasp]
Hey! Let us through!
We need to get to Ami!
No! Stay back!
[gasp]
As you can plainly see,
this isn't over yet.
And I left surprises for
your little friends, too.
If you resign and knock over
your king, I promise not to
hurt you.
I won't let you have
Chibi-Usa. She and Sailor
Mars are not pawns!
I'm done playing games!
Mercury Star
Power! Make up!
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for intelligence.
I am Sailor Mercury!
Douse yourself in
water and repent!
[screaming]
They aren't living
creatures.
They're some sort of robot,
made to look human.
Shine Snow Illusion!
[screaming]
[rev up yell]
I am Berthier of the
Four Spectre Sisters!
Your little parlor trick
won't work on me!
[scared gasp]
I can't breathe...
Now, tell me where
the "Rabbit" is!
I'm not telling you
anything! I'd never turn
Chibi-Usa over to the enemy!
Venus Love-Me Chain!
[gasp]
Now Sailor Moon!
Finish her!
Moon!
Princess!
Halation!
[gasp]
[death scream]
[frustrated gasp]
It's no use.
Berthier's water sphere
is a torrent that will
never run dry.
[gasp]
[chuckle]
Mercury!
Hey, do you know if Sailor
Moon is really strong?
Invincible.
Mercury!
The Black Moon... who are
they? What do they want?
We still don't know.
Their moves are totally
unpredictable. And they
were hidden among
us long before we ever
knew they were there.
They aren't the usual
suspects. Maybe they want
Chibi-Usa and don't care
about the Silver
Crystal at all.
Chibi-Usa?
It's possible. She may very
well hold the key to all of
these mysteries.
Act.17 Secret:
Sailor Jupiter.
The moonlight is the
messenger of love.