Not so fast! I've got the
Silver Crystals now!
[gasp] Prince Dimande!
That woman it can't be!
Small Lady?!
I'm going to end it all! And
take all of you with me!
No!
[gasp]
This is the end! The
end of everything!
Time!
I command thee. Stop!
Pluto.
Yes, Queen Serenity?
The third law, the
most important one...
Do not stop time. Never. Not
under any circumstances.
Both you and your Garnet Rod
possess tremendous power.
You have the ability to
move space and alter
the flow of time.
You could stop time if
you wanted. One day
you may even be tempted to.
But listen to me, and
heed my warning.
If ever you were to break
this most sacred law...
[gasp]
[gasp] Nothing is moving...
Pluto!?
She didn't. She
stopped time?!
Why is it suddenly so calm?
Everything is completely
motionless.
And not just Nemesis...
The very air itself is
completely still, like it's
all been frozen!
Has time stopped?
Usako...
[gasp]
[groan]
Pluto! Are you alright?
I can't believe you stopped
time! How could you do
something so reckless?!
Pluto has broken the most
sacred law of time!
By stopping it?
Why is that wrong?
She saved us all.
What does breaking "the
most sacred law" mean?
What's going to
happen to her?
Queen Serenity
warned me not to...
Pluto.
If ever you were to break
this most sacred law, it
would cost you your life.
Cost you your life?!
Time has stopped,
but not for very long.
Please hurry,
before it restarts.
Go to Dimande, retrieve
the two Legendary Silver
Crystals from him,
and be very careful
not to let them touch.
Only you can do
this, Sailor Moon.
But Pluto!
Go quickly!
[gasp]
Pluto!
I got both Silver Crystals
back just like you told me
to. They're right here!
Thank goodness...
Yes, Pluto. It's
all thanks to you.
I always wanted to serve you
as a Guardian; to be of
help, the way
your friends are.
I had long hoped to fight
alongside you, and now
that's been fulfilled.
Sailor Moon, Future Neo
Queen Serenity... I have
always admired you
for your inner strength,
and the size of
your heart.
So please Sailor
Moon, I beg of you...
...save Small Lady.
She needs you.
[coughing]
Pluto! Please
stay with us!
Let us help you!
No my King, I
broke the law.
I committed this crime
of my own volition.
And now I must
atone for my sin.
Diana.
It's Pluto!
[gasp]
Pluto!
What happened to you,
Pluto? Are you badly hurt?
Thank you so much, Diana.
You did a fine job of
guarding the door in my place.
Guarding time and being
keeper of the door, they
were my duties, but
I also took a great
deal of pride in them.
King Endymion, I can see
your face so clearly.
Do not be sad my King.
This is as it should be.
I've never seen your cloak
this close up before...
Such a beautiful
lavender.
Like the color
of sunrise.
My King...
I failed you. I wasn't able
to protect Small Lady.
Please forgive me. [gasp]
Small Lady...
[gasp]
Pluto!
No! Open your eyes!
[crying]
I am Black Lady.
I have no friends, no
family. No one cares about
me. I am all alone.
This is a Space-Time Key.
It is a very important key
that can allow someone to
travel through time.
I- I remember...
Small Lady?
[coughing]
Small Lady!
I'm sorry, Pluto!
That's the key I stole from
her to go to the past.
I love you so much, Pluto!
You're my one
and only friend!
Mommy got mad at me for
coming to see you. I told
her it was okay. That
you were my friend!
But she was still
pretty upset.
I'm her daughter. But
sometimes I wonder if she
even loves me at all.
She loves you.
There are many kinds of love
and many ways of showing
affection. More
than you know.
There are even times, you
cannot show your love at
all, but you can still
watch over them from afar.
These memories why
are they flooding
back all of the sudden?
What's going on?
Why can't I stop crying?
I love you Small Lady.
I love you very much.
Pluto!
You're my best friend...
I love you too!
Pluto!
[gasp]
Huh? [grunting]
What light is this?!
Chibi-Usa!
[gasp]
Her power has awakened.
She can transform now!
Chibi-Usa harnessed the
power of the Silver Crystal.
It is the birth of a new
Guardian, one to carry on
the Legacy of Sailor Moon!
Chibi-Usa!
Usagi! Daddy.
Pluto.
I did it Pluto! Look at me!
I was finally able
to transform!
See Pluto? Now I'm
just like you!
Come on... Why won't
you open your eyes?
After all these years I can
finally transform, but
what's the point if
you're not here to see
it? Please wake up!
I'm so sorry.
You were given the greatest
power in the universe and
you threw it away.
I had such high
hopes for you, Black
Lady. What a waste!
[crying]
Nemesis! How dare you
toy with the heart of an
innocent girl, and
manipulate her to do
your dirty work!
Her best friend is
gone, all because of
your lust for power!
I'll never forgive you!
Moon Crystal
Power Make up!
You're going to pay for what
you've done to Chibi-Usa,
and for Pluto's
death as well!
I am the Pretty Guardian!
Who fights for love
and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now In the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
Moon Princess!
Halation!
[chuckle] You managed
to repel my darkness?
What marvelous power!
But do you really think
you stand a chance
against me now?
No one else is going
to die on my watch!
Earth is my home! It's my
planet! And I won't let you
keep doing what
you want with it!
Daddy was right. Sailor
Moon really does
have a strong heart.
[chuckles] Puny human!
[grunting]
Mamo! You're back!
I'm so sorry, Usako.
It's okay.
[gasp]
The Moon Rod! Our combined
power is repairing it!
Let's go!
Right!
Shine Aqua Illusion!
Burning Mandala!
Sparkling Wide Pressure!
Venus Love Me Chain!
[groans]
So this is what it means
to be a Sailor Guardian...
They fight for their
friends, they fight for this
planet. They're willing
to give their lives
to protect what's most
important to them!
Could I really do that
one day? Will I be able
to stand strong too?
[scream]
[gasp]
Prince Dimande!
Your tricks might fool
them, but they don't fool me!
I know you!
Dimande, why do
you interfere?
I won't let you take what
belongs to me. Sailor Moon
is mine! I'll be the
one to kill her!
And If anyone walks away
from this with the Silver
Crystal, it's
going to be me!
[chuckles] You may
have been bewitched by
the beauty of the queen.
But make no mistake, you are
my puppet and nothing more.
I gave you your power. I can
take it away. And leave you
to be consumed...
by your own darkness!
[pain scream]
Dimande!
Poor Prince Dimande.
So naïve. So immature.
Such delusions
of grandeur.
How could he think he ever
stood a chance against me
with that insignificant
level of power.
My Queen...
Die!
[gasp]
[laughs]
One must wait an
overwhelmingly long time,
hundreds of years,
before one first starts
obtaining power.
I gave them dark energy,
guidance, everything that
they needed to reshape
history into the
future of their dreams, and
they squandered it all!
[gasps]
What's going on?
I regret to inform you, but
whether you like it or not,
you insignificant
little creatures are
already within my grasp.
Malefic Black Crystal
energy levels are
spiking off the charts!
We're trapped in
distorted space!
The darkness of the
Malefic Black Crystal
is surrounding
us on all sides!
All it would take is the
slightest shift of my mass,
and I could smash
you all into pieces!
The distortion! It's
getting worse and worse!
[gasp]
Now what!
What's happening!
[scream]
The darkness!
It's sucking us in!
[gasp]
[chuckles]
What the hell is that?
What are you Wiseman?
Are we finally seeing
your true form?
My name, is Death Phantom.
That is Death Phantom?
Defeated in battle
for the blue planet;
I was exiled to this
cold, dark place.
Alone in the universe, with
nothing but blackness and
hate; I became the
king of solitude.
But now...
I am the planet! I am
Nemesis. Nemesis is me.
As an invincible planet
filled with Malefic Black
Crystal, I own the greatest
power that exists!
With this power, the past,
the future, and the entire
universe are all
mine! And I will do
with them, whatever I wish!
Death Phantom's
all-consuming hatred soaked
into Nemesis for so
many hundreds of
years, that now it's
fused with the planet?
If that shapeless, evil
thing wants planet Earth,
it's going to have to
go through me first!
Take your best shot,
Queen of the Earth,
future Neo
Queen Serenity!
I am invincible! You
cannot defeat me!
Oh yes I can!
Your evil plans are
going to end right here!
Usako, whenever you feel
lost or uncertain, I will
always be there for you.
I am yours: mind, body, and
soul. My life exists so I
can give you the strength
to keep fighting.
Mamo, I wouldn't be who I am
without you. Only with you,
can I truly become myself.
Your love gives
me infinite power.
Act 26: Replay, Never Ending.
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.