Who are you?
You're cute, Bun‐head.
But don't get in our way,
or you'll be sorry.
Some of the games we play...
...are dangerous.
Sailor Moon, are you okay?
Could she possibly be
a Sailor Guardian?
You made contact with this
supposed Guardian?!
Mmhm...
What happened?
She said don't
get in their way.
That's it?
Did she mention her name?
Was there anything else?
[gasp]
No. That was it.
Like Luna said, we
still don't know that
she's really a Guardian.
We need to nail down
her true identity.
Haruka Tenoh...
He does look like her...
Hey, Bun‐head!
[gasp]
Who are you?
[snicker]
Wait!
Why are you always
running away?
We don't have much time. We
have a mission to complete.
We must gather...
Huh?
The Talismans...
We must gather
the Talismans.
The three...
Talismans...
For the God of Destruction.
[gasp]
Talismans?
Destruction God?
That nightmare again.
What does it mean?
Something seems to want
us to gather those
Talismans. But I have a
bad feeling about it.
We must gather
the Talismans.
The three Talismans...
For the God of Destruction.
What did that mean?
Good Morning, Usa.
You're late again.
Sorry, Mamo.
Michiru Kaioh...
[gasp] It's her!
Oh wow. I didn't realize
she was a professional.
Mamo?
Is he thinking
about Michiru?
Is he interested in her?
"The multi‐purpose hall,
erected on the grounds of
Mugen Academy, is
finally complete."
"Plans to build hotel and
condominium complexes
adjacent to the dome are
also in the works."
"In recent months, the
entire Mugenzu area has
experienced a
construction boom."
Interesting.
Your friends were pretty
clear they didn't want me
anywhere near you.
So I wasn't going to
come here anymore.
But then, I missed you.
What's going on? Why
is my heart pounding?
It's strange, but for some
reason I can see him as
both a boy and a girl.
Hey...
I never did tell you
my name, did I?
You don't have to.
I already know it's
Haruka Tenoh.
Turns out you're famous. You
both are, you and Michiru.
Hear her play just once...
and you'll wish you
could listen forever.
The way she breathes
life into her instrument
it's like magic.
If you're interested,
you should come.
So you know my name,
tell me yours.
Usagi... Tsukino.
Usagi Tsukino.
That's a cute name.
Haruka, wait!
He vanished...
Here one moment and gone
the next. Just like the wind.
Who are you, Haruka Tenoh?
I want to know more...
Hey guys, what's wrong?
You all look so serious.
We were talking about a
dream we had last night.
It was kind of upsetting.
What? Did it have to
do with Tailsmans?
So you had it too?
All of us having the same
dream on the same night...
Can't be coincidence.
Look! Mimi Hanyu is giving a
concert at the new dome!
Aw! But it's only
for Mugen kids.
If I could, I'd transfer
to Mugen Academy
just to be able to go!
That is a perfect idea!
What're you talking about?
The very first act to grace
the stage of the new Mugen
Academy Dome will be none
other than the ultra‐fabulous
superstar, Mimi Hanyu!
Who's Mimi Hanyu?
[gasped scream]
What?! Are you
serious, Usagi?!
She's only like the
best‐selling teen pop idol
in Japan! You had to have
seen her commercials!?
I have to go to her concert!
It'll be so awesome!
Mina! Now is not the time
to be a rabid fangirl.
Why not? If I can sneak into
her concert and spy on Mugen
Academy at the same time, it
kills two birds with one stone!
Hey, look at the
other poster.
Michiru Kaioh is
performing too, apparently
on the same day.
Maybe I should go.
To see Mimi Hanyu's concert?!
Uh, no. I meant to
Michiru's recital.
You already have tickets?
Yeah, somebody gave me
a whole bunch. See?
There's enough for
everyone to go.
Michiru plays so beautifully.
I'd love to hear more.
Yeah, me too. Let's
all go check out.
I'm in. And who knows,
maybe we'll learn something
about the Talismans.
As long as we're
together, we'll be fine.
Absolutely.
But I wanna see Mimi Hanyu!
Mina...
The Sailor Guardians...
They defeated Eudial so easily,
their strength is formidable.
Especially this one,
and the power of the
light she possesses...
A power like that of our
Taioron Crystal. I must
obtain it and give
it to the Master.
First, however, I need to
identify the three Talismans
I saw reflected in my water
mirror, the Talismans
foretold to bring destruction.
It is imperative I
seize and destroy
them as soon as possible!
I am here, Magus Kaolinite.
How may I be of service?
Eudial failed us, Mimete.
You must make up for it.
Of course, leave it to me,
Mimete of Witches 5.
As class prefect of Mugen
Performing Arts, and a teen
pop sensation, complete
with her own fan club,
I, Mimi Hanyu, will use my
lyrical and angelic singing
voice, to collect many Hostes
for Master Pharaoh 90.
Don't forget the Sailor
Guardians will try to
interfere. So make sure
you are prepared.
[giggle] Not to worry!
Chibi‐Usa!
Look! I brought some
of the photos we
took at Mugen C park!
[chuckles]
I'm making such
a weird face!
You scared me, ya know.
When you left the park to
find your hat, and didn't
come back, I got really
worried about you.
Oh! I'm sorry.
That reminds me... I still
have her handkerchief.
I never gave it back to her.
Hey Hotaru!
I wanted to return your
handkerchief. Thank you for
helping me the other day.
You came all the way
here just to return this?
[chuckle]
It's cold out here. Would
you like to come in for a bit?
Wow...
You have so many lamps
in here... [gasp]
They make your room feel
like a romantic fairy tale.
I like dimly lit places.
You also like wearing dark
clothes, don't you?
I just noticed you wear
black tights all the time.
When I was little, I
was badly injured.
And I still have
a lot of scars.
Hotaru! Are you okay?
It's just one of my
attacks, don't worry.
Do you need anything?
My amulet, that helps.
It's sitting over on my desk.
Could you please
get it for me?
Here. Will you be okay?
You should go now.
Hotaru...
I'm not normal.
You don't want to be
around someone like me.
Please leave! Pretty soon I
won't even be me anymore.
Here, Hotaru. Give
me your hand.
It's my turn to be the
one to help you.
My body stopped hurting.
I feel so warm now.
Somehow it's giving me
my strength back...
Is the stone on this
necklace your amulet?
I'm not sure what you mean.
Amulets are good luck charms
that are supposed to protect
you. They have mystical
powers to keep you safe.
Wow! You know, that's
exactly what it is!
But it can protect more than
just me, It's got lots of
power, enough to
protect you, too.
You know, I haven't even
asked you your name yet.
My real name is Usagi
Tsukino. But all my friends
call me Chibi‐Usa.
That's pretty. And hey,
don't worry,
I won't tell anyone
you're Chibi‐Moon.
Your secrets will be
safe with me.
[chuckle]
Also, about the other day,
I owe you an apology.
The creature that
attacked you out in front of
the school... I'm
sorry about that.
I think it might have been
one of the test subjects
from my father's lab.
Daddy is kind of eccentric.
His research and
experiments are creepy.
Please don't tell,
almost no one knows.
He's really not a bad
person. I wouldn't want him
to get into trouble.
Back when I got hurt,
the one who saved
me was him.
I won't tell anyone.
It stays between us.
Pinky promise.
It's darker than I realized.
I should call Usagi or Mamo.
Need a lift Little Bun‐Head?
If you're going back to Usagi's,
we'll give you a ride.
Who are you? Are you
guys friends of Usagi's?
I don't think she knows us,
but we know her very well.
You might say we were...
friends in another life.
This is so cool!
[giggle] I've never gotten
to fly in a helicopter before!
[chuckle] I saw you
were visiting Hotaru.
‐Are you and she friends?
‐Mmhm!
Hey wait, does that mean
you know Hotaru, too?
Kind of... So, you two discuss
anything interesting?
That's a secret.
Okay then...
[chuckle]
Well, one thing we talked
about was amulets.
Like good luck charms?
You know what they are!
Does that mean you have one?
I suppose you could say my
hand mirror is an amulet.
[chuckle] It is much more
than just a simple trinket.
This mirror is a Talisman.
A Talisman?
What is that?
Goodbye, Little Usagi.
Don't tell anyone what we
talked about, okay?
It's a secret.
Chibi‐Usa!
What's going on Here?
Isn't it cool? They gave
me a ride home in their
helicopter after I went
to visit Hotaru!
I almost didn't go with
them. But they said they
knew you, so I
figured it was okay.
Till we meet again...
Goodnight, Bun‐heads.
That's one of the
girls who flew me
home in the helicopter.
She's a professional
violinist?
Chibi‐Usa.
Coming, Mamo.
Is that Chibi‐Usa?
She's with Mamoru?
[gasp] You guys are here, too!
Mamo, I didn't know
you were coming.
Michiru gave me a
couple of free tickets.
I had originally planned
on asking you, but I
heard you say you
were already coming.
So that's what happened...
♪
The melody reminds me of an
ocean current, with rolling
waves that ebb and flow...
It's as if I'm at the
bottom of the sea.
There's Haruka...
Hey, Minako's gone.
Do you think she went
to the restroom?
I don't care about some
stupid violin. I'm going to
that Mimi Hanyu
concert. Usagi's not
the only one with
something up her sleeve.
Ta‐da!
My special compact from
back when I was Sailor V.
Moon Power!
Change me into a Mugen
Academy student! A boy one!
All right!
[cheering]
Thank you everybody!
I'm so happy to be
performing for you all today
on our brand new stage.
Oh‐my‐gosh! Oh‐my‐gosh!
Oh‐my‐gosh! She's
even cuter in person!
I love our dear
Mugen Academy,
and all my fellow students.
Are school is the best and I
would do anything for it.
Even offer up my own body.
You feel the same way, right?
[cheering]
Alright everyone, I would
like you all to quiet down
for this next song. I
wrote it just for you.
Give over your bodies, your
souls, your hearts and
minds. Offer them up to me...
...and to our Master Pharaoh 90!
[gasp]
What's happening to my body?
[chuckle]
What's going on?
It's over already?
Usagi!
Where are you Minako?
Mimi Hanyu is one of
the Death Busters!
Get over here, quick!
Venus Planet Power Make Up!
I'm onto you, Mimi Hanyu.
Beneath that glitz and
glamour lies the face of evil!
Wake up! Don't let
this siren fool you!
And who are you?
Protected by Venus,
the Planet of Beauty.
Guardian of Love.
I am Sailor Venus!
In the name of Venus, I
will punish you with love!
This is a private
performance!
Get off my stage!
Sorry! No encore for you.
Venus Wink Chain Sword!
Daimons!
Awaken!
[roaring]
What are they?
Hurry! Everybody evacuate!
[roaring]
[screaming]
[attacking roars]
[gasp]
Mars Snake Fire!
Jupiter Coconut Cyclone!
Mercury Aqua Mirage!
Just in time!
Neo Queen Serenity!
Lend me your strength!
Lend your power to
my Heart Moon Rod!
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
Are you okay?
Curse you! Take this!
Chibi Moon!
Deep Submerge!
World Shaking!
[screaming]
It's you!
Protected by Neptune,
the Outer Planet of the Seas,
Guardian of the Deep Sea.
I am Sailor Neptune!
Protected by Uranus,
the Outer Planet of the Wind,
Guardian of the Heavens.
I am Sailor Uranus!
[gasp] Who are you guys?
Next time, " Act. 30 Infinity
4, Haruka & Michiru ‐ Sailor
Uranus & Sailor Neptune."
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.