My name is Black Lady:
Queen of Darkness.
Wiseman, Ruler of Darkness,
chose me to be at his side.
And now I am queen
of the dark planet,
The Queen of Nemesis!
She has a dark crescent on
her forehead, just like
the Black Moon does!
No! That's impossible!
She's lying! She
can't be Chibi-Usa!
She appears to be grown up,
But has she truly awakened?
Oh, my daughter, what
have they done to you?!
Chibi-Usa! Listen
to yourself!
You're not part of
the Black Moon!
Do you realize what
you're saying?
Small Lady! Small Lady!
Small Lady! Small--!
[gasp]
Luna-P!
Stupid toy. How annoying.
Chibi-Usa...
Small Lady! Come
to your senses!
[snickering]
Save your breath!
The Rabbit you knew no
longer exists. She is gone.
No trace of her remains in
the woman in front of you.
This is Black Lady!
[evil laughing]
Chibi-Usa!
Dimande, Saphir!
Show yourselves!
Since Esmeraude is no
longer with us, the
Beast Hands are mine now.
And I believe, you already
know my Evil Sight.
Feel it's power!
[gasp]
Watch out!
[screaming]
Venus!
[grunting]
Jupiter!
[grunting] I can't move!
You're not laying a
hand on Sailor Moon!
Oh yeah?! Try and stop me!
[scream]
Oh no! Mercury! Mars!
[evil laughing]
[grunting]
Hold on! I'm coming!
This has nothing to
do with you four, so
just sit back and watch.
[scream]
[scoff]
Stop this, Chibi-Usa!
Don't you remember
us at all?!
We don't want to fight with
you. We're not your enemies!
You were born
here, Chibi-Usa.
This is your home!
And The Black Moon destroyed
it! How can you join them?!
[scoff]
The Earth and
everything on it mean
absolutely nothing to me.
If you need proof,
just look over there.
[gasp]
See that second Malefic
Black Crystal monolith?
That was my doing.
It produces a distorted
darkness, which warps
time and space even more.
And the effect just grows
and grows. Now anything it
touches gets absorbed
and disappears.
People, buildings...
everything!
Hundreds, even thousands of
times faster than before!
But that means...
Yes. The Earth will
vanish completely...
It will cease to exist.
[snickers]
I can't believe what I'm
hearing. Chibi-Usa, you
really did this to
your own home?!
My name is Black Lady!
And I couldn't care less
what happens to Earth.
It doesn't matter. I
have what I want.
[gasp]
Tuxedo Mask?!
Mamo!
He belongs to me now.
[gasp]
[laughs]
I always wanted
him all to myself.
And now, I have him.
Endymion is mine and
mine alone. [laughing]
Mamo, no!
Make her suffer.
Mamo...
[gasp]
What's wrong with him?
His eyes are vacant.
It's like he can't
even see me.
Huh?
Look out!
[pain screams]
[gasps]
We combined our powers and
summoned the Moon Rod
together... And he
struck me with it!
This can't be
happening! Mamo!
He can't hear you. He
only listens to me.
Sailor Moon!
[laughing]
Come to me, Endymion.
I have him. As long as he
loves me that's all I need.
You're wrong...
You think this is
love, but it isn't.
It won't make you happy.
Can't you see that?!
She's like me. All I wanted
was Mamo's attention.
I was desperate for it. I
couldn't see straight.
I couldn't think straight.
I was selfish and
incredibly jealous.
And all because...
I know how it feels, loving
someone so much it hurts.
It's overwhelming and
confusing and so intense
you can't handle it.
You're afraid you need
them more than
they need you.
But what scares you the
most is feeling as if
you are not good
enough...
I know, because I
feel the same way.
I'm sorry I was
mean to you.
Forgive me! I care about
you more than you realize!
I need you, Chibi-Usa!
You are more like Sailor
Moon than you know.
Shut up! Don't talk to
me like you know me!
You don't know anything!
You and I are nothing alike!
[scream]
Sailor Moon!
Hmph!
She's all yours, Dimande.
Taking someone prisoner and
making them love you...
You're wrong! It
can make you happy!
No... It doesn't work that
way. That's not love!
Be quiet!
[gasp]
[laughs]
My god!
[gasp]
What the--?!
A third one?!
[gasps]
[grunting]
Oh no!
Chibi-Usa, what
have you done?!
[laughing]
Damn the Moon Kingdom
and its palace!
I want the darkness to
swallow up this whole,
wretched planet! Until
there's nothing left!
[chuckles]
Yes, my dear Black
Lady. That's it.
You understand.
Those who control great
power, control the universe!
The people of the Moon
Kingdom taught me that.
They used the power of the
Silver Crystal to take
over the Earth and remake
it as they saw fit!
[laughing]
Isn't that right,
Sailor Moon?
[gasp]
My heart is racing.
I've never felt such a
sense of disquiet before.
What's happening
beyond that door?
A spreading darkness blocks
my sight. Small Lady,
King Endymion,
Sailor Moon...
Please be safe,
my friends!
The palace?!
Look! It's glowing!
Sailor Moon?
It's the Legendary
Silver Crystal!
[chuckles]
You would still dare to
fight me, Sailor Moon?
How foolish...
I hold all the cards. I have
everything that is precious
to you, and can crush
them at any time!
If you want them back, both
you and the queen must
surrender and hand
yourselves over.
Along with your Legendary
Silver Crystal from the
past, the one you are
trying to use now!
I'm not giving you anything,
no matter what you do.
I will protect Neo
Queen Serenity's palace
and this planet!
[gasp]
[chuckle] Launch another
Malefic Black Crystal.
[gasp]
You'll destroy the Earth,
and all of us along with it.
So?
[gasp]
The Queen and the second
Legendary Silver Crystal,
are practically
within my grasp.
The rest is of
little importance.
So that's it? We're just
expendable to you?
Prince Dimande!
[laughs]
Wiseman! You would
think this was funny.
It's ironic, really. The
Evil Sight you gave me,
shielded me from your
mind-control attack.
You didn't know
that did you.
I've never been
under your spell!
Rubeus and Esmeraude are
gone, but they fought
alongside me for years.
If I am to die, it won't
be in vain! I owe them that!
Saphir!
[growl]
This is what it's come to. I
must fight, my own brother.
Saphir, I am ashamed I ever
questioned your loyalty.
You always followed me
despite hating what the
Malefic Black Crystal
had made me become.
Your only act of defiance
was refusing to wear
any of it yourself...
That is, until now,
little brother.
I dragged you into
this. I'm so sorry.
[screaming]
Forgive me.
Now die! Wiseman!
[gasp]
That... is Wiseman?
It's a corpse!
[snicker]
You thought that
was his true form?
Wiseman!
Show yourself!
What the- ?
It can't be!
[gasp]
The storm died
down. It's clear.
Is it over? Is
everyone alright?
I can't shake this feeling
that my friends are in
danger. If they're fighting,
I want to charge
through that door and
fight alongside them!
But I am the Guardian of
the Underworld, the lone
keeper of the Door of
Space and Time.
I mustn't, I cannot
move from this spot...
Pluto...
Hm?
You are the keeper of the
Door of Space and Time,
the Guardian who watches
over all of Space-Time.
This is a great honor,
but with it comes
great responsibility.
There are three sacred laws
of time you must promise
never to break.
The first law forbids all
time travel. The second
requires you to always
keep watch at this door.
And the third law, the
most important one...
Wha- What is that thing?
[gasp]
It's huge!
[gasps]
I don't believe it!
It's the Planet Nemesis!
I am Wiseman!
Agh! Where did that
voice come from?!
That sound...
It's deafening!
[laughing]
What the hell
is going on?
[laughing]
That putrid body is
a relic of the past.
It was something like a
human once, but it drifted
to Nemesis and became
a corpse long ago...
As time went on, my
consciousness merged with
the place meant to be my
prison, until eventually...
We became one!
I am Nemesis!
[gasp]
Wiseman is the planet?!
This is the true identity
he kept from us?!
[laughing]
[groaning]
Can't stand up...
What is this?
My whole body hurts!
The darkness! It's
draining our energy...
Sailor Moon...
Jupiter! Mars!
Mercury! Venus!
Hang on, you guys!
[laughs]
Soon the entire
Earth will disappear.
Every last trace.
[snickering]
Nemesis is getting closer!
The effect of its dark
distortion is spreading!
If I don't do something
quick, what's left of the
Earth will die and
vanish forever!
I can't let that happen!
I have to stop it!
At any cost!
We were toys, puppets
he manipulated...
Insignificant specs in
Nemesis' shadow. Nothing
more than tools to be
used and tossed away.
[gasp]
That light?
I feel a gentle power...
The palace is shining.
It's getting brighter
and brighter!
It's so beautiful.
Such a comforting glow.
The power of the Silver
Crystal is even stronger now.
It defies logic. Sailor Moon
is using her own Legendary
Silver Crystal
here in the future.
She is performing
some kind of miracle!
Is that... Sailor
Moon's true power?
[gasp]
Oh no you don't.
Wiseman!
[grunting]
The Crystal Palace!
It'll be crushed!
Sailor Moon!
Hmph!
[scream]
[gasp]
Pluto!
Diana?
Please, help them!
Before it's too late!
What's happening?
It's Small Lady!
She grew up!
Huh?
Something awakened
her power...
And she's become queen
of the Black Moon!
[gasp]
She opened a wormhole and
the entire planet Nemesis
came through it! It's about
to crush the Palace!
It might really be the end
of the Earth this time.
I'm not sure Sailor
Moon can save it.
If only I wasn't
bound here...
If only I could
do something...
Pluto...
Don't you think I want
to help them, Diana!?
Small Lady is in trouble,
and she's my friend.
I wish I could go to her...
But I cannot...
Oh Small Lady...
What if I were to stay here
and keep watch in your
place? Then could you go?
I may be tiny, and I don't
have powers like you do. But
I can still guard the Door
of Space and Time, at least
for a little while.
Diana...
Okay? So go. Save our Small
Lady. I love her too.
Go through the door, Pluto.
Cross the threshold. It's
time. It's not a question of
whether or not you
want to, you have to!
Diana...
You're so kind and
thoughtful, just like Small
Lady. Thank you, my friend.
[meow]
Good luck, Pluto! I
know you can do it!
The true power of the
Legendary Silver Crystal...
Such pure, beautiful energy.
With a light that
pierces through the
dark veil of time...
I could use the Malefic
Black Crystal to rewrite
history again and again.
But that gleaming
power will always
reign supreme!
Can nothing surpass it?
Is there no way to
achieve what we dreamed?
I wonder which is going
to give way first.
Will it be this planet?
Or will it be you and
your pathetic
white light?
If you're asking yourself
whether you can hold
on, I can answer
that for you: No!
[laughing]
I am Black Lady, Queen of
Nemesis! Bow down to me!
The fate of planet earth
and its entire future...
All of it rests in my hands!
I can't keep this up
for much longer...
[laughing]
Chibi-Usa...
Hmph!
Take it then!
[gasp]
Take the Legendary Silver
Crystal. Take my life if you
want it! All that I have,
all I ever cared about.
I'll give it to you!
Just stop being Black Lady!
That's not who you are.
You are Chibi-Usa!
You are sweet, and
lonely, and you always
drive me crazy...
But I can't go
on without you!
I've had enough
of this future!
I don't want to
see it anymore!
[scream]
Endymion. Go!
[surprised gasp]
Mamo...
[gasp]
[screams]
Sailor Moon!
Mamo...
Mamo!
Endymion?
Endymion!
[chuckles]
Two Silver Crystals.
One from the future
and one from the past.
[chuckle] And
they're both mine!
[laughing] [gasp]
Not so fast! I've got
Silver Crystals now!
[gasp] Prince Dimande!
What's he doing?
[gasp]
That woman it can't be!
[shocked gasp]
Small Lady?!
Listen up Black Lady!
You too Wiseman!
The Malefic Black Crystal
has unrivaled power.
Or so you said.
But does it stack up against
two Legendary Silver
Crystals, whose power can
overcome space-time?
I no longer trust
anything anymore.
I believe in nothing.
I follow no one.
I am my own master!
Calm down, please! You don't
want to do anything rash!
The two Crystals must not
touch each other! If they
do, it will destroy the
entire universe!
Give them back!
No, Small Lady!
I'm going to end it all! And
take all of you with me!
[gasp]
I am Black Lady,
Queen of Darkness!
I am not Small Lady!
I don't have friends or
family. I am all alone.
So what is going on?
What is this feeling
and why does it
hurt so much??
Why can't I stop crying?
Act.25, Showdown:
Death Phantom.
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.