So where am I? What
is this place?
You're in my apartment.
I remember, I used the
Moon Stick and Moon
Healing Escalation for
the first time, and
then I'm not sure...
[gasp]
After the battle you passed
out. You fell into a deep
sleep. I couldn't wake you.
Do you remember?
Yes. I do now.
I can't believe I
never noticed before.
The low tone of voice
and the tuxedo tie...
And those eyes that I
can't seem to look
away from...
I see it now, you
are Tuxedo Mask.
Why did you become
Tuxedo Mask in the
first place?
I did it so that I could
find my lost memories.
They're gone. And I need
the Legendary Silver
Crystal in order
to get them back.
Your memories?
Yes.
Dad! Mom! C'mon
let's go for a
drive!
Ahh!
Sadly, neither Mr. or Mrs.
Chiba survived. Only their
son, Mamoru, managed
to pull through.
However...
Who... Who am I?
What am I doing here?
Oh no...
On my sixth birthday, my
parents died in a car
accident. And I lost all
my memories. I couldn't
even recognize my own name.
They had to tell me what
it was. Who I was...
"Mamoru Chiba", is
that who I really am?
I don't know. I could
be someone else entirely.
That's how I've felt for
years, but then I started
having this dream.
"Find the Legendary Silver
Crystal", that's all she
says, and that's the
only thing I know.
Before I knew it, I
was roaming the streets
at night, like a
sleepwalker on a mission.
I needed to find the
Crystal. It was the only
clue I had to my
lost memories.
So? What about you?
Huh?
The Crystal. Aren't you
and the Sailor Guardians
looking for it too?
How come?
Oh, well I...
I don't know why.
Luna didn't give a reason.
She just told us to find
the Silver Crystal and
protect it.
I see...
His eyes look so sad...
If it's alright with you,
can we keep this a secret
between the two of us?
I appreciate it.
Something just between
us... A secret.
He could just be using
you to get to the Crystal.
I know him. He's not my
enemy. I trust him.
I wish I could stop time
at this very moment.
And that it would
stand still forever.
I-I'm sorry.
Everyone must be worried
sick about me by now.
I should go.
Usako...
[sigh]
Your bag...
Mm-hm.
Usako...
He's Mamoru, so I guess
I'll call him "Mamo".
So you've found all four
Guardians, but they haven't
regained all their memories
from their past lives yet?
I'm afraid not.
Sailor Moon in particular
is still having a lot of
trouble, unfortunately.
I think she needs
some more time.
Time's a luxury
we don't have.
But I don't think-
The enemy will
be upon us soon.
[gasp]
O Great Ruler, Queen
Metalia! Your humble
servant awaits!
[moaning]
I offer this energy from
the humans. May it revive
you, Great One.
[moaning]
Human energy alone is not
enough to revive me.
Where is the Legendary
Silver Crystal?
My apologies, O Great
Queen Metalia. The Sailor
Guardians have appeared
and they're thwarting
our efforts.
Sailor Guardians? As in
the ones who defeated me
in ancient times
and sealed me away?
Yes...
And I'm afraid that
it may be worse.
It's possible they already
possess the Crystal.
Do not allow that! The
descendant of the putrid
Moon Kingdom must
never fully awaken!
Yes, O' Great Ruler!
Crush them and get me
the Legendary Silver
Crystal!
This time not just the
planet, but the entire
universe will be mine!
Once Queen Metalia fully
revives, she may indeed
devour the whole
world and beyond.
But there's no
turning back.
Not since that fateful
day when I first stumbled
upon D-point.
It was as if some force
had drawn me there and
wanted me to discover
the Dark Kingdom.
With my own hands I broke
the seal, and freed Queen
Metalia from her
ancient prison!
It may have been my destiny
to release her. But when it
comes to the Legendary Silver
Crystal, I won't hand
it over so easily!
I shall keep the
Legendary Silver
Crystal for myself.
Then the entire planet
will be mine for the
taking!
Come Zoisite!
Yes, my Queen!
Your wounds are healing
nicely. So I have a new
task for you. I believe
Sailor Moon could be the
key to the Legendary
Silver Crystal.
I understand,
my Queen.
Hm...
Huh?
Yumiko! Kuri!
Over here!
Huh?
Did you come to
rent movies too?
Uh huh. Lately I've been
kind of hooked on romance
movies.
I can't make
up my mind.
Hm?
Seriously! There's
too many to choose
from!
I know. That's why this
store's so popular. They
have everything!
I've gotta watch the
movies. I've gotta
watch the movies.
Gotta watch the movies.
Uh...
Sailor Moon
has it, right?
I'm going to be the
first one to catch her!
I don't like this.
It's so good.
These homemade sandwiches
you brought are the best,
Mako!
Well there's plenty
more. So eat all
you want.
All right!
[giggling]
Here Ami.
Want one?
Oh, I'm fine.
Thanks.
Oh. Huh?
Is that Sailor V?
Well you mentioned her
before. So I thought I'd
do a little research.
Look! She has a crescent-
shaped mark on her forehead!
It looks just like Luna's
mark. So maybe it means
that she's from the
Moon Kingdom too.
Hmm...
Huh?
Hello ladies!
[giggling]
Umino!
Are you still talking
about Sailor V?
That girl's
old news.
C'mon get with the
program. Sailor
Moon's what's hot!
Right, Usagi?
Ugh!
Everyone all over town is
looking for Sailor Moon,
but I intend to be the
first one who's actually
going to catch her!
[snickering]
What the heck are
you babbling about?!
Uh, hey Umino, are
you feeling okay?
Why is he being
so creepy!
He was a little overly-
aggressive today, don't
ya think?
Luna!
Sorry.
Tell me, Luna, about
Sailor V, you sure you
don't know who she is?
Uh...no. I don't think
she has anything to do
with the Moon Kingdom.
Really? That's
too bad.
But I'm still kinda
curious about her.
Perhaps Usagi can sense
something about Sailor V
that the rest of us aren't
able to pick up on.
Usagi was the first
Guardian Luna found
and she's our leader.
She could have some
kind of special
ability.
A special ability?
[laughing]
Hey, what is it? What
are you laughing at
Mako?
It's your face, Usagi!
My face?
[giggling]
What is it? Tell
me you guys?
What's wrong
with my face!
Here, take a look
in the mirror.
Huh?
Oh no! I got ketchup
on my face!
Oh! Handkerchief!
Handkerchief! I gotta
find it! where could
it be? Oh!
[sigh]
Usagi's definitely
"special".
Stop teasing
me, Luna!
[laughing]
Just great. Now
everyone's laughing
at me.
His watch. I must've
accidentally taken it.
Usagi?
Yes! What?
Did you find your
handkerchief?
If not, you're welcome
to use mine.
Oh yeah, I found it!
No worries. Thanks
anyway!
Okay then!
So Ami I've been
meaning to tell
you,
I found this great little
shop in town that sells
the cutest backpacks.
I know I should
tell everybody...
About Tuxedo Mask. That I
know who he is and about
how he knows that
I am Sailor Moon.
I'm sure they'd be
surprised, maybe even
shocked.
Luna might even yell at me!
But... What if they
wouldn't let me see
him anymore?
Mamoru...
Mamo...
How come my heart aches
whenever I think of him?
I miss you...
What are you thinking
about right now, Mamo?
Do you miss me too?
Hey Naru! Want to
walk home together?
Is something wrong?
I can't walk home with
you. There's something
I need to be looking for.
What are you looking
for? Maybe I can help.
Sailor Moon...
Huh? Sailor-
Agh! I'm so sorry!
Let me get that!
Listen to me Usagi.
Your friend Naru
isn't herself!
Something's wrong
with her?
And the rest of
your classmates
too!
Hm?
I must find
Sailor Moon.
Find Sailor Moon...
[gasp]
That DVD!
Rental Shop Dark?
Put the DVD in here.
Okay.
It's nothing
but static?
[screams]
Wh-what made
it do that?
Oh no! What happened to
the game! Don't tell me
we broke the machine!
What are you waiting
for, Sailor Moon?
Hurry!
That is a brainwashing
DVD from our enemy!
They're all over town.
People are in danger!
You need to hurry!
The Sailor V from the
game is talking to
me again...
A brainwashing DVD?
You should go Usagi.
Try to help anyone
you can.
I'll check out this
disk and see what I
can find.
[affirmative grunt]
Why did I tell
her all that?
Something's
wrong with me.
I must find
Sailor Moon...
I need to know
where Sailor
Moon is...
I must find her
and take the
Crystal from her.
What the-
Sailor Moon.
Find Sailor Moon.
Where is Sailor
Moon? I must
find her.
I don't understand.
What the heck is
going on?
Find and capture Sailor
Moon. Sailor Moon holds
the key to the
Legendary Silver Crystal.
She must be
taken alive.
I feel so weak...
Get away from the
monitor or you'll
be brainwashed too!
Sailor Moon must
be sacrificed!
Given as tribute to
the Dark Kingdom!
Did he say, Dark
Kingdom?!
Where is Sailor Moon?
Must find Sailor
Moon and capture
her.
Mako, can you
hear me?
Ami, this is
really bad!
People all over the city
are saying they want to
capture Sailor Moon!
Same thing where I'm at!
I'm worried about Usagi!
I think she's in danger!
The enemy has brainwashed
the entire city! Hurry
everyone!
You must protect Usagi!
Did you hear
that? Let's go!
[affirmative grunts]
Sailor Moon.
Find Sailor Moon.
I'm so scared. But I
have to do this. There
isn't any other way.
Now more than ever I
need you to lend me
your strength.
Help me Mamo.
Moon Prism Power
Make Up!
Want Sailor Moon?
Here I am!
Catch her...
Catch Sailor Moon...
[growling]
Moon Healing
Escalation!
What the-? Where the
heck am I? How weird.
Oh no! It's late!
I better get home.
Huh? Where am I?
How did I get here?
Huh?
Ah thank goodness!
They're all okay!
[screaming]
[snickering]
Well well, Sailor Moon
you really do have
special powers.
But they won't save you.
Zoisite?!
You walked right into
my trap. What a fool.
You took advantage of
people who were just
trying to watch movies for
fun. That's unforgivable!
I am Sailor Moon!
In the name of
the moon...
I'll puni- Ahh!
Tell me! Where is the
Legendary Silver
Crystal hidden?
I don't know!
Tell me where it
is or you die!
Let her go!
Huh?
Mercury Aqua Mist!
Trying to blind me?
Evil Spirit, be gone!
Supreme Thunder!
Oh no!
Tell me where the
Legendary Silver
Crystal is now.
If you don't, I'll
kill you and all
your friends.
[groaning]
No! I have to
save them!
Tuxedo Mask...
Help me...
[growling]
You came for me just
like I knew you would.
Tuxedo Mask...
Hey you in
the mask...
What gives? I thought
you wanted the Legendary
Silver Crystal too.
What I want?
You have no idea
what I want!
Don't think I'd
let you do that
again.
[screaming]
Tuxedo Mask!
[struggling grunts]
You sure you don't want
the Crystal? Cause it
seems like you want
something pretty bad.
He does...
Tuxedo Mask does want
the Crystal! He needs
it to remember!
And he's been searching
for it all this time
alone with no
one to help him!
It's true. For a long
time the Crystal was the
only thing I wanted.
But now, when I see her...
Angry one moment and
laughing the next...
The Crystal?
No. That's not what
I really want.
Usako... You're
what I want!
Oh Mamo!
I've had enough
of this!
[gasp]
No!
Let go of me!
Get out of my way!
Agh!
Usako!
[gasp]
I think I'll kill you
first. And then once
you're out of the
picture, I can take
the Legendary
Silver Crystal.
[nervous breathes]
Agh! Usako!
Now die!
No!
What?
[painful yell]
Damn you!
What on Earth
was that?
[gasp]
Who is that?
A crescent mark on her
forehead. Is it possible
that she's...
The legendary Guardian
of justice...
Sailor V?
[giggle]
Are you really
Princess Serenity?
I am, and I've been
watching over you
for quite a while.
We've been
looking for you!
Where have you been?
Now that we've found
you, what do we do
next?
You've all awakened as
Guardians, but you still
need to remember who you
were in your past lives.
Who we were... in
our past lives?
Act. 8, Minako,
Sailor V.
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.