Sailor Moon! You're
my only hope!
I'm from the future!
30th century Earth!
And I need you!
[gasps]
Chibi-Usa?
The truth is...
I'm from Crystal
Tokyo, a city on
Earth in the
30th century.
And I traveled through
time to come here...
I shouldn't have
kept that a secret.
I was just so scared...
But I'm not lying now!
You have to believe me!
There was a huge
explosion in Crystal Tokyo!
And then Mommy...
She won't wake up.
And it's all my fault!
[gasp]
So Chibi-Usa's
from the future.
That could mean the
Black Moon is too.
[gasp]
Chibi-Usa, can you tell us
what caused that huge
explosion in Crystal Tokyo?
[gasps]
Was it the Black Moon?
Uhh, I don't know...
Sailor Mars, Sailor Mercury,
and Sailor Jupiter, could
the Black Moon have taken
them to the future?
I don't know. I don't
know anything, really!
We can help you. But you
must tell us everything!
Chibi-Usa, you can
travel in time.
You need to take us
all to the future.
[gasp]
I don't understand what
happened or how you want
us to help you, but
it's clear we need to
go to the future!
To the future?
No! I can't go back! I
don't want to! I'm scared!
But even if we did go
back to the future...
It may already
be too late!
[crying]
It's okay.
We won't force you
to do anything.
All we want is to help you
and save our friends who
were kidnapped.
Alright? So take your time.
Just promise me you'll think
about what Venus said. Deal?
Deal.
Chibi-Usa, It's been a long
day. Why don't we all go
home and get some rest.
I don't wanna go home!
I wanna sleep over
at Mamo's house!
Hah!?
Happy now little princess?
Come on. Time for bed.
Okay.
When you came from
the future, were
you all by yourself?
Mm-mm...
No, I had Luna P with me.
I see.
Hey, would it be alright if
I asked you about your mom?
[gasp]
About Mommy?
She is kind and beautiful...
And a lot braver than me.
[whimpering]
Chibi-Usa...
Huh?
I believe, it's
okay to be afraid.
Being brave doesn't mean you
don't have any fears. It
means you have the
courage to face them.
You traveled
through time.
That must've been scary,
but you did it anyway!
In my book,
that's bravery.
[gasp]
Mamo.
It seems like the
only thing you care
about lately is Chibi-Usa...
Do you like her? Do you
think she's that cute?
Haven't you noticed it?
Mamo, Chibi-Usa is
in love with you!
What?! That's
ridiculous!
She's still in
elementary school!
She's just a little kid!
So what if she's little?!
That doesn't matter in love.
She's still
another woman!
[embarrassed gasp]
I'm so sorry.
I don't know what's
gotten into me lately.
You're right.
It's ridiculous.
How could I be jealous
of a small child?
[uneasy laughs]
Mamo?
Could I?
Spend the night? I
don't want to go home.
I just want to be
close to you right now.
[gasp]
I guess I'm a
little insecure.
It took us so long
to find each other.
I won't lose you again.
All I want is to love
and protect you!
Usako...
I feel the same
way. I love you...
And I promise, I will
never leave your side.
I will always be there to
protect you. Forever.
A Time warp... Do you think
that's how Chibi-Usa was
able to travel here
from the future?
Luna?
[chuckle] Guess we
have been burning
the candle at
both ends.
Luna. Luna!
Where are you?
You have gone too far!
No one is allowed in
this part of the castle!
Luna. What are you doing
all the way out here?
This place is off-limits.
You know that.
Come. Let us go back.
[gasp]
Stay back.
That is a forbidden door.
Beyond it lies sacred
ground, secretly defended
by a solitary Guardian.
Luna, forget what
you've seen here and
everything I've just said.
Do you understand?
[gasp]
Was I dreaming?
A Silver Crystal
from the future...
and a mysterious key?
Could that mean
Chibi-Usa is?
Being brave doesn't mean
you don't have any fears.
It means you have the
courage to face them.
Oh! Good morning.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I just heard
Chibi-Usa get up.
I've made up my mind!
Huh?
I'm going to face my fears
and go back to the future!
And Usagi, Mamo, I want
you both to come with me.
You want me to come?
And me too?
[chuckle]
This is a Space-Time Key.
And if we use it, it will
take us all to the future?
Mm-hm!
Small Lady...
Time travel is strictly
prohibited. You must
never attempt it. You
should not even know
about it! Breaking this
ultimate taboo, could have
severe consequences.
I'm not sure if this is
gonna work. I've never
time-traveled with
anyone before.
Hold onto my hand and
don't let go. Okay?
Okay!
Right!
Got it!
Everybody ready?
O Guardian of Time,
tear apart the heavens and
open wide for me, the Door
of Space and Time!
"I summon thee by thy true
name, O Omnipotent God of
Time, Father of the
Guardian, O Chronos!"
Guide us on our journey!
Protect these travelers!
Grant us the Path of Light!
[yell] Oh no! I
can't hold on!
Usagi!
Hmph.
Oh, my. Interesting.
Someone has opened a time
warp, and it is not the one
we use to go to and
from Nemesis.
Do you think
it's the Rabbit?
There are multiple energies.
If it's her she's not alone.
Well, well...
So the little brat has gone
running home to her mommy.
Prince Dimande!
The moment has come.
Now is the time to crush the
Legendary Silver Crystals of
both the past and future!
And the Crystal Palace
along with them!
Destroy the palace?
Hm...
I'll do it! It's the
perfect opportunity.
Just leave it to me.
And don't you worry. No harm
will come to your sleeping
beauty. I know she's
what you really want.
[horrified gasp]
[snickering] Esmeraude,
you can't pull that off.
[angry scoff]
Chiral! Achiral!
We're the Boule
Brothers: the Black
Moon's finest creation.
Using the awesome power of
the Malefic Black Crystal,
we'll put on a show
you'll never forget.
Chibi-Usa!
Where are you?
Now what? Chibi-Usa said
we had to stay with her.
I think we're somewhere in
between the past and the
future. If we don't
find Chibi-Usa quick,
we could be lost
in time forever.
[screaming]
I gotcha. Hang on.
Luna, are you okay?
Yeah. I'm fine.
Thank goodness.
[gasp]
What is that?
I know that door!
Halt!
None shall pass!
It is forbidden!
[gasp]
I am the keeper of the
Door of Space and Time.
I am Sailor Pluto, Guardian
of the Underworld!
Any intruders beyond this
point, will be destroyed!
Sailor Pluto?!
That means, she's a
Sailor Guardian!
Dead Scream!
[scream]
Now I understand why Queen
Serenity wanted me to stay
away from that door!
"Forbidden ground ,"
"Defended by a solitary
Guardian"
The Queen was trying to warn
me about Sailor Pluto!
Stop! Don't hurt us! We're
Sailor Guardians too!
No matter who you are,
the law requires all
trespassers be
eliminated.
There are no exceptions.
Prepare yourselves!
[gasp]
I must fulfill
my mission.
Pluto!
Wait! They're my friends!
You can't kill them!
They're with me! I'm the
one who brought them here!
To save Mommy!
[gasp]
I know you told me
not to. I'm sorry!
Where have you
been all this time?!
I broke the law and
went back to the past.
I wanted to steal the
Silver Crystal, that
belonged to Sailor Moon.
I thought it would be more
powerful than this one, and
that I might be able to
use it to help Mommy.
The Silver Crystal is
unchanging. Its power
remains the same
in any era.
Regardless, as you
are now, you lack the
ability to use
either one.
But I...
You disobeyed. You stole
a Space-Time key, and
used it to go to the past...
without permission.
Chibi-Usa!
[gasp]
But I'm just glad
you're safe, Princess.
What?! Chibi-Usa?
Is a Princess?!
Thank you for returning
the Princess safely to
her own time. I deeply
regret my earlier actions.
Please forgive me.
That's right I'm a princess,
just like she said.
I guess I shoulda
mentioned that earlier!
But...
Now that you know...
Guess you'll all have to bow
down and start calling me
"Your Highness."
Eh?
[growling]
Princess? You're a snobby
brat! What kind of parent
would let their kid
become a little monster?
Somebody needs to
teach you some respect!
What's your problem?!
I've always been royalty!
Just now you know it!
[chuckle] My life never
seems to be easy when
I'm dealing with
the two of you.
The Door of Space
and Time is now open.
This way, Usagi.
Okay.
Sailor Pluto, aren't
you coming with us?
My place is here. I am not
allowed to abandon my post.
Please protect Small Lady
for me, and be careful.
We will Sailor Pluto. And
thank you for everything.
Beyond this door, lies
the 30th Century...
The moon is so low in the
sky. It's practically right
on top of the city.
This is 30th century
Crystal Tokyo?
[whimper]
I never thought
it'd be this bad.
It's too quiet.
Where is everyone?
Oh god!
[whimpering]
[gasp]
[gasp] Chibi-Usa!
Can you hear me?
Are you in pain?
Turn back!
[gasp]
Don't go that way!
That voice again...
Are you alright?
Speak to me!
Look over there! What's
that black monolith?
I don't know...
That day, a sudden, massive
explosion rocked the city...
When the dust settled,
that's what was left behind.
I didn't see how
it got there.
All I know is, people were
lying on the ground
everywhere; And they
weren't moving!
Over time, the
bodies began to--
Chibi-Usa?
Let's go. We
shouldn't be here.
Okay...
Follow me...
I'll take you to
where Mommy is...
She's at the
Crystal Palace!
[yell]
What just happened?
Is this the palace?
Are we already inside?
[frightened gasp]
Hello, we're the Boule
Brothers of the Black Moon.
The Black Moon!?
Chiral.
And Achiral.
[chuckles] It's quite an
honor to meet the Rabbit and
the legendary guardian,
Sailor Moon.
Allow us to
welcome you, with
Achiral's isomeric
display.
[laughing]
What's happening?
[grunting]
I can't move!
[evil chuckling]
Achiral's Electrochemical
Side Chain, there is no
reaction that can sever
its molecular bond!
It's not over yet!
No creepy doppelgangers
are going to beat me!
Moon Princess Halation!
The Moon Rod! Why
isn't it working?!
[gasp of pain]
Don't bother struggling.
You're fixed in Chiral's
magnetic field, called the
Chirality Center.
All of you have
been immobilized
at an atomic level.
How does it feel
to be cornered?
There's no escape from
this beautiful monument.
And this is but a taste
of what the Malefic Black
Crystal is capable of.
I intend to use its full
power to bury you, along
with the real Crystal Palace.
That won't
happen! It can't!
The palace! Mommy's there so
it can never be destroyed!
Chibi-Usa...
Mommy is strong! As long as
she's inside the Palace
nothing can shatter it! It
will stand for all time!
Mommy! Mommy! [chuckle]
Oh but that's terribly
insensitive of me. Tell you
what, Rabbit, show
Auntie Esmeraude the
Legendary Silver Crystal
and I'll take pity on you.
I'll bury you and your
mom in the same grave.
[screaming]
Now vanish! Into
radioactive vapor!
[screaming]
Use your will!
Command the false
crystal to break!
There it is again...
Do it!
Agh! Alright!
False crystal! I
command you! Break!
Impossible! They escaped
from our masterpiece!
Now's our chance!
Venus Love Me Chain!
Tuxedo La Smoking Bomber!
[screaming]
Whose voice was that?
His advice saved us all!
Why is he helping me?
Oh wow...
This must be the
real Crystal Palace.
Follow me.
The Crystal Palace...
[gasp]
Someone's in there.
I'm home.
Chibi-Usa, who
is that woman?
This is Mommy.
Neo Queen Serenity.
Neo Queen Serenity?
[meow]
A kitten?
Diana! I'm so happy you're
alive! Where are you going?
[meowing]
[gasp]
Tuxedo Mask!?
Welcome to Crystal Tokyo
in the 30th-century.
And to our home,
the Crystal Palace.
Who are you? And why do you
look like Tuxedo Mask?
I am King Endymion.
King Endymion!?
Daddy!
Daddy!?
Act. 20- Crystal
Tokyo, King Endymion.
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.