I wonder when it's
gonna stop raining.
[yawning]
Try to be a little more
alert, Usagi. You don't
pay any attention to your
surroundings whatsoever.
Hm? Which means?
You need to keep your
guard up and be ready
to face danger at a
moment's notice!
How am I supposed to
do that? And besides
Luna, I've noticed
you've put on a
little weight lately.
Is that how you keep
your guard up?
Usagi!
It's dangerous. You
should be careful.
Yeah... Thanks.
Usagi, are you okay?
Her perfume, it
smelled really nice.
Curse those meddling
Sailor Guardians!
Not only have we failed
to obtain the Legendary
Silver Crystal, but we
haven't gathered enough
energy for out Great
Ruler either!
Let me try again. I've
learned their weakness,
I can defeat them my Queen.
Does that mean you
have a plan, Nephrite?
Yes, I shall gather energy
and beat the Sailor Guardians
by exploiting humanity's
greatest mortal flaw... Love.
Hmph!
You look so
beautiful, Naru!
[giggling]
My cousin's getting
married this summer.
She and her fiancé
couldn't make the
wedding dress fitting,
so since I'm about her
size, I went for her.
Where did you
take this?
It was at the bridal
shop near the entrance
to the shopping district.
Do you know it?
I heard that some of
the grooms-to-be who
visited that shop with
their girlfriends
vanished off the
face of the earth.
Maybe your cousin's
fiancé will go
missing too.
Umino! What a terrible
thing to say!
Yeah! Shut up!
Well they're getting
married in June and they
say marriages that month
are supposed to be lucky.
Then they'll be
happy for sure!
Oh! She's a June Bride!
[giggling]
Awww!
I can't wait to
get married!
And wear a beautiful
wedding dress!
A white one with-
You should be careful.
Whoa! The new girl
looks tough.
Hey!
Why aren't you wearing
this school's uniform?
Because the sizes here
are all too small for
me, that's why.
So that's the new girl
who just transferred
into Class 6 today.
They say she's got
superhuman strength,
and that she got kicked
out of her last school.
Supposedly for picking
fights.
Oh.
She does look kinda
scary, doesn't she.
She didn't seem
that way to me.
Uh...
So, that's how
it's gonna be.
I heard she's some
kind of amazon.
No way. Scary.
I got it!
Lunch time! Lunch time!
What's in the box today?
I hop-
It's that transfer
student...
Whoa! Her lunchbox
is super cute!
[giggle]
Wow! That looks yummy!
[gasp]
Huh?
Hey!
Be a little more
careful next time!
Huh?
Uh... Thanks!
Oh! It's you again!
I heard she's some
kind of Amazon...
You shouldn't zone
out like that. You
could get hurt.
Um, tell me, does
it taste as good
as it looks?
Uh... Yeah...
Oh...
Here. Would you like
to have some too?
Yeah! You sure?
But it's your lunch,
I really shouldn't...
Oh! But maybe just one!
Bon appetit!
This is as delicious
as it looks!
It's no big deal
They're easy to
make.
What?! You mean you
made this yourself?
Yeah.
That's so cool! How
did you learn to
make all that?
And your lunch box and
matching bag are both
totally adorable too!
Where did you buy
them? What store
was it?
Oh, I just found
this lunch box at
my old house.
And so I decided to
make a bag to go with
it.
Amazing!
That's really
impressive!
It's just a
little bag.
And also...
Your rose earrings
are really lovely.
Oh. Why thank you.
[giggling]
What on earth was that?
My mom would be so surprised
to hear that you make your
own lunches.
I can barely cook at all.
Uh, since I'm new here
and living on my own
do you think you could
tell me a bit about
this town?
Huh?
Everyone else is too
afraid to talk to me.
They won't even look
me in the eye.
[laughing]
Scared of a pretty girl
with cute earrings and
perfume?
That's ridiculous!
I'd be happy to tell you
whatever you might want
to know about town.
Ask me anything!
Well in that case, can
you tell me where to find
a discount supermarket,
a place to buy cute
accessories... Oh!
And an arcade, too!
What? An arcade?
Wow! You're really
good at this!
You sure you've never
played this game before?
It's the same as
fighting in real life.
You let the bad guy chase
you so you can catch him
off guard, then you hit him
with your ultimate attack!
Ultimate attack!
Hi Usagi! You're
here early today.
Oh! Hi, Ami!
That girl is good.
She's mastered the
game already.
Have you met the new
girl yet? She just
transferred into
Class 6 today.
I'm Makoto Kino.
I'm Ami Mizuno. I go
to Juban, too. It's so
nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too!
Hey Usagi! So are all
the girls you're friends
with cute?
I don't think
we've met.
It's... you...
Oh! Nothing! I thought
you were someone else.
Hm?
I'm Motoki Furuhata.
I work here part-time.
Hey, does everybody
usually call you
Motoki like I do?
Well my college friends
call me "Furu".
Furu? Huh?
Hey!
That gives me an idea!
I'll call you "Mako"!
Makoto is now Mako, the
strong and careful chef!
I've never had a friend
give me a nickname before.
I like it.
[giggle]
You really are something,
Usagi. You've got such a
big heart.
You can make
friends with anyone.
So do you guys
want to hear a
weird rumor I heard
from a customer
the other day?
A rumor?
Well this is the bridal
shop he was talking about.
It's also the same one
Naru went to, I think.
Hm? Where's Mako?
So gorgeous. I wish
I could wear a dress
like that.
I think you'd look
great in that dress.
Hm?
Yeah. You're so tall and
statuesque. A strapless
dress would suit you.
You think so?
Ah! When I get married
I'm going to wear a
wedding dress
just like these!
Yeah? I think I'd prefer
a white wedding kimono.
What about you, Mako?
Uh? Well I...
I guess I'd wear
whichever kind of dress
my fiancé liked best.
Mako, you are
too cute!
Well, I'd just
like to match him.
Such an old-
fashioned girlie
girl!
Okay, cut it out
Usagi. Quit teasing
me.
Hey, isn't this the
bridal shop that's
supposed to be haunted?
You mean the one
with the ghost bride?
Yeah I think it is.
Huh? Ghost bride?
Hm?
Rumor has it that one of
the mannequins comes to
life at night and seduces
men. They say a lot of
grooms-to-be have gone
missing after visiting
here with their fiancés.
Ooh, that's so creepy.
Hi Rei!
Oh hi, Usagi.
Stop worrying, Usagi.
There's no scientific
proof that ghosts
are real.
You really don't
think there's a
ghost at all?
I don't care what it
is. If a weak man allows
himself to be seduced
it's his own fault.
I think all men are
fools. I don't trust
them.
[nervous laugh]
Okay...
All of it sounds too
complicated for me.
I'm gonna go
home! See ya!
Oh. Bye.
I get the feeling
this isn't the last
we'll be seeing of her.
Yeah, I think you may
be right about that.
Please, please I beg
you! Let my fiancé
come back to me.
[sobbing]
Don't cry, dear. The
ghost bride is just
an urban legend.
He hasn't been
kidnapped.
He'll turn up soon.
You'll see.
We definitely need to
investigate this.
Okay. All locked up.
Is that a bride?
Yes. Gaze into my
eyes and become
my slave.
[gasp]
Give me all your
energy. Pour out
your love.
You're...
so beautiful.
It's getting late.
I should hurry.
So are you gonna come
to my game this Sunday?
[giggle]
Sure, I'll make
you lunch.
A huge bento that
we can both eat
afterwards.
Kino...
[sigh]
Of course that wasn't
him in the arcade.
That guy there just
reminds me of him.
[giggle]
There you are, Mako.
I've been looking
for you everywhere.
[gasp]
Look into my eyes.
Oh...
I love you.
[gasp]
An evil aura...
This way. Hurry!
Over here!
Who's there?
Where are you?
Huh?
Tuxedo Mask...
Am I still dreaming?
[gasp]
Usagi?
Oh no!
Rei! Ami! Can you
hear me? Usagi's
in trouble!
Where are you going?
Tuxedo Mask, where
are you taking me?
[gasp]
Motoki! Mako!
What's that weird
green light?
Usagi!
[evil laughter]
[gasp]
Is that?
The ghost bride?!
[evil laugh]
That's it. Pour
out all of your
energy!
Sacrifice yourselves
to our Great Ruler!
The rumors were wrong!
That's not a ghost!
It's a Monster!
Are friends are in
trouble! We have
to save them!
Moon Prism Power
Make Up!
Mercury Power
Mars Power
Make Up!
How dare you pretend to
be a blushing bride and
take advantage of innocent
people who are in love!
I am the Pretty Guardian!
Who fights for love
and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now in the name
of the Moon, I'll
punish you!
I was expecting you
Sailor Guardians!
What is this? I
can't see anything!
I've got her.
Leave it to me!
Evil Spirit, be gone!
Where'd she go?
There! Next to Mako!
[gasp]
Mako!
No one moves! Or
I kill the girl.
[gasps]
[chuckling]
So he's the one
behind all this!
Hmph! Pathetic humans.
You are so easily deceived
by appearances!
Appearances?
What happened?
Hey! Wait up! Are
you on your way
home?
Huh? Oh, hey
there Kino.
I thought we could
walk home together.
Didn't I tell ya?
I have a girlfriend
now.
Hm...
So yeah, I'm gonna
walk home with her
from now on.
Sorry, Kino! See ya!
Was it... all a lie?
That girl, she's
still conscious?
Motoki, he looks like
the boy I loved. He
told me that he loved
me... But it was a lie.
Ridiculous humans. So
obsessed with trivial
emotions.
Why can't they
just face the truth?
I heard she's some
kind of Amazon.
Who am I kidding?
They'll never see
me as anything
else.
How could you ever
believe anyone would
love you?
I was a fool to
believe in love.
He never loved me.
Love isn't real. I
don't believe in
anything anymore.
Don't say that, Mako!
[gasp]
To love another
person isn't wrong!
Usagi... You're...
I believe in love. I
believe we each have
a soul mate that we're
destined to be with.
I believe I will
find that person.
The one that's meant
for me, that I'll love
with my whole heart!
There's someone out
there for you too,
Mako. I know there is!
So please, don't
stop believing!
Believe in love!
Love can conquer
anything!
Thank you, Usagi!
Agh! Fine then, Sailor
Guardians! Believe in
love all you want,
Let it be the
death of you!
[gasp]
[screaming]
[grunting]
Oh no!
[chuckling]
I'm not gonna let you
get away with this.
[gasp]
I will show you...
How powerful
love can be!
How did-?!
If you want to try and
use love to defeat me,
then bring it on!
That vision...
I knew it!
[gasp]
Hm!
Jupiter Power
Make Up!
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for courage!
I am Sailor Jupiter!
I'll fill you with
regret, it'll leave
you numb!
Mako!
Damn it! Not another
one! You're a Sailor
Guardian too?
No one can defeat
the power of love!
Flower Hurricane!
What the hell is this?
I can't move.
That look in her
eyes... Do I know it?
Jupiter, my guardian
planet! Bring forth
a storm!
And bring down
your thunder!
Jupiter Thunderbolt!
[screaming]
Sailor Jupiter...
Mako!
[groaning]
Is this a mannequin?
What the- Why am I
sleeping on the
sidewalk?
Tuxedo Mask, did he lead
Usagi here so that she
could save everyone?
I fell in love with a
senior who broke my
heart. After that it
was painful to be at the
same school with him.
I'm so sorry.
But, that's not why I
transferred. He's not
the reason I came here.
It felt like something
more important than
love was calling me here.
Like there was a
whisper on the
night wind.
And it told me I
needed to come here.
Good for you. Life's
too short to waste
it moping over some guy.
I'm glad. Because now
we get to have you
as one of us.
She's right. We're
happy to have you,
Sailor Jupiter.
You are our ally,
guardian of thunder
and courage.
Sailor Jupiter...
I remember now. That's
who I really am. And I
know that there's a
mission I have
to carry out!
Huh?
Luna?
There are four Sailor
Guardians now.
Sailor Moon, you must
now take your place as
leader of our mission
to find the Legendary
Silver Crystal and
the Princess!
You want me to
be the leader?
Wait, what did
Tuxedo Mask
confess to?
He claims some of the
robberies were his doing
because he was looking for
the Legendary Silver Crystal.
He's definitely up to
something. Usagi, I'd
stay away from him if
I were you.
Tuxedo Mask, are you a
friend? Or are you...
an enemy?
Act. 6: Tuxedo Mask
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.