I'm sorry, Mamo!
Please forgive me!
I can't stand seeing you
like this anymore!
Mamo...
Are we star-crossed lovers
always destined...
...to suffer the same fate?
Mamo...
I love you.
[Gasping]
Endymion...
You are my one and
only true love.
No matter how many lifetimes
we live, I know we will always
find one another.
And we'll fall in
love all over again.
Our souls will transcend space
and time eternally, until the
day comes when we can at last...
...be together.
Hmph!
Usagi!
This can't be real!
Oh no!
It's not fair.
This is wrong!
Why would fate give us new
lives if it was just going to
end like this all over again?
That light!
The Legendary Silver Crystal.
It's become whole!
[Gasps] No!
We can't allow it to grow here!
Not in the Dark Kingdom!
Oh, what a brilliant light!
Such energy! Such power! it
fills the Dark Kingdom!
Queen Metalia!
[Screaming]
At last, everything I wanted is
mine! I have all the energy
I need and I shall
have the Crystal too!
No you won't!
[Grunts] Luna!
Stay out of my way!
[Screams]
Usagi!
[Laughing] Foolish cat!
Luna!
Queen Metalia, she's
enveloped the whole
thing, it's inside her!
[Grunts]
Luna!
Please forgive me.
Luna, promise me that you'll
watch over the Princess forever.
Even if she should
one day be reborn.
[Whimpering] I couldn't
protect her.
I failed my princess and my
queen. I'm so sorry.
Yes! The power! I can feel
it coursing through me!
[Screams]
Queen Metalia's gone.
She took Usagi and
Mamoru with her.
What do we do now?
There's still hope.
[Gasps]
The princess is with the
Crystal. It will protect
her and Endymion.
Mhm.
Artemis is right! It's
not over yet. There's
still time to save them!
Queen Metalia
must be stopped!
We can't just let her
have the Crystal. We
have to get it back!
Okay. Let's get going!
Hmph!
Hurry girls! Everything's
up to you now!
[Grunting]
Luna!
It's all my fault, Artemis. I
forced Usagi to fight the man
she loves!
[Gasps] I've got you!
Take me to the Moon, Artemis,
to Silver Millennium.
I need to go to the Chamber of
Prayer in the Moon Castle.
Alright.
[Gasps]
We're in the Arctic Circle!
Shouldn't there be ice?
It's a barren wasteland!
It feels eerie, like a
massive graveyard.
The rock here is like the ruins
of Silver Millennium.
It's been so long!
For ages I languished
underground, suffocating in
the prison where Queen
Serenity sealed me.
[All] Queen Metalia!
But I am reborn! Reinvigorated
by the power of the Legendary
Silver Crystal now within me!
This time nothing
will stop me!
[Gasps]
If she keeps feeding off the
Crystal's power, she'll get
even bigger!
Hmph!
Everyone ready? Power up!
Jupiter Power!
Mercury Power!
Mars Power!
Venus Power!
[All] Sailor Planet Attack!
[Chuckles]
You cannot hurt me!
[Screams]
[Grunts]
[Gasps]
It's no use. She's
too powerful!
At this rate Queen Metalia will
engulf the whole planet.
All energy makes me grow
stronger! Even the power
of your attack!
As long as I have the power of
the Legendary Silver Crystal,
I'm invincible!
She's taken all we ever cared
about, and we're not strong
enough to get it back from her.
[Gasps]
[Groaning]
[Attacking Grunt]
[Screams]
[Groaning]
[Laughing] Miserable little
humans! They're all mine now!
Their whole planet is mine!
[Grunting]
Luna.
[Gasps]
Your Majesty, Queen Serenity.
It's Luna, your humble servant.
I beseech you! Please! Show
yourself once more, my Queen.
I need you to release what
remains of the Moon Power.
It is the last hope that Planet
Earth and the humans have.
Help me, my
Queen, I beg you!
Take my life
if you have to!
Just please, save Usagi!
[Groaning]
So, it's all over then.
There's no way to stop her.
Queen Metalia's evil darkness
will swallow this whole planet.
The Earth...will it fall to ruin
like the Moon Kingdom did?
Yes, it's possible. But there's
nothing else we can do.
[Gasps]
You're not alone anymore,
Minako. You don't have to do
everything by yourself!
Huh?
Has anybody ever told
you how cute you are
when you smile, Ami?
[Gasps]
How dare you accuse Rei!
She's a beautiful girl,
both inside and out!
[Gasps]
Scared of a pretty girl with
cute earrings and perfume?
That's ridiculous!
[Giggling]
[Gasps] I can hear
Usagi's voice!
Same here.
I heard it too!
That must mean
she's still alive.
She's calling out to us.
Usagi always believed in us.
She gave us the courage
to be the best we could!
She's the heart of our
team. Her spirit is
a ray of sunshine!
We can't give up! Not until
we see her smile again!
I can feel the Legendary Silver
Crystal protecting her. She is
still alive! I'm sure of it!
Ridiculous! Sailor Moon is
inside me. She belongs to the
Darkness now!
You're wrong! Usagi is alive!
All four of us know it! We
have no doubt!
How can you be so certain?
Because we can feel her in our
hearts. She's always with us.
We love you, Usagi!
What? The Sacred
Sword of Light?!
The Silver Crystal is waiting
for us to set it free.
Waiting for the right moment
to strike down Metalia!
We lack the strength to seal
Queen Metalia and her darkness
ourselves!
But there is one
last thing we can do.
We can give Usagi a fighting
chance to save this planet!
But if we're going to do
it, we have to do it now!
These pens are not just
for transformation.
They contain our sacred
power as Guardians,
our very life force.
We can send them to Usagi to
help her, but that means making
the ultimate sacrifice.
O Sacred Sword! Take all
of our power as Guardians!
For the Princess!
Venus Power!
Mars Power!
Mercury Power!
Jupiter Power!
Please
Princess! Awaken!
Make up!
Hah! Are you pitiful little
Guardians from the Moon Kingdom
still trying to fight back?!
[Screams]
Princess!
[All] Usagi!
[Laughing]
What a waste!
To just throw away
their lives like that!
Princess!
[All] Usagi!
Hmm? Where am I?
I remember...
...a fight, and the sword...
I'm alive? How is
that possible?
[Gasps] The Legendary
Silver Crystal!
[Gasps] Mamo!
His pocket watch.
It stopped the sword from
running me through.
Mamo, even now, you're
still saving my life.
[Crying] But why?
Why couldn't you
take me with you?
The Legendary Silver
Crystal is mine!
[Gasps]
[Moaning]
[Gasps] Stop it!
[Grunting]
I don't wanna hear anymore!
The voices of humanity's
darkness!
Such a beautiful
cacophony of bitterness
and malice!
Now that I have the Legendary
Silver Crystal, every living
thing on Earth will become
part of my darkness!
Please no more! Stop!
The royal line of the Moon
Kingdom ends here!
I have you in my clutches,
Princess! You will become part
of me! There is no escape!
No, don't!
[Laughing] Scream and cry all
you like! There's nothing you
can do about it!
If I don't do something soon,
the darkness will consume me. I
have to get out of here!
Please, Legendary Silver
Crystal, lend me your power. I
don't want to die like this!
I want...
...to be with my friends,
the Sailor Guardians!
The power, I can feel it!
Wait, what's happening?
My body's getting hot.
What have you done!?
[Grunting] We're free.
We actually managed
to escape from her.
The Legendary Silver Crystal,
it did what I asked.
Hmm? [Gasps]
His hand!
It feels warm again!
Did the Crystal do this too? Is
it giving him back to me?
[Gasps]
[Gasps] Usako...
He's alive!
[Grunting]
Mamo.
Usako.
[Sighing]
[Sighs] It's a miracle!
Yes it is, and it's
all because of you.
[Growling]
Metalia!
[Grunting]
[Growling]
[Sighs] I won't let
you have them!
Not the Princess, or the
Legendary Silver Crystal!
[Sighs] Mamo!
Usako, listen to me. Take
the Legendary Silver
Crystal and use its power!
Vanquish Queen Metalia!
I will!
Give it to me! The Legendary
Silver Crystal is mine!
Queen Metalia!
I won't let you win!
What incredible energy! It's
even more powerful than when it
was inside me!
[Growling] I want it!
I must have it!
No! Why isn't this working?!
I can't! [Gulps]
I can't do it! She's too
powerful, I can't seal
her all by myself!
[Growls]
Where are the Guardians?
I need them!
I can't do it alone! Without
their help she'll suck me back
inside her!
Luna, Artemis!
Mercury! Mars!
Jupiter! Venus!
I don't know what to do!
I'm lost without them!
I can't!
Huh?
Sailor Moon.
[Grunts]
[Gasps]
Master Endymion, we
are reunited at last.
Kunzite?
Master, it is time to destroy
that evil once and for all.
Queen Metalia is a
terrible monster.
She devours the life force of
all living things and transforms
it into darkness, leaving worlds
turned to stone in her wake.
The star mark on Metalia's
head, that is her weak point.
If you strike her there, with
an attack from the Legendary
Silver Crystal...
We can end her for good!
Master.
It's good to see you again.
This time we hope you
and the Princess...
...can live happily
ever after.
I understand now.
The stones, they were you! You
stopped the sword from piercing
my heart!
You gave your lives to protect
me, just like you promised! My
loyal Knights, thank you.
[Growling]
I can't hold on, not
on my own! [Grunts]
It's okay, I've got you.
[Sighs]
Sailor Moon!
[Sighs] Mamo, it's you.
Nothing can replace your
friends. But you're not alone.
I'm here, right beside
you. You can do this!
You're Sailor Moon!
[Gasps] I am!
Sailor Moon.
That's right.
Serenity.
Endymion.
My love, you've always
given me strength.
Your support and
courage make me
believe in myself.
When I'm with you, I feel
confident, like there's
nothing I can't overcome.
Like I can do anything!
I am...
...the Guardian of justice...
Sailor Moon!
What!? You're just a child! How
can you possibly control the
Legendary Silver Crystal?
Hmph.
Give it everything you've got,
Sailor Moon. Don't hold back!
Remember, aim for the star
on Queen Metalia's forehead.
Hmph.
No matter what happens
next, I'm right here with you.
Hmph.
Give me the Crystal's power or
I'll rip you into little pieces!
No, Queen Metalia!
I'll never let you have it!
Legendary Silver Crystal! Grant
me the strength to triumph over
Queen Metalia!
And rid the world of her evil!
Usagi!
I am the Pretty Guardian who
fights for love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon, and
Princess Serenity!
By the power of the Moon...
...and the Silver Crystal...
I banish you! Forever!
You did it, Usako.
I'm so proud of you.
Oh, Mamo! I'm so happy
you're alive, and that
we're finally together again!
Serenity...
Endymion...
You are my soul mate, my
destiny. We were born to be
together.
I love you, Mamo! I'll never let
anything separate us again!
Act. 14 Conclusion and
Commencement.
Petite Étrangére.
The moonlight is
a messenger of love!