I am...
Sailor Moon!
Give me the Crystal's power
or I'll rip you into little
pieces!
Legendary Silver
Crystal...
Grant me the strength to
triumph over Queen Metalia!
And rid the world
of her evil!
I am the Pretty Guardian
who fights for love and
for justice.
I am Sailor Moon and
Princess Serenity!
By the power of
the Moon...
And the Silver
Crystal...
I banish you!
Forever!
I am Sailor Moon.
In the name of the
Moon, I'll punish
you!
It's not effecting
her at all!
[evil laughter]
[gasp]
Always remember my dear
Serenity, The Legendary
Silver Crystal
follows your heart.
Beseech the great power
of the Moon to awaken.
Offer a prayer to the Moon's
sacred tower. Then peace will
return to our kingdom.
Sailor Moon! Don't
hesitate! Just pray!
Believe in yourself!
Mamo's right!
Luna!
Ami!
Rei!
Mako!
Minako!
For everyone!
I won't give up!
O Great Power of the
Moon, Awaken!
Lend me your strength! And
I will match it with every
ounce of energy
that I have left!
Usagi.
[gasp]
The Tower! It's
regenerating!
[gasp]
Luna...
I have something
to show you.
This is the Chamber of
Prayer: A sacred place, at
the very heart of
the Moon Castle.
And there stands the
sanctuary's holy monument:
The Crystal Tower.
If there should come a
time when our kingdom,
or those that we love,
are ever in danger...
Offer a prayer to
this tower...
And the Moon's power,
will protect them.
Prayer is the key!
That's what's activating
the tower! Someone is
praying to it!
A resolute and heartfelt
prayer... Could it be?
Sailor Moon!
She's free of Metalia and
fighting to save the Earth!
She's praying!
What?!
You're not alone, Sailor
Moon. I will pray with you.
Two hearts are
stronger than one!
Together, we will release
the great power of the
Moon!
The power!
Such brilliant white light!
I've never seen the Moon
shine like this!
It's gleaming just like
the Legendary Silver
Crystal!
Oh! What luminous
radiance!
The supreme power I have
been thirsting for! At
last!
What's going on? I cannot
reach it. What is this
force?
It is... pushing
me back!
Be gone Queen Metalia!
By the power of this
sacred moonlight...
I will vanquish you!
[screaming]
Sailor Moon?
Sailor Moon!
Luna?
Huh?
Oh Artemis! We did it!
Luna, just now, beside the
tower, you looked almost
divine.
I could see you praying
with Princess Serenity.
It was like you had become
Selene, the moon goddess
herself.
[gasp]
Look Artemis!
Over there!
Huh?
[gasp]
The Moon Castle... and
Silver Millennium, our
beloved kingdom!
When Usagi used the power of
the Legendary Silver Crystal,
it returned everything
to its former glory!
The moonlight is soft
again. Just like it
always was.
She saved the
Earth. She did it.
Sailor Moon?
Her body is cold.
Did using all her
power like that-?
Wake up. Come
back to me. Usako!
It's you Endymion.
Serenity.
We're together.
At last...
I can see them.
The prince woke the princess
with a kiss. True love does
conquer all!
I'm so happy. I
missed you Mamo!
Usako, I've wanted to
hold you for so long.
We are soul mates. We were
born for one another, meant
to be.
I love you Mamo,
so very much!
And I won't ever
let you go again.
Way to go Usagi!
Congratulations!
We wish you the best!
Be happy!
[gasp]
My friends...
Where are they?!
Don't worry.
I'll find them for you.
But how?
[gasp]
A vision! Just by holding
Mamo's hand like this I
can see images from
all over the world.
Endymion... Is
this your power?
It feels like... the
Earth's energy is
flowing through you.
[gasp]
My friends!
Oh no!
Usagi...
[gasp]
Usagi... Can
you hear me?
Luna? Is that you?
Where are you, Luna?
The moon.
Huh?
If you come here,
you can save the
others.
I can't. My brooch
is broken, Luna.
I lost the ability to
transform. In fact,
I lost all my powers.
There's still a
way for you to get
here.
Huh?
You have the Legendary
Silver Crystal.
It's fused with the
Moon Stick. Use that.
Silver Crystal, please
take us to the Moon.
It's the Moon Castle.
That's right, Usagi.
Silver Millennium has
been restored.
Luna! Artemis!
Oh Usagi! I'm so
proud of you!
It's beautiful.
You are the master of
the Moon Castle now,
Usagi.
From here you will reign
over all of Silver Millennium
as the new Queen Serenity!
Luna, I can't stay and be
queen. I have to go home.
My family and friends
are waiting for me.
Usagi?
Even though I remember
now that I'm Serenity,
I'm also Usagi Tsukino.
My home is on Earth with
Mamo. I belong there with
those I love.
What're you saying?
It sounds like you've
made your decision, my
Serenity.
Queen Serenity...
Yes. I've decided. I want
to go back, to my life
on Earth.
You see, I figured out
the real reason I was
reincarnated.
I was meant to live my life
with those I care about:
Mamo, my family, my friends.
Especially the ones I came
to save, they gave their
lives for me!
What I want, is to be an
ordinary girl to live and
laugh and cry, with
the boy I love...
On the planet I've always
cherished, on Earth.
I have only one wish
for you, Serenity...
Be happy. Live with
the ones you love.
[gasp]
What's this?
It's a new brooch,
but it's different.
Place the Legendary Silver
Crystal inside and shout
these words:
"Moon Crystal Power
Make Up!"
That's your new
transformation phrase. Go on.
Try it! You will be
stronger and more
powerful than ever!
Thank you, Mother.
I will transform into
Sailor Moon again...
And go save my
friends!
Moon Crystal Power
Make Up!
I am the Pretty Guardian!
Who fights for love,
and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
Ami! Rei! Mako!
Minako!
And every living
being on Earth!
Moon Healing Escalation!
Huh?
[groaning]
When did it
get so late?
This is weird. What
the heck happened here?
How are we alive?
Hey! Everyone!
[gasps]
Usagi!
[crying]
I thought I would never
see you girls again! I
love you all so much!
Usagi!
Everyone's alive
and back to normal.
But does this mean they
can never transform into
Sailor Guardians again?
Come here Artemis!
Silly artemis. You should
know by now that we'd never
die that easily.
Yeah... we're
tougher than
that.
After all, we still
have a job to do.
We're sworn to protect
our princess. Now,
and forever...
It's not just a new
day, it's a new world.
Come on. Let's
go home.
Back to where
we belong.
Bye Artemis!
I'm off to school!
See you later!
Mornin' Ami!
Oh! Good Morning,
Mako!
Usagi! Time to wake
up or you'll be late!
[giggling]
Surprise! I'm
already awake,
Mom!
Oh my!
Usagi's ready for
school on time? That's
a first.
I guess pigs must
be flying now.
Shingo!
Don't tease your sister!
It's good that she's being
more responsible.
Come have some
breakfast, dear.
Agh! I forgot about
my homework!
Ugh...
I'm supposed to
turn it in today!
Oh! Good Morning,
Usagi!
Morning, Naru!
[gasp]
What was that?
A bad omen?
Please, let me be wrong.
Things are finally peaceful.
Can't they just stay
that way for a while?
[giggle]
You're late, Usako. You
had to stay for detention
again didn't you?
Detention? Me?
Nah, I stopped to
pick this up.
Remember your broken
pocket watch?
I took it to the jewelers
and had it fixed for you!
Listen!
See? You hear that?
It's ticking again?
Huh?
[screaming]
[groaning]
My neck! What the
hell was that! Oww!
Hey! What do you think
you're doing?! Get away
from my Mamo right now!
Mamo?
Uh? A little kid.
Who're you?
My name is Usagi!
You're... Usagi?
Yeah! Who the heck are
you? And how come you're
wearing buns like that?
Are you copying me?
What are you talking
about? I'm the Usagi
here! Usagi Tsukino!
[gasp]
You're... Usagi Tsukino?
Yeah...
If you are who you say you
are, then you should have
the Legendary Silver Crystal!
[gasps]
Hurry up and hand it
over! Now! Or I'll shoot!
Hey Chibi Usagi! Tell us
who you really are! Oh!
So now you've got nothing
to say?! Well that's not
gonna fly!
Out with it!
We're not gonna let you
off easy just cause you're
a kid! Right, Rei?
I'm not sure, but I think
we may have an intruder
among us.
Huh?
I have a bad feeling
about this.
Rei, what's wrong?
What is it?
Act. 15 Infiltration
Sailor Mars
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.