[gasp]
Come on... You're getting
warmer. I'm right over here.
Usako? Chibi-Usa?
[snicker]
[laughing]
I'm going after them!
Space-Time storm or not, I
have to find them!
You can't go! It's too
dangerous.
We don't even know where in
space-time they are.
I don't care how dangerous
it is! If Mamo's out there,
then I'm going!
I broke out of Nemesis just
so I could see him again!
In the great oblivion
between space-times, the
laws of physics don't apply.
It is a gaping abyss,
littered with pitfalls and
hazards that appear without
warning.
Even under normal
conditions,
none should
venture there.
Too bad. I'm going.
And if she goes, that means
we all go, too!
Have faith in Sailor
Moon, Pluto.
We know she
can do this.
And as Sailor Guardians,
it's our duty to protect her.
Right. Plus, there's no
talking her out of it.
Very well then.
Hm.
These coordinates are
unstable. I can't get a fix.
There's a
chill in the air.
Are we even headed in the
right direction?
I am not certain.
Out here in the
In-Between, you need a
Space-Time key to have any
reference point for knowing
where and when you are.
Those without one, become
drifters, destined to wander
forever in this interval of
time.
Or else until they
disappear into the void.
A powerful shockwave
preceded this storm. My
guess is, that was Small
Lady colliding or clashing
with something, and she has
ended up somewhere.
Well, wherever
Chibi-usa is,
Tuxedo Mask must be there
too, since he followed her.
Maybe. But there's no
guarantee he found her and
they're together.
Mm.
Mars is right. We don't know
that he's with her.
He is.
He made a promise to protect
her. And Mamo keeps his
promises. He'll follow her
to the edge of the universe
if that's what it takes.
Usagi...
I know what he's thinking.
He's the man I love. I know
him better than anyone.
When he said he would give
his life for her, he meant it!
Mamo has a strong sense of
responsibility, and
Chibi-Usa is our
daughter.
He'd do anything for her. I
know they're together
because he'd find her, no
matter what!
That's just the kind of man
he is.
Mamo... I'm sorry...
You have no idea
how much I
wish I could be with
you right now.
Fate is so cruel. I wanted
to see you so badly, and
just when I thought I could,
we were ripped apart again.
Mm.
I'm sensing
something.
Is anyone there?
Luna P?!
Uh--
So Chibi-Usa did
come this way.
Small Lady would never go
anywhere without Luna P.
It is too dangerous
to go any further.
We need to go back.
Chibi-Usa... Mamo ...
Sailor Moon!
[grunt]
Where am I?
Saphir!
[grunt]
Brother...? What happened?
Where are we?
I don't see Rubeus.
Wait a minute... Are
we in the Dark Chamber?
Yes. Things are a bit
nasty with the reactor
right now, so I decided
to bring you down here.
I'm afraid your little
science project has gone
berserk.
It's melting down?
Better! The power of the
Legendary Silver Crystal and
the explosion that followed,
triggered hyper-accelerated
fusion reactions. The
entire planet is ablaze!
The energy
is unbelievable!
And it's all thanks to you,
Saphir. Because of the
reactor you constructed,
Nemesis is finally reaching
its full potential.
This may not have been what
you intended, but you should
be proud. With this
planetary evolution
the power of
Nemesis is unsurpassed.
The mark of the Black Moon.
Who are you? What's your
name?
[chuckle]
We'll get to that later.
Wiseman is calling.
Now, come with me.
What is this? Are we passing
through the core of Nemesis?
[giggle] The core is
bursting with chemical
reactions right now.
It wouldn't be this cold,
dark, or quiet if that's
where we were.
Okay then. Where are we?
This is a pocket of warped
space created by the Malefic
Black Crystal's negative
energy. A hidden corner at
the edge of Space-Time,
which Wiseman controls.
Black Moon Castle is gone.
Ahead is your new base of
operations: Wiseman's Castle
of Darkness.
Wiseman has a castle of his
own? Does that mean he lives
here? Is this distorted
space where he disappears to?
And her... She looks so
much like the Queen.
Who are you,
mysterious lady?
[chuckle]
Welcome to my humble abode.
I never realized you
had your own dimension.
Grand, isn't it? And what do
you think of my dear Rabbit?
Have you said hello?
Now I see...
So you've grown up and
switched sides, is that it?
Don't be rude! Wiseman
needed me and so, here I am.
Wiseman's will is
absolute.
It is truth. He
leads, we follow.
Surely this was
explained to you.
Have you
forgotten it?
Wiseman.
Something's changed. He's
different from before.
Where is Rubeus? Any
idea what happened to him?
If you mean your red-headed
friend, Wiseman killed him.
What!?
It was his own fault. He
questioned Wiseman's
authority and then
tried to desert.
I say he had
it coming.
Rubeus...
Wiseman... Now you've gone
too far!
Just who the hell are you?!
And what is it
that you really want?
[groaning]
Help me Brother!
Saphir!
[grunting]
I am your Lord and Master!
My will is absolute! You
shall serve me in any way I
see fit! I give the orders
and you obey!
Yes, Wiseman.
Your will is absolute.
We're yours to command.
Not only are these Malefic
Black Crystal earrings
stronger than any you've had
before; they are symbols of
power and signify
your loyalty to
Nemesis. Wear them with
pride.
At last, I have you, my dear
Rabbit. And this
Legendary Silver Crystal you
were kind enough to bring
me. But something is
missing... This is just an
ordinary piece of glass.
Where is its light? Where is
its power!?
Only Neo Queen Serenity can
use that it. That is her
Silver Crystal from
the 30th century.
But there're two, and
the other one
belongs to
Sailor Moon.
I see. Then the surge of
power I witnessed, in the
reactor chamber,
came from the Legendary
Silver Crystal of the past.
And to use either stone, I
must have Neo Queen
Serenity and Sailor
Moon within
my grasp.
All right, then. Bring me the
Legendary Silver Crystal of
the past as well...
The rest should be simple
enough, especially for you.
I will get you the
other crystal right away.
I am at your
service, Wiseman.
This will not
be difficult.
Oh really?
Neo Queen Serenity's
castle is impenetrable.
It can't be breached
by just any old attack.
Hmph!
Also, that's a pretty
piece of glass you have
there, but is it the real
thing?
I have my doubts. It doesn't
work. And there's no proof
it is what you say it is.
Are you sure you can trust
her, Wiseman?
Because I don't.
How dare you? Once I capture
Neo Queen Serenity, you'll see.
We'll fire a second giant
piece of the Malefic Black
Crystal into the Earth. That
should get the queen's
attention and force her to
show herself. Then I'll
make her kneel before me.
The planet's already been
badly damaged.
A new attack
could destroy it.
So be it.
Who cares? What does it
matter? I already have what
I want. The only
man I love.
Endymion.
You know what needs to be
done. Now go. With your new
earrings, you can travel
freely in space and time.
Get everything ready to
attack the Earth.
Do you see that Saphir?
Nemesis is alight! Just look
at it burn!
I never realized what an
enormous planet it actually is.
Finally, I have you
all to myself.
I won't let anyone
get in our way.
You are mine and mine
alone...
... Forever...
Chibi-Usa... Mamo... You're
surrounded by darkness...
Where are you?
Chibi-Usa... Mamo...
You're awake!
Guys?
Are you okay? You slept
for a long time.
Mom? [gasp]
My room? How did I get here?
[chuckling]
Your friends brought you
home. Don't you remember?
You fell in gym class
and got a concussion.
[sigh] My Usagi,
such a klutz.
You girls catch up. I'll go
make some tea.
[gasp]
Luna P!
King Endymion repaired it
for us, and I was able to
use it to alter your
mom's memory...
At least for
the time being.
What really happened?
Tell me.
You overdid it while we were
searching through
space-time, and you passed
out.
We thought we'd come back
here for a bit so you could
recover. You'd been there
too long anyway.
Must feel nice to be back
home in your own bed.
You were talking in your
sleep and snoring too.
I was?
We tried pinching your
nose to make you stop.
Really?
But it didn't work. You were
still louder than a buzz saw.
Aww. You guys are so mean!
Everyone came over to play!
[gasp]
Uh--
Usagi?
[exhale]
It all seems so unreal.
I'm home and the five of us
are together again. I can
hardly believe it...
And I'm really happy!
I mean that. I am. It's
just... something's missing.
I want Chibi-Usa and Mamo
here with me. too.
Without them, I'm lonely.
Guess what, Usagi! I brought
Luna P to school for show
and tell! And now everybody
wants one! [giggling]
[crying]
Jeez, you're a hopeless
case, you know that?
No kidding. Everyone is
trying to comfort you
and this is
the thanks we get?
But we know it's your
maternal instinct kicking
in, so we'll let it slide.
Don't be sad, Usagi.
We love you.
And we just want
to see you smile.
Heh.
I have to find them. I'm
not going to stop looking.
They are both coming
home safe and sound.
That's a promise.
Chibi-Usa, Mamo
and you guys all mean
everything to me!
I need to find them,
will you help me?
Of course we'll help!
They're our friends.
We want to find them
just as much as you do.
If we all put our heads
together and come up with a
plan, I'm sure we can save
them.
Plus, we wouldn't let you go
alone even if you wanted to.
-That's for sure!
-[laughing]
You've gotten so strong,
Usagi. I'm proud of you.
Serenity... Can you hear me?
Forgive me, my love.
I could not protect
our daughter.
And now she's gone.
You saved Sailor Moon,
didn't you?
She told me she felt your
presence and you shared your
power with her. But the
Legendary Silver Crystal
from the past cannot be used
here in the future. Did you
activate it for her? Or were
you somehow with her when
she escaped?
Serenity... Are you awake?
Please lend me your
strength. As a disembodied
spirit, I can hardly do
anything. Serenity, why
won't you answer me?
She hasn't forsaken you.
It's just not time
for that yet.
Diana?
The queen would never
abandon her loved ones. If
things were truly desperate,
you know she'd intervene.
Just like she did with
Sailor Moon.
But for the time being, she
remains inside the Legendary
Silver Crystal, healing her
wounds. She needs to build
her strength back up, so
that we'll have it when we
need it the most.
It's good the queen's not
awake yet. That
means things aren't as
bad as they could be.
So, please try to
cheer up, okay?
Hm.
[meow]
Thank you, Diana.
Get to bed early. You need a
good night's sleep.
I will.
See you in the morning,
Usagi.
Okay, bye guys!
Have a good night.
Mm.
A blood-red sunset is a bad
omen.
Mamo, Chibi-Usa... Wherever
you are, please be safe.
Huh? Pluto's
Space-Time Key?
[gasp]
What's going on? Why is
everything getting all
warped and twisted?
[gasp]
It feels like it's ripping
my body apart!
[screaming]
[gasps]
I think it's over. You all
okay?
Yeah, we're fine. What was
that?
[panting]
The Key... Was it Pluto
trying to warn me? Does she
need me to come to the
future?
Usagi!
Are you okay?
Luna! Something's wrong!
I agree! We need to get to
the 30th century right away!
Let's go.
Ready?
Mm!
Moon Crystal Power!
Mercury Star Power!
Mars Star Power!
Jupiter Star Power!
Venus Star Power!
Make up!
[panting]
Pluto!
Sailor Moon!
Did something
bad happen?!
We felt a shockwave all
the way in the past!
It's awful! Take
a look.
[gasp]
Oh no!
A second Malefic Black
Crystal? But the Earth was
already destroyed, why would
the Black Moon attack it again?!
Hello... Neo Queen Serenity.
Wake up. It's me!
Who are you? What are you
doing here?
[gasp]
Don't you recognize me?
I'm your daughter.
Princess Usagi Small
Lady Serenity.
You're not Small Lady. You
can't be!
Oh, but I am.
How else could I be
here? Only members of the
Silver Millennium
royal household
may enter
the Palace.
But then... why do you look
like that?
I grew up. Now I look like
who I really am.
Someone gave me the power
to change and finally,
I have awakened.
[gasp]
King Endymion!
Who are you?
It couldn't be!
Did you miss me? Don't tell
me you forgot!
Not that it matters! Now
give me the Silver Crystal!
[gasp] [yelp]
[gasp]
[grunt]
[groaning]
Neat trick. So that's how
the unworthy are cast
out of paradise.
Guess this means I'm kicked
out of the family and can no
longer inherit the throne.
Fine! Keep your crown!
I never wanted it anyway.
Not from a world that
didn't want me! Now it's
time to turn my back on you!
[panting]
Small Lady!
Chibi-Usa!
[panting]
Chibi-Usa? Is that you?!
Yes. My name was Chibi-Usa,
once upon a time.
But not anymore. I've grown
up. I'm not the little girl
I used to be.
Wiseman!
[gasp]
My name is Black Lady:
Queen of Darkness.
Wiseman, Ruler of Darkness,
chose me to be at his side.
And now I am Queen
of the Dark Planet.
The Queen of Nemesis!
Please, Chibi-Usa! Stop!
Take the Legendary Silver
Crystal!
Take my life! Take
whatever you want!
I don't care
what it is!
Just stop being Black
Lady...
Please! That's not
who you are!
I've had enough
of this future.
I don't wanna see
any more of it!
Act 24: ATTACK - BLACK LADY
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.