That is the Moon Stick.
It's yours now.
Oh...
It's very powerful.
It will help you
in battle.
[battle cries]
Find the Legendary
Silver Crystal.
[gasp]
That same dream again.
Someone is calling
to me from my dreams.
Who are you?
And why do you need me
to find The Legendary
Silver Crystal?
Ah! Ami! Mako!
Good morning!
Good morning to
you too, Usagi!
Atta girl. You
didn't oversleep.
I've been having a lot
of weird dreams lately.
I wake up and then I
can't go back to sleep.
Recently it's been the
same dream over and over
again every night.
Who are you
mystery man?
Agh!
Owie!
Are you alright?
[gasp]
Not you again!
Bun-head? You should really
learn to watch where you're
going. You could get hurt.
Same to you, pal!
No thank you!
[gasp]
Take care of
yourself.
Who's that?
Uh, I don't know! I
just keep bumping
into him!
Usagi, your face is
red. Are you okay?
Oh! You're
blushing!
No, I'm not!
It's hot today!
That shirt...
I recognize that uniform.
It's from Moto-Azabu, the
very elite private high
school. Are you sure
you don't know him?
I know his name. It's
Mamoru Chiba and he's
always mean to me.
Aha! So you do
know him?
Oh! It's not what
you're thinking!
Usagi, Mako!
Hm?
Look there.
This mysterious person,
calling himself Tuxedo
Mask, has made a statement
to the media.
He claims to have committed
numerous offenses, and says
he did it in order to obtain
a lost treasure called
"The Legendary Silver
Crystal."
Hey, did you guys
see the news?
Yeah, about that
Tuxedo Mask guy?
What was that treasure
he wanted?
The Legendary Silver
Crystal. They say it's
priceless and it's somewhere
here in Japan.
They're doing a special
news report about it on
TV tonight. Might be
worth checking out.
Really? That's
a pretty big deal.
Oh...
Tuxedo Mask. What
are you up to this
time?
Tuxedo Mask?
What is the Legendary
Silver Crystal?
[chattering]
This should flush out
some more information.
I will find the Legendary
Silver Crystal. I don't
care what it costs me.
There have long been rumors
of The Legendary Silver
Crystal, but its existence
has yet to be officially
confirmed. Stay tuned.
We'll have expert analysis
right after the break.
[chuckling]
Now the Sailor Guardians,
Tuxedo Mask, and the humans
are all searching for the
Legendary Silver Crystal.
How very amusing.
Do not laugh, Kunzite.
This is no joke.
The Legendary Silver
Crystal rightfully belongs
to the Dark Kingdom. Yet
thus far you have failed
to obtain both it and
sufficient energy for
our Great Ruler.
Queen Beryl, I beg of
you, give me one more
chance!
But Nephrite...
You are injured. You
underestimated the
Sailor Guardians.
Sailor Jupiter...
You will pay.
Allow me, Queen Beryl.
Nephrite has failed you,
but I, Zoisite, will not.
Hmph!
This is a good thing. I
shall be able to exploit
this turn of events for
our gain, and get you
everything you seek.
This has turned
into a huge mess.
It's a trap. It has
to be. Right Luna?
Could this mean danger
for our Princess, too?
Shouldn't we do something?
I don't know. I never
imagined anything like
this.
Tuxedo Mask, I didn't
think he was our enemy,
but...
[gasp]
Luna, do you have any
idea who our enemies
might be?
Or where the princess is?
I've been doing a lot
of research. I have a
few hunches but I don't
know for sure.
If a certain evil being
should awaken and gain
the power of the Crystal,
it could mean the
end of the world.
Can the Legendary Silver
Crystal really destroy
the entire world?
It is that powerful.
Depending on how it's used,
it could blow up a whole
planet, easily.
[shocked gasp]
Is that really our mission
as Guardians? To find and
protect something so
potentially dangerous?
Yes.
I have told you about The
Legendary Silver Crystal and
the princess from the Moon.
I have faith in all of
you that you will find
them.
But you must do it soon.
They need your protection.
That is your fate.
It is your destiny.
Why you were made
Sailor Guardians.
And it's also why I came
here and awakened all of
you. I was sent here from
the Moon to do so.
The missing princess
we're searching for
is from the Moon?
Someone from the Moon
sent you here?
They sent you...
to awaken us?
Luna, you're from
the Moon?
You will all understand
more once you've awakened
fully. Right now I must
learn more about who
our main enemy is.
And I need to continue
my investigation of
Tuxedo Mask, as well.
The power to blow up a
whole planet? A royal
princess from the moon?
I don't believe it.
Huh? That looks like
the Moon Stick Luna
gave me.
Don't be afraid. You
can do it. You're
Sailor Moon.
[gasp]
Uh...
Did Sailor V really
just talk right now?
Or did I imagine it?
Usagi? Is something
wrong?
Oh! No, it's nothing.
But tell me, is Sailor
V a Guardian of
Justice, too?
Huh?
It's possible. She
could be a Sailor
Guardian like we are.
Or she could be
just a regular girl.
The papers used to run
stories on her all the
time. But lately I haven't
heard anything. It's
like she's dropped
out of sight.
Welcome! Today's program
will feature a new topic:
The Legendary Silver Crystal.
Educating us about this
mysterious treasure,
is today's guest,
Professor Izono.
Thank you. It's a
pleasure to be here.
The Legendary Silver
Crystal has both
amazing and terrifying
magical powers.
It can grant immortality
or cause massive destruction.
So we need everyone's help to
find it as soon as possible.
Everyone watching this
broadcast right now
must search for it!
[dazed sigh]
I'm home, Mom!
I can't find it.
It's not here. Or here.
Or here. I can't find
it anywhere. Where
could it be?
The Legendary
Silver Crystal...
Mom?!
Where is it?
What's wrong?
What's going on,
Mom? Answer me!
It's not here.
I can't find it.
It's likely hidden somewhere
very unusual. So check
everywhere! leave no
stone unturned!
Ami!
Ami, can you
hear me?
Yeah! Things are getting
really bad out here!
Where's the Legendary
Silver Crystal?!
What's happened
to everyone?
Something evil must
be controlling them!
Alright girls! Let's
meet up at the arcade!
Ah...
[gasps]
Ooh...
Luna, what is
this place?
No way!
A secret base!
Awesome!
I needed a place to
do research, investigate
our enemies.
Huh...
The evil energy is
concentrating in
one spot.
[gasp]
The TV station?
Luna, someone must be
using the broadcast signal
to transmit some sort of
mind control.
I underestimated him.
I never thought Tuxedo
Mask would do something
like this.
He isn't the
one doing this!
Huh?
Tuxedo Mask is always
coming to my rescue.
He isn't our enemy.
He's always there for
me. It's like he knows
me!
Usagi... It almost sounds
like you've fallen in
love with him.
Uh...
Think carefully, Usagi.
Are you sure about him?
He could just be using
you to get to the Crystal.
You're all wrong!
You don't understand!
Usagi...
Who are you, Tuxedo
Mask? And why do you
keep saving me all the
time? It's not true.
You're not my enemy.
You can't be!
These human beings
are pathetic.
None of them have been
able to find The Legendary
Silver Crystal.
They're of no
use to me!
[chuckling]
I'll take their energy
though, drain them of
every last drop.
Oh no you won't!
The Sailor Guardians.
I was expecting you.
Such evil energy.
Reveal yourself!
It's Zoisite!
Your plan didn't work!
We stopped the signal
in time!
Guardians! Let's
transform!
Mercury Power
Make Up!
Mars Power
Jupiter Power
Make Up!
[struggling breaths]
What's the matter with
me? I feel so weak and
dizzy.
[gasp]
Tuxedo Mask...
Are you all right?
So warm...
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I was too rash and
impulsive. This giant
mess is my fault.
You mean, it
was you?
I started it. But
this isn't my doing.
Please believe me.
I do believe you.
[chuckle]
The Silver Crystal,
I must find it. I
need to.
But, I didn't have any
information.
And I don't have special
powers to help me.
I know how you feel.
Even though I'm the
leader, I don't feel
like it. I'm powerless.
It's my job to protect
everyone but I can't.
I guess all we can
do is try harder.
Oh no...
[grunting]
Hah!
Surrender. Now!
You stole people's
energy! How dare you!
Give it back or pay!
Don't underestimate me.
[gasp]
[screaming]
[evil laughter]
This is the most evil
aura I have ever felt.
Is that...
Our enemy?
[gasp]
Sailor Guardians...
My name is Queen Beryl. I
command the Four Kings of
the Dark Kingdom. And I
have sent them to obtain
the Legendary Silver Crystal.
Once I secure it, the
Dark Kingdom will rise
again.
Then every human being
on Earth, shall perish.
[struggling breaths]
I can't move!
She's too strong!
We're no match for
her incredible power.
We need you, Sailor
Moon! Help us!
Come on, Usagi.
Where are you?
I've gotta transform.
The others need me!
But I can't change into
Sailor Moon in front of
Tuxedo Mask.
[gasp]
Well, Sailor Moon, what
are you waiting for?
Hurry! Transform!
You knew then, all this
time, that I was Sailor
Moon?
Only you can save them.
You're their last hope.
But how? I can't summon
mist or fire or lightning
like the others can.
I'm just a big crybaby.
And without Luna
I'm totally useless!
[gasp]
Your power is very
special. You open
people's hearts.
You saw the other Guardians
for who they really were and
brought out the best in them.
You made them smile.
In my book, that makes
you the best one to
lead them. So...
He took my hand again.
I feel stronger like I
did before. Like I can
do anything!
Usagi!
There's no time
to waste!
Moon Prism Power
Make Up!
I am the Pretty
Guardian, who fights
for love and for justice!
I am Sailor Moon!
And now in the name
of the Moon, I'll
punish you!
Sailor Moon!
Sailor Moon, you're too
late. Kneel before my
awesome power.
I am not going
to give up...
I may be a crybaby...
and a bit of a klutz
too...
Don't be afraid. You can
do it, you're Sailor Moon.
But I am Sailor Moon. I
am the leader! So, please
Moon Stick, help me save them!
What?
Sailor Moon, do it!
Moon Healing
Escalation!
[screaming]
The evil aura
is weakening...
She did it! Usagi
saved us all!
Mark my words, you
will pay for this.
Usagi...
[exhausted breaths]
Sailor Moon...
[chuckle]
You completely wore
yourself out. But
you did it. Thank you.
I feel so safe and warm
in his arms. Some of my
strength is already returning.
I think I've been carried
like this before... This
embrace feels so familiar.
That dream I've been
having... It's always the
same. A man's voice calling
out to me. But whose
voice is it?
And where, am I?
A pocket watch that
shows the phases of the
moon, but it's broken.
I wonder whose it is.
Could it belong
to Tuxedo Mask?
You're finally awake.
[gasp]
Is that you?
Tuxedo Mask...
I was in a car accident
on my sixth birthday. My
parents died and I lost
all of my memories.
I don't even know
who I really am.
That's awful.
I have a recurring dream
where someone implores me
to find the Legendary
Silver Crystal."That's
my only clue.
Is that all you
want? To regain
your memories?
No, my true wish is...
Act. 7 Mamoru Chiba,
Tuxedo Mask.
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.