Her heart is
no longer beating.
She's gone.
It's not true...
she can't be...
[stunned groan]
(USAGI TSUKINO) Chibi‐Usa...
[sobbing] Chibi‐Usa!
(HARUKA TENOH) Her soul's been
taken.
Huh?
Haruka...
[gasp]
You mean Hotaru, or rather
Sailor Saturn...
...she killed her?
That wasn't Sailor
Saturn. She hasn't
awakened, yet.
If she had, the three
Talismans would have
activated. But so far,
they have not.
There is a way to
save Chibi‐Usa, but...
[gasp]
How? What way?
How can we
save her?
We must kill Hotaru.
[gasp]
(TENOH) That girl...
...she isn't
Hotaru anymore.
She has become their vessel.
She's an enemy now.
Chibi‐Usa's soul and the
Legendary Silver Crystal are now
in her hands.
To save Chibi‐Usa we must get
them back and that means
destroying our enemy.
Destroying?
There must be
some other way.
Sailor Saturn may not be
awake yet, but, if we don't
act, the Earth will be
destroyed.
So the three of us are going,
...not only for
Chib‐Usa, but to save
all of human kind.
[stunned breath]
Usagi?
[emotional grunt]
She's right... I know she is. We
have to save the planet.
But still...
[sigh]
Her little body
is getting so
cold...
[holding back tears]
Her heart's stopped,
and her blood's not
circulating.
Even if we retrieve her
soul, we won't be able to
revive her, not if we leave
her here.
What do you
mean?
Her body is dying. If we don't
get Chibi‐Usa's soul back fast,
she could be gone forever.
[shocked gasps]
[stunned breath]
Act.34 Infinity 8 "Infinite
Labyrinth" 1
(MAMORU CHIBA) I'm going to link
my body with Chibi‐Usa's.
That way...
Instead of machines, I'll
be her life support. And my
body can keep hers alive.
that[s pobutbi angn ]in
credible
strain on your body?
I'll be fine.
Right now, Chibi‐Usa
and I are one.
Hey, you guys, could you please
give us a moment alone?
Mhm...
Chibi‐Usa's life,
Hotaru's... or everyone
on Earth...
How can I possibly choose?
[sigh]
I can feel your heart beating
through her, Mamo. It's as if
Chibi‐Usa's alive and still with
us.
[crying and sniffling]
What should I
do?
How can I...?
(MAMORU) Usa.
Huh?
[gasps]
(MAMORU) Her soul and the
Legendary Silver Crystal...
[gasp]
You have to
get them back.
Focus on that,
Usa.
Right now that's
all you can do.
You must go.
Don't lose hope.
[agreed sigh]
[reassuring sigh]
That vision...
Was that the Messiah?... or
the God of Destruction?
Such a small, inconvenient
vessel..
So uncomfortable...
Hm?
[gasp] Mistress 9!
We have been
awaiting your arrival
for some time...
[satisfied sigh] You're finally
here. It's been so long since
the day I implanted your egg
into my daughter, Hotaru.
But it remained
undifferentiated, so I thought
you might never wake up.
So that's it...
[gasp] Huh?
Why did she have to awaken now?
(MISTRESS 9) Kaolinite.
[gasp]
Thank you for your loyal
service. You've worked very
hard.
However, since I am Master
Pharaoh 90's partner from our
old world, I shall now be taking
over his care.
[angry grunt]
(MISTRESS 9) You have other
things to attend to. Our master
gave you an important mission.
And I need you to carry it out
immediately.
Eliminate the anomalies!
Failure is not an option.
Of course. I understand.
If she thinks I'm going to back
down that easily, she's got
another thing coming!
(MASTER PHARAOH 90) Ah...
Mistress 9. I've been eagerly
awaiting you.
I have something for you
Master.
Take it.
Mmmm... what is this power?
I have never
seen such a
Host!
Actually, sir, this isn't a
Host. It is the light of one who
is protected by a Guardian
Planet.
It is a source of great power!
The Legendary Silver Crystal!
Such a mysterious light...
almost as if something resides
within. A sacred glow that is
strong, yet soothing.
(HOTARU TOMOE) Of course it is!
[gasp]
That crystal is protected by a
pure soul, the beautiful soul of
a girl.
Who said that?!
[regaining composure]
I'm hearing things.
[waking up]
"PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE"
Hear me, O loyal minions, my
Witches 5...
I command you to rise from the
dead, and curse the anomalies!
Bind them with your spells for
eternity!
[snickering]
[gasp]
Guys...
Are you ready?
We're all going
to get Chibi‐Usa's
soul back.
The only thing
we can do now
is to keep
moving forward.
[agreed sigh] Let's go... to
Mugenzu!
(MINAKO AINO) When did Mugen
Academy turn into that?!
There's a massive
evil aura here.
Abnormal power is covering this
place like a dome...
Or rather, in the shape of the
letter Omega.
Let's go!
Mhm!
[running exertion]
Huh?
Uranus, Neptune, Pluto...
Will our hearts never be able to
unite and become one?
Hm? Sailor Moon?
[gasp]
[heavy breathing]
(HARUKA TENOH) I'm sorry, Sailor
Moon.
But Neptune, Pluto, and
I are going into that school
to kill Hotaru...
There's no other way...
[gritting teeth]
[grunts]
[chuckling] Finally.
The Sailor Guardians are here.
We've been expecting you.
[gasp]
Enjoy your stay at the Infinate
Labyrinth.
[groans]
[screams]
[gasp]
Your manners are
the worst I've
ever seen.
As Mugen Academy's
prefect of etiquette,
I, Yuko Arimura,
shall have to
discipline you.
Eudial!
[charging]
[gasp]
[kicking grunt]
[pained yelp]
[pained grunt]
[gasp]
I don't really think you
wanna keep on having all
these battles.
What?
(EUDIAL) Y ou lack a fighting
spirit. I can tell.
What if I told you
that you didn't have
to fight for Sailor Moon
ever again?
Wouldn't it be much better if
you were learning etiquette,
martial arts, or forune telling
instead?
[gasp]
[heavy breathing]
I'm lost. Where'd everybody go?
[gasp] Huh?
Woah!
I think I saw this in a book
once.
It's the world's most
advanced super computer with an
artifical life program that
can evolve on its own.
Hello, there.
Viluy?!
Oh, no, I'm Yui Bido.
Prefect of Mugen Academy's
Science Class.
I'm so glad to finally
be able to show you
the true essence of our
school.
[attack yell]
[pained yell]
[scream]
How many days
have you spent wasting
your precious time?
How often did you
have to squander your
abilities fighting for Sailor
Moon?
Wouldn't you prefer to be
studying more?
Yes...
It's true. I do have to study
more. Otherwise, I won't be able
to get in to medical school.
What happened to everyone?
[scared breath] Where did they
all go?
[groan] My head is splitting.
[pained groans]
Hey guys, I, Mimi Hanyu, would
like to welcome a very special
guest to our stage...
Sailor Venus!
Venus! Venus! Venus!
[confused gasp]
(MIMETE) What's wrong?
Huh?
What are you
waiting for? Go
ahead and sing.
It's always been your dream to
become a teen idol, right?
It's true... being a teen idol
is what I've always wanted.
I should quit being a Sailor
Guardian... It's so stupid.
[gasp]
Where am I?
Welcome to Mugen
Botaical Garden.
What? Tellu?
[giggle]
Let's not fight
today.
Huh?
Look!
[gazing]
So many roses. [giggle]
La France roses! The first breed
of hybrid tea rose!
[gasp] And here are some Soleil
d'Or!
[chuckle] And these are the
finest Kosai roses I've ever
seen! [happy sighs]
[happily sniffing]
I don't wanna fight anymore. I'd
rather stay here.
My dream is to be in a rose
garden like this...
With someone that I love...
forever and ever...
[giggle]
[gasp]
Where am I?
Where is everyone?
Mercury! Mars! Jupiter! Venus!
Look what you've
done to us. We're
all falling apart.
[gasp]
(MAKOTO KINO) We're sick and
tired.
We don't wanna
fight for you.
[gasp]
[whimpering and scared
breathing]
[grunt and gasp]
[choking]
It's all your fault, Sailor
Moon!
[strangled] I can't breathe.
[struggling]
[giggling]
[coughing and struggling for
air]
(HARUKA TENOH) Need a hand,
Chibi‐Usa?
Let us help.
I always found
Sailor Moon... very
annoying.
[giggle]
[gasp] Uranus! Neptune! Pluto!
I can get rid
of them all.
[gasp]
Chibi‐Usa, Hotaru...
And you, Usa...
I'll kill you, too!
[scared gasp]
[gasp] Usa!
[grunt] Don't be deceived!
[determined grunt]
Neo Queen Serenity!
Lend your power to my Heart Moon
Rod!
Moon Spiral Heart Attack!
[sigh of relief]
Gotta hurry! [running exertion]
[attacking grunts]
[grunt] What the hell are these
things?!
No matter how
much we cut
them, they still
attack.
I've got a bad feeling... Be
safe, Sailor Mooon!
Uranus! Pluto!
[gasp]
[shocked gasp]
Look!
[gasp] Oh no!
[gasp]
Guys!
[snikering]
[gasp]
[swinging effort]
Sailor Moon is in danger!
Then, we'll force our way
through!
Space Sword Blaster!
[attacking yell]
[gasp]
[snickering]
[grunt]
[bracing]
[attacking yell]
[groans and screaming]
[snickering]
Submarine...
...Reflection!
[screams]
[grunt and catching breath]
Chronos Tyohone.
[cathing breath]
(HARUKA TENOH) Sailor Moon!
[gasp]
Neptune! Pluto! Uranus!
Sailor Moon, are
you okay?
[deep breath] I knew you would
come and help us.
Mhm.
(SETSUNA MEIOH) Is everyone
okay?
Pluto. Neptune.
You're here!
You came just
to save us?
Yes...
We are all
Sailor Guardians.
Thank you.
[pleased sigh]
I knew it... I kept on
believing...
... that deep down in our
souls... all of us felt the
same.
Stay out of it!
We must kill Hotaru.
[scared gasp]
(MICHIRU KAIOH) Which is why we
cannot be friends.
Sailor Moon is in danger!
Then we'll force our way
through!
We would never abandon you.
How could we? We always wanted
to fight by your side.
(CHIBA) That's it.
Join forces and
fight together.
The greater your power becomes,
the closer you are to making the
impossible possible.
[gasp]
Huh?
[chuckle]
[gasp]
Mhm.
[happy sigh]
We are the Sailor Guardians. If
we unite as one, we can create
any power!
Moon Chalice, come into my
grasp!
And gather! The scared power of
the Holy Sailor Guardians!
Moon Crisis Make Up!
"PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE"
"60TH FLOOR"
Upstairs.
[agreed grunts]
Let's go!
This ends now!
[groan] So you managed
to undo my greatest
spell as Magus
Kaolinite?
Well that's the last time! No
more interference!
[roaring]
[gasp] A daimon?!
[dodging grunts]
I don't think so!
Jupiter Coconut Cyclone!
Venus...
Wink Chain Sword!
[roars and screams]
Mercury Aqua Mirage!
Mars... Snake Fire!
[screaming]
{woozy growls and roar]
[gasps]
Take this!
[groans and grunts]
Hurry! Finish her! Now, Sailor
Moon!
We are going to save this
planet!
I won't let it suffer the
nightmare of destruction!
Rainbow... Moon... Heartche!
[growl]
[screaming]
No matter what sort of labyrinth
I may wander into... I swear...
... I will never lose hope!
Come on guys, let's hurry.
Let's find Hotaru!
[MISTRESS 9] So... Super Sailor
Moon even managed to defeat
Magus Kaolinite.
No matter. The time has come to
make this Omega Area into our
sacred land.
And, so long as we have the
Legendary Silver Crystal...
...no one can stop us. We've got
nothing to fear.
[licking lips]
(USAGI TSUKINO) No more
hesitating! I'm going to save
Chibi‐Usa and Hotaru, no matter
what!
Next time, "Act.35 Infinity 9
'Infinate Labyrinth' 2"
The moonlight is a messanger of
love.