You thought you were
wandering aimlessly, but you
were searching for me
without realizing it.
Someone who wants you.
Someone who needs you.
Come... Come with me...
Her key...
[gasp]
What could cause a storm
here?
Something has disrupted the
natural flow of Space-Time.
And Small Lady is
at the heart of it!
I sense great
danger!
[grunt]
King... Endymion!
What an incredible library!
I can't believe they have
digital records of all
recorded history here!
[gasp]
King!
I need to see Pluto
immediately!
Something's wrong. I think
it's Chibi-Usa.
Hang on! Wait for me!
No, you stay here! We'll be
right back!
[grunt]
What gives?! Why does
everyone keep leaving me
behind?! It's driving me
crazy!
Venus, look!
I think we found the right
case file.
You'll definitely want to
see this.
"Death Phantom."
"Considered one of history's
worst criminals, he
possessed the superhuman
abilities of "Evil Sight"
and "Beast Hands."
It also says he
single-handedly destroyed
the previous Crystal Tokyo
and turned it into a city
overrun with crime.
But despite his powers,
Death Phantom was human.
Thus the queen could
not bring herself
to execute him.
Instead, she exiled him to
Nemesis.
That dark world seems to
be involved with quite a
few unfortunate events.
Both past and present.
I'm certain none of this
would be happening, if not
for Nemesis. No one
should've gone near that
planet. Death Phantom has
cursed it.
[panting]
Are you alright, Pluto? This
storm... What's going on?
Small Lady... She went deep
into Space-Time without a
key and vanished.
Chibi-Usa's gone?
She may be caught in this
storm. It started in the
same area where I felt her
disappear.
Something terrible must
have happened to cause
such a disturbance.
Mm.
Something powerful enough to
tear the very fabric of
Space-Time.
Chibi-Usa's out in this
storm all alone.
I'm going after her!
Tuxedo Mask, wait!
Come back! Don't go that way
without a key! You'll never
be able to return!
I wonder how long I've been
here for.
This Black Moon Castle is
like a labyrinth. No
matter how far I walk, it
seems like I'm just going
around and around in
circles.
But I know they're here. I
felt them. I'm sure of it!
My friends...! Where are
you?
Mars, Mercury, Jupiter...
It's hard to breathe.
It's like all the energy
is being drained out of me.
[gasp]
I hear our Guardian
prisoners are still present
and accounted for.
Yes, but they were just
bait for Sailor Moon and
now my brother has
what he wanted.
We should get
rid of them.
They are just wasting away
in the Dark Chamber.
Why prolong the
inevitable?
I knew they were alive!
Where is this "Dark Chamber"?
Because none of us
want to go anywhere
near the Dark Chamber,
that's why.
Yes. It's hostile
territory.
Some strange
stuff down there.
Hidden dangers seem to be
lurking around every turn here.
Lately it feels like this
whole place has a mind of
its own and we're all
at its mercy.
Maybe the lot of us are
cannon fodder and the
planet's the one in command.
[fainting]
Uh--
Stay back! Don't touch me!
[grunt]
What have you done with my
friends? Tell me where the
Dark Chamber is!
None of that matters. Your
friends are all dead.
I don't believe you!
They're alive and I will
find them!
Hold it together, Usagi.
You can't die here.
Not now! Not yet!
Not without seeing
Mamo again!
Fabricating Droids this
advanced is quite complex
and requires considerable
amounts of energy.
But it's worth it.
How may we
serve you?
Droids will always stick to
their plan. You give them
their instructions and they
follow them, without question.
[panting]
What is that?
Please, come in, future
Neo Queen Serenity.
It is an honor to
greet the beautiful
ruler of Crystal
Tokyo.
I am Prince Dimande's
brother, Saphir.
This chamber is the core of
Nemesis: the Malefic Black
Crystal reactor.
A reactor?
This planet is sealed off.
The reactor is the only
opening to the outside. You
and your friends came
through it to get here.
Take a moment to admire the
Malefic Black Crystal's power.
Beautiful, yet dangerous. It
could melt down or explode
at any second, but without
it we would never be able to
execute our grand plan.
The plan to rewrite Earth's
history!
My brother doesn't know how
unstable it is. Nor does he
understand the full extent
of the danger.
We forcibly accelerated the
core's fusion reactions
without fully comprehending
how they worked. If the
whole system collapses and
the planet goes out of
control, I won't be
surprised.
In a way, Nemesis is much
like my brother.
He too is dangerous and
unstable.
He often acts on impulse and
allows his emotions to
distract him.
For example, attacking the
Earth with the Malefic
Black Crystal was a rash
decision and not part
of our original
plan.
Your Majesty, I beg your
forgiveness.
[gasp]
We were disillusioned and
naive. When Wiseman
appeared, with his omens and
prophecies, he told us
exactly what we wanted to
hear.
None of us should have ever
set foot on this cursed
planet. But we followed him,
blindly.
The Malefic Black Crystal is
a type of invincible stone
that takes in light and
energy, and converts them to
negative energy. It can
even warp time and space.
So with this stone, all that
I have ever wanted will
finally be within reach.
Yes. You can have
everything. The entire
universe is yours for the
taking.
Only one thing stands in
your way...
The Legendary Silver
Crystal... which belongs to
the Earth's queen...
Her crystal is the only
stone whose power rivals
the Malefic Black
Crystal.
It is a threat to us! As
long as it exists, we cannot
obtain unbeatable power.
Destroy it! Eradicate it
from the universe!
The "Legendary Silver
Crystal"...
I've always wondered.
But I have yet to see
its power for myself.
Perhaps if we were to attack
our former home with the
Malefic Black Crystal, the
queen would show us.
[gasp]
My poor brother...
The Malefic Black Crystal
has ahold of him. He's
possessed. And he doesn't
even realize it. [grunt]
[gasp]
I doubt that anything can
stop him now. He's gone mad.
It's too dangerous.
But for the sake of the
future, for the Earth, for
all of us, for
everything...!
Someone has to try. Would
you be willing to help me?
You want my help? What do
you mean? What could I do?
[scream]
You could stop living.
Perhaps then my brother
would realize Sailor Moon
isn't so special.
[gasp]
My brother and I, we had it
all worked out. We were
going to stop the Moon
Kingdom from ruling the Earth.
The Black Moon was
supposed to go to the
past and rewrite
history.
That was the plan.
But then you came along
and ruined everything!
He lost his mind and it's
all your fault!
That's not true.
Vile Witch! You and that
Legendary Silver Crystal of
yours wrecked human history!
But I can fix it. Right
here. Right now.
With your death!
Is he right? Is it
all my fault?
Did I somehow
cause this?
Am I the one... who
destroyed the future?
What is this light? Why
can't I strike her?
[grunt]
Usako!
What incredible light! It's
strong enough to penetrate
even the furthest reaches of
space-time!
You are correct, Wiseman.
What you are seeing is the
light of the Legendary
Silver Crystal. It's true
power; which has been
concealed within that woman
all this time.
If you're going to drop by
Nemesis for a closer look,
I'll go with you.
[gasp]
Are you who I think you are?
Mm.
[grunt]
[scream]
The light! Its power!
Don't accuse me of trying to
wreck history! You and the
Black Moon are the ones
doing that!
Well no more. You will not
manipulate time any longer!
[scream]
I don't believe it!
I'm overflowing with power
like never before!
If I try it now, I'm sure I
can transform!
Moon Crystal Power...
Make up!
Mm!
[grunt]
She transformed.
The power of the Malefic
Black Crystal is supposed to
nullify all other
energies!
[gasp] I feel them!
Where are my friends? Show
them to me.
There they are!
Mars,
Mercury,
Jupiter!
I found you! Now time to
wake up!
[gasp]
Sailor Moon...
I can feel her power.
She's close by!
But we're stuck here.
How do we reach her?
If you can hear us, Sailor
Moon, tell us what to do.
Transform! You can
do it now!
Come on! I'll give you a
hand!
Mars Star Power!
Mercury Star Power!
Jupiter Star Power!
Make up!
Mm!
Mars, Mercury, Jupiter!
Sailor Moon!
Impossible.
Yes. And yet somehow there
they all are.
It's the power of the
Legendary Silver Crystal.
That power is indeed
exceptional, just as he
said. Wiseman!
Right here, my prince.
[chuckling]
What is that black
shadow behind him?
[chuckle] Now you have all
witnessed the remarkable
power of the Legendary
Silver Crystal.
A stone that can
unleash such powers across
the reaches of time
and space, and overcome
the negative energy of the
Malefic Black Crystal as
though it were nothing.
Truly a sight to behold!
What fearsome power it
possesses. I see why men
would wage war over it,
why it wrecks havoc
and causes disasters.
Open your eyes, Dimande!
[gasp]
You're wrong!
The Legendary Silver
Crystal protects peace!
Its true purpose is to bring
harmony and love!
If not for the misguided
and evil actions of
men like you, war itself
might never have existed!
All could have lived in
peace! But for you, peace
wasn't enough!
Are you so blinded by hate?
Can't you see?
The Malefic Black
Crystal is dangerous
and you are
misusing it!
Sailor Moon?
No, Ami. I don't
think that's her.
That's Neo Queen Serenity!
Neo Queen Serenity... I see
far better than you think.
"Peace" and "harmony" are
illusions. Fear and
malice are the Silver
Crystal's true Legacy! As
long as mankind
desires it,
that stone is the
root of all evil!
Exactly, my Prince. You see
the Legendary Silver Crystal
for what it really is.
Now take it! And crush them
all!
Uh!
Do it, my Prince.
[chuckle]
With my friends by my side,
nothing can defeat me!
And you're not getting the
Legendary Silver
Crystal! Not now!
Not ever!
[grunt]
Burning... Mandala!
Shine Snow Illusion!
Sparkling... Wide Pressure!
Wait Brother!
Prince Dimande! Time to show
them your Evil Sight!
I'm stuck! I can't move a
muscle!
Hurry, my Prince! Kill them
all! And take the Legendary
Silver Crystal from Sailor
Moon's dead body!
[gasp]
The reactor!
[grunt]
The power of the Legendary
Silver Crystal this close to
the reactor is causing it to
melt down!
I'm not about to stick
around and die here!
Going somewhere?
I see through your
camouflage.
You can't fool me!
I know you've got another
mission on the side,
so fess up!
Who are you, Wiseman?! And
what do you really want?!
[giggle] Such a coward.
Who?
You. Who else?
[struggling]
Bye bye...
Who are you? [scream]
Pathetic dreg!
[grunt]
Now's our chance! We need to
get out of here, quick!
[gasp]
Sailor Moon.
But how?
We're trapped,
there's no way out.
Pluto! Please lend us your
power.
If we all use our power
together, that should be
enough to get us back to
Earth!
The power of Neo Queen
Serenity...
Pluto!
Please help us get back
home to Earth!
You're not getting away from
me!
Brother! Hurry, we have to
go!
To think you could just slip
through my fingers like
that... Sailor Moon, your
power is truly awesome!
However...
You'll be back soon enough,
along with the Legendary
Silver Crystal. Of that, I'm
quite certain.
[chuckle]
Chibi-Usa! Where are you?
Usako... I need you.
Lend me your strength.
Help me find Chibi-Usa!
[giggle]
Mm!
[giggle] Over here.
This way!
[gasp]
Come on... You're getting
warmer. I'm right over here.
Usako? Chibi-Usa?
[giggle]
[chuckle]
[gasp]
You're back!
Jupiter, Mercury, Mars,
Sailor Moon!
I never lost hope! I knew
we'd be together again!
Thanks for staying strong!
Hope you weren't too
worried!
It's good to see you!
How did you escape?
Neo Queen Serenity. She
shared some of her amazing
power with us! That's how we
were able to transform and
get back here!
Yes. But it wasn't just her.
Mm.
[gasp]
Your own power helped too,
Sailor Moon.
You called on your inner
strength. You summoned the
Silver Crystal's power
through space-time.
Well done. You should be
proud of yourself.
Mm.
[gasp]
Tuxedo Mask and Chibi-Usa!
Where are they?
We do not know.
Small Lady wandered deep
into space-time and went
missing. We believe
that is what's
causing this
unusual storm.
Tuxedo Mask rushed into the
tempest after her and neither
of them has a key to return.
[gasp] What?!
My name is Black Lady, Queen
of Darkness.
Wiseman, the Ruler of
Darkness, chose me! And I
have been reborn as the
queen of Nemesis!
I'm not a little girl
anymore. I'm all grown up.
[laughs]
Act 23: Covert Maneuvers
Wiseman
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.