Who is that?
A crescent mark on
her forehead...
Is it possible
that she's-?
The legendary
Guardian of
Justice...
Sailor V?
There is a fifth Sailor
Guardian now? That
can't be.
Sailor V?
I don't believe it.
What is she doing
here?
Is she really the same
Sailor V from the news
and video game?
Her costume seems different.
I am.
I assure you it's me.
I've just never taken
off the mask in public
before.
Sailor V's red mask?!
So you really are her!
How rude! Show
some respect!
While it is true she
is Sailor V, there is
more...
My mistress is of the
Moon Kingdom, Silver
Millennium.
She is heiress
to the sacred
Legendary Silver Crystal!
She is Princess Serenity!
[gasp]
Sailor V is the
princess? I
knew it!
And that crescent moon
mark on her forehead.
I was right! It must be the
symbol of Princess Serenity!
What's going on? My
forehead feels hot.
My tiara! It
changed shape!
[gasp]
That was strange. For
a second there it felt
like I was on the verge
of remembering something
important.
Damn it! This time
I was so close!
Princess Serenity?
Tuxedo Mask!
That man...
Princess Serenity...
That name... It sounds
so familiar.
Tuxedo Mask!
Usako...
I wasn't strong enough.
I couldn't protect her.
Ohh...
You've done a pretty
good job so far, Sailor
Moon, I'm proud of you.
Sailor V, my hero, is
standing right here in
front of me?!
And she's the princess?!
I don't believe it!
I'm proud of you all.
[stunned gasp]
This may sound odd but
I feel like I already
know all of you.
Because I've been
watching you for so
long through the game.
Huh?
We've been using the Sailor
V game as a combat simulator
to teach you how to fight.
Looks like it
worked.
You were watching us?
What are you waiting
for, Sailor Moon?
Hurry!
Oh wow! So it was you
talking to me through
that video game!
I thought I was
going crazy!
[giggle]
Usagi? Are you
all okay?!
That you, Luna? Are
you at the command
center?
I'll see you soon.
Huh?
So you're really
just a girl?
This is kind
of my disguise.
Down here on
Earth, I'm Minako
Aino.
And I'm a middle
school student,
like you.
Please accept my apologies,
Princess. I should've been
there to greet you.
There's no need to
apologize, Luna. You
needed to be here.
You were just
doing your job.
Ah, the Command Center.
It's been a long time.
Sailor V... I mean,
Princess, we were
searching everywhere
for you.
Where have
you been?
I guess I have some
explaining to do.
I met my partner Artemis
long before you met Luna.
Back then we had no idea
any of you existed.
It was just the two of us.
I went by the codename:
Sailor V. And together, we
set out to solve the rash
of mysterious crimes that
seemed to be plaguing Tokyo.
Eventually we noticed
a pattern. The crimes
were all connected but
there was something more...
Behind every unusual
case we encountered,
was a large, s
sinister shadow...
The Dark Kingdom.
The kingdom is ruled, or
rather controlled, by a
terrible creature
born from the darkness.
A being made out of
pure evil, unlike
anything else.
In its lust for power, this
diabolical thing has become
determined to possess the
Moon Kingdom's sacred
stone, the Legendary
Silver Crystal.
It will stop at nothing.
It has plans to conquer
the Earth!
Right now, human energy
is the power it's been
surviving on.
That's why the attacks
involve so many people.
Have you actually
encountered this
creature?
Yes, a long
time ago.
It was responsible for the
destruction of the Moon
Kingdom, Silver Millennium.
It robbed everyone
of their happiness!
In the end, we managed to
seal it away.
But someone broke the seal
and now it's free again.
Do you understand?
This time we have to
seal it away permanently.
We can't let history
repeat itself.
We must stop this
thing once and for all.
I understand. That's why we
were made Sailor Guardians.
To ensure that doesn't
happen again!
Tell us, Princess.
Do you know where the
Legendary SilverCrystal is?
I do, but for your own
safety, I can't share
that information just yet.
The enemy will come after
us again for sure. It's
better if you don't know.
Whatever you say,
Sailor V...
Uh, I mean, Princess...
Don't worry you
can count on us!
The four of us are with
you. We're here to support
your endeavor.
No matter how strong this
enemy is or may become,
we'll face it head on!
We're not afraid!
As Sailor Guardians,
we'll fight for you
till the end!
Hmm...
Princess?
Yes. Thank you,
everyone.
Goodnight Princess!
See you soon!
[giggling]
Time is running out.
Soon they'll remember
everything.
I must hurry. This all
needs to be settled as
soon as possible.
Minako, you've been
fighting for so long,
all by yourself.
Please, stop!
Let them help you!
Artemis. I can't.
You know that.
I have a mission.
A very important
mission...
...that only I
can carry out.
[battling yells]
Get him!
Endymion!
Princess Serenity!
[gasp]
It was just a dream...
I guess I probably dreamed
that because I actually
met the Princess
the other day...
Princess Serenity!
"Serenity." That was the
name he called out. Was he
talking to me? Who is he?
I've seen him in my dreams
before. But I called him
"Endymion," this time.
What does it all mean?
Sailor V... I guess she's
the princess, but I feel
like she's still hiding
something from us.
Something important.
Mamo. Hi.
[uneasy laugh]
Good morning.
Hi.
It became an
obsession.
I needed to find the
Silver Crystal. It was
the only clue I had
to my lost memories.
The Legendary Silver
Crystal... the princess
said she knew where it
was but couldn't tell us.
I don't know. I'm not
sure what's real anymore.
I'm sorry, Usako.
Huh?
I wasn't able
to protect you.
I'm ashamed to look
you in the eye,
but I guess I was
destined to bump into
you again.
So why fight it?
[gasp]
Yeah. Must
be fate.
Hey! I just remembered!
This pocket watch, it's
yours right?
I meant to give it
back to you, but
I forgot.
No. You keep it.
In fact...
I have something of yours
that I've been holding
onto as well.
Huh? You have something of
mine? What on earth could
that be?
I didn't leave
anything with you.
Well then maybe I'll
let you have it next
time. Sound good?
[gasp]
Yeah. Next
time then.
When did she start looking
at him that way? Mamoru
Chiba, Tuxedo Mask...
So much I still don't know.
Is it okay for her to
fall in love with him?
Don't fret, Luna.
Artemis.
What is your
primary mission?
To find the Sailor
Guardians and train them?
There's more to
it than that.
Before the Moon Kingdom
fell, you had a place
in the royal household.
You used to look
after the Princess.
What are you
talking about?
You don't remember
do you?
To reduce the burden you
had to bear, part of your
memory was sealed
and kept from you.
But now, it's time for
you to know the truth.
All of it.
Huh?
Oh? The princess of
the Moon Kingdom,
you say?
Yes, O great
Queen Metalia.
She thought her mother had
defeated me, thought I was
sealed away forever. No doubt
she's reappeared to try
to rebuild her lost
kingdom.
This reborn princess...
I believe she has memories
of her past life.
She could know the location
of the Silver Crystal.
I agree. Lure her out and
force her to reveal it. I
want that Crystal immediately.
This time I will
be victorious.
And I will reign over
this world once more!
My Queen.
Queen Beryl, it would
seem the time has come.
Allow me, Kunzite, the
strongest of your four
commanders to be of
service to you now.
Do not let me down.
[sigh]
When did it get
so late?
Hello Sailor V...
or should I say
Princess?
I know that voice!
It's Kunzite!
Bring the Legendary Silver
Crystal to the top of
Tokyo Tower in thirty minutes.
Come alone. Or everyone
in this entire city
will perish.
[gasp]
It must be a trap.
You should call the
others, Minako!
No, Artemis. This fight
is for me alone.
I will face Kunzite
by myself!
Minako!
Hey Princess!
You're here! What
perfect timing!
Timing for what?
What's going on?
We were on our
way to come get
you.
I thought I'd cook
dinner at my place
tonight.
We were just going to
ask you to join us.
I wish I could. But I've
got some errands that I
need to run. Sorry!
Wait!
But Princess...
Tick Tock, my dear
Moon Princess. Time's
almost up.
What's going on? Is
this a blackout?
Can you all
hear me?!
The electricity just went
out all over Tokyo, and
it wasn't an accident!
[gasps]
What's going on?
It's like the energy
went out of them too.
Mamo!
Endymion!
[gasp]
A dream? No...
Someone was calling
out to me.
A blackout? Wait...
It's more than that.
You got what you wanted,
Kunzite! I'm here!
What kept you, Princess?
You're late.
Show me the Legendary
Silver Crystal.
I don't have it and I
won't give it to you!
Now turn the city's
power back on!
We could have done
this the easy way...
But I guess you
prefer the hard
way!
Crescent Boomerang!
[gasp]
[roaring]
[screaming]
You can't protect
anything, Princess.
Not your Silver Millennium
or planet Earth.
Listen to me, Kunzite!
Please don't do this!
Remember who
you really are!
Why are you hesitating,
Kunzite? She's the Moon
Princess. Destroy her!
Hmph! If you won't give
me the crystal, then you
can die!
Not so fast!
You're here!
Stop Kunzite!
How dare you steal our
light, and force our
princess to fight
you, that's awful!
So in the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
Don't! Please! This
is my fight!
No, Princess...
We got this.
We won't let you fight
all alone. We're your
Sailor Guardians.
We're here to help you.
[gasp]
We were each alone
in the beginning,
just like you.
Then we met Usagi and
became a team, but
it's more than that.
We became friends too.
When the going gets tough,
we support one another.
Because that's what
friends are for.
Thank you...
Enough with the
sentiment, it's
time to die!
Mercury Aqua Mist!
Evil Spirit,
be gone!
Supreme Thunder!
Crescent Boomerang!
Those attacks aren't
strong enough to work
on me!
Now, Sailor Moon!
Hit him!
What?!
Moon Healing
Escalation!
[gasp]
That didn't work.
[growling]
[screaming]
Sailor Moon!
[grunting]
Princess!
[screaming]
[gasps]
[gasp]
Tuxedo Mask!
I don't believe it! He's
here! He came to save
me again!
It's too dangerous here.
You have to get away from
this place.
I'll be fine. Leave
the rest to me.
Sailor Moon...
I've never seen you this
strong and confident.
You've more beautiful
than ever.
Every time we meet, I
learn something new
about you.
But I have so much more
yet to discover.
What kind of girl
are you really?
I want to know
everything. Who
are you?
Sailor Moon...
Time to finish off
the rest of you!
[gasp]
Sailor Moon!
Don't do it!
[roaring]
[gasp]
Usako! I will
protect you!
And this time,
I won't fail!
Ah!
[grunting]
Tuxedo Mask!
At last, it's time for
all to be revealed.
It's all coming back.
We used to be...
Guardians: sworn to
protect our Moon
Princess.
Now we've been reincarnated
so that the Moon Kingdom
might live again!
That's right. And the
real princess is...
I remember everything
now... my beloved...
Endymion.
Act. 9 Serenity Princess
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.