Hmph.
The prince already
has the other two.
This is just needlessly cruel.
[gasp]
Jupiter!
That's impossible!
What happened?
I had a lock on her
and she vanished!
[gasp]
What's going on?
Where's Jupiter?
They took her!
[crying]
We couldn't stop them.
Luna! Look at that!
What is that?
Is that the best you can do?
I've seen that type
of crystal before.
The Black Moon had
stones like that.
I want a sample.
Artemis do you copy?
Get that thing in a
containment module.
On it!
Take it. Perform
your analysis.
Hopefully you'll
be able to gain
something useful
from it...
...to make up
for my failure.
[crying]
I'm so sorry, Usagi. I
should've saved her.
I've been investigating
these so-called UFOs that
the Black Moon used
to abduct Mars,
Mercury and Jupiter. They're
actually worm-hole like
portals through space.
But I haven't been able to
identify their point of
origin, or the place
and time the next one
might appear.
If the Black Moon came from
space through these portals,
does that mean
they're aliens?
Not necessarily, but that's
the most logical assumption.
There must be
some reason that
they're targeting
the Earth.
Are they trying to kill us
because we're in their way?
They don't know who
they're messing with!
Kill us? Does that
mean the others are?
No Usako...
Jupiter, Mercury, and
Mars. They're all
alive, I'm sure of it.
I can't take it anymore!
It's like they're
toying with us!
I've had it!
Enough is enough!
We have to confront
Chibi-Usa about the Black
Moon. And make her tell
us everything she knows.
Let's settle it, once and
for all, whether she's our
enemy or our friend.
How are you feeling? Are you
sure you're up to this?
Yeah. I'll be okay.
Welcome home!
[giggling]
Oh! Minako, and Mamoru!
[chuckle] Sorry
about all the noise.
Chibi-Usa brought a little
friend home with her after
school for a play date!
Come meet her, Mamo!
Don't call him that!
She's in the same class as
me! And her name is Momo!
And her family
owns that really
good Chinese restaurant
in the shopping district!
Going to school has been
good for her. It's like
she's just a regular,
happy little girl.
Look at that face... She
just couldn't be an enemy.
Hi Momo! Nice
to meet you!
So what were you guys
doing? Can I play too?
Sure!
[happy giggling]
[gasp]
[screaming]
Huh?
What's wrong?
What is it?
It's okay! I'm right here!
No!
It's just Mamoru, Chibi-Usa.
No! Keep it away!
Keep it away! [crying]
What is it about this
Black Crystal earring?
It's like she's
scared for her life!
We should just
kill those Sailor
Guardians and be
done with it.
And you, Rubeus. Three of
your subordinates have met
their demise. How can
you be so laid-back?
Casualties are inevitable. I
just follow my orders.
Ugh... All of you are out of
your minds if you ask me.
Esmeraude!
Did I say that out loud?
Saphir, don't get yourself
all bent out of shape over a
few minor setbacks.
With any plan of
attack, there are
bound to be some losses.
We have the Planet Nemesis
and its supply of
Malefic Black Crystal.
So what if we lose a
few battles. We'll
still win the war.
Is there still a
war to be won?
Brother, the world already
knows the fearsome power of
the Malefic Black Crystal.
You used it to unleash
an apocalypse!
Everything you wanted
is already yours.
The planet is dead.
Why are we continuing
to spend time on this?
Not everything.
This isn't over.
We have yet to make our
grand ambitions clear.
The planet may
be dead but
it's still not fully
within my grasp.
Not until the queen's corpse
is stretched out before me.
Wiseman.
As long as the Legendary
Silver Crystal exists, our
Malefic Black Crystal will
never be invincible.
However, at this very
moment, I sense that
detestable stone is in the
hands of the Rabbit.
Seize the opportunity to
capture them both!
Make the true power of the
Black Moon known to all!
Get the Legendary
Silver Crystal
and use the Malefic Black
Crystal to destroy it!
Without delay.
I think I'll retire
for the evening.
Wiseman again. Why does
he trust that creepy
fortune-teller?
We don't know anything
about that old man.
He just appeared one
day out of nowhere.
And yet he's managed to
completely manipulate the
Prince, with his slick
tongue and cheap tricks.
Wiseman did grant Prince
Dimande the power of
"Evil Sight." Not
exactly a cheap trick.
It's no wonder our Prince
hangs on his every word.
The Prince didn't care about
the Legendary Silver Crystal
until Wiseman brought it up.
It's like he can't think
for himself anymore.
One day I'm going to
rip the cloak off that
old man's back and find
out what's underneath.
Sisters, I will avenge you
so you can rest in peace.
Master Rubeus...
Channeling the
dead, are we?
Please don't let
me interrupt.
I regret what happened to
your sisters, Calaveras.
But they did manage to split
up the Sailor Guardians.
And without a complete unit,
those girls are powerless.
Like it or not, Planet Earth
belongs to the Black Moon.
They should accept
it and fall in line.
Please let me go to Earth.
They were my sisters.
This is my fight.
I will use the power of my
slain sisters to punish
those who destroyed them.
Code "Zero-Zero-Four".
Operation Re-birth.
[crying]
Please, Chibi-Usa, we
need you to talk to us.
Tell us what's wrong.
Why are you scared of this
Black Crystal earring?
Is it the stone?
Because of that
stone... My mommy...
Yes. What about your mom?
Did something happen to her?
No more stalling Chibi-Usa.
Tell us everything you know!
The Black Moon, we
need information!
I don't know
anything! I swear!
What happened
wasn't my fault!
That's enough for
today. Leave her be.
Okay. We'll stop. But I just
need to know one thing.
Chibi-Usa, can you prove
you're not our enemy?
I'm not! I swear! It's not
anything like that--
How can I believe you when
you won't cooperate?!
I can't take your
word. If you want
my trust, you'll
have to earn it!
[gasp]
I took it for granted they
would always be here with
me. Rei, Ami, Mako...
But now they're gone.
Usagi!
Why don't we have
lunch together today?
[giggling]
It's true! The
stores were all sold
out but I was still
able to get it.
Get what? What are
you talking about?
Just the hardest DVD
to find in town.
Is it a movie?
It's a program about
psychic channeling.
Hunh,what's that?
I'm surprised you haven't
heard of it before.
It's the biggest
craze right now.
Since you don't know,
I'll fill you in.
Channeling is when
a medium goes
into a trance and
ghosts or beings
from other dimensions
inhabit their
body and talk to
us through them.
Other dimensions? I have a
bad feeling about this...
The world-famous medium,
Miss Calaveras, has now
entered her trance.
So let us begin
the interview. To
whom am I speaking?
My name is Crimson
Rubeus of the Black Moon.
The Black Moon!?
I come from a race of beings
that are not unlike humans.
Though our home
is far away, some
of us have come to earth.
But do not fear us. We
are not your enemies.
We come in peace and
wish only to help
guide you to
your true path.
She's lying!
Huh?
Usagi? Is
something wrong?
Wait a minute!
Where are you going?
Usagi...
I've suspected for a
while that you've
been leading a double
life. I know there are
things you have
to keep hidden
and a side of you I
can't be a part of.
But still, you're my
friend and. I wish
there was something I
could do to help.
Miss Calaveras, do you
believe these beings of the
Black Moon truly
mean us no harm?
I do. I channel those beings
often. I sense their
feelings towards us
are benevolent.
The beings from the White
Moon are the ones who have
sinister intentions.
White Moon?
Is she implying
that that's us?
"Guide the people of Earth
to their true path"?
These aliens, they're
beginning to sound
less like invaders
and more like a cult.
I understand you have plans
for a public séance in Tokyo.
That's right. This
weekend in the park.
I invite skeptics and
believers alike to attend,
and learn the truth.
They've declared war
on us and now they
want people to
choose sides?
Minako, it's a trap.
Don't worry. They won't
catch me. I am Sailor Venus!
If the Black Moon
wants a fight,
then I'll give 'em one.
You're right. It appears we
really do have intruders
among us and they snuck in
without anyone noticing.
Miss Hino... where are you?
You're right. We're not
like other people. We have
special abilities and a
destiny as guardians.
Makoto... I haven't seen
her since that night.
Master.
Hello Kunzite,
Jadeite, Nephrite
and Zoisite, as well.
We've had a dire
premonition.
We sense something ominous
behind your enemy's grand
scheme. Their plan
is larger, more
nefarious than we
initially believed.
A strange distortion
of time and space
is emanating
from that stone.
Wait... Are you telling me
that they're time-travelers?
We're not certain.
Whatever they are,
they're very dangerous.
Master, as your loyal
knights, we are still here
to advise and support
you, but we cannot be
with you, so
use your power.
Protect the Princess.
I see visions through touch.
How's that going to help?
It's no good in a fight.
Sometimes I wonder why I
was even reborn at all.
Usako is in danger,
and I am still
powerless to
protect her.
Master, do not doubt
yourself. You are powerful.
This is your destiny.
You were not reincarnated
by accident!
Events have been set in
motion. The day draws near
when the Princess
will become Queen
and you the King.
[gasp]
My brooch! It's gone!
The Earth is entering a new
era. This is the dawning of
the Age of Aquarius,
the Water Bearer.
Peace will guide the
planets, love will steer the
stars, and the mystic
crystal revelation will
free the minds of man.
Usagi! Where are you?
Minako!
My transformation brooch is
gone! Someone stole the
Legendary Silver Crystal!
What?! Are you sure?
Chibi-Usa must have taken
it. I'm going after her to
get it back. I'll be
there as soon as I can!
Great. Perfect timing.
Minako!
Something's wrong.
We shall bring a grand
reformation and lead the
people of Earth down the
path of righteousness.
Be cautious of those who
bear the mark of the White
Moon, they wish to destroy
these golden dreams,
...with their evil
Legendary Silver Crystal!
The Legendary Silver
Crystal is evil, and the
mark of the White Moon
is not to be trusted.
This is bad!
Everyone stop! None of this
is real! She's a fraud!
Don't listen to her!
[gasp]
Quit wasting your breath.
You can't get through to
them. I am Calaveras,
second eldest of the
four Spectre Sisters.
My mind control is absolute
and soon it will reach
everyone on Earth.
[gasp]
Minako! Now!
Venus Star Power
Make up!
I am the Pretty Guardian...
Who fights for
love and beauty!
I am Sailor Venus!
In the name of Venus,
I will punish you!
With the power of love!
There you are. It's about
time you showed up.
I knew you'd be coming so I
prepared something special.
[gasp]
Venus, my guardian planet!
Bestow on me the
power of Love!
Rolling Heart Vibration!
[gasp]
You cannot kill what's
already dead. Spirits of the
four Spectre Sisters,
Energy Attack!
[scream]
Venus!
My body... It's
being torn apart!
[chuckling]
And so the last two Sailor
Guardians meet their end!
"The Last two"!?
Crimson Rubeus himself
should be doing away with
both Sailor Moon and
the Rabbit as we speak.
No! He can't! Usagi!
Found her. Chibi-Usa!
[gasp]
I knew you were the one
who stole my brooch.
That's not yours!
Give it back now!
[gasps]
How nimble.
Just what I'd expect from
the ever-evasive Rabbit.
Though she did have help.
You were a worthy
opponent, Sailor Moon.
But now it's time to die.
[gasp]
[gasps]
Tuxedo Mask!
I've been hit. That
doesn't happen a lot.
I would have given you all
a quick death, but now
you'll feel the full
power of my flames!
What now?! He's
going to kill us!
Usako!
Use your power, Tuxedo
Mask. You can protect them!
[gasp]
Concentrate.
Focus your energy.
And release it!
What's going on? I feel
power in my hand...
Hah!
Tuxedo La
Smoking Bomber!
[gasp]
Damn him! How was he
able to repel my fire?!
What was that power?
And where did that
voice come from?
You saved us.
Usako! Are you
girls both okay?
Yes. Thanks to you.
Chibi-Usa, give Usako
back her brooch.
Please Chibi-Usa, I've lost
three friends already.
I don't want to lose Venus
too! Let me save her!
Moon Crystal
Power! Make up!
[screaming]
[giggling] You'll be seeing
your friends very soon,
Sailor Venus.
[gasp]
Hey, what took you so long?
I don't know what you are or
where you came from, but you
won't be hurting anyone I
care about ever again!
I am the Pretty Guardian!
Who fights for love,
and for justice.
I am Sailor Moon!
And now In the name of the
Moon, I'll punish you!
Stay out of my way!
Moon Princess Halation!
[death scream]
Chibi-Usa, you
took my brooch.
Were you planning to
do something with the
Legendary Silver Crystal?
I knew it was hopeless. No
matter how many Legendary
Silver Crystals I have, I'm
still not able to use them.
Huh?
I knew it, but I
took yours anyway.
I know the Legendary Silver
Crystal from the past, has
no power except in the past.
And the one from the
future only works there.
I was taught that if both
Crystals were ever in the
same time, it
could be dangerous.
Even so... I didn't care.
I had to try it anyway.
With the power of two
Legendary Silver Crystals,
I thought, maybe, I
could do something.
A Silver Crystal from the
future and one from the
past... I don't
understand.
What does that mean?
Chibi-Usa...
What are you trying
to tell us?
Sailor Moon! You're
my only hope!
I'm from the future!
30th-century Earth!
And I need you!
[gasp]
Beyond this door,
lies the 30th Century...
Halt! None shall pass!
It is forbidden!
I am the keeper of the
Door of Space and Time.
My name is Sailor Pluto,
Guardian of the Underworld!
Any intruders beyond this
point will be eliminated!
Act.19 Time warp-
Sailor Pluto.
The moonlight is a
messenger of love.