Unexplained cases of human combustion all over the world.
The World Health Organization is investigating
cases of spontaneous human combustion.
"Burnish" is thought to cause self-combustion.
A Burnish independence movement is also growing,
and public opposition to it is deepening.
On a related note, UN-appointed
specialist, Professor Prometh,
has stated that the oppression of the
Burnish may lead to concurrent blazes worldwide.
The Great World Blaze has come to an end.
Half the population has been wiped out.
30 years after the Great World Blaze,
we must strive more than ever to maintain peace.
Trails of fire
You always knew
They would carry me home
They'd lead me to you
Trails of fire
You always knew
They would carry me home
They'd lead me to you
Though you can't see the sun
A new day has begun
And I fall out of bed
To a siren call
In the frame on the wall
See you in fire
You guys are smiling at me
And you inspire
Not good enough
If I just let them get away
Not satisfied until I'm making 'em pay
I'm a fool for adventure, you know
Inside my heart feelin' the Inferno
Barely catchin' my breath
Lay my eyes on the crest
Gonna square up to all of the heat that is left
So, I carry the torch to Inferno
Inferno
It's out of the park
And I'm smilin' again
Here we go.
High-rise fire, Area B-25,
Promepolis New Town Center.
Dispatch request for Burning Rescue.
Repeat, dispatch request for Burning Rescue.
Burning Rescue!
Dispatch!
NATIONAL RESCUE AND FIRE PREVENTION BUREAU
FORESIGHT PHARMACEUTICALS
Where's Burning Rescue?
Auto-fire supression's out!
We're not even making a dent!
The building's done for!
Vinny!
Yeah, yeah, we'll be there in just a sec!
LUCIA
Civilians on 58th floor,
and they're getting pretty sweaty!
Looks like the center of the Burnish blaze!
Varys, Remi!
Emergency deployment with anti-Burnish combat gear!
Okay.
Roger that.
Lucia, there's no time to stop.
Prepare for mobile launch.
Fire in the hole!
Varys, on the scene!
VARYS
It's full of Burnish Flares in here.
Remi, get in here, quick!
REMI
They're in here!
You're safe now, please remain calm.
The ceiling!
I'm on it.
It's time to go!
All aboard, everyone in the container!
Rescue-mobile on the scene and ready.
IGNIS
Aina, what's the story up there?
58th floor rescue complete, in transit.
There are more people on the roof.
We gotta get them outta there!
Burnish lightning is jamming my instruments.
I can't get in closer.
Get Galo up here!
AINA
Whoa, it's really burning hard, isn't it?
More than worthy of extinguishing.
It sets my firefighter's soul ablaze!
GALO THYMOS
Sorry for the wait.
Burning Rescue is finally here!
Breathe easy, citizens!
The amazing Galo is on the scene!
Quit screwin' around.
We're launchin' you and your
rescue gear to the 108th floor.
I'm not screwing around, I'm getting the crowd pumped!
If you don't shut up, you're gonna bite your tongue off.
Blast off!
The great Galo will now...
Help, we're over here!
Uh, where are they going?
He's dead, right?
He's gotta be dead.
I'm alive!
Let's go, over here everybody, come on!
Galo, do something about this smoke, I can't see!
Okay, everybody, let's keep it moving.
Galo, behind you!
Multiple Burnish signals detected behind the smoke.
They're converging, making them even stronger!
Kakusei
MAD BURNISH
Bad news, Captain, those guys are Mad Burnish!
Inferno terrorists?
Affirmative, most of them were captured, but their
leader and two of the top generals are still at large.
Galo, listen up. Don't underestimate him.
He's the root of all Burnish crime,
and the world's been hunting him for 30 years!
He's the leader of Mad Burnish.
The rescue gear you're wearing wasn't
designed for this. Wait for backup!
So this guy's the boss.
Galo, don't!
Aina, you need to get those people out of here.
Right now!
Don't do anything crazy.
You know he already made up his mind.
You're damn right I did!
Getting scorched is part of the job!
If I let these pyros get away, the shame would kill me.
Come on, you flame-covered terrorist trash!
After that whole speech, that all you got?
You the firefighting intern?
This is bad. His rescue gear's
too heavy to keep up with those bikes.
Too bad you don't have a faster suit, huh?
Lucia, now's the time, do it!
Right-eo.
Way ahead of you! It's prepped and ready to go anytime.
NEXUS
Okay, tech engage!
The fire may be gone, but the heat still lingers.
On-the-scene equipment docking!
Matoi Tech!
I'll extinguish you with my burning soul!
Click.
Behold, Matoi embodies the firefighting heritage
and soul of a Far East island nation.
It symbolizes the spirit of the brave men
who fought fire with their bare hands.
Your reign of fiery terror ends today,
you pyromaniac bastards!
This guy an idiot?
Definitely it is.
He's too fast, no way!
One down.
Gueira, what?
That's two.
Come on down, big boss.
Why don't you get off your high horse,
and fight me, man to man!
Aw, shit.
Coward, you attacked me in the middle of my pose!
What kind of idiot poses while he's fighting a fire?
Hey, Lucia, what the hell is that toy?
Sorry, it's just a personal project.
Galo, try not to get all worked up.
You gotta stay calm, okay?
I'm always calm.
Hey, are you just messing with me?
Big surprise, he's lost his cool.
Finally, one-on-one.
What's so fun about burnin' people's houses down, anyway?
It's not about fun.
The flames are part of us.
We have to burn in order to live.
It's just who we Burnish are.
The only thing that should be burning is your soul.
Your blaze is a nuisance, and I'm gonna put it out!
With my own burning soul! 'Cause that's who I am.
Complete nonsense.
Shut up!
Alley-oop!
Psych.
What the hell's going on? You're just a kid!
And who are you to talk?
Get out of my way or you're gonna die.
The Burnish don't kill people unless they're forced to.
This is over, you're unarmed, and naked.
That's big talk for a little pyromaniac.
I'm, no, actually we,
we're a rescue team.
Lucia!
You got it!
Vinny!
You like that?
We hope you enjoy Matoi Tech rapid cooling.
This is the invincible teamwork
of Special Mobile Firefighter Rescue Unit Burning Rescue.
BURNING RESCUE
So are you amazed yet?
You know, I didn't get naked just for fun.
It hadn't crossed my mind.
Today you met Galo Thymos,
the unbelievable blazing firefighter with a burning soul!
So Mad Burnish boss, burn my name into your mind.
It's Lio, Lio Fotia.
LIO FOTIA
I don't know how you got so full of
yourself, kid, but you're still just a rookie.
Owl.
You almost wrecked that brand-new suit.
Would it kill ya to be more careful?
You'll have better data on it now, you're welcome.
Have some respect, rookie.
You know, you didn't have to hit me so hard, Varys.
Next time, you should hit him even harder.
Otherwise this idiot will never learn.
You know, you got a...
It's Freeze Force.
Vulcan
Colonel Vulcan.
Good job out here today, Ignis.
VULCAN
Mad Burnish, huh?
Don't worry, we'll take it from here.
Hey, you got some pretty ancient gear there, huh?
Low-level rescue team sure have it hard.
That's why Burnish crimes are always
under Freeze Force's jurisdiction.
Way to take credit for our work.
Galo, shut up, you idiot.
So it was you? You're the one who caught this guy?
And what if I said that I was?
You're under arrest, firefighter.
I'm what?
The law explicitly forbids
civilians from dealing with terrorists.
Your lack of training could've
caused a major disaster.
I'm afraid I can't overlook your reckless actions.
It's the Burnish's actions that can't be overlooked,
and all I did was stop them from destroying the city!
You'll be free to plead your case in court.
Hold it. We're authorized to deal
with the Burnish in a fire emergency.
That exception gives us jurisdiction.
Guess who judges whether that applies or not, this guy!
I'll note that in my report.
Vulcan.
What, can't take a joke?
What a pointless internal power struggle.
Public officials are so worthless.
You've got a big mouth for a Burnish.
Take him away!
Looks like Vulcan was just
letting off some steam, asshole.
The Burnish suddenly appeared 30 years ago.
Wild blazes caused by fire-wielding mutants
took a huge toll on the world.
But now, the Burnish threat is finally being driven out.
Days ago, thanks to the noble efforts of Special
Mobile Firefighter Rescue Unit, Burning Rescue,
Mad Burnish's leader was arrested.
This noble act marks the end of the flame terrorist group.
No, wait!
He told you to wait! You get back here!
It's better not to fight them.
You'll only end up with your limbs frozen solid.
Sure seems that way.
Boss.
Look at them.
My God. It's just like we heard.
Mad Burnish was our only hope for ages,
and now you've been captured too.
Boss, look.
Why did they do this?
Now, allow me to introduce,
Burning Rescue's rookie hero, your Galo Thymos!
Join me as we celebrate his great
achievement, the annihilation of Mad Burnish.
Galo please continue to protect
the citizens of Promepolis.
You can count on me, Governor.
I'll keep on protecting Promepolis
just like you once protected me.
You've always been my greatest
hero and inspiration as a firefighter,
ever since you lost your arm saving me.
KRAY FORESIGHT
I'm counting on you, we all are.
One Inferno Volcano Margherita Megamax, enjoy!
Ow, so yummy and hot right from the oven.
Two more please.
You got it.
Gotta hand it to ya, it's always cooked just right!
Yeah, he's very good at what he does.
Here ya go, enjoy!
Saw you on TV, Galo, nice job out there.
Oh, you mean this?
Yeah, those terrorist guys were a real pain
in the neck, you know?
What is it they were called, the Mad Burnish?
What a relief to know their boss is finally in jail!
Yep!
I'm sure some of those Burnish guys are pretty decent.
And the discrimination is just
'cause those terrorists give 'em a bad name.
Yeah, I couldn't have said it better myself, Pops.
The Burnish are just misunderstood.
It's not like being one of them makes you a bad person.
It's a mutation.
It says nothing about your character.
What matters is how you use it.
Like Varys with his superhuman strength.
Anyway, you guys can count on me for any
fire in Promepolis. I'll stake this medal on it.
Hey, you got this man!
Yep, we're in good hands!
Yeah, but who wears their medal to go get pizza?
A real man must always wear his medals on his chest.
Not to mention that the Governor gave it to me himself.
It means a lot.
He saved your life or something, right?
Yeah, when I was a kid.
He must've been a college student back then.
Thanks to that rescue, everyone knew who he was.
And that's how his research on
fireproof materials gained attention.
Before you knew it, he was a billionaire.
Now he's the chairman of
the Foresight Foundation and the city governor.
Talk about a meteoric rise, right?
So can't you make money with your inventions?
Inventions that make money are nothing but heresy.
That was totally something a mad scientist would say.
You know, you're older sister's one too.
Yeah, maybe.
I don't even know what she's researching.
Huh, looks like warp engines?
But they still have a long way to go.
You think we'll ever see something
like that in our lifetime?
Even being able to join a rescue team.
That was thanks to Governor Kray.
I have to pay him back somehow,
no matter what the risks are.
Hey, Pops! We need more Inferno Margherita over here!
Uh, I hope you don't think
we're gonna be splitting the bill.
Hey that's mine!
Freeze Force?
Nobody move a muscle!
If you do, I'll consider you a Burnish!
Hey, What the hell do you think you're doing...
Oh, it's you again.
Shut up and watch.
You over there, don't move!
Hey!
Stay away!
Pizza guy is a Burnish?
Wait, what are you doing?
He's not a criminal!
All he's trying to do is make some pizza!
Did you know what he was?
Boss, it's okay.
It's not. Look, kid, all you are guilty of
is wanting to make the best pizza in town.
Old man, you're under arrest too.
Cordon off this restaurant.
Back off.
That Burnish is innocent.
And why're you dragging Pops into this?
He was sheltering a Burnish fugitive.
In the eyes of the law, anyone caught harboring
a Burnish is considered as guilty as the Burnish.
You should study the law
before running around like you're some kind of hero.
Just wait a minute!
It's true that harboring a Burnish is a crime.
But that's a special law that applies only to terrorists!
This guy is not a terrorist!
That's for a court to decide, not a little girl!
You're saying this pizza was made by a Burnish?
Oh, disgusting.
How could they?
It's like they served us all garbage!
Hey, knock it off!
Galo, you need to calm down.
It's not like we can tell people what to think.
Even if it sucks.
Where are you going?
Lets go you three.
You're being transferred.
Gueira.
Boss.
And Meis.
Right.
Here we go.
Bastard!
Burnish will always be free.
I won't let the Foundation hold us!
We'll rescue our wounded comrades.
That's much better.
Go and free the others.
You got it!
Don't kill anyone.
We Burnish don't kill without reason.
Yeah, yeah, I know!
A wall of fire!
C'mon, we're breakin' all of you out of here.
But how did you...
Oh, you mean the freezing rings?
Breaking out of those was a piece of cake for the boss.
Let's move!
You are so irritating.
Everyone, come on, let's go!
I never knew this place existed, what is it?
I dunno.
How did you even know about it?
I found it totally by accident one day.
I was riding around all pissed off.
Now whenever I need to cool off, I just come here.
Well, I guess it's good for that.
Not many people would come all the way
out here in the mountains.
Unless it's someone like you, who has way too much energy.
Oh, then what are you doing out here?
I'm here because when you left before,
you seemed like you were about to go raid Freeze Force HQ.
Oh, you wanted to help?
No, I wanted to stop you.
You think I'm an
idiot, don't you?
Well, yeah.
Jeez.
Hey, be careful! That ice could break!
Don't worry. I dug five meters deep
once and it was ice all the way down.
You dug through five meters of ice?
Yeah, I was curious to see how far down it went.
Come on, you know you can skate with shoes too.
Well, this is a relief.
It's good to know you've got the sense
to come here and cool off.
The last thing I wanna do is give Gov Kray any trouble.
Well, all the higher-ups know
that he was the one who saved my life.
So if I go rogue and start causing trouble,
they're gonna think I'm misusing his authority.
I can't do that to the Gov.
Wow, you do have a deep side, who'da thought?
Know what?
I think I understand how you feel.
It's the same for me.
No one ever thinks of me as just "Aina".
I've always been Heris' younger sister.
She was the smart one ever since we were little.
They called her a child prodigy.
But you know what?
I'm actually proud,
I'm proud to be Heris Ardebit's sister.
My sister is the cornerstone of Foresight Labs.
You should be proud of yourself too,
because you're you, Aina.
Burnish flame.
Where are you going?
You call it in, I'm gonna go check it out!
Jeez, same old Galo.
It's you, Mad Burnish's boss.
It's Lio Fotia, I already told you once, Galo Thymos.
What?
Be quiet, we're trying to eat.
I didn't know you Burnish even ate food.
Is that what you really think of the Burnish?
We're human beings just like you.
If we don't eat, we die.
You're right, I'm sorry.
Lio.
Hang in there, Thyma, the truck is coming.
A truck?
A helicopter would be too easy to spot.
Gueira and Meise went to find a vehicle
that can fit all of us.
But, I don't think she's gonna...
Let me help!
You?
She's in this condition because of people like you.
But I'm part of a rescue squad.
I have emergency medical training.
I got first-aid equipment on my bike.
There's no need.
From flames to ashes, from ashes to earth.
Rest in peace.
She turned into ashes?
It's the fate of the Burnish.
What?
The flames burn our body,
but they also give us the power to regenerate it.
While we're alive, our body is eternal.
No matter how much we burn, we recover.
But then once our life comes to an end,
our bodies turn into ashes.
For real?
Is it that much of a surprise? All humans die eventually.
We feed the flames until the day we burn out.
That certainty is a blessing.
You're saying you only live for the flames?
We can hear them.
We can hear the cries of their anguish.
Let me burn harder, burn stronger. I want to blaze hotter!
The flames are alive.
They call to us, and to answer their cries
is the destiny of the Burnish.
But we don't kill people.
When the Mad Burnish attack a city
we always provide an escape route.
And we take great pride in that.
Boss, the truck is ready. There's room for everyone.
Good, let's go. It's dangerous to stay here any longer.
Oh, so you're running away again?
That's right, as long as we're being hunted.
Why can't you just stop starting fires?
If you could hold back,
wouldn't you be able to live a normal life?
Then you wouldn't have to keep running.
Do you honestly believe it's that simple?
Yeah.
Then you're an idiot.
What?
Do you even know what killed her?
It was the Foresight Foundation's experiments.
You really had no idea?
How naive can someone be?
It wasn't just her.
They were all almost killed by Kray Foresight.
He dissects us, and kills us!
All of it for his research, even though we're humans too.
That's a lie!
The governor would never do something like that!
If you want to keep ignoring the truth,
that's your choice.
Hey, wait, hey, hey, come back!
Galo, are you okay?
Galo.
You want to return it?
Yeah, Lio, the guy I captured, escaped.
Nobody reported that to me.
I found him hiding in a cave.
He said he escaped from your detention facility.
Even if that is the case,
I don't see why you'd need to return it.
Some people deserve to wear medals.
And those medals should come from people
who deserve to award them.
Neither you or I are worthy of this medal.
I don't understand.
Governor Kray, is it true that you're doing
human experiments, with Burnish prisoners?
You're my hero.
You saved my life, started the Foundation,
and even built this city.
How could you do such a horrible thing?
Horrible?
The Burnish are people too.
They get hungry, they cry when they lose a friend.
We can't just let them start fires,
but you can arrest them and leave it at that!
You can't just kill them for no reason!
I see, please follow me.
Ever since the Burnish appeared 30 years ago,
magma from the Earth's core has been out of control.
At it's current rate,
it will completely cover the planet in six months.
What?
What the heck?
The devastation will make
the Great World Blaze look like nothing.
Our Earth will become a dead planet.
No way.
Why so many doors?
This is the Parnassus Project, mankind's last hope.
Is this a, spaceship?
We've discovered a planet very similar to
Earth four light years from here, Omega Centauri.
The interstellar cruise vessel, Parnassus,
will be our new Noah's Ark.
It will carry 10,000 chosen ones,
who'll migrate to Omega Centauri.
Wait, only 10,000 people?
Yes, that's the maximum number of passengers it can carry.
No way.
You.
Aina's sister.
HERIS
What is he doing here?
It's okay, progress report?
Uh, yes, we're about to start the final test now.
That's the pizza guy, what are you doing to him?
Just watch.
Initiate test.
Initiating test.
Activate Prometech pod.
Activate warp.
Stop Prometech pod.
Stopping the pod.
It was successful.
Full implementation of the warp engine is in sight.
It's just as I told you.
We should have been using the Prometech engine
from the beginning.
That's horrible.
It's a precious sacrifice for the survival of mankind.
We can't build the warp engine without the Burnish.
There has to be some other way.
If we can just stop the magma,
then we won't have to go to another planet!
I've considered that, of course.
But with our current technology,
there's no way to stop the magma's rampage.
Migration is our best bet.
So you have to sacrifice the Burnish?
Exactly, do you understand what I'm doing now?
Yeah, I do, but there's no way I can accept it.
Okay, what then?
Extinguish the magma and I'll do it myself!
I knew that's what you'd say, Galo.
We're short on time, we can't have an idiot making a fuss.
Gov Kray, why?
Don't call me "Gov"!
It's Governor!
I've always hated when you say that!
You've never been anything but an eyesore to me!
Take him away.
What the hell is going on here?
Why are you doing this, Kray?
Kray.
Begin the final stage of tuning.
We'll install the Prometech engine on the Parnassus.
Biar, call the car.
Yes, sir.
Let me out of here!
Hello, is anybody out there?
Somebody just open the door already,
I shouldn't be in here!
Kray, why?
Kray, you were my hero, why?
You knew I was against this course of action.
We've already completed production of the pods.
So you were planning to use
the Prometech engine from the start?
Yes, I was just waiting for you to find your resolve.
What kind of person are you?
We're going to abandon most of mankind.
If you lack the will to make hard decisions,
you aren't going to survive what's coming.
How's the Burnish crackdown going?
Freeze Force has already been deployed.
The final act, we're going to be busy.
We're approaching our destination.
Let's show them what we've got.
Who would've thought they'd be hiding right here?
The darkest place is under the candlestick.
We didn't notice them with all these volcanoes around.
Check that out!
Hey, wait!
Everyone, run, it's Freeze Force!
Whoa, careful, we're not trying to kill these guys.
They're our precious fuel!
How the hell did you find us?
Gee, I dunno, kid. Let's see if you can guess.
Watch your back, Lio.
Boss! You bastard!
Mr. Vulcan, I've been waiting for you!
You told him, what have you done?
Now!
It was the sweet old man.
We implanted a tracker before you left.
That was foolish.
No, you're the fool!
We don't stand a chance against the Foundation.
The less time you have left,
the more you value saving your own skin.
Thank you for your service old man.
We can't let good fuel go to waste, can we?
Even this old geezer can still be of some use.
Bastard!
ΛSHES
The Absolute Zero Chain Freezing Bullet.
It freezes by absorbing your body heat.
Good luck burning through that.
By the way, I knew you'd let yourself
be captured so you could free the prisoners.
You actually thought you outsmarted us, didn't you?!
We saw you coming from a mile away!
Not today!
You ended up gathering all the Burnish together
for us to pick up, how considerate.
Let me show you my gratitude.
Vulcan, Vulcan, Vulcan, Vulcan.
This is for the boss!
And this is for the settlement!
Burnish scum!
We'll make you pay!
Stop it, get out of here now!
Forget about us!
The Burnish's flame won't fade as long as you live!
The boss's flames are invincible!
Please stop!
No you don't!
Go!
Guys, no!
We did it!
You think you're so smart.
Where did that blast send Lio?
A crater inside Fennel Volcano.
We don't have the right kind of equipment
to withstand that kind of heat.
It doesn't matter. There's no way he'll
survive. That absolute zero bullet won't fail.
Governor Kray, the test was a success.
Yes, we've confirmed the same from here.
Well done, Doctor.
We will commence the Parnassus Project immediately.
Yes, sir.
We'll start contacting selected citizens
in accordance to the simulations.
Hey, were you able to find him?
No luck, he wasn't even at the frozen lake.
The last time anyone saw him,
he was on his way to see the Govenor.
It's not like Galo to miss a shift.
It's been a week already.
Jeez, where did that idiot disappear to?
I've got so much new stuff that I wanna test out!
I wish you and Galo would stop wasting
all this time on your personal projects.
It isn't a waste of time.
They're for emergency use, you never know.
Emergency, right.
That idiot!
Well, I finally got word from a friend
at the city office, Galo has been arrested.
What, but why?
They're saying that he's a terrorist.
He was arrested after an alleged attack on the governor.
Impossible!
Do you think it's true, Captain?
True or not, Galo's been arrested.
Hmm, the whole thing sounds kinda fishy.
What the heck?
Aina, where are you going?
You can wait outside.
Don't worry, I'll shout if I need help.
You sure about that?
I'm sure you're not the kind of
guy who'd attack an unarmed person.
Aina always said you were honest,
and maybe too blunt for your own good.
Here, you should eat something.
It'll be your last supper.
You can't be okay with this.
Aina told me that she's proud of you.
Does she know anything about the migration?
Or what you're doing to the Burnish?
What I tell Aina is none of your business.
She doesn't know, does she?
There's no way she would be okay with this!
You know it's wrong, that's why you haven't told her.
It's because, if it'd guarantee Aina's survival,
I'm prepared to do anything.
And you think Aina will be able to live with that?
Heris!
Aina.
Heris, is it true Galo was arrested?
Yes.
There must be a mistake. He's not a terrorist.
Please, you have to talk to Governor Kray, help him!
Aina, I need you to calm down.
Heris?
I saw it happen with my own eyes.
He really did try to assault the governor.
Listen to me, Aina.
You need to start thinking about yourself now.
I'm going to contact you soon.
Come straight here as soon as you get that call.
Can you do that?
I love you, Aina.
Heris...
I won't forgive you.
I'm gonna make you pay, Kray Foresight!
You're gonna feel it, the rage of the Burnish!
What happened?
Unexplained fires have broken out all over Promepolis.
A massive Burnish flare is coming from underground.
This is a message for Kray Foresight.
Release all Burnish prisoners immediately.
If not, I will turn Promepolis to ash.
And I will show no mercy.
Is that, is that Lio?
That fire... is he crying?
Lio Fotia, surprised you're still alive.
So sad it was for nothing!
So irritating, be gone!
Now you die!
Vulcan, Vulcan, Vul, Vul, Vul!
Stupid eyelid!
How long will you hide behind these weaklings?
Show yourself, Kray Foresight!
The source of the fire's moving too fast.
We cant keep up.
This is bad, Captain. Every single one of the
Freeze Force interceptors has been shot down.
Varys, get to C-5, that's the worst of it.
The rest of us will do what we can in transit.
Yes, sir!
Galo?
Captain Ignis!
Captain, you've gotta listen!
Fire, big one, it's moving!
You mean like the one on your ass?
Ow, ow, ow! It's hot, it's hot!
Wait up, guys I'm comin' too!
Weren't you, in jail?
Worry about that later.
Right.
Putting out that fire's our
first priority, same as always.
Did you escape or something?
Yeah.
Galo!
I am Galo Thymos, a firefighter with a burning soul!
This is right where I belong!
Tuned her up good as new, orders from the captain.
Captain, Captain, don't worry I've got this.
Aina!
Hm?
Mad Burnish, I'm the one you want.
Finally.
Kray...
Kray Foresight!
Bring it on, Mad Burnish bastard!
Ow, it's hot!
Galo, stay out of this!
It's not that hot at all!
Your spiteful flames are barely even lukewarm!
I was honestly expecting more from you!
The temperature of my burning firefighter's
soul is a million and ten times...
HOTTER!
Oh, it's cold, it's cold!
So be it.
You again, Galo Thymos!
I understand your anger. I was betrayed by Kray too!
What?
But even still, I can't just sit back and let
you take it out on a bunch of innocent people!
Yeah right!
You're the ones doing human
experiments on innocent Burnish!
Didn't you tell me you took pride
in not killing people without a reason?
All right, you two, why don't you cool off a little bit?
Ow, it's hot, it's so hot!
So did you calm down a little?
Guys, are you seeing this?
What is this place?
The structure isn't even wet.
It was in some kind of cavity, underneath all that ice.
That is correct.
Greetings, Galo Thymos and Lio Fotia.
That's weird, How do you know our names?
Yeah, and who are you?
I need to speak to you both immediately, kindly follow me.
What are you doing, don't follow it.
Great job, everybody. I can't believe
that idiotic move actually worked.
It's the idiot's superpower.
Doesn't really matter, man, he's still an idiot.
Where's Aina?
No word from her since she ran off with the idiot.
We don't have time to worry about the two of them.
We've got rescue work to do.
You got it, boss!
Governor, the fires in town have been extinguished.
The transport network will soon be back to normal.
Very good.
Bring the selected citizens on board and make
sure to keep the rest of the population from the ship.
Parnassus is about to launch.
Activity in the earth's core has intensified.
We've run out of time.
Where are we?
Some kind of research facility?
So, you're not going to announce the Prometech pod?
No, killing the Burnish for energy is unconscionable.
I can't make such a thing public.
I understand, you haven't told
anyone else about it, correct?
You and I are the only ones who know about it.
And the same for the Promare?
That's correct.
Well, that is a relief.
Someone must shoulder the fate of mankind,
and if you won't, I will.
Actually, it should be me.
You, my research...
Yes, I'm taking it all.
Have you been planning this all along?
I don't know, maybe I have been.
So Governor Kray is a murderer?
That guy that he killed,
he's the one that brought us here.
Exactly, I was murdered by Kray.
Who are you?
Deus Prometh, a researcher specializing in the Burnish.
Instant freezing agent, fireproof armor, all of it,
they're all anti-Burnish patents
belonging to the Foundation.
Those are all my inventions.
Kray stole them and released them as his own.
So how are you talking to us?
I have backed up my entire
consciousness into this computer,
so that I might live once again
after the termination of my physical body.
Of course, I made sure Kray didn't find out.
A virtual personality?
How did you know our names?
I was able to hack into the Promepolis network.
I stay informed on whatever happens there,
so that I can keep an eye on Kray.
What's going on? Is that...
Volcanic eruption in South-West Promepolis.
Core magma activity?
Core magma activity is within our projected models.
Good, get ready for departure.
All of the passengers are already on board.
Governor, please, you have to wait.
What's wrong?
Aina isn't on board.
We tried to contact her,
but she didn't respond to the transmission.
You can't launch until she gets here.
What are you saying?
If she doesn't survive, this will all be for nothing!
We'll wait as long as possible.
But we can't postpone the launch because of one person.
I'm sure you understand.
Return to your post, Dr. Heris.
Kray...
Immediately.
What is that?
It's a spaceship.
Kray took me underground and showed me.
What?
Magma is about to gush out of the Earth, and go, ka-boom!
Their plan is to run away to another planet.
The ship can only hold 10,000 people.
Only 10,0007?
And that's not all, the ship is human powered.
What?
They're going to use the Burnish's flames
as fuel for their warp engine.
And using that fuel will cost them their life.
That monster.
I know.
Galo, my sister, was she working on this thing?
She was, wasn't she?
Yeah.
Kray is a fool.
What he fails to realize,
is that the instant he ignites that incomplete engine,
the entire Earth will be destroyed.
Whoa, wait, what?
If he hurts the Burnish with the Prometech engine,
the Promare in the Earth's core will retaliate.
The planet will be doomed.
What do you mean?
The energy the Burnish use only appear to be flames.
They are in fact a fire-based life-form,
from a parallel universe.
What, a fire-based life-form?
I named them "The Promare."
Promare?
Correct.
Together, they form a sentient-fixed star
in this parallel universe.
In other words, it's an aggregate of living organisms,
achieving life through nuclear fusion
and consciousness via electromagnetic fields.
What we see as flames are but a fraction of their energy
seeping through a space-time rupture.
What is this old guy even talking about?
30 years ago, a distortion of space time,
linked Earth's core to the Promare universe.
Some humans resonate with the Promare
and thus can use their power at will.
Some humans, you mean the Burnish.
That is correct.
So it's the Promare,
their voices pushing us to burn harder and stronger.
If that's true then everything we've been doing here...
Harnessing the Promare's inter-dimensional energy,
it is indeed possible to achieve teleportation.
But the nerve signals of a Burnish
are linked to the Promare they've synced with.
The Promare feel the Burnish's pain.
If these incomplete Prometech pods
cause a large number of Burnish great pain,
the Promare in Earth's core will spiral out of control,
destroying the planet.
So the Promare are located in the center of the Earth?
That is where the space-time rupture is.
And that is where the Promare live.
Galo Thymos, Lio Fotia,
I want you to stop Kray Foresight.
Wait, us?
Yes, using the complete Prometech engine
that I have built.
But how?
With this.
A super weapon I have created
in the event of Promare disaster, Deus X Machina!
DEUS X MACHINA
Well, this thing looks like a lot of fun.
How did they already get in there?
The completed Prometech engine causes no pain.
It uses Lio's body as a gateway,
through which the Promare energy is channeled.
All you have to do,
is focus on synchronizing with the Promare.
But why us?
What made you choose the two of us?
I did not choose you, you just happened to land here.
Kray has to be stopped.
But I could not do anything on my own,
then out of nowhere you two showed up.
It seems mankind still has luck on its side.
Yeah, but what would you have done if no one showed up?
I suppose, Kray's plan would've doomed the Earth.
What's this guy's deal?
I am not a guy, I am a computer.
And now the fate of planet Earth is in your hands.
My work here is done. Deus out.
What? Wait, Professor!
So, are you feeling conflicted?
Yeah, you probably are.
You just found out your flames are aliens.
What do you know about how I feel?
Absolutely nothing, I guess.
All I really know is that if there's a fire,
I'm putting it out.
So you gotta do what you do and burn it out.
I, what?
Yeah, uphold your Burnish pride.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
Yeah, let's do this.
We'll save the Burnish and the Earth.
I like your style!
All systems check, ready for departure.
Very good, start up the Prometech engine.
Prometech engine, activate.
That's...
The warp gate.
Keep going, Dr. Heris.
Watch as we open the door to mankind's future.
What the heck is that?
What was that?
This makes no sense.
Volcanoes are erupting simultaneously all over the world.
At long last.
Large unidentified machine approaching.
It's not responding to hails.
Impossible, attack with all weapons!
Fire freezing missiles!
Use conventional weapons as well!
That's an order, fire!
Collision on deck, the target has stopped.
Is it dead?
That hurt, what the hell are you doing?
You're supposed to be piloting this thing!
Man, I'm sorry.
For some reason, I just can't get in the zone.
What are you talking about?
This suit, it just, I mean, look how lame the design is.
I can't get my firefighter's soul to burn in this thing!
This is the crap I get after you insist I come out here?
Well, we cant sit here, how about this?
Oh, yeah, good call.
That's what I'm talkin about!
This is my jam!
That thing's showing an extremely powerful Burnish signal.
According to these readings,
it's more pure than the Prometech engine.
NEXUS
Even if the ideals you look up to come crashing
to the ground, your hope will never be broken.
A burning firefighter and an ice-cold firestarter,
oil and water combined as one!
Absolute Firefighter, Lio dé Galon!
LIO DE GALON
We'll extinguish every last fire on Earth!
What the hell are you talking about?
"Deus X whatever" doesn't really have enough impact.
Its new name is Lio dé Galon.
Gotta love my modesty, I could've called it Galo dé Lion.
Shut up and fight.
I knew it, that machine is the Deus X Machina.
I didn't know it was completed.
Hyper Fire Safety Punch!
That voice, is that Galo?
Sure was.
What is he doing?
Where did he find it, where did it come from?
I need answers!
What the hell is going on, Galo?
Heris, do you read me? Come in, it's me, Aina.
Aina, where have you been?
I'm fine, but more importantly, look at this.
If you start the Prometech engine,
the Earth's core is going to go out of control!
You cannot launch that ship!
Isn't that Professor Deus?
The governor killed him?
This footage is...
It's only a video, they're easily falsified.
Do not let the rebels tricks get to you.
Is what I'm seeing real?
Did the governor really murder Professor Deus?
He did, Deus told me himself.
Anyway, Kray's engine is incomplete.
If it fully activates, at this rate,
the earth'll become a sea of...
Aina, Aina?
You shut off my external communications didn't you?
No, it wasn't me.
An attack from that robot must've been the cause.
Killer move, One Match Arson Kick!
Kick, Kick, Kick, Kick!
Hey, Burnish prisoners, where are you? We're here!
Everyone, hold on!
Heris, the robot is insignificant.
Now set the engine to full power, we're warping at once.
Don't you care what happens to the planet?
It'll be destroyed sooner or later either way.
Concentrate on the migration project.
You, you knew, didn't you?
That using the Prometech engine would destroy the planet?
It's either now or in six months.
I, understand.
Prometech engine, full power.
Oh no, they're about to warp!
Damn it!
Tell me, where are the Burnish?!
We have to abort. They're going to destroy the bridge!
All personnel move to the second bridge.
Transfer the ship's main system controls
to the secondary bridge as well.
I'll get rid of that thing.
Biar, take control of the launch procedures.
Yes, sir.
Galo, you're pushing your luck!
Huh, what's that?
Your futile struggle..
is now over!
That voice, it's Kray!
Kray, free the Burnish!
Filthy terrorists, how dare you?
What?
The buildings, they turned into dirt!
Genocide Cultivation Beam,
it destroys mountains, turning them into farmland.
Just one of the terraforming tools
we'll use on our new planet.
I wasn't expecting to have to use it here.
Hey, what about the people inside?
They're all in underground shelters, obviously.
Damn you!
If you can make things like that, why didn't you
use your science to get the magma under control?
I tried and I couldn't,
that's why we were forced to migrate!
Do you really wanna destroy mankind?
If you already know it's gonna be destroyed
then you just have to stop it!
You can think about the rest later!
You hopeless idiot!
I'm not gonna let you commit any more atrocities.
Our Lio Dé Galon versus your Krazor X!
KRAZOR X
Time to find out which one's more powerful!
Lio!
Got it!
So you stopped Lio Dé Galon's flames.
Most impressive, Krazor X.
BUT NOW,
TAKE THIS, Krazor X!
STOP,
MAKING UP,
STUPID NAMES!
Pulverizing Pile Driver,
designed to break through hard
bedrock to reach water veins.
Compared to this, your armor is nothing, like paper!
That robot's bad news.
I know, no way can we win like this.
Dammit, wish I had my Matoi gear.
Matoi, that weird costume you were wearing before?
It's not weird, it's cool!
It embodies the firefighter heritage
of a far-off island nation!
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
Something like this?
Bring it on!
Nothing in the world gets me fired up like Matoi!
Gaze in awe, Lio Dé Galon, Matoi Decked out!
What?
Heris...
Doctor, the engine is out of control
because it's being over-fueled!
At this rate, the central pod is going to overheat!
If we don't do something is gonna explode!
Heris, what's going on?
I've destroyed the central pod
by overloading it with energy.
The Prometech engine is now inoperable.
You did this, intentionally?
I was a fool to have ever believed in you, Kray.
That idiot, she's been blinded by her love for her sister.
Call Colonel Vulcan at once.
Ow, it looks like the Parnassus just crashed.
The warp gate must have closed, that means...
The death of the Earth is now inevitable.
This ship and its passengers the only future for mankind.
And it's Kray Foresight who'll create that future!
Absolute Zero Heat Death Cannon.
It's the ultimate freezing weapon,
created for protection from Promare
attacks and solar flares on our new planet.
If you've got something like that,
why don't you use it to save Earth?
You'd have to be inside the planet core for that to work.
This machine couldn't withstand those conditions.
You just want to migrate no matter what.
If you bothered to cool off you'd see that.
Do you two idiots really think you can beat me?
I'll send you to absolute freezing hell!
Galo, you didn't even try to dodge that!
What are you planning to do?
Just grin, and bear it, that's all!
You're an idiot!
Yeah, the world's number-one firefighting idiot!
I'm gonna put 'em out now.
Not only your flames but your stupid ambitions too!
Okay, let's do it!
I dare you to come and take your best shot!
Did we get him?
Wait, look.
Does saving the Burnish mean that much to you, Lio Fotia?
Guess what, you're going to fail.
Because the Burnish are destined to die.
Listen, listen to the death throes of your friends!
Bastard!
If you hate me so much, then kill me, Lio Fotia, do it!
Be careful what you wish for, Kray!
Stop it, calm down, Lio, don't kill him!
I will never, forgive you!
Did you really think you'd be able to burn me...
with your pathetic flames?
You Burnish really are just a bunch of fools.
What?
Impossible, are you...
Ah, indeed. I was cursed with the
same mutation, that's why I understand.
Yes, I understand how difficult it is
to have a strong enough will to control the flames,
as well as to control the urge to burn
everything to the ground.
The Burnish live under the control of the Promare.
They're nothing but slaves to their instincts!
You make it sound like you're any different.
That's because I am!
Don't even try,
my Burnish power is far greater than yours will ever be.
Damn it.
But still, as long as I have you,
I can harness your power to restart my Prometech engine.
You'll be the engine's core now.
What?
I thank you.
Let him go now, Kray.
Good grief.
From the very moment we met, I've hated the sight of you.
I had my first Burnish spasm when I was a student.
I was trying to hold back the flames, but I couldn't.
So, you're saying that you didn't save me?
No, it was a complete accident.
But it was a good opportunity to build my reputation.
No way.
I had you placed in Burning Rescue
because it was the job with the highest mortality rate.
I wanted to be rid of you, but you kept surviving,
and you kept coming back!
My life has always gone according to plan,
except when it comes to you.
You're not just an idiot, you're a cancer!
You were, my hero!
But this is the end for you!
Galo!
You're a monster!
No...
I am a hero!
The savior of mankind!
Nowhere left to run.
You know that wasn't very smart of you,
turning against the governor.
She'd rather jump than face me.
What?
You cheeky bastards!
Aina!
We made it!
Let's go get Galo.
Galo!
The Burnish are inside these pods surrounding us.
You'll fly us across the stars,
powered by the Burnish's screams.
You shall become a legend.
An undeserved distinction for a Burnish fool.
You won't get away with this.
That's right, go on, get angry.
All your rage will be fuel for my Prometech engine!
This is Kray, restart the countdown now.
We warp in five minutes.
Understood.
Parnassus, five minutes to warp.
Galo, Galo!
He's still on fire!
Wait.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Lio's flames protected me.
The ship, it's gonna warp.
How? I destroyed the engine.
He's using Lio to replace the core.
Doctor, where's the engine?
What are you gonna do?
Isn't it obvious? I'm gonna save Lio.
I'd ask how, but I know your plan
is to just run head-first into the core, isn't it?
Yeah, I'm a Burning Rescue member.
Firefighting and rescue is what I do.
I'm gonna save Lio and extinguish the...
Ignis, hand over the doctor and that punk,
or I'll consider you a traitor as well.
Not gonna happen.
You've got some balls defying the Freeze Force, Ignis.
This is an emergency situation, we're authorized to fight.
Doesn't matter, you're all gonna get burned!
I refuse!
Lucia!
Aye-aye, Captain!
I installed new drill gear on the spare Matoi,
just in case, 'cause you never know.
A new drill?
Yup, the drill of your dreams can penetrate any armor!
Also, I sent you a schematic of the Parnassus.
I'll calculate the angle
and launch you straight into the engine.
Nice, Lucia.
Skip the silly announcements, just get going!
Go get 'em!
I'm coming, Lio!
This is...
Vulcan!
Ignis!
How long is this gonna go on?
Me thinks there's a good chance
that we've run out of time!
Promare activity has increased.
Galo.
Lio!
Lio! Lio, are you okay?
Oh, no!
Why are you still alive?
Why can't I get rid of you?
This is a rescue operation, back off!
I'll extinguish you.
No, extinguishing is my job!
Give up, you can't beat me!
What?
Gallant Ones
It's just like before.
Lio's fire protected me from those flames of yours.
This little spark was my shield.
Now here's what I'm gonna do, save him, save Earth,
and even save you!
Save me?
Just shut up and watch.
Hey, bud, stay with me!
Lio, come on, dammit, don't you disappear on me!
I've gotta do something.
G...Galo?
Hey, you're awake, welcome back.
Did, did you just save me?
What have I done?
For the first time in my whole life,
I lit a fire, because of you!
This is all your fault!
How are you gonna fix this, you jerk!
How about you and I burn the Earth to the ground?
When I was in the pod,
I synced with the Promare in the Earth's core,
and I understand now.
Their combustion is incomplete.
We have to let them burn out just once.
Lio, have you lost your mind?
How could you even ask me, a firefighter, to do that?
That's why we need you, your firefighter's soul.
This time, let's call it Galo Dé Lion!
Wait, stop it, what are you doing?
I thought that would be obvious, we're going firefighting.
We'll extinguish the Earth's magma
and the flames of your ambition.
We'll need help from all the Burnish too!
With all of our flames we can ignite the whole planet!
You got it, boss.
Yeah, let's do this, boss!
Boss!
Now, I'll show you my burning firefighter's soul!
Inferno
What?
Dammit, he didn't make it in time.
But these flames aren't...
Yeah, that's right.
They're not hot.
It's like what happened to Galo earlier.
They're protecting us.
That's right, the Promare synched with human will.
When my desire to burn everything on Earth to the ground,
and my will, the will to save human lives from fire,
when those desires...
Join as one.
GALO DE LION
Now our flames will burn out the entire Earth!
Total incineration of the entire planet Earth!
I'll extinguish you with my burning soul!
What did you do?
We satisfied the Promare's primal drive to burn.
We sent them back to their universe
and closed the dimensional rift.
There are no more Promare
and no more Burnish in this world anymore.
It wasn't supposed to be like this.
Whoo, yeah, what a blaze!
This is the beginning, a new beginning for this city.
Time to clean up after the fire.
Lio, you're gonna help too.
What?
We're low on manpower, so everyone's gotta do their part.
Let's get your friends to pitch in.
Wait.
Don't worry. If anybody gives you heat, I'll put 'em out.
Through spark and flame, I got your back.
I swear, Galo, you really are an idiot.
Yeah, I'm the universe's number one firefighting idiot!
Trails of fire
You always knew
They would carry me home
They'd lead me to you
Though you can't see the sun
A new day has begun
And I fall out of bed
To a siren call
In the frame on the wall
See you in fire
You guys are smiling at me
And you inspire
I down a coffee, grab my axe and then I'm out
I got a rage inside that's making me shout
get high on the fighting, you know
Inside my heart feelin' the inferno
Barely catchin' my breath
Lay my eyes on the crest
Gonna square up to all of the heat that is left
So, I carry the torch to inferno, inferno
It's out of the park
And I'm smilin' again
Here we go
I know, I know, I know, I know.
I will be here for you
Wherever you go
Yeah, I know.
I know, I know, I know, I know
I will be here for you
Wherever you go
Yeah, I know
Trails of fire
You always knew
They would carry me home
They'd lead me to you