[GIN] Joichiro?
Pardon me?
Gin?! What brings you here?
Business. I have a quick meeting
today with a company I'm doing
some work with.
I'm working too.
I'm here to cook some food.
What a coincidence.
"Coincidence," my ass!
Why don't you ever
get in touch?!
I thought maybe you were
dead in a ditch somewhere!
I've been worried sick about
you, do you realize that?!
I met your son, Soma, you know.
Oh, yeah? That's cool.
Listen, man...
Joichiro, it's been a while..
Yeah.
This calls for a celebration.
Let's drink!
I can't. I've made plans
for this meeting-
Come on, just blow it off!
Have a cold one with your old-
I can't, you pushy
son-of-a-bitch.
[cell phone ringing]
It's me. Is something wrong?
[GIN] (shock)
Wait, you're saying
Master Senzaemon is gone?
Azami?!
Azami Nakamura?
HE's the new director?!
[music playing]
[TSUKASA] Now then,
as a result of our latest vote,
the Totsuki Council of Ten
shall formally support
Azami Nakiri as the
new school director.
Let us consider
the matter closed.
[YUKI] Isshiki! Is it true that
we have a new school director?!
They say it was a majority vote
from the Council of Ten.
That's right, but,
I'm just as surprised as you.
I mean, I can't believe the
Ten had this scheme going,
and that someone would actually
show up to be the new director.
Don't you think it's messed up
that they can just do
something like this?!
[SATOSHI]
Not really. In terms of the
process, it was by the book.
The proposal was made and
the votes were cast
according to procedure.
Say, you know what,
if I remember correctly,
I heard the Totsuki's director
was always passed down
to the Nakiri family.
[hmm] Is that so?
I still think it was kinda
freakishly sudden.
Still, we don't have to
really worry, right?
It's got nothing at all
to do with us students?!
And yet...
Yeah?
Got something on your mind?
Well, this talk of aligning
with a new director,
wouldn't it have reached YOU,
before it happened, Isshiki?
[SATOSHI] (ulp)
[SOMA] Um, Erina,
why are you shaking?
[SATOSHI] Oh, you know what?
I do believe it's about to get
underway, isn't it?
The event to welcome the
director to his new post.
Welcome,
colleagues and friends.
I would like to thank you all
for gathering here today.
By the will of the
Totsuki Council of Ten,
I, Azami Nakiri,
will now be director,
and made to serve the academy.
The contributions to this school
of the prior director,
Master Senzaemon,
are many and varied.
And as his successor,
I feel a great sense of pressure
to fulfill these obligations
as justly as he did.
However, I know that this role
is a pivotal one in driving
Japan's culinary culture.
I am humbled by this,
and intend to push Totsuki
to even greater heights!
[applause]
Director, a car has been
prepared for you, sir.
[AZAMI  My apologies,
have them wait a bit longer.
I'd like to go for
a little walk.
It's only proper that Totsuki's
director turns his gaze
toward the future.
For this reason, I would like
to take a long, hard look
at the school as it stands.
Don't you see?
It's only YOUTH that allows one
to oppose the prior generation.
Physical strength must make up
for lack of experience.
He's not at all what I expected.
Yeah, I thought he'd be a bit
more stiff and one-sided,
but he seems like he might be
a really nice person.
The hell was all that?
It was just the other day
he showed us his true colors
with Ms Nakiri!
Yes! He spoke so abusively
before a roomful of people,
but now...
Erina,
what is all this nonsense?
Your cooking is not meant for
the likes of these people.
This encapsulates fine dining.
Its value should be shared with
only a select few of
chosen worth.
Only then is worth being
called "cuisine."
Or else it's not true
cooking at all; it is slop.
You know, he may not actually
think he was being abusive.
[KITA] 'xcuse me?
At the restaurant,
and now here today,
he's simply acting on his true
feelings and whatever he
thinks is right.
[NATSUME] Yes, very true.
He probably does exactly what he
wants, without any hesitation.
[AZAMI] Hisako Arato, yhank you
for your service up till now.
What?
You have my sincere gratitude.
I appreciate you
looking after Erina.
I am quite aware that your
presence has been
a tremendous help.
And I will always be in your
debt for taking her on.
[HISAKO] (shaky) Oh...
As of today, you are officially
relieved of your duties
as her servant.
Please, wait a minute!
I don't-
[AZAMI] I'm sure you agree.
Yes, Erina?
No, I don't, Father.
I would like Hisako to
remain with me as-
[AZAMI] But there's no need
to worry anymore.
Going forward you will always
have ME by your side.
Similarly, I will decide
all of your clientele.
That way, we will make
the most of your talents.
With your hand in mine,
we will push forward together.
Yes, Erina?
Yes, Father.
[FUMIO] Is Soma here?
Yes, he went up to
his room just now.
Is everything all right?
Yes, he has a visitor
here to see him.
At this time of night?
[SOMA] (sigh) Now that we have
a new director in place,
I can't help but wonder what
happened to the old one.
[gah!] He's HERE?
[SENZAEMON] (muscle flex)
[SENZAEMON] Soma Yukihira,
please forgive me for
this sudden intrusion.
Well, I don't mind, sir, but
do you need me for something?
Come to think of it, I believe
this is the first time
we've actually spoken
outside of competitions.
Yeah, I guess so.
It was I that suggested to
Joichiro that he should have
you attend Totsuki.
I hope you don' t mind.
When your father was here, he
was the No. 2 Seat on the Ten.
A position that was held highly.
Things didn't always
go smoothly,
but he truly was
a splendid chef.
So then that must mean you
and my dad got along
pretty well, huh?
[SENZAEMON] (chuckles)
Why don't we step outside
for a bit?
[SENZAEMON] My apologies
[SOMA] (panting)
for having you join in
my daily routine.
[SOMA] No problem.
Oddly, being relieved of
my duties as director
has been somewhat of a
surprising weight off
my shoulders.
[hearty laugh]
[out of breath] Oh, really?
That's good to hear, sir!
[pull up grunts]
So, what was it exactly that
you wanted to see me about?
[SENZAEMON] (hyah!)
Tell me, what kind of chef
would you say Erina is?
Hmh? Well, I would say...
That she's super picky
about taste.
And she's always on edge
about something or other.
Half of that is YOUR fault,
Soma Yukihira!
When she was little,
Erina was full of laughter.
Disgusting.
[ALICE] (waahh)
What the heck is your problem?
I made that dessert
especially for you, Erina!
Well, it just
doesn't taste good.
[about to cry]
But, um, thank you for
making this, Alice.
Huh?
I'm not gonna finish this, okay?
[ALICE] You gotta be kidding me!
(grrrr!!!!)
[giggles]
[ALICE] I want to go to Europe!
Please, Father!
Okay, the next time I see you,
I will have learned some
awesome cooking techniques
that will make you
want to eat my food.
When I'm back from Europe,
don't go getting all tearful
and sobby on me, okay?
What's with you?
You could at least wish me
good luck on my travels.
Um, Alice...
Please be sure to
always write me, okay?
[giggles]
[AZAMI] Erina, come here.
Yes, Father.
Where are we going?
[AZAMI] Erina,
do you want to become a chef?
Yes!
Good girl.
Then just follow me.
Now then, from today onwards,
I shall teach you the
meaning of "cooking."
[AZAMI] Tell me,
which of these is
seasoned correctly?
The right one?
The one on the left is putting
too much emphasis on
animal fats.
The flavor is unbalanced.
Very well done.
Now, be a good girl
and throw what's on the
other plate into the garbage.
What? But, um...
Wasting food doesn't seem like
the right thing to do.
[AZAMI] Do it.
You're hurting me!
Please don't!
Stop it, Father!
Do it, girl.
[fearful]
What a good girl you are.
[shaky breathing]
[AZAMI]
You must let go of sentiment.
TASTE is all that matters.
An ill-prepared dish
is unforgivable.
Anything that does not
meet my approval is...
Filth! Garbage! Trash!
Father doesn't approve,
so this food is nothing but...
Filth! Garbage! Trash!
It's nothing but trash.
Disgusting! Disgusting!
Disgusting!
You have some nerve serving
a dish like this to ME!
Apologize.
Azami Nakamura!
You are banned from Totsuki
until further notice!
That's quite perplexing
of you, Father.
For it's thanks to MY exacting
education that the God Tongue
will soon be fully realized.
[SENZAEMON]
This isn't education!
It's brainwashing!
You are far too dangerous.
You are forbidden to use
the Nakiri name ever again!
[SENZAEMON]
And so, Azami was finally
driven away from Totsuki
and from seeing his daughter.
After that, I heard he set
up operations overseas,
creating a community closed
to all but the wealthy,
his elitest followers.
I never dreamed he would worm
his way into the Ten and
instigate a rebellion.
He is without shame.
Erina, though brainwashed,
slowly began returning to her
old self once he was gone.
Hisako Arato, among several
others, were of great
help to her.
But somehow, Azami found out.
Erina's heart, that poor child,
is still trapped within a cage.
His methods are the same as
they were 10 years ago
when he was cast out.
I know him.
He will start to restrict
Erina's contact with others,
making HIM the only one
she can ever count on.
Back when Alice was in Europe,
he'd shred all the
letters she sent.
Erina once again will be
trapped in a place
where no voice can reach her.
And she will be forced into
doing what he expects from her.
[SENZAEMON] Soma Yukihira...
I would ask just
one thing of you:
I want you to save my
grandaughter, Erina!
I beg you!
[AZAMI] Now then, you can
only trust your father.
All else, you must cast aside,
Erina.
[ERINA] (pain)
F-Father, please stop!
I don't wanna do this anymore!
I don't like it!
Is that so?
I have no use for such a child.
[gasp]
[deep sigh]
Hisako's not here anymore.
I have only my father
by my side, no one else.
[ALICE] Erina! ERINA!
[ERINA] Alice?!
[ALICE] (straining)
[ALICE] Ryo! Just a little more!
[RYO] 'kay.
[ALICE]
And keep your eyes to yourself!
[RYO] 'kay.
What's going on, Alice?
[ALICE] What's it look like?
Well, don't just stand there!
We're here to break you out
of this stupid place!
[ERINA] (huh?)
[HISAKO] Ms Erina...
[ERINA] Hisako!
[ALL] (panting)
[ALICE] Well, if we've made it
this far, seems we weren't
being followed.
Alice, why are you doing this?
[ALICE] Hisako looks like
she's about to die.
[HISAKO] Ms Erina... Ms Erina...
Um, are you doing all right?
Alice, it's just, yadda-yadda,
homina-homina, blah, blah, blah!
Yes, I know already.
Uncle Azami is doing the
same thing to Erina now
that he did to her
when she was growing up.
I heard from Father and Mother
what our uncle was up to.
I always knew he was a
jerk wad from the start.
Also, my father spoke
to me as well.
[ALICE] I wrote you all
those letters, and yet...
You never wrote me
back even once.
Uh, well, that...
Yes, I know.
That's why this time,
I will not let Uncle Azami
get away with this!
Just run! That's what girls
these days have to do
when dealing with
scumbags like this.
Run away?
But I couldn't possibly go
against Father like that.
Stop sounding so pitiful
over there!
You don't have to always
put on a brave face, Erina!
So, uh...
[ALICE] What is it, Ryo?!
Leaving home is
all fine and good,
but where will she even go?
I think she'll need
a place to stay, don't you?
Hey, how about the
Arato mansion?
What?! People from the
Nakiri family are always
coming and going,
so it would be totally
impossible to hide her there!
Don't forget Alice and I
live on the grounds of
the Nakiri mansion.
Huh? Someone's gotta be able
to take her in somewhere?!
Don't refer to Ms Erina like
some she's abandoned cat!
Abandoned cat?
Oh, I know!
You can get a room in a hotel!
Erina doesn't know a thing
about the outside world, she
wouldn't last one minute!
[shocked]
'K!
In that case, I'll go with her!
If the both of you
disappear at the same time,
you'll immediately draw
suspicion and be found
sooner rather than later.
[HIASKO] We can like hire a
shadow warrior or get
a 3D printer!
[rain begins to fall]
I'll go back to the mansion.
Ms Erina!
[ERINA] If any of you get more
involved in this,
it will most likely end up
getting YOU in trouble as well.
But! Wait! Ms Erina!
[bushes rustling]
Who is it?!
What?
Why are you here?
[SOMA] Wow, it's really
coming down now, huh?
Sure enough, that's my cue
to start heading on back
to the dorm.
Soma Yukihira...
[SOMA] Look, I know Erina is
probably having a hard time
at home and everything...
but that doesn't
really involve me.
What I have to do right now was
decided a long time ago.
It's just like when I was
told when my food
was disgusting.
It's disgusting!
[SOMA] So it's like this...
I won't be able to rest
until I find a way to make
her say it's delicious!
Well, if you'll excuse me!
I'm out.
[chuckles]
It's just as you said,
Joichiro.
If Erina can be helped at all,
surely it will be by this boy
and his generation of
classmates.
Megumi Tadokoro,
what are you doing here?
I'd ask you the same.
Why are you here?
You're going to catch a cold.
Hurry up and come with me
to Kyokusei Dorm.
[door creaking open]
This is weird.
I...
I'll be staying here, now.
Uh, Hisako? What's up?
Well, that's actually
quite a long story...
Just run! That's what girls
these days have to do
when faced with
scumbags like this.
[SOMA] Wow, you ran away, huh?
Nice! I dig it.
Good job, Erina!
Don't make fun of me!
I'm not tryin' to make
fun of you at all.
But um, what happend to Nakiri
No. 2, where is she in all this?
Miss Alice and her servant
have already returned home.
Well, see you later!
They just took off?
A bath has already
been drawn for you.
You must be cold.
Go warm yourself up.
[AIDA]
Ms Erina isn't in her room.
[rain continues]
And it would seem that she left
accompanied by Miss Alice.
Shall I send some men
out after her?
[AZAMI]
That's Erina all right...
Yes, do that.
Go ahead and find out
where it is she has gone.
I am quite busy dealing with
some important matters
right now.
Tomorrow, the curtain rises
on our great revolution.
[YUKI] What? We're gonna help
Erina Nakiri hide out?
Like, she'll be right
here at Kyokusei?
But she's part of the
Nakiri family.
[hmm] Having someone that
important here in our dorm...
could cause some problems.
[SATO] I think it's better
to just bug out, man.
Are they gonna treat us like
vicious kidnappers or something?
So, why did she leave home
in the first place?
[RYOKO] Maybe something happened
to a member of her family.
[ERINA] (sigh)
All right then, I guess you all
need to be told what's going on.
Please, I ask that none of you
share this information
with anyone else.
I want you all to know what
Ms Erina has gone through,
so you will understand.
Um, thank you for allowing
me to take a bath.
Believe me, I am very grateful.
[ALL]
(chaotic screaming and sobbing)
This "Azami" guy sounds like
a real dill weed!
It's totally whacked, bro!
Yeah! That's no way for
a parent to act! Lame, dog!
Feel free to stay here as long
as you want, sweet little,
Erina-poo!
Erina-poo?!
[sobs and cries continue]
Hey, Erina, have you eaten?
No, not yet.
Then the timing is just perfect.
Everyone! We have a special
guest here visiting
Kyokusei Dorm!
What do you say we
hold a feast tonight?
[ALL] Yeah!
[ERINA] (uuhhh!)
[AOKI] White fish slow-cooked
in clarified butter!
Give it a little nibble!
Guess I don't have a choice,
do I?
Well, tell me whatcha
think of it?
[ERINA] I believe you have
made use of the ingredients'
intrinsic flavors.
I know! [chuckles]
But the use of clarified butter
has ended up muddling the taste.
The Vin Jaune and Macvin du Jura
in the sauce must be more
harmonious than this.
The comte cheese in the garnish
isn't a good match for the
soba-like flavor of the crozets.
That's a demerit. This could be
compared to stepping outside,
then finding yourself in
a sudden downpour and
falling into the mud.
In summary, it's no good at all.
[urk!]
WHATEVER! Who cares about some
prissy "God Tongue" anyway?!
YOU asked ME.
Let's see what you think
of MY dish, m'lady!
This is our chance to have the
God Tongue taste our food!
This is very exciting!
I'll bring something out
I smoked yesterday.
Hold on! I can't eat possibly
eat all that food in one night!
Erina-poo, have a big bite
out of my dish right here!
Are you even listening to me?!
Just look at her.
[YUKI] Erina=poo...
She seems to be feeling better.
[ERINA] All right, fine!
Seriously? She looks like
she's throwing a tantrum.
[HISAKO]
The thing is, I understand.
(babble continues)
When we first met each other,
as beautiful as she was,
it's like there was this
dark cloud that was just
hanging over her.
But slowly, bit by bit,
she was able to change.
[excited babble]
Oh, Soma,
you make something too!
Yeah, like some rad delicacy.
Sweet! Then just leave it to me!
[SOMA] There!
[gasp]
Huh? Is something the matter,
Erina?
I'm fine. It's nothing.
Incidentally, you should
know better by now.
I will not eat YOUR food!
You never change, do ya?
All right, then,
I wonder what I'll make?
[music playing]
[HISAKO] Okay, Soma, I'm asking
that you look after Ms Erina.
[rain continues]
Well, it makes no difference
to me either way,
but I think it does
to everyboady else.
Let's play cards!
ALL] Yeah!
[ERINA] Play cards?!
I hope Erina's father
learns something
from her running away from home
in the middle of the night.
I doubt things will go that
smoothly with her father.
After all, Ms Erina is the key
to Master Azami's plan.
He won't give up that easily.
[AZAMI] This is the method
that I shall introduce.
From here on out, this school
will become a utopia
of fine cuisine,
where all those with true
resolve can become the splendid
chefs they are meant to be.
How is THIS a utopia?
This is...
the Devil of Cuisine splitting
the world in two!
A dystopia!
[evil chuckle]