[ANNOUNCER] It's Rentaro
Kusunoki versus Ryo Kurokiba!
This friggin' Food War battle...
Starts NOW!
Amazing!
He cut that salmon in no time!
He sliced it so dramatically,
but it turned out so refined.
How exciting, Ryo has
developed even better skills
than when he battled me
at the Selection!
[shudder]
He's really great too!
His knife-work looks to be
about on par with Ryo's.
He's in Central.
What do you expect?
Of course, all those guys
are going to be top-level chefs.
So, what do you think of the
skills of your superior?
Are you regretting your decision
to challenge me?
Aww... No one likes a killjoy.
Oh? What is this?
It's rice!
[KUSUNOKI] (huh?)
[OIZUMI]
Plus, he has two varieties.
And what's in that bowl?
It's bread dough!
What does young Ryo
intend to make for us?!
[RYO]
What I'm gonna make now is...
the absolute BEST fish dish!
You cannot lose. Got it Ryo?
What do you think now, Central?!
You stand there lookin'
self-satisfied,
but you're just a poor man's
version of ME!
[KUSUNOKI] (huh?)
Come at me with
everything you've got,
you pretentious "elite" bastard!
What's your problem? You looking
for an excuse to lose?!
Soma and Takumi talked a whole
lot of smack as well,
but you have a knack for
infuriating people, don't you?
But rest easy,
for I already decided to show
you the full extent of my skill.
And I'll even show you my cute
little friends, while I'm at it.
What's that?
[ALICE] (small gasp)
Take a look,
you pansy-ass of a chef.
[music playing]
[student cheering]
[ANNOUNCER B]
Thank you for participating.
That concludes today's
B Venue Food Wars.
Central has won all matches.
Hey dude, you record that?
Yeah, man. Those were some
awesome matches, bro.
That's the No. 6 Seat,
Nene Kinokuni.
[ZENJI] She's the next
seat above Isshiki.
They say she's the best chef
among all the 2nd-years.
[YUKI] No way!
So many clubs and seminars took
the Food War challenge,
and yet they still lost!
To think, they didn't win
a single one.
Damn! This is all going
exactly the way Azami Nakiri
wanted it to!
I've seen those things before.
Alice Nakiri used them at
the Selection finals.
[ALICE]
It's a steam convection oven,
and a cryogenic grinder.
[THREE] (huh?)
But, Rentaro Kusunoki,
will you be able to properly use
the very latest equipment?
[KUSUNOKI] We've got a pretty
good size crowd here today,
so I hope you don't mind ...
if I make you look bad
to make me look good.
"Steam convention"?
Yeah,
it's a steam conVECtion oven.
That's correct, Takumi.
It uses an interior fan
to evenly circulate the
steam and heat.
Then the steam and heat are
automatically and digitally
controlled,
making it a revolutionary device
that let's you do all kinds
of cooking with one unit.
Also, it doesn't
transfer any aromas,
allowing you to cook different
sorts of dishes all at once.
[MOMO](grr...)
Oh,yeah?! That's cool!
In the hands of the right chef,
it's kind of a dream machine.
But because there are
so many different settings,
it requires a deep understanding
of how it works.
[MOMO] (grrr...)
It's a device that will surely
test your intelligence
of ingredients and
cooking methods.
[SOMA]
Still, it's sort of unexpected.
I mean, will that guy be
able to properly use
those types of things?
Like, he's too hot-headed
and always going off
about something.
Now, now Soma!
True, he doesn't seem
to be that smart.
I can't imagine that
cutting-edge technologies
are within his range.
[MEGUMI] Not you too, Takumi?
[MEA] (laughing)
You just say it like it is, huh?
You guys are fun!
[MEA] The thing is...
If it bothers you that much,
then watch.
You're about to be lucky enough
to witness Reni's
amazing cooking.
[MEGUMI]
He's taken the fillets and...
marinated them!
Those are long, thin cuts...
[MEGUMI]
He's wrapped them in bacon!
Doing that will make it fattier
as well as saltier.
[SOMA]
Oh! He's using the steam thingy!
For an internal temperature
of 45 degrees,
I need to heat it at 60 degrees
Celsius for 18 minutes.
Reni is a specialist
at gauging heat.
As well as a master of
low-temperature cooking.
Now you just do your thing!
Low-temperature cooking?
As I'm sure you already know,
when cooking,
the protein in fish and meat
start to break down at about
58 degrees Celsius.
But when the temperature
reaches 68 degrees,
the flesh contracts even more
and becomes stiff.
So, if you cook
between 58-68 degrees,
it doesn't put so much
stress on the ingredients,
which in turn, will then leave
the flesh nice and tender.
And that my friends,
is the basic premise behind
low-temperature cooking.
[giggle] Exactamundo!
The steam convection oven!
Water baths!
Pass circulators!
Gastro packs!
He's got it all.
He's learned all of the latest
in heating technologies!
THAT is Reni,
Rentaro Kusunoki!
[KUSUNOKI] Proper heating...
if you can master it,
you can compete in any field
you ever dreamt of!
Heat and flame...
I shall reach the very pinnacle
of these techniques!
It looks like he's finally
started to concentrate, huh?
When it's time to heat
the ingredients,
he suddenly gets calm
and composed.
It's like that
constant heat of his
gets transferred to the food
that he's preparing.
[timer buzzes]
What the?!
Look how it glistens!
It's completely different from
when it was put in the oven!
That really is quite beautiful.
You can tell by looking at it,
how tender it is!
It has reached its
peak tenderness,
where a dull knife could
slice through it as if
it was warm butter.
That looks so incredible.
It's like his soul really has
gone into his cooking.
I'm shocked.
He's a great cook.
[TAKUMI] The salamander.
The salamander?
The heck is that?
The name's super fun
to say though!
[ALICE] It comes from a kind of
fire lizard that appeared in
medieval European folklore:
the salamander.
That's the origin of the name.
In cooking, it's a blanket term
for an oven that heats from
above rather than below.
Oh, I get it.
I bet I could use that.
[ALICE]
It's used to cook the surface,
so as to give it
more depth of flavor.
He's now browning it
because he's reached
the final stage of his dish.
[KUSUNOKI] Finished.
I call this beauty,
"Saumon confit flamme."
"Flamme" if you don't know
is French for "flame."
Now then, enjoy the artistry
that comes through fire.
This is the dish
that made him "chosen".
It's the one that caught
Central's attention
in the first place.
[KUSUNOKI] Oh, that's right.
Chef Momo, would you please
try my cooking as well?
Why are you giving it to me?
[KUSUNOKI] This plate contains
a gimmick, if you will,
something made using sweets.
There's sweets?
I think you'll find
that you like it.
Is that supposed to be
some sorta challenge?
I'm very picky when
it comes to sweets.
[ANNOUNCER] Our first tasting is
Rentaro Kusunoki's offering.
At last!
Oh...
It's sparkling!
And the delectable rich aroma
of the roasted fats!
True, the plating and aroma
are nice, but what matters
is TASTE.
[OIZUMI] (rising yell)
[MOM] (delighted squeal)
[ALL] It is delicious!
[OIZUMI] I'm dizzy!
The interior looks almost
completely raw!
It has an incredibly
mild flavor.
But then, the exterior!
That's where the smoky,
rich flavor from the
salamander comes in!
It shows off his mastery
of the flame!
Yeah, well, it is pretty good.
Let's try this garnish here...
Okay, I see...
This garnish is actually
salmon ice cream,
and it was made without
using any sugar.
[MAN] What?!
Is that even possible?
[WOMAN] Salmon ice cream?
[MAN 2] How'd he do that?
You used the cryogenic grinder,
didn't you?
Very nicely done, Alice!
I took the salmon paste I'd made
in the blender and froze it,
then let it set in the
cryogenic grinder,
and since the blades move at
extremely high speeds,
it resulted in a fine,
smooth ice cream.
Once you allow your tongue to
invite the chilling cold of
the ice cream,
it makes the heat of the
lightly cooked salmon
stand out even more!
[OIZUMI] The different
temperatures elevate
the presence of the salmon
dancing on your taste buds.
That's thermal sense!
It's a technique that
Alice Nakiri used as well,
during the Selection.
Temperature, flame,
and correct timing.
All these act together
as my special "seasoning"!
[MOMO] It's true!
The differing temperatures
really draw out
the flavor of the
theme ingredient.
It's like being in the middle
of a cold, clear stream,
and then suddenly the hot,
tender salmon leaps out.
My body...
It's getting so worked up!
No! This unending
onslaught of salmon...
It's too much!
[contented sigh]
[MAN] Well, that settles it.
[FEMALE] Looks like this match
is going to Central again.
Rentaro nailed it.
Better not decide just yet...
Till AFTER you've seen what
I've just created.
Feast your eyes on MY dish...
Coulibiac!
He made a Coulibiac?
[ERINA] It's so quiet.
[HISAKO] If anyone can save
Totsuki from the hand
of Master Azami,
HE would be the one capable
of pulling it all off, right?
[SATOSHI] Hey! Is anyone there?
Oh! How're you doin', Erina?
[ERINA] (urk!)
Do you perhaps know
where everybody went?
[ERINA] (screams)
I thought my heart was going
to leap out of my chest!
[SATOSHI] Um, you okay?
[SATOSHI] Oh,
everyone went to go watch?
That should be fun.
The Food War Alice
is involved with
should be going on right now.
[ERINA] Huh? Alice? But why?
Curious about how things
are going out there?
[OIZUMI] Coulibiac!
Oh, yeah...
Now I see it.
So that's why he had bread
dough at the ready.
So what kind of dish is it?
It's basically salmon,
rice, and seasoning,
all wrapped in brioche dough
and then baked -
a French adaptation of a dish
popular in the royal courts
of 19th century Russia.
The filling uses mushrooms,
shallots, and other vegetables,
then takes all of that and
combines it with grains.
The two kinds of rice are
butter rice and kasha,
which is primarily eaten
in the Eastern European region
and is made of cooked buckwheat.
Oh! I can smell the richness of
both the dough and the salmon!
Just look how juicy it is!
You can see the butter-rice
mixed with the kasha
and other ingredients!
Quit yer yappin' and eat before
it gets cold, you old farts.
The salmon is gonna EXPLODE
with so much flavor,
your tongue won't be able to
fight the delicious invader
wrestling in your mouth!
[BOTH] (ulp)
[BOTH] (blissful moans)
I can't even talk!
The ingredients are
all so delicious,
and wrapped tightly in
that brioche dough!
The main flavors are fish,
rice, buckwheat, vegetables,
and bread!
This packs them all
into a single dish!
[OIZUMI]
The juices are bursting with
the umami of the salmon.
This dish is rocking my brain
to the very core!
[ALICE] (giggles)
You want to try it?
I went up and grabbed some
from Ryo.
No, I couldn't!
Y... oh, yes, please.
It's like the bread dough is
packed with the concentrated
ENERGY of the salmon.
It's such a powerful sensation!
Oh... oh, no!
This kind of overwhelming
direct hit...
[estatic scream]
Oh god! I can't escape it!
[sigh] Delicious!
Yeah, thatta way to knock it
to 'em, Ryo!
It's the perfect fusion of a
dish from the royal courts
and the skilled hand of a chef,
who sharpened his fangs
living in a port town.
It feels as if it could have
been made by both of them,
as they've battled
these many years.
[MAN]
So, who's gonna be the winner?
[students muttering]
[MAN 2]
It has to be Rentaro, right?
[WOMAN]
I'm thinking Ryo Kurokiba!
[ANNOUNCER] And now, judgment!
They... they're even.
[BOTH] (huh?)
I can't say that one's
any better than the other.
All I can think is that BOTH
of them have created the
best possible salmon dish!
No need to rush.
If we just taste and compare,
we'll know.
There must be a definitive
gap between the two.
A definitive gap? It looks like
they both put out dishes
that can't possibly be topped.
Don't overlook the most
important point:
to place judgment on the
umami of the salmon!
It's also highly likely that
both dishes have some kind
of secret hidden in them.
[giggle] That has to be why
Renni decided to use the
convection oven.
I think the judges have
already noticed it.
[KUSUNOKI] Very observant, Mea.
The answer is THIS.
It looks like that
might be olive oil.
[MEGUMI] Ah!
[SOMA] Huh...
That would be the deciding
difference between the
two dishes:
the succulent amount of moisture
that the salmon retains.
That's a good thought, Mea.
When wrapping the salmon
to cook it over low heat,
I don't apply heat until after
I've placed them in olive oil.
Normally, even if you take
the time to go about carefully
wrapping the fish securely,
the sheer weight of the dish
itself applies pressure,
which in turns can cause the
fish to lose all of
it's moisture.
That's where the
olive oil comes in.
The buoyancy of the fat
allows you to apply heat
without having to
apply any pressure.
Now, that's juicy.
Yes! Yes, that's right!
I mean when I was eating this
dish, it just completely
fell apart in my mouth.
Despite how long it was cooked,
it was surprisingly
not dry at all!
All of it, from corner to
corner, was just so juicy.
It's lost no moisture!
His handling of the ingredients
may very well have exceeded that
of Ryo Kurokiba!
It can't!
[SOMA] Incredible...
But Ryo is a true expert at
handling his seafood!
You understand yet that6
I'm on a whole different level?
What was that, that thing
you made in the finals
for the Selection?
Ah, that's right,
it was called a cartoccio.
For that,
as well as this coulibiac,
you stuffed ingredients into
something and cooked it.
While you did manage to come
up with a well-rounded
and flavorful umami
that's way too simplistic,
if you ask me.
One must perfectly preserve
the moisture of the ingredients
while delicately applying heat.
This truly is something you
cannot ever hope to copy,
the ELITE art of the flame!
In this Food War,
that vast difference is obvious!
Isn't that so, O judges?
Sure enough,
you haven't grown at all
since losing at the
Fall Selection.
Using umami so bold
and explosive
that it overwhelms a
person's taste buds?
Please, there are much more
elegant approaches than
resorting to such tactics.
Still, I wouldn't mind
if you came over and kept
doing your thing, under ME.
[SOMA] The thing is,
the match isn't over yet.
[MEA] (huh?)
I haven't tasted either
one of their dishes,
but even I get it.
There's just one problem
with what Chef Rentaro was
saying about his dish.
There is clearly one dish here
that elevates the salmon,
in both deliciousness
and in the umami.
And that dish belongs to...
[MOMO] (mmm)
the Cutting-Edge challenger,
Ryo Kurokiba!
What the?!
That's right.
There is no mistake.
The dish that best expresses the
salmon is Ryo Kurokiba's!
[SOMA  Yeah!
HUUUHH?! What is this?!
What are you saying, old man?
My heat was applied perfectly.
How could it possibly be
inferior to THAT?
[RYO] Oh, whatever.
Just shut up already.
If you can't accept it,
[KUSUNOKI] (grr...)
then just try some!
Eat my big tasty coulibiac!
Wh-what?!
The umami...
The umami of the salmon just
keeps coming,
crashing into you
like the raging rapids!
I don't understand how
this is even a possibility!
What is in there?
There's some green layer wrapped
around the inside of the bread!
Lemme tell you something,
Central.
I've changed quite a bit
since competing in
the Selection.
That is a crepe lined
with spinach!
A crepe?
[MEGUMI] Oh, that's it!
That's what the soft,
delicate bite was,
it was spinach!
I knew it tasted like
something familiar to me.
It really brought out the umami
of the fattiness of the tuna.
Ah, man, that looks SUPER
delish, all right!
A layer of brioche and a
layer of crepe,
that's truly incredible!
But that can't be all!
There must be
something else behind it.
Something for the
raging flood of umami!
It was this:
the crepe was flavored
with a special seasoning.
Special seasoning?
Yes, it's an original blend of
his, a mixture of spices.
This special seasoning has
a mixture of thyme, oregano,
garlic, and rock salt,
as well as a little something
called dried bacon powder!
Bacon?!
But I used that in my dish!
Ah! Strangely, both used bacon
as a focal point in their dish.
But the application was very
different from each other.
Rentaro wrapped his bacon
around the salmon
and then cooked it at low heat
to bring out the flavor.
Much like the standard broth
of ramen, which combines
pork bone and seafood,
this allows the umami of both
to fuse while not losing
a drop of flavor.
This dish perfectly preserves
the deliciousness of the salmon.
But, wait!
If that's the case,
what could have been wrong
with Reni's plate?
The answer to that
is disproportion.
[MEGUMI] What'd he say?
You see, it has to do with the
way the human tongue's arranged.
It tends to respond more
to flavors that are
disproportionate
rather than those that
are uniform.
It's like how a lot of people
like milk in their coffee.
Or how some like sesame seed
oil in their ramen.
It's basically the same
principle of mixing flavors.
Yeah, totally. Putting an egg
in your rice and stirring it
all up is pretty delicious.
Then it's all up to you to add
however much soy sauce
you want in it.
That's exactly what I was after
in making this.
I added just a small amount
of the seasoning.
So, there were bites where
you taste the umami of
the salmon as-is,
and other parts where
it tastes much richer
because it was mixed with the
flavor of the added bacon.
That's why each time
you take a bite,
it just keeps hitting
your tongue,
getting more and more
delicious every time.
It's like a constant barrage
of the salmon's flavor
knocking you down!
That's a world of flavor your
salmon would never even
hope to reach
if all you ever expect to do
is wrap it up in some bacon!
At first, Rentaro looks
to be more impressive,
but the softness of Ryo's bread
and the crepe elevates
the umami to a new level,
pushing the salmon
to the front.
He came up with the idea to
add spice to make it
non-uniform on purpose?
You should've been nothing
more than some amateur to help
me practice new techniques.
There's no way you came up
with something this refined
at the Selection!
You better believe it.
[OWNER]
Hey! What are you doing?!
I allowed you to come and
be a member of my kitchen
as part of your Stagiaire.
You need to work much harder!
[RYO] 'kay.
Dammit! Of all things, it
had to be a curry restaurant.
And now, I can't help but think
of that guy's ugly smug face.
[RYO] I'm done.
Can you check it?
No! Awful!
You know nothing of spices
or depth of flavor.
I was hoping for the student who
actually WON the Selection!
He was wonderful at spices, yes?
Unlike yourself!
Yeah.
How are you doing over there,
Ryo?
Are things going well
with your Stagiaire?
[RYO] As well as expected.
[ALICE]
You haven't lost your temper
with the shop owner, have you?
[RYO] (doh!) Not yet, no.
It doesn't seem like this
thing will ever end.
It's taking forever.
But we have to get over how
we feel about losing
at the Selection, don't we?
Yes, you're right.
I'll do it. Watch me.
As long as I'm here,
I'll learn everything there
is about how to use spice.
I WILL make it mine!
[chuckles] So, it's NOT like
you haven't changed since the
Selection have you, eh, Ryo?
[RYO] I'm not the same as
I was back then.
To me, your damn salmon is...
no better than frozen!
[KUNUSOKI] (screams)
[OIZUMI]
Victory goes to Kurokiba!
Ryo Kurokiba is the winner!
[music playing]