[SOMA] A televised address?
Yeah, the new director supposed
to be holding it today.
They say it's going to air live
across the whole campus.
[SOMA] Woah...
Still,
for Erina to leave home...
She must have some pretty big
reasons to do something
like that.
But will she be okay
staying there?
If word gets out that she's
holed up in the school dorm...
[hmmm]
Yeah, who's to really say?
Hisako has been coming by to
bring her fresh clothes
and stuff every day.
And Nakiri No. 2 and Ryo
have been stopping by as well.
[ALICE] Hey!
Still, it looks like her
secret is safe.
No, I'd say it's not really
a secret at all anymore!
I'm coming to you live
from the scene.
Azami Nakiri, the new director,
has arrived to make an
announcement!
Students of Totsuki,
you have my thanks.
I'm Azami Nakiri.
[music playing]
Students of Totsuki,
you have my thanks.
I'm Azami Nakiri.
This pasty guy is Erina-poo's...
Yeah! That's her piece weak nut
father dude up there.
[ZENJI] He was on the
Council of Ten, too?
Allow me to be honest with you.
I'm here to share my vision
of the perfect world,
one where Totsuki Academy
is reborn, and exactly
what that involves.
The first point is this...
Beginning immediately,
all cooking-related
lectures and seminars,
as well as study groups
and societies,
hereby, are stripped of all
rights to operate autonomously!
[shocked]
What?
He's gonna take our rights?!
The dial is at zero...
and everything ends NOW.
[STUDENT] What did he say?!
What the hell?
Are you kidding me?!
On to the second point...
A new organization shall be
established on campus.
It will be an elite corps,
comprising of myself and the
Council of Ten at the top,
as well as any students
I personally choose, with the
goal of seeking out new cuisine.
It shall be a world of gods,
where knowledge of all things
delicious is exchanged:
The Central Institution
for Fine Cuisine: or, "Central."
"Central Institution"?
Starting today and going
forward from now on,
everything you make
will be decided by the
members of Central.
Which means, you no longer have
to conceive of your own dishes.
My apologies, but any who
disagree with this method will
be asked to leave the school.
Huh? How dare you?!
[angry students]
Someone needs to
put you in your place!
[STUDENT A] What?!
[STUDENT B] I just don't get it!
Come now, if you would
just think about it.
The system up until now
has been quite illogical.
Those who fail to achieve under
the merit-based systems
are simply let go,
regardless of the proven fact
that chefs are highly known
to develop at their own speed.
Do you not find that this
is needlessly cruel?
So just let me state, from now
on, all cooking lectures,
and all teaching will be
held at Central.
All will have equal opportunity
to reap its benefits.
In time, EVERYONE will aquire
the techniques and skills
to one day be on the same
level as with the Ten.
Shut your mouth! How can you
even call yourself a chef?!
It will be a new world free
from conflict without merit.
Unnecessary expulsions!
Unnecessary exclusion!
Unnecessary competitions!
You will be freed
from all of these!
Listen up!
You are not pawns
to be sacrificed.
You are the all-important force
upon which the future of
Totsuki shall be built.
Join with me.
And together we'll advance the
culinary scope of this country.
[RINDO] (hmph!)
[KABUTOYAMA]
He's screwing with us!
There's no way we can
accept this sort of crap!
[GIRL] Y-yeah, but still...
We can get the Ten's
"leftovers," right?
I mean, that's sure to be
of some benefit in the future,
right?
Don't you think?
What the hell are you saying?!
I will NOT bow to tyranny!
Tetsuji Kabutoyama of the
Skewered Research Society,
I have a message from Central.
[MAN 2] As of today,
the Regional Cuisine
Research Society is closed.
Please clear out your room
immediately.
[IKUMI] You... you bastards!
You better leave right now
if you don't want your
asses handed to you!
The matter has already
been decided.
Please know that your
only choice is to comply with
Central, Prof. Miyazato.
This can't be!
Professor!
Is the Miyazato Seminar
really coming to an end?!
[EIZAN] As I'm sure you know,
Kyokusei is the only dorm
on school grounds.
Until today, you have managed to
support yourselves financially.
But make no mistake,
it has made you a target
for removal.
This dormitory will be
razed to the ground.
It's no longer of any
real use to Totsuki.
"No longer of any real use"?
You're taking Kyokusei
and knocking it down?!
Both the building and the
property itself will be taken
over by those in Central.
So in other words,
this place will no longer
be yours.
I'd like to see you try, bro!
[SATO]
You dudes suck! Like hard!
Whatcha lookin' at?
You want a piece of me, huh?
Yuki, please!
[Yuki] You sonofa goat herder!
Say, where is Isshiki?
He's a member of the Ten.
If he were here, these guys
wouldn't be able to just
barge in like this.
He'd need to actually be here
for that to happen, but he
hasn't been here for awhile.
Is Miyazato Seminar
in trouble too?!
[SOMA] Well, as long as we're
standing around talking,
have some tea or something,
please.
[SHUN] Have...
[RYOKO] ...some...
[AOKI] ...tea...
[SATO] ...or...
[ZENJI] ...some...
[YUKI] ...thing...
[MEGUMI] ...please?
[SOMA] Why do you even want
to knock our dorm down?
I thought heard we were
kind of like some sort of
an independent nation.
I mean why would the school
interfer with us now?
[EIZAn] You've just answered
your own question.
Having an autonomous
organization other than Central
on campus would pose a problem.
We don't need two
quarreling bodies.
This is our final
decision on the matter.
These documents state when
you'll be expected to vacate.
BUT you can rest easy.
So long as you toe the line
and do as Central says,
you can all remain
here as students.
Mind if I cut in?
The decision to knock
down the dorm...
It can be reversed, right?
Through a Food War?
Soma!
Absolutely! You are correct.
Any decision made by Central
can be overturned through
a victory in a Food War.
But that rests entirely on
whether one of us would
willing to accept.
We are under absolutely no
obligation to engage in
any sort of Food War.
And currently, we're being
flooded with requests
from almost every
organization in the Academy.
It would seem people aren't too
happy with the new policies.
Now, simply doing nothing
would lead to their ruin,
but in my case, I actually
sympathize with their
plight to be heard,
and have decided that
I will accept.
[ALL] (shocked!)
Huh? Doing a Food War
when you don't have to?
That's mighty big of you.
Of course, my opponent
must also take on
an appropriate amount of risk.
But I'm fairly certain you
probably realize that.
I already have a Food War
scheduled for today.
Why don't you come see
how it turns out?
And if you still wish
to move forward,
you can come at me however
you deem necessary,
Soma Yukihira.
[drum beats]
You're mine, Eizan!
I won't let you disband
Skewer Society.
The theme is Largehead Hairtail-
Yes, I get it.
And I'll be sure to include
a skewering technique
during preparation.
Now then, if you lose,
you leave the school.
I take it you have
no complaints?
Yeah, whatever.
You will learn the full weight
of the skills I've honed.
Day in, and day out I've-
Okay, enough with the
blabbering already.
I'm going to take your best dish
and destroy it.
So come on,
give me everything you've got!
And now, Food War!
So it begins!
[RYOKO] It's started.
[SATO]
Give 'em hell, Skewer-Soc!
He can do it!
Yeah! It's not over yet!
If he can win this...
Then, we can totally
save this place.
And I will never give up easily!
We can still take them down...
ALL] ...by beating them
in a Food War!
What is he doing?
He doesn't look like
he's concentrating on
his dish at all.
Something's off...
No matter how much he goes out
there and crushes Kabutoyama,
I don't think it's gonna make
other research societies or
seminars back down.
So then, what did Chef Eizan
mean about this being
a "warning"?
It is now time for judgment!
[hmm] What is this?
What the?
This is weird!
Look, the readout's
broken or something.
It's showing a score even though
no one's tried anything yet.
[ALL] (evil chuckles)
[KABUTOYAMA] Huh?
Eizen, don't tell me...
You got to the judges?!
Too bad, Skewer Boy!
[evil laugh
[ANNOUNCER] We have a winner!
Skewer-Soc is hereby dissolved!
Hold on, Eizan!
Can't believe you would
cook for bought judges!
Cut the crap! This kind of
"Food War" means nothing!
This is simply outrageous!
[EIZAN] Well now, Kabutoyama...
Say goodbye.
[EIZAN] Looks like you're out.
Can't be!
This is a whole
different Totsuki
you're dealing with now.
That's some evil stuff
right there!
So the judges dudes
are on the take?!
Our safety net is now ruined!
Just how dirty can that
bastard Eizan get?!
This is a losing battle.
He turned every one of
the judges against us!
None of them would even
bother tasting the food!
If we can't even get a proper
competition, then that means...
Whether we challenge him
to a Food War or not,
the outcome will be the same.
No matter what we do,
Kyokusei is finished!
Bro, you gotta be kiddin' me!
There's nothing we can do,
our home is gonna get torn down!
What should we do?
Erina, you'll lose your hiding
place if they take it!
Well, Soma?
Let this be the "warning"
to you all.
The Food War is
dead and buried.
[SECRETARY]
Chief, are you all right?
Yesterday's Food War was
something of a shock to me.
This is a disaster.
I can't believe Eizan would
actually buy off the judges!
Hey, how's it going, Chief?!
[door slams open]
Chef Eizan!
You can't just come barging in!
What's the matter with you?
I just came by to
confirm something.
[door slams]
I heard a rumor that we'd
received over 100 applications
challenging me to a Food War.
I just wanted to see where
that number stands now.
[grrr...]
Well, they've...
They've all been cancelled.
[EIZAN] (maniacal chuckle)
What a shame!
I suppose wonders never cease,
do they?
I had my heart set on doing a
whole BUNCH of challenges.
[KAGEURA] (grrr...)
[TEACHER] As of today, you'll
be working off of this menu,
which Central has decided
was the best recipe.
This method of cooking will
be the standard here at
Totsuki from now on.
Now, let's do our best!
What are you doing?
Those ingredients are to be
braised in the oven.
Did you not bother to read
what the recipe said to do?
I mean, it's written right
there in the instructions,
isn't it?
As far as I know, this is
how it's always been done,
so I see no reason for us
to change it now.
You're just a student.
There is no need for you to
weigh in on this.
Central's word is absolute
for all recipes.
Don't do it again.
[SHUN] (grr...)
[ZENJI]
Oh, Regional Cuisine got the
order to disband too, huh?
[MEGUMI] (uhm)
And Miyazato Seminar?
Yeah.
And the other groups are
getting handed their notices.
Unfortunately, we have
no options in trying to
repeal it, either.
We have 10 days till
we need to leave the dorm.
There's no way out of it now.
[sigh]
[RYOKO] Erina?
Are you okay?
Why are you in here with
the lights off?
It's about time for dinner,
so let's head down.
Umm, Ryoko!
Sorry, no, it's nothing.
Oh, come on now.
It's gonna get cold,
so let's hurry up and
get to the table, okay?
Do you think they'd actually
get rid of this dorm?
Looks like it.
[dispirited sigh] Well,
guess there's nothing we can do.
This old dorm is gonna be gone
just like that, huh?
But it's always been here
for us. It'll be weird.
Dude, looking back, we've sure
been through a lot, haven't we?
I was super surprised by
Ms Fumio's dorm entrance test,
ya know?
It took me three months to
pass her test, but I
remember during that time,
Ms Fumio was so kind to let me
stay in the barn while I
kept trying.
[agog] For real?
I had no idea you
slept in the BARN!
You may notlook it,
but you're pretty tough.
You know that, Megumi?
In all ways!
And remember when Soma
transferred to the
High School Division?
I might as well
take the top spot.
See a few of you at graduation!
[outraged shouts from crowd]
Oh wow, we all have such
fond memories here.
[MEGUMI] I know, right?
[ZENJI] Then there was the time
we all made it through the
training camp from Hell.
[YUKI] I really had no idea what
would happen when Megumi had
a Food War with Chef Kojiro!
[startled gasp!]
A Food War?!
Oh, it was nothing!
[RYOKO] Summer vacation...
[SHUN] The Fall Selection...
[AOKI]
And then, the Lunar Feast!
[SATO] We totally killed
that hot pot party, huh?
[YUKI] Soma and Megumi's
Chinese food stall!
[RYOKO] And we've always made
lots of food together, huh?
[MEGUMI] Yeah, we really have!
[ZENJI] So many good times...
[YUKI] There really have
been so many things, huh?
I mean, like, if we started
talking about them,
we'd never stop!
So many things, I just can't...
You okay there?
My heart can't take any of this!
I don't want Kyokusei to be
taken away and gone forever!
[BOTH] (aww...)
[YUKI] I wanna spend
more time with you all!
More... MORE time!
[sobbing]
I wanted to spend more time
cooking together!
Yuki...
[MEGUMI] (beginning to sob)
[begins to sob as well]
[ALL] (sobbing wildly)
[YUKI] It's so unfair!
This place,
Kyokusei Dormitory...
What was it like for you
living here?
I had a blast.
Everyone brushing up on
their cooking skills,
in whatever way they liked...
Huh?!
What the helll do you
think you're doing?
Come on now, don't do something
stupid, Soma Yukihira.
Do you still not understand
the situation you're in?
The judges are all on my side.
It's not a matter of
winning or losing,
they won't even taste it.
See, the minute you enter that
ring, you're gonna be done for.
And yet, you still want
to have a Food War?
[SOMA] Yep.
Did you grow tired of
listening to the weeping
of your dormmates?
I understand wanting to help
your friends and trying to
play the hero, but...
Just stop already.
Foolishness and bravery
aren't the same thing.
That's nice, but I'm not really
doing it for dormmates.
Why then?
Easy...
It's for me.
Kyokusei is my castle,
which I've used to
hone my cooking.
So guess what!
You won't knock down my dorm.
Got it?
Accept this Food War.
[EIZAN] (grr...)
[SECRETARY] Chief, look!
What's that?
An actually Food War?!
[YUKI] "I'm off to challenge
Chef Eizan to a Food War.
I cooked up some curry
and left it in the fridge.
Everyone, microwave it
and have some.
Sincerely, Soma Yukihira"
What is he doing?
Is he crazy?
But why?
Why would he go off on his own?
Is he making sure
we don't get involved?
What the heck has he done?!
He's a member of
Kyokusei like us!
So then why?
Why do it?
Why act as if he's
alone in this?!
And at this rate, Soma's sure to
be expelled from...
[front door opening]
Ms Erina!
Turn on the TV!
You gotta check out
what's on the campus feed!
It's Soma!
Yeah, look, it's on right now!
Attention,
a Food War has been accepted.
I repeat,
there will be a Food War!
Etsuya Eizan has
accepted the challenge.
The competition will
begin any moment!
[EIZAN]
The theme ingredient is...
local Satsuma chicken
from Kagoshima.
It has a fair degree of fat,
and is known for having
an unique texture,
and depth of umami.
Hey, are you even
listening to me?!
What are you doing, you idiot?
Just checking out the
ingredients, dude.
This is YOU, I'm dealing with.
Never know when you're gonna
try to pull some dirty trick,
after all.
[heh!] Well, fine then.
Do what makes you feel good.
It's all for naught, anyway.
[door flys open]
Jerk! What you are doing, Eizan!
[urk!] What the hell are
you doing here, Rindo?
You will address me as
your superior, you got that?
Would you shut up
and get outta here?!
This area is for involved
parties only, okay?! [ugh!]
You better start showing
some respect!
[EIZAN] (painful sounds)
Hey, how ya doing Soma?
Running off half-cocked
as always, aren't you?
Hello there, it's been quite
a while, Chef Rindo.
Yeah, that's the thing.
This has turned into
one heck of a ride!
Thanks to Azami Nakiri's
revolution, things are
changing all over campus,
and the members of the Ten are
super busy making documents
and doin' official business.
We're practically
dead in the water!
[hmm?]
Well, I went ahead and
put all that on Tsukasa.
[SOMA] (uh...)
I'm gonna start prepping,
so I'll take the
interior kitchen.
[JUDGE] (evil laugh)
I wouldn't think that, after
the Food War the other day,
there would be any one dumb
enough to challenge Central.
I take it this person must
be quite the simpleton.
Shall we just taste
YOUR dish Eizan,
and then leave the
challenger's on the table?
Do whatever you wish.
I'll look forward to your
final "judgment" today as well.
[JUDGE] Of course!
Well then, see you soon.
[RINDO]
What a pity for you, Eizan.
But as I recall, the real goal
behind this little "warning"
as you like to call it,
was actually to break soma's
fighting spirit, was it not?
Yet not only did he NOT break,
but he managed to come in
right after behind you.
[EIZAN] (hmph)
But don't let it
get to you though.
That's just the hardheaded
little bratty punk he's
grown up to be. [oh?]
Is it ready?
Good.
Then do as I've instructed.
[evil chuckle]
Now, contestants,
to your stations!
[ALL] (nervous)
[SHUN] (huh?)
What? What is all this?
[EIZAN] By the way,
I forgot to mention.
My men are headed to
Kyokusei Dorm right now
to go and pay their respects.
[SOMA] (gasp)
Huh? They've got some
business there or something?
Oh, it's that little matter.
You know about
vacating the dorm?
The timeframe has been moved up
just a TINY bit.
Sorry to tell you,
but your friends
are about to be forcibly
evicted from Kyokusei.
ALL] (huh?!)
I'm sure it will proceed with
the utmost reverence with
regards to my men.
[EIZAN] Now then: the Food War.
You have three hours
to prepare your dish.
By the time this
match is finished,
your dorm will just be
sitting there empty.
All that awaits you is the
look of despair on your
friends' faces
when they realize you
let them down!
Now, let's get started!
[music playing]