His greatest strength is that
he refuses to give in.
It's what fuels his curiosity,
and his desire to learn.
It drives him forward.
It's what makes him take that
one step no one else would.
Go get it -
a seat on the Ten,
the No. 1 spot.
[SOMA] Sir!
[KOJIRO] As it is,
you're one of the few chefs
that I've ever bothered
to acknowledge.
So, join me up here
at the summit,
Soma Yukihira!
I will never join with
the likes of Central.
I will be the one who will win
this battle today.
He can't do that.
He's challenging the
No.1 Seat on the Ten?
That's too much!
[ERINA]
Look at that protein he has.
Okay!
I've trimmed off all the muscle.
[ERINA] I think...
that's leg meat.
He chose leg meat?!
He's covered it with
minced onion and garlic,
and now he's just letting it
sit for a bit.
That will make it soft,
and give it that extra flavor
he's been wanting!
[HISAKO] But he's up against
the very best,
the No. 1 Seat on the Ten,
Eishi Tsukasaa!
There's no way he can fight him
just by using
conventional methods!
Soma Yukihira...
If you lose, you'll have to
become a member of Central.
And if that happens...
[music playing]
Oh, that's right.
I have to get THAT out!
Got a little secret
up your sleeve, Soma?
[SOMA] (unh) There's just one
more ingredient my dish needs.
And it's somewhere in your bag?
Let's see, where did I put it?
Not this. Or this.
Definitely not.
Ah, here it is!
THIS'll do the trick!
Some "shelled sweet chestnuts"!
[BOTH] What?!
He plans to use that in
his dish as an ingredient?!
So what is that thing, Megumi?
This "shelled" ingredient?
W-well, um, it's a snack of
shelled chestnuts he had
in his bag.
[ERINA] Chestnuts?
That's actually a
good ingredient,
one that is a great match
for wild game.
It's not an uncommon pairing
in French cooking.
But all said and done,
that's still just a
snack bag he pulled out.
I don't see how on Earth this
can turn out well at all.
[SOMA] (huh?)
[TSUKASA] What, this?
Turn off the heat
for a little bit,
and cover the protein
with a bowl and let it rest.
The steam builds up
within the bowl,
and that slowly transfers
to the meat.
Then, once it's re-heated in
the oven, it will be done.
Oh wow, I totally get it.
That was really interesting!
Thanks a lot.
I didn't learn anything
like that from Chef Kojiro!
Idiot!
This is no time for gratitude!
You really are quite
a bizarre person,
you know that, Soma.
Thanks, I guess?
I'm not sure about your plan.
Experimental ingredients don't
always make a good dish.
But what do I know, I'm just
the No.1 seat on the Ten.
[SOMA] In that case,
I'll go ahead and apologize now.
Because I think I'm about
to surprise you again,
Chef Tsukasa.
[heh, heh, heh]
Charcoal grill!
He's using that for
FRENCH cooking?!
All right, the temperature
is about perfect...
Now to finish
everything up at once!
But this is supposed to be
about French cooking!
Do you even get that?!
Hisako, if you keep that up,
they're going to
hear us out here!
What's he up to?
I know a charcoal grill
used like that
can give seafood
a really decent sear,
but I've never heard of
it ever being used
to cook meat all the way through
in any form of French cooking!
I just don't know
what he's thinking!
And yet... Cooking with charcoal
definitely has its merits.
You can get a surface
temperature of 600 degrees.
And if you fan it, that can
get up to 1,000 degrees.
What's more, the infrared
radiation emitted by
the charcoal
will act as a means to
heat the meat directly.
And as a result of using
this cooking technique,
the venison should not only turn
out crispy on the outside
but juicy within.
[HISAKO] But, Ms Erina!
I know.
The charcoal brings
about a bitterness
that's difficult to incorporate
into French cooking.
Which means this
potential dish...
We may be, in all likelihood,
seeing the birth of a dish
that only he,
Soma Yukihira,
would ever be able to pull off!
[SOMA] Okay, Chef Tsukasa,
what do you say the two of us
go ahead and finish this duel?
Bon appetite.
[TSUKASA]
Fine, don't mind if I do.
[SOMA] OH!
[TSUKASA] Huh?
You know what,
we never thought about
how we were going to even
judge this Food War!
Well,
since it's just the two of us,
we'll just have to taste each
other's dishes and compare them.
Hey there! So, you guys wanna
come and eat our stuff or what?!
[ALL] He busted us!
Oh, my goodness!
You were here this whole time?!
Why were you ladies hiding
from us, anyway?
Uh, well, it's sorta like this,
you know?!
Why are we here again?
Well, I think it
was regarding Ms Erina...
[BOTH] How come, you reckon?
I-I don't have an answer
to that either!
Well then, how about we have
you three be our judges?
Yeah, that works out perfectly!
Thanks for helping out,
you girls're the best!
Um, hold on a minute, Soma!
We can't just go and say yes
to something like that.
But why not?
Because depending
on the outcome,
you might end up having to
become the next member
of Central!
Listen to me...
I could never back down after
hearing what he told me.
But you're right
about one thing.
Central's true goal is
yet to be realized.
And that is to obliterate all
of Japan's restaurants, pronto.
So the way I see it,
I don't have a choice but to
settle this once and for all!
But Soma...
Well if that's it...
If that's how
it's going to be...
Then I shall be the judge
of this challenge!
Soma, bring out your dish
for me to try.
Right away!
But Ms Erina...
You two should judge as well,
and cast your votes HONESTLY.
Now, first off, the aroma...
The charcoal has given it
depth and a richness...
[gasp]
[moans of ecstasy]
[HISAKO] This... this is...
[TSUKASA] Such a pleasant,
plump-and-melts-in-your mouth
texture...
It has the distinct, mildly
sweet flavor of the chestnuts.
When paired with the
aroma of the charcoal,
it serves to further draw out
the juiciness of the venison.
This flavor wouldn't have been
possible with normalchestnuts.
It's a unique flavor
made possible by the
CANDIED chestnuts!
And the chestnuts were diced
and added to the sauce too,
am I right?
Yep! And before I let it
all simmer down,
I added cinnamon, orange zest,
and diced chestnuts to
the fond de veau.
I call it,
"Yukihira-style chestnut sauce"!
I get it!
That must have been what let you
get that delicate sweetness
into every morsel of
the venison!
What a real surprise.
But I'm missing something.
The taste of charcoal shouldn't
lend itself to French cuisine
like this,
but in this dish,
it works perfectly.
Is there some other
secret flavor?
He added coffee to it.
Huh? It's coffee?!
You nailed it. That's the
God Tongue, all right!
I learned this working
for Chef Kojiro.
Cacao apparently pairs really
well with wild game.
Honestly, I don't really
have very much experience
working with cacao,
so I thought I'd use
instant coffee.
The bitterness seemed like
the perfect fit for
pairing with wild game,
and the deep, rich flavor
is just the thing for
a French-style sauce.
Hence, my secret ingredient.
This is my new, original take
on French cooking:
Char-grilled thigh of venison
in chestnut sauce!
[ERINA] The protein, the sauce,
and the garnishes...
Together, these form a
trifecta of harmony.
That's the basis of
French cooking.
The dish makes no sense!
It makes no sense at all!
And yet, without a doubt,
it can only be called "French."
[moans of pleasure]
[ERINA]
I want to reject this dish,
but it's as if my very common
sense is being peeled away!
Well, for a dish that
YOU'VE managed to put out,
I suppose you could say that
it meets the standards
of being considered
French cuisine I guess.
For Ms Erina, that's an
incredible thing to say!
[MEGUMI]
But what about Chef Tsukasa?
[HISAKO] What's your plan,
Eishi Tsukasa?
Oh, yeah, right! I have to
present MY dish too, don't I?!
Wait just a little longer, okay?
I hope it's to your liking.
I call it: "Two Expressions
of Roast Venison."
[HISAKO] The surface of both
slices is a perfect rose-red.
[MEGUMI] It's like the
meat is glistening!
[HISAKO] The knife
went right through it!
[ERINA] Harmony...
[MEGUMI] Harmony!
[HISAKO] Complete and utter...
[ALL] ...harmony!
It has depth,
but at the same time,
the flavor's so light.
There's no bitterness
present at all,
and it's so incredibly juicy!
THIS is the result
of the care he put into
the cooking temperature?!
What's even more shocking,
though, are these two
beautiful sauces!
[SOMA]
What the heck is going on?
How does this sauce
taste so incredible?
The one on the right is
commonly known as a poivrade.
It uses venison stock as a base,
so it's a bit rough,
but it has a fine clarity
that lingers on the tongue.
For the other sauce,
I added different kinds of fruit
to make it sweet and refreshing,
but also to try and give it
some more acidity.
This one's a sauce
poivrade au baie.
If you're curious about
what the name means,
then poivrade comes from
the French poivre,
which refers to "pepper."
The delicate bite of the pepper
that's on display in the sauce
helps to round out the subtle
flavors that are present within
the pairing of the venison.
The fruits that I used were-
Blueberries, redcurrants, as
well as some blackberries, too.
After that you added crème de
cassis, red wine, blueberry
vinegar, and raspberry jam.
Incredible!
You got all those right!
Still, I guess that's only
natural for you.
[ERINA] It's nowhere near
that simple though.
This sauce alone incorporates
several different kinds
of fruits.
But of course, that's what
gives this sauce such a rich
and multilayered flavor to it.
[HISAKO] One miscalculation,
and it would have made
the flavor combination bitter.
It's like walking a tightrope.
[MEGUMI]
Without a perfect knowledge
of the properties of
each ingredient
and how they would best
combine with each other,
there's no way he
could have made this!
[ERINA] Only Eishi Tsukasa
could have made this.
This is cooking on a
superhuman level.
Through the contrasting flavors
of the two sauces,
he was able to not only fully
express the strength,
but also the elegance
of the venison.
[SOMA] This is bad...
I don't believe it!
[TSUKASA] Now then...
Your judgment, please.
In your opinion,
which was the better dish?
[HISAKO]
It's not that easy to choose!
[MEGUMI]
Still, if I had to pick one...
[ERINA] The dish that most
effectively brought out
the flavors of the venison...
...is clear.
[ERINA] All right then,
I shall announce the winner.
The winning dish in this battle,
I would say belongs to...
[ERINA] Eishi Tsukasa!
I take it you have no
objection to the outcome.
You do understand now,
don't you?
There's a huge gap between us.
[MEGUMI] Soma's dish was
really astounding, too.
He created a whole new
perspective of flavor!
[HISAKO] Eishi Tsukasa's dish
was the ultimate pinnacle
of deliciousness,
like something from Eden.
[MEGUMI]
But if Soma loses here...
[HISAKO] Soma...
he'll end up at Central!
[ERINA] Tsukasa's dish was
undeniably superior.
Soma Yukihira has lost.
Well, Soma...
You're way too much of a wild
card to be of any use to me.
[ALL] (gasp)
I knew it the moment I
tasted your dish today.
If I brought you into Central,
Any "support" you gave would
be no help to me at all!
I think I'd collapse from
you causing me anxiety!
I feel you wouldn't follow
directions and just make
whatever you want!
I think I understand
what you mean.
Don't take it
the wrong way though.
I just don't think I'm
able to control you.
That being the case,
I'm inclined NOT to make you
become a member of Central.
[SOMA] Huh?
[MEGUMI] You're okay with that?
That's right. Since this
wasn't an actual Food War,
I don't mind if we just
forgot the whole thing.
So, why don't we just
call this one a draw?
That okay with you, Soma?
Well, it was fun.
See ya.
No way.
I LOST FAIR AND SQUARE!
[HISAKO] HUH?!
[MEGUMI] No, Soma!
A loss is a loss.
The difference in our skills
is crystal clear.
If you concede this as a loss,
you'll end up having to
join Central!
[growly] Yeah well,
I don't want that to happen.
You make no freakin' sense
at all, you know that?!
Soma,
please just rein yourself in!
[SOMA] Whatever!
[HISAKO] Stop complaining!
[SOMA] But I lost!
[HISAKO] Stop being an idiot!
[SOMA] I don't deserve to-
[HISAKO] Stop talking!
[ERINA] Tsukasa...
Are you taking pity on him
or what?
[TSUKASA] "Pity"?
If anything, the opposite.
His cooking will never budge,
nor will it ever compromise.
And there's nothing
I could do to change that.
It's the reason I think he would
be dangerous if I were to
have him at my station.
He's not a good fit.
Later guys.
[SOMA] Dammit, I lost again.
[HISAKO] Huh? Ms Erina?!
Where did you go?
[MEGUMI] Come on,
he's the No. 1 Seat, Soma.
[HISAKO] You're not in the
salamander, are you?
Yeah, I didn't come
anywhere close to him.
But that doesn't mean he's
so far ahead that I
can't reach him!
Next time, Tsukasa,
I am GOING TO reach that summit!
[STUDENT A] Holy crap!
[STUDENT B] What's going on?!
Central has been out there
beating all the groups
left and right.
[STUDENT]
But these guys are unstoppable!
[FEMALE STUDENT]
(squeal) Ikumi Mito!
Megumi! Go and get 'em!
You can do it, Megumi!
Meat-Meat!
You're a total rockstar!
[GUY] DO IT!
[GIRL  You got this!
[MEGUMI] It was Soma who went
out there and protected our
dorm all by himself.
And I won't let them take the
place where I belong either!
So watch out Central!
[IKUMI] After all, it was Soma
who told me to join Bowl-Soc.
So there's no way I'll let
anyone shut it down!
That settles it...
I felt enough will
in that cooking,
to see this battle
through to the end!
[OIZUMI] The Regional Cuisine
Research Society wins!
[MEGUMI] (shocked gasp)
[OIZUMI] It shall continue!
Noooo! It can't be!
Way to go Meat-Meat and Megumi!
And Kenji too!
Yeah, eat that in the face,
Central!
You did it, Zenji!
Come to think of it...
What's going on with Akira
and the Shiomi Seminar?
I'm finding there's something
much different about this
batch of 1st-years.
And it seems to me
that Soma Yukihira
is the person right at the
center of all that
rebellious chaos.
Huh! Soma Yukihira, you say?
I believe he's one of the
residents of Kyoksei Dorm,
is he not?
Okay dudes!
To celebrate Megumi's
victory today,
let's kick off the seventh "God
Tongue" Taste-Testing Festival!
[GIRLS] Yay!
You want to do this AGAIN?!
[ALL] Yes, we certainly do,
thank you!
Fine, then.
Ms Erina has certainly settled
in here, hasn't she?
[doorball rings]
Who could it be at this hour?
I don't suppose it's
Master Senzaemon
dropping by to pay us
another visit.
Yeah, what's up?
Whoa, it's the NEW director...
Azami Nakiri!
Well, hello, Soma Yukihira.
I happened to be in the area,
so I stopped by.
Father! It's you!
What do you want, ya d-bag?!
Sonofa... Just stay back you!
[SATOSHI]
The new director, I see.
And what may we help you with?
I've come to see my daughter,
of course.
Is that okay?
We were in the middle
of a rather fun
and pleasant celebration
this evening.
May I ask that you go away?
[AZAMI] Erina, come here.
[ERINA] (scared breaths)
[RYOKO] Erina!
[YUKI]
No, Erina-poo! You can't go!
[FUMIO]
I thought I heard a ruckus.
Do you seriously think you can
just waltz back in here
like nothing ever happened?
It is truly astonishing
how much nerve you have,
Nakamura.
[MEGUMI] What?
[RYOKO] "Nakamura"?
[chuckles]
Now, now, Ms Fumio.
Haven't you heard
I go by "Nakiri"?
What's more,
that's no way to speak to a
former dorm member, now is it?
[ALL] (shocked gasps)
No way!
He's a Kyokusei alumn?!
I'll have you know that I've
done a little bit of
research on you, my friend,
Master Azami - Azami Nakamura.
As a 1st-year in the high school
division,
you took the No. 3 Seat
on the Ten,
and the No. 1 Seat
the following year.
Some years later, you married
into the Nakiri family,
the famous clan of the so-called
Demon King of Food.
From there you became a top
star of the culinary world,
until you were exiled
by Master Senzaemon.
He was a former No. 1 Seat?
So when he was our age,
he was already the No. 3 Seat
on the Council of Ten.
However, there's one thing
I simply cannot abide.
This man standing right here
was planning to destroy
his former dorm
without a second thought.
I wasn't really trying to
destroy it exactly.
It simply became involved
because of the groups
I was trying to destroy.
In any case,
you are not welcome in
this dorm now or ever.
Get out, Nakamura.
Have it your way.
Until next time.
I'm glad to see that you're
looking well, Erina.
[AZAMI] Nothing to worry about.
Erina will return to
my side before long.
I'll give her a little bit
of freedom for now,
until the time comes
for the great revolution.
[door opening]
Um, excuse me.
Yeah?
Have you come to see me off?
[SOMA] Nah, it's just...
Something's been
really bugging me.
You stayed in this dorm
for a long time.
Do you not feel anything for it?
Don't you have memories of
this place, Chef Nakamura?
Have I earned your scorn
for thinking that?
The world that I seek does not
lie with this dorm.
[AZAMI] Well, at least, not now.
[SOMA] Not now?
I was living here back during
the golden age of Kyokusei.
There was one chef that
I looked up to, then.
He was unprecedented,
and refined.
A genius, beyond all doubt.
He was a chef for whom I have
the fondest of memories
that only continue
to warm my heart:
Joichiro Saiba!
He was there at the start,
in the bloom of my youth.
His technique and skill were
such that he made you think
he was different on some
other genetic level.
So, uh...
You may not know this about me,
but...
Did you say Joichiro Saiba?
'Cause, uh, that's my father.
[ending music starts]
You mean, you're actually
Chef Saiba's son?
Yeah.
You knew each other, right?
That's pretty cool,
Chef Nakamura.
[ERINA] Soma is...
Chef Joichiro Saiba's WHAT?!
[music playing]
Who's Saiba?
Saiba is Soma's famous father.
He attended Totsuki and
was the former No. 2.
The No. 2?!
Oh! I have a photo.
We took one of him
when he came by the dorm once.
Someone that incredible
is HIS father?
[ERINA] (shocked gasp)
[evil chuckle]
[AZAMI] Well now, how much
of this was a coincidence,
and how much of it was
actually planned out?
[MEGUMI (gasp)
[SOMA] What?
[AZAMI] This concerns you
as well, Soma Yukihira.
The great revolution I've set in
motion here at Totsuki Academy,
ALL of it!
Is nothing more
than the salvation
of the corrupt culinary world
that once ruined the great
Chef Saiba!
[SOMA] (angry growl)
That once ruined Chef Saiba?
That salvation shall
soon be complete.
I find that I'm quite lucky.
Joichiro Saiba's son
will see it.
He will see what the great
revolution will finally
look like.
[car door closes]
[MEGUMI] Wait, what?
What did he mean by that?
[SOMA] What could have happened
between him and my dad?
[ERINA]
What my father is doing...
is somehow deeply connected
to Joichiro Saiba!