[MITSURU] Just in folks:
the Lunar Feast guidebook!
Brand new and hot off
the presses.
Come and get yours today!
Here!
[MALE STUDENT A]
Hey... Look at this!
[MALE STUDENT B]
Soma Yukihira? For real?!
Chef Yukihira...
I did exactly what
you asked of me,
I put the write-up about
your stall just where
you wanted it...
next to the one
about China Society!
His stall is right next
to China-Soc?
AND he's doing Chinese cuisine,
as well?!
He even placed his advertising
right next to theirs.
That boy's a firecracker,
I tell ya.
I had a feeling he would try
to pick a fight with one of
the Ten, but...
I never thought he would go
after one of them head-on
like this.
[TAKUMI]Soma Yukihira,
you're something else.
You're antics never fail
to get me all fired up!!
Watch it, Takumi, you're
wrinkling the guidebook.
Oh, sorry.
That's notfair!
He's getting all the attention!
Ah!
[delighted laughter]
Soma, that "Whatever" look on
your face is priceless!
Here's to hoping you don't
come to regret the choices
you'vet made. [chuckle]
[music playing]
[SOMA] "You know that
if sales are in the red,
you'll be kicked out of school."
It sure threw me for a loop
when Erina came at me
with that little gem.
But there's no way
I'll end up in the red.
I mean, this monster draws
500,000 people in five days,
right?
Yeah, it's a pretty big deal.
[LION] (roar)
[IKUMI] You know, you're not
doing yourself any favors
by putting your stall right next
to your fiercest competitor!
What're you thinking?!
[air-headed laugh]
Yeah,
it'll work out in the end.
You're going to act like
this challenge is nothing!
I mean, I bet you don't even
have a plan in mind, do you?!
[GUY] Excuse me.
[IKUMI] (huh?)
Pardon, Ms. Ikumi?
Can we look at your forms,
please?
Sure thing.
Just hang on a second.
[FEMALE STUDENT] Chef Ikumi
is the absolute coolest!
Whoa, Bowl-Soc sure has grown,
hasn't it?
For sure. We've been
flooded with applications
from the Junior High Division.
It's getting absurd.
Ol' Meat-Meat has gotten
even MORE popular.
And she won that Food War
against Nao Sadatsuka
like it was nothing!
So hey, Soma...
[SOMA] (hmm?)
I'm like really sorry, I would
have loved to help you out
with your stall and everything,
but I kinda have to look out for
all these newbies nowadays.
So, I'm sorry.
What are you talking about?
I'M the one who said to give
Bowl-Soc your all.
Great! But let us know if you
run into any trouble, okay?
Cool.
Yeah, we're ready to help out!
I mean, after all,
you and Megumi...
you'll always be honorary
members of Bowl-Soc!
We are?
Well, I guess the only
thing to do is just do it.
[ERINA]
What is this nonsense, Alice?!
You don't have to get
all pissy about it.
The deadline for the Lunar Feast
has long since passed.
It's way too late for you
to just say you want
to run a shop NOW.
I may be on the Council of Ten,
but there's nothing I can do.
I doubt it.
For instance,
you could just take someone's
spot by declaring a Food War.
Among other ways.
You were the one who decided
to sit out last year!
Hey! Whatcha fighting about,
Nakiri girls?
Oh, hey there, Soma.
It's none of your business!
Ms. Erina!
Traffic is so bad now
that the interior
construction workers
are running about an hour late.
Well, I suppose it
can't be helped then.
[SOMA] Hey, you guys free?
[ERINA] Huh?
I was thinking of making some
food that we used to
serve back home.
Mind doing a little taste test?
What?! Why would I ever do
something like to help you?!
You can have just one hour,
Soma.
Ms. Erina is very busy today.
[ERINA] (gasp)
Hisako, what are
you doing to me?!
Go ahead and count me in too.
Thank you!
[sizzling]
I chopped you up some
spring onions.
But that's all the help
you're going to get.
Cool, thanks a lot.
Hisako, seems you've
been warming up
to Soma Yukihira recently.
[ahem!] Hisako...
Ma'am?
Oh no, it's nothing.
Never mind.
[SOMA] This is Yukihira-style
Mapo Tofu Set Lunch!
Go on, eat up!
To sit here and look at, it just
seems like the standard fare
from some local eatery
doesn't it, Ms. Erina?
Yes, it's not bad.
So spicy!
[ERINA] However, this isn't good
enough to beat Chef Kuga.
The reason being...
There is far too little
ma and la in this.
Did you say "Mandala"?
What the heck are
you talking about?
You're so dumb,
you should be ashamed!
Listen, in Chinese cuisine,
there are two main "pillars"
of spiciness.
Red peppers impart
the la flavor,
a spiciness that
burns the tongue.
While Sichuan peppers give
a numbing heat called ma flavor.
Combining the two flavors of
the peppers is what creates
"ma la flavor."
[uh...]
Sichuan peppers...
Like that spice mix
Meat-Meat used during
the prelim Selection.
Honestly, when one mentions
"Chinese cuisine,"
it covers a wide range
of culturals.
[ERINA] The varying climates
and customs of mainland China
gave rise to a wide variety
of cooking styles,
called the Eight Great Cuisines.
Out of these, the Sichuan
cooking that Chef Kuga
specializes in
is known for its
ma la flavor.
Totally rad!
[ERINA] Oh, no!
I just gave him information
he can use!
Man, that made things
nice and clear.
Sorry to make you explain
all that to me.
No! Strike it from memory!
Forget everything
you have just heard!
That's impossible!
Impossible.
Ms. Erina, that's not possible.
[gah!]
Okay... I remember is that
China-Soc's mapo tofu
is super spicy,
but the way Chef Kuga is able to
use all that ma la flavor
leaves you wanting more.
That's correct.
He's also a master of
cooking techniques.
but I would hazard to say
that there's another reason
for that spiciness
being so addictive.
[SOMA] Huh?
[ALICE]
Physiologically speaking,
"spiciness" isn't a taste,
it's more of a sensation...
of pain.
Wait, what? So you're telling me
it's about pain?
Yep! Spiciness is different
from sweetness, bitterness,
sourness, and saltiness,
which are picked up by
taste receptors.
Instead, it's felt through what
are called vanilloid receptors.
To put it another way,
extreme spiciness
causes adrenaline and beta
endorphins to be released
within the brain.
These are what cause one to
transmit feelings of
excitement or euphoria.
It's why people can crave
spicy foods and eat
peppers straight.
That's right! It's a phenomenon
that's unique only to spiciness.
And in medicinal cooking,
spicy foods are said to help
aid in the digestive process,
as well as relieve people
from the burden of stress.
I think I get it...
This what makes someone who
can manipulate it at will
so formidable.
Kuga once put it like this...
There comes a moment
in my cooking,
where everyone breaks into
a sweat and turns bright red.
And yet, they keep on
eating like crazy.
Seeing that is the
ultimate feeling for me.
Using my food to make people
gasp and cry out in pain
is almost more fun than
any one human can stand!
I sort of get where
Kuga's coming from.
I've cooked food that was so
good it made people laugh,
and so disgusting that it made
them wanna pass out and die.
Both were a lot of fun for me!
Good times!
This guy has
a screw loose as well.
Anyway, you need flavor
paired with incredible
intense spice.
It has to bring people
down to their knees.
And Chef Kuga is a master at it.
That's how he rose through the
ranks and made it to the Ten.
He combines the powerful heat
of Sichuan cooking
with multiple layers of flavor.
Unless you have a way
of combating that,
you don't stand
a chance against him!
[MEGUMI] Oh, really?
Erina said all that
about your cooking?
Is your mapo tofu really so bad?
I can't imagine that.
It's not that it's really "bad,"
per se, but...
Yeah, this dish won't be enough
against that Sichuan cooking
he's has mastered.
It's kind of like when I was
going up against Mimasaka
in the beef stew battle.
I guess this was just a
trial dish.
I need to learn more about
that spiciness from
the ground up,
till I find something that
can actually win.
[MEGUMI] Oh! You know what?
I thought these might be
somewhat useful,
so I brought you some Chinese
recipes and stuff.
You did? But didn't Isshiki
ask you to run the stall
with him and the
rest of the gang?
He wants you with Kyokusei Dorm,
doesn't he?
[MEGUMI] Yeah! I was
also asked to do one
with the Regional Cuisine
Research Society, as well.
But I kinda already turned
both of them down.
What? But why?
Wha? Because, I figured you were
probably going to be
shorthanded, you know.
[AH!] Sure, I'll probably get in
the way a little here and there.
But, you know, I, uh, I do
have some experience!
I've helped with service
at the family inn from
time to time,
and I learned a bit at
the Stagiaire too,
so I'm not entirely uncertain
I wouldn't be of some
help to you in the kitchen!
I mean, I'm sure there's
something I could do!
So, I could lend you a hand at
your stall, if you want me to.
You know what? If that's all
right with you, Soma.
Megumi...
That would be totally awesome!
[happy exhale]
Okay! Whaddya say we make
something great?!
Yeah!
[ALICE] Akira?
Might I intrude?
What are you doing here?
I come with a message.
I, Alice Nakiri, will be
making my long-awaited debut
in the ever popluar
upcoming Lunar Feast!
I'm very proud of you.
The thing is, they're not
taking in any more applications
at the moment.
So, let's team up and
do our best, okay?
The three of us can use the
Shiomi Seminar's location
and work together!
Professor Shiomi's already
given me her permission!
HUH?!
[ALICE]
The thing is, Professor...
Your wonderful seminar group
can keep doing this sort
of thing indefinitely,
but for me, it's a
once-in-a-lifetime chance
to take part in the
1st-years' festival.
Once-in-a-lifetime?
Yes, you heard it correct.
All the two of us ever wanted
was to be teamed up again.
To be able to cook side by side
with our dear friend, Akira.
Right, Ryo dear?
What was that?
He's a "dear friend" of yours?
I'm so happy.
Akira made friends in
the same school year?!
If you don't mind, would you
sign this form for us?
Dammit, Jun!
I'm assuming you know
what this means.
Oh, and of course, I will need
to be the team leader.
Like I would ever let you
tell me what to do!
Come on, Ryo, you gotta
say something to her!
Once she's already
made up her mind like this,
it's near impossible
to stop her.
Are you kidding me?!
Where's your spine?!
Now just you wait and see,
Soma! And you too, Erina!
This school festival won't have
any idea what hit it!
Okay, just so you know,
my spot is in the area
off the main road.
Soma and Erina will be
someplace else entirely!
Oh! Well, this is bad.
[whoosh! sizzle]
[SOMA] First, we fry minced
pork over a high flame.
Boil silken tofu for
two minutes and strain it.
Once the pork has become
aromatic and slightly crisp,
it's time for the spice!
To a soup of chicken broth,
add sweet bean sauce, chili
bean sauce, black bean paste,
garlic, and chili powder.
Well?
Nah, that's not it.
It's nowhere even close to
the spiciness of China-Soc.
[SOMA] (urk!) That is SPICY!
But it's still not enough.
I need more heat!
Gotta keep going! [gah!]
Gotta push through it!
[yeow!]
All done, Megumi.
It's an ultra-spicy mapo tofu!
[MEGUMI] (frightened whimper)
Huh?
Go on, try a bite.
[MEGUMI]
Your lips are already swollen!
Sh-sh... shpicy!
That's spicy as hell, isn't it?
Well, why dont we go ahead
and try out some other
Chinese dishes.
Twice-cooked pork...
and pepper steak!
[frightened whimpering]
Oh, yeah, sorry, Megumi.
You can take a little break
if you need one.
No, I have to taste-test these!
[ow, ow, ow!]
I did it...
I really did it!
I ate it, didn't I?
It's like I get it,
but I'm still nowhere close.
It's spicy,
but that's all it is.
[waah!]
Once you get past
all the spiciness,
China Soc's dish has
something more to it.
It has a depth of flavor.
[frantic gulping]
Oh, you know what, Soma,
I heard something from
Hojo earlier.
For their restaurant,
China-Soc will be using
chili bean paste,
also sweet bean paste,
douchi, and oyster sauce.
But it's not just about
the ingredients.
It's the fact everything
will be made special
by Chef Kuga himself.
[SOMA] "Special"?
[MEGUMI] I think that's why,
even though their food is spicy,
it still has lots of flavor.
Oh I get it...
These may be staples of
Sichuan cuisine,
but they've been infused with
Chef Kuga's conviction.
You can almost see the face of
the chef when you taste it!
Spice is the key.
[MEGUMI] (woow!
That's right! We're doing a meat
and potato hotpot party!
Isn't that super?!
And we'll be using
other vegetables from
Isshiki Farms too!
The signboard sure came out
great didn't it?
I designed that sucker
all by myself!
And we were the dudes
that put it together!
But still, is it okay for you
to put up a tent in
the mountain area?
We were going for something that
would be simple and intimate.
And we've already gotten
a ton of reservations
from all the elderly madams
that participate in
Isshiki's cooking class.
Yeah, I bet, but still...
Isshiki,
what's with that outfit?
[SATOSHI[ (laughs)
One normally has a hotpot
party by the riverbank,
so I was thinking...
we could put one right here!
[SOMA] He's going to
dig a whole river?!
[DUDE] Hey, we're out of paint!
GUY] Would one of
you guys lend me a hand?
Wow, things are
really coming along.
It's going to be busy
after school like this
every day until the festival.
It sure is exciting, huh?
[ISAMI] Megumi!
Soma!
[MEGUMI] Isami!
A branch location of
"Trattoria Aldini"?
Wow...
You runnin' it with Takumi?
Yeah, and the whole class
is in on it.
[TAKUMI] Soma Yukihira!
It seems you've decided
to challenge Chef Kuga.
[GIRLS] (oohs and aahs)
[SOMA] Yep.
[TAKUMI]
I'll say this right off the bat:
You're not the only one
who's grown since we
came back from the Stagiaire.
You'll find that I've changed
since the Selection.
And I will be the one to
take you out- (woah!)
[ISAMI] It's time to go
shopping, Big Brother.
You hear me, Soma Yukihira?!
[SOMA] (uh...)
[AKIRA] Enough of your nonsense!
The menu's already
been decided!
[ALICE] But WHY? It doesn't have
to be just curry, right?
We're inviting heads of
businesses that are here to
fund the Shiomi Seminar Group!
I won't let you screw things up!
Then, there's no point in me
even participating,
now is there?! [gah!]
Here's what Professor Shiomi
had to say...
Don't you worry, I'll find a way
to accommodate our sponsors
somehow.
Do your best as you bloom
into youth, Akira!
[AKIRA] Oh god...
And besides, Professor Shiomi
herself told me...
[SOMA] Those three
sure are something...
[MEGUMI] I wonder if they'll
be able to work together!
[SOMA] Say what you will:
This is the prime of our lives!
[MEGUMI] Yep! It's like we have
the wind at our backs!
[whip crack] All right, all
right, move it, move it!
[SOMA] Man, look at
these poor suckers.
[KUGA] One, two, one, two...
Oh! Hey, Soma.
'Sup, dude? So, all this
is to make your shop?
[KUGA] Yeah, and it's
a lot of work!
My place will be a big one,
since APPEARANCE is just as
important as well, right?
At a glance,
it looks kinda cruel.
No! It's good!
We are enjoying ourselves here!
[SOMA]
Well, that's what counts.
And yet, if we don't turn a
profit, we'll be expelled!
What a shame that Soma,
the young little genius,
will have to leave the academy!
I simply can't take it anymore!
There's no way that's what
you're thinking right now.
Well then, do your best not
to get kicked out of
the academy, okay?
Now then! One, two! One, two...
So "appearance is just as
important as well," is it?
Wait, come to think of it,
that's what my dad
used to do too.
That's how we got more
customers at the festivals.
[SOMA (realization!)
[MEGUMI] (Huh?)
Oh, yeah, it's just
like Alice said:
Chinese food's more
than just Sichuan.
Could that be what she meant?
Megumi, there's something
I would really like
your help with.
Do you mind?
Whadda' you need?
This it?
Is this what Soma was after?
Mmm! Yes! Are you sure
it's all right?
You don't mind if we use it?
Yeah, we've already gotten
the okay from the head of the
Chinese Cuisine Department.
What'd I tell you?
If you ever need anything,
you just ask me.
Thank you so much!
I really wish I could help
you with running your stall,
but I've already committed
to helping someone else
with theirs.
Not at all!
You've already done so much.
Also, you have your family
restaurant that you need
to look after, don't you?
Yeah, it's day by day,
but recently,
I feel the restaurant staff has
started to open up to me.
I hope that someday real soon,
I will be a chef
as reliable as you are.
[embarrassed] Oh, come on!
Megumi! You having any luck?
Soma! We got it!
No problem!
[laugh]
Thank you for this, Hojo!
Sure thing. Now go out there
and show Kuga what's what.
Kick his ass!
[SOMA] Yeah!
Hey, Dad!
What is this?
It's weird.
It's a kiln I borrowed
from a friend.
Just doing yakisoba every year
gets kinda old.
With this little baby
right here,
we'll be the festival's top
earners AGAIN this year!
[SOMA] Wow...
This is what we need to
get things started.
If we want to make it
right, that is.
[URARA] Now on sale:
500-yen "Pickled Plum" tickets,
1,000-yen "Bamboo" tickets, and
10,000-yen "Pine Tree" tickets!
These will be given to the
customers so that they are able
to exchange them for your goods!
[YUME] They're also used
as proof of how much
each stall sells,
so please make sure you don't
lose them while out and about!
And the deadline for submitting
your earnings is 6 PM!
So try not to get lost
on the way! [Tee-hee!]
[ALICE] Soma Yukihira, Erina...
[SOMA] Wha...
It seems the day
has finally come.
Your preparations are in order,
I presume?
Yeah, I guess they're in order.
Oh? Good for you.
But it's a real crying shame
that we're not going to be
in the same area as you.
Although, we'll be running
the show from the main area,
so you don't need to
worry about us.
The two behind you seem
to be pretty drained.
Are you sure you'll be
able to pull it off?
Well, of course we'll be fine!
And you do your best out there,
and don't let anyone beat you,
okay?
Oh! Well, well,
speak of the devil.
[SOMA] (huh?)
[SOMA] (grr...)
[KUGA] (hmpf!)
[URARA] And now, we'll kick
things off with Tohtsuki
Academy's school song!
School song?
Oh, yeah, we do have one, huh?
[piano music playing]
Hey, uh, Megumi...
[singing] At the bosom of the
Land of the Rising Sun
High spirits gather
alongside fangs
Gaze upward at the bounty
of the harvest
And lift up your voices, aah!
Refine (refine),
O sacred land of haute cuisine
Totsuki Academy is here
[singing ends]
Tsukasa...
make sure to honor
what you said before.
Your promise...
The time has now come!
[SENZAEMON]
I formally announce...
the commencement
of the Lunar Festival!
Enjoy the feast!
[wild cheers and applause]
[pleased] Uh-hmmm!
This turned out quite well,
if I do say so myself!
[MEMBER A] Indeed!
[MEMBER B] By comparison,
just look at Soma Yukihira's
pathetic setup.
[MEMBER A] He seriously
wants to challenge us with
that rickety old stall?!
[chuckles]
[music begins]
All right now! This here...
is the first thing I'll use
to beat China-Soc.
Hujiao bing!
[MEGUMI] Hot, fresh hujiao bing!
Who wants some hujiao bing?
[WOMAN A] Huh? Hujiao bing?
I think I've heard of that!
It's famous at Taiwanese
food stalls, right?
[WOMAN B] Wow, look at that!
They're stuck there right on
the inside of the oven!
What do you think's inside?
Inside the buns you will find
that the meat patties
are made of coarse-ground pork
with lots of black pepper.
Wow, I wanna try one!
And me too!
Can I get two of those, please?
Thank you so much
for trying them!
Thank you very much!
Oh, it's so hot!
Okay, here it goes!
[gasp] So much hot, meaty juice!
The bun is so nice and crunchy!
It's like a pie crust!
[WOMAN A] The patty inside is
full of chopped scallions,
and the black pepper
gives it a nice bite!
[WOMAN B] My mouth is filled
with the rich but mellow flavor
of the ground pork!
[BOTH] It's delicious! (ahhhh!)
Oh, thank goodness!
Look how happy they are, Soma!
Yep!
[hmpf!]