[NARRATOR]
The Totsuki Fine Dining Academy:
This institution is known
for producing a number of
famous chefs,
as well as providing a chosen
few with unlimited power and
resources.
The prowess of these ten
individuals is without equal.
They are Totsuki's
Council of Ten!
[small sigh]
[MEGUMI] Hey, Soma?
Soma!
Oh, what's up, Megumi?
Well, it's just, um...
It's kind of dangerous
to get lost in thought when
you're driving, so...
Sorry, yeah, you're right.
It would be pretty lame for
me to get in a wreck
after I'd barely bought this
thing, huh?
I know what's bothering you.
The Council of Ten again, huh?
Yeah, I guess so.
[MEGUMI] It's understandable.
After all, it was only yesterday
that those of us who got through
the Fall Selection had the
honor of meeting them.
The greatest chefs currently
at Totsuki Academy:
the Council of Ten.
[drum beats]
[WOMAN] Presenting the Totsuki
Academy Council of Ten!
[MEGUMI] And then...
In front of all these wildly
talented upperclassmen,
you had to go and be your self.
So, uh, I'd prefer to join the
Ten, like, right now.
Would one of you guys be
interested in doing a
Food War with me?
Soma, come on!
Yeah, but still, every
single one of 'em said no.
Talk about a letdown!
Yeah, but you just about gave
me a heart attack!
Maybe I should've had them
warm up to me a bit first
before that.
I don't really think
that's the issue here!
Even now, just thinking about it
makes me want to curl up
into a ball.
Those members of the Ten
were incredible!
The cake that Seat # 4, Chef
Momo Akanegakubo made for us
was just...
[ahhh!]
[SOMA] Yeah, that really was
something else.
I got to see firsthand just how
awesome the Ten really are.
Do you finally understand now?
The difference in skill between
the average chef
and those of the Ten
is undeniable.
That's the shape of things!
So better get used to it!
I'm getting the feeling
the nuance kinda sorta
got through to you.
You guys, totally,
for real, no joke,
you're not even a blip on our
radar, speck of dust.
That bein' said, just for
grins, let me say this:
If any of you newbies have
even one thing you think
could possibly beat me,
I might consider a
Food War with ya.
[NENE] Their height.
We're talking about food,
you ignorant swine beast!
It's cool Chef Kuga said
he'd be game to do
a Food War with us.
But coming up with something
that's actually good enough to
beat him will be tough.
We don't even have a proper
place where we can battle him.
Yeah, you're right.
And we hardly ever have
cooking classes
together with the second-years.
What?
I thought you were against me
challenging the Ten to
a Food War, Megumi.
Um, well, of course I don't want
you to end up getting expelled
from school or anything.
But I mean, you're an
amazing chef, Soma.
I thought, "Even if he is our
senior, that must have stung to
be talked down to like that."
Oh, I see. Thank you.
That's a really big truck.
They gonna build
something again?
Well, yeah! It's about time for
prep work to get under way.
"Prep work"?
[MEGUMI] Yeah!
There's an event every year
around this time.
It's so we can mark
the end of fall.
It's Totsuki Academy's
school festival!
School festival?!
Yup! It's called
"The Lunar Feast"!
Whoever enters gets to open up
a mock restaurant,
either individually or
as a group-
[SOMA] (laughs)
Soma, what is it?
That's it, Megumi!
What?
[music playing]
[GIRL]
What are you gonna do for lunch?
GIRL 2] Uh, I don't know...
The Lunar Feast runs
for five days.
Total sales of all restaurants
are supposed to be announced
daily, huh?
This is looking like just the
thing! Huh?!
Ho! Well, hey there, Erina!
Huh? Hello, Soma.
What a surprise!
What sorta class did you
just come from?
I've told you repeatedly
not to engage me in
casual conversation!
I can't believe Hisako's not
here at a time like this...
By the way, are you gonna do
one of these things as well?
I take it you mean
the Lunar Feast?
Well, of course.
Each year, the members of the
Ten who open up food shops
draw throngs of people.
Huh? Well, you don't say?
In that case, Chef Kuga is
sure to open one up too.
Yeah, that is perfect!
Oh God, don't tell me...
Yup! You can count me in too!
If I can get more sales than
Chef Kuga at the festival,
I'm sure he'll see fit to
accept my challenge.
[ERINA] (huh?!)
Not to brag,
but back home when we'd
work the summer festivals,
I was kind of a big deal,
you know!
[DUDE] This is delicious!
What'd ypu put in here?!
Of course, I'll be going up
against your restaurant too!
Let us both do our best!
See ya, Erina!
He honestly thinks he can
challenge Kuga?
Does he even know what the
Lunar Feast is about?
He's such a dummy.
[COACH] Okay, one more!
[MEGUMI] Oh, really?
I should have known you'd
be opening up a stall.
You bet! I figured this
was my only shot.
So, Megumi, you happen to know
what kinda food Chef Kuga cooks?
If I don't know that, I can't
come up with a plan of attack.
Let's see... I believe Kuga's
area of specialty is perhaps
Chinese cuisine.
Oh, Chinese, huh?
Uh...
Hmm?
Boom!
She's so cool!
That girl's got some bounce!
Huh?
[HOJO] You wanna beat the
#8 Seat, Terunori Kuga?!
Well, you are the same idiot
who challenged Chef Kojiro.
You sure do like
running your mouth.
Hojo was also stationed in
B Block with me during
the Fall Selection.
And her specialty is
Chinese cooking too.
Yeah? You don't say?
But unlike Kuga, whose focus
is mainly Sichuan,
I've trained in a variety of
different Chinese styles.
So, how many people have you
recruited for your staff?
What staff?
It'll just be me.
[MEGUMI] (urk!)
Whaaaat?!
Yeah, it's just a stall at
some school festival.
Uh, yeah, about that...
(sigh) Are you by chance free
after school?
[SOMA] Huh?
I'm scheduled to attend a
study group on regional dishes
after school today.
I guess Soma alone
will have to do.
You'll understand once
you've seen it for yourself.
I'll be taking you somewhere:
the Chinese Cuisine
Research Society,
Terunori Kuga's stronghold!
(ah!)
Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
This is nuts.
They're training to flip
uncooked rice in a wok?
There are so many of them!
But they're all moving
perfectly in sync!
Are these guys cyborgs
or something?
Okay! One, two! One and two!
Yeah, good, that's it!
Keep it up everyone!
Hey, baldy!
You're falling behind!
What are you doing?!
I-I'm so sorry, Master!
No! That won't be good enough
for you to properly do your job!
And you all share
responsibility,
so give me thirty more sets.
Now, go!
Hyah! Hyah! Hyah!
What's up, Miyo?!
Whatch' doin' up in here?
You finally decided to come
and join our group?
Not a chance.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah,
but still,
you know that you're
always welcome any time.
And here we have, um...
Soma, if I remember correctly.
What brings you here?
Well, I was just curious
what you were doing
to get ready for the
upcoming school festival.
"School festival"?
I was thinking about
doing a restaurant too.
I was just about to start
coming up with recipes.
If I rack up more sales
than you,
would you accept my
Food Wars challenge?
Oh, so that's it?
Of course I will.
I always like to
keep my promises.
I'm glad to hear it, man!
So, for now, you mind telling
me what you'll be serving?
This is supposed to be
covert recon!
Do you have any idea
what you're doing?!
(laughing) You sure are a funny
kid, aren't you, Soma?
But well, I'm still going over
what I want to make
for the festival,
but I'd have to say my top
seller is always mapo tofu.
Mapo tofu?
I used to do a killer mapo tofu
set menu back home.
The folks really loved
that stuff!
Huh? So your place served up
set menus, did it? Hmpf!
Ten of you, line up!
Make the mapo tofu we're
all SO proud of for
Little Soma here.
Yes, sir!
Hey, Soma, have you ever heard
of this famous Chinese saying?
[SOMA] What?
It was coined by the people
in Sichuan province
as well as neighboring
Hunan and Guizhou.
"Sichuan people don't
fear spiciness."
"Hunan fear no level
of spiciness,"
"and Guizhou people fear
that which isn't spicy."
In other words, it sounds like
they freaking love spicy foods.
It's not only that they
love their food spicy.
It's that it's such a part of
the regional cuisine that it
led to this phrase.
It's been that way for
hundreds of years.
And yet, my cooking has
elevated that even further
than anyone else has.
[MINON]
Presenting Terunori Kuga's
Ultra-Refined Sichuan Mapo Tofu!
Eat it while it's hot!
Ten servings' worth,
and they all came out
at the same time!
Talk about precision.
[urk!]
What the heck is this?!
[ugh!]
It's hot, but delicious!
It's hot and delicious!
IT'S HOT AND DELICICIOUS!
My tongue feels like
it's gonna burn off,
but then I'm hit by wave after
damn wave of flavor!
This is totally different from
the "Yukihira" mapo tofu.
What's more...
They all taste the same.
There's no difference!
These guys must have
trained like crazy.
This is true spiciness, Soma.
That perfect combination
of deliciousness and
overwhelming heat...
Your set menu doesn't even
come close to getting that,
does it?
What's more, my boys here have
been drilled to the point where
they can replicate it perfectly.
And I did the drilling!
(giggles)
The Lunar Feast is a crazy
event, one that gets
500,000 visitors a year.
If you want a chance
at the top spot,
you'll have to serve
around 1,000 dishes a day.
A thousand?!
Let's see...
You have how many people
on your staff?
Oh, yeah, just one.
And you don't even have
a recipe yet, right?
Tell me, Soma:
Just how are you planning on
going about beating me?
If you don't mind,
I would like you to share that.
You wanna know how I'll do it?
That's easy! I'll do it with
my cooking skills, of course!
You get it now, right?
Kuga is incredible.
A while back, China-Soc used
to be just that:
a society made for studying
the art of Chinese cooking.
But he wielded those raging
spicy flavors like a weapon,
forcing them to specialize
in Sichuan cuisine.
[SOMA] I get it. So then...
[horn beep]
What the heck am I gonna do?
What happened to all the
self-confidence you were
waggling around back there?
Say, Hojo...
You sure helped me out by
taking me to that study group.
Well, see ya.
Hold on! What will you do now?!
That's easy.
I'm gonna go home and
come up with a game plan.
Then there's something else
you need to keep in mind.
Kuga also has the jump on you
in another big way -
and not just staff.
His reputation goes
beyond the academy.
In other words,
he's got name value.
What do you mean
by "name value"?
[SOMA] (laughing
What's all this?
"China-Soc is not only
known for it's food,
but also for its many
dedicated repeat customers."
"But this year, it's garnered
even more attention
from the fact that
it will be helmed by the one
and only Terunori Kuga of the
Ten."
The fight to get customers
doesn't start the day of.
It seems this battle has
already started.
Thanks for this, Mitsuru.
I really do appreciate you
coming to bring me this.
Please let me know where
you're gonna be setting up
your booth,
and what you plan on
serving the crowd!
Huh? But why?
It's the Newspaper Club
that publishes
the guidebook to the
Lunar Feast!
And well,
if you would like me to,
I'll save a whole page for you!
Oh, that's so cool!
Thanks a lot!
Sure enough, being on the Ten
makes Chef Kuga a lot more
well-known than me.
What can I do to break down
that advantage?
[giggle]
We've been waiting for you,
Soma!
All of us at Kyokusei Dorm
have decided to be with you
at the Lunar Feast!
[urk!]
We will band together with a
single dish to present as one.
It's the most spectacular event
of our young academic career!
This is... the springtime
of our youth!
What it means to be students!
And so!
Let's walk this road together.
Uh, well, the thing is, I was...
Hmm, I see.
You're going solo on this one.
It's a shame we can't
do this together,
but we understand.
Yeah, sorry!
Wait, did Soma just say
he's going to challenge someone
for a seat on the
Council of Ten?
He did. It seems he's as
impetuous as always.
Yeah, well, you know...
Anyway, I was about to start
filling out this entry form,
but what's this "Area of
Operation" all about?
Ah! The thing is,
a section of the school grounds
will be specifically reserved
just for the festival.
But the space is divided into
three main areas for the shops.
Where you set up is
pretty important.
You have to choose a spot
that matches the concept
of your stall.
Huh? They differ that much?
They do. Each is unique
in its own way.
[SATOSHI] The first one
is the most famous:
the area along the
central street.
[RYOKO] It's the main road,
and right when you walk in,
there's row after row of
portable tents.
[YUKI] They sell things
from 500 to 1,000 yen each.
[MEGUMI] It's easy
to buy food, so it gets
a lot of traffic.
[SATOSHI]
Then, there's the central area:
where you'll find
most of the cooking facilities
used in our lectures.
[RYOKO] That's where you'll
find the vendors that
serve special dishes
or require special equipment.
[MEGUMI] If someone's in the
mood to eat some authentic
cuisine,
then you can find it there.
[YUKI] And it's a little more
expensive,
with items running from
1,000 to 5,000 yen.
[SATOSHI] Finally, there's the
area in the mountains
where a lot of places run by
the Ten have tended to be.
[RYOKO] The restaurants there
have a kind of secluded,
high-end feel to them.
[YUKI] You can expect to pay
at least 5,000 yen per item,
but there's no telling how
pricey things can get.
I mean, I've ever been there!
[MEGUMI] It's hard to get many
customers there unless you
have a reputation.
Incidentally, Kuga seems to be
setting up in the central area.
Huh? Why would he do that?
[SATOSHI]
Because in the central area,
you're free to make your shop
whatever size you like.
He probably avoided
the mountain area
to make use of
China-Soc's sheer size.
Still, no matter where
he sets up,
just being a member of the Ten
will bring customers to him.
Yeah! Sure enough, his name
value is certainly a
powerful weapon.
[RYOKO] Each year,
all the differnt groups
scramble like mad to get
the best possible location
for their shop.
If they end up choosing the
wrong place, that's it for them.
So there's no way I can
possibly compete with Kuga.
Is that what you're saying?
[footsteps]
Oh, Soma Yukihira.
It's the last day to
submit your application
if you want to enter
the Lunar Feast.
Are you still under the delusion
that you'll be able to
take out Kuga?
I hope you have
some sort of plan.
[ha!] Judging by your dumb face,
it would seem you haven't come
up with anything, have you?
[SOMA] (ugghh...)
[ERINA]
Hey, you need to answer me!
It's not like I'm talking
to myself, you know?
I have to get the best spot I
can on the Main Road Area,
because of all the
foot traffic.
Otherwise, there's no way I can
compete with Kuga's ability
to draw in customers.
At least, that's how it seems.
But is there more
to it than that?
Hey, what's up, Erina?
Didn't see you there.
You're so rude!
You're next to me in class, huh?
Pretty cool!
Get up and
go find another seat!
You and I sure do end up being
side-by-side a lot, don't we?
Like in the semifinals
during the Selection.
You chose to sit next to me,
you piece of crap!
[SOMA] Then, the time when
we were coming home from
our school trip.
[ERINA] Once again,
YOU sat by ME uninvited!
Oh, and there was that time
during class...
[gasp]
You know...
Yeah, that's it.
That has to be it.  It must be!
[ERINA] (gasp)
[KANICHI] You're out of your
stinkin' mind!
You want me to give up
MY space?!
Bowl-Soc uses the same spot
every Lunar Feast!
There's no way I'm givin' it up!
Stop hiding behind me like
a little puppy-dog.
Ask me how much I care about
your pathetic little boy needs.
That's the best spot for
my cuisine of discord.
Why don't you peddle your
second-rate beef bowls
somewhere else?
"Second-rate beef"?
Is that so?
Well, how about we settle
this with a Food War, creep?
It would be my pleasure.
Be careful, Meat-Meat!
You could end up getting cursed!
Hello, Administration?
It looks like this is leading
to another Food War again.
[ERINA] Excuse me. Would you
mind moving aside, Ikumi Mito?
WHAT?!
[gaaahhh!
Miss Erina, I-I-I'm so sorry!
You, Nao Sadatsuka!
You will stay fifty yards
away from Erina!
[waahhh!]
My beloved best-friend-ever
just spoke to me!
Thank you so very much!
[HISAKO] (uhh...)
[GUY] Okay... Your festival
application form
has been approved, of course,
Miss Erina Nakari.
Sounds good, thank you.
Soma?
Oh, am I next?
Thanks a bunch.
[GUY]
Wha? A-are you sure about this?
(gasp)
[GUY] This puts you...
right in front of China-Soc!
(gasp)
[SOMA] Yup! Is it open?
Yeah...
but they're very popular.
They've been there forever.
No one would ever want to be
set up next to THEM.
[SOMA] (chuckle) Oh, yeah?
Well, that's great news to hear!
And as for what
I'll be cooking...
It'll be Chinese.
(GASPS!)
Remember that training camp
from hell where we had to cook
200 dishes for everyone?
I figured the only way I was
going to be able to squeeze in
some kind of a win
was by mostly appealing to
customers who were in
line to see you.
Worked out pretty well for me.
When you think about it,
in a way, I owe it all to you.
It was your help that got me
through it all.
You're the best, Erina!
How dare you mock me,
Soma Yukihira?!
I've had enough of you,
your face, and your
ridiculous insults!
So, I'll just do
like I did back then
and use Kuga's popular
Chinese cooking against him.
Unfortunately, that's the
only way I can see me
pulling a victory out of this.
[GUY] All right, your
application is approved.
[SOMA] (chuckle) Much obliged!
Now then, the stage is set!
Looks like I'll have to
wrangle that that fiery heat
of his by the horns!
[ERINA] Some Yukihira, about
these shops that we'll be
setting up...
You do know that if your
sales are in the red,
you'll be kicked out of school?
Huh? Leave school?!
[music playing]
[TSUKASA] Soma Yukihira?
[RINDO] That's right!
He made quite the show
of challenging Kuga at
the Lunar Feast eaerlier.
Oh?
What's with you, Tsukasa?
Can't you look at least
a little bit interested in this?
I'm not in the mood for
that kind of stuff.
Will the interior furnishings
going to be ready in time?!
Will everything be to spec?
I hope nothing's going to
collapse or anything!
God, I'm so nervous!
[laughing] You're the same
worrywart as always, aren't you?
However! We now have one more
thing to look forward to
at the Feast. [chuckle]