In today's news... The mysterious worldwide
Aurora Phenomenon has made its way to Japan.
The strange kaleidoscope of colors glowing
across the night sky, was first observed
on the west coast of the United States of America,
but soon began to quickly spread across the world.
The government believes the Aurora will
have a minimal impact on our daily lives,
and has confirmed to citizens that the
beautiful spectacle poses no danger whatsoever.
Hey, I'm gonna be a bit late. Huh?
Hello? Hello?
Look what you did!
But I had the light!
I had the light!!
Heh, he's mad.
Huh?
Are you okay!?
It's not safe to stay here.
Yeah, thank you.
Sorry, T.K.! We just got here!
Kari, it's heading right for you!
I'm on it!
Angewomon!
Tai, we need you!
Polly want a cracker?
Let's do this, Agumon.
I told him not to mess with my goggles.
Izzy these new glasses you gave me are completely useless!
I told you... It's only a prototype! Not ready to use!
Forget that, you've got an incoming attack!
Yeah, I can see that.
Agumon!
Digivolve!
Agumon digivolve to...
Greymon!
In 90 seconds, I'm going to open a
digital gate at the designated location.
You have to lead Parrotmon there,
and send it back to the Digital World.
Roger!
Greymon! Kari, TK!
Yeah, we're on it!
You need to drive it toward the gate!
Angemon!
Parrotmon isn't usually this eager to fight.
What's changed? Well, the Aurora for one thing.
One small hole in your theory... The aurora's all gone!
Sixty seconds 'til the gate opens!
We have to lead it there now!
I'm trying!
Don't let it get away, Greymon!
Angemon!
Greymon!
Oh no, you okay?
Stop him!
All right!
Oh no, the building!
Do something!
They're not gonna make it!
Look out!
Garurumon.
You've gotten sloppy, Tai!
Finally, Matt!
You took forever to get here!
Izzy, target is at the designated location.
Target is verified.
Gate opening in twenty seconds. Keep it there.
We can talk about this later on.
Fine. Let's finish this.
Greymon digivolve to...
MetalGreymon!
10, 9, 8, 7, 6...
...5, 4, 3, 2, 1, 0!
The Digital Gate confirmed closed.
Parrotmon's transport is complete!
Hm.
Hm!
Nice work, Tai!
Way to go, Matt!
Hurry, T.K.!
Only four of us showed up? What's
with that? Where's everyone else?
I'm sure they have their reasons.
Let's be grateful we were able to make it.
I just realized I hadn't had
breakfast yet. Anybody else hungry?
I am!
Food, food, food!
When am I not?
What about you, Kari?
Yeah, let's all go eat.
How about you, Tai?
I got class, which is more than I
can say for Matt. Smell ya later!
Hey Tai! Mom said she would like to
see your face again one of these days!
Sorry, guys, I've got things to do as well.
T.K., can you look after Gabumon?
Sure!
We're still eating, right?
Hey, Tai. You've barely started
on your breakfast... or your thesis.
Oh my, you still haven't started your thesis?
I'm working on some radical ideas.
That doesn't sound promising.
I don't get it, Tai, don't you even want to graduate?
Yes, I do! That I do know.
And what about a job?
Yeah, I'll get one!
Don't point at me with chopsticks!
I've got three job offers. And you?
I'm guessing you haven't even started looking yet.
Do you even know what you're doing?
I've totally got this!
It's just not the right time... that's all.
I have a right to know who's saying that.
Everybody's saying that. Word is you're
joining the Self Defense Forces as an officer.
Come on. That's the dumbest thing I've ever heard.
Sounded believable to me.
But I guess it's hard to keep rumors from spreading
when you're the center of the universe around here.
What do they call you, Digi-Ordained or something?
I don't really follow you.
Just this morning, you and your digi-friends
saved the day once again didn't you.
But I'm just a regular dude,
graduating to work a regular job.
You got an offer?
Yeah! My first choice!
All right! That's great news.
Mhm!
Mmm. I see. In other words... you're crying
after someone called you lazy, which you are.
Well, I don't think I used the word "crying."
It's just... it made me realize
what I really want to do after school.
So if you've got it all figured out, what do
you need me for, other than to buy you beer.
Tell me something,
you said you decided to go on to
grad school. Why not look for a job?
Good question.
You don't know?
I have no idea if grad school
is the right choice for me or not.
But trying to find the thing that I really want to do...
It just seems like I'm postponing the inevitable.
Most of our friends know what
they want to do in life already.
...It makes you wonder.
That's for sure.
Joe is on his way to being a doctor.
Mimi is accessorizing the internet
with the online startup she launched.
And Izzy's is already a company president!
Even Kari and Davis... They seem
to know exactly what they want to do.
What about, T.K.?
He's writing a novel. But he
hasn't let me read a word of it yet.
Hm. Novel, huh?
Seems like Sora's getting serious about flower arranging.
Yeah...
Too bad things can't stay the same forever.
Friends sometimes grow apart... as
their lives go in different directions.
Agumon and the other Digimon never change.
We've had lots of adventures with those guys, huh...
Too many to count.
...You're right. They don't change.
Why don't you take 'em to school with you?
Heh! Ha, that would be a total scene!
I think you should take them to your school.
Like that's even possible, I've
got things going on in my life, Matt.
It's been so crazy, John lost his job.
No one ever told me being an adult was so hard.
Matt, tell me... Do you think we'll...
Ayaka, what's wrong? Please wake up!
Is she all right?
She just passed out!
Matt, quick, call an ambulance!
Ayaka, please...!
Is she drunk?
No, she wasn't drinking! Ayaka!
Wake up!
Ayaka!
Well, you see, in these changing
times, we need new public policy,
"PEOPLE FALLING UNCONCIOUS FOR NO APPARENT REASON"
Thanks, guys. I know how busy you
all are. I appreciate you coming.
Digimon!
It's an emergency. So let's get to it then.
All right, gather around my monitor.
Hola! It's Yolei checking in!
I'm in Spain studying abroad.
The paella here is so gooood!
The camera can't focus if you move like that!
Aw, Hawkmon, your camerawork stinks. Give me that!
Well, don't smudge it!!
Like I said, I'm studying abroad in Spain.
I was checking out the local Digimon
community here. And then I got this email.
Yolei, you're zooming in too much.
Good. That's better.
I didn't know what to do with it, so I
thought I'd just pawn it off on... I mean...
just run it by the old IzMaster to help me figure it out.
You know... by himself.
I mean I'm really busy out here.
So, thanks for understanding and I'll
have an extra helping of paella for you!
Adios!
She said, "Pawn it off."
So then... What does the message say?
Rather than explain it myself, I think we
should hear it straight from the source itself.
Huh? You mean there's somebody else here too?
Okay! You can come in now!
Huh?
Good morning, DigiDestined!
It's nice to meet you all. I'm Menoa Bellucci
...associate professor at New York's Belica University.
And I'm her assistant, Kyotaro Imura. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Welcome to Japan, Menoa. If you need
a guide while you're here, let me know.
Thank you!
We're both specialists in a new branch of science
we're developing at Belica called Digimon Research.
We'd like your help in an investigation.
We're hoping you'll help us solve
a certain incident we discovered.
You're heroes after all... having
saved the world countless times.
So you've done your homework, I see.
Oh, we're excellent researchers.
We're here because we need your help with a mass
coma phenomenon that's currently occurring worldwide.
A number of people around the globe have suddenly
gone comatose with no explanation and no warning.
So far, worldwide, there have
been over 300 confirmed cases!
We didn't see a pattern at first, but then we noticed that
all the victims had something particular in common.
They're all...
Don't tell me, they're all DigiDestined.
Yeah, that's right.
You're as smart as they say. Izzy, I'm impressed.
Well, I guess if I wasn't so smart
you guys wouldn't be here, would you?
Anyway... Lately I've lost touch with
a number of DigiDestined in my database.
I was wondering what had happened to them.
So far, none of them have regained consciousness.
And their Digimon partners have also suddenly disappeared.
They just vanished.
No way.
Where'd they all go?
At all four sites we investigated, we detected traces
of the missing Digimon in the form of a digital noise.
So, whoever's behind this, is after the Digimon.
Yes. We're positive that's what they're after...
We analyzed the noise pattern, and after
performing a trace... we found the Digimon behind this.
However, it seems that the data pattern of this
Digimon differs from those in the Digital World.
So then it's...!
A new...
...Digimon...
Right. We're calling it... Eosmon.
Eosmon?
It's the first of its kind to be identified by us,
so I decided to name it after Eos, a
Titan who was the Greek goddess of the dawn.
It goes without saying, there's no way we can just
stand around waiting and let this to continue to happen.
A Digimon that robs DigiDestined of their consciousness...
However, the good news is we can save them.
It seems Eosmon robs people's
consciousness by somehow digitizing it.
And then... it saves the data in
cyberspace, in a location only it knows.
So then...
If we defeat Eosmon, and salvage their
consciousness data from cyberspace...
We can save every last one.
We're here because there's nowhere else
to turn! We desperately need you to help us!
Then we can't say no! Am I right guys?
Yeah. But just remember... All those
people's lives are on the line here.
This calls for a carefully crafted thought-out plan.
But we both know that we don't have the time for that.
Which is why... we already came up with one ourselves.
We're here to assist you in any way possible.
Let us know if there's anything we can do.
Guys, does everyone know what they're supposed to do?
Relax, I told you, we got this!
Hello! Can everybody hear me?
Loud and clear! Are you ready
to receive the consciousness data?
We're banking on the theoretical
possibility we can restore their
consciousness if we get all their data from cyberspace.
Okay, you're almost there.
Is everyone ready?
Yeah, we'll get this done in no time!
Good to see you've learned nothing, Tai.
Good luck!
Transmission complete.
Hm.
Execute mission phase two.
Commence backup of area data.
Position... identified, transferring enclosure.
Okay, let's begin.
Wide-area enclosure expansion at 100%.
Activate.
Enclosure complete. Now you can salvage
the data, if you do your job right.
Who does this joker think he's talking to?
All we gotta do is smack that thing down.
Let's go!
It's too fast!
Yes, but it can still be caught!
Do it!
We got it!
Over here!
Finish it!
What is this!?
What's happening...!?
It's digivolving.
Eosmon has...
it digivolved.
Who cares!?
Yeah, it's still going down!
Greymon!
Garurumon!
It had no effect!
Moth scales...! It excretes a type of
moth scale that deflects our attacks.
Even this?
What!?
Angemon!
It's too fast!
Those panels that it keeps launching off of...
It's for acceleration.
I'll stop it!
...No I won't!
Kabuterimon!
Menoa...! Is the area backup done?
Sixty-two percent. No! We need more time!
Tai, it's time we go all out!
Right! Let's go!
What's happening...?
It's Omnimon.
Go!
It's too fast!
That's why Omnimon's trying to anticipate it's next move.
Come on!
Now, Omnimon! Finish it!
What's wrong?
Omnimon!
What in the Digital World...? Why'd
Omnimon break apart? Izzy, what happened?
How should I know? Somehow they
reverted to their In-Training level?
Tsunomon!
Could it be...?
It's trying to get away!
I'll stop it!
Angemon!
Izzy, I'm going to...
Kabuterimon!
Huh?
Oh no, it's getting away!
I don't get it!
Why did Omnimon's fusion suddenly break apart?
It doesn't make sense...
even if he sustained significant damage.
But even worse, two of our Digimon
reverted to their In-Training level.
We just have to regroup and get back on our feet.
Back on our feet?!
Just look at them. What're we supposed to do?
Guys... Let's focus on Eosmon
and locating the consciousness data.
Don't worry. I'll look into
why Omnimon's fusion broke apart.
It could be, something in cyberspace
may be inhibiting digivolutions...
No.
Huh?
What do you mean?
And how do you know?
All I can say... is that's your problem.
Didn't know we had one.
Please explain yourself.
Do you know why Digimon partners
pick the children they work with?
It's because they're full of potential.
"Potential?"
The possibilities are endless...
Their choice results in growth.
And that growth and potential
produces an enormous amount of energy.
Surely you understand.
Your growth was the trigger...
For your partner Digimon to be able to Digivolve.
As we live our lives, the choices we make help us grow.
But as you grow older, the power
of your Digimon steadily dwindles.
And once it's gone... the bond between
Digimon and partner... is broken forever.
I don't get it.
You mean we just leave and go our separate ways?
What!? No way!
I'm afraid I don't follow either.
It's just like I said...
How come I didn't know any of this?
You guys don't have a monopoly on all-things Digimon.
But how come you know about this?
The first sign is an inability to
digivolve successfully to the next level.
Agumon!
Yeah?
Let's go! Eosmon is ours!
No, don't.
Forcing your partner to digivolve
accelerates your separation!
You don't know that!
Let's go, Agumon!
What in the.... huh?
I'm sorry, but that proves it.
That ring of light is the last
link to your Digimon partner.
Once it's gone, you'll go your separate ways.
This isn't fair.
I won't let this happen!
Where are you going!?
Wait, Matt!
Poor Matt.
This is awful. Does this mean we all have to...
say goodbye... to our Digimon once we grow up?
I have to agree with Matt. I'm not gonna let
this happen, even if what you say is actually true.
I'm going to find a way to fix this, no matter what.
I know how you feel.
But this is just the way it
is. There's nothing you can do.
Hey, Matt, look!
Huh?
Okay, on my way.
Come on, Gabumon.
You know, Tai, I'd hate to be
comatose like those Digidestined.
Think of all the meals I'd miss
Don't worry. We're gonna find them, and save them.
You got that right! And you can count on me!
I know.
Tai... is it true we have to say goodbye once you grow up?
I'm sorry, Tai.
Agumon...
Hey, let's eat.
Rub-a-dub-dub... thanks for the grub!
Great!
Thank you for this food.
So what made you want ramen so badly?
I'm hoping to open a ramen shop right here one day!
Consider this a "recon opp!"
This is yummy, thanks, Ken.
It's good, but you can get this kind of
ramen in Tokyo, and at a much cheaper price.
Who asked for your opinion, Cody?!
Come on Davis, I want some!
I think I like Matt's ramen much better!
Yummy!
They're gonna kick us out of here!
Looks like a telemarketer. What're you selling?
Oh! Hi, Matt! I didn't recognize the number!
Yeah, it sure has been a while.
Now?  I'm with Ken and Cody!
We're just chillin' eating ramen in New York City!
Yeah. T.K. told me you were there.
Digital gates really come in handy!
They're like a free plane ticket!
So have you noticed anything different about your D3s?
No. Not recently anyway.
Okay. Nevermind then.
Why, is something up?
Actually, I have a favor to ask.
A background check?
He asked us to look into two
Menoa Bellucci and Kyotaro Imura.
What does he want to know?
No idea.
Mmm! I smell a new case brewing!
Hey, Davis! I know who Bellucci is!
Really?
Since she was little she's been known as a wiz
kid, skipping grades, entering college way early,
and now she already has a Ph.D. and a patent.
Good to know! Well, let's just get this over
with, so we can go to a Major League game in Chicago!
Nice bachelor pad!
Kinda small though.
Who asked you!? Wait a minute... is this
really the first time you've been here?
Mm-hmm, I'd remember this smell.
Ooof.
The walls are really thin, so keep it down.
I think I'm gonna grab something to drink.
Uh, Tai...?
Huh?
What are these things?
They're nothing! They're not mine,
I'm just holding them for a friend!
If they're nothing, let me see them.
Only grownups can look!
Um, why are you so red?
You okay?
Agumon...
Huh?
We're never gonna grow apart, little buddy.
Never.
Huh?
Ahh!
Long time no see.
Master Gennai!?
We know Menoa is kind of famous,
but... the other guy? Kyotaro?
We didn't find a single thing about him.
And I used the internet and everything!
I feel like I let Matt down.
Maybe I should get him something.
Anybody know if he uses body spray?
Hello!
Huh?
How's it been going, guys?
You're all looking well!
Hey, Yolei. Thanks for coming so quick.
With a digital gate, Spain's practically next door!
It's handy being only minutes away from New York City.
Well, now that the hello's are out of
the way, would you mind helping us out?
Of course! That's why we came! So, what's the story?
We're trying to find out some info...
But we hit a dead end.
Maybe this calls for a different approach.
What if we just went straight to the source?
Oh, I get it.
Cody, what your were thinking is that we
should take a look around her laboratory.
And how're we supposed to that? The door's locked!
Ta-da!
Jackpot!
That opened a little too easily.
Hello in there...?
There it is.
A little too many books if you ask me.
Ok, now it's my turn to show what I can do.
Huh?
What a pretty picture.
What are they doing? They've been in there for awhile.
Matt, I think Kyotaro's got a gun!
So then it's true...? Our partnerships do end.
I'm afraid so Tai, and I'm sorry that
this is the way you had to find out about it.
Why am I just hearing about this now?
For the same reason why people don't like
to talk about how long they have to live.
Then this ring on my digivice...?
That's right. It shows how much time
you have left together as partners.
Once our partnership ends,
will... I mean... Agumon will...
What exactly happens?
Once the ring is gone, your Digimon will likely vanish.
Unless... if you still have some potential locked away...
Otherwise...
Okay, Palmon, let's finish doing
this inventory. The sooner, the better!
Okay!
Five, six, seven, eight, nine...
Mimi, I think you have a phone call!
Yeah, I hear it! Hold on one sec...
I'm hungry again, Kari.
Mmm, I'm kinda hungry too.
You're not looking too good, Matt.
You haven't had any sleep for hours!
You really need to get some shut-eye, or you'll pass out!
It's nothing that I can't handle.
Plus, we're in crisis mode.
Hmmm.
Huh?
Joe...!
Someone reported a loud noise from the warehouse...
And when the police finally got there...
they found Mimi collapsed all alone.
What's wrong with her, Joe?
We don't know yet.
There doesn't seem to be anything wrong with her at all...
except for being unconscious.
Eosmon... It's got to be him.
Tai, Izzy... I need to talk to you.
We could've talked anywhere... Why in here?
Because there are no cameras in here.
So you think we're being watched?
It's just in case... Pre-paid burner phones.
Your smartphones are traceable.
Burner phones... What are we, spies?
Let's brief each other on what we've been up to.
Good idea. I want to know what you two have been doing.
I met with Master Gennai.
What did he say to you?
Anything about how to stop the ring from
fading, or at least how to slow it down?!
We can mope about it later.
What's this?
Check out that bottom photo.
By her side... is that a Digimon?!
Yeah... no doubt.
So that means Menoa is a DigiDestined, just like us!
The fact that her Digimon partner
hasn't revealed itself means -
I don't know. There's something even
more suspicious. Menoa's assistant.
The big guy?
Check out page two.
Kyotaro started working for her around the same
time she announced her research findings about Digimon.
Right after.
I don't know who he is or what he wants...
but I'm gonna get to the bottom of this.
I don't like being made a fool of.
We'll leave him all to you then, Matt.
I'm currently analyzing the Eosmon fragments
we recovered. And I'm doing my best to locate it.
How's that going?
No luck at all, so far.
Just in case, I've already issued a warning
to all the DigiDestined in the database.
Thanks, Iz. Be careful out there, okay?
Try limiting your contact with the outside if you can.
Yeah, I... I know.
Guys if... If we can't... I
mean this could be the last time...
We have to win.
Oh, Sora, shouldn't we be joining the others?
I already decided... I wasn't going to fight.
I'm going to stay right here with you, Biyomon.
Huh?
So... what brings you here?
There's something I wanted to talk to you about in person.
I see.
We know you're Digidestined. With a Digimon partner.
Yeah, I am. Her name's Morphomon.
We met when I was nine and right away we were inseparable.
I even took her with me to school and on trips.
No matter where I went or what
I did... she was always with me.
I have such fond memories.
And now?
And now it's been eight years since our partnership ended.
Like you guys... I didn't know it would
happen, and when it did... I was confused, and sad.
Sorry, I didn't know.
I don't want others to have to
experience that same sad farewell.
I mean, don't you think that it's rather
unfair... they'll leave once we grow up?
That's why I research. There's so
much more to learn about Digimon.
So then... you don't know how to keep
us from losing our Digimon partners?
Sorry. I would've already told you if I did.
Why'd you come? Why'd you even
approach us in the first place?
Simple, because you're the best team.
So... If anyone can do it, it's
you and the original Digidestined.
I believe in you.
Come on.
Look, Matt... on the wall!
What is that?
Quick, Matt, we gotta go tell the others!
Yeah, hello?
Yes, I'm looking for a... Matt?
Davis, is this a secure call?
Safe and secure! I'm calling from a
public payphone, just like you told me to!
Excellent. Got any results on your end?
We hit the jackpot! Where should I start?
Start with her assistant.
That guy is as shady as they come, believe me.
Who even knows if his real name is Kyotaro Imura?
What do you mean?
Yolei, here. We were able to hack into Menoa's
office computer, which was chock full of research files.
While her assistant's laptop was suspiciously empty.
But I found evidence of a ton of data on
Eosman being wiped clean from his hard drive.
Really?
Ken here. I thought it was fishy, so I dug even deeper...
but there were no records of anyone
named Kyotaro Imura. It must be an alias.
It's like this guy doesn't even exist in the real world.
Not that I could find.
Maybe Menoa... is being used by him in some way.
I don't know. But would someone
like her... as brilliant as she is...
really allow herself to be used like that?
She's so pretty, if I'm still allowed to say that.
I'll tell ya what was purty, it was
that picture of Aurora, in Menoa's room.
Aurora?
The Roman goddess of the dawn.
Armadillomon is simply obsessed with her.
The goddess of dawn...
I taught him all about her!
Aurora?
You wouldn't know a goddess from a bodice.
Okay, anything else I should hear?
Yeah! Take us out for our favorite
sushi when we get back, your treat!
Let's make it All-you-can-eat!
It'll be arranged. Thanks, guys.
Let's go, Gabumon.
Right, Matt.
Wow... I never expected to find this...
after analyzing Eosmon's data.
So... this series of incidents is...
Izzy... any empty plastic bottles?
Kari? I wonder what she sent.
Which one next? What?
Huh?
So, no recyclables?
This is bad...
Izzy, which way should we go?
Hiroo! That's where Kari's being held!
And T.K.?
Matt is on his way to Nerima right now!
Tai... I can't get through to Joe. Be careful out there.
Joe too?
Slow down!
Hang on!
We stick together no matter what happens, right?
No matter what!
Let's do this, Gabumon!
I only hope that they're not too late.
Huh?
Wait a minute... that's not...
Did you locate Eosmon, Izzy?
Yes, but this is... there's way
too much... There's way too much data!
You found Eosmon?!
Menoa?
What took you so long? I've been waiting.
It's a trap.
What are you doing here?
I'm on to your pathetic attempt to
sniff me out and expose my evil plan.
But unfortunately though... you're too late.
I'm impressed!
If we can locate Eosmon, we'll
find the consciousness data.
And if we're able to defeat it, we can save
the three hundred people it stole the date from!
I'm too late?
That's right. While you were out playing
detective, Eosman just struck again.
He robbed your brother of his consciousness.
T.K.?!
Wait, Matt. He could be behind it!
Yeah! How do we know it wasn't you?!
Menoa?
What is it?
What exactly are you here?
Oh, right. I forgot to tell you,
I found a way to save everyone!
All I need from you is your database of
DigiDestined, and I should be able to do it right away!
Can I have it? Shouldn't take long.
Let T.K. go, now!
Or I swear...
Wait. Matt, you've got it wrong. I'm not who...
Don't play dumb! You used Eosmon to rob those
DigiDestined of their consciousness, didn't you?!
Let me show you something.
Menoa... When we were battling it out in
cyberspace... I managed to recover a piece of Eosman.
Did you, now?
Eosman contains a number of formulae
that had to be written by a human being.
And when I looked into them deeper...
it led me to a certain someone.
...Menoa Bellucci.
Eosmon is an artificial Digimon...
created by none other than you!
I guess you really are... as smart as they say.
FBI?
That's right, I'm Agent Kyotaro Yamada.
So then...
I'm on the side of the law, Matt.
Whoa! I guess we were wrong about him!
Yeah, it seems so.
I can see why you were mistaken. It's the haircut.
Well, then why the heck is the FBI involved?
Because of this... right here.
So then she is the person behind all of this!
She used Eosmon to steal their consciousness.
Tell me, Menoa... Why did you...
I did it for all of you.
T.K....
He was unconscious when I first got to him.
Menoa has been on the FBI's radar for several years
now... but we never had enough evidence against her.
I wanted to be the one to arrest her with my own hands...
But she's made a fool of the FBI
again. Which was one of her objectives.
She's with Izzy.
What do you mean... you did it for us?
That's the reason you robbed
everybody of their consciousness?!
No one in their right mind
would ask you to do that for them!
Yes. They all did.
Every one of them.
Izzy!
Oh no!
We're too late.
I'm sorry!
Tentomon's not here!
No good. The list has been stolen.
Kyotaro, what is Menoa up to?
I don't know. But many times she said she
wanted to save the DigiDestined if she was able to.
Does she really think that this is saving us?
Any idea where she might be?
No.
After all this there's nothing I can do...
It's not over yet.
Do you know something that we don't?
Take a look at this. It's a message from Izzy.
What do all those different numbers mean.
Those are coordinates.
Coordinates in the Digital World.
But there's nothing out there.
Nothing at all.
Well if Izzy left those coordinates...
that means Menoa has to be there!
Uh... you with us Matt?
You okay?
I don't know... You sure about this, Tai?
The second we find Menoa...
...Is the second we'll have to fight her and Eosmon.
And at that same second our
partners will have to digivolve...
And that will only speed up their goodbyes!
Even so... we can't just abandon all
those who lost consciousness forever.
So you're...  okay with that?
No, I'm not.
But still, someone's gotta do it!
So, this is my fate.
Opening a digital gate.
Try to make it back... in one piece, okay?
Mmh!
What is this place?
Is this the Digital World?
What's that?
Let's check it out.
What's this made out of?
I think it's crystal.
Hey, Matt, isn't this the train?
The one that goes to File Island?
I think you're right. But...
it's a totally different material.
What in the world's going on?
I'm impressed you were able to find me.
Where's the database that you stole?
Yeah, hand it over.
Okay... but maybe we should
ask everyone else. What d'ya say?
What's happening?!
What is this place!?
Look over there!
Kari...
T.K....
Mimi...
Joe...
Izzy...
Meiko...
They've all become kids again!
They're with their Digimon.
All these DigiDestined...
All of their memories... They're trapped in them!
Welcome to the Never World!
The perfect place to be a child forever.
You call this place perfect!?
You forced them to come here!
You're right. I am responsible for bringing them here.
But, believe me, they wanted to come.
They don't want to grow up.
They want to stay children.
That wish of theirs is what drew
Eosmon to them in the first place.
This is the only way.
The only way for us DigiDestined to be happy forever.
No one can stop a Digivice's
countdown ring. Believe me, I've tried.
The fated farewell with our Digmon... is inevitable.
However... if we return to our childhood...
we'll never have to leave our partners.
...We won't suffer all that pain...
Tai... Matt... I can save you, too.
Come join us. Join us in the Never World.
Tai, no!
Don't, Matt!
Let's get this show on the road!
We've got work to do.
Save them all!
All of them!
Yeah, ready when you are!
Oh, shoot.
Fighting will only reduce the time
you have left with your partners.
Well, it's worth the risk if we stop you!
So if this is our last time...!
Greymon!
We've got a two-on-one!
Let's use it then! Garurumon!
Yes!
It's all over, Menoa. We want everyone back.
You think you won... but, you
just delayed things a little.
The water!
It's turning into light!
What's going on?
What is all of this?
Eosmon.
We're surrounded!
There's so many of them.
Not good!
Insane.
This is my Digimon. I created
her to save the other DigiDestined.
She is a goddess.
No! She's not even a real Digimon!
When you were a kid you had a real Digimon partner!
That's right. And she was the best friend I ever had.
I've been trying to get her back ever since she vanished.
For years... and years... I've been very patient...
But no matter what I did, I couldn't
spark life back into her digital data.
Then one day...
...the day that the aurora appeared...
Life sparked into that lifeless digital data.
And the Eosmon that appeared... had a special ability.
It could digitize a Digidestined consciousness.
Exactly
When I realized that, I heard a voice in my head.
It said use this power... use
it to save the other DigiDestined.
It was Morphomon speaking to me.
That's why... I have to save her. And the
other DigiDestined throughout the entire world.
Throughout the entire world?
It's Izzy's list.
Every name and location... of
every known DigiDestined in the world.
Menoa, don't. Don't do it!
I'm going to bring them all to the Never World.
What you're doing is wrong!
They will be here forever... With their
best friends... and their fondest memories.
Stop her!
What's that?
Tentomon? What are you doing?
Greymon!
Huh? Patamon? They're attacking us?
Gatomon? Gomamon? Palmon?
Why are they doing that?
I think... they're being controlled!
No.
It's of their own free will.
This is their dream.
This is their desire.
This is where they belong.
And by trying to destroy it, you've become... the enemy.
This proves... that I was right from the very beginning.
But...  Does this mean...?
And now I save myself.
Now I can save all of the DigiDestined
that haven't lost their partners yet.
And there's nothing you can do to stop me.
Wow, nice one, ExVeemon!
You all right?
Yeah.
You should run...
What's that?
I told you it was bad idea to
connect your pad to the internet!
Hey, I have no choice!
When you're trying to save all the DigiDestined
around the world... you need to have a browser!
So all these Eosmon are after us, huh?
Spiking Strike!
Megaton Press!
I'm telling you, I think
something's happened to Matt and Tai.
Hey, Yolei! Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm okay!
Looks like we're gonna have to deal with this ourselves!
All right, guys. Everybody ready to go?!
Yeah!
We should be safe for a while here.
I guess so.
Huh?
What do we do now?
Maybe we were never good enough to win.
You're not alone, Tai.
We should fight.
Tai, let's go! We can do it.
We still have the power to defeat it.
But then, it'll all be over.
Do you understand what it means to keep fighting?
Of course, I do, what am I, an idiot?
But it's the only way that we can save everyone!
Besides, it makes us so happy to see how
you guys grew up to be so big and strong.
It's so exciting to see the changes
you've gone through in your lives.
You guys...
Besides... I have the feeling that
we're gonna see each other again one day!
So, come on, Tai, let's go.
Yeah, let's go, Matt!
Okay.
Let's go, Gabumon! Let's save them!
Let's show them the strength of our bond!
One last adventure!
Mhm!
Okay, guys! Time to go back where you belong!
More DigiDestined are on their way to join us here.
Lots of them from around the world!
This place will become even more fun than ever!
The smiles are never going to end!
You can all stay right here with
your best friend... together forever.
Let's stay here together... forever and ever.
I'm surprised you came on your own.
Did you change your minds?
You know that we didn't.
We rather save everyone.
That's nonsense.
This is our world. Our perfect world!
You ready, Agumon?!
Ready, Gabumon?
Yeah!
Attack!
Just leave. Just leave us be.
Your perfect world is nothing but a big lie!
Please, stop. Why are you destroying it?
All this place does is freeze people in their childhoods!
That's not true. I've saved them all from heartbreak!
As long as they're here... they won't
suffer that same sense of loss that I had!
Like having part of yourself... torn away!
This is unbearable.
To lose something... something so important...
I can't... I can't bear it...!
What's happening?
What is this?
Only I know how it feels to suffer like this!
I will save everyone... because...
I'm going to become their goddess!
I don't believe it...
She digivolved... No!
She was absorbed...!
Menoa...
Tai, Matt!
Matt...!
I'm alright! Where's Omnimon?
Omnimon!
Now, ExVeemon, go!
Ex-Laser!
Blast Rings!
Nice one, Aquilamon!
Unfortunately, we're still way out numbered!
I smack 'em down, but they keep coming!
I know, but we still owe it to the others not to give up!
I agree with Ken!
Who said anything about giving up?!
I mean, it's not like we're the
only one's fighting around the world!
Omnimon!
This isn't over yet.
Agumon!
Kari...?
Izzy?
Let go, T.K.!
Let me go, Kari! You, too, Izzy!
We've gotta save Agumon and Gabumon!
T.K., let me go! I need to do this to save you!
I know you understand me, Kari! Escaping into
your old memories is no way to live, believe me!
We can't stay kids forever, we have to grow up...
You okay, Matt...
But, why?
You have to... grow... up!
We all have to... grow up... one day!
Into the future!
That's Tai...
Where's Matt?
Tai...
Big brother?
Kari... you're all here!
We are here.
I used to hate that damn whistle.
Wait, Tai, where's Eosmon?
Let's go, Gomamon! I don't like being turned into a kid!
Way ahead of you, Joe!
Palmon, let's join this fight!
Yeah! Eosmon is in for some prickly pain!
Ready, Patamon?
The big kids need some help!
There's no bigger kid than me!
What do you say, Gatomon?
Just one thing... Meow.
So that's Eosmon's top digivolved form.
We can only hope! I'd hate to think
there's another level bigger than this one!
You said it. Get ready Tentomon?
I believe...
I believe in you all!
Harpoon Torpedo!
Needle Spray!
Tai...Matt...
Agumon, I want to save them as bad as you.
I know exactly how you feel, Tai.
Gabumon... I want to fight alongside
you... even if it's our last battle.
Well let's get to it then, Matt.
This is going to be our... final digivolution!
Where's that light coming from?
Pretty...
It's a new... Digivolution!
I don't believe my eyes!
Neither do I...
That is prodigious.
I need you, Matt!
I'm with you!
Oh, Morphomon! We'll be together
forever! Morphomon, everyone's avoiding me.
I can't wait to grow up so people
will stop treating me like a weirdo.
What are we seeing?
They're Menoa's memories.
I'll make a life for myself! I'm gonna be fine on my own!
Morphomon
I can hear the pain in her voice.
It's a cry for help.
She's been crying on the inside.
Morphomon... Morphomon!
Morphomon! Guess what! They told me in school
that I skipped enough grades to start college!
It's time for me to live my own life for once!
I'm going to help the world by
conducting the research I love!
Morphomon...?
Morphomon! What's wrong? Why are you glowing like that?
Morphomon...!
Morphomon... Morphomon...!
Morphomon...
I... I...
I made this choice... I chose to grow up!
Did I... did I make the wrong choice?
I just don't know. Nothing makes sense.
Somebody... please... somebody help me!
Menoa! We're here to help you!
You didn't make the wrong choice!
That's right. Even if you made a bad choice along the way.
We all live with the choices we
make. It's what makes us human!
We may not be able to change our fate... but who cares!?
Our lives aren't preordained!
That's why we'll never give up fighting the good fight!
We'll always be together...
Please forgive me.
Whoa...
Is it all over?
Boy, I hope so.
Seems like it
Yes, I have to concur.
Ah, thank goodness!
Those older guys know what they're doing!
Yeah, they must have won.
I reckon!
Where am I...?
I can't see without your glasses.
Oh, Mimi! I had the strangest dream last night.
Another beautiful day!
It's so hot.
Well, it is summer.
Tai, do you remember the first time we met?
How could I forget?
Wow! What an amazing view!
I like coming up here...
You still have that harmonica, huh?
It's actually a new one!
I suddenly felt like playing again.
Well then, let's hear something.
Hey, Tai...
What is it?
I want you to buy me some shaved ice.
Huh? You're such a handful!
You're favorite is melon-flavored, right?
You know, Tai, you sure have gotten big.
And you never change.
In case you didn't know, you're
the best partner ever, Matt.
Hey, Tai...
Hey, Matt...
What will you do...?
...tomorrow?
That's a good question. I guess no one knows...
...what tomorrow may bring.
Whoa.
Anything can happen. Tomorrow...
We can...
And that was how we finally grew up.
But... our story hasn't ended yet.
It's just "digivolving" in a new direction.
But I can promise you this... I will see you again!