[fighting efforts]
Damn it! I can't
tell who's who.
I can't sniff out the
transformed fakes
from our own guys.
[agreeing whine]
Hm?
You're finally back,
Shino. You okay?
Yes, I am.
Be careful. There's
no telling where the
enemy will come from next.
[painful grunt]
I had a feeling
you were one of them.
Damn it!
Byakugan!
It's no good. I can't
distinguish them by
looking at their chakra.
[shocked gasp]
Are you a fake?!
No, stop! I'm real!
Not being able to tell
who the fakes are is so
annoying.
Whatever happens, don't
step out of your circle!
Do it and you'll be
considered a transformed
enemy!
Choza, we aren't getting
anywhere with this situation.
I know that, but
it can't be helped!
So we'll just have to
continue to wait.
Just wait?! Wait
for what?!
Got it? No one here moves!
We can't tell who's
a disguised enemy!
More of those Reanimated
Shinobi can show up
anytime, too.
Anyone who moves will
be considered an enemy.
So don't move!
And in the meantime, the
number of our wounded
is only going to keep
increasing.
We have no choice
but to wait now.
Lava Style!
Lava Monster Jutsu!
It never ends...
Yeah, we have to
do something about
the real one!
[startled yell]
Make sure you
don't get hit!
[shocked gasp]
[determined grunt]
[grunts of pain]
What now?!
Don't panic!
Surround them!
[shocked gasp]
[surprised gasp]
I've detected a new
group of the enemy.
It's a small unit,
but the chakra
is unusual.
I think...
It's Madara!
What did you say?!
Madara is now leading
a small unit into battle!
And can you tell
who's in this unit?
This chakra is...
The Fourth Mizukage!
Do you mean the one
who was a Jinchuriki?
There's no doubt about it.
And all the others are
Jinchuriki, too!
I can't believe he
had more pawns under
his control...
And Naruto...?
Where is he?!
Finally caught up
with you, Naruto!
Well, it's about time!
What have you been doing?
A persistent pee, yo!
Man, sure took
you long enough!
Well...had other
problems, too.
Anyway, one of your
shadow clones contacted
me earlier.
How are all the others
doing, by the way?
They should arrive on the
frontlines of every last
battefield right about now.
Then all the fakers we're
gonna seek out. All the
bad guys we'll defeat,
no doubt!
Yeah, that's the plan.
But we gotta hurry!
Shikamaru...Just how
long do we have to
stay like this, anyway?
If that big statue thing
comes back anytime soon,
then we're gonna be toast!
Relax, it's only
until Naruto arrives.
And until he does, no
one steps inside of
anyone else's circle!
Or they'll be tagged
as an enemy, even you.
But can't we just confirm who
people are using secrets only
their friends would know?
No way! I mean, we already
lost some people trying
that method, remember?
Sometimes a lucky guess
ends up being right.
Man, this is dull...
[agreeing hum]
I'm sorry about this.
Please be patient
just a little longer.
Sure thing, I
understand.
You made it!
Yeah, finally
got here!
[shocked gasp]
Nawaki...?
All right, there he is.
Oh great, that's
good news.
He's gotten really
flashy though, hasn't he?
Hey, Naruto!
Naruto?
He looks just
like Nawaki...
We already got the
heads up from HQ.
Thank you for coming.
Although I have to say,
I'm surprised Lord
Raikage gave the okay for this.
Well, you can thank
Granny Tsunade for that!
She convinced Pops
Raikage to let me
do this!
Tsunade sent that boy
out here? Exactly who
is he, anyway?
He has the Nine Tails sealed
inside him. He's what
all the adults call a
Jinchuriki.
What? That boy?!
His name is Naruto,
my idiot classmate who's
yelled about becoming Hokage
since he was a kid.
Who are you calling
an idiot, idiot?
Anyway, now that I'm here,
I can find all the enemies
for you.
But now? He makes you
believe it actually
might be possible
for him to become Hokage.
It's crazy!
Lady Tsunade has hedged
all her bets on him.
Naruto, huh?
So guys like Nawaki
and the old me exist
in this era, too...
Everybody, come on!
Let's take down the
transformed white ones!
Yeah!
Right!
Yeah...
We can start with
that guy right there!
[stunned gasp]
The rest of you around
me I know aren't
imposters!
All of you who've gotten
Naruto's seal of approval
can leave your circle.
Consider anyone else
the enemy.
Now let's go!
Hey, stop right there!
Get back!
Help me!
Do not approach!
What's the matter?
My husband! He still
might be saved with
Medical Ninjutsu!
Just stay put!
I told everyone
not to move.
How can you prove
you're allies? You can't,
and that's the whole point.
I know, but at
this rate...!
[breathless groan]
He's going to die
without your help!
Please, I beg of you!
Help him! Do what you can!
Don't let my husband
die right here in
my arms!
[shocked gasp]
[scared breath]
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?!
If you can't trust me, then
I'll just take my own life
right here and right now.
But please, just
save my husband!
Hey, stop that!
Come on...
No! What if
they're enemies?
And what if they're
actually comrades?
I have to tend to
that man's injuries.
[shocked gasp]
Sakura!
[scared gasp]
Are you okay, Sakura?
It's Naruto!
Naruto? How
did you...?
Well, it looks like
you're all right to me!
Gentle Fist!
He was a fake after all!
Bad news this way!
Hinata's in trouble!
Neji!
[worried gasp]
[grunts]
Damn! I won't
make it in time!
[triumphant grunt]
[worried reaction]
Hinata!
[shocked gasp]
[gasp]
So that one was a
transformed enemy?!
All right now,
who's next?!
The two to
your left!
You got it!
Don't tell me...
Neji! Where are you
going? This way!
[painful groan]
[gasp]
Sorry I'm late!
N-Naruto?!
That's Naruto?!
He smells different
than before!
It's gonna be
all right!
[quiet breath]
[loud grunts]
Are you hurt at
all, Hinata?
I'm okay.
Summoning Jutsu!
[startled gasp]
Finally...
It seems you've managed
to successfully groom
that brat Nagato.
I never imagined the
next summoning
would be...
[amused chuckle]
If I'm not mistaken,
you are...
The caster of
the Reanimation
Jutsu has a keen
understanding of war...
To think of using you...
Did you say Reanimation
Jutsu? Then this is not
the Rinne Rebirth Jutsu?
Why didn't you tell
us sooner that Naruto
had arrived?
Because he just got
here, that's why.
Sure I happened to run
into him first, but I was
still in the middle
of fighting.
Naruto smells different
than he did before, so I
didn't notice him.
And besides, you're the
one with long range vision.
But he looks different
than before.
Even his chakra
nature's changed.
Then who are you to
talk if you can't even
recognize him now?
Are you really Naruto?
I hope you're not
a transformed white
one, too.
I'm really Naruto.
So you say, but
can you prove it?
No! It is Naruto!
You can tell by his eyes.
But Hinata...
And besides, he saved me.
Actually, Naruto saved
me, as well.
Wait, hold on! When
did you get here, Shino?
Did you know a fake you
showed up just a while ago?
Well I'm the real deal.
I've been with Naruto
since shortly after he
arrived on the battlefield.
Naruto, I'm sorry about
this. We've all become
so distrustful.
At least now that I'm
here, you don't have to
fight a defensive battle
anymore.
I'll find all the
fake ones one by one.
All right! That
sounds good to
me, Naruto.
And I've memorized
your new scent.
And your chakra.
Well, unfortunately, smell
and chakra don't matter
much with their transformations.
Those guys can mimic
everything, even chakra.
But don't worry,
I'll take them down.
And when I do, as you saw,
they even turn into trees!
When I'm in this mode,
I can sense all the malice
and hatred they give off.
I'm gonna find every last
one of those fakes, and then
together, we can defeat all
of them!
The one we're supposed
to protect...is always
protecting us...
I'm so useless!
Please, don't worry
about it.
You've already protected
me twice. It's time I
return the favor.
Oh, uh...I wasn't
worried or anything.
I just, uh...
I can see it in your eyes.
Don't be so hard on
yourself. You are strong,
there's no doubt!
[distant yelling]
Let's go!
Which one's the fake?!
The one with the axe!
Got it!
And that guy, too!
[shouting out in the distance]
Thank you, Naruto.
[startled gasp]
Not so fast!
[grunt]
[panting]
All set!
Sai, now!
Sealing Jutsu!
Crouched Tiger
Bullet!
Good! Only three
more left now!
You all right, Sai?
Yes, I can keep going.
Please keep drawing
tigers without fear!
And I shall keep
protecting you!
Here come the enemy
reinforcements now.
There's a whole lot
of them, too.
They're the white ones...
Are these the ones that
can transform their chakra
as well as their bodies?
It's gonna start
getting wild, Kakashi.
Our reinforcements are here.
Or should I say
reinforcement, singular?
But Naruto can make
multiple Shadow
Clones, as well!
But, uh, actually, not
right now, I can't do that.
Today, I'm going for
quality instead of
quantity.
And so, here goes...
Things have changed around
here, Kimimaro!
Yes, I can tell that
time has passed simply
by looking at you.
It appears that you've
grown up in ways other
than just your height.
Get ready! Here I come!
[painful grunt]
I put too much effort
into that...
What's going on?
He's just as rash and
scatterbrained as ever.
That's for sure.
You're kidding. Is
that him?
Oh, yeah. It's
him all right.
It appears that Naruto
has now reached all
of the battlefields.
That's good.
Naruto has managed to join
up with Gaara and the
rest of the Fourth Company.
And all their enemies-the former
Kage of the Wind, Lightning,
Earth, and Water-have been
successfully sealed.
So, what's the plan?
What do we do now,
Shorty Gramps?
I told you before, I'm
the Tsuchikage!
We should rendezvous
with another company
and keep fighting.
Our real enemy isn't
all the reanimated
shinobi.
It's Madara!
You're right. This war
will not end until
he's brought down.
Our target should
be Madara.
Octopops and the real
me should be heading
over this way right
about now.
[determined hum]
Over there!
The merged First and Second
Companies have sniffed out
almost all their enemies.
[grunt]
Earth Style!
They're advancing with
incredible momentum!
[aggravated grunt]
What was that, Naruto?!
Sorry, Bushy Brows!
The Third Company
also seems to be
dominating their
field.
Wind Style: Rasen Shuriken!
This is...
...enormous!
The Fifth Company
has gained the upper
hand as well.
[loud grunt]
[attacking yell]
The Medical Unit has
suppressed all their enemies.
Seems the plan worked. The
tide of battle has
undoubtedly turned.
It's overwhelmingly
in our favor.
See?
Hmph.
Now all we need to do
is to stop Madara, who's
approaching with the Jinchuriki.
We should focus all our
remaining strength there
and hit him with everything
we've got!
[heavy grunt]
Please, hold on!
Just wait one second!
What is it?!
I suddenly sense a
new enemy near Gaara's
Fourth Company.
[struggling grunt]
But what is this chakra?!
[panicked gasp]
Wait, was is that?!
What's the matter?
What are you sensing?
It's right over there!
What now?
Hm?
The Second Tsuchikage!
I thought that you had
him sealed away, Gaara?!
Impossible! In that
state, he fragmented
himself?!
What do you mean?
Lord Mu was able to split
his body, and in doing
so, he created clones.
Well, no. Not clones.
It's closer to say that he
splits his body into two
pieces.
Although each one only
has half his normal
strength.
No, I don't mean him.
Someone else is here!
What?!
Really?! There's
another one?!
[shocked gasp]
That one is...
[stunned breath]
Who is it?!
So he's come...
That...is
Madara Uchiha!
That's him...?!
So that's what he looks
like beneath his mask, huh?
But he looks exactly
the same as he did before!
What is going on here?!
What do you mean?
Take a close look
at his eyes.
He's a reanimated
shinobi!
The Reanimation Jutsu
brings the dead back
to this realm.
Which means he's
been dead...
Wait just a second!
HQ reported Madara elsewhere,
approaching in the other
direction with a bunch
of Jinchuriki.
Isn't that correct?
But there's no mistaking
it! He's definitely
Madara Uchiha!
He's the one I fought
against back in my
younger days!
But then who could
possibly be the man...
...behind the mask?
If that guy up there
is the real Madara...
...that means the guy
with the mask who we
thought was Madara
isn't actually him?
Yes, so it seems.
What is this?!
It can't be...
Is this ninjutsu?!
We can't outrun it!
Woah...This is way
out of our league!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Madara Uchiha."
Is this the power
of a God?