-Kakashi.
- If even the
faintest scent still
lingers from when
Sasuke was here.
-Yeah, that's right.
No way we're giving up
after coming this far.
- We'll just keep
searching until we
can't find any
trace of his scent.
-Byakugan.
Nothing.
We have to find him.
-Sasuke.
[whine]
-Yeah, I know it.
There's no trace of it.
His scent is gone.
-Damn it.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Where did you go?
We've done all we
could, but now it's
time we went back
to the Hidden Leaf.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sasuke.
[theme music]
TOBI: What are you doing?
The preparations are
already completed.
- Whenever I look
upon the full moon,
it takes me back to that night.
Memories.
I've been trying
so hard to forget.
I can finally recall
things about Itachi.
Faint memories that were
buried deed in my heart
and now floating back
up to the surface.
-By all means, flee.
Cling to your retched life.
And when you possess the same
eyes as me, come and face me.
-No, wait!
-I saw him crying then.
I thought I'd imagined it.
I didn't realize it.
It seems that what you told
me is the truth after all.
-So what about Itachi's eyes?
You going to transplant them?
-No, I won't.
What Itachi wanted to
see, and what
I will see from here on out,
will be completely different.
I can't do what
Itachi wished me to.
I will restore the Uchiha
clan in my own way.
- So, um, I needed to
talk to you, Kisame.
- First,
it was Zetsu and now you're
coming around bothering me?
I actually thought
you were dead, Tobi.
- It turns out that you
will be the last to know.
I'm sorry that I had to deceive
you, the person closest to me.
-So that's how it is.
I had no idea.
I never would have guess you
were Tobi, but I'm relieved.
If you're the one
pulling the strings,
that makes it easier for
me former Lord Mizukage.
I mean, Madara.
TOBI: I shall continue
to count on you, Kisame.
-The same goes for me.
So Itachi is out, and now
this little brother joins up.
What an interesting
turn of events.
- We, the Taka,
will destroy the Leaf.
-Easier said than done.
So how?
What's your plan?
- We are going to
kill the elders,
the others are of
no concern to me.
- If you aim high the ones
below will shield them.
It's not going to be easy
as you seem to think.
And you four Taka
don't have the strength
to handle this kind of
thing by yourselves.
-Ah, listen, Kisame.
You really shouldn't make the
mistake of underestimating us.
We still haven't settled
that little game of ours
we started the other day.
So let me show you my real...
-Stop it, Suigetsu.
Enough.
- Sasuke, you haven't
trained them very well.
SUIGETSU (VOICEOVER): He
stopped me with just his arm.
-Suigetsu, are you that stupid?
This isn't the time or place.
- My objective is that
sword of his, Samehada.
I've been traveling
with Sasuke only
so I can get my
hands on that thing.
-All right, Sasuke.
What now?
-Fine by me.
Do whatever you feel
you have to, Suigetsu.
But know this,
you cannot win against him yet.
KISAME (VOICEOVER): Yet, huh?
- Gee, thanks a lot for the
vote of confidence, Sasuke.
Have a little faith.
I'll treat you to some
tasty shark's fin.
- The Akatsuki is low
on manpower right now.
We should avoid
unnecessary skirmishes.
- The pot shouldn't be calling
the kettle black, you know.
- We share common
interests so from here on,
Taka will little work
together with the Akatsuki.
-Oh, is that right?
And just what's in it for us?
-A tailed beast.
-Tailed beast?
-You don't know about them?
-Of course we do.
They're enormous
amounts of chakra
that physically manifest as
beasts, like the Nine Tails,
and they're held within hosts...
-So what does that mean?
-They're chakra monsters.
Long ago, the first Hokage
collected several of them
and kept them under his control.
Each time a great
ninja war threatened,
he used them to maintain the
power balance distributing them
to other lands, starting with
the five great nations as proof
of alliances.
You could call them the
ultimate chakra weapons.
Not a bad proposition, is it?
-How generous of you.
- However, if you betray
the Akatsuki, you will die.
- There are nine of the
tailed beasts in this world.
And the Akatsuki has
collected six of them so far.
Only three remain.
- Taka and the
Akatsuki will split up
to hunt the last three.
That is our immediate goal.
- You don't have the
Nine Tails yet, do you?
-Taka will captured Eight Tails.
The Akatsuki will
hunt the other.
That means Naruto.
-Well?
TOBI: It went perfectly.
-That's good to hear.
- Itachi is dead,
so our eyesore is finally gone.
And now,
we need no longer keep our pack
to stay away from
the Hidden Leaf.
-Such a long wait.
- But now, we can proceed
according to plan.
It was worth the wait.
Itachi had placed insurance
in Sasuke, the Amaterasu.
- Itachi believed no one
knew the truth about him,
so why would you
go to such lengths?
- True intentions
aside, he probably
feared I would try
to recruit Sasuke,
and wanted to guard against
such an eventuality.
- But whoever would have
thought that the Akatsuki would
have to lose so many members
just to get to this point?
-We face trouble at every turn.
But everyone made a
valuable contribution
in their own way, Deidara.
Sasori.
Hidan.
Kakuzu.
Without them we wouldn't have
gotten as far as we have.
And thanks to them,
everything is following my plan.
Most importantly, I claimed
Sasuke and won him over.
- So,
where is this Eight Tails guy?
- You don't know who
you're messing with.
We're not going to say anything,
not to the likes of you.
We of the Yotsuki clan
are stronger than that.
We don't betray one of our own.
Never.
- A fearful heart is
more likely to crack.
-Suigetsu, enough.
He's under Sasuke's
genjutsu now.
- Aw, I was just
getting to the fun part.
- Give me the location
of the Eight Tails.
- He's busy training at
Unraikyo, Storm Cloud ravine.
-And what does he look like?
He's the wielder of many
blades, eight blades.
He has steel tattooed on his
right shoulder and bull horns
on his left cheek.
SUIGETSU (VOICEOVER):
That's just great.
Those eyes of his have improved.
All that's going to do is
make him even more difficult
to deal with.
KARIN (VOICEOVER): Oh wow,
Sasuke has gotten even cooler.
JUGO (VOICEOVER):
It's nice here.
I think I'll be able to
keep myself under control.
I feel so calm.
[footsteps]
-Oh, my sight.
Light, too bright.
Noon already?
Damn it, man.
No fooling, you fool.
Training all morning,
my belly's starving.
I'm a rap loving guy.
I got me a hunch that I just
decided on sukiyaki for lunch.
Yeah.
Hm?
- Are you the Jinjuriki
host of the Eight Tails?
- That's Lord Eight Tails
Sir, to you.
No, wait.
You say,
are you Lord Jinjuriki, sir?
Got it?
-I'm here to capture you.
-Un-huh.
Now here is what you say.
Freeze, let me capture
you, sir, please?
You got it?
-Suigetsu, take the right.
Jugo take the left.
Karin, behind me, cover my back.
-Let's see now.
I'm in the midst of my rhymes,
y'all are busting my time.
Now, I gotta spit my
line, fools.
You fools.
- We're not supposed to kill
the Jinjuriki, you know.
Remember what the Akatsuki
told us, Suigetsu?
-Don't worry.
I feel his chakra
loud and clear.
Damn it,
talk about a showy diversion.
-Come on.
- Only one who gets to dig
me, is me, yo.
So stand back and stay back or
you're gonna get whacked, fool.
Yah.
-Just step back, Suigetsu.
-I am peeking at you.
See you're not quite through,
but in all your crew,
your brain cells are few.
-Stop joking around.
Blood lust bravery
makes me go ballistic.
Knowing you can't stop
me makes me optimistic.
My blades goin' round and
next you're going down.
Come on and get your fill of
my sweet and awesome skills.
Yah.
My powers are flashin'.
Still more in my stash.
Eight Tails, that be me,
the rappin' Killer B. Yah.
This battle, you initiated,
but I'll leave you humiliated.
Before you get disintegrated...
ow.
Bit my tongue.
-What's up with this guy?
He's completely
crazy but he still
managed to take down Jugo.
SUIGETSU (VOICEOVER): First he
blocks my executioner's blade
and then he wields
it like he owns it.
What is this guy?
- You made me bite my
tongue, fools.
[groaning]
KARIN (VOICEOVER):
You all right?
-Yeah.
-I'll handle this.
- Just who in the hell
are all y'all fools.
You fools.
-Would you shut up all ready.
You're getting on my nerves.
-Yo, who are ya?
Why you want to capture me?
What's the deal, yo?
- I'm under no
obligation to tell you.
- Why do we have to fight
such a weird rhyming
guy in the first place anyway?
This whole thing is a pain.
- It's to obtain more power
as quickly as possible.
If you don't like it, leave.
-Pf.
SUIGETSU (VOICEOVER):
That's your prerogative.
- And I also want to confirm
the Akatsuki's promise,
whether they're pledge to give
us the tailed beast is true.
Regardless,
we are the ones who are
going to use the Akatsuki,
not the other way around.
So all of you,
keep that in mind.
KILLER B (VOICEOVER): Akatsuki?
-Yes, of course.
KARIN (VOICEOVER): Oh,
you are so cool, Sasuke.
I knew that he would never
let himself be used as a pawn.
- OK, let's do this and shut up
this witless pain in the ear.
-That is the plan.
[theme music]
- Your illusions,
I'll obliterate,
and you, I shall annihilate.
My true mode as the tailed beast
abode is that of a monster.
See, I told ya,
transformation, yah.
Eight Tails will make
you pee your pants,
you little ants.
To spare my foes,
I was born a glorious longhorn.
Ya.
KARIN (VOICEOVER): Such
Chakra, is this even possible?
JUGO (VOICEOVER): Next time on
Naruto Shippuden, "The Eight
Tails versus Sasuke."
SUIGETSU (VOICEOVER):
That's his true form?