We've been
walking quite
a while.
Ever since the
sun began to
rise.
It's got to
be time for
us to fight,
then.
But who are
we fighting
against?
No way...
Are they close?
Something feels
familiar,
nostalgic...
[surprised gasp]
Itachi Uchiha?!
Nagato?!
You know
these guys,
Naruto?
Yeah, I do.
I know both
of them.
Incredible. I never
would have thought
I'd have to battle
you again, Naruto.
Not like this...
For you, it's been
a while since we
last met, hasn't it?
But for me,
it's only been
a matter of
moments.
You're different
now, Naruto.
Oh, you
mean this?
I sure am!
I'm in control of the
Nine Tails Chakra!
What you're seeing
is my Chakra mode!
Your what?!
I see...
You are quite
different then.
I see it
in your face.
You're now
in command of
the power of
the Nine Tails?
I'm impressed
with your
development.
Well, he and
I are sibling
students.
I'm not
surprised
at all.
I made him be what
he could be. Talk all
you want his control
is thanks to me.
No way!
That's so
not true!
Have you
actually
done it?
Have you been
able to
overcome
hatred, Naruto?
Sure did!
As my elder,
you taught me
about what
pain really is.
Then Octopops
showed me how
to handle the
Waterfall of Truth.
And my
mom and dad...
Everyone who cares
about me helped me!
I have all of you
to thank!
I see...
Naruto...
There's something
I must ask you.
Huh?
Wait, that reminds
me! I have stuff
that I wanna
ask you, too.
Well...It seems
that I found you
first! Eight Tails
and Nine Tails...
With those two cards
up my sleeve, Madara will
have no choice but
to fall right into my hands...
Too bad I won't get to see
the look of shock on his
face under that ridiculous
mask when he realizes I've won!
[sinister chuckle]
[anxious gasp]
Fire Style!
Fireball Jutsu!
[low grunt]
Naruto, there's
something I
must ask you.
Huh?
Wait, that reminds
me! I have stuff
that I wanna ask
you, too.
[gasps]
Yo!
[painful grunt]
Hot, huh?
Didn't mean
to burn, when
will I learn?
That's Samehada...
So, Kisame's
dead...
He's still
talking!
Naruto, don't
forget that
they're both
being controlled!
If he cuts you
off, you just
gotta roll! Okay?
Above you!
I see him!
[grunts]
Where is
Sasuke?
[quick breath]
He says that
he's gonna
take revenge on
the Leaf Village!
He even went
and joined up
with the Akatsuki!
Why did he
turn his back
on the village?!
He found out
the truth about
your top-secret
mission!
And now he's
gonna destroy
the Leaf!
What secret
mission?
Did Madara...?!
Yeah, he did.
And Madara told
me the truth about
what happened, too!
Oh he did,
did he?
Just tell me!
Is what he said
actually the truth
or isn't it?!
Was the Uchiha
Clan really going
to take over
the village?!
Naruto!
That's enough.
Is he telling
the truth, Itachi?
Itachi...
You made yourself look
like the bad guy in order
to save Sasuke and the
whole Hidden Lead Village!
Sasuke understands
all of your pain, and
your resolve to do
what you did!
But Sasuke
isn't like you...
He's really
going to
destroy the
Hidden Leaf!
He's going to kill
everyone in order to
avenge the pain...
...That the
village caused
his older brother
that he loves so much.
Damn that
Madara...
So he did
know the truth
about me...
And does everyone
in the village
know about this
as well?
Kakashi Sensei
and Captain Yamato
heard it when I did...
But, there wasn't
any proof of what
Madara told us.
So Kakashi Sensei
said to keep quiet.
I don't think
there's anyone
else that knows,
though.
Then please, Naruto...
You mustn't tell
anyone about this.
You cannot let
the Uchiha Clan's
name be tarnished!
Also...
Damn! My
body's moving
on its own!
[struggling grunts]
Universal Pull!
That was nicely
dodged, Naruto!
Thanks! I'm a whole
lot stronger now
than I was when
I fought against Pain!
You'll have to
take care of
Sasuke.
I was always
gonna do that!
I was right to
believe that you
could finish this.
[stunned gasp]
Okay, Naruto!
Get me away from
here! I can't move
on my own anymore!
[surprised groans]
Summoning Jutsu!
[shocked gasp]
Or maybe
I can...
Well would you
make up your
mind already!
C'mon!
I'm behind
you!
Got it!
Okay!
Fire Style!
Phoenix Flower
Jutsu!
Yeowch! Hot
Hot! Hot!
[painful gasp]
Hah! I got ya
good! Fool,
ya fool!
Heh! For such a
big dog you sure
go down easier
than I thought!
Don't let your
guard down yet,
Naruto!
Huh? What
the what?!
What the hell's
going on here?!
[startled gasp]
Genjutsu!
No! Do not
look into
my eyes!
[painful grunt]
Hey! Wake
up, Bee!
Huh?
Wee!
Samehada!
Yo! Check it!
Eight Tails that
be me, the rapping
Killer Bee! Aww yeah!
[leaping grunt]
[surprised gasp]
Man, this thing
never stops!
He multiplies when
you hit him.
So knock me
out first!
[anxious grunt]
Stay on your
toes, Octopops!
Watch out!
If you get
hit by Amaterasu
or Tsukuyomi
you're done!
That's the
Mangekyo
Sharingan!
[grunting and
choking sounds]
[gagging sounds]
Excellent, it's
out now.
Did he do
something to
Naruto with
his Visual Prowess?
[gagging and
choking sounds]
No way! Why
did a crow just
come out of
my mouth?!
Are you
kidding me?!
[gasp of
realization]
Why are you
so obsessed with
my brother?
He's just a
rogue ninja.
It's true that
we may not be
blood, but...
He's more of a
brother to me than
you ever were to
him.
[grunts]
You're already
under my
genjutsu...
[grunting
and struggling]
I'll say it
again. I just
want to talk.
I'm aware you
want to take
Sasuke back to
the Leaf.
But, what if
it doesn't go
the way you
want?
[angry grunt]
I'll do anything
to make it happen!
Even taking
him by force?
Sure, if you're lucky.
Sasuke will just
obediently return with
you to the Village.
But tell me,
what if the
opposite were
to happen?
What are you
talking about?!
You just said
you consider Sasuke
to be like a
brother to you...
What if Sasuke
were to attack
the Hidden Leaf
Village?
What would
you do then?
Why would...?
No, there's just no
way that Sasuke would
ever do something like that!
Sasuke is still a
blank canvas. He can
easily be dyed into
any color.
If he resists...
Will you be able
to stop him?
Or even kill
him, if need be?
Come to
think of it...
That day...
[gagging sounds]
I have shared
some of my
power with you.
Though I hope
the day that you
will have to use it
never comes.
[shocked gasp]
This feeling!
Naruto! It's
Amaterasu!
[throwing
effort]
No!
Almighty push!
Damn it!
I lost
control again!
[gasps]
What was that?!
What the
hell just
happened?!
[stunned gasp]
Then it wasn't
Amaterasu!
[startled gasp]
Ah, so
that's it,
huh?
What is
going on?!
Amaterasu!
Huh?!
[worried grunt]
[landing effort]
Wait, did he mess
with the
Amaterasu?!
That crow
down there.
It's one of
yours?
What exactly did
you do with
that bird?
I underestimated
him...
Itachi Uchiha...
He's clearly very
different than
all the others.
He resisted
the Reanimation
Jutsu.
It worked...
Of course, I
understand now.
Amaterasu!
Hey, he-!
Take it easy.
I am no longer
being controlled.
I used a new
genjutsu against
the enemy's jutsu.
Huh?!
This genjutsu
orders me to
protect the
Leaf Village.
The Reanimation
Jutsu...is undone
[stunned gasp]
Thanks to
that crow...
It emerged in response
to my Mangekyo Sharingan,
and prepared it in case...
For a time just like this.
What are you
talking about?
I implanted it
in that crow's
left eye.
Wait, it's his eye!
Yes, there's only one
genjutsu that's capable
of doing that!
Shisui Uchiha's
Mangekyo Sharingan...
The ultimate genjutsu:
Koto Amatsukami.
That genjutsu broke
Kabuto's control
over me...
However, it appears
that the Mangekyo
had already worn
off.
I don't get it.
Shisui Uchiha?
Uchiha's most
powerful Genjutsu
user, Shisui the
teleporter?!
Shisui's Visual
Prowess...is
unique.
It creates a powerful
Genjutsu that allows
you to control someone
without them even realizing it.
I programmed the
Genjutsu to protect
the Hidden Leaf into
Shisui's eye.
I put the command
in the crow's eye and
then gave the eye
to you, Naruto.
Of course I never
realized that I'd
be using it against
myself someday.
But why did you even
have that eye in the
first place?
And why did
you give it to me?
Self-sacrifice.
A true shinobi
does not set out
to seek glory.
They protect from
the shadows. That is a
mark of a true ninja.
Shisui was the
one who taught
me that.
Shisui knew...that
a battle for the possession
of his eyes would
ensue after his death.
He faked the
destruction of his
eyes and took his
own life.
I helped him by
letting myself
become the target
of suspicion
The last time
I saw Shisui, Danzo
had already stolen
his right eye.
The left one,
he bequeathed
to me.
He instructed me to
to use it to protect the
Village, and then
disappeared.
I gave that eye
to you, a ninja with
the same integrity
as Shisui.
If Sasuke, whom I
left behind, ever became
a threat to the Village...
Then I would have violated
all that Shisui entrusted
me to do.
You were the only
one who could
ever make it right.
You said that
you consider
Sasuke a brother.
That's why I knew
that you, Naruto, were
the only one who
could stop him.
I knew Sasuke
would at least
try to transplant my
eyes into himself.
He wanted that
true power. The
Eternal Mangekyo.
If that did
come to pass...
The crow was set to
emerge from you
when it came in contact
with my eyes.
The crow would cast
the Koto Amatsukami
on Sasuke, making him
want to protect the Leaf.
That was my plan.
Why didn't you just
cast that jutsu upon
Sasuke right from
the get-go then?
It's not a
question of
didn't...
...It's simply that
I couldn't.
Not back then.
Shisui's Mangekyo...
takes more than a
decade to
reactivate...
...Unless you have
Hashirama Senju's
chakra.
Sasuke wanted
me dead for
many reasons.
I had to concentrate
on what my death
would do to
Sasuke.
Itachi...
Thanks for putting
your trust in me...
And you don't
have to worry
any longer.
You've done
enough for the
village.
You don't need
to do anymore
at all!
Just let me
take care of
the rest of
it.
[grunts]
I would defend the
village! And I'd find
a way to stop Sasuke
without killing him!
My little
brother...
...is luckier than
he could ever
imagine...
...to have you
as a friend.
[scheming chuckle]
Even Shisui's eye!
Luck just
keeps smiling
on me.
Almighty Push!
[startled breath]
Where'd he
go?!
Is he...?
Here!
Almighty Push!
[painful screaming]
Hah! You fool, ya!
I'm about to
school ya!
[sharp breath]
Lariat!
Gakido!
Wait, are you absorbing
my chakra, ya fool?!
Hey, Octopops,
are you okay?
[shocked grunt]
[worried gasp]
Now!
Ningendo!
No!
What are you...?!
What is
this jutsu?!
Planetary Devastation!
He used this jutsu
against me once before!
This thing's super bad,
you know? Get caught
in it, and you're done
for!
Then tell me this...
If it's a sure death
how are you
still alive?
Then we'll be
alright. We'll get
through this fight!
Come on, Octopops!
This is no time
to be joking!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: The
Acknowledged one.
Every jutsu has a
weakness, you
simply have to
find it.