"JIRAIJA NINJA SCROLLS: THE TALE
OF NARUTO THE HERO-COLLISION"
There it is!
That tower is
Sasuke's goal.
Where is Sasuke?
(NEJI) He's already inside.
[grunt]
Our strategy to weaken their
team one by one has been
working, but it's also making
them impatient.
Those two plan
on settling this
right now.
Yeah, so what's the big
deal? There are only two of
them, but there are three of us!
No, actually, there
are still quite
a few problems.
Neji, I'm counting
on you!
I'm on it.
Listen... I'm sure that
the three of us can handle
the two of them, Shikamaru!
Just run, would
ya?
[grunt]
Give it up. The
entrance to the bridge
is within the range of my
Eight Trigrams.
So neither one of
you two will be able
to get past and enter
the tower.
We'll see about
that.
[gasp]
A clone?! Damn
it!
[grunt] Well, I shouldn't
get greedy. One
is enough...
I will not let you pass!
Hmph!
Multiple Striking Shadow
Snakes!
Gentle Fist!
8 Trigrams, 2
Palms! 4 Palms!
[grunt and gasp]
8 Palms!
16 Palms!
32 Palms! 64 Palms!
Hm? [grunt]
He's here!
Damn it! From
above, as well?!
Quick, get inside!
[grunts]
Naruto, are you
alright?!
Yeah, I'm fine.
Sasuke's up there...
(SHIKAMARU) Naruto! You go on
ahead!
Huh?
Don't you worry,
I'll stop this
guy.
What are you
talking about! You're
coming with--! Hold
on..
Is this because
I'm the Hokage's
son?!
[chuckle]
Yeah, that's right.
You are the
Hokage's son. But
no.
Huh?
In my own
way, I've watched
you two all
this time.
What?!
The one who
can sway Sasuke...
The one who can
bring him back is you,
Naruto. You're the only
one who can do it.
Shikamaru...
He's coming! Hurry,
Naruto!
Okay...
I'm counting on
you, Shikamaru!
[gasp]
SHadow Possession Jutsu...
now complete.
So you're a
shadow user...
Sorry, but you're gonna keep me
company right here for a little
while.
I bear no grudge
against any of you.
This is just my mission.
By the way,...
did you happen
to catch the
weather report today?
[gasp]
(SAI) Cloudy with a chance of
rain...
[gasp and grunt]
Ugh, damn it,
this is not
my kind of
thing.
Well, you must
be Sasuke... I've
been waiting.
And you're Orochimaru...
[chuckle] I understand there's
something you want
very much...
It's power!
Enough so that
I can hold
this world in
my fist!
[chuckling]
My, what a
promising statement.
[licking lips]
Ah!
[struggling] What the-?!
Huh?!
I'm sorry... I
took a shortcut...
and I've been
waiting for you.
Just a little further
and I'll catch up to Sasuke!
Why are you interfering?!
You won't be getting
to Sasuke. I can't let you
go any further than this.
Just shut up! I'm
not gonna let Sasuke
become a vessel for Orochimaru!
That chakra...!
[power yell]
You want it,
don't you, kid?
You want my
power.
Huh?!
[power yell]
Four tails so
quickly?! How can
this be?!
[growl and roar]
Hokakge Style Elder
Jutsu: 10th Edict
on Enlightenment!
Huh?!
What?! How is
this even possible?!
[growls and roar]
[gasp] The fifth tail?!
I want power.
Hurry. Give it to
me.
[chuckling] So impatient...
[gasp]
[pained grunt]
[pained groans]
[growls and roar]
[angry growls]
(SASUKE) Ah!
[gasp] His movements!
[angry roar]
Sasuke!
Ha! That's it? after
coming this far? You
need my power, don't
you?
No, I don't need
power. All I want
is to talk to Sasuke.
So for right
now, you just
back off.
[angry roar]
Ah!
[grunts]
[pained groans]
[heavy breathing]
[heavy breath and gasp]
Sasuke!
What the-?! What's
happened to you?!
Amazing, Sasuke.
Your body's already
adapting to the
power.
[gasp] So you... You're
Orochimaru...?!
What did you-?!
What did you
do to Sasuke?!
[chuckle] I fulfilled Sasuke's
desire, that's all!
What's that mean?!
You're still as
annoying as ever...
Sasuke! [deep breath] I'm here
to bring you
back home to
the village.
Yeah, right. Give me
a break! What could a
loser like you hope to do?
I'll use force
if I have
to!
Go ahead, and try
it. There's no way I'm
gonna lose to you.
Huh?!
I feel...
...power surging!
[gasp] Huh?!
[grunt]
[grunt and groan]
[grunts]
What's this power?!
It's... it's different
from before!
You really don't get
it, do you, Sasuke?!
Orochimaru is trying to
make you his new vessel!
Hmph!
This is power! As
long as I have power,
that doesn't matter to me!
Chidori Stream!
Ah!
[pained groans]
Change in Chakra
Form comes so
easily... This power...
I'll show you
the enormous difference
in my power!
Alright...
Then I'm gonna
show you too,
Sasuke...
...what my power
is!
Well, how 'bout
it?
By now... it should be fully
infused.
Okay, this is
it. Get ready,
Sasuke!
What..? What happened
to him?
Hmph! Plain taijustsu,
that's it?
[gasp] What?! I thought
I dodged it
with my Sharingan...
[grunt]
That child... He
just used Nature
Energy. So this
is...
It's a little
something called Sage
Mode!
[angry grunt]
[heavy breathing]
All this power...
[heavy breath]
Naruto, why do
you always keep
on-?!
Why is it
always you, huh?
Listen, stop talking
all this nonsense
and let's go
back home!
I see... So
that power has
a time limit...
Well, then...
Fire Style: Fierce
Dragon Flame Jutsu!
Hm?
You disgust me,
Naruto... It's time
you get lost!
Now disappear with
the thunder!
[attack yell]
Seems you lost
focus... Your real
target was here
all along.
Sasuke you'd... really
do this to
me?
[coughing]
[chuckle]
What could possibly
be funny?!
Sasuke... I've always
thought... that you
and I... were
alike.
What are you
talking about now?!
I'm the son
of the Fourth
Hokakge.
You're the son of
the Leaf's Police Force
Chief, from the prestigious
Uchiha Clan.
Both of us grew up under exactly
the same shadow, being
constantly compared to our
fathers...
So we know how hard it is to
live under that... to always be
under the watchful eye of
everyone.
I thought you were
the one person in the
village who was able to
understand all that.
But even though our
circumstances were the same, you
were totally different than
me...
You just kept on
progressing and
getting stronger...
At first, I
was frustrated.
But then... I became
proud of you. That's why...
I decided to do my best to be
just like you.
You've been my
rival and my
role model for
this entire time!
Well, I'm different!
You... You should've
just stayed the
same person that
you were.
Why, Naruto?! Why couldn't you
have just remained a loser, the
weak and useless son of the
Hokage?!
Sasuke...
But even you...
even you had
to become strong!
You've no idea
how much that
made me--!
Is that why?
Is that the
reason why you're
trying to find
more power now?!
That's right, Naruto! I wanted
the power to bring you down!
[grunt]
You're the real
loser here,... Sasuke...
What is this?! This red
chakra... He still has power
like this?!
Naruto... His power
is still several
levels above yours.
Your only choice
is to use
mine...
[angry roar]
I'm gonna stop you
even if I have to break
every last bone in your
body!
I've had enough
of this, what
are you?!
I'm your friend,
Sasuke!
That's why I'm telling
you, I won't let the likes
of Orochimaru get ahold
of you!
Fine, I acknowledge you.
Now it's time we have this
out as equals.
However, you still won't
be able to lay a single scratch
on my forehead.
Sasuke!
[grunt] Rasengan!
Chidori!
Big Brother!
I came to bring
you back, but it
seems I'm a little
late.
No! No way!
Naruto...
...please, get along
with my little
brother.
[speechless]
Forgive me... Sasuke...
[shakey breath]
[gasp]
[pained groans]
I must say,
that was quite
entertaining.
(NARUTO) [gasp] What is that
thing?
(SHIKAMARU) Well, as you can
see, this is something that
seems to defy explanation - and
reality...
(NARUTO) Hey, Neji! Is everyone
in the village still safe? I
mean...
can you confirm what's
inside that big thing
with your Byakugan?
(NEJI) Yes! I'm on it now!
(NARUTO) Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Another Moon"
I don't know what kind of jutsu
that is, but I'm gonna undo it
right now!