-Naruto?
-Uh.
-I--
-You'll be fine.
-Thank you.
-What's the matter, Naruto?
-Sorry, Captain Yamato.
But I think you better
go on ahead without me
because I've got to go
back to that village.
-Go back?
-Something about
that place bugs me.
I can't stop thinking
about the way
those villagers looked at her.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Damn!
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
-You must be tired from
your long journey, Hotaru.
Please come.
-Uh, sure.
-Follow me.
VILLAGER 1: Oh, what
is the chief thinking?
VILLAGER 2: Does he really
intend to shelter her here?
VILLAGER 1: You must be kidding.
If something happens, we'll
all be in big trouble.
-Shh.
Don't say anymore.
-Uncle, should I
not have come back?
-No, don't be silly.
You're finally home,
just as you should be.
Now, get some rest.
-Thank you.
-Hm, of course.
-[sighs]
MAN: So we finally meet,
granddaughter of En no Gyoja.
-Who are you?
-I knew you'd count
on this village
to protect you
and keep you safe.
-You must be the ones
who attacked the fort!
Help!
Let me out!
Uncle, please open the door!
Uncle!
Uncle, someone, please!
Help!
-Give up.
It's useless.
Hand over the Forbidden Jutsu.
-No, never!
Ugh!
-Don't give us any trouble.
-Take it easy.
You really shouldn't handle
a lady like that, you know.
-[snickers]
Like you've ever
been nice to a lady.
-Here it is.
-At last, the jutsu is ours.
-[grunts]
Aah!
-[coughs]
[chuckles]
Should have guessed
it was rigged.
-Ugh, where is that brat?
-Quick, we can't
let her get away!
HOTARU (VOICEOVER):
I can't believe
those thieves had already
infiltrated the village.
I have to get away
from here, and fast!
-Trying to hide in the forest.
Humph.
-[panting]
[gasps]
-[chuckles]
It looks like we
found you, young lady.
-[gasps]
Water Style Raging Rain!
-Agh!
Aah!
-Ugh!
-Huh!
I can't believe that a jutsu
like that stopped you, Chushin.
-Shut up!
She caught me by
surprise, that's all.
-Heh.
-Enough!
Playtime's over.
Tell me before I
lose my patience.
Where is the Forbidden Jutsu?
-Uhh.
-Nyah, what a pain!
-[chuckles]
I'd start talking if I were you.
Benten may look like a
girl, but when he gets mad,
he's really quite scary.
-I won't talk.
That jutsu is my
people's last hope.
You can't have it!
-Ah, this is getting ridiculous.
[slurp]
If you don't feel
like talking, then I
guess I'll just have to convince
you to change your mind.
-[gasps]
-Don't kill her yet.
-[chuckles]
That just depends on whether
she's willing to cooperate.
-[sobs]
-What?
-What is all this racket?
Can't a guy even get
a nap around here?
-Utakata!
-He's back?
I can't believe
you're still alive.
I thought we killed you.
-Huh, well, I really am
sorry to disappoint you.
[yawns]
Look, it's not like
I'm particularly
eager to fight the four of you.
But she and I have a
little unfinished business
to take care of.
NARUTO: What, Hotaru's gone?
Wha-- what happened?
-I'm not entirely sure
myself, I'm afraid.
This house is where I hid
Hotaru to try to keep her safe.
Then I heard a loud noise.
And when I rushed over to see
what happened, she was gone.
-All right.
I'll help search.
First, tell me where
you've already looked.
-Oh, uh, well, you see we
haven't actually started
looking for her yet, so--
-What?
Why wouldn't you look
for her right away?
Judging by the damage,
something bad happened.
She could be injured!
-Yes, I know.
It's just--
-What is wrong with you people?
She's one of your own!
You should be doing
everything you can!
MAN: Enough, Naruto.
Arguing about it won't help.
-Captain Yamato,
why are you here?
-We were worried about her, too.
So we rushed back
as fast as we could.
Seems we were right.
So when did you last see Hotaru?
-Just a while ago.
After you three
brought her here,
I showed her
directly to her room.
Right there in that house.
-Then not much time has passed.
She couldn't have
gotten too far.
Let's hurry, Naruto.
-Yeah, but--
-Her safety is our
primary concern.
Go.
-I knew you'd come.
I just knew that
you'd come to save me.
-Well, that isn't
quite the situation.
But now that I'm here, I
guess I better do something.
-What's with this guy?
I was completely certain
that we'd taken him out
with our jutsu back then.
-Boy, are you scheming!
You think you could steal
our treasure away from us?
-Not on my watch.
-Acid Flower.
-Uh!
-Nango, get back!
-Oh, well.
It looks like I missed him.
-Hah!
-Surround him.
He won't get away this time.
-He's out of range.
-Bye-bye now.
-No, you don't!
-Look out!
-Uh!
-Quick enough to
dodge that kunai.
-Duh!
-Even if he is fast, he
couldn't have gotten very far.
So let's go get him.
MAN: Forget it.
-We can catch him.
-Yeah, you're not just
going to let him get away
with our treasure, are you?
-This is a Bingo Book
from the Hidden Mist.
-And it tells us that
we've just stumbled
upon a very interesting man.
-Ah, I see.
The price on his head is so big,
he made it into this book, huh?
-No way!
That guy is worth 50 million?
-Well, I guess we're in luck.
That girl's jutsu
is worth a fortune.
And now this?
We'll all be rolling
in money soon.
-But a bounty this high
means a serious downside.
He must be a pretty
formidable guy.
-Heh, don't get cold
feet now, Chushin.
This is finally our
chance to hit it big.
-Cold feet, huh?
Listen, you little--
-Quiet!
I've heard enough out of you.
All right, so what's
the plan then?
-Hm.
Now, listen up.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
This is my fault.
I should have
returned immediately.
-Captain, let me ask you.
Our assignment, it was
to protect that woman
until we reached
the village, right?
-Yes, that was
supposed to be it.
But if we can't
completely guarantee
that she's safe in the
village, then the mission
has no meaning.
-Hm.
-This assignment--
our mission is
based on a treaty that was
drawn up by the Third Hokage
and En no Gyoja of
the Tsuchigumo clan.
That means that if
the clan is currently
unable to protect her, then it's
our responsibility to do so.
Go, Sai, find her.
Scan the whole area if you must.
-Understood, sir.
Ninja Art, Super Beast Scroll!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Hold on, Hotaru.
We'll find you, I promise.
-Utakata, where are we?
Oh!
[giggles]
We're up so high!
-This looks safe.
-I thought I was done for.
You truly are an amazing man.
-Don't get the wrong idea.
It wasn't really my intention
to come and save you.
-Then why did you show
up and fight those guys?
-Well, I-- it's
because I've become
very curious about this
Forbidden Jutsu of yours
that they want so badly.
-You're lying.
I know you are.
You aren't like that at all.
-Well, you never can tell.
There isn't a single
person in this world
that doesn't love money.
-Oh, stop.
Don't pretend to be a villain.
-Uh, eh.
[sighs]
You really have this knack
for knocking me off-balance,
you know that?
So what will you do now?
Those guys aren't the only
ones who want that jutsu.
I'm sure others are bound
to turn up sooner or later.
-I know you're right.
That's exactly the reason
I have to become stronger,
why I must become your student.
-Not again.
I cannot keep having
this discussion.
Besides, this memento
of your grandfather's
or whatever it is, why do you
feel so driven to protect it?
-Well, first and
foremost, it's to honor
the wishes of my
master-- my grandfather.
You see, he was the
first person to teach me.
A master and student
must be one in thought.
And I want to fulfill
my grandfather's dream--
to restore the Tsuchigumo clan.
That jutsu must never
leave my possession.
-Hah!
Be one in thought.
You're deluding yourself.
-Where are you going?
-I'm under no
obligation to stay.
So if you want to play
"master and student,"
go find someone else.
-I'm not playing.
I'm totally serious about this.
It's important to me.
I need you to be my master.
-You can't stop me
from leaving, you know.
-I know I can't.
But still, my feelings
aren't going to change.
That's why--
-Uh.
Hey!
Stop that!
Why are you doing this?
Uhh.
-I don't want any
secrets between us.
I want you to know--
-Uh, eh, uh, I--
---to see absolutely
everything about me.
-Hotaru, you didn't-- how
could they do that to you?
-No one else knows
anything about this.
But I didn't want
to hide it from you,
not after all that
we've been through.
Please, Ushakata, be my--
-No!
Don't say it.
Just don't.
-Hidden Jutsu, Kirisame.
-[gasps]
Damn it.
I knew it.
This rain is Kirisame.
MAN: Utakata, there is
no escape for you now.
-What's going on?
MAN: We cannot keep the
village waiting any longer.
-You certainly are persistent,
I'll give you that.
Stay back, Hotaru.
MAN: Water Style, Water Whip!
-Aah!
-Hotaru!
MAN: I'll only say it once.
Stop resisting and come with us!
Try anything and this girl dies.
-[gasps]
Utakata.
-Do whatever you want to her.
That girl means
absolutely nothing to me.
I couldn't care less
what happens to her.
-I see.
Well, I guess we'll find out.
-[grunts]
-I thought that would work.
Now, will you return
to the village with us?
-No matter how many times
you ask, the answer is no.
-Then we have no choice.
-Lightning Style, Earth Flash!
-Aargh!
Aah, aah.
-Utakata!
-This isn't personal,
I promise you.
But it's essential that we
take him back to our village.
-Must you be so cruel?
Stop it, please!
-Don't worry.
This isn't going to kill him.
We're just draining a little
of his strength, that's all.
-Aargh!
-Please, he's had enough!
What could he have done to
deserve to be treated this way?
-A monstrous crime.
He killed his own master and
then fled from the village.
-What?
-We need to restrain him.
Get started on trying him up.
MEN: Yes, sir.
-[groans]
-Rasengan!
-What?
UTAKATA (VOICEOVER): What?
-You got some nerve holding
her hostage like that.
-Naruto!
-Sorry, if I kept you waiting.
[music playing]
NARUTO: Back off!
Let her go, you bastards!
SAI: Wait, Naruto.
NARUTO: Why are you
telling me to stop?
SAI: Their masks.
They're Tracking ninja.
They're not after Hotaru.
They must want Utakata.
He's a rogue ninja of the Mist
who's listed in the Bingo Book.
-What?
Next time on
"Naruto Shippuden"--
"Rogue Ninja's Past."
What happened to him?