-We-- we did it.
We did it!
-Yes.
IZUMO (VOICEOVER): No doubt
it, that was one close shave.
If not for Shikamaru's quick
assessment of the situation
we'd have been done before.
Man, he really is
something, this gu.
No wonder Asuma
respects him so highly.
-Shikamaru!
Are you OK?
-All right. That's--
that's one down.
-Yeah.
And one more to go.
-If you wanted my help, Hidan,
you should have asked sooner.
-It was you!
You're the slow one, Kakuzu!
It was on purpose, wasn't it?
-You were the one who told me
to stay out it at the start.
I really don't think
you're in any position
to complain right now.
-All right, all right.
Point taken.
So maybe I did tell
you not to butt in.
But I assure you,
my friend, it wasn't
out of disrespect, or
anything like that.
Anyway, Kakuzu, would you mind
bringing my body over here
for me?
Come on, Kakuzu.
Won't you please bring
my body back to my head?
Please, Kakuzu.
Old friend.
Pretty please.
Huh?
No, hey, wait!
What are you doing?
I asked you to bring my body
to my head, not the other way
around.
Don't you get it?
-It's lighter this way.
-What do I care?
This isn't about you.
Hey!
Are you even listening to me?
[theme song]
-Ow, ow!
That hurts!
Hey, Kakuzu.
You're pulling my hair.
Do you mind?
-I would think your heck
wound would hurt more.
-You idiot, of course it does.
It hurts like a son of a bitch.
This is no ordinary
injury, let me tell you.
ASUMA (VOICEOVER): Incredible.
He's-- he's still alive.
-Yeah, it really,
really hurts, you know?
You fools have no idea
how incredibly painful
it is having your
head sliced off!
-What's going on?
That doesn't make sense.
-I don't know how
to explain this one.
I mean, how did--
-Yeah, but you gotta
look on the bright side.
Even if he's still
alive, so long
as he's not attached
to his body,
he can't perform any jutsu.
He might be immortal, but
he's completely useless.
-That's true.
That means just one left to go.
-Yeah.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
But still, this guy-- I
suspect he may be even
stronger and faster
than mister immortal.
And someone who won't let
himself get carried away.
A cool customer.
Not phased a bit by
his comrade going down.
A heart of stone.
I don't think we've
seen his true power yet.
Maybe that's intentional,
to make us overconfident.
This kind of guy is cagey,
always gauging his opponent,
looking for any way
to gain an advantage.
It would be in his
best interest to have
us thinking we've
got the upper hand.
-Shikamaru!
KOTETSU (VOICEOVER):
Shikamaru's at his limit.
And Captain Asuma's wounded.
While we may have
gained the upper hand
by disabling one
of the Akatsuki,
it also means we've created an
opportunity for us to escape.
In either case my main worry
is Shikamaru's condition.
-Can't leave ourselves
open to attack!
-Enough of this.
-Captain Asuma!
-Since you asked for my help I'm
giving it, whether you want it
or not.
-Yeah, all right. Fine.
Ow!
Hey, that hurts!
-Just hold still.
-Those two.
What are they up to now?
-That should do it.
-Ah.
That's better.
-His head--
-The other one reattached it.
-Finally in one piece again.
-Don't move it too much yet.
or it'll come right off.
-Don't be such a nag, Kakuzu.
-What?
What in the world
are we up against?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
One of them's immortal
and the other has a jutsu that
can sew a body back together?
Man.
It's just one thing after
another with these guys.
They're both so skilled.
-Your battle prep
and repartee are as
drawn out and tedious
as your rituals.
Just stick with the cash cow.
-Ah.
I better be sure to
pay him back in spades.
It wouldn't do to violate
the sacred commandments.
-Not that again.
Well, anyway.
As for the other three,
leave them to me.
-Izumo.
-Yeah, I know.
-All right.
-Water style, syrup trap!
-Yeah!
-That do the trick?
-I presume your plan
was to distract me
with that eye-grabbing
aerial display
while all the time your
friend was launching a ground
attack at my feet with
this strange liquid.
However-- it didn't
quite come off.
So much wasted effort.
-Oh yeah?
-What the--
-Right.
-What a surprise.
-That's it, Izumo.
Gotcha!
-Kotetsu!
Oh no--
-They're giving me
a run for my money.
-Sounds like Kakuzu is
just about worn out.
I better cut this
short and step in.
Otherwise I'll have
to keep hearing
about how my rituals
go on forever.
Nighty-night.
-Asuma!
Behind you!
-Nighty-night.
-Asuma!
Behind you!
-How many times you think
I'll fall for that--
-You fool!
It's the same trap again!
-Ugh--
-Dammit--
-Damn!
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): So
in the end-- in the end
you decided to do it
after all, didn't you?
To sacrifice yourself for
the sake of your comrades.
-I don't get it.
What's wrong with my strategy?
If I can just tie up one of the
enemy with my shadow stitching
we'll reduce their fighting
strength by half, right?
But we know from
prior experience
if I try and use it
against an opponent who's
far away I can mess up.
Clearly shadow stitching becomes
less effective at long range.
But in close combat its
binding force is powerful.
So the success rate would
increase exponentially.
That's the key to the strategy.
-So it'll be a
two-tiered formation.
You and the vanguard engaging
the enemy with your shadow
stitching, with me
acting as your backup.
-Exactly.
With me in the front lines tying
up the enemy, we can't lose.
-Actually, I think it's a
brilliant strategy, Shikamaru,
and I like it very much.
-Then why not try it?
-For that very reason.
Our team is an excellent one.
Not that much different
from other four-man squads
in terms of fighting
power, but we
have something most
other teams don't have.
A strategist.
That's you, Shikamaru.
A good strategist has to be able
to clearly assess the situation
moment by moment in
order to direct his team.
The skills you possess are best
deployed in the rear guard,
not in the thick of battle.
Putting you at risk
in the front lines
only increases the chances of
our failing in the mission.
-You're forgetting.
I understand the pain of
losing a comrade too, you know.
I know what it feels like.
I'm aware of the risk.
But what does it matter?
You admit it's
the best strategy.
It's the best way for me
to protect my comrades
so I don't have
to lose any more.
-If by protecting your comrades
you're referring to us,
the team, then you haven't
understood anything.
The things we're
protecting, the reason
we're fighting--
you still don't see
the true purpose of all of this.
And until you do
there's no way I
can put you on the
front line, Shikamaru.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
It's all my fault.
If I'd only come up with a
better strategy none of this
would have--
-Don't you guys get it?
It's the only move we've got!
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): I've
never seen Asuma like this.
-To penetrate the
enemy's line sometimes
you have to risk a bold move.
-Climbing silver.
It's not a role that suits you.
-I'm not gonna be the
sacrificial piece.
I've got you with me, after all.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Dammit!
It's my fault.
My fault!
If I hadn't been
such an idiot this
wouldn't be happening to Asuma!
-Well?
Does it hurt?
Hm?
How about now?
Finally.
Now I can finally savor it.
Savor the pain
caused by your death!
KOTETSU (VOICEOVER): Captain.
IZUMO (VOICEOVER): Damn.
-The end.
-No!
No!
KURENAI (VOICEOVER): Asuma--
-Yes.
That's the stuff.
-No!
No!
Asuma!
[music playing]
-Don't bother trying to heal me.
I wouldn't make it anyway.
I can feel it.
The things the Third
Hokage did to protect
the village-- I think
I finally understand.
I was always slow
figuring things out.
You know, Choji, Shikamaru,
I've got something
I have to tell the three of you.
-Next time, Last Words.