(Orochimaru) [screams] Bugs are
super gross!
(Orochimaru) There are bugs
here, too!
(Orochimaru) Bugs! Everywhere!
Good job. But what's happened to
the ones who haven't returned
yet?
Huh?
What's up with all these bugs?!
Ugh.
Go on, Tsukune! Chase 'em all
away! Ugh, I just can't stand
bugs.
These are weird! I wanna catch
'em and add 'em to my
collection!
Uh, please cut it out, kids.
The reason is because those
insects are my friends.
These bugs are your friends?!
So what's the deal with this old
guy, anyway?
[groans] Those troublemakers.
It's time for their after-school
study session. Where'd they go?
Huh?
(Sansho) No way!
Whoa, that is really cool! I've
never seen an Insect User
before!
You know, being able to do that
would make me a huge hit at
parties!
No way! Then the party would be
crawling with a whole bunch of
gross bugs!
It seems that you don't like
insects.
But if you keep living with
them, you actually become quite
attached to them.
[awes]
[excited] Hey, maybe you're
right! I guess they are kinda
cute.
I wanna try that, too!
Do you think you might want to
become an Insect User?
Nah, there's no way that's
gonna happen. This guy wants to
become the Hokage one day.
The Hokage?
That's right! I wanna surpass
Naruto Uzumaki as a shinobi.
I see. Well, to do that, you'll
have to become the Hokage, then.
That's what I said! You think
so, too?
Well in that case, I guess I'll
become Hokage!
I know someone else who wants to
become the Hokage.
But you know what? I think
you're the top contender.
The reason is because no one
says they'll be Hokage as an
afterthought.
(Tsukune) Yeah, I know, right?
See, I'm the top contender!
(Sansho) Top contender for
running your mouth.
(Tsukune) Shut up! You'll
see in ten years!
So you want to be Hokage, too?
Oh, no. I never really gave
much thought to it.
You just wanted to become an
Insect User?
Uh, yes, that's right.
So your dream came true! Just
what do you have to do to make
that happen?
'Cause I wanna take the first
step toward mine as soon as I
can!
I'd have to say the first step
in doing that is to...
Wait! What time is it now, you
guys?!
Oh, no, we're gonna be late! We
forgot our study session!
Better hurry back, And do your
very best to surpass Naruto.
Yeah! I'll make my dream come
true, just like you! Well, see
ya!
(Mibuna) [chuckles]
"My dreams," huh?
Sorry I'm late.
It's about time, Shino! Anyway,
how'd it go?
It seems that just about
everyone else has already gotten
their wedding gift.
Well then, guess we'd better
figure out what we're gonna get,
too.
Now listen, Shino. Kakashi
Sensei told us all that this is
a mission, right?
I understand why he and
everybody else are making it
sound like a big deal.
But in all honesty, as far as
I'm concerned, this truly is a
serious mission.
In terms of Team 8, this could
be our final mission.
This is Team 8's final
mission?
Yeah. I mean, once Hinata's
married, I really doubt that
we're gonna get much chance...
to work together the way we used
to.
Yeah.
Guess that's true.
And I'm gonna have to get even
more serious if I intend on
actually becoming...
the next Hokage. I can't keep
relying on you all the time,
Shino.
Yes. We ought to keep it that
way.
All right, what's that supposed
to mean, huh?!
I'm sorry.
Anyway, we really should stay
focused on our last mission as
Team 8.
Especially since it's for
Hinata. Is that what you're
saying?
Yeah, you sure got that right!
So the question is, what are we
gonna get them for a gift? Hmm.
(Kurenai) So you need a gift for
Hinata, huh?
It's gonna be for her and for
Naruto.
Do you have any idea what we
could give them that would make
them happy?
Akakiba! Akakiba and Kibamaru!
Almost, Mirai! But you're still
mixing up the names. Sorry, I'm
kinda busy right now, okay?
[chuckles] Instead of hot tea,
it might be nice to relax with a
little shochu.
Oh, that reminds me. Have you
ever heard the story about the
Senju Clan?
Hmm?
Long ago, so the story says...
the Senju Clan maintained a
tradition of giving honey wine
as a wedding gift.
(Kurenai) Back then, the Senju
Clan lived in the forest, and
they happened to discover...
an unusual liquid produced
from rainwater that collected in
beehives.
That was the start of honey
wine.
It was a nourishing wine and
also quite rare.
Since that time, it's been
served only during auspicious
occasions.
Honey wine could be used as a
medicinal tonic as well as for
cooking.
Hinata would find good uses for
it.
[chuckles] It might be
the perfect gift for her!
It also conveys the wish that
Hinata and Naruto spend their
days together...
Living in sweetness.
Hah! That was a seriously cheesy
joke! Hinata'd groan if she
heard that!
I have to say, it's strange
seeing you two doing things
together without Hinata.
But I guess I'll get used to
it eventually.
[chewing] Where can we go to get
some of this honey wine, anyway?
(Kurenai) I'm not entirely sure,
but there's a place called
Soraku.
Seems there's a beekeeper living
there who makes it.
Tracking's your specialty, so it
should be easy!
Okay, then it's decided.
Let's get over there and find
this beekeeper.
Bye bye, Kibamaru and Akakiba!
All right, it's Team 8's final
mission! So let's do this, you
guys!
[eager bark]
It's our last mission, huh?
It's quite a desolate place.
I'll say! It's completely
depressing, too.
(Momo) Sorry, it's so
depressing, meow.
[gasps]
What?!
[growling]
Judging by your headbands,
you're Hidden Leaf shinobi,
meow.
(Momo) You reek of dogs, you
reek of bugs, and you're a real
dog.
Damn, you sure are a sorry
bunch, meow.
Is that a ninja cat?!
We've come here in order to find
a beekeeper who lives in a place
known as Soraku.
We aren't sketchy guys.
[grunts] You're totally
sketchy, meow!
And I'm not gonna tell you
anything I know, meow!
That must mean you know
something, like where this
beekeeper is, right?
Okay, then I guess we gotta
catch this ninja cat and get the
information out of it!
C'mon, Akamaru, let's do it!
[eager bark]
Foolish humans, meow!
[grunting] Hey, what is...?!
[grunting]
Insect Summoning Jutsu!
[grunts] Thanks, you saved us.
(Kiba) All right, you wanna mess
around with us?! Fine, then!
[chuckles] Tada! Here!
Go on...
What are those? Food pills?
This is something called dog
mint. It's a kind of herb that's
similar to catnip!
Well? You can't resist it, can
you?
Oh, damn it, come on!
My pride'd never forgive me if I
got caught by someone who reeks
like a dog, meow!
(Kiba) Hey! Come back!
You're not supposed to just
steal it and run off, ya damn
cat!
Momo!
[grunts]
[frightened meows]
All right, just who are you
guys? And why are chasing my
Momo!
Must be the ninja cat's
master.
Akamaru! Kiba! Careful!
Oh, hey. So its name's Momo,
huh?
[chuckles] Well, well! Fancy
that! And let me introduce my
dog: his name's Akamaru.
[sighs]
[chuckles] So, let me guess, by
any chance was my cat rude to
you earlier? If so, I'm sorry.
No, no, not at all! You've got
quite a cute little ninja cat!
[scoffs] What the hell are you
talking about?! Just a minute
ago, you called me a "damn cat!"
Oh, yeah. And my name is Tamaki.
Hey, there. I'm Kiba. And this
is my ninja dog, Akamaru.
What?! You're a ninja hound
user?! Oh, wow!
Oh, you know! [cocky chuckle]
It's nothing, really.
Although, to let you in on a
little secret, I'm actually one
of just a handful...
of people on the inside track to
becoming the next Hokage.
Whoa, the next Hokage?! That's
amazing!
Yeah, it is. [chuckles]
[embarrassed whine]
So what's such an important
person like you doing in a place
like this?
Well, actually, we're...
We're on a mission to track
down a beekeeper who supposedly
lives in Soraku somewhere.
Oh, him? Would you like me to
guide you part of the way?
Really?! You know him?! Yeah,
that'd be just great!
Right, Shino?
[exasperated sigh]
He lives deep in the bamboo
grove beyond here.
You probably won't be able to
find him, meow. Even cats get
lost in there, meow.
We're shinobi! Getting lost
isn't something that we do!
All right, good luck! Be
careful!
Yeah! Thanks for your help!
Yes, I know.
Intruders.
First, I'll track this guy down
with my nose. And then, when I
find him, send in your insects.
[sneezes]
Hah! Hey, do you think that girl
we met is talking about us?
You got a crush on her?
Come on! Have you lost your
mind?! No, it's nothing like
that!
This is a crucial time if I'm
gonna become Hokage! There's no
time for love!
You're too easy to read, Kiba.
Huh? What did you say?
[groans] Nothing. I just said
that I envy you.
Oh? Really? You do, huh?
And I'm gonna have to get even
more serious if...
I intend on actually becoming
the next Hokage.
Kiba always talks big, and maybe
I've dismissed him too much
because of that.
However...
I'd have to say the first step
in doing that is to...
Who am I to criticize anyone?
I mean, once Hinata's married, I
really doubt that we're gonna
get much chance...
to work together the way we used
to.
The way we used to. Huh.
Huh?
Kiba! Hey, Kiba! Where are you?!
What, really? You guys don't
know where he is either?
This is most definitely due to
somebody's jutsu.
Yellow jackets, huh?
What is this jutsu?!
[grunts]
You're from the Aburame Clan of
the Hidden Leaf.
(Shino) That's right.
[gasps]
You're skilled if you can
deceive me.
(Beekeeper) But how? The poison
should've...
The poison did get me, but it's
not a problem.
The reason is because this small
amount of poison isn't enough to
kill me.
Well, then, this is my loss. I
guess that it can't be helped.
I'm proud to die by the hand of
an Insect User of your caliber.
No, wait.
I didn't come all the way in
here to kill you. I want your
honey wine.
Huh?
Thanks so much. How much is it?
Oh, just take it. Money means
nothing to me.
I see. Well, if you could just
point me toward the road back,
I'd be very grateful.
There is no road back.
Hm? What do you mean
by that?
Just what I said!
(Beekeeper) This bamboo grove is
surrounded by something like a
barrier.
Once you step inside, there's no
way to get back out.
Try to leave, and you'll only
continue to wander through an
endless fog, that's all.
That's what this jutsu does.
No way!
Huh?
(Beekeeper) I'm sorry to tell
you but this jutsu cannot be
broken. Not even if you kill me.
What do you mean?! How?!
(Beekeeper) Originally, this
mist contained a special
component...
that was meant to lead
people astray.
When I made my jutsu formula, I
incorporated a little of that
component into it.
But that can't be the reason
that the jutsu can't be broken!
(Beekeeper) No.
You see, the nasty thing about
this jutsu is that it takes the
doubt inside its victims...
and turns it into fog, making
it thicker and thicker.
It what?!
(Beekeeper) Haven't you noticed?
This bamboo grove makes people
lose their way.
And when the jutsu is activated,
the thicker fog confuses them
even more.
In other words, this jutsu has
no effect on someone...
who does not harbor doubts
within themselves.
So you're saying that I'm filled
with doubt?
Yeah! I'll make my dream come
true, just like you!
I mean, once Hinata's married, I
really doubt that we're gonna
get much chance...
to work together the way we used
to.
I have to say, it's strange
seeing you two doing things
together without Hinata.
But I guess I'll get used to it
eventually.
I get what it all means now.
I've really been questioning
just how I'll live as a shinobi
once Team 8 finally disbands.
After Hinata has gotten
married.
(Shino) To always be together
with my friends in Team 8.
That was my most cherished
dream.
(Shino) I see.
I was just doubting
myself.
(Beekeeper) You and I are alike,
you know.
I still find myself feeling lost
on this path called life.
So, what do you say?
There may be doubt here, but
there is no true suffering. I'm
finally really living life now!
Your friends would understand,
too! I'm sure of it.
It's okay to have doubts. It's
not your fault that you have
them.
Kiba. Hinata.
You don't always have to keep
pushing forward!
Just abandon it all, and stay
here with your doubts.
If you agree, then just stay
here with us!
Yeah, Shino, come on!
Just stay!
All right, it's Team 8's final
mission! So let's do this, you
guys!
[gasps]
(Shino) No.
This isn't what I've been
looking for. Not at all.
What?
What I'm looking for instead
is...
(Shino) What I'm looking for is
to be with my friends who keep
moving forward.
Not to be with someone who keeps
the same pace as me.
I can't allow myself to get
stuck in a place like this
forever.
I have to return to the village
right away.
[gasps]
And the reason that I must do so
is because I have to attend the
wedding...
of a couple of very important
friends.
You actually believe that you
can find your way out of this
fog?!
When you're in so much
doubt about your life?!
Yes, I do.
But to make certain that my
friends can walk their paths
without worry.
I'm definitely gonna find my
path in life.
And I have no doubt about that
at all!
The entrance!
No wait, It's the exit.
(Beekeeper) So, you found the
path beyond the guardian deity
of travelers.
I see. Then go quickly, before
you lose the path once again.
Hold on. You told me that you're
really living life now.
But can you actually say that's
the truth?
(Beekeeper) What?
If there's someone stuck in the
past who can't see the future...
then can it be said that they're
really living?
(Shino) I know people who live
every moment striving as hard as
they can to reach their goal.
Even when it seems so far out
of reach.
People like that are the ones
who are really living life. That
is what I believe.
(Beekeeper) I'm shocked. You're
nothing like the quiet man I
thought you were.
On the inside, you carry a
great deal of passion.
I feel like I'm being lectured
by my teacher.
Just what does that mean?
(Beekeeper) Go now. In time,
perhaps I'll be more like you.
Oh, there you are, Shino! Where
have you been?! You just
disappeared all of a sudden!
[agreeing bark]
I'm very sorry. However, I did
manage to get ahold of this.
Whoa! When did you do that?!
I was sure you were just lost
out there somewhere!
Actually, I was lost. But I've
found my way.
It's because...
Anyway, let's get this stuff
back home now, Akamaru!
[agreeing bark]
(Shino) Hey, wait. What about
that girl?
Huh?! Why are you bringing that
whole thing up again, huh?!
I'm sorry.
Damn it, I don't know. Maybe
I'll write her a letter or
something like that.
(Shino) A letter? How unlike
you!
(Kiba) Huh? Why?! There's
nothing wrong with letters!
Right, Akamaru?!
[whines]
Akamaru, not you too?!
[screams] More bugs!
That's so amazing!
Maybe I'll try to become an
Insect User, too!
You know, I'd better get started
on my goal too, or I'll never
become Hokage.
I think you're wrong. You've
already taken the first step
toward it.
Huh?
It's because...
Putting your goals into words is
the first step toward making
your dreams come true.
I understand! Thanks for that,
Big Brother!
Let's go!
Tsukune, come on!
Yeah!
[laughing]
Iruka Sensei!
Seems you've managed to
completely win over those
difficult kids.
Maybe you should become a
teacher!
A teacher?
It's hard even for me to keep up
with mischievous kids like those
guys year after year.
What you did is quite
impressive.
Well, in all honesty, it isn't
that difficult for me. The
reason's because...
(Shino) I've always hung
around...
With the kids that everyone
calls difficult.
(Kakashi) [sighs] The wedding's
coming up soon.
(Hinata) What's wrong Kakashi
Sensei?
(Kakashi) Huh? I was really
happy at first, but when I think
about the upcoming wedding...
I haven't finished making the
rounds to greet people...
I haven't pinned down the
expenses, and I'm worried
if everyone will make it or not!
I'm kind of freaking out.
(Hinata) Next time on Naruto
Shippuden:
"Hidden Leaf Story, The Perfect
Day for a Wedding, Part 6: The
Outcome of the Secret Mission."
Are you suffering from cold
feet?
(Kakashi) Me?!