-Fang Over Fang!
-Ma, He's a bomb!
[bark]
-Yeah, I know that.
-He must have used the
other one as a shield.
-I figured as much.
Just as intel said,
physical attacks
seem to be his weak points.
-Heh.
Well, then.
We of the Inuzuka
clan couldn't have
asked for a better opponent.
Ma, let's take him
down with one strike.
-Hold it, Kiba.
After all, this guy
is one of the six
who brought down Lord Jiraiya.
We're going to be
cautious and bold.
And while Han is out
protecting the puppies,
I expect you to fill in.
-Of course.
-Shiho.
We'll attack at full power.
-Yes
-Boy, I am so hungry.
Let's take a little break.
All of us are really
tired from the mission.
-Hmm.
Is something wrong, Sensei?
What is it?
-Have you noticed
large numbers of birds
have been flying in the
direction of the village?
It's like they're fleeing.
-Yes.
Makes me uneasy, too.
We ought to just head
straight for the village.
-Awww!
-Let's go, everyone.
-Aww, man.
-Behind you!
-Six nose piercings and
seven studs in each ear.
That's him.
-You are?
-It's been a long
time, Lady Tsunade,
the last remaining member
of the legendary Sanimoon.
You and I, we have
something to discuss.
[theme music - japanese]
-Kiba.
Use that move.
-Yeah.
Good idea.
Let's go, Akamaru.
[bark]
-Dynamic Marking!
-Oh, no you don't.
-I've got this under control.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of them.
-Great.
Thanks.
-(VOICEOVER) Now that
Akamaru's marked you,
there's no way for
you to escape me.
-This isn't Pain.
It's because
characteristics differ
from the information
gathered on him.
-Stay alert.
-Of course.
I don't let my guard
down for anyone.
-Paper clones.
-No matter how many
clones there are,
our beetles will
devour them all.
-That smell!
Get back, Shino!
-Hm?
Hm!
The paper clones are
armed with paper bombs.
The real one was already
saturated with water.
-She used her weakness
to gain an advantage.
This one's good.
Very good.
-Wait.
You're that child, aren't you?
That boy from long ago.
-So you do remember me, then?
-You know him?
-Yes, I do.
-Who or what is he?
-A god who restores order.
-It seems like he's
not in his right mind.
-Naruto Uzamaki.
Where is he?
-No one knows.
-We now have almost
all the junchuriki,
so the balance of power
between the ninja villages
is no longer maintained,
the tailed beasts.
It's meaningless to continue
harboring a Nine-Tails now.
-So your target truly
is Naruto, after all.
-The rise of conflicts
are imminent.
The kindling coals of war
are smoldering everywhere.
And we shall control those wars.
If you cooperate
with us, we would not
be averse to helping you.
From the state of
this village, you
ought to have a sense
of our strength by now.
-Don't underestimate
the Five Kage.
You are only terrorists
seeking to destroy the peace
that our predecessors
strived so desperately
to achieve and to maintain.
We will not heed you.
-Such arrogance.
-So much chakra.
-This is the power
of the Rinnegan.
I've never seen
anything like it.
-I have a bad
feeling about this.
-What you like to
call peace has only
brought violence
down upon us all.
-I cannot say that everything
the Leaf did in the past was
just or correct.
But your actions here
are unforgivable.
-Be careful of what you say.
This is your final
warning from a god.
Where is Naruto?
Speak.
-We will pour every
ounce of power
that we possess into
bringing you down.
I have nothing more to say.
Except that you're
wrong about one thing.
You've made a huge error.
What you desire most,
you shall never have.
-If you think that the
Shinobi of the Hidden Leaf can
successfully protect
Naruto from me--
-No.
Naruto is stronger
than you know.
-There are six
Pains, and each one
can only use one jutsu type.
That woman used Summoning jutsu.
And that means the Pain
that Lord Jiraiya defeated
was brought back in
a different body.
-There's no mistake.
When she was brought
to that tower,
that woman was
undeniably a corpse.
-When you saw her, did she have
one of these embedded in her?
-No.
I'm positive that she didn't.
-So Lord Fukasaku was right.
Incredibly, Pain
somehow has the power
to bring the dead back to life.
Plus, he can substitute himself
in other bodies at will,
and he makes them move by
implanting these black chakra
receivers.
-So then, are all six of
those Pains actually--
-Yes.
It's possible that all
of them are dead bodies.
And if these rods
are receivers, there
must also be a transmitter.
-Someone's in the
shadows, broadcasting
all of these chakra
signals, and using
them to manipulate those bodies.
-Yes.
The coded message that
Lord Jiraiya left behind.
"The real one's not among them."
Perhaps it means that none of
the Six Pains is the real Pain.
-Hold on.
Are you saying there are
others still out there?
-Exactly.
-(VOICEOVER) I had
anticipated that possibility,
but only as the
worst-case scenario.
I didn't want it to be true.
-Whatever's out there
possesses considerable chakra.
To control so many so easily?
-It's similar to our Yamanaka
clan's Mind Transfer Jutsu.
But we can only manipulate
one person at a time.
So if there are
six of these Pains,
does that mean there are
six others in the shadows?
-There's no way
to know that yet.
-If this is a mind
transfer jutsu,
they'd have to be as close as
they could to the receivers
to transmit their chakra.
Or they couldn't possibly
do such a complex jutsu.
-They must be hiding somewhere
near the Leaf village, then.
All right.
We'll tell Lady Tsunade
and organize a search party
immediately.
-Ah!
-What?
How did we not notice him?
-Ah!
-Do not move.
Or she dies.
-Damn it.
[whimpering]
-Mount Myoboku.
-That's my father's jutsu.
But he just searched her mind
in seconds without any device.
-Well, it would appear
Naruto's not here.
Mount Myoboku.
-What?
[growling]
They're retreating.
-What's going on here?
-Mount Myoboku.
The toads' hidden village, yes?
Then I will linger
here no longer.
-How did you know?
-You.
-Lady Tsunade.
Perhaps we should
let them withdraw
so we can fortify our
defenses while they're gone.
-Ugh.
-Just one last thing.
The chakra you're emitting
through your feet.
Is it to counteract my jutsu?
So my ability has become
known to you, has it?
However, all is meaningless
before overwhelming power.
You Great Nations proved
that over the years.
You all think of yourselves as
the main forces of this world,
and push death out
of your thoughts.
Lulled by peace,
you become shallow.
If you kill, you
shall be killed.
Hatred is what connects
this cause and effect.
-Quit babbling such nonsense.
-In battle, both sides suffer
death, injury, and pain.
-We Great Nations have
suffered our share of pain.
Enough excuses.
You can't justify your actions.
-How absurd.
-Lady Shizune!
-Feel pain.
Contemplate pain.
Accept pain.
Know pain.
-Wait, Pain.
Come back!
-Feel pain, accept
pain, and know pain.
-(VOICEOVER) He's still
planning something?
-Those who do not know pain will
never understand true peace.
-Lord Fukasaku!
Bad news!
-Huh?
-What's wrong?
-Big brother Kosuke, our
messenger, has been killed.
-What happened?
-I don't know, but his name
disappeared from the register.
-This doesn't bode well.
Has something happened
to the Leaf village?
-What?
-Naruto-boy, I have
a really bad feeling.
-Wait, Geezer Sage.
Is it the Akatsuki?
-It's just lucky for us Ma
went to gather provisions
and is near the Hidden Leaf.
And Ma can summon up quite
a bunch of strong-arms
to defend the village,
including the two of us.
So go get ready.
-Yes, sir!
[background chatter]
-(VOICEOVER) Damn it.
At this rate, I'll never
get to all of them.
-Lady Shizune!
-What?
-Hm?
-What's going on?
-I'm going to use that jutsu.
-What?
-It seems they've retreated.
-Yeah.
But why?
It doesn't make sense.
[crying] Lady Shizune?
-Their scents are
completely gone now.
They're obviously
not here anymore.
[laughter]
-Well, then.
I guess my power must
have scared them off, huh?
-(VOICEOVER) Hmm.
Leave it to Ma.
It's just like
that time with Pop.
-What does this mean?
-It's hard to believe
they would just retreat.
-Pain.
-Those who do not know pain will
never understand true peace.
-He's planning to do something.
I just know it.
-But what?
-That I don't know.
But it's bound to
be something big.
[sigh]
-I'm counting on you.
Make sure Ma gets the message.
-Yes, sir.
-Katsuyu.
Protect everyone.
-Lady Tsunade!
-Something terrible
is about to happen.
(VOICEOVER) Where is Naruto?
-I have to tell her, quick!
-That's coming from the
Hidden Leaf village.
Oh, my goodness.
-Lady Shima!
I used the Distance
Teleporting Pool.
Lord Fukasaku sent a message.
-To summon them here, huh?
-Pain!
What do you think you're doing?
-You can't.
That jutsu will significantly
shorten your life.
The power of the Sixes.
You really mean to do this?
Nagato.
-I will never forget the
pain that Yahiko suffered.
And now--
This world shall know pain.
-Summoning Jutsu!
-Almighty Push!
[coughing]
-What happened?
No!
But why?
How could-- Naruto!
Hurry!
[sobbing] Please!
Naruto!
[theme music - in japanese]
-There's no need for the
Hokage to bother herself
with the likes of them.
You just sit back and
sip some tea, Granny.
I'll take over from here.
Keep the rest of the
village out of this.
I can't be worrying
about everyone else.
Not during this fight.
Next time, on Naruto Shippuden.
Explosion-- Sage Mode.
Let's settle this.
[theme music - in japanese]