[eagle cry]
[groan]
Looks like a poisonous
cactus thorn...
[groan]
You're from the Sand!  You
should be familiar with the
flora of your homeland! Pitiful.
Kouji, Please get the
bandages ready.
I know, Ameno.
Now I'll extract the poison.
Medical Water Style: Water
Mosquito!
[mosquitos buzzing]
[patient shouting]
Are you sure
you don't want it?
A Medical Ninja stays on the
front lines in order to help
their comrades stay alive.
We aren't here to battle.
Of course, I'm not a
Medical Ninja, so that
doesn't apply to me.
What was that?
I was just kidding.
If word got out that I took a
scroll from an injured comrade,
then I'd never live it down.
Look, just hurry
up and get lost.
(Shishio)
Would it have been okay if they
weren't comrades?
Shishio, You doing
a sensory check nearby?
I could swear that this
wave pattern is...
♪
Hey, do you guys think
that maybe we could slow
down a little bit?
You hear that, Sakura?
Choji's worried about
whether you can keep this up.
It sounds to me like he's
worried about you , Ino.
So whenever you're ready to
admit that you need to rest,
you just let us know.
[weary sigh]
(Ino)
Anyway, I hope that
you're right about this.
(Sakura)
Right about what?
(Ino)
About if there's an
oasis, what else...
...You're the one who said that
even with the scroll, we'd never
make it to the central tower
without water!
Now wait, guys!
You know, you're to blame for
this in the first place!
Ahh!
[laughs] This reminds me
of the last Chunin Exams!
[panting breaths]
All right, then! Let's see if
we can find some weaklings!
Just shut up, Choji! That
was a tactical withdrawal,
and you know it!
Someone decided to be cautious
after we got the scrolls, and
now just look at the mess we're
in!
We should've headed straight for
the goal instead of going with
your lame-brained strategy,
Sakura!
What?! We all talked about
this and agreed to it! And
that includes you, too, Ino!
But even so... at the
time it seemed like a
good idea!
I thought it would
be easier...
You just drank too much
water earlier, Ino! You
big bloated blister!
Ugh! Bloated Blister!?
Well, you'd have to drink 100
times more water than me to fill
yours up, Miss Flat-as-a-Board!
If drinking some water were all
that it took, then I'd be happy!
[angry growls]
Now, now, you two.
Let's calm down.
-Oh just shut it, you fat--!
-Oh no, it's coming!
Whaaa!
(Ino)
Let's go!
(Thinking)
Wait, is this a surprise attack?
Choji!
-Right!
Mind Transfer-
It's faster than it looks!  I
can't do Mind Transfer, then.
I'll have to-!
Super Expansion Jutsu!
Way to go, Choji!  Just like
that!  Clobber it!
We did it!
Whoa!!
[gasp]
[attack cry]
You know... You really should
tell us if you have a move like
that up your sleeve!
You probably have more
power than me, since
yours is instantaneous.
Oh, I don't know.  I wouldn't
say that that's true...
(Ino)
Let me see...
I mean, even if you are a
Medical Ninja, it's still
pretty hard to heal your
own fist isn't it?
[heavy breathing]
I can't do any more. My
head feels like it's on fire.
Yeah...  Everyone feels that at
first.  But once you're able to
overcome it...
...you'll find the true
Secret Ninjutsu, the Bond
of the Three Families.
Even Shikamaru and
Choji are...? No way.
I don't believe it! There's just
no way that those two are
training as hard as I am.
The recent incident with Sasuke
has hurt everybody very badly...
In body and in mind.
Although because of it, they'll
mature and get stronger.
But of course, mastering this
Secret Ninjutsu will take you
several years, even if you do
continue to train this hard.
However... This is all so that
you can keep up with them
and to protect the Ino-Shika-Cho
tradition as well as our clan's
tradition.
That's why I must pass our
Secret Ninjutsu on to you.
And it's also why I was really
happy and proud when you came
to see me...
...and asked if I'd train you.
[proud sniff]
Uh... Wait a second. Did you
say that it would take
several years to master?
Well, there's no shortcut when
it comes to this training.
But I'm certain that you'll be
able to see it through until the
end and after that--
Hey, you know what? I remembered
I have something to do!
I'm not finished talking to you!
Have you forgotten the
meaning behind the
Oath of the Piercings,
the oath you took when your
Sarutobi Clan mentor presented
those earrings to you?
That you'll keep that vow, and
pass on new piercings to the
next generation...?
You will eventually lead the
Yamanaka Clan, and entrust a new
earring to the child you give
birth to.
Not this story again...
I know, but the thing is...
today is the day that Choji
is being discharged!
What?  Choji?
I have to get a present
and go get things ready,
so I have to leave!
Oh, I understand. Guess
it can't be helped.
Yeah! Okay! See
you later!
[thinking]
Several years?! You've
got to be kidding me!
I've gotta get
stronger way faster!
And show those guys
what I'm capable of!
What's the point if it takes
years and years?
(Ino)
Sakura!
Ino!
We're celebrating Choji's
release from the hospital.
You wanna come join us?
Oh, wow really? Choji's actually
well enough to leave now, huh?
Sounds great! But...
Sorry, I'm right in the
middle of training.
So please congratulate
Choji for me, okay?
(Ino)
Huh? Where's Shikamaru?
(Asuma)
He's seeing off the delegates
from the Hidden Sand.
Well, anyway, thank
you for the food!
But only having the three
of us here to celebrate
is pretty sad, isn't it?
Hey, Asuma Sensei!  Does that
mean I can eat his share too??
[chuckle]
By the way, Choji, I
heard all about it!
How you were flirting with all
of the nurses the whole time!
Ino, I'm going to tell you the
one universal truth about men.
There isn't a man alive who
doesn't go crazy over nurses.
Right, Asuma Sensei?
Hm? Yes. Yes,
you're right.
Oh, come on! What kind
of nonsense is that?
I mean, you know that
Asuma Sensei only has
eyes for Kurenai Sensei!
[spits]
Huh!? Is that true?!
Three orders of the prime beef
filet!  And get it here fast!
Yes!  Score!
Although...
Open wide, Sasuke!
Listen, Ino. I thank
you. I owe you my life!
[smitten giggle]
That actually might work...
Ugh! Hey! What are you doing!?
And what am I doing!? Why am
I feeding you!?
Listen, I never refuse
food if it's offered to
me. That is my ninja way!
Another one, please!
You know, right when you
were first discharged,
you were still so skinny.
But that sure didn't
last long, did it?
Yeah, with that kind of
appetite, I'd say you're
completely back to normal.
Hey, Asuma Sensei...
after I'm done eating,
can you help me train?
Choji! Have you lost
what's left of your mind?!
I mean, you just got
better, remember?!
Ridiculous. Everybody is so
stuck on training around here!
How come you're so eager
to get back to it, Choji?
For starters, I want to catch up
to Shikamaru, since he beat me
to becoming a chunin.
After all, together we're the
Ino-Shika-Cho trio, right?
You do your best too, okay, Ino?
Yeah, of course! I don't
need you to tell me that.
All right.
Now, don't get overconfident
because of one or two successes.
You have to become faster
and more efficient
No one waits for treatment on
the battlefield, you understand?
Yes!
Blargh!
Heh heh!
Huh...
Who's there!?
Lady Tsunade! Please, will
you make me your apprentice?
You're from the
Yamanaka Clan, right?
Sakura was able to
learn to revive that
fish in three months.
So I'll test you and see just
how far you can get.
I'll give you three months, too.
I understand. Please
let me try!
I have to work
with this thing?
The usual way to go about
resuscitating a creature
that's asphyxiated
is to use one's own chakra to
stimulate its heart or brain.
Octopi generally have one
systemic heart and two
branchial hearts.
And separate from the brain,
they have eight nervous systems
in their arms.
You need to pay attention and
address each of these areas if
you're going to have any hope of
resuscitating it.
In short, it has many
parts to take care of.
Oh...
You can quit if you
don't like it!
Sakura! Be quiet!  You still
know practically nothing at all
when it comes to healing!
I have to-- All of these?!
You can quit if
you don't like it!
[grunt]
Agh!
That happened because your
chakra control is too rough.
You have to fine-tune your
technique, or the octopus
will be ripped apart.
You must learn to control
your chakra more carefully
and delicately!
Uh... Right!
(Thinking)
She's having a hard time.
She's made some mistakes, but it
hasn't been that long, and she's
already...
- I am never going to let
myself lose to you!
Huh..!?
[snoring]
Today is the three-month mark.
Let's see what you've got, Ino.
Right!
Haaaaa....
[shouting]
[squirming]
[laugh]
You did it!
[giggles]
Hey! Sakura!
You took too long and
made lots of mistakes.
It took me three months, too,
but when I did it, I was able to
complete it much more
smoothly than you did.
Oh, shut it, Sakura!
You just broke my
concentration since you
kept peeking over at me!
What did you just say?!
[chuckle] Alright, you pass.
So uh... what made you want to
learn Medical Ninjutsu?
Huh? Well...
I wanted to create a
place where I belong.
Oh...
See, Naruto... Naruto kept
his promise to me and got
all beaten up for it.
He acted reckless...
all because of me...
I was always... standing in
the back, following them...
But...  I'm a member of the
team, too.  I wanted to walk
shoulder to shoulder with them.
And so I made a promise to
myself: From that point on,
that is exactly what I'd do.
This is all so that you can
keep up with them
and to protect the Ino-Shika-Cho
tradition as well as our clan's
tradition.
That's why I must pass our
Secret Ninjutsu on to you.
After all, together we're the
Ino-Shika-Cho trio, right?
You do your best too, okay, Ino?
Team 10 is where I belong. And
I want to walk shoulder to
shoulder with them, too!
But...
But of course, mastering this
Secret Ninjutsu will take you
several years,
even if you do continue
to train this hard.
(Thinking)
Maybe I've just been running
away and taking the easy way out
[gasp]
Hey, you're wounded, Sakura!
Oh, Yeah, I guess I
hurt myself earlier.
That's not good!
Ino...
I have to thank you, Sakura.
Because of you, I'm going to
the place where I belong.
All right! There! Done!
(Ino Thinking)
Choji's Expansion Jutsu is way
better than it used to be.
The size, the power,
the duration...
He's improved
so much!
Sakura, too!  She can do Medical
Ninjutsu, and she had that
awesome attack up her sleeve!
Both of you have really
progressed. I have to try
harder too!
Yeah, that's right!
Let's all do our best and
pass these Chunin Exams!
[stomach growling]
Good idea. But making sure we
eat is important, too.
Here ya go!
I never turn down food when it's
offered. I mean, I know that's
my Ninja Way, but...
What's wrong? Once you
process it, that scorpion's
toxin becomes medicinal!
Are you saying that fighting
this thing was partly to
gather provisions?!
Well, it's rich in amino
acids and great for
countering fatigue!
Come on! Let's eat!
You know, you might be the
one who's matured the most.
Out of all of us!
It looks like it's the
two women and the fatso
from the Hidden Leaf.
Sakura Haruno's team. She's
Lady Tsunade's apprentice.
That powerful big guy's
team? How interesting.
And there's also another
interesting thing, that there
are two Medical Ninja on their
team.
What? Two Medical
Ninja on one team?
Whatever.  Let's just get going.
Since you won't ambush them. Or
am I wrong?
(Ino)
I found all three of them!  I
can sense their chakra.
(Ino)
They're on the move! The
enemy's heading this way.
(Sakura)
Since when do you have sensory
powers.  That's amazing!
(Ino)
I know!  Cool, right?!
Or at least that's what
I want to say.
(Ino)
But in actual combat,
it's still difficult.
(Ino)
If I don't have the time to
concentrate I can't do it.
(Choji)
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden:... "The Yamanaka
Clan: Secret Ninjutsu"
(Ino)
Too bad no enemy will give
us the luxury of time...