(Tsunade)
You're wrong!
[gasp]
L-Lady Tsunade?!
What's the matter?
It's that damn Jiraiya! He
understands nothing!
Oh, I get it now!  You were just
worked up over Jiraiya's novel!
It's not funny!
It's inexcusable!
Even if it is only a novel, you
can't bend the truth this much!
There is simply no way that
Sakura, my beloved apprentice,
would ever be this meek!
I brought rice balls for dinner.
I thought that they'd be easy
to eat while you read...
Please, take a break!
Oh! Rice balls, nice! That
was quite thoughtful of you.
Mmm..
(Tsunade)
[screaming]
What is inside of this?
Oh, that?  It's just a
ten-year-old pickled plum!
It's so salty!
[giggle]
[spitting]
Blegh!
And that tea's still very hot!
You should've told me sooner!
[sigh]
♪
[gasp]
The future of the Hyuga... or
rather the future of all
shinobi... rests on this test.
Watch carefully until the end.
Their true, hidden selves
will soon be revealed.
Do not worry. I won't
let them be killed.
[angry grunt]
How dare you! How dare
you do this to Sasuke!
You're annoying...
What? Do you
want to die, too?
(Masked Man)
Don't forget your mission!
Your orders were only to
uncover their true selves...
I never gave you the
order to kill them.
So he's been spying on me...
I know. This is just
a test, right?
Just keep watching. I'll prove
there's no future for shinobi.
Alright, that's it! Cha!
[labored breathing]
[groaning]
[breathing heavily]
[determined grunt]
[struggling breaths]
I've managed to remove all of
the poison.  So you should be
okay now.
When did you learn Medical
Ninjutsu, Sakura?
I've secretly been apprenticing
with Lady Tsunade.
Really?  Well, your skills
just saved my life.
So, was that all of it?
If that was the entire test,
well, then... what did it prove?
No, there's more. And
it's just about to begin.
Ha!
Oof!
All right, I was able to clear
all your Chakra Points.
So you should be able
to move just fine now.
Wow, that's great!
Thank you so
much, Pervy Sage!
Here.  These pills will help
replenish your chakra.
Okay!
But... what are you doing
here, Pervy Sage?
I've been searching for a
certain someone and I came upon
some intel, so I stopped by the
Hidden Leaf Village...
And while I was there, I heard
about what was going on with
this mission of yours,
so I convinced Minato to
transport me here to help
you guys out.
I'm kinda surprised he
even knew where I was.
I know, I was, too!
But apparently, the seal that
Minato placed inside you also
contains a Marking.
As long as you have the Marking,
his jutsu can get us to you
instantly, no matter how far
away you might be.
Aww, dad!
By the way, how's everyone?
I don't see them here...
Well... Kakashi Sensei
and the other Captains
have all been abducted.
And Neji and I were locked
up in this weird place.
Oh? Then what?
Neji left with a guy
wearing a mask to find
out what he's up to.
And you just saw
the rest of it.
Ugh, If I had more power,
I could've beaten up that
masked guy no problem,
and then I could've gone to save
Kakashi Sensei and all of the
other captured captains!
Y'still have a
long way to go!
Aw, damn it!
Today's the last day
of this training.
But even when I'm gone, I want
you to keep practicing on your
own.
Do you remember our Summoning
Jutsu training?
Yeah!  In fact, just the other
day, I was falling toward the
bottom of this enormous gorge,
and it was almost game
over! But I summoned the
Great Toad to save me!
Oh, yeah? Is that so?
Okay, then, try it again
right here and now!
All right!
Summoning Jutsu!
Huh...? Oh, uh...
Wow. Well, that is
just plain sad.
I can tell that you've been
ignoring your training!
No, no! I've been
doing it, I promise!
And besides that, Dad's
even been giving me
training on his own, too!
(Thinking)
The first step is... rotation...
[struggling grunts]
[sigh]
It's been three days, and
nothing! It stretches,
but it won't burst...
[cat's meow]
Huh?
[screech]
That's it! If I get the water
spinning in a bunch of different
directions like that cat...
Hm.
Whoa!
Dad...?
I did the first part, dad!
I was watching this cat play
around with my balloon, and I
got a brilliant idea!
Oh, yeah?
Enough with the kids' stuff--
Teach me what comes next!
Whoa, whoa, just slow
down! Not so fast, okay?
Listen, what do you say we take
a little popsicle break first?
Huh?
If I master up to step
three of this, can you teach
me the Summoning Jutsu?
If I can't show Pervy Sage that
I know it the next time I see
him, then he'll be mad at me.
As with anything,
one step at a time.
Right, dad. Got it!
It was all because of Dad's
training that I was able to
summon the Great Toad!
Though it was only
that one time...
And that's when I met Nine
Tails for the first time.
Oh? All right... Well, then,
let's try that now!
Huh!?
I'll go ahead and loosen up the
Eight Signed Sealing Formula
just a little bit
and then the Nine Tails
Chakra will be released.
[affirming grunt]
But just remember this: if you
aren't able to control that
power, then the Nine Tails will
rob you of your consciousness.
I'll try it!
Go on, do it!
Hey, hey! Slow
down, would you?!
No!
Stop!!!
Ow! What was
that for, Tenten?!
Just take a look!  There aren't
any more paper shuriken.
Huh?
You are right. There are
no more signs of the
enemy around at all!
And also... something
weird is going on...
We were under such
heavy attack before...
Yes...
(Kiba)
Lee! Tenten!
Hey, Kiba!
You guys!
We finally caught up to you!
So, where's the enemy?
And how many are there?
Well, um...
I was able to see with my
Byakugan that the two of you
were being attacked and
pursued by somebody...
The thing is... as soon as
we got here, all sign of
them disappeared.
Disappeared?
Yes... as if a fox
spirited them away.
And where's Neji?
Is he...?
Oh, uh...  Naruto fell into the
enemy's trap, and then Neji fell
in when he went after him.
Naruto, too!?
Hold on...  I
know that scent.
Sasuke and Sakura should
be nearby here, too!
Byakugan!
We have to hurry! There's a
shadowy figure that's
approaching them...
...but they seem unaware of it!
Big brother, You made me a
promise! I mean, you are going
to help me train today, right?
I'm sorry, Sasuke.
But Lord Fourth has just sent
a summons asking for me.
Aw, come on, don't go!  I was
really looking forward to having
you help me, Big Brother!
Some other time, OK?
Why don't you ask
Father to teach you?
But...
Whoaaa!
Now, this is the key jutsu
of our clan, Fire Style:
Fire Ball Jutsu.
I've already shown you
the hand signs...
The next step is to build up
your Chakra and focus it at a
point in your chest,
...then force it up the throat
and out the mouth.
All right!
(Thinking)
Father's actually teaching me
the jutsu himself..!
He's finally giving me a chance
to show that I matter too...
I can't disappoint him.
I can do it!
Fire Style: Fire Ball Jutsu!
[groan] Why did I think you
would be like Itatchi?
It's too soon. You're
not ready yet.
Sakura...!
I know. I wasn't able to
inflict a fatal hit with
my attack before!
There is a limit to life...
But art... is forever!
Do you want to see my
everlasting army?
Each one is a truly valuable
work of art that surpasses life.
Secret Red Move: Performance
of a Hundred Puppets
One hundred puppets...?!
How can we...?!
There's just no end
to all of them!
This is impossible!
So... what now?
Will you fight each of my
hundred pieces of art?  Or will
you just cower in fear?
The choice is yours to make.
He said he was the
gatekeeper... If thats true...
These things are here to prevent
us from returning to the Hidden
Leaf Village.
Which means... as long as we
don't try to pass them, they
won't attack.
But... can Sakura and I really
take on a hundred puppets and
make it through?
That's gotta be close to
impossible for anyone!
Although, with more on our
side...
[bark barl]
Everyone!
Finally, we're able to
rendezvous!
Let's hide
our presence
for a while...
[gasp]
What exactly is going on?!
Are they puppets?
Yeah. And there's a
hundred of them.
And on our side... There are ten
including me... plus a dog.
What's happening
here, anyway?
A puppet user put all of these
things out there to create a
blockade.
A blockade? Where's
the puppet user?
(Sasuke)
Watching to see our next move.
Sasuke, what was
your initial plan?
Well, if we want Lord
Fourth to be able to
conduct a rescue mission,
we have to return to the
village and report to him.
But if we just bring down
all one hundred puppets now,
we can get out of here.
You sure do
make it sound easy!
Still, it's not
impossible, is it?
If we're going to complete our
mission, we really don't have
another choice.
Hey, hold up!  We don't wanna go
back to the village yet!
We're not just gonna give up on
rescuing the team captains!
So you plan on
abandoning the mission?
No, that's not it.  The reason
is because there's also the
option of breaking up into two
teams:
one to look for the captains
and one to report back to
the village.
No way.  I also think it's a
better idea if we stick together
and work as one united team.
What? Shikamaru! What the
hell are you talking about?!
Yeah, I know!  In the beginning,
I thought that we should break
up into two separate groups.
But now... a lot of time
has passed since then.
We have to take into account
that the longer this takes, ^
the smaller our chances of
finding the captains.
Put simply, we don't have the
time to return to the Leaf.
Not to mention,  if we commit to
fighting all those puppets,
we'll exhaust our remaining
time.
Why did I think that
you would be like Itachi?
Well, then? What
are you gonna do?
Are you gonna come
with us, Sasuke?
No, I'm not going to
go with you guys.
I'll do things my
way, on my own.
Well, we succeeded in one
thing: we brought all the
Leaf genin together.
But things aren't looking good.
Is there friction
between them?
Why would they...
If they decide to try to
break through that
barrier of puppets,
it will mean they've chosen to
stick to the rules and place
their first priority on their
mission.
But then... if they decide to
ignore the puppets and instead
go to try to find their
comrades...
In that case, it would mean that
nothing was able to sway them
and that they'd made their
choice of their own free will...
...because they prioritized
saving their friends.
When they finally sop arguing
and coalesce into a united group
of Hidden Leaf Shinobi
I wonder which option
they're going to choose...
So what will they do?
When they make their choice...
that's when we'll see the true
nature of these young shinobi.
Think of it like kind
of an experiment.
When the Eight Signed Seal is
loosened, even I don't know
what's going to happen.
You understand,
right?
Yeah!
then I, Jiraiya, one of the
Legendary Sannin, will stop him.
Thanks, Pervy Sage...
[groaning in pain]
Oh, man... Three tails
in almost no time at all!
Now, Naruto! Suppress
your chakra now!
[struggling grunts]
[struggling]
What? The seal that keeps
me bound is weakening!
All right, listen! Lend me
your power, demon fox!
Arrgh!
[screaming]
You have to strengthen your
resolve!  And use your will to
control the Nine Tails Chakra,
Naruto!
[grunt]
[struggling grunts]
[deep growling]
A fourth tail,
huh...?! Well..
I guess it was still too soon
for Naruto to be able to control
the Nine Tails' Chakra...
[low growling]
(Great Lord Elder)
The future of the Shinobi
World will be wrought
with many calamities.
One of your apprentices will be
the one who will prevent those
calamities.
However, if guided wrongly,
they'll bring about great ruin.
(Jiraiya)
What, seriously?
My apprentice will?
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Child of Prophecy"
(Jiraiya)
Impossible!  To think the one
who might bring about great ruin
is--!