[attacking yell]
This time, I'll
reach the other side!
Just aim it a little
higher than you'd expect.
That's the trick.
Yeah, I know! It'll
get there, if I simply
put my all into it.
Who the hell
are you, anyway?
Right now, I'm your
stone-skipping rival,
but my stone is
already on the other side.
And that was my
first encounter
with Madara Uchiha.
Answer me! I asked
you who you are!
First name's Hashirama,
but I can't tell
you my last name.
Hashirama, huh?
Just watch me!
I'm gonna make it.
The way he throws. Just as
I thought! Shuriken Jutsu!
Why you! You stood
behind me on purpose
just to distract
me, didn't you?!
I'm so sensitive that
I can't even pee if
someone stands behind
me like you're doing!
I'm sorry!
Uh... There's no need to
get all depressed about it.
I was making
excuses... I'm sorry.
Well, I had no idea you
had such an obnoxious
self-diagnosed neurosis.
You know, I can't tell if
you're a nice guy or just
some kind of jerk!
[laughter]
Well, one thing's for
sure! I'm better at stone
skipping than you!
You want me to skip you
instead, you punk?!
Sorry...
I didn't mean
to make you mad.
To make amends, I'll
let you throw me into the
river. Go ahead, do it.
Good grief. Are you
aware of your own
obnoxious neurosis?!
It's just...
I hope that I reach
the opposite shore...
You're so annoying!
Look, just get lost!
Well...
No, wait a sec!
Which is it? Why
don't you try to be a
little bit clearer?
No, Well it--
What the...
Are you a shinobi?
This place'll become
a battlefield.
Go home now.
This is the crest of
the Hagoromo Clan.
Sorry, but I've gotta go.
Later.
Oh, uh...
First name's Madara.
Madara...
Not proffering one's family
name to a stranger
is shinobi law, right?
I thought so.
You're a shinobi, too.
Our personalities differed,
and yet I sensed a
mysterious kinship with
him all the same.
I felt that I knew why he'd
come down to the river, too.
[crying]
Kawarama...
Shinobi don't cry!
They're born into this world
to fight and die in battle!
Be glad that we have
even a piece of his
corpse left to bury!
Because our enemies
this time include the
Uchiha Clan in addition
to the Hagoromo Clan!
They're particularly
merciless!
Kawarama was just
seven years old!
How long?! How long are
all of these conflicts
going to last?!
Until the very last foe has
been vanquished.
The path to a world that is
free of battle is not easily
paved!
And children must
be sacrificed?
I won't allow
disrespect for Kawarama!
He fought and died as
nothing less than a
full-fledged shinobi!
He wasn't a child!
Elder brother
Hashirama, are you okay?
You know what happens
when we defy Father.
C'mon, elder brother...
I don't want...
Itama...
Tobirama...
I don't want either
of you to die in vain!
Senju, the Clan of
love? Yeah, right!
A full-fledged
shinobi? Come on!
All this is just adults
ganging up on kids and
driving them to
their deaths!
We're doing exactly the
same thing as the Uchiha!
That is how we
honor our opponents.
Even an infant, if
wielding a weapon,
is deemed an enemy.
And raising one's child
to become full-fledged
is a true sign of a
parent's love!
In order to become
full-fledged, you have
to die, is that it?!
We kill and are killed
so much you can't keep
track of the grudges!
It's too risky to even say
your last name!
I swear that this shinobi
world is totally messed up!
Children like you
are known as brats!
Father, no!
Elder Brother's feeling
depressed today...
So please, forgive him.
Just go and cool
your head, Hashirama.
Grown-ups are so stupid.
It's simple! If they
really wanna stop wars,
then they should just
make pacts and stop
fighting with each other.
What about avenging our
parents and our siblings
and all our friends
who were killed?
Keep saying that stuff
and you'll end up dead.
Both you and the adults
are way too hotheaded.
Sorry...
Forthcoming shinobi really
need to suppress their
emotions, create suitable
rules that they then follow,
and mantain and avoid any
extraneous conflict.
Can't a true pact...
...a true alliance
be achieved?
A "true alliance,"
Elder Brother?
During the Era of Warring
States, the average life
expectancy of both
shinobi and citizens
was around 30 years old.
And what was keeping that
average so low was...
[gasp]
Itama!
...the deaths of
many young children.
Itama! [crying]
Hey, long time no see!
So, um...
It's Hashirama.
Hashirama. This time
you're depressed right from
the start. What happened?
What do you
mean?! I'm fine...
Liar! Wanna talk
to me? I'll listen.
It's nothing...
Come on, just spill it!
No. There isn't anything.
Hey, stop dragging this
out! I promise I'll listen!
It's really
nothing, I swear!
It's nothing at all.
Look, out with
it, already!
What's the matter?
My lil' brother died...
I come to the river
because I feel like all
the haziness in my heart
gets washed away as
I stare at the water.
So that's what happened...
Your name's
Madara, right?
Could it be that
way for you, too?
Do you have siblings?
I'm one of five.
Well, there used
to be five of us.
Used to be?
We are shinobi, after
all. We never know
when we might die.
If there's a way where
neither side has to die...
It'd be where they
revealed what's inside
them, hid nothing.
And they drank together
like they were brothers.
But then that's impossible.
'Cause one can't
really look deep inside
someone and see
who they really are.
In reality, they both could
be seething inside.
It's impossible to
show what's inside
us to each other?
I don't know...
But every time I come here,
I make a wish that I'll find
some way to make it happen.
Hey, look! Seems I
finally got it to go
in the right direction!
It's not just yours...
Mine too reached
the other side.
In all honesty, I was
shocked that another person
understood how I felt,
especially considering all
the people that didn't.
So there was another foolish
kid who thought as I did,
who wanted to try to
change this war-torn era.
But rather than being
shocked at this turn of
events, I considered Madara
a gift from the divine.
But with you, I can
tell without even
having to look inside.
Tell what?
That your hairdo and your
outfit are totally lame!
Not that we thought alike in
every respect, of course...
After that we
started meeting up
every now and then...
...still without knowing
each other's last names.
We'd spar and compare
our shinobi moves or
talk about the future.
Taijutsu and kumite.
You did a nice job pulling
out a draw against me!
No way. It's not
quite a draw.
'Cause I'm
still standing.
Oh?
Ow!
You were saying?
Not a draw, huh?
But how could you?
[laughter]
I threw it the instant
you blew me away.
I'm not gonna get
taken down that easily!
But the question is,
how do we bring about
concrete changes?
We've gotta have a
vision for the future.
The first step is to not
give up on our ideals.
And we're gonna have
to get stronger, too.
A couple of weak
pups barking won't
change anything.
You're right...
If we can master all
sorts of jutsu and
become stronger
then the adults won't
be able to ignore
our words anymore.
We gotta master many jutsu
and cover any weakness.
Well I'm half there already!
I'm stronger than most of
the adults around me.
Really? That's
impressive!
You really
weren't kidding.
I said not to stand
behind me! Get lost!
Found your
weakness! [chuckle]
How about I throw you into
the river I just pissed in?!
Take this! It's
my Water Style!
Yech! Disgusting!
Don't whip it around!
Each time we met,
we became closer.
Madara!
I've come up with
an amazing jutsu!
Let's both master
it together!
Really? Show me.
Secret Taijutsu Technique, a
Super Fire Style Genjutsu
Slice Giant Shuriken
Two-Step Drop Jutsu!
No good. I
can't visualize it.
I mean, which is it,
taijutsu or genjutsu?
It's not clear!
Plus...
The name is way too long!
Who could remember
all of that?!
Just give me a second,
let me explain it...
Shaddup! Today, we'll be
competing in cliff climbing!
Quit getting
depressed so easily!
That's your weakness.
And your weakness
is always assuming
that's what's going on!
Huh?
Don't you get it? I'm
just psyching you out...
[gasp]
...so I'll win at
cliff climbing!
You bastard!
[laughter] See
you at the top!
You were only
pretending to be sad?!
[chuckle] I won...
Of course you did! I mean,
you did have a head start!
Wow, what a sweeping
view of the forest!
Yeah, you can
see really far!
Speaking of eyesight, I'm
pretty sure you can't beat
me. Wanna challenge me?
What are you talking about?
You seem really
proud of your eyes.
Yeah, of course I am!
'Cause I've got the Sha-
What's up?
Uh, guess it's not all
that. Never mind.
[scoff] Come on, what is
it? You're being awfully
candid for once.
Or else my siblings
wouldn't be dead.
But I wasn't even
able to protect them.
I shouldn't...
Shouldn't...
Madara...
Sorry, I guess I brought
back some memories
for you too, huh?
So do you have
any siblings left?
I do. I still have one
younger brother
who's still alive.
And I'm going to
protect him, no matter
what happens, I swear!
So what about you?
I have one brother left,
too. And I also intend to
protect him, no matter what.
I've decided!
Let's build our
settlement right here!
Huh?!
And there we'll make
it so kids won't
have to kill each
other, and
we'll create this
awesome school where kids
can train and grow up
to become stronger!
Assign missions that
fit people's abilities
and their strengths, too!
Have superiors who are
able to properly assign
ranks to commissions!
A place where kids
don't have to be sent
into harsh battlefronts.
[chuckling] You do
realize it's only you
spouting such nonsense.
Yeah? What about you?!
It sounds pretty good!
Well, then it's decided!
All right!
If that settlement is built,
then that would mean...
I could protect my
brother here, from this
boundless vantage point!
[happy chuckle]
[laughter]
That was where the Village
Hidden in the Leaves
would eventually stand.
I made a resolution that
day. I swore that I would
endure for the
sake of my vision.
We both made it across.
That's a good
stone for skipping.
I'll let you hold onto it
'till the next time we meet!
What is it, Tobirama?
Elder Brother,
we must talk.
Hashirama, about
this boy you've been
meeting up with...
[gasp] How'd you?
I've been tailing you,
following father's
orders, elder brother.
You what?!
I have more sensory
skill than you.
You've been going out all by
yourself quite often lately.
So I suspected
something was up.
I looked into
that young man.
And learned that he
belongs to the Uchiha Clan.
He has killed capable
adults from our clan.
It seems that he's
a genius born with
inherent shinobi talent.
So I was right.
And given your obvious
lack of surprise...
Don't tell me that the
two of you were actually
aware of each other's
family names already!
No! I didn't know.
And I doubt he does...
Hashirama.
You understand what
this means, don't you?
The Senju Clan
and the Uchiha Clan
are bitter enemies.
I haven't mentioned
anything about this
to the other Senju yet.
But if we're not
careful, you could be
branded a traitor.
If you don't want to be
suspected as a spy
then you must shadow that
youth after the next time
the two of you meet.
You're to bring home
intel on the Uchiha Clan.
That is your mission.
And if he should
notice you, kill him!
Maybe it just isn't possible
for us to reach that pipe
dream of ours.
Madara, what are you?!
It might have been brief,
but it was fun, Hashirama.
Our next meeting will likely
be on the battlefield.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Era of
Warring States."
I truly wish it wasn't so...