"Itachi's Story - Light and
Darkness: The Pain of
Living"
Uh?
Father!
We'll discuss this again
later on.
Father!
Coming back from
a mission, are you?
Yes, sir.
We haven't walked together
like this in quite a while.
Well, I'm a genin now. I
have to go out on missions.
Ah! I see!
Yes, that's right... Since
the Uchiha Clan moved
here...
... three years
have gone by.
Pushed to the outskirts of
the village...
...and the higher-ups took
away our authority, leaving
many Uchiha strongly
dissatisfied with their
methods...
You're aware of all that,
too, aren't you?
We still hope to regain
our power one day...
...and step out of the
darkness--
Father, look!
Huh?
[chuckling]
Oh-uh-uh.
What's so funny, Itachi?
Sorry, Father.
It's just that you're the
face of the Uchiha
and I'm proud to be
able to walk alongside you.
That's enough
flattery for now.
Wanna get your favorite
snack on the way back home?
[gasping] Mm!
Can't be helped if
they're all sold out.
Itachi?
Hmm?
Izumi.
I'm sorry, Itachi.
You sure I didn't
interrupt things with
you and your dad?
I'm sure. It's fine.
It's been a while.
Yeah! I haven't seen you
since you became a genin!
Oh! That's right! I'm
sorry I didn't even get
you a gift.
I mean, I didn't even
congratulate you. I'm
really sorry!
You don't have to
apologize so much.
Listen, it's nothing
big, but...
How 'bout, you have one of
these as a gift? Ya know, if
you want...
My mom loves the three-color
dumplings from that shop.
But... I guess that someone
like you... someone who's
brilliant and who excels in
ninjutsu and taijutsu and
who breezed through the
Academy in just a year...
...wouldn't have
much of a sweet tooth.
I'm sorry that I just
assumed...
I guess that since I already
opened them up...
...I'll just have to eat
them myself!
[gulping]
Uh--
Don't tell me...!
Want one?
[grunting]
[giggling]
Do you think it's weird?
Mm-mm! It's
not that...
I've known you for quite a
while, but I never knew that
you liked this kind of food!
Well, rank and gender don't
really have anything to do
with what someone
might like to eat...
Yeah, that's true. Sorry.
[giggling]
I'm sorry, Itachi! It's
just... [giggling]
I'm laughing 'cause... you
looked like you were ready
to use your Sharingan!
I just thought it was
funny... But I won't laugh
anymore. Sorry, Itachi!
Oh!
I'm sorry about that! Look,
let me make it up to you,
okay?
Is there anything else you
might want?
Anything I might want?
Mm-hm!
(Itachi thinking)
That's right, she's--
Yeah... I thought so.
Sorry... but that isn't
something that I can give
you.
Mm.
Hey!
We have another mission.
Stop flirting.
We are not flirting!
Itachi?
I can't give them to
you, but I'll pray for you.
I hope that your Sharingan
awakens soon.
And when it does, I'll
congratulate you!
[meowing]
So? How was the kunai that
you bought the other day,
Itachi?
Uh, yes, it was quite
amazing.
Quite amazing, eh?
You're good with words,
I see.
It's lightweight and
possesses a very sharp
and durable edge.
You'd never be able to get
it anywhere else for the
price that I charged
you for it.
My father also extends
his thanks.
I don't need your thanks,
but how about you give me a
discount on the price of
this latest request,
Captain?
I'm sorry, but that job and
this one are two separate
things...
Yes, of course, I understand
that, but uh...
All right, then, so we've
accepted the mission.
Do you three
understand the specifics?
No! I don't get it,
Minazuki Sensei! We just
have to find a cat, right?
So why are you making all of
us wear these ridiculous
things?!
Tenma, you don't always have
to be so sassy, you know.
What's that?! What did you
say? You got a problem?
Hey, stop! Pipe down, you
two! Or you'll wake up
Tamaki!
[groaning]
[gasping]
[lightly grunting]
[sighing]
[exhaling]
I'm not asking you to find
a run-of-the-mill lost cat,
here!
You're searching
for a Ninja Cat!
What's more, you'll be
going into the Den of Cats,
were cats congregate.
Oh, so that's why we need
this Ninja Tool, huh?
This'll allow us to
understand cat language,
right, meow?
It's intel work...!
...so I just don't see why
we have to...
[swooning]
Ahhh!
Oh, wow... those things
really do look cute on you!
You know... you graduated at
the top of the class at the
Academy!
Don't you have any
shame at all, Itachi?
What? Shame?
But appearance isn't
a consideration when it
comes to a mission, is it?
Uh!
Okay, you two, no fighting.
This is a picture of the
Ninja Cat we're looking
for.
Uh! This cat is...
[meowing]
Meow, meow, meow!
Aww, don't say that!
You're really super cute!
Meow, meow.
Since you're wearing that
translator thing, you can
drop the "meow, meow"
cat-talk. It's hard to
understand, especially
with the way you talk.
[chuckling]
[grunting]
Yeah, so what?!
It's a mission, so it
can't be helped! I gotta
wear 'em!
But... It's a total
embarrassment...
[giggling]
You may say that, but it
looks so cute on you, no
matter what you say!
All right! All right! Let's
go gather intel.
We'll split into teams.
Itachi with me, and Tenma
with Shinko.
Scatter!
[scoffing]
Let's get going!
[meowing]
We sure got our intel really
quickly!
Well, Itachi? Let's
go find the others.
All right, sir. I'll get
them.
[meowing]
Hey, what's the matter,
Tenma?
Listen, just drop it! It's
nothing! Well, no... not
really...
The mission we're on...
No, I mean... actually, the
Ninja Cat that we're
after...
Mm.
It seems like that cat... is
pretty special.
What? Since when did you
turn into a cat expert, huh?
I'm not sayin' I am!
It's just that the leader of
our clan... I mean, my dad
has been sick.
And the medicine he needs...
Well, it calls for some
whiskers from that Ninja Cat.
Oh... then you'd
better take some, right?
Yeah! Think it's okay?
Doubt it.
[grunting]
Just keep me in the dark
about it. If you take them
without me knowing...
It's okay.
Mm. But, uh...
Make sure not to tell
you-know-who!
Huh?! Oh, get it together!
Talk about being a coward!
Are you just jealous 'cause
Itachi, who's way younger
than you skipped a bunch of
grades, to graduate from
the Academy at the top of
his class?
If it weren't
for that kid...
What? You'd be ranked at
the top, is that it?
I didn't say that! Stop
putting words in my mouth!
Yeah, yeah...
whatever.
Anyway, Itachi's awesome!
There's no point competing
with him!
I'm not competing with
him! And it has nothing to
do with being top-ranked!
Reall--
We've found the Ninja
Cat's location.
Please regroup with Minazuki
Sensei.
[groaning]
Rejected again!
And that dang clan of mine
just keeps harping on me
about getting married...
[hiccuping]
Ah! So he was chasing some
female cat around and ended
up here of all places...
Seems like it.
I guess that our mission is
complete now, but...
Okay, I'll go in.
You guys hang back here.
Hey!
What do you want?!
I just overheard your story
and I can sympathize,
believe me! So I just
thought that you and I could
talk a bit.
Wait, you mean that
you can understand me?
And the feelings of
a dumped cat, meow?
I do! I understand that
feeling well!
[chuckling]
Oh, I see. You're not
good with the ladies
either, meow!
OOO!
Uh, yeah. That's it.
Meow, meow.
Have a drink.
These women... they just
don't understand a guy's
charm, you know?
Ladies just don't have
perspective... a discerning
eye...
I mean they're
clueless.
How dare you
insult my woman?!
[gasping]
Looks like there's a
communication breakdown...
Damn it! We should've just
done this right from the
start!
Hiyaaaa!
What's going on, meow,...?
... ya little brats?
I'll take you on, meow!
You're not
gettin' away!
Damn it, he's going on
ahead of us?!
[grunting]
[gasping]
[yelling]
His... toe beans
were so...
... soft and so
squishy.
[fainting]
This guy's good...
(thinking)
I have to do something about
his mobility first...
He's balancing himself
with his tail.
That's not all...
Those whiskers enhance his
spatial perception.
In that case...
[gasping]
Uh!
What are you aiming at,
meow?
You're good with the
kunai, but you've got a
ways to go, meow.
I know... You're right.
I thought that I'd manage
five millimeters more...
Huh?!
[yelling]
[grunting]
Meow.
[chuckling]That all went
pretty well, but... was it
in time?
[grunting]
Don't underestimate Tenma
the Speedy!
[grunting and chuckling]
Heh-heh... I might get more
than a scratch out of this
one...
Huh?! [grunting]
Oh, that's good... I was in
time for both! [sighing]
[giggling]
I...I actually did it!
We owe you a big thanks for
your help meow.
I told him that he should
hurry up and settle down
meow...
But I never thought that
he'd fall in love meow.
This one's skilled except
when it comes to picking
girlfriends meow...
All I ever wanted to do was
find the best bride I could
for the sake of our clan meow.
Meow, the most important
thing is that you're
meow-kay.
You fulfilled the mission
just as I requested,
or at least that's
what I'd like to say!
But... what happened to his
whiskers?!
In order to keep the
fighting to a minimum, there
was no other choice.
So you cut them off?!
I guess that's my fault
for not giving you a
head's up about his skills.
Any chance that you brought
them back...?
No, uh-- they blew
away in the wind.
Mmm.
[gasping and whistling]
[sighing]
Well, I guess it
can't be helped.
Thank you for your hard
work.
Itachi!
The next time you come...
I'll have you take care
of the debts that the Uchiha
have racked up!
[awkward chuckling]
It sure is a good thing that
you got what you needed,
huh, Tenma?
Yeah, I guess...
Oh, come on, cheer up,
already, would ya?
You said the fate of
your clan rests on
it, right?
It isn't actually that
critical...
Although... If this does
cure my dad,
then my clan really
is going to be more secure.
(Itachi thinking)
That Ninja Cat... And those
grownups...
All of them... are always
thinking about their
clans...
[grunting]
All right, listen... you'd
better not be thinking you
saved me or something.
That never crossed my mind.
You know, even if you
didn't end up helping me-
[groaning] Hey, what'd
you do that for?!
Why are you still saying
stuff like that, anyway?!
He's your friend! Of course
he's gonna help you out
when you need it!
Hold on! I was just
completing the mission!
Me be friends
with this guy?!
[grunting]
You stop being so difficult,
too, got it?!
All right! Anything you want
to say to Itachi?!
I'll swear I'll make it
up to you for this!
[gasping]
Why can't you just say
"thank you" like a normal
person, Tenma?
[groaning]
Shinko! That was too hard!
That really hurt!
(Itachi thinking)
Friend, huh?
[groaning]
Oh, my face. Ugh.
Hey, Big Brother! What is
this?
Oh, that's from
that time...
Mmm!
[chuckling]
Life is born... and life
dies... But sometimes...
life is saved again...
Wait... when I saved
Tenma back then...
... I didn't really think
too deeply about it.
He's your friend! Of course
he's gonna help you out
when you need it!
A clan grows. A village is
born. And bonds are
formed.
If that's what friends
are... then we were friends,
no doubt about it.
We formed a bond. That's
why it happened.
We shared a bond...
That's why he--
(Tenma)
I'll swear I'll make it
up to you for this!
...died.
I didn't understand back
then...
...what real pain is.
Pain of losing a life.
I first felt it after
losing-- No. I was forced
to realize it.
The feeling of not wanting
to lose something precious.
Big Brother! Your eyes!
Will the day come when you
possess these eyes, too,
Sasuke?
The day when you come to
know what sadness truly is?
Well, I have to go.
Big Brother! You said you
were gonna play with me
today!
I did, didn't I? But I
have a mission now.
Sorry, Sasuke. Some
other time, okay?
[gasping]
(Shisui)
I apologize, Sasuke. I
need your brother for a bit.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Shisui's
Request."
(Shisui)
He's probably going to
resent me now too, you know.