-(VOICEOVER) Finally.
It all makes sense.
What Sora said.
His use of the word "King."
There's no doubt about it now.
The one who attempted that
coup in the Land of Fire
is the same one
who's behind this.
-Charging Process Complete.
[moaning]
-What's going on?
We being invaded?
-But what exactly are they?
-There sure are a lot of them.
-There's something
not normal about them.
-You guys are late.
-Genma.
What in the hell's
going on here?
-We're about to find out.
Ino.
Go and back up the
Medical Ninja Corps.
They're going to need you.
-Right.
Look.
Those markings.
-Ah.
The Kohaku clan.
-The what?
What do you mean?
What's the Kokaku clan?
-They're Shinobi who
lived near the border
with the Land of Fire.
Their village was
one of those hit
in the recent series of attacks.
-When we went to investigate,
we found no survivors.
Whole villages and
everyone in them
had been destroyed
in a single night.
-To do this to our own people.
It's unforgivable.
-But then, do you really
think these guys are
some of the Shinobi
who didn't survive?
-The enemy must have used
some kind of reanimation jutsu
to bring them back to life.
-So they're using the
victims of one attack
as weapons in the next?
-How many villages do you
think they had to destroy?
-What a horrible
thing to have done.
-Sorry about this.
[bark]
[shouting]
-Oh, man.
-No way.
[laughter]
-Furido.
It's time.
-Much as I'm enjoying the
show, yes, the four of them
should be ready by now.
And Sora.
-Then now's the time for us to
lend our support as planned.
-Right.
-Then let's go.
-Yes, go.
-(VOICEOVER) Kitane.
Nauma.
Tou.
Saito.
With the jutsu they
possess, it's unthinkable.
-CHILD (FROM
BEHIND): Uncle Asuma!
-Konohamaru!
What are you doing here?
The village is on a
Level One state of alert.
-Yeah, we know that.
In fact, we just
supervised the evacuation
of all the kids in the
village to a safe area.
-I see.
Well then, I have another
mission for you three.
Anyone you see of
Chunin rank or higher,
tell them to come to
the main power station.
-Huh?
Why?
What's going on?
-The village is at risk.
-(VOICEOVER) No.
I can't believe they'd
really kill everyone.
It can't be true.
-Sora!
Wait!
Come back here!
[theme music - in japanese]
-What is this?
What?
[gasp]
[grunts]
-So.
So that's what
this is all about.
They didn't just
revive your jutsu.
They revived the
four of you as well.
Saito.
Tou.
Nauma.
Kitane.
-Asuma?
Is that Asuma?
-Yeah.
I see.
Yes, of course.
This is your village, isn't it?
-Kitane.
The four of you.
I'm sorry.
-Please go back.
Just go back to
your resting place.
To that world where you belong.
-Go back to what?
We are no longer living.
We belong to no world.
However, since we have been
brought back to this world,
we must do what we must do.
-What you must do?
-Hold it right there!
[grunting]
-OK, Sora.
What's this all about?
What's going on between
you and Asuma-sensei?
-Nothing!
Get off me, you jerk!
-Hey!
You can't really believe
that Asuma-sensei
had anything to do with
your father's death.
-You heard him
yourself, didn't you?
You were there.
He came right and said it.
He admitted it.
He betrayed my father
and he killed him.
-Not Asuma-sensei.
He'd never do
something like that.
-Not even on the
Hokage's orders?
[gasp]
-You know that the Third Hokage
was Asuma's father, right?
Admit it!
-So what?
What about it?
What's your point?
-My point is that it
was the King of the Leaf
who ordered the
death of my father.
"The Land of Fire
doesn't need two Kings.
There will always be
distrust and confusion
as long as there are two
kings of equal strength."
It was my father's dream
to unite his people
under one king.
And for that dream, he
paid a terrible price.
And all because that man,
Asuma, chose the other king.
-The other king?
-Yes, Naruto.
He was ordered by the Hokage
to eliminate my father.
And those living
under the Hokage
must obey his orders,
no matter what.
That's why my father
did everything
he could to bring him down.
-Even so, that's no reason
to attack Grandma Tsunade.
-I've been such a fool.
And to think that I was
actually grateful to my father's
assassin when he told me
he had died honorably.
[gasp]
-That's why I got to thank you.
I can't tell you happy I
was when you cleared that up
for me, old man.
For a moment, I weakened.
For a moment, I thought
maybe there was no need
to avenge my father, after all.
I even thought taking revenge
might stain his honor.
So I thought.
-Sora.
But-- Come on.
There's no way.
The Third Hokage
wouldn't do that.
He would never make
Asuma-sensei do
something-- something
that terrible.
-But you can't be sure, can you?
-Well, I-- but the
same goes for you.
How can you so sure
that it's true, anyway?
After all, you never
felt like Asuma-sensei
was your father's
enemy, did you?
Not until-- who told you he was?
Who was it that convinced you?
-That's none of your business.
-Don't tell me you're
actually working
with that group causing
all the trouble down there.
The ones who are planning
to wipe us all out?
-Never!
I had no idea!
He never told me
about that part.
-He?
-The only target
was the Leaf's king.
No one else.
Not even Asuma was
supposed to be--
-OK, then.
So what went wrong with
this plan of yours?
-That's what I'm trying to find
out, if you'd just get lost!
-Ahh!
-I understand what
it's like to be lonely.
I know what you're
going through, Sora.
I really do.
I was thinking, we
have so much in common,
we might even be friends.
You've got to decide who
you're going to believe.
Us or-- Sora!
Wait!
[laughter]
-Long time no see, little boy.
-Not you again.
-It's time to finish
this once and for all.
Haha.
Those lips of
yours will be mine.
This time, I'll make sure of it.
-Listen.
All of you.
-I am sorry, Asuma,
but we don't have time
to wax nostalgic
over this reunion.
-No.
You're not going
to use Limelight.
Wait!
Tou!
Saito!
Nauma!
-Don't interfere.
-Kitane.
-I have no other choice.
I've been restored to life
by a reanimation jutsu,
and I must obey the will
of he who cast the jutsu.
I'll kill anyone who interferes.
Even if that person
was a friend.
Very well, then.
-Ahh!
-You have grown old, Asuma!
[groans]
-Asuma!
-Asuma-sensei!
-Konohamaru said you'd be here.
-Who was that?
-Kitane.
One of the guardian
Shinobi 12 whose bodies
were stolen from
the hidden tombs.
-Wait, what are you saying?
-He and the others
were restored to life.
-Reanimation?
That's an advanced jutsu.
-But then, where
are the other three?
-They've gone to
take up positions
to the east, west, and
south of the village.
-Huh?
Why do you think they
split up like that?
What's their plan?
Of all the 12, these four had
the most powerful Lightning
Style jutsu.
They're planning to unleash
the Limelight, renowned
as the greatest and most
powerful Lightning Style
Jutsu of all time.
-What exactly is this Limelight?
-A jutsu whereby four people
in position to the north, west,
east, and south of an area
can incinerate everything
within that area in an instant.
The moment those
four are in position,
the village will be destroyed.
-It can't be.
-What do we do?
-Prevent the other three
from getting into position.
If you can stop
even one of them,
the jutsu can't be activated.
Go.
Yamato.
Sakura.
I'll take care of things here.
You go after the other three.
-Hmm.
-Understood.
-Now.
Having made that
boast, I'll have
to do my best to live
up to it somehow.
-You always were that way.
The more hopeless
your chances were,
the more eagerly you threw
yourself into the battle.
-And you.
You never made a move
without carefully calculating
every possible outcome, Kitane.
-True.
But in this case,
I have no choice.
I'm at the mercy of the jutsu.
Die, Asuma!
-Water Style!
Mouth of the Serpent!
-Woah.
Now it's water style?
-(VOICEOVER) That's right.
She can use all
five chakra natures.
Ahh!
[laughter]
-Oh, no.
After water comes--
-That's right.
A touch of a lightning!
[screaming]
[laughter]
[moaning]
[grunt]
-What's going on here?
-Where are the reinforcements?
-Come on.
You guys are pathetic.
We're going to have to
do this job on our own.
-That's right.
We are Shinobi of the Leaf.
Complaining is
strictly forbidden.
-Yeah, but even so.
If these guys keep
popping up like this--
We've got to find the
source of this jutsu.
-The village will be
buried under these things
soon if this continues.
[growl]
-Ahh!
There seems to be an
endless supply of them!
-You're telling me.
-Hey, what's going on?
Where's Shikamaru, anyway?
We thought he was supposed
to be helping us out, here.
-In a word, the
situation is grim.
From what we found
out, the enemy
can come and go as they
please through the defense
barrier, which
begs the question,
why concentrate all their
forces on the main gate in such
a big, splashy show of strength?
Unless, of course,
that's the whole point.
-In other words,
it's a diversion.
-I suspect another unit is
already secretly at work
elsewhere.
[approaching footsteps]
-We've got trouble!
The whole village is about
to be burnt to a crisp!
[gasp]
-(VOICEOVER) That's him.
Oh!
-Oh, no.
This jutsu again.
[laughter]
-That's right.
Amazing.
I can't believe
you're still alive.
-Seeing is believing.
-Ha!
Well, this time I'll
finish you for sure.
-Huh!
-Grr!
[gulp]
[roar]
-Ahh!
Oh.
[laughter]
[gulp]
-What is this?
-Hmm.
What a shame.
I was so hoping for a
reunion with the young man
I met before.
I despise girls.
[gasp]
-Oh, no.
I feel a chill.
-You're so annoying.
[screaming]
[laughter]
-I could leave you to fry
with the rest of them.
But I'd rather do it myself.
Lightning Style.
Earth Flash!
-Augh!
[laughter]
-It won't be long now, will it?
Before those lips
of yours are mine.
-What's the matter
with you, Asuma?
I thought you meant to stop me.
If you can't do
better than that,
your village is as good as lost.
Show me you can do
it, Asuma, or die.
-Where are you?
Come out.
We have to talk.
-Over here.
Ahh!
-Yao.
-Furido.
It's time we had a talk.
-Hmm.
Before that, don't
you want to take
a look at the Leaf village?
Check out the fireworks.
Aren't they lovely?
-Huh?
What are those lights?
-Well, you see, when those
four lights get into position,
the village will vanish.
-Then you really do mean to
destroy the Leaf village.
-Yes.
It will burn.
The Leaf will be burned
away by the light.
[theme music - in japanese]
-The latest word is
that our attempts
to turn back the undead
invaders are failing.
It's only a matter of
time before our defenses
are overrun.
-What about reinforcements?
-I've already sent Kiba,
Ino, Chogi, and Lee,
but they're heavily outnumbered.
-Unlike us.
The enemy has
unlimited resources.
-We'll eventually be
overwhelmed, unless we
can find whoever's
casting the jutsu.
-Lady Tsunade.
I request permission
to join the front line.
-Next time.
Everyone Struggle to the Death.