Check out their headbands,
they're all from the Hidden Rain
Village...
What matters is which scroll
they have, Heaven or Earth?
[grunting]
[grunti]
You guys gonna run off?!
Be nice and give us your scroll!
Never.
Ajjisai...
Fire Style!
Unsealing Jutsu! Confetti Storm!
[yelling]
They ran away?
Of course they did! Our strength
must've scared them off!
That's too bad. We almost had
their scroll!
[sighing]
"Tenten's Troubles"
Lady Angel...
Lady Angel, you said that
there's a special mission for
us. What is it?
I want you to use the Chunin
Exams as an opportunity to
locate a Jinchuriki.
A Jinchuriki...?
Suiren, Fuyou...
Use your Sensory Perception
skills to look for a shinobi who
harbors enormous amounts of
chakra.
Is that what a Jinchuriki is?
Even if you don't find a
Jinchuriki, you're to bring back
intel on the other villages...
...and on any extraordinary
shinobi.
Understood!
You'll go with these two,
Ajisai.
I understand.
The Hidden Rain is currently in
the midst of a reformation.
And the other villages must not
learn about it.
They must continue to believe
that Hanzo of the Salamander
still rules the Hidden Rain.
Yes, ma'am!
What is it, Ajisai?
You can see so many stars in
other nations...
The stars, huh...?
So, this is what a starlit sky
is like...
Oh! A shooting star!
I've never seen one before!
We'll be able to see them in the
Hidden Rain Village someday,
too...
[blowing]
All right, let's do it...
There are no other shinobi in
the area.
Then, that means we can finally
relax and have a nice meal!
How 'bout okonomiyaki?
What, really?
Wow, who would've expected that
out in the desert?!
Well, we have to make sure to
eat well if we wanna maintain
our strength.
It is so convenient having you
around!
What's that mean?!
That...you are convenient!
I'm sorry, excuse me? I may have
convenient tools, but I am not a
convenient tool, okay?
No, no, Tenten! You are
absolutely convenient
Seriously?!
You listen to me! I'm not
convenient.
You're in charge of making
dinner, now!
Uh...Hey, Tenten...
Don't follow me!
What just happened?!
I have no idea...
What now?!
Don't look at me!
Huh?
[sigh] Oh, damn it...
Guess I just needed...to vent a
bit...
[yell]
8 Trigrams: Air Palm!
Third Gate of Life...
Open!
[yelling]
You've improved greatly, Tenten!
Thanks so much, Guy Sensei!
You've really perfected your
skills.
But, to be completely honest, it
isn't good enough.
Hmm?
What's wrong?
Mastering weapons for single
combat is fundamental for a
ninja, right?
Fundamentals are important.
I know that. But, now, the issue
is going beyond fundamentals...
Neji has honed his Gentle Fist
and developed a new jutsu.
So I've seen! He's brilliant!
Lee only has fundamental
taijutsu skills, but he can open
the Eight Inner Gates, now.
Oh...Those are the fruits of his
labor!
Yeah, but...all I have is the
basics!
Huh?
I wanna have a really awesome
skill, too!
At the rate things are going,
all that I'll ever do is stand
behind them and support them.
You know, Tenten,...a role such
as that is actually critical in
teamwork.
You see, I know both Neji and
Lee are taijutsu users, and
because of that they're
close-contact fighters...
Don't you get it, Tenten? We're
able to fight so aggresively
because we know that you have
our backs.
And, we are incredibly grateful
that you're there for us.
That's nice to know, but, rather
than just gratitude, I'd like to
have my own special ninjutsu!
Isn't there something I can do,
Guy Sensei?
Hmm...huh...hmm...
How about the Sansetsukon?
That isn't really different than
this!
Wait, that's right, Tenten!
Don't forget that you have a
skill that no one else on this
entire team possesses!
So, you should work to hone it!
A skill no one else has?
You're really convenient to have
around.
Please don't talk me like I'm
some kind of tool or something
like that, Sensei!
Oh no, I didn't mean to make it
sound like that at all!
You know, I'd already given this
a lot of thought before I came
to talk to you...
Tenten!
Okonomiyaki is ready!
So, come and get it!
How did they turn out, anyway?
I have my doubts about them...
Looks like it's another hot day.
It's the opposite of the Hidden
Rain.
[grunt]
Yeah, a little dampness would be
nice.
I do see some green over there.
Byakugan!
What do you see, Neji?
That there's no one around here
at all.
Well, let's just keep moving. As
we get closer to the finish
line, we're bound to run into
other teams.
You are right. That is way
better than lying in wait.
But if we wanted to, I see a
good spot for it ahead.
Where?
Want to check it out?
This place is creepy.
I can see caves all around us.
It seems we found a ruin.
A ruin?
That's right. Of the Land of
Wind.
Yep, as I thought...
They're Hidden Leaf shinobi.
They're different than
yesterday's bunch.
That trio we saw yesterday was
entirely unimpressive.
I wonder what these guys are
gonna be like?
They're heading right for us.
They have a Sensory-type, too.
All right, we'll ambush them.
They're lying in wait for us.
What about getting the scroll
they have?
Well! We'll fight them and grab
it!
Looks like they plan to do the
same thing. They're coming!
Right now!
Let's not waste each other's
time, here.
I'll put it bluntly.
We possess the Heaven scroll.
So, if this is what you're
after, let's cut to the chase
and fight.
Unsealing Jutsu: Shuriken!
That jutsu...!
Rotation!
[gasp]
[yell]
Summoning Jutsu, Gate of
Rainwater!
[grunting]
[growl]
[gasp]
[boom]
Why you...!
You're not the only one who can
use Transportation Jutsu!
They're quite good.
That's true,...although...
None of them possess large
amounts of chakra.
Ajisai...
Unsealing Jutsu! Confetti Storm!
[gasp]
They ran away!
Byakugan!
Let's go!
They're after us.
They definitely have a
Sensory-type with them.
Water Style! Hidden Drizzle
Jutsu!
What's wrong?!
There's so little moisture
around here that my Water Style
doesn't work well.
[gasping]
I know that we don't have the
advantage of higher ground,
here...
It's an impossible battle, but
we have to fight!
Take this! Leaf Hurricane
Lee, above you!
[gasp]
Senbon Rainstorm!
[grunting yell]
[yelling]
You're not bad!
Gentle Fist!
[shouting]
Now try this! Leaf Drop!
[shout]
[gasps]
[shrieking]
Tenten!
Ajisai!
[gasp]
I can still sense their chakra
underground...But it's deep...
All this rubble's in the way...
We can't waste time fighting
senselessly.
We're going to save our
teammate, now. Please, don't
interfere.
The same goes for us.
Good idea! Let us all call a
truce for now!
After all, we're not at war.
It's just the Chunin Exams.
The safety of our teammate is
more important than passing.
We agree to your plan. But,
we'll conduct our own search and
rescue operation.
This looks like a ruin from the
Land of Wind.
I'm guessing Ajisai and the
other kunoichi fell into an
underground corridor.
If it's a corridor, it has to
connect to somewhere. So, let's
find where.
Should we just use brute force
and dig from above?
There's a risk we could cause a
collapse, that way...
We should search for a passage
into the ruins and follow it
underground.
[whimpering]
What's the matter, Tenten? Just
burn with the passion of youth!
Let all of your youthful energy
flow! And fill up with burning
chakra!
Yeah, but, Guy Sensei,...I
thought we were just going to be
doing some strength training out
here!
You're naive, Tenten!
Somewhere here, your physical
strength is going to reach its
limits.
Then you'll fall and then you'll
die.
I'll die?!
To stay alive, you must overcome
the limits of your physical
strength.
Of course, in order to do
something like that, you must
have a strong will.
Yes, Sensei!
Hi, there! Are you guys cliff
climbing, too?
Hang in there!
Kakashi?!
Your arm, why is it behind your
back?!
Oh, that? It's just a little
habit of mine.  Well, see you
later!
"See you later?" No way! This is
a rivalry contest! And I'll
finish first!
[growl]
Don't get so worked up, Guy!
This is only training.
And what's wrong with a little
rivalry during training?!
Hey, wait! Guy Sensei, please
come back!
Just go your own pace!
Come on...!
[grunting]
[cry]
[exhale]
Damn it! Damn it!
Damn it all! Damn...
Huh? Good job, Tenten. You made
it, huh?
Did you overcome your limits?
I'm not quite sure...But I feel
like I overcame something.
Water?
Here.
You are convenient, after all!
Can you please stop saying
that?!
I just mean your jutsu's
convenient.
[slurp and exhale]
Storing items inside a scroll,
or using a scroll to pull out
items from far, far away...
...using the Transportation
Technique, a type of Summoning
Jutsu.
You have that skill or you
don't.
So, wait, are you saying that
you think I have the skill for
it?
Seems so!
And honing that skill is the
path to gaining the strength and
usefulness that you so wish to
have.
You think I should hone my
skill? Won't that only increase
my physical strength?
Your mental strength, too!
I'm certain that you must be
aware that chakra is the
combination of physical energy
and mental energy, aren't you?
Yes, of course.
An individual can increase their
chakra by merely training.
Simply put, if you're able to
increase your physical and
mental power, your chakra will
increase as well.
I'm sure increasing my chakra is
good for me, but what exactly
will happen?
With the Summoning Jutsu, the
quantity or size of what is
summoned is directly
proportional to the caster's own
chakra. So...
For example, you just summoned
this amount of water.
By increasing your chakra, you
could summon enough water to
fill a bathtub, or a lake, or
even an ocean.
An ocean...
[yelling]
[chuckling]
And, that is why we will
continue our training to
increase our chakra, Tenten.
Right!
We just climbed up, so why do we
have to climb down, too?!
This is also training! Just burn
with the passion of youth!
Let all of your youthful energy
flow! And fill up with burning
chakra!
Come on!
[screaming]
[gasps]
Where am I?
Huh?!
Hey, there...! Are you all
right?
Hey! Talk to me!
Lee, did you find something?
Not yet. I thought this was an
entrance, but it's just a dead
end.
I see. We have to find a way
into the ruins quickly. We don't
know how long before they'll
collapse since that shockwave
weakened them...
Oh no! Can you find them with
your Byakugan, Neji?
It seems they fell down a
considerable distance...
Tenten...
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Imprisoned Pair."
I hope that you are safe!