Kakashi.
The Kazekage thinks you should
be appointed as a troop
commander during the war.
Why me?
For one, because you took
part in the battle of
Kannabi Bridge during the
Third Great Ninja War.
It's very sad to say, but
there aren't many veterans
left from that war in any
of the five great nations.
This is also a direct
order from me.
Then I guess I can't
refuse, Lady Hokage.
However, I do
have one request.
What is it?
One person can't
wage a war alone.
I need a good shinobi
to act as my right-hand
man and assist me.
Right. Well, is there
anyone that you can
trust implicitly?
A man who's presently on a
mission escorting Naruto.
You mean...?
Huh?
Turtle, turtle...
This is...
...The ninja tortoise
Guy uses in emergencies!
[retching]
Whew! Guess I'm past the
first stage, I hope.
Gyah.
Finally feeling
better now, Guy?
Huh? Ah, no,
not to worry!
These waves are
nothing to me!
[hurf]
He's been seasick the
whole trip and he still
puts on a tough act.
Who does he think
he's fooling?!
Anyway, since all
of us are here now,
[Yamato]
We'll enter the Land of
Lightning's territory,
after replenishing
our supplies on this
isolated island.
[Aoba]
We've turned the final corner.
Our goal's in sight.
We can't be complacent.
The enemy will seek out
any chance to attack us.
[Guy]
But...
Since we're so close now,
we can call for backup from the
Allied Shinobi Forces, right?
You may be right, but
those reinforcements
could be disguised
enemies.
What?!
That's right.
We can't let
our guard down.
Even if it's someone we
know well, like Lady
Tsunade or Kakashi.
Tch, come on!
Surely we can identify
their chakra. We are
jonin, after all!
But I've heard a rumor there's a
transformation jutsu that can
copy and disguise chakra.
What?! Are you being serious?!
Hey!
Aaah! Eternal rival!
Ha ha ha ha!
[impact]
Ohh...
[shivers]
Well, knock on wood!
Also, I have to
emphasize that no one
can tell Naruto the real
purpose of this mission.
I mean you, Guy!
Right. I got it!
This mission's a cover!
Hah! We're really here
to protect Naruto.
[yawn]
Uh, oh! Oh, man,
I'd better hurry!
[Guy being muffled]
[zip]
Mmhmf! mmmlmf! Mfflffmm!
[pee sounds]
[Naruto] [drowsy]
Go! Rasen-pee!
[chuckle]
[shiver]
Hm?
What are you guys doing out
here this late at night?
Oh, I'm, uh...
I'm getting
a massage!
A massage?
That's right! We're
totally not keeping
a secret from yo--
Mmff!
Hey, wait a second here,
you guys aren't...
[gasp]
... hiding something really
delicious to eat from me?
Are you?! Huh!? Huh?!
[relieved sigh]
Don't worry, Naruto,
if we find something
delicious, we'll be
sure to share with you!
Good night.
The three of us were just
discussing the schedule for
the remainder of our journey.
Oh, and, Guy?
Remember what we
talked about, okay?
Right! I got it!
And I'll take
first watch!
Hmm.
Something funny is
going on around here.
"Kakashi, My Eternal Rival"
you know, I can keep
watch by myself. Why
don't you get some sleep?
No, thanks.
I've had nothing to
do all day except sleep.
So now, I'm wide awake.
I wonder sometimes
what everyone in the
village is up to.
It's been such a long time
since I've seen Kakashi Sensei.
Huh? Ah!
Kakashi!
The man that they call,
the eternal rival of
the Leaf's Might Guy!
This is a good opportunity
to tell you about our
younger days together.
You really don't
have to tell me.
I remember it like
it was yesterday!
It was right around the
time that we became genin
that our rivalry began.
Seriously!
You don't have
to tell me!
Move, you're in my light.
Heh! People call me Might Guy,
the Blue Beast of the
Hidden Leaf Village!
You're one of the super
elite here, right?
You're Sakumo's son, known as
the White Fang of the Leaf!
What about it?
See, I have this bad habit:
whenever I see a guy with
tons of talent, I just
have to challenge him!
How about it? Let's go
lay our youth on the line
in hot-blooded battle!
Why, if I
don't have to?
You were born an elite,
whereas I made myself elite
through sheer effort!
It's a classic story!
We could have an
amazing rivalry!
Huh?
Your sense of humor
leaves me speechless.
Hey!
What about my challenge?
No, thanks.
Heh hah! But that
just makes me even
more determined!
'Cause once I've made up
my mind, I never back
down! That's my rule!
He hee!
I won't quit!
Just fight me!
[pee sound]
Yah!
Fiiight meee!
[gasp]
It's like
an acorn.
Dghgg!
Please,
fight me,
Kakashi!
I don't want to!
[relaxed sigh]
Fight me!
Seriously?
In the end, Kakashi
succumbed to the intensity
of my youthful determination
and agreed to fight me.
Hearing this makes
me feel bad for
Kakashi Sensei.
And that's the way we forged
the unbreakable bonds of our
eternal rivalry!
But, what kind of
fights did you guys
have, anyway?
We both gave it our all in
honest, intense battle, of
course! That's the only way!
Although I must admit,
I'm reluctant to tell
him about some of them.
Ulp!
Bow and arrow,
sickle and chain,
and now shuriken.
I've beaten you
in all of them.
You finally satisfied?
Not yet! So,
I challenge you
to spar with me!
There's no way I'll lose
to you in taijutsu!
Seems you finally have
something to brag about.
You're a true prodigy,
with skills inherited
from the White Fang!
But you're too
quick to run away!
What strength!
Leaf Hurricane!
Ah!
Ha! You're mine!
Ha ha ha ha!
I guess I overdid it
a little bit, huh?
Gaah! Substitution?!
Ghhhk!
Guuhh...
Heh. Have you
had enough yet?
From now on,
know your place.
[smack]
Huh?
Let go, trash!
No way. Not yet.
You can't go;
I'm not done challenging you.
And I am not trash!
I've beaten you in
every challenge.
[sniffly sobs]
[exasperated sigh]
All right, then, what do
you want to try next?
Ah! Hah!
Here I come!
Bring it on!
Rock, Paper...Scissors! Go! Go!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
I can't tell him about
challenges like that one.
I'd never hear the end of it.
[yawn]
You know, I think I'll try
to go to sleep, after all.
Oh, are you sure? I was just
about to get to the good part!
[door shuts]
Aw.
[yawn] Boy, I'm starting
to get sleepy too.
[snoring]
[Kakashi]
Hey! Guy! You there?
Guy!
Huh?
Did someone call my name?
Over here, Guy!
Hm?
Oh! It's you, Kakashi!
Hold on... What're you doing
way out here on the water?
Hnn!
Ow! No, it's not a dream.
Could it be?
But I've heard of a rumor that
there's a transformation jutsu,
that's able to both copy
and disguise chakra.
Could this be what Yamato
was talking about?
Well, I won't allow
myself to be fooled!
I can't let the enemy
get close to Naruto!
What nerve to disguise
himself as my eternal rival!
I'll strip his façade
off with my bare hands!
All right!
Be right there!
Hey! You all right?
What happened out here?
Oh, so that's his
little game, is it?
Making it sound like
we sent some kind of
distress signal, and
he's come to help out.
Well, I won't be fooled as
easily as that, you imposter!
Sorry, what do you mean,
"Are you all right"?
Oh, well, you sent an
S. O. S. message, didn't you?
Mehhh!
Ha! What a fool, telling such
a bald-faced lie like that!
But attacking him out
of the blue would be
too impetuous.
I'll have to wait
for absolute proof
that he's a fake.
But how am I gonna
get that proof?
Is there anything that's
happened between Kakashi and
me an enemy wouldn't know?
Uhm...
Hmmm...
Ah!
I've got it! Of course!
That's perfect!
Oh, and by the way!
What are the stats in our
rivalry battles these days?
You know, our
win-loss record?
What? Guy, I don't think
that this is the time to
discuss something like that!
I knew it! He may
appear identical,
but he couldn't have delved
that deeply into our private
affairs to impersonate Kakashi.
I see. So what you're
saying is that you
really don't remember!
Well sure,
I remember,
it's just...
What? You can tell me?
Yeah. Of course.
[gulp]
The way it stands now,
I'm winning, 51-50.
Right?
Ah ha! That phony's just
given himself away!
But never mind that.
What was the reason
for the S. O. S.?
The reason is the
danger standing right
in front of me!
Severe Leaf Hurricanes!
What are you doing?!
Of course you'd take on
Kakashi's speed along
with his appearance!
Hyah!
You can't escape my taijutsu,
no matter how much you try to
run.
You didn't call me here
just to continue our
rivalry, did you?
You are a pretty
good imitation.
But if you want to prove
you're the real thing,
then copy my taijutsu,
just like "Copy Ninja"
Kakashi would!
How do I know you're
the real Guy?
What? Are you
kidding me?!
The real Guy would know that
even with the Sharingan,
I can't copy everything!
That's just like an imposter:
to accuse me of being the fake
to throw me off the trail!
What's all the commotion
about out there?
Looks like Guy.
Must be him, I didn't
see him anywhere onboard.
This doesn't seem like
something trivial.
Let's go help him out!
Yeah!
What can I say to make
you believe that I'm me?
So you're just going to keep
denying the truth, huh?
Guy!
Oh, good; you two
are just in time!
Oh! It's Kakashi!
Hey, how's
it going?
Don't let him fool
you that easily!
He's tricky!
He's a fake posing
as Kakashi!
What?
But just take a look
at him, he seems like
the real Kakashi!
[Aoba]
Yeah. You are
Kakashi, right?
Yes! But Guy won't let
me off the hook, here!
Don't be fooled!
It's just like
you said, Yamato!
He's even transformed
his chakra into an exact
copy of Kakashi's!
I have all the proof
that I'll ever need!
So the three of us should
move in and take him down!
Huh?
Hey! What are
you doing?!
Did you ever consider
that you might be
trapped inside an
enemy's genjutsu?
Or maybe that you're
still just not feeling
well from being seasick
for days on end.
Right? He's not
acting normal,
is he?
So you'd rather side with this
impostor than listen to me,
your friend and comrade?!
Ohhhh!
Of course! I see clearly now!
All of you are fakes!
[all]
D'agggghh!
He's really acting strange.
I'll just use my Wood
Style to restrain him.
Forget it. I won't let you.
Eight Inner Gates!
Sixth Gate of Joy, open!
This is bad! He's serious!
Dive as deep as you can!
Yoooooooo!
Asakujaku!
[panting]
[Kakashi]
Just what proof do you have
that I'm an impostor, anyway?
Irrefutable proof! From our
battles as eternal rivals!
There's no way the real
Kakashi would ever get our
win-loss record wrong!
But it's 51-50 in my favor,
I'm certain. There's no mistake.
Or maybe, you're just bitter
that I took the lead after I
defeated you in our last match.
What?
[crack]
So you must have been
spying on that battle then!
[sigh] I don't know
how else to say it:
I'm really me!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
You just can't stop
giving yourself away!
That match tied us!
Kakashi and I are
even at 50!
No, you're wrong.
Huh?
There was the sushi eating
contest after that.
Where I won right?
I'm so stuffed...
I... I forgot about that one!
D'ooogh!
You must've been
watching that
battle too!
Will you cut it out, Guy?
Yeah you almost
killed us!
Guy, if you really want,
I'll reveal your secret, the
one that only I would know.
Interesting ploy, phony.
If you know of a secret
such as that, then I'd
like to hear it, too!
[Yamato]
What? Guy has such a fine
physique, but it's the
size of an acorn? Really?!
[Aoba]
That small? Maybe we
should call him the
"Little Beast" instead.
[Guy]
It's not like that anymore!
I was just a kid!
[Guy]
Sorry. I really was
convinced the enemy was
trying to infiltrate us.
But what are you doing
here anyway, Kakashi?
I already told you. You sent
your Ninja Tortoise to the Leaf
carrying an S. O. S. So I rushed
over here as fast as I could.
Huh?!
So back then, when
we thought something
whizzed past us.
Guy was sending out
his Ninja Tortoise!
What are you
talking about?
Ohh!
[heaving]
Ow!
Turtle!
Help me...
[Yamato]
Uh? Did you see that?
Did something just
fly past us?
[Aoba]
Yeah. I think so.
Sorry about that,
you guys.
Then this
entire thing
was all your
doing, Guy?!
Ah ha ha ha ha ha!
So, how are things
back in the village?
He's changing
the subject!
Well, things have gotten
a bit complicated.
Oh? What's wrong?
I'll contact you
again once it's
all decided.
Oh, okay.
Did you want to
check on Naruto
before you go?
I don't need to.
He has you with him.
Yeah. He sure does.
Guy!
Yeah?
If anything should ever
happen to me, you'd rush over
right away, wouldn't you?
You're damn right.
Never doubt that.
[yawn]
I could have sworn that
I heard Kakashi Sensei.
Huh?
You are hiding something
from me, aren't you?!
And it's something
delicious, I bet!
[Aoba]
We're not!
[Naruto]
Liars! Then why are you
huddled together like that?
[Guy]
We're gazing at stars!
[Aoba]
And acorns...
[Guy]
Heh, stars are a lot bigger
than they seem from afar!
[Naruto]
Hey! Why are the Stone
and Mist fighting here?
[Kurotsuchi]
That's what I want to know!
These guys just attacked us
right out of the blue!
[Ganryu]
Move it, Leaf ninja!
If you interfere,
I'll kill you, too!
[Chojuro]
This ends now, Ganryu!
It violates Lady
Mizukage's will.
Per her orders,
I'm going to
have to stop you!
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
Naruto's Vow.
[Chojuro]
I mean, if I can.