No way!
It's useless.
Huh?
What?! But how-?!
Itachi?!
The Forbidden
Visual Jutsu
Die.
Amaterasu!
I have to give you
credit for placing
me under a genjutsu.
Heh.
Sasuke! Now's your chance!
Why did you stop?
But yours is still a
far cry from Itachi's.
With his masterful Tsukuyomi,
he was able to freely
manipulate time within
the dreamscape.
A Curse Mark that
causes paralysis.
[Madara]
He must have placed it then.
[Karin]
Sasuke...
you can't move?!
Aagh!
[Danzo]
I don't need to use
ninjutsu against that one.
Sticking with Taijutsu, eh?
looks like he wants
to preserve chakra.
Release!
The flow of Danzo's
chakra has changed.
What's he up to?
If Sasuke knows the truth
about Itachi, then the
Akatsuki must know as well.
[Danzo]
It's impossible to conceal what
really happened any longer.
But why?
Why did you ever believe that
it was necessary to save the
life of such trash, Itachi?
Rgh!
No! Sasuke!
Take a good look, Itachi.
Look at the state he's in.
This boy...
Is your ultimate mistake,
without a doubt.
[silence]
[Madara] [flashback]
He couldn't kill...
his little brother.
He killed every shred of
feeling in his heart in order
to slaughter his own kin for
the sake of his village.
But he just couldn't bring
himself to kill you.
Do you understand
what that means?
Huh?
[Madara] [flashback]
To him, your life...
was even more precious...
than the village!
Huuaaahhh!
Yaaaahh!
[Danzo]
He broke free of
the Curse Mark.
Is that the Susano'o?
It's almost completely
different from before!
[inhale] [exhale]
This is Sasuke?! His chakra!
He's changed into something
totally new.
Good. His rage has matured
and gained in power.
And his body is naturally
responding to it.
This is really going
quite well indeed.
He doesn't need my
help at all.
He's aiming right at me.
Can't weave the signs in time!
I have no choice!
At least I managed
to divert its path.
Danzo's chakra level
plunged with that jutsu!
But why dodge Susano'o's attack,
especially at such a cost?
I thought the jutsu he's
been using is supposed
to make him immortal.
The jutsu he released earlier
must have been protecting him!
That was Wood Style.
now it makes sense.
With that many Sharingan,
I knew there had to be
some kind of secret,
to allow someone who
wasn't an Uchiha to
be able to use them.
Damn that Orochimaru.
It seems he was in close
contact with Danzo.
[panting]
[Madara]
He had the cells of First Hokage
Hashirama implanted in him to
enhance his physical energy.
That's how he's able to
control so many Sharingan.
[panting]
No! He can die! If he
hadn't dodged that attack,
he would have died!
That's why he exhausted
so much chakra!
Sasuke, listen!
That's the real Danzo!
But the jutsu that makes him
invincible is undone right now!
And that means
he's vulnerable!
So that woman is a
Sensory Type ninja!
Looks like she's caught on
to me. But it's too late!
Yes! Got him!
No, I was wrong.
As soon as Danzo weaved those
signs, the feel of his chakra
shifted just slightly.
He launched that other jutsu!
I'm probably the only one
who's able to pick that up.
That means Susano'o's
attack just then probably
wasn't in time. Damn it!
He recast that jutsu, But
those three eyes stayed shut.
As far as I can tell, there
are ten Sharingan on that arm,
in addition to the First
Hokage's cells.
Uchiha's power and
Hashirama's power.
It looks like he's
planning to try to
control Nine-Tails.
So he's after Naruto, too.
Danzo's chakra dropped
again just now.
It seems like that jutsu
really takes quite a toll.
That must be why he
needed to undo it before.
Release!
In order to preserve his chakra!
And another thing; those
Sharingan on his right arm
are definitely linked to
his jutsu, I just know it!
[Karin]
There's some secret to those
eyes that keep closing.
There's no mistake.
This is the Visual Jutsu
forbidden even among the
Uchiha: The Izanagi.
I certainly didn't expect to
see it here, of all places.
[panting]
[wet cough]
Ah! Sasuke!
Don't panic! I have to
figure out Danzo's jutsu!
I've gotta stay focused
on that right now!
Huuuah!
The Izanagi.
Where for a few
seconds' span of time,
anything disadvantageous to the
wielder, like damage or death,
can be rewritten as a dream.
[panting]
[inhale]
[exhale]
And anything advantageous,
such as the wielder's attacks,
are kept as part of reality.
An ultimate genjutsu cast upon
oneself that blurs the border
between fantasy and reality!
And the eye that uses
Izanagi loses its light,
never to open again.
But with that many eyes...
The duration of the Izanagi
varies with each user.
He wanted to extend that time
no matter what it took, so he
became Orochimaru's lab rat.
That Madara. There's no chance
he'll join the battle, but I
can't take any chances.
I must keep enough power
in reserve to fight him.
It'll be some time before my
right eye recovers from using
it during the Summit.
However, fighting the Susano'o
won't be easy, either.
That arrow attack is
very difficult to dodge.
I can't undo the Izanagi yet.
I have to finish
things this minute.
Summoning Jutsu!
That Summoning.
It's the Baku, a monster
that devours nightmares.
It's a lot larger
than I imagined.
I will not lose sight of Danzo!
No matter what!
Now Susano'o won't
be able to move.
And I'll augment the Baku's
already impressive suction
power with even more force.
Wind Style:
Vacuum Blast Barrage!
The weak spot in the Susano'o
is right there!
[Sasuke]
Fire Style!
Fire Ball Jutsu!
Fire Style. Clever, using
the Baku's inhalation
against itself, Sasuke.
[panting]
[wet coughs]
53... 54... 55... 56...
57... 58... 59... 60!
Those eyes!
One shuts about
every 60 seconds.
And Danzo's chakra keeps
dropping rapidly all the while.
Which means...
That right arm of his can be
used to measure the duration of
action of his weird jutsu.
Just four left!
About two hundred and forty
seconds, or four minutes, is the
time limit of that jutsu!
From what I can tell,
while his jutsu's active,
it allows his attacks to be
successful but makes Sasuke's
attacks ineffective.
If that's the way
this jutsu works,
Danzo's got to be desperate to
take Sasuke down while the jutsu
is still up and running.
Even a mutual strike
would be a win to Danzo!
[Karin]
Sasuke! I think I'm
starting to get his jutsu!
Are you
listening to me?
When all ten of the eyes you
have on your right arm have
closed your jutsu will be
undone, isn't that right?
You knew? You knew about
about the Izanagi?
As I suspected!
You tricked it out of me!
Why, you crafty brat!
No! You fool!
Don't engage him!
Stop, Sasuke! You should
just retreat for now!
Prolong the battle!
That would be pointless,
for in that case, Danzo
would just undo the Izanagi.
If that happens, Sasuke would be
at an overwhelming disadvantage,
since he's already used up so
much of his strength.
Sasuke is pressing him with the
super-fast, super-strong
Susano'o to force Danzo to
continue using Izanagi,
and thus use it up.
Sasuke has long known that
this battle will be won by
whoever outlasts the other.
He's putting his remaining
strength into a chakra blade.
This is the deciding moment.
How many Uchiha did you
have to kill to get that
right arm of yours?!
It was all thanks to Itachi.
You made him do it!
[Danzo]
Shisui's eye has
recovered at last.
However, Sasuke is no longer
useful with that injury.
As I thought, Madara's the
one I need to place under
genjutsu and manipulate.
I can't waste time. My wound
is too deep. I simply cannot
afford to die here today.
[Sasuke]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
Danzo Shimura.
[Danzo]
I win.