This one's proven to
be quite a challenge...
...but that just
means it'll be a
great puppet once
I master it.
I wondered why
you'd been cooped
up in here so long.
(Temari)
...Working on
a new puppet?
Yeah...
This one's a bit
complicated to
assemble... Ugh!
And I wasn't
cooped up!
Are you preparing
for war?
In a way...
(Kankuro)
You heard what
happened to the
Leaf Village...
(Kankuro)
At this point,
nothing would
surprise me.
(Temari)
The Leaf Village
is our ally.
(Temari)
We can't shrug this
off as someone else's
problem.
[painful scream]
(Kankuro)
Not to mention
their village
was destroyed...
(Kankuro)
Rebuilding it
won't be easy...
(Temari)
They also have to fill
the void left by their
Hokage's absence.
(Kankuro)
You're right...
Both politically and
psychologically...
(Kankuro)
...being without
their leader and
anchor.
...that has
to hurt...
Damnit. I
screwed up.
Frankly, can they
get over what the
Akatsuki did to then
without their Hokage?
(Kankuro)
Gaara..?
I don't know.
But... At least
the Leaf Village
still has him.
(Kankuro)
I don't wanna
say this, but-
You know how
(Kankuro)
-they see you.
You're a weapon
of terror!
Seriously. Leaving
us and joining the
regular troops won't be
easy. Nowhere near it.
They're full of
Jonin who think
pretty pooly of
you...
And most of the
villages are as
terrified of you as
they've always been.
However-
I know that.
(Gaara)
But doing nothing at all
will almost certainly
bring even greater pain.
And I know
exactly what
I must do now.
I must find a
way to clear my
own path...
Perhaps then the
day will come when
I can be like him.
(Naruto)
SERIOUSLY!? This is
a joint mission with
the Hidden Sand?
Come on! We can
handle this without
those guys! Can't
we!?
Don't be that
way, Naruto.
There's trouble
on the boarder we
share with the Sand
Village...
,,,if only one side
was asked to help,
the other might be
offended.
Isn't it better if
the two allied
villages work together
on this mission?
It makes both
our jobs easier!
[annoyed groan]
This alliance was
formed after the attack
on the Leaf Village,
but it's untested.
There are
still problems
to work out.
The first step
is to build trust
on both sides...
...and that's
really what this
particular mission
is all about.
Wow, Sasuke!
Impressive!
You're so
clever!
But, it does
take all the fun
out of it if you
put it like that.
put it like what!?
I still don't get
it you guys!
Guess it's just
too deep for you
to understand!
It's about nations,
villages, important
people, and critical
ideas!
Knock it off,
Sakura!  You
don't have to
sound so mean!
In any event, we're
allied nations, so
let's try to get
along, okay?
Yeahhh, okay.
I think that's enough
talking for now.
Let's just head to
the rendezvous point
with the Sand.
Yeah! Let's race to
see who gets there
first! Last one
there's a rotten egg!
No fair! You
didn't even
say "go!"
I win!! That
makes you a
rotten egg!
You're so
immature!
Bahaha!
Stop it.
This should be our
rendezvous point.
Looks like they're
not here yet.
Of course they're
late! What do you
expect from a bunch
of jerks like that!?
You can never tell what
those guys from the Sand
are thinking. And they're
sorta scary, too.
(Naruto)
If they really
wanted to be friends
with the Leaf Village
(Naruto)
They would have
shown up on time!
I'm sorry if
we were late.
G-G-Gaara!
(Thinking)
Of all the
people...
(Sasuke Thinking)
He's the one we're
doing the joint
mission with!?
Uhh, not to worry,
Gaara! You guys did
just fine!
We got here a
little early,
that's all!
Not so.
Heh heh,
pardon us!
It looks like
we owe all of
you an apology!
We kept you
waiting, and
we are sorry.
(Thinking)
Hm. Looks like he's lost
his bloodthirsty demeanor
and mellowed out.
(Thinking)
The Sands!
Ultimate Defense!
Ow ow ow!!
Well, what was
that about, Naruto?
Nothing! I was
just joking around
and saying "hi!"
Come on, a little
rock like that
couldn't hurt No
Brows anyway!
Hey wait. Where'd
those other guys
go..?
He just made Lord
Gaara use his
Ultimate Defense!
I know! How
scary was that!?
Heh heh, I guess
he still has
trouble fitting in.
What's up with
those guys? What
a bunch of wimps,
huh?
(Naruto)
So Gaara, what happened
to the Make-up guy, and Fan
Girl? Aren't they with you!?
I think you mean
Kankuro and Temari.
I'm enlisted with
the regular forces
right now.
Let me introduce
Yaoki and Korobi.
They serve under me.
I'm Yaoki!
I'm Korobi!
I'm Kakashi
Hatake. I'm
heading up
this mission,
And this is Naruto,
Sakura, and Sasuke.
Hey! What's up?
Nice to
meet you!
Hi there!
Nice to meet
you too!
They're still
rookies, so
please, be
patient.
Now that we're all
together, I suggest that
Gaara's team approach
from the Western side-
-of the mountain
and my Squad 7
will approach from
the East.
Then, at midnight,
we'll simultaneously
attack the bandits
at the summit.
How's that sound?
Ugh! I don't see
why we have to
wait till then!
Squad 7 can take
care of those
bandits by ourselves
right now!
These bandits are
made up of rogue
ninja.
And word has it
that there are
even chunin-class
ninja among them.
Yeah, you hear
that, Naruto!?
If you rush in
there, you'll end up
putting us all in
really serious danger!
Got it...
There's nothing
wrong with my
hearing...
I believe we
should go with
your strategy.
But I must
speak with you.
Hey, why's Gaara
acting so secretive
all of a sudden?
The team Captains
probably just want
to go over the
details, that's all.
[harrumph]
(Naruto)
Captain!? That Gaara's
so full of himself.
Someone has been
tracking you?
Yes. Hopefully they
won't interfere
with the mission.
But I thought
it was important
to let you know
what's going on.
Do you have
any ideas who's
behind it?
The elders in
my village fear
and despise me.
I'm afraid that
I may cause you
troubles.
(Kakashi)
It's fine. We
can handle it.
Heh, this mission
of ours...
It will only have real
meaning if the Leaf and
Sand Villages complete
it together.
(Kakashi)
The more problems we face
doing so, the stronger
our bond will become.
Alright! Naruto!
Sakura! Sasuke!
Let's go!
Right!
And try not
to be late
this time,
Gaara!
Come on. We're
heading out.
(Mask A)
I still can't believe
he volunteered for
the regular forces...
(Mask B)
It certainly makes
our mission easier.
(Mask C)
The elders will be very
pleased with us if we can
settle this matter swiftly.
(Mask C)
And our reputation
will benefit as well.
Hmf. Gaara of
the Sand...
Your head will
soon be ours.
Of course I'd heard
all of the rumors
that Lord Gaara was
very different now...
But still...
(Korobi)
He's the Ultimate
Defense of the Sand!
(Korobi)
It's undeniable that
countless shinobi have
become victims of his wrath.
[shivers]
I sure hope
nothing goes
wrong...
[gasps]
Ahhh!
Enemies!
Is it the
bandits!?
(Gaara)
No...
Their target...
is me.
They're full of
Jonin who think
pretty poorly of
you.
The villagers
fear you...
I decided to
move on.
I can't be held
back by it, not
now!
What's the matter,
Kakashi Sensei?
How long are you
going to follow
us?
Show yourself!
Huh? What?
(Mask D)
[chuckle] No wonder
they call you Kakashi
of the Sharringan Eye,,,
(Mask D)
I thought I'd
hid my presence
well...
(Mask D)
Please, just
continue on
your way...
We have no intention
of interfering with
the mission of an
allied nation.
Allied Nation?
You're from
the Sand Village?
Perhaps it's easiest
if you simply think of
us as... auditors.
Auditors? What
does that mean!?
They're like
inspectors.
They're probably
here to report back
on how this mission
goes.
And why do they
need masks to do
that!?
I don't know,
I don't trust
these guys one
bit.
Actually...
Huh?
(Kakashi)
They don't
trust Gaara.
(Kakashi)
Isn't that
what's really
going on?
Huh?
The people of the
Sand Village know very
well that Gaara's power
poses a serious threat.
...most of all
to them.
You've seen Lord
Gaara's Jutsu in
action yourself.
Don't you agree that
it's an abomination?
That it shouldn't
exist?
(Thinking)
They've decided to
eliminate Gaara.
(Thinking)
So, an Anbu squad
has been dispatched
to kill him?
(Mask D)
It's a good proposition
for the people of
the Leaf, as well.
(Mask D)
After all, it'll mean a
nearby nations won't
have a powerful weapon.
How cruel! He's
one of your own
ninja!
(Mask D)
Don't you understand?!
Lord Gaara is a danger
to both our villages!
(Mask D)
We cannot allow
him to continue
to exist!
Grr...
I'm a threat to
the village I was
meant to save.
To them, I was a
relic of the past
that they wished
would disappear.
Back then, that's
what I thought about
myself as well.
Or... I couldn't
help but believe
it was true!
And that, of
everything I
faced, was the
hardest to bear.
The thought that my
existence simply didn't
matter one little bit
to the rest of the world
What then was left
for me in this
existence? Why go
on living?
Lord Gaara simply
cannot be allowed
to---
Hunt them down!
Don't let them
excape!
(Kakashi)
Surley there are some
in the Sand who are
sympathetic towards Gaara.
[gasp]
I understand that you
are unable to accept
Gaara as one of you...
And I can see
your point about
his power.
But just because I
understand, don't
assume I feel the
same way.
They fell for it!
Huh??
What's happening!?
What are those
puppets doing!?
Lord Gaara! No!
[gasp]
[shouts]
[grunts]
Ahhh!
We're both
gonna die!
That's right! He's
a killing machine
who thinks nothing
of taking human lives!
(Mask D)
He's a monster
who enjoys
killing!
No..! Lord
Gaara!
[groans]
[screams]
[heavy breathing]
I never imagined
he'd fall for our
trap so easily!
(Mask A)
Now our mission
is almost done!
Puppet Water Style!
Mystic Rain Dance
Jutsu!
[panting]
Are we
safe here?
Wait... This
is wrong...
Huh?
Back there...
Did you hear
what he said?
Lord Gaara... He
told us to get away
I'm sure of it!
(Naruto)
Are you guys
alright!?
Huh?
Where's Gaara!?
Huh? Are you
serious!? You
just abandoned
your friend!?
But, are we?
Are you and I
really friends
with Lord Gaara?
(Mask A)
This water is
infused with
our chakra...
(Mask A)
It's wetting down
your sand, making
it less cohesive.
Your jutsu is
sealed.
Die!!!
What!?
Gaara! We've
come to rescue
you!
[gasp]
Naruto
Uzumaki...
(Mask A)
They're only shadow
Clones, Don't be
afraid of them!
(Mask A)
Only one
is real...
(Yaoki)
You're not alone!
I'm not gonna
run! Not anymore!
Lord Gaara is
our friend and we
won't leave him!
Lord Gaara!
We're sorry we
ran off without
you before!
But we're here
now! And we'll
fight by your side!
Nice job, guys!
You annoying
gnats!
[gasp]
The elders
underestimated
my power...
It will take more
than just a little
water to kill me.
[grunt]
Ahh!
(Gaara)
These few grains are
more than enough for
the likes of you!
Good one! You
big show off!
(Kakashi)
What an unfortunate
situation.
(Kakashi)
But at least these
conspirators were
flushed out and subdued.
(Gaara)
As I thought, I've
caused you trouble.
Forgive me.
They're the ones
who caused the
trouble! Not you!
(Gaara)
Don't...
Huh?
I know perfectly
well what these
men can be like.
But still...
Let them be.
They're my people
even if they
cannot accept me.
I understand.
Well, alright then!
Shall we get back to
our original mission now?
(Gaara)
That's where it
all started for me...
(Gaara)
With that small
bond... that hand
extended in trust.
(Gaara)
I wanted to be
something precious
to others, too.
(Gaara)
NOt just to be
viewed as some
hideous weapon.
(Gaara)
But as the Sand's
next Kazekage.
Your people
do need you.
You forged a bond
with all of them,
and were accepted
by them...
You are the
Kazekage of the
Hidden Sand!
He's the reason
my eyes opened.
He's known the same
pain as I have-
and he taught me
that I can change
the path that my
life will follow.
(Gaara)
The Leaf Village
has him...
(Gaara)
One who cherishes the
bonds of friendship
more than anyone I know.
(Gaara)
Naruto Uzumaki...
Knowing him... and
the friends that he
holds so dear...
(Gaara)
They'll overcome
this disaster.
(Gaara)
And grow even stronger
as a result of getting
through it together.
(Gaara)
Tell me again...
Huh??
(Gaara)
Tell me what you
said back there.
Just one more time.
We're sorry we ran
off without you.
(Gaara)
Not that...
Huh?
The other thing.
Before that.
Huh? Oh! Heh.
Yeah! Of course!
We're your
friends!
(Tsunade)
Are you
kidding me?!
(Tsunade)
After all this time your
people still haven't
captured Naruto!?
(Shizune)
I'm sorry, Lady Tsunade! He's
proving more troublesome
than we'd expected!
(Shizune)
Naruto is just more
than the medical teams
alone can handle!
(Tsunade)
Given the danger he posesses
we must stop him by whatever
neans necessary!
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Naruto
Outbreak"
(Tsunade)
This time you won't
get away, Naruto!