Red Vapor. The blood
vapor... that's peculiar to
all eight gates being open.
Heh! But now, actually
seeing it with my own
eyes... it's almost the
color of dead autumn leaves
that've fallen off their
tree...
I'll admit, you're not
wrong. But they're not
falling without reason
or purpose!
Hm?
They'll become the
nourishment for fresh green
leaves!
And thus the period they
bridge, until the new spring
when fresh leaves bud
once again...
...is the climax of youth!
When it burns most crimson!
"The Eight Inner Gates
Formation"
Now, First Step!
Go for it, Guy Sensei!
I am already... I am.
[yelling]
[struggling]
Guy, is- is that your-?!
Sensei's Sekizo, The
Evening Elephant!
Second Step!
Ah!
He stopped partway?!
Sekizo should be a
continuous attack that can
be shifted up in speed from
one to five times.
I see... What unbelievable
pain!
But I've acclimated. Next
time I can keep going without
giving him an opening.
Great stress is placed on
the body even through the
Fifth Gate of Closing...
I bet the Gate of Death's
level of pain is something
that exceeds my imagination!
A Taijutsu move that
bombards one with blows of
punched air...
A kind of air cannon...
Getting hit by four or five
of those would be bad.
And... I should definitely
avoid getting hit by the
fists that are creating them.
Did he succeed?!
[gasping]
One rarely gets to fight the
Eight Inner Gates Formation!
All right I'm game!
I'll play with you.
[grunting]
Madara still can't be taken
down, huh...?
But what exactly
has Might Guy done?
The Eight Inner Gates
Formation.
It lets someone draw out
their maximum power by
releasing all the limiters
that are placed on it.
This is the final stage of
the jutsu Lee used against
you in the Chunin Exams
so long ago.
Releasing all eight limiters
results in power tens of
times greater than that of
the Five Kage.
But it's only temporary.
And afterward...
... the user will
inevitably... die.
He's making his way
towards me by kicking air!
...he is my student. And also
because he is precious to me.
Rock Lee, are you...?
No, I am not sad!
Showing compassion or sorrow
to someone who has resolved
himself... would be an affront!
[yelling]
We have to go lend
assistance to Guy,
so listen up!
Sensei, those black weapons
of Madara's are troublesome.
They don't activate from
nothing. They're an always
on standby type that undergo...
Change in Form...
And also... their impact
points...
...disappear. But there's
clear sensation if they make
contact with you. He can
only send them about seventy
meters out before losing
control.
Since they physically exist
and can be traced and
followed, your
Kamui should be able to work
on them, Kakashi.
By sending them away, we
can prevent Madara from
controlling them.
To be frank,... I'm
starting to lose sight
in my left eye.
I'm going to have to get pretty
close to them to target them
accurately.
Gaara, can you ready some
sand?
In order to transport
Kakashi, is that what
you're thinking?
But it won't be fast enough
to avoid Madara's attacks.
Don't you worry.
That's my job.
Kakashi will carry one of my
kunai.
Eight Inner Gates: The Sixth
Gate of Joy!
Open!
[gasping]
You've mastered the Eight
Inner Gates, too?!
I can only open up to the
Sixth Gate.
I have never cursed my own
lack of power as much as I
do now!
No. It seems to me that
it's plenty, Lee.
Huh?
You're still a fresh
new leaf... that Guy wants
to risk his life to protect!
Lee, I want you to stay here
to support and guard Gaara.
And one other thing... Take
one of my kunai.
First Step!
[gasping]
He's fast!
Second Step!
Third Step! Fourth Step!
[grunting]
I can't move!
Fifth Step!
Just keep forging on, Guy!
Go!
Here he comes!
[yelling]
Great timing, Lee!
Kamui!
[coughing]
[heavy breathing]
Huh?!
You're the first since
Hashirama to make me this
excited!
You can still dance, can't
you? Do you have any other
moves?
Come on, give me
some more fun!
He got up... from a Sekizo
barrage?!
[gasping]
Where am I? Does this
mean...?
...I'm dead?
What makes thee think thou
art dead?
[gasping]
Thine ethical viewpoint on
death differs much from that
which prevailed in my time.
To so easily replace oneself
with the term 'death', thou
must gain mettle, oh fledgling.
Who are you?
'Tis quite precise
question for this place
but...
I am quite uneasy over
whether thou shalt be able
to connect my name with my
actions as a herald...
Uh--
I am he who shall achieve
peace and order...
And my name is Hagoromo.
But on the other hand...
I had already foreseen that
thou wouldst end up in such
a state as that one, after all.
Uh... I don't really
understand what he's
saying... He seems to be one
of those annoying geezers!
Hey... Sorry,
gramps, but I--
Now then...
No way! Those eyes!
Rinnegan!
Thou dost appear to possess
observant eyes.
All that remains is for thee
to pragmatically comprehend
thy circumstances...
Firstly, thou hast not died
as of yet... This place is
thine own inner mind.
I understand thine haste--
This geezer's not an
enemy... But...
Look, a lot simpler, please!
Can't you just speak using
easy, normal words?!
Forgive me. I'm an
anachronism.
Over the passage of much
time, cultural traditions
and notions, ethics, have
managed to bring about some
rather significant changes.
In each instance where I
cross time and meet a
reincarnate, I have come to
sense greatly the
differences between myself
and the other....
I was also able to
formalistically regulate and
learn new mores and words,
however-
Shut up, already!
I don't have the time to
be sitting around and
listening to some weird
geezer prattle on, you
know?!
Not just searching for
words... But there also
remains some ambiguity in
scholarship.
If communication of wills
can't be achieved in
addition to difficulty of
definition...
I can see that I shall have
to speak simply...
...taking into account
current idealistic and
materialistic thinking.
Listen, are you an alien or
something? I mean, you do
seem super dignified but...
That's a bit much dontcha
think? An alien? Seriously?
[chuckling]
Huh...?!
Well, maybe that ain't too
far off. Anyway...
Hmm?
You still don't understand?
That conversation would pose
such a complex challenge...
No! No, no! That was fine
just now!
No, I finally get you! I was
just shocked 'cause your
speaking style changed so
much, ya know?
Oh, yeah, for real? Then
I'll keep going like this.
I'm much pleased!
Uh, yeah...
[groaning]
Oh... uh... but those words
don't really match up with
your face at all, so it's
kinda super-scary...
And he loses all dignity
too...
I guess... dial it back a
touch and be a bit formal...
Or else you sound kinda
lame.
Now you're going too far,
no? What do you mean by
lame?!
Although, considering how I
was talking, I guess I
can't blame you...
So... does this sound all
right, then?
That's it! All right!
That's just perfect!
Indeed. I'm getting the
hang of it, too.
Oh, man, finally, I can talk
with you!
So, anyway, who are you? And
if you know a lot about this
place, I want to know how to
get out of here, all right,
gramps? I'm in a hurry!
Don't ask everything all
at once!
I'm someone from the past,
someone who is already dead.
A monk wandering the world
as chakra, crossing
generations, ascertaining
the course of Ninshu, the
Ninja Creed.
My name's Hagoromo. I'm the
founder of Ninshu, the Ninja
Creed, known as the Sage of
Six Paths.
The Sage of Six Paths?!
You mean that you're the
sage that Nagato and Pervy
Sage told me about?! Really?!
Oh, so you know of me?
Yeah, of course I do!
You're the one who first
created Ninjutsu right?
No, not ninjutsu, but
ninshu... the Ninja Creed
that I had meant to be
something that gave birth to
hope.
Do not confuse it with
ninjutsu, which just breeds
conflict.
Oh, well, in any case, if
you're the Sage, I've
got tons of things that
I wanna ask you.
But first, right now...
Huh?
You are my son,
Ashura's.
In any event, right now a
lot of conditions have lined
up...
There are things that I must
entrust you with.
What is all this? Ashura?
Entrust me?
Look, no offense, but quit
spouting nonsense and let me
get out of here, all right?!
I apologize, but
unfortunately that's not
something that I can affect.
That all depends on the
actions of those outside.
For now, I can only
relay things to you.
We're back to this? You're
starting to lose me again
here, Gramps.
It means that right now...
trying to rush won't make
any difference.
So, I'd like you to listen
to me. No! You must hear
this.
First, I'll tell you about
my mother and my sons.
My mother, Kaguya Otsutsuki,
came to this land of yours
from a faraway place in
order to claim the fruit of
the Divine Tree.
The chakra fruit of that
same Divine Tree that you
have seen in this very war.
Kaguya consumed the fruit,
gained power, and subdued
this land.
So where did Kaguya come
from, anyway? And is she
stronger than you?
Well, I guess that all moms
are pretty scary when
they're mad, huh?!
It matters not from where
she came. Yes, Mother was
powerful. More powerful
than any other.
Some called my mother the
Rabbit Goddess and others a
demon. They both worshipped
and feared her.
Later, Kaguya would give
birth to two sons. I was one
of them.
We brothers, to atone for
the crimes mother left
behind, battled Ten Tails,
an incarnation of the Divine
Tree, and sealed it inside
me.
The Divine Tree, robbed of
its Chakra Fruit, went on a
rampage in an attempt to
recover it.
And then... much, much
later, I had two sons of my
own.
I named the elder Indra and
the younger Ashura,... and I
taught them the Ninja Creed.
But there was a huge
difference between the two
of them.
One possessed the genes that
contained my powerful
chakra, and the other
one did not.
This manifested in the most
extreme manner.
Uh, it's starting to get
hard to follow you again,
you know?
What does all
this stuff mean?
In short...
There was the exceptional
older brother Indra and the
dunce younger brother Ashura.
So he was a dunce, huh? Even
though his dad's the Sage
of Six Paths?
Perhaps there's no need to
say this to you, but...
No matter how exceptional
both parents may be,
there's no guarantee one
will inherit outright either
of their abilities. Sound
familiar?
Just as it seems to have
been in your case, Naruto.
[sighing] For some reason, I
understand that completely.
And you are truly quite
similar to Ashura. In your
actions, as well.
Huh? What do you mean, my
actions?
Indra and Ashura walked very
different paths in life.
Elder brother Indra
possessed strong Visual
Prowess and senses from
birth... and was called a
genius.
He always did everything by
himself, leaning only on his
own strength, and came to
understand that his powers
were different and special.
He perceived that power
could achieve everything.
On the other hand, nothing
ever went well for little
brother Ashura from the time
he was small, and he
couldn't do anything on
his own.
In order to attain the same
power as his older brother,
he always needed the
cooperation of others in
addition to his own effort.
While struggling through
training, the power of
bodily chakra awakened
within him, and he attained
power rivaling his
brother's.
He understood that he
became strong thanks to
the cooperation and help of
those around him.
He learned of the love for
others that arises from
thinking about them...
...and perceived that it was
love that can achieve
everything.
I believe that I caught
a glimpse of new possibilities
within younger brother
Ashura's way of living.
I partitioned the power of
the Ten Tails that was
inside of me, named each
of the pieces...
...and believed that the
bond known as cooperation
was true power.
Hm.
And I then named the younger
brother Ashura as the leader
and as the guardian of the
Ninja Creed...
...believing that his older
brother Indra would cooperate
with his younger brother.
However...
Huh?
Indra did not accept my
decision. And thus, from
that day on...
... interminable conflict
raged.
Even after their flesh
perished, the chakra that
the two honed continued to
reincarnate across time,
without vanishing...over and
over.
That's creepy. It kinda
sounds like being haunted
by a ghost.
So, is it still possessing
someone even now?
It possesses you,
Naruto.
Huh?!
Younger brother Ashura
has reincarnated as you.
If all chakra were to be
reunited into one again,
a new Chakra Fruit would
take shape.
That must be prevented at
all costs or this world will
end.
I would like you to stop
Madara.
I feel the possibility
exists there... in your
maverick nature.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Sage of the
Six Paths."
So you still believe
in us. Thank you.