[groaning sounds]
-Then you're really going to
kill everyone in the village?
-Yes.
Everyone, and that way, we
restore the Land of Fire
to its glory.
-But I thought-- I thought
that your cause was the same
as my father's, to remove a
king who is a rival to our own.
Tell me why all these
other innocent people
must die as well.
-None of them is innocent.
As long as there remains
even a single Leaf Villagr
loyal to their king,
the Land of Fire
will never be united as one.
Don't you see?
Your father was
struck down by Asuma,
because Asuma was
loyal to the Hokage.
The king is not the problem.
The problem is those
who believe in the king.
As long as they're
around, a king
can be replaced over and over.
That's the one thing your
father failed to understand.
-The one thing?
-It's not the king that
must die, it's the pawn.
The king will
cease to exist only
when everyone in the
village ceases to exist.
And then the land of Fire
will at last be unified.
The limelight jutsu.
When the four sources of
lightning come together,
everything begins anew.
That is the time when all our
aspirations will be fulfilled.
Fuka, Fuen, Fudo, defend them.
Guard the steps of those we
have brought back to life.
Kitane, Nauma, To
and Sato, as soon
as everything is in
readiness for the limelight,
we'll abandon this village.
That goes for you too, Sora.
[theme music]
[groaning sounds]
-That huge mound of
earth seems to be
the source of these things.
-Yes, you're right.
My guess is they've summoned
the earth from all the villages
they've attacked along with
the villagers buried in it.
-And once they bring
the villagers back
to life with their
reanimation jutsu,
they've got themselves
an instant army.
-They're getting on my nerves.
-How many did they kill anyway?
-Expansion jutsu arm.
This could go on forever.
-They just keep
coming and coming.
-At this rate, the village
will be buried under them.
-The enemy's army of reanimated
shinobi continues to grow.
The reinforcements have
arrived, but even so, it's
all we can do to keep them
from over running the market
district.
-I see.
-Request permission to join
the forces on the front line.
I'll never come up
with a defense plan
by staying here and trying
to work it out in my head.
It's not my style.
You know what I mean?
-Very well.
-Don't worry, I'll
come up with something.
-I'm counting on it.
-Right.
-You look so cute hanging there.
What a brave boy you are.
I might even spare you, if you
let me have that body of yours.
-I'm not going to
give you anything
but a beating if you don't
get lost, you old hag.
-What a shame.
You little brat.
Furido was very emphatic that I
was supposed to keep you alive.
Oh well, everybody
makes mistakes.
Lightning style
electric needle spark.
-Shadow clone jutsu!
-Just as stubborn as I expected.
-Listen lady, I can't afford to
be wasting time here with you.
-Well, all right, shall
we finish it then?
-Now, you die.
-Wood style domed wall.
-Stop hiding, you coward!
Oh, that's right.
I forgot.
You're an earth style user too.
Well, let's find out
who's better at it.
I
-Earth style falling
earth spears.
-Tricky, but what good is
it against a body that's
harder than rock?
-What is this?
Whatever, I gotta
get out of here.
[screaming]
-No!
-Can't you just
forget about this?
-No.
You know I can't.
-I always liked you.
-And I, you.
And yet, here we are.
I never imagined that I
would have to kill you.
All right, lightning
style lightning bind.
This way, at least
I can let you live.
Now, I must go.
I've waste too much
time on you already.
-Kitane!
No way--
ASUMA (VOICEOVER): Kitane!
-Soon they will all be
in a proper alignment,
and then you will witness
the activation of limelight.
-No.
-Hm?
-No, Furido.
I won't let you kill them.
I won't let you.
No, Furido, I won't
let you kill them.
I won't let you.
I hate Asuma, but this--
this is different.
-Just the same, just
like your father.
-To him-- you--
-Sora, how very
pathetic you are.
This is what
happens when someone
who's been shunned all his life
is shown a little kindness.
-I don't know what
you're talking about.
-It was the same
with your father.
It's that weakness that
needs to be crushed.
-Ahh!
-It's what ruined
the Land of Fire.
That soul killing
weakness is what
has allowed this
village to survive.
Don't you see?
Do you want to die
just like your father?
-Sakura?
Hey, Sakura.
-Naruto?
-You OK?
Don't worry,
everything's all right.
-What happened to-- the walls
were covered with moths.
They attacked me.
-Poor, Sakura, it sounds like
you had a real nightmare.
But don't worry, everything's
gonna be find now.
I know just the thing to
put your mind at ease!
-No!
-Sakura, why are
you running away?
-Yeah, come on, Sakura.
It's me.
-I don't get it, what
are you so scared of?
-Don't you recognize me?
-There's no need to run away.
-Stop it.
Stop it.
Stop it, Naruto, leave me alone.
INO (VOICEOVER): We've got more
wounded than we can handle.
This isn't working.
We've got to find
a better solution.
-So what's the situation, Ino?
-Shikamaru.
--[laughing] She passed out
from the illusion caused
by my poisoned moths.
I wonder what sort of
dreams she's been having.
I can't imagine.
Little girls have the
most vivid nightmares.
Release!
Goodbye, little girl.
A substitution.
-See you later, you sick jerk.
-Ahh!
-But how-- how did
you escape my jutsu?
-The second I heard
your voice I knew.
I had a pretty good idea
of what kind of trick
you'd try and pull.
Like in the labyrinth, remember?
That giant poisonous spider.
Only now it was poisonous moths.
I simulated another attack
like that and prepared myself.
-You gave yourself an antidote?
-You're evasive.
You never face your
enemy head on in battle.
Once I knew that, I knew
just how to deal with you.
[bark]
-What the--
-The defense barrier.
-Yeah, it's breaking up.
-That means that
one of our units
must have defeated whoever
was casting the jutsu.
-Terrific, but that doesn't
change our situation
as long as these things
keep coming at us.
-Since that other unit, whoever
they are, did their job,
the least we can do is
take care of our end.
-That's the spirit, Choji.
-Huh?
Shikamaru.
-This is a diversion.
They're real objective
is elsewhere.
That's why we've got to wrap
things up here as quickly as we
can, then go link up
with the other units.
-Yeah, yeah, we know
that, so why don't you
quit standing there yapping
and come up with a strategy
already.
-You an be a real
drag, you know?
Choji, you must still have
some chakra left, right?
-Sure, plenty.
I'm ready to go any time.
-And how about the rest of you?
-My power of youth
reservoir is full.
-And I won't be outdone
by a bunch of children.
-I was just hoping for a
chance to really go wild.
[bark]
-Yeah, we're good to go too.
-Yeah, sure.
-All right, then, let's do it.
-Now, now, it's too
early for beddy bye, boy.
Earth style mud silhouette.
Water style mouth
of the serpent.
The earth gains momentum from
the water creating a mud slide.
-Are you going to
stand and fight,
or are you just going to
keep running around forever?
-Oh, I was doing more
than just running around.
-What?
-I was waiting, waiting
for the conditions
to be perfect before
launching my counterattack.
Water style tearing torrent.
-Water style?
I guess I should have been
on the alert for water style
from a wood style user.
But I hope you weren't counting
on me to be beaten so easily.
-You prepared the ground
very nicely for me.
This type of sandy
soil, when broken down,
absorbs water easily
and liquefies.
-Damn you.
You were planning this
from the very beginning.
-This way, I don't
have to take part
in a battle of earth styles.
Wood style tree
bind eternal burial.
-What?
What is this?
-Now, your earth
style will become
part of the Leaf Village's soil.
-No!
-Go, Choji, now!
-Expansion jutsu.
Feel my power!
-Next up?
-Here I go!
Leafs of youth hurricane.
-Kiba.
-Man beast clone.
-Wha-- What the hell's going on?
[theme music]
MALE SPEAKER: As storm
clouds blot out the stars
and thunder splits
the air, the Leaf
totters on the edge
of destruction.
Comrades scramble to avert
the impending catastrophe.
Meanwhile, amidst the chaos,
yet another crisis lurks.
The secret of Sora's origin
will at last be revealed,
and Sora can only
listen in horror
as Furido unveils the full
reach of his terrible plan.
Next time, "Moment
of awakening."