[music playing]
[explosions]
[gasping]
-Hurts, doesn't it?
[music playing]
-Judgement has been passed.
-Wha? What hell's going on?
-So what do you think?
Helps you understand
the suffering
of others a bit
more, doesn't it?
ASUMA (VOICEOVER): My
arm got burned, too.
Was it his jutsu?
Or something else?
-I have already cursed you.
And the rituals shall now begin.
[music playing]
-Well then.
Let's experience the ultimate
pain together, shall we?
[theme music]
[music playing]
-And the ritual shall now begin.
Well then, let's experience
the ultimate pain together,
shall we?
-I don't understand.
What happened to Captain Asuma?
That fire jutsu engulfed
the Akatsuki, not him.
-There's no question about it.
Although somehow
it looks like Asuma
must have caught a piece
of the jutso as well.
-Oh no.
Don't tell me.
-This one will net us
another 35 million.
[laughter]
-All the preparations
have been completed.
Now you and I will share
in the ultimate pain!
[music playing]
Hurts, huh?
And I didn't even
hit a vital spot.
But that kind of
pain is the best.
Hit the other person's agony at
the final moment of death seeps
into my body.
The pain is transcended and
becomes the purest ecstasy.
[music playing]
-Asuma.
He's holding on to his left leg.
Something weird's happening.
-His injury, it's the
same as the Akatsuki's.
-How the hell?
[music playing]
-I have already cursed you.
-That's it!
ASUMA (VOICEOVER): I see.
Somehow this guy has
linked his body to mine.
So that any injury he
suffers, I do as well.
Only he is immortal.
[laughter]
-Now then.
Where do you want
to feel pain next?
Up here, maybe?
Or further down?
How about your legs?
That'd be fun, huh?
What do you think?
Or should we just
end it already?
Well?
-Shikamaru!
No physical attacks,
like shadow stitching.
Use shadow strangle jutsu
to hold him, and hurry!
-Already on it!
Come on.
-Please!
[music playing]
-Now die!
-I don't think so!
[music playing]
[droplet]
-Good job, Shikamru.
-You think you can stop me?
[music playing]
-Izumo, how long's it been since
we called in for that backup?
-10 minutes or so.
At least another 20
before they get here.
-Damn it all.
We're stuck.
What the hell do we do?
If we kill him, we kill Asuma.
-To nullify a
continuous jutsu, you
have to take out the caster.
But that option's
off the table here.
-Every jutsu has
its limitations.
There's always a loophole.
We just have to calm
down and analyze him.
ASUMA (VOICEOVER):
Shikumaru saved me.
Now I've got to think of
a way to break this jutsu.
[music playing]
[groaning]
ASUMA (VOICEOVER): Shadow
strangle doesn't last too long.
I only have a little
time to think.
-If this is going to
drag on, I can help.
Can't let a cash cow get away.
-I told you to stay
out of it, didn't I?
Now butt out!
I don't need your help.
I can handle it.
-Truth be told here,
we're lucky the other one
hasn't entered the mix yet.
-Even so, what do we do?
-Only a matter of
time now, I guess.
Hm?
So he's the one.
-Think back.
This is exactly the kind
of impossible situation
you've been preparing for.
[nature sounds]
The Akatsuki had 10 members.
But Orochimaru withdrew.
Sasuri of the Red Sand is dead.
And we only know the
identities of three others.
Kisame Hoshigaki took
on Gai Sensei with ease.
So he uses water style, huh?
Then there's Sasuke's
brother, Itachi.
With his Sharingan.
Yeah, it was his handiwork that
put Kakashi in the hospital
for over a week.
And Datara, the
one Naruto fought.
Able to remotely
detonate clay explosives.
Supposedly blew himself up.
But I have my doubts.
That leaves five Akatsuki
we know nothing about.
All as deadly as the
ones in this file.
They've got to be weilding
some serious ninjutsu.
We may not know who they
are, but there's no question,
they'll have powers
beyond our imagination.
Boy, what a pack a wolves.
Trying to come up with
a strategy in advance
would be impossible.
Heck, our preconceptions
would probably
just get us into trouble.
[music playing]
So what's the solution?
Obviously, you've got
to train, get stronger.
But how do you handle
an unbeatable foe?
Discern what you can and
make a call, I guess.
Their ninjutsu,
taijutsu, and genjutsu
can tell you a lot about them.
Then get a feel for how they
work with their partner,
and their place in the
organization as a whole.
We'll have to make
snap decisions,
based on what we can
glean in the moment.
Ah boy.
Going toe-to-toe
with the Akatsuki.
There's probably no time
to blink, let alone analyze
those guys.
-The Akatsuki, huh?
-Huh?
A- Asuma.
-So, you trying to carve
out a strategy for them?
-I was.
But in the end, I
think it's impossible.
-Don't be so sure.
Once we've dug up a little
information on them,
that brain of yours
will cook up something.
-Assuming we can
get any information.
And I'm not sure it would
help with these guys anyway.
They could squash me like a
bug, if they really wanted to.
-You're probably
right about that.
-They certainly don't do
anything halfway, do they?
-Yeah, but that's only if
you're fighting the Akatsuki
one-on-one, though.
-Huh?
-Your analytical skills
are some of the best
that the Leaf
Village has to offer.
And if there's no time
for deductive reasoning,
your comrades will be there.
Looking out for your
team is crucial,
but if you can't in
turn rely on them,
you aren't fulfilling your
responsibility to the team.
No man's an island, and with
your comrades next to you,
it'll all work in
the end somehow.
-Crossing my fingers
isn't going to cut it.
-Figure something
else out, then.
Before your friends
all get killed.
-Asuma gave you tons of advice.
Now think!
You've got to think!
[music playing]
His words, personality, speech
patterns, his clothes, weapons,
his behavior, the meaning
behind all of his actions.
And how every move he
makes relates to the next.
From it all can be
gleaned insight.
A hypothetical
framework of the jutsu.
Its probability and selection.
-The gods shall punish.
-The gods.
Punish.
-I have already cursed you.
And the ritual shall now begin.
-Curse.
Ritual.
-All the preparations
have been completed.
-Preparations.
[music playing]
-Trust that Shikamaur
has analyzed him already.
-You come up with
something, Shikamaru?
-Think so.
-I can't believe he
was able to do it.
And all while casting a jutsu.
-Shikamaru can think
10 steps ahead.
And imagine over 200
possible moves to make.
He has the instinct for
picking just the right one.
-All right, then.
Here goes, Asuma!
[music playing]
-That shadow jutsu.
It forces the victim to mimic
the caster's actions, huh?
[music playing]
-No way.
He's caught on to my jutsu.
-What are you doing?
-I'm trying to force
the stupid creep out
of that weird diagram
he drew on the ground.
That'll undo the
jutsu, and his curse.
-What do you mean?
-That giant scythe of his.
It's got three blades.
By the shape of it, I'd say it
wasn't meant for mortal blows.
But extending the
wielder's range,
allowing him to
reach his opponents,
and cause some degree
of external injury,
great or small.
In short, if he can inflict even
a single, shallow, abrasion,
his jutsu will lead to the
opponent's certain death.
-That's his curse then, huh?
But how in the world
does it all connect back
to the initial wound inflicted?
-Blood.
In order to link himself
to his intended victim,
he has to take his opponent's
blood into his own body.
-I saw him lick the blade, too.
So the blood.
I see.
If he could wound his opponent,
and get even the slightest
drop of it onto his scythe,
he's then able to curse them.
-So that's it.
-We he licked the blood
his body changed color,
so it was pretty easy
to figure that part out.
But that's not all
there is to it.
There's one more
crucial step that
needs to be completed
to activate the curse.
-There's another one?
-What an impressive brat.
-That guy totally
ignored the fire style
jutsu Asuma threw
at him earlier.
He didn't even
bother to avoid it,
just went straight
for that marking.
Then once inside it, he
said the ritual would begin.
Then barked about the
preparations being done.
So my guess is the
curse jutsu can only
be completed while he's
inside the diagram.
-You little brat!
-It's not my fault.
You run your mouth too much.
-He's brilliant.
-Enough talk, then!
I'm going to tear you apart
now, and then kill you later,
you hear me?
-There won't be a later!
He's out!
-All right.
Let's see if that did the trick.
[fighting noises]
-Yes.
-How dare you?
Still stuck.
-I'm at my limit.
I can't hold it much longer.
-Nicely done, Shikamaru.
[music playing]
-Kakazu!
Help me out here!
You idiot!
Do something, already!
[music playing]
-I told you to be
careful, didn't I?
[music playing]
[theme music]
-All right.
One down, one to go.
-Careful, though.
His partner's power and
speed border on superhuman.
Who knows what he's capable of.
-Shikamaru!
-He's at the end of his rope.
And the Captain's
even worse for wear.
What's the plan, Izumo?
-Well, now that
his friend's down,
we do have him outnumbered.
But maybe we should
start looking
for a chance to retreat.
-Next time, Unfulfilled Scream.