(crowd cheering)
We've stopped the Hidden
Stone's deplorable schemes!
Now our village is one step
closer to victory!
We have only one
person to thank for the
successful completion
of this mission.
The hero of the Hidden
Sand, Pakura of the
Scorch Style!
(crowd cheering)
Sensei!
Yes, Maki? What
do you need?
Please, I want
you to train me!
I just finished a
very demanding
mission.
Sensei, you- even
you get tired?
(surprised gasp)
Oh, honestly,
Maki!
Ahhhhh!
A diversion?
(surprised gasp)
Aww! So close!
No, you did well.
A trick like that
would have caught
anyone else.
Please, just
one more time!
Don't be hasty.
I'm sure you'll
become stronger
in time.
You really think so?
The reason you want to
get stronger is so you
can get revenge, isn't
it?
Yes! For my father!
A Hidden Mist shinobi
killed him.
That's good. Because
those feelings will
make you stronger!
(gasp)
The strong emotions
you possess for your
family, for your friends,
for your home, and your
desire to defend
your village...
Those emotions make
a shinobi strong.
Right!
Now then, it's time to
discuss our negotiations
for a truce with the
Hidden Mist.
They still seem to
hold a deep-seated
grudge against our
village. Even though
we made a proposal
that is ridiculously
in their favor, they
refused to budge or
even consider it!
I say that it's time
for a showdown with
the Hidden Stone! We
shouldn't worry so much
about what might be!
I guess we have no
choice. We'll need to
make use of Pakura again,
for the sake of the village.
Our hero, Pakura of
the Scorch Style has
died. But she never
gave up! She fought
until the very end!
We shall not let her
death be in vain!
She died for the village,
for all of us! So we must
carry on her will and destroy
the Hidden Stone Village!
(crowd cheering)
Pakura Sensei...
Ninja Art!
Needle Senbon!
You're all weaklings!
Captain Monga!
Just hold tight. I
don't want you to do
anything until we get a
handle on the situation.
Captain Monga!
The enemy is now using
guerilla tactics instead
of engaging us in large
squads.
And we're facing the
Seven Ninja Swords
Men of the Mist.
He's mummified!
I wonder if she's out
there, too. Fighting
against us again.
We don't know where
the enemy will appear!
So don't let your
guard down!
Captain! We should
go search for the
enemy!
Our orders are to contain
the battle and wait here
until we receive commands
from the front lines.
But still! There must
be something we can do!
The sealing, medical,
and intel teams are
needed on the
battlefield. Our
mission is to make
sure they stay safe!
We can't put ourselves
in unnecessary danger.
He's right. The only
people who are really
able to stop the
reanimated shinobi
are those in the
Sealing Corps.
That may be true,
Ruka, but you and
the Medical Corps...
Don't you worry! As
long as I'm here, they
won't be able to lay
a finger on you!
I'll risk my life
to protect you.
Captain...
It's all right. If
my Captain's ever in
danger, I'd risk my life
to save him, as well.
I got it, I got it.
Man, he's strong even
without a ninja blade!
Yeah, but there's only
one of him. If we can
just surround him and
attack in waves, that
should create an
opportunity for us
to win this.
It seems like a
tough fight.
I'm sure it is
considering who
they're up against.
Maki, tell me. Why
do you think the enemy
isn't just attacking
us with large force?
I don't know, but we need
to figure out the enemy's
strategy and put together
a way to counter it.
Huh? Ahhhh!
(gasp)
How many enemy's
are there?
I'm not sure! They
just suddenly appeared!
Maki, Ruka! I need
you both to fall back!
You should tell them
to run fast, too.
Because if they don't,
then they'll go boom.
Gari, of the
Explosion Style!
I never expected
to face you, Gari.
Yeah, that's clear.
You don't have anywhere
near enough men to take
me on.
You fools. You've
done exactly what
we wanted!
I see! Their guerrilla
tactics are just to
scatter our forces!
You've been targeting
the support squads in
the rear from the
start, huh?
Well, after all,
that's the quickest
way to end the battle,
isn't it?
And besides, I've
just been brought back
to life! I can't stand
the thought of becoming
immobile again because
of some foolish Sealing
Jutsu!
I never thought that
someone like you would
be satisfied with being
a mere puppet.
Yeah, well, you've never
been dead before, have
you? So there's no way
that you could possibly
understand.
Why, you! Death isn't
something to be taken
lightly!
Earth Style! Earth
and Stone Shoots!
Careful!
Don't get near him!
So sorry, but it
seems that your
advice has fallen
on deaf ears!
Captain Monga, I-
You two stay back!
I can handle
this myself.
How fun! It's a pity
you can't stop me
with only confidence!
You think that'll
protect you from
my Explosion Style?!
You did it,
Captain Monga!
Excellent job!
Yeah...
But we're not done.
Maki, seal him
away immediately.
(painful scream)
Captain!
This jutsu!
Pakura Sensei!
Wait, are you...
...Maki?
I never, I never
expected to see you
again, not this way.
Your face paint
hasn't' changed
a bit.
Hey, Maki, what do
you mean, Sensei?
She was once a great
hero of the Hidden
Sand. And also, she's
the person who trained
me to become a
shinobi.
My, my. Coming back
to life has been
full of surprises.
Why are you fighting
against us, Sensei? Are
you not able to move
of your own free will?
To vent my anger at
being banished to
death and silence!
To vent your anger?
I was made into the
village hero. And yet
after all that praise,
I was sacrificed as a
lowly pawn for
the benefit of
the village.
My anger and
frustration.
The ones who used me
may be long gone, but
the village that killed
me still exists and
is a painful reminder
of what was done to me!
That's right! The
reason that I'm
fighting is to
finally eradicate
the Village Hidden
in the Mist!
The Hidden Mist Village?
But I had always been
told that you died
fighting against shinobi
of the Hidden Stone.
That was just a story
made up by our superiors
so they could use my
death to the advantage
of our village.
That day, I realized the
truth about everything
just before I died...
The Kazekage ordered
me to travel to the
Hidden Mist Village to
act as an ambassador.
It was a top-secret
mission, so I left
in secret.
Lady Pakura of
the Scorch Style!
I've been sent out
here to welcome you.
It's truly an
honor to meet
you.
Because this thick mist
enshrouds us, we thought
someone should come guide
you.
Thank you, very much.
But there's no way I
could get lost going
through a valley like
this one.
Hah, very true!
Well then, please
after you.
Thank you.
(painful grunt)
What are you
doing?
Showing you the same
pain felt by my
comrades...
...when your village
killed them!
Now, don't get the
wrong idea. Don't think
this will even begin to
get rid of our grudge
against you.
But at least your
sacrifice...will
be a small comfort.
The ones from the
Hidden Sand who
betrayed you to us
are probably thinking
that same thing.
I was used as a
bargaining chip with
the Village Hidden
in the Mist...
...sacrificed for
the benefit of
our village.
That can't be...
Horrible...
From what I can see,
one of them appears
to have slipped into
your ranks.
A Shinobi from
the Blood Mist.
But all of that was
in the past! The Fifth
Mizukage has ushered
in a whole new age of
peace and diplomacy
for the Hidden Mist!
Do you really think
that erases the past?!
The Hidden Mist's history
of blood and treachery?!
Please stop this,
Pakura Sensei!
If you want to hate,
then pin your hatred
on our village for
betraying your trust!
If anything, you
should blame the
Hidden Sand
for casting aside
a hero as loyal as
you were!
Honestly, I find
myself conflicted by
your story. But
regardless of that...
I strongly believe that
it's wrong to attack
these people, who have
absolutely nothing to
do with whatever grudge
you might be holding
onto now!
They are involved!
And that's because
you won't let yourself
see the truth, Sensei!
I've learned something
fighting in the Shinobi
Alliance.
Even people who are
extremely prejudiced
against other villages
and the people who are
from them, can still
find a way to work
together and to talk
together, to understand
each other and to
endeavor for the
common good of all.
If that's true...
If that's true, then
who can get rid of this
grudge that festers deep
inside of my heart?!
Are you telling me
that it couldn't be
helped?! That I
should just give up?!
Well, no...
Enough of this chatter!
Besides, I've been
reanimated, I couldn't
go against my orders
to fight the Allied
Shinobi Forces even
if I wanted to!
Listen, the two of
you go on, get out
of here! But I'll
need the transmitter!
No, you just leave
all this to me!
Hidden Cloth Jutsu!
That was a nice move!
But I wonder how far
you can run away!
We can't defeat her
in a straightforward
fight. We have to rejoin
the rest of the team.
I'll try to
contact them.
You saved us, Ruka.
My Water Style is
pretty good, isn't
it?
I'm sorry that I've
been so useless to
you in this battle.
So this is where
you were...
(gasps)
You've shown you can't
fight me, and now it
looks like you can't
run away from me either.
So what'll it be?
Are we going to
continue our game
of hide and seek?
Sensei, please, just
hear me out for a
minute first.
You can't change the
past, but you can make
the choice to help
create the future.
I believe our experiences,
fighting together in the
Allied Shinobi Forces will
change the relationships
between the villages.
And because of that,
we'll have a new shinobi
world that won't make
the same mistakes.
You choose, Pakura
Sensei. When you died,
you were a hero of the
Hidden Sand.
Please remain a
hero! I beg you!
(gasp)
Wow, this sure is
one flashy fight.
Zaji, Omoi!
I'm sorry we took
so long to get here.
But we ran into a
little trouble back
there.
Do it now!
Did we get him?
It seems our enemy
possesses Kekkei
Genkai.
If that fireball hits
you, it's all over.
Don't worry. We'll
cover the two of you!
Good. We're
counting on you.
(attacking grunts)
(attacking growl)
Ruka!
Right!
Gotcha!
Huh?
They multiplied?!
(strained grunts)
No, don't stop
moving!
I see that you've
mastered it, Maki.
But I won't let you
capture me!
Now's our chance!
On my cue, use
maximum waterpower!
Hey! Zaji!
Come on, Maki!
Bring it on!
You're going to have
to get through me!
You certainly are
difficult. Then I'll
take care of you first!
Now, Ruka!
It's my turn!
You're mine!
(painful grunt)
We've got her now!
Explosion Style!
It's Gari!
This is bad...
All these people just
keep popping up out
of nowhere.
You're an absolute
mess, Pakura.
If I had recovered a
little later, it would
have been all over for
you.
Are they really
that good?
You've gotten
strong, Maki.
The best thing about
this body is that you
can start over again
quickly.
Well, let's continue.
It's time to finish
this.
First that pesky
Sealing Jutsu user
goes...
(surprised gasp)
No way! We
won't let you.
That's right! And
we're going to make
sure that you can't
start over ever again.
You have no chance,
but you'll have plenty
of time to regret this
in the afterlife.
Huh?
(surprised gasps)
What do you think
you're doing, Pakura?
If children don't hurt
themselves, they'll
never learn.
So I feel like
giving them a
chance.
I'm going to give them
this opportunity to
change their future!
I don't understand. Are
you actually feeling
some sympathy for your
old comrades?
I don't care how you
choose to take this.
Now run, Maki!
Go! While I'm
still conscious!
I think we should
listen to what
she's saying.
Yeah, it would be
difficult to fight
them both together,
that's for sure.
Come on, Maki!
Let's go!
Maki, we...
Ruka, go.
Hurry up, you two!
(painful grunt)
Pakura of the Scorch
Style...
I always wanted to face
off against you in a
battle at least once.
But it seems I'll
never get that
chance now...
Yes...
My consciousness is
being taken away.
Maki...
Still not able to
contact any of the
other teams?
Can you please be
quiet for just a
minute?! It's hard
enough to hear
as it is!
Hey, where'd Maki
run off to?
Hm? She was here
just a second ago...
Tsunade, when did you
first decide to place all
your bets on Naruto? Was
it when he defeated pain?
No, it was long
before that.
Back in those day, the
only think I could bet
on was money, and if the
money, or the booze, ran
out, I just kept
topping them off.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Things You
Can't Get Back."
In this world, there
are some things you
can't get back...