(Kakashi) All right, with that
being said, our mission is now
over!
You're all dismissed.
Already?! It's only ten in the
morning! Our missions
have been so boring!
When are we gonna get an
S-rank mission? Come on!
Hmph! "S-rank?" Yeah,
right. A loser like you?
What are you talking about?
We're still only genin,
remember?
I want something with more
pizazz, more oomph! So...?
There just aren't any
missions. Anyway, dismissed!
[groan]
You heard him! So, Sasuke, how
about today, the two of us...
I'm going home.
Wait. Just hold on a minute.
I know of one S-rank
mission the three of us could
actually do right now.
Hm?
A mission that's failed again
and again, one that only we can
pull off...
(Naruto) To see what Kakashi
Sensei's face really looks like!
Let's find out our target's
best-kept secret!
Do you even know
what you're saying?
Listen, just forget about
that. It's impossible!
I mean, right, Sasuke?
This would be the perfect
mission for a day like today!
(giggling) I couldn't
agree more.
Sasuke! How could you? You
betrayed me! Cha!
[chuckling]
But what do we do? Every single
time we try this it never goes
well.
[chuckling] Not to worry! I
already have a plan!
What is it?
Photographs!
If we go through every single
photo Kakashi Sensei is in,
there's bound to be at least one
without a mask.
Actually, I never told you this,
but I already checked them out
once before.
And he has a mask on in every
one!
The photo submitted to the
Hokage for the Ninja
Registration Form.
That should be a picture of him
where he isn't wearing a mask.
But of course, it's an extremely
classified, top-secret document.
Getting your hands on it won't
be an easy task.
He overheard us!
Oh, who cares if he overheard us
or not!
Who are you?
I'm Sukea. I'm a photographer.
I travel from east to west
looking for stories.
Not north or south?
Naruto! Stop getting hung up on
insignificant details!
Well, anyway, I was on
the hunt for a scoop,
and I happened to overhear your
fascinating conversation.
He did hear us! Let's get
rid of him! Ready?
Idiot!
Owie...
This guy's right.
That is the regulation. The
Ninja Registration Form photo
must show your face.
It's so obvious, but none of us
even thought about looking there
before now.
So listen, do you think you guys
would let me tag along with you
on this little adventure?
And why would you want to do
that?
It's simple! If I'm able to
capture this Kakashi guy without
a mask on,
it'll be the biggest scoop since
the Leaf was established!
Even if it were to get hushed
up, I'd be sure to make a lot of
money on this.
Oh! Hey! Hey! Hold on! When you
get the money, you gotta treat
us to ramen! Promise?
I'll even throw in some gyoza.
Does that sound good?
Hm! Now this is getting
interesting.
[sighs] I don't know you guys.
Aw yeah! I'm getting excited
about this! [giggles]
This is where they
store secret documents.
This'll be an infiltration
mission. Sukea, you think you'll
be able to keep up?
I don't think it'll
be a problem.
Before I became a photographer,
I was a rank-and-file ninja.
All right! Let's get this
mission started!
[yawn]
You're still not done, Sasuke?!
Shut up! Just hold on!
Can we switch places?
Just for a moment?
Hm?
Wow, it opened!
That's awesome!
So, Sukea, what division
did you belong to before?
Oh, I was in the Intel Unit that
reported to Lord Hokage.
Wait, he means the...
ANBU Black Ops.
[gasps]
Well some things happened,
and now I'm retired.
Given your past, is it wise for
you to be doing this?
(Sasuke) You'll be targeted by
the ANBU.
Don't worry about it, I'll be
just fine. C'mon, let's go!
(Sakura) We have to search all
these?
(Sukea) Let's hurry.
Found it! This is it!
All right, let's open it up!
No way! The moment is finally
here!
(ANBU) Don't move!
[gasps]
We're taking you in. Make a move
and we'll assume you're
resisting.
And we may have to take you
down.
Uh oh! I feel like
I'm gonna sneeze!
Idiot! Hold it in!
Damn it! And we were so close,
too!
Really? An infiltration mission?
I know. I'm really sorry about
that. I tried to stop them, but
they insisted on doing it.
What? You jerk!
So right from the start, you
planned on blaming us if this
failed?!
They just wanted to see what
your face really looked like!
You're a former ANBU
Black Ops, right?
Honestly, it's ridiculous! Who
cares what I look like
underneath this mask, anyway?!
[uncomfortable chuckle]
You've really got
some nerve blaming us!
I thought it was pretty strange
that you wanted to join us.
You're skilled and a former
ANBU, so you could've easily
done this alone.
I can't stand handsome guys who
think they can get away with
awful things.
Sorry, sorry!
How about I make it up to you by
helping you photograph Kakashi's
face?
Take advantage of my
photography skills!
What? You still wanna do this?
Why not? Are you gonna
give up already?
Uh, all right. So what's your
plan?
Let's go for Kakashi himself.
We'll lure him out to a meal,
then photograph him while he
eats.
We already tried doing that a
whole bunch of times, but
nothing we did ever worked.
Every single time, right at the
very moment when we'd have a
chance to see his face,
we'd get interrupted.
Well, with this multi-exposure
camera I built, I bet we can get
at least one photo.
Sensei! I need to talk to you
about something very important,
ya know?!
What is it?
Uhh.
[chuckling] Actually, why don't
we eat some dumplings while we
talk?
Okay, I'm ready to go.
Well all right, don't
mind if I do!
Oh, hey, Naruto! You guys out
taking a little break, too?
[worried gasp]
Don't bother us right now!
We're doing something really
important!
Like what?
[panting]
I was just about to
find that out.
What?! He already ate them?
[giggling] But this time, we got
him on camera! [giggling]
How can this be?
It's impossible!
Are you kidding? Not a single
one?
It feels like some divine
power's at work here.
Yeah. that's a shame. Oh well, I
guess this means,
we'll have to say that the
mission is over and
dismissed, huh?
All right! I guess it's
time for me to be...
(Kiba) Hey, Naruto!
You wanna tell me what's really
going on out here?
Oh, hey! What's up you guys?
[heavy breathing]
Kakashi Sensei! I'm
so glad you're here!
Because, you see, um, it's just
that over there is a...
It's going to be all right. But
first, just calm down and tell
me what's wrong.
I think that a woman might have
drowned, right over there, on
the riverbank!
[gasps] What?!
This is really not good. Her
pulse is very weak.
(Naruto) Yes! Sakura did an
awesome job! Her medicine's even
fooled Kakashi Sensei!
All right, this calls for...
(Naruto) [giggling] He
definitely has to take his mask
off now!
[gasps]
This woman's in danger! We can't
waste any time! We have to get
her to the hospital right away!
Plan A has failed.
(Shikamaru) Understood. Everyone
switch to Plan B.
Sukea, please get into position.
Roger that.
[sniffing] Okay, he's coming our
way now!
Just as Shikamaru predicted,
he's gonna pass by on his way to
the hospital.
Everyone, get in position!
Huh?
Expansion Jutsu!
Human Boulder! Roll! Roll! Roll!
Roll!
What the?
Roll! Roll! Roll! ROLL!
Uh oh.
[crash]
[gasps]
What are you doing? I have to
get this woman to...huh?
Huh?
Hmm.
Go! Hidden Jutsu! Beetle Sphere!
Now!
(Ino) 3...2...1...Go!
Scatter!
Mind Transfer Jutsu!
[groans]
Ribbit, ribbit ribbit ribbit!
Look, you guys. I get that you
want to see what I look like,
but we have a situation here!
She needs to get to the hospital
as soon as...[grunts]
[chuckles] Shadow Possession
Jutsu! Now complete!
[groaning]
All right, Sukea! Do it now!
[grunts] It finally worked,
Naruto.
Guess you get to have those
ramen and gyoza now!
Haha! Hey guys, see that?
The plan actually worked!
Hah! Yeah, finally.
You should all be grateful to
us. The reason is because...
Okay, Kakashi Sensei! I hope
you're ready!
Do it, Shikamaru!
It's time for the unveiling.
Wait you guys, hold on! Why
don't we just talk things over,
okay?
[chuckles]
Hey! Hold on a second! Stop!
Just stop!
[inhales of anticipation]
Let's all calm down.
I mean, having this remain as a
mystery makes it much more
alluring, don't you think?
[scared laugh]
Ramen and gyoza at Ichiraku
sound more alluring to me!
You mean to tell me all of you
were bribed to do this?
That's checkmate!
All right, now stop! I mean,
please you guys, wait!
[gasps]
You're so annoying, Lee!
Please, spar with me, Neji!
What?! Hey, stop! Don't
interfere!
Seriously, come on, already!
Enough is enough!
[Lee screaming]
Hey! Wait for me!
[grunts]
Sorry!
[yelling]
[grunts]
He was a Shadow Clone?
What the hell is going on here?
Was Kakashi Sensei on to us
right from the very start?
Well, it's too bad. But I really
am grateful to all of you.
No way! We all had such an
awesome time! And it's actually
because of you, Sukea!
So thank you!
I'd better get going now.
Call me anytime if something
comes up!
I really hope you get that scoop
that you wanted!
It seems like they had a lot of
fun.
It was quite a coincidence that
Kiba happened to show up at the
dumpling shop.
Huh, who would have thought that
all of them would team up?
I think that something like this
is good for them, at least every
once in a while.
Yeah, but I gotta say, this
really wore me out!
It's tiring to use so many
Clones and Transformations.
It was a really close call with
my mask because everyone had
such good teamwork.
Of course, even if they did get
the mask off, there wouldn't
have been any real harm done.
Because I'm wearing a back-up
mask underneath. [chuckles]
[sighs] I still think food is
the best way.
Yeah, it probably
is our best chance.
But the problem is, how do we
get Kakashi Sensei to eat with
us?
Bad timing! Here they come!
[gasps]
[sighs]
(Guy) Hey!
Uh.
Excuse me, but did you notice
any trouble going on around
here?
Huh? Uh, no, I didn't see
anything at all.
Kakashi...
[grunts]
I heard that he and his team
were causing a commotion around
town.
Anyway, my apologies for
stopping you.
It's okay.
(Guy) Hey!
[grunts]
[gasps]
Uh, can I help you
with something?
Don't I know you
from somewhere?
Uh, no, uh, I don't think
we've ever met before.
Really? Okay then,
well excuse me.
See you later!
I could've sworn I met that guy
somewhere before. Oh well, I
guess it doesn't matter.
[sighs]
[vocal exercises]
Changing your voice like that
really strains the throat.
[clears throat]
It actually turned out to be a
good mission after all.
Plus, I have to say, their
teamwork has gotten much better
than it was,
during the bell-snatching
mission.
Well, I'll only be able to do
this a couple more times.
(Naruto) Can't use a pervy joke
move to distract her anymore.
So I gotta go back to the basics
and corner her!
If she tries to escape through
that weird window again, I'll
enter it with her.
That's where I'll search for
Sasuke!
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Connecting Thoughts."
I can still sense Sasuke's
chakra clearly!