Huh?
What in the world is that?
That's Guy!
Ah!
It's his Afternoon
Tiger attack, Hirudora!
Hirudora?
What a lame name
for a jutsu!
I thought Guy Sensei wanted to
sound like a young shinobi,
not some old dork!
[gasp]
This is no time for
philosophizing!
Hirudora has a wide blast
radius! It's almost here!
Get ready!
Don't you move.
That jutsu of yours.
It wasn't an
Energy Bomb, was it?
And what's the blue
aura you're emitting?
Hirudora's a taijutsu;
it isn't a ninjutsu
that uses chakra.
It's just an ordinary punch.
But it's a super fast punch.
A focused blast of
pressurized air aimed
right at your opponent.
After initial compression,
it spreads quickly outward.
And this aura that's
surrounding me isn't chakra.
Anybody who opens the
Seventh Gate of Shock,
will perspire blue
sweat like this!
You're seeing evaporation,
from my passion and exertion.
Ah! no wonder.
What I at first thought was
an Energy Bomb seemed to
shrink but wasn't nullified.
This is the third time we
have clashed, you know.
I can't believe you still had a
move like this up your sleeve.
Although, you don't seem
to remember me. still.
[wet cough]
I thought I told
you not to move.
"The Man Named Kisame"
Nice one,
Bushier Brow
Sensei!
You sure took
him down!
♪ I guess you really are
capable despite your looks,
Bushier Brows.
♪ But that blue sweat of
yours sure packs some pows. ♪
If this goes well,
I'll be able to get
the Akatsuki's plans.
And, their
leader's
identity.
I'm not as adept as
Inoichi, but I'm going
in for the Intel!
Well, here I go.
I'm in.
Now comes the hard part.
Mister Hoshigaki?
Mm?
Listen, why don't you
come over and eat
with the rest of us?
I'm fine here.
I don't need you
to be sociable.
Hey, didn't I tell you?
Leave him be, that's
how he wants it.
He said he doesn't
get along with us
Cipher Corps eggheads!
But all of us are here on
the same mission together!
Things like that
shouldn't matter!
Besides, we wouldn't
have anything to
talk about with him!
We're the brains.
He's just the brawn.
Huh? What is it?!
We have to leave. Now.
Huh?
Mister Hoshigaki?
Sorry about before.
Maybe we could get
together after the
mission's over.
[chuckle] For dinner.
Listen up, Kisame.
Make sure you protect
the Cipher Corps and the
encoded missive, too.
However, you must not let
any of the Cipher Corps fall
into the hands of the enemy.
Your mission is to defend
our code, no matter what
you have to do.
Do you understand
what that means?
Move! Now!
Just surrender! We've got
you completely surrounded.
You have no chance of winning.
They sent you?
I know who you are.
You're from the Hidden Leaf.
You're with the Anbu's Torture
and Interrogation Corps.
Want to fight?
Now's our chance. Run!
Rrgh!
Capture them alive!
Ungh!
Agh! There are too many
of them to protect.
Keep going!
Augh!
Please, help me...
No! Wait!
What are you doing?
What do we do now,
mister Hoshigaki?!
What? What's wrong,
what's the matter?
What are you
doing, Kisame?!
However, You must not let
any of the Cipher Corps fall
into the hands of the enemy.
Your mission is to defend
our code, no matter
what you have to do.
Do you understand
what that means?
Yes, don't worry.
I will not hand over
any of the Cipher Corps
shinobi alive.
[distraught]
Agh!
But... Why?
Because killing my
comrades is my specialty.
My personal mission.
That's so sad.
You have a terrible life.
Why would you
kill them?
Because.
You should understand why.
We cannot afford to
let our code fall into
the enemy's hands.
These shinobi
talk too easily.
I look forward to
facing you again should
we both survive.
Egh!
[wet stab]
Kisame! Why would--?!
[wet cough]
[Fourth Mizukage]
Good work, Kisame.
I thought he'd let his
guard down around you, his
subordinate. I was right.
He was colluding
with the enemy.
From this moment on,
you are the owner of
the great blade,
Samehada.
And my
subordinate
as well.
Or at least I am until
you eliminate me, too.
Am I right, Lord
Fourth Mizukage?
I'm can trust you because
of who you are, Kisame.
For the sake of our
nation and village,
you've done our dirty work.
And additionally, you've
followed through on
traitorous assignments.
You're well aware this world
is full of lies and deceit.
That's right, I knew all about
it from the very moment that
I first killed a comrade.
I killed a Hidden Mist ninja
despite being one myself.
So, what am I, then?
An enemy or an ally?
What is my purpose,
my status?
Where am I trying to get?
And where can I go to
achieve inner peace?
There is only one thing clear
to me: that I felt I was
trapped in a false existence.
[Madara]
Allow me to free you
from the pain of
those falsehoods.
I will create a place
where you belong.
Who are you?
We'll start with
this nation.
You have toiled to deal
with and dispose of your
comrades up until now.
Join me and
become my
comrade.
You seem to be willing
to put your trust in me.
But I can't reciprocate
since I still have no
idea who you are.
Ngh. That gleaming eye.
In the dark.
Ah, yes,
I see it now.
So the person that I
believed to be the Fourth
Mizukage was actually you
all along, then.
I can't believe that
the Sharingan was
manipulating him.
Heh. I guess this world
really is full of lies.
But you. Visual prowess
great enough to control the
Three Tails' Jinchuriki.
Just who exactly are you?
Tell me!
Madara Uchiha.
[gasp]
Everyone knows
that Madara is dead.
So why should
I believe you?
Reveal yourself to me!
Very well. And then you
must decide whether you
will trust me or not.
I'm going to find out
who Madara really is!
[gasp]
[straining]
Hrrgghhnnnhgghh!
[gasp]
[straining]
Unbelievable! He bit
off his own tongue!
He willed himself awake
in order to prevent me
from extracting Intel!
Huaa ha ha ha ha!
Hueaaaa ha ha ha!
[Kisame] [flashback]
Are you serious?
Yes. That is my goal.
Project Tsuki no Me.
[Madara]
It will be a true world,
free of lies.
I would have liked
to have gone there.
[gasps]
Huaaah!
I was suppressing his
chakra with my Wood Style!
He still has this
much strength?!
He just doesn't know
when to give up.
Please, recapture
him alive!
This could be our last chance!
We need to get his Intel!
I know!
Water Prison Jutsu!
Eagh! I can't reach him
through this wall of water!
He's using the
Water Prison Jutsu!
Summoning Jutsu!
What do we do?
No need to panic.
I mean, look at the
situation he's in.
He can't do anything!
I'll take care of him.
Itachi. It's just
like you said.
[Kisame]
I'll be teaming up with
you starting today.
I'm Kisame Hoshigaki,
formerly of the Hidden Mist,
one of the Seven Ninja
Swordsman.
So pleased to make
your acquaintance.
And you are Itachi Uchiha,
formerly of the Hidden Leaf.
I've heard the rumors.
that you slaughtered
all of your fellow
Uchiha clansmen.
I think that we're
alike, you and I.
That's the reason I
wanted to be teamed with
you in the Akatsuki.
It's really indescribable,
isn't it?
Killing your comrades is
quite a sensation, wouldn't
you say so, Itachi?
You talk a lot.
You don't understand me.
You don't even
understand yourself.
You're just a thug who got lost
in the mist and ended up here.
You can't even control where
you're going. Am I wrong?
Do you want to know
something interesting?
Most sharks are ovoviviparous,
which means that the eggs
hatch inside the female's body
before the young are born.
However, with some kinds
of sharks, the number of
eggs that hatch
will differ from the number
of young that emerge out of
their mother's belly.
Do you know why that is?
Because of cannibalism.
Right from the moment
they hatch, they start
eating each other inside
their mother's uterus.
The fratricidal
warfare begins as
soon as they're born.
To each shark, all the others
are just food to be eaten.
Starting today, you are
an Akatsuki member and my
companion. So be wary.
Of me.
Same goes for you.
He he he he he.
Well, let's be
friends and have
some fun, all right?
And hope that we will
not end up as each
other's final opponents.
No one who dares to raise
their hand against a comrade
ever dies a decent death.
Remember that.
[chuckle]
Hm hm hm hm hm!
Well, that means our
fates are sealed.
Seems you and
I are depraved
and worthless.
Not true.
We are both human, not fish.
No matter who you are, you
do not truly know what kind
of man you've become until
you reach the very end.
[Itachi]
One realizes one's true nature
at the moment of death.
Don't you think that's
what death is about?
[Kisame]
Itachi...
Did you find it at the moment of
your death? Did you discover the
kind of person you truly were?
Well, Itachi, It seems
that in the end, I was
not a worthless human
being, after all.
[gasp]
[Aoba]
He actually fed himself...
to his own sharks.
He was weakened
pretty badly.
I guess he figured that
he wouldn't be able to
escape from us.
An Akatsuki member
strong enough to be
paired with Itachi.
He was long feared as
the scourge of the Mist.
I never imagined he
would go out this way.
Is he dead?
I mean, really?
[sad growling]
Well, this fella sure
seems downhearted.
It looks like it's for real.
He's actually departed.
But, still.
He died instead of
giving up intel on
his comrades.
Even in the Akatsuki, there
remain some who put their
comrades ahead of themselves.
An admirable foe.
A shinobi's life
is measured by the
manner of his death.
Kisame Hoshigaki!
I will remember you
the rest of my life.
[Guy]
In any event, we've averted
our intel from being leaked
to the Akatsuki.
But he recorded
information about
us on that scroll,
and was planning
on smuggling it
out of here.
If that's the case,
we should confirm the
contents of that scroll.
If we find out what they
were interested in, then
we can counter them.
Yes, you're right.
[gasp]
Yahh!
Heavy water!
The Water
Prison Jutsu!
He left a booby trap
for us on that scroll!
Watch out!
Sharks!
[Yamato]
Damn! It's headed
out to sea!
Man, it's hard to move
in all this water!
Try, fool,
ya fool!
I'm still drained
from using the
Eight Inner Gates!
Guy! Hold on!
Gyaahhh! Hey, careful where
you're biting, shark!
[Naruto]
Damn it! It's getting away!
What do we do now?
[Konan]
Just as Yahiko believed
in Nagato, Nagato
believed in Naruto.
Since Naruto is carrying on
their will... I will believe in
him, too.
If you're asking me to give
up on our hopes, then I
have no choice. I will.
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
The Angelic Herald of Death.
I will kill you!