[gasp]
There's someone else
where Sasuke is.
You recognize the chakra?
No! But...
But what, Karin?
This chakra... has a real
nasty feel to it!
Then we're going to need
to hurry even more.
After all, we have
absolutely no idea what this
stranger might be planning
to do to Sasuke.
Is this where his wind
seizes to blow?
[growl]
Wha-?!
Karin! If you don't pace
yourself, you're going
to collapse!
Alright! Let's head out to
join the others at youth
power max!
Lee! Tenten!
S-Sasuke!
Who's that guy?!
Hey you! I don't know who
the hell you are, but what
do you think you're
doing with Sasuke?
Oh, I see, so that's
what's up...
Huh?
Ah, so it was you, Kabuto.
I sensed your group rushing
over here, too.
It's really you, Lord
Orochimaru.
Wait, that's Kabuto?!
His chakra's different!
His apperance too!
Well, he did take into
himself Sage Jutsu Chakra,
as well as all sorts of
other people's chakra.
I can't blame you for not
recognizing him, Karin.
I wonder if his chakra feels
nasty because he still has
some of my own chakra
inside of him?
Or perhaps it-
Step away from Sasuke,
you nerdy creep!
What have you come here to
do, Lord Orochimaru?
And what about you?
What are you planning,
Orochimaru?
Look, Kabuto. You're not
planning on trying to absorb
Sasuke, are you?
And would that make you
Kabuke or Sasuto?
[gasp] So you're the one who
took down Sasuke?!
You're gonna pay!
Suigetsu, I have no desire
to do that anymore. Karin, I
have no interest in trying
to steal Sasuke, either.
Sasuke's chakra! I can just
barely sense it! N- No way!
Kabuto, you're
helping Sasuke?
That's right. With my
Medical ninjutsu and my
Hashirama cells I've
experimented on
extensively, along with a
certain someone's
suggestion, I just managed
to stop him from dying.
And there we have it.
Oh!
Hm? Well, well. If it isn't
the Hokage I respect most,
Lord Second, Tobirama.
However, Kabuto.
Your presence here must
mean that you were somehow
able to escape the endless
loop set up by
Itachi's Izanami,
isn't that right?
That's right. I'd stopped
acknowledging myself and
didn't know who I
was anymore.
That allowed you to give me
easy answers and use me,
making me lose even
more of myself.
If you're not satisfied with
what you've had...
Just find other things and
add them onto yourself from
here on out.
[discomfort yell]
It's still not enough, yet!
This still isn't who I am!
But through that jutsu,
Itachi helped me realize...
That I am none other
than Kabuto.
And where my home is.
Hey, did he change
inside, too?
Such is the power of
the Izanami.
It's a jutsu that cannot be
undone unless you reexamine
yourself and accept
who you really are.
Sasuke...
I now wish, from the very
bottom of my heart, not to
lose my home.
And Itachi, who wanted to
protect Sasuke even unto
death.
His feelings have pierced my
heart quite strongly.
Yeah, well, listen, it's great
for you to say that now!
But you're still one of the
ringleaders who joined up
with that fake Madara guy
and started this whole war!
You're right, of course.
Both Obito and I thought
that we'd lost our place in
this world, and we dragged
everyone else into this.
But, now I know who I am
and what I must do!
You may be reinforcements,
but you're nothing
more than pebbles.
You won't make any
difference, now.
That guy's Madara?!
Yes, that's him.
Kakashi, are you all right?
I am, thanks to Guy.
No, not that part. I'm
talking about my Sage Art
Rasengan hitting you earlier.
That was okay, too.
I teleported it with my Kamui
just as it was making contact.
Kamui!
Good. I'm glad...
Wait, Sage Art?
You mean, Sage Jutsu?
That's right. Only Sage Jutsu
works against him.
Well, that and physical
attacks, such as Taijutsu.
So at this point in time,
our only hope is the Fourth
Hokage's Senjutsu and
your Taijutsu, Guy.
If I recall correctly, Sage
Jutsu isn't your forte, Sensei.
Yes. Honestly, I'm weak
in Sage Jutsu.
It takes me too long to
infuse the chakra, and I'm
not able to maintain
it for too long.
And I haven't used it much
in real combat, either.
Plus, I can't weave signs at
all, right now, so I don't
think I can fight effectively.
So, I guess that now it's
showtime for this wild Blue
Beast, huh?
Eight Inner Gates!
Seventh Gate of Shock!
Open!
Blue vapor?
Guy!
One gate short of the Eighth
Gate of Death, huh?
He insults me, not bringing
out the Red Vapor.
Don't let the black spheres
or rod touch you!
I can't believe Guy's
mastered the Eight Inner Gates!
Those aren't human
movements!
Take this!
Hirudora!
Gotta use the Flying Raijin
to throw myself into the
Black Sphere's path!
Kakashi! My kunai!
Right!
That's Rock Lee!
Guy Sensei! Are
you all right?
Yeah, Thanks to you, Lee.
Where is Tenten?
She told me to go ahead
because she wanted to check
something out.
I finally catch up to you
and, you launch the Hirudora?!
Are you all right, Guy?
Yeah, only my right arm and
a few ribs are hurt.
What are we going to do if
your Taijutsu, our last ray
of hope, is no good?
He's too strong.
Wait, Kakashi...
It's still too early to
count my taijutsu out!
But...
Our youth hasn't faded!
Not yet, at least!
Don't lose hope!
Guy Sensei...
It's true that not
everything we wish for will
come true.
But, things that we ought to
do must always begin with a
wish.
Just like my challenges
to you.
[shocked gasp]
Fight me, Kakashi!
And I assure you that
this is no bluff.
Don't tell me you?!
The Leaf's Wild Blue Beast
is no more. It's time for
the Red Beast to emerge!
No way! Not the final
Gate of Death!
[shocked gasp]
Guy, you mustn't do it!
Please, just think it over!
Not a single person here
wants you to do that!
Not even you father would-
I know. But I want to do it.
Guy Sensei! Guy Sensei,
you think that right now is
actually the time for that?!
Now, don't look at
me like that, Lee.
This time, you sit back
and enjoy the show!
We're a lot alike,
you and I.
I was a "loser" too, once.
But I made myself the equal
of any ninja, even Kakashi.
You say you wanna show the
world you can be a splendid
ninja, even if you don't
have all the gifts that
others are blessed with.
That's your nindo, your
ninja way, right?
Well, I think that's a fine
goal. Fine as I've ever
heard, and one worth
sticking to.
Don't let anything steer you
off the path you've drawn
for yourself. Forge
ahead to the end!
Become strong so I can just
sit back and enjoy the show!
Father...
No, no, no!
No... No... No...
Listen, son, search to your
heart's content!
My name! It's not anywhere
on the Academy
entrance list, Papa!
You just keep on looking,
Guy! You've worked hard and
did everything that you could!
There's no way that all that
effort won't be rewarded!
Those tears are probably
just making your vision
blurry! I bet you see
your name soon!
Right, Papa!
Might Guy... Might Guy...
Might Guy...
That kid just won't give up,
will he?
It's a very unsightly
way to behave...
Kakashi!
Papa, I'm sorry...
I'm sorry!
Don't give up! You hear?!
Don't look away!
You'll find it! You will!
Hey, isn't that the kid who
was making such a big fuss
about failing the test?
For my papa who never gave
up on me, I will get in!
What was all that stuff he
was talking about?
"Self-rule" or something?
[laughter]
Like you just decide
something, and it happens!
I know all about him. He
can't perform ninjutsu or
genjutsu at all.
The only thing that he
really has going for him is
that he's pretty good
at physical stuff.
That may be true, but even
so, he looks ready to drop.
Don't quit! But, still... My
son, you're getting it all
wrong!
Two hundred thirty-five
laps!
[laughter]
What a joke! He's
not even half done!
Papa...
Guy!
Guy, you fool!
I'm sorry, Papa...
I'm five already, but I
can't even complete five
hundred laps yet!
No, stop that! Don't
apologize! That's not why
I'm scolding you!
Huh?
Never apologize for trying
hard! It's an insult to your
determination, Guy!
Then, why did?
Because you're not using
your self-rule in the right way!
Five hundred laps will get
you accepted into the
Academy?! That is
not a self-rule!
That's only a wish! And
nothing more than that!
Listen...
You impose a self-rule in
order to spur yourself onward!
To help you overcome a
challenge or difficult
situation.
But a self-rule applies to
yourself and only yourself.
Uh-huh.
Because of that rule, you're
able to gather your strength
and focus on your efforts...
So, even if you fail, having
applied that rule in the
first place keeps you extremely
disciplined and focused.
And that is the way that a
self-rule truly works!
I'm so sorry, Papa.
However, no one can
find fault with your
determination. Even if you
only make it half way,
hard work is hard work.
And for that, you
deserve a big, ol' hug!
Papa!
Guy!
Looks like that father and
son are at it again...
Isn't that abuse?
And what's up with
those bodysuits?
They're just so weird!
Thank you for your support!
Papa, I don't think
that was support.
Well, encouragement, then!
I guess that since I can't
do ninjutsu or genjutsu...
...I failed the test.
Listen, Guy! Your youth has only
just begun, do you hear me?!
Never turn your back on
youth! Just like me!
The fact that you aren't
able to use either ninjutsu
or genjutsu actually pleases
me, as your Papa!
Huh?!
Knowing your shortcomings
will highlight your strengths!
Your Taijutsu's already
shining brilliantly in my eyes!
I'm really, very happy now!
I've discovered my son's
strengths when he's still at
such a tender age!
Papa, you're not just
saying that-?
Your shortcomings can become
strengths! Being repetitious
is being kind!
To be loud is to be lively!
Obstinacy's earnestness!
Those who are selfish
are like cats!
And hairy people?
Uh...
They're like cats, as well!
Long-torsoed people?
They're...
...also like cats!
Hey! Might Dai! What are you
doing, playing at training
with your kid again?
You work hard for an
"eternal genin!" [laughter]
Sure thing! Thank you for
your support!
[laughter]
[angry growling]
That guy's such a joke!
Still trying to act young at
his age? [chuckle]
Ow!
What's that for?!
Hey, if it isn't Dai's brat!
What do you think
you're doing?!
Don't make fun of my Papa!
Look, kid, I only
spoke the truth!
Say stuff about my papa, and
I'll punch you- five times!
That's my self-rule!
Huh?
Your self-rule? I'd like to
see that, so I'll say this:
Your dad is a
good-for-nothing who can't
do ninjutsu or genjutsu,
and can't even do
taijutsu that well.
Everyone says he's more of a
comedian than he is a genin!
[laughter]
And he's a comedian whose
jokes about youth aren't funny.
[angry growling] That's
two bad things!
Which means ten punches!
Why don't we punch you
twenty times instead!
Damn it... Damn it...
[chuckle]
I can't believe that you
couldn't return a single
punch after what they said
about your father.
Guy, why'd you do
such a thing?!
Papa, how can you stay so
positive and optimistic?
When does one's youth really
come to an end?
As long as you never turn
your back against youth,
then it will never end.
You're saying that youth
doesn't come to an end
when you die?
Oh! C'mon, Guy!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Papa's Youth"
That is when youth reaches
its climax! And when it
burns the brightest of all!