[music playing]
SASUKE: Suigetsu, I will release
you from this place someday.
[music playing]
-It's you.
I knew you'd come.
You being here must mean
that you killed Orochimaru.
-That's right.
But never mind that, for now.
Let's get you out of there.
[crash]
[music playing]
-Ah, free at last.
Thank you, Sasuke.
-Suigetsu, you're the first.
Now, come with me.
-What do you mean, the first?
Who are the others?
-There are two others.
Jugo of the Northern
Hideout, and I'm
also getting Karin of
the Southern Hideout.
-You sure about that?
-What's wrong?
-Ah, nothing, except that I
can barely stand those two.
I just don't think
we'd get along, is all.
But you know, that's
just my $0.02.
[chuckle]
I understand why you'd
picked me, of course,
but choosing those two is making
me wonder about you, Sasuke.
-Do you ever shut up?
Come on, get dressed .
We're leaving.
[laugh]
-Ordering me around like
some kind of big shot, huh.
I think it's time we clarified
our relationship, Sasuke.
-OK.
-You were the one who
chose to rescue me.
You made that
decision on your own.
I never said anything
about following you
if you came back for me.
Just because you
defeated Orochimaru
doesn't make you better than me.
Everybody wanted to kill him.
You were Orochimaru's favorite.
He let you stay by his
side, while the rest of us
were confined.
So, you just had more chances
to kill him than the rest of us.
[music playing]
-Gotcha.
I was just kidding you.
But I did just let
you go when I didn't
have to, which makes us even for
you letting me out of the tank.
I'm free of that prison
at last, and that
means I'm free to go do
whatever I want to do.
-I see, that's too bad.
[music playing]
-Hey I forgot to ask you.
It was your squad, wasn't it?
[splash]
You were the ones
who brought down
my predecessor, Zabuza
Momochi, weren't you?
So tell me, whatever happened
to his sword, the Executioner's
Blade?
What?
Cat got your tongue?
Come on, I'll make you a deal.
You tell me where the blade is,
and once I get my hands on it,
I'll agree to join your team.
[music playing]
-Get dressed.
[theme music]
[seagulls]
-Hm, the Great Naruto Bridge--
wow, what a weird name.
-Say, did Master Zabuza
put up a good fight?
-Look out!
[music playing]
-Now, it's over.
-But I'm not that easy to fool.
[music playing]
-Kakashi, no.
-No.
-But to call upstarts
like you ninja is a joke.
You're just brats.
-What's the matter, Sasuke?
Sasuke--
-Nothing is the matter.
Let's go.
[sigh]
-It's not here.
Sasuke, are you sure
this is the right place?
-I am.
-Well, it's not here.
So, what's the deal?
-I don't know.
Look, I'm not the
groundskeeper, don't ask me.
If it's gone, then someone
must have taken it.
-Well yeah, of course,
that's obvious.
It's not going to
walk off on its own.
Sasuke, sorry, but since
Master Zabuza's blade is gone,
so is any chance of
me joining your team.
-What are you going to do?
-What else can I do?
I'm going to look for the sword.
The blade of the Seven
Ninja Swordsmen of the Mist
was passed down from
generation to generation.
That's the tradition.
I was all set to become
one of those swordsmen.
That's what I was training for.
So, it only makes sense that
if Master Zabuza is gone,
I'm the only one who should
inherit his Executioner's
Blade.
-Why don't you watch where
you're walking, idiot.
[sigh]
-Hm--
-What, you got a problem, buddy?
You want to make
something of it?
[drum]
[gasp]
[speaking gibberish]
-Just watch it.
I tell you, this place
is crawling with idiots.
-Man, you are way
nicer than I am.
So, it looks like you owe
me for not starting trouble.
How are we going to settle up?
[giggles]
-Hm, oh-- man, this
yogurt is so great.
It's been ages since I've
had anything this good.
I was locked in that
tank for way too long.
-Is that why you're
wasting my time now?
-How should I put this?
You're the one in
such a hurry, not me.
Why are you putting a
team together anyway?
Just what are you up to?
-I'll fill you in once the
whole team is assembled.
-Hm-- hey, let's
conquer the world.
You're not going to say
something like that, are you?
-If you want to
conquer the world,
do it with your own team.
I'm after something bigger,
something much bigger.
-Hm, if anyone else said
they wanted something bigger
than the whole world,
I wouldn't believe it.
But I don't know--
when you say it,
I start to think it maybe such
a thing is really possible.
It's weird.
Oh hey, I've got a
question for you.
You know The Great
Naruto Bridge?
You ever heard of a large
sword being found near there,
or where it might be now?
-A sword?
Yeah, I may have heard
something about that once.
Why?
-He's looking for it.
He'd really appreciate the help.
-Really, he would?
Maybe someone else knows.
I'll go ask right away.
[squeal]
[giggles]
-Boy, those girls
really like you.
-OK, so we think we know
who might know, you know?
Tazuna, he lives by the river.
[giggle]
Yeah.
-Tazuna, huh?
-So who's this Tazuna guy?
-The master carpenter who
built the Great Naruto Bridge.
BRIDGE KEEPER: Sorry, the
boss isn't here right now.
-All right then, where is he?
-He and his grandson, Inari,
went to the Land of Lightning
to build a bridge.
No point in waiting
around for him, either.
They won't be back for
a whole other year.
-Uh, the Land of Lightning,
you know how far away that is?
-Maybe you can help us.
Do you know of a
large blade that
was left near The
Great Naruto Bridge?
-Oh, that old thing-- sure,
Tenzen Daikoku took it.
He came here to fight the
ninja who wielded that blade.
But once he found out the
ninja was already dead,
he just took the sword and left.
[sigh]
-This just keeps getting harder.
Now, we've got to find Tenzen.
-Hm, he was an aid to the feudal
lord of the Land of Water.
Apparently, a whole
lot of his men
were killed back when Master
Zabuza staged his coup
in the Hidden Mist Village.
And I guess he's held a
big grudge ever since.
-Hey, why don't you watch
where you;re going, loser.
-How lucky, you're just the
guy we were hoping to find.
[yelling]
-Who the hell are you?
What do you want from me?
-You just seem like someone who
might know all sorts of things.
-Look, I don't know
anything about Tenzen, OK.
-Tell us what you do know,
anything at all is fine .
But don't make me ask you twice.
[gasp]
[whimpers]
-Well--
STREET MAN: OK, OK, I'll talk.
Tenzen is a politician,
but that's not all his is.
He's also the leader of
a large band of thieves.
I hear that he doles out
huge bribes, left and right.
And because of that,
the feudal lords
let him do whatever
evil things he wants.
-See, you know a lot.
So, where does he live?
STREET MAN: His place is to the
south, deep inside the forest.
Rumor has it that several
thousand mercenaries guard it.
It's supposed to
be impenetrable.
[crickets]
[gasp]
-Who are you?
How did you get in here?
SASUKE: The day after
tomorrow, over 10,000 soldiers
will lay siege to this castle.
Make sure you gather
every available man.
and don't forget my name.
It's Suigetsu.
[music playing]
[gasp]
-Intruder!
All men, gather up your arms.
[neigh]
-Ah man, what in the
world is going on now?
-Apparently, a rival clan
plans to attack Tenzen's castle
tomorrow with an
army that numbers
in the tens of thousands.
-No way.
Are you just making that up?
[sigh]
-All right, fine.
The more confused the enemy
is, the better my chances.
Whether it's one opponent
or tens of thousands,
it doesn't really matter
to a ninja like me.
I'll sneak in and steal the
Executioner's Blade right
from under their noses.
-All right, how
about a little wager?
-A wager?
-A competition to see who gets
the Executioner's Blade first.
[laugh]
-Never in a million
years did I expect
you to have a
playful side, Sasuke.
All right, let's do it.
Sounds like my kind of fun.
-Then we start now.
But there is one rule, Suigetsu.
Don't kill anyone.
-Huh?
[neigh]
-Hey, who are you?
No matter, you're mine.
[yells]
[battle yells]
-So now, you mean,
starting right now.
[grumbles]
-I guess you really
meant right now.
Oh man, I'll never live it
down if I lose this bet.
All right, let's do this then.
-Fire style, fireball jutsu!
-Nice one.
I've got to hand
it to you, Sasuke.
Sasuke, where did you go?
[yells]
-Oh, you've got to be kidding.
-All right, let's
get this over with.
[yells]
[music playing]
-Hey, that actually
tired me out a little.
Now, to get what I want.
-That's impossible.
There's no way that
a single man could
defeat all those
soldiers in combat.
-There's a way.
Attacking me with conventional
weapons is pretty much useless.
-C-- c--
[sigh]
If conventional weapons are
useless, then how about this!
-Hey, thanks.
My Executioner's Blade,
I was looking for that.
[laugh]
-You got him.
-You let your guard
down, and now you
paid the price for
you're arrogance.
[growl]
[laugh]
-Oh, I'm sorry.
Did I forget to tell you?
Blades don't work on me, see.
But I'm feeling
awfully jealous here.
I didn't think anyone
would be able to wield
that sword without
special training.
I guess it helps to have a
good strong physique, huh.
[growl]
-Now, I hear you've been
telling anyone who'll
listen that you killed
the demon Zabuza
and took this blade from him.
-No way, not me.
Lord Tenzen, he's the one.
-I see.
So, you're the one who
killed Master Zabuza.
-No, not me.
The person who
killed Zabuza was--
-Where's your respect?
-I mean Master Zabuza.
I was just trying to
say that it wasn't me.
It was--
[gasp]
You're the one, the
one from yesterday.
Yes, him, right there.
He's the one you want, the
one who killed Master Zabuza.
The only thing I did
was bring the blade
back from where I found it.
[laugh]
-I got to say, that's
pretty impressive.
I was amazed you could come
up with such a good lie,
under the circumstances and all.
[laugh]
Suigetsu--
-You're so thoughtful.
I was starting to
feel a bit dehydrated.
I think you've got
the wrong idea.
I knew Master
Zabuza, but it's not
like he and I were
particularly close.
-Oh--
-But still, he was
an elder of mine.
[gasp]
[scream]
-I can't let rumors keep flying
around about him losing to you,
especially when you're
a bunch of losers.
You understand.
-You-- you'll never get
away with this, you know.
You can't just walk in
here and do what you want.
-You have to pay for what
you did, you know that.
[whimper]
-I think I'll test
this out on you.
-Just forget it.
What's the point of killing
someone like him anyway?
[scream]
-I've cut through all the main
support pillars, so you better
get out of here quickly.
I'm sparing your life, such
as it is, out of respect
for Sasuke.
-Sasuke-- no, not him.
The Sasuke that
killed Orochimaru--
-Hey, did you hear what
that guy just said?
You're famous, Sasuke.
They know about you even way
out here in these back woods.
[crash]
[yells]
[scream]
[laugh]
-You know, as long
as I have this blade,
I could defeat even you.
Well, maybe.
Hold on, you knew that I was
going to go after this blade
even before you
freed me, didn't you?
And wait, you also
knew from the start
that the blade wasn't at
the grave site anymore.
Of course, and the one who told
that guy his castle was going
to be attacked and got
them together all of us
men together was you.
Tenzen acted like
he'd met you before,
and I don't think
that was a lie.
Hey wait, did you
suggest that wager just
to get me to go into
enemy territory with you?
Was this your way of testing me?
It was, wasn't it.
[chuckle]
Man, you're terrible.
I could have gotten
seriously hurt doing that.
Well, at least now I understand
exactly what kind of person
you are.
And you're pretty much just
the way I imagine you'd be.
Well anyway, I got
my blade, so I'll
help you just like I promised.
Now what?
Which way do we go?
No wait, let me guess.
Whatever path is
closest-- I bet that's
what you're going
to say, isn't it?
I'm starting to get
inside your head, Sasuke.
-Hm, yeah, let's take
the closest path.
-Oh.
-Just because Orochimaru
is dead doesn't
mean you can do
whatever you want.
[gasp]
-The sensation of chakra--
It can't be.
[theme music]
SUIGETSU: Why are you
dragging a team together?
-I have a goal and
having a team will
let me reach that goal faster.
-OK, but I'll still not
sure why you chose Karin.
You could do better.
I mean, unlike me, she was
one of Orochimaru's followers.
Besides, that
personality of hers is--
SASUKE: But she has
a special ability.
-Yeah, I can't argue
with you on that one.
NARRATOR: Next time,
"Guardian of the Iron Wall."