(Kosuke)
He's quite a fascinating
boy, this Naruto Uzumaki.
(Kosuke)
The one who managed
to save our Village from
complete destruction.
I'm Hayama, the
team leader for
today's mission.
Nice to meet you all.
You too! I've
really been dying
for a mission,
Captain Hayama.
[big yawn]
Hey, uh, listen, gramps,
we're having a strategy
meeting here before we
go on a mission.
Sorry, it's official
Leaf business... you
gotta go.
(Hayama)
Naruto!
Huh?
That man there
is a member of
our team!
Huh!? Gramps
here is a
Ninja!?
[happy chuckle]
[laugh] You mean
you haven't heard
of Kosuke? He's the
Eternal Genin!
The Eternal
Genin?
Just how long
have you been
doin' this?
This year will mark
50 years as a Ninja
for me. [chuckle]
50 years!? Wow,
that's amazing.
But Captain Hayama,
isn't there someone a
little better suited
for this mission?
Well, I personally
asked Kosuke
to join us.
From everything I've
heard, he should
be very helpful.
What'd you hear
about me!?
Well, I didn't ask for
you in particular, but I
needed another Genin, and
you're the one they sent.
Grrr...!
Ok. Our mission
is to patrol the
Northern Boarder.
We're only on
patrol? Ha! This'll
be the easiest
mission ever!
(Hayama)
Let's hope so. If nothing
goes wrong, it'll be an
easy C-rank mission.
(Kayama)
But we can't take anything
for granted right now, that's
why we're being dispatched.
[gasps]
The Hidden Leaf was
just destroyed. And other
lands may come at us while
we're weakened. Is that it?
(Hayama)
Exactly, Tekuno.
The point of this "easy"
mission, is to show
our strength and keep
our enemies in check.
And we'll show all
of them that Hidden
Leaf Ninja are as
vigilant as ever.
[frustrated grunt]
I haven't seen
anything dangerous
here yet!
[chuckle]
Well I found some
nice mushrooms
for us to eat.
Ugh! Listen, gramps!
You shouldn't just be
wandering around the
area like that!
Captain Hayama ordered
us to search around
for enemy footprints,
remember!?
No traces of the
enemy nearby.
Yes, I agree.
Wait, what do you
mean, "you agree"!?
All you were
doing out there
was picking
mushrooms...
I finished laying
all the traps!
Kosuke, is there
some place suitable
for us to set up
camp?
Oh yes. I believe
the Second Hokage's
cave is very close
to where we are,
Second Hokage?
It's a cave I
found a long
time ago.
Way back when
I came here in
service to the
Second Hokage.
That was seriously
a long itme ago!
Well, when you've
been a Genin for
50 years as I have-
Chances are that you
have worked with many
who've gone on to
become great  masters.
(Kosuke)
I even had the chance
to work along side the
renowned Lord Jiraya.
One of the
legendary Sannin!
And I also teamed up with
Master Sakumo, known as the
White Fang, back when they
were both young.
I dunno... Sounds
like some pretty
tall tales to me,
pops!
Say, Naruto... Would
you mind catching me
some crab or fish with
that net of yours?
I can't! My
assignment is to
examine whatever
floats downstream!
You can catch
them while you
do that!
No way! I
gotta focus!
The captain told
me to see if any
evidence of an enemy
floats by here! Huh?
Whoa! Huh?
Ooo, not
bad!
I'm all done!
The traps are
laid! Huh?
[sniffing]
Whoa! That food
smells delicious!
[happy eating sounds]
It tastes
delicious too!
Heh heh, well
I guess I better
go get our beds
ready.
I told you
he'd be good
to have around!
You were right!
He is helpful!
I'm the one who
caught the fish
ya know...
[snoring]
Hey! You there! Do
you intend to spend
the rest of your
life as a Genin?
How goes it?
Huh? Oh.
All clear.
It would be
idel if we
encountered
no enemy.
I'll take over
the watch now.
[yawning]
Stay awake!
Gimme a break,
would ya!? I'm
not sleeping!
Hm.. Hmmm...
Hm!
Hey! Don't sneak
up on me like that,
old man!
Well, no signs of
an enemy in this
area.
Tsk. And how
did you figure
that out so fast?
Simple! These
birds here!
If they sensed other
humans nearby, I
wouldn't have caught
them so easily.
[happy eating sounds]
Oh wow! So tasty!
(Kosuke)
Turned out Ok did it?
Heh heh, well I'm
glad you like it.
We're close now.
I know it's right
around here.
Aha!
(Kosuke)
This is the spring the
Third Hokage and I
discovered a while back!
(Tenuko)
Just how long
ago did that
happen?
I got quite a
harsh lecture
from the Third
Hokage here.
You're kidding!
Old Man Third
Hokage!? How come?!
At the time he
was questioning
if I had the
Will of Fire.
Will of Fire?
Hm?
Hm.
Captain?
Something's not
right. Be on
alert, everybody.
(Hayama)
What Village
are you with!?
[struggling breaths]
(Hayama)
Answer me!
Or we'll assume
you're trespassing
in the Land of Fire!
(Hayama)
Tekuno, take
them down.
About twenty
remain. Your
thoughts?
Nobody forms a
group this size
for just a routine
scouting party!
Captain Hayama!
They've got
us surrounded!
(Hayama)
That's just
a diversion!
Look up!
Huh?!
I don't think so!
Shock Blade!
We have to
change strategy...
...One of us has to
get away and make it
back to the Leaf
Village to report this!
Captain!
(Hayama)
Tekuno!
Take charge!
Right.
Let's go!
Quick! Go,
Naruto!
(Thinking)
Earth Style!?
I'm Hidden Leaf
Jonin, Hayama
Shirakumo!
Don't dare think
that you're going
to get out of
here alive!
But- the Captain!
Will he be alright?
I have full
faith in him!
The enemy's quite
strong in numbers,
though...
They have enough
men to go after the
Captain and still
come after us too?
Alright, what
are we going to
do now, Tekuno?
If we can just buy
a little more time,
we'll be able to teach
our second line of defense.
More time, huh?
Just leave it
to me!
Multi Shadow
Clone Jutsu!
Go!
[shouting]
What is it?
What's wrong,
Naruto?!
Those guys already
wiped out every
single one of my
clones!
The enemy is
right behind us.
You two,
go on ahead!
But we can't!
You guys are
only going to
be in my way
here!
But, Tekuno..!
Just go!
Alright! Come
and get me!
Looks like they
recruited some
very quick Ninja.
Ahh!
[grunts]
(Kosuke)
Leaf Ninja Art...
Yanagi.
[fearful gasps]
A....mazing...
Hey! Old man!
What kind of
Jutsu was that?!
When you've been
a Genin for fifty
years you pick up
a few tricks.
I'm not
buying that!
(Naruto)
No way was that
a Genin-level
Jutsu!
[chuckle]
I wouldn't call your
Shadow Clone Jutsu Genin-
level either, would you?
[gasp] It's just...
I had my reasons.
Well I've also
had my share of
reasons, my friend.
Huh?
This whole mess...
It was all my fault!
It was...!
[sobbing]
Being a Ninja means
that you risk death.
They all expected to
face danger.
They died because
I gave an order
without thinking of
the consequences!
I just...
I wanted to become
a Chunin! That's all
I was thinking about!
(Kosuke)
Naruto, can you make it
back to the Village and
deliver our report alone?
Huh? But, what
about you!?
We must demonstrate to
our enemies that the
strength of the Hidden
Leaf remains in tact,
That's fine, but
let me help you!
(Kosuke)
Someone has to
report back to
the Village!
[gasp]
Please go!
I'm counting
on you, Naruto.
[frustrated grunt]
(Female Jonin)
Earth Style:
Landslide Jutsu!
(Female Jonin)
Explode!!
If you wish to be a
Genin the rest of your
life, so be it. But I
won't let you be idle.
Come on, and I'll
make sure you
learn my Jutsu.
Water Style:
Water Barrier!
(Female Jonin)
Avalanche Formation!
Shuriken!
Shadow Clone
Jutsu!
[painful gasp]
Ah! It's fake!?
(Female Jonin)
Having some
trouble, gramps?
[panting]
You deserve it.
You've made this
quite difficult.
Difficult...?
Difficult, huh?!
You sacrificed your
Genin like they were
nothing!
It this really
your land's way
of doing things?!
If you receive an
order to give your
life, you obey it.
Isn't that what
Genin are supposed
to do?
You used two of
your subordinates
as diversions,
didn't you?
[chuckle]
[gasp]
The two who stayed
behind to buy us
time were Jonin.
They put themselves
on the line so we
Genin could escape!
What!?
No Leaf Ninja would
sacrifice the lives
of Genin under his
command!
Not a single
Leaf Ninja would!
You mean, it was
Genin that took
down so many of us?
Unforgivable...
Absolutely
unforgivable!
Did you think I'd
grant you a swift
and painless death?
I will cut
you up...
Into tiny
little pieces!
You've atoned enough
for your comrades'
death.
Enough, Kosuke.
It's time to
become a Jonin.
But Lord Hokage...
I'm still just...
(Lord Third)
Otherwise, from now on,
you'll only be assigned the
simple missions of a Genin.
[gasp]
As long as I remain
alive I won't allow
you to go to your
death on a mission.
Kosuke, if you're
a Hidden Leaf Ninja
then find your
Will of Fire!
Don't let your
life burn away
pointlessly!
(Thinking)
Second Hokage...
Third Hokage... Did I
too have a Will of Fire?
Huh?
(Kosuke)
Naruto?!
But why?
I don't need
to run away
from this...
What?
'Cause there's no
way that I'm gonna
die here today!
What are...?
I'm gonna be
Hokage one day.
[gasp]
And a guy who
plans to do that
can't allow a comrade
to die for him!
Not when he
can help out!
You're always
so reckless!
[scream in pain]
Well of course
it hurts!
Please don't ever
do that again!
I will not allow
a comrade to give
his life for mine!
Hm... [chuckle]
As long as I remain
alive, I won't allow
you to go to your
death on a mission!
You can make
amends after you
come back alive.
Gramps?
I don't think that
I can die just yet
either my boy.
Hey! Are you
two about
done yet?
Behold the
Hidden Leaf
Ninja!!
What!?
I will not let
the likes of you
destroy the Leaf!
Just die!!!
I will not!
Earth Style:
Earth Dragon!
Water Style:
Water Dragon
Jutsu!
[grunting]
(Kosuke)
Naruto...
Huh? Yeah?
[chuckle]
Like father,
like son.
How true!
I'm gonna be
Hokage one day!
Well, I guess we
better go back
for Captain Hayama
and Tekuno.
You got it!
Let's go!
[cheering]
...And that's
just when the
enemy ninja
attacked!
So I turn to the hero
who saved the Hidden
Leaf Village, and without
any hesitation, I shouted
"just go! Leave
all those guys
to me!" Like
that.
Sounds like a
tall tale to
me! [laughs]
Hey! Captain
Hayama! Tell em
I'm not making
this stuff up!
Yeah! Sure!
Whatever you
say!
(Tekuno)
Awww come on!
[chuckle]
(Kosuke)
You've left behind a
fine son, Lord Fourth.
(Naruto)
Wow! Did you
see that, Sakura?
(Sakura)
That woman with
Kakashi is so
beautiful!
(Sasuke)
Could she be
Kakashi's...
(Naruto)
So you're curious
about that too,
are ya?
(Sasuke)
It's not like
that, you idiot!
(Naruto)
Ah, quit
pretending
you're not!
(Sakura)
Guys! They're
leaving! What are
we gonna do!?
(Naruto)
Isn't it obvious?
We're gonna follow
them in secret!
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Kakashi's
Love Song!
(Naruto)
This is some
seriously big
news!