♪
Listen, guys, since we already
have both of the scrolls we
need, I think we should just go
for the goal.
I hear you. I wish
that we could!
But there's a big risk of
getting ambushed that way.
We should stick to Sakura's plan
and take the detour, okay?
(Choji)
Sakura...?
(Ino)
Huh? Sakura!
[labored breathing]
Sakura...
Two reservoirs... Two...
Next, I'm going to teach you
the jutsu to revive all of
the organs, the entire system.
Ninja Art: Mitotic
Regeneration Jutsu.
Regeneration Jutsu?
This isn't a jutsu that revolves
around healing skills.
It's the same kind of
regeneration jutsu that
the First Hokage used.
He had such immense amounts of
chakra that he could activate
it without weaving signs.
But I don't have that much
chakra! How can I do it?!
That is why I have one
other jutsu to teach you.
The 100 Healings Jutsu.
The 100 Healings Jutsu?
Even I don't have as much chakra
as the First Hokage.  And that's
why I developed this jutsu.
By using it, you're able
to keep an enormous amount
of chakra in reserve.
When you combine those two
jutsu, the body will continue
to regenerate,... keeping
you from dying.
(Sakura)
Amazing...
(Lady Tsunade)
However, there's a problem
with The 100 Healings Jutsu.
Hm?
Not only does it require
extremely delicate chakra
control, you must continue to
amass chakra for a
total of three years.
(Sakura)
Three years...?
(Tsunade)
Good. Your keeping a constant
amount of chakra infused.
You must maintain that
state for three years!
[grunt] I have to keep
this up for three years?!
[weak attack cry]
(Tsunade)
Sakura!
[labored breathing]
Due to the effects of The 100
Healings, your normal chakra
level has become extremely low.
This shortage will be a
hindrance to you during
healing and battle.
As a result, I can't let you
perform any surgery... Or go
onto the battlefield.
The 100 Healings Jutsu creates a
smaller second reserve in which
to store the saved-up chakra...
If I keep two reserves of chakra
and make sure I use each of them
for their specific purpose...
I should be able to
perform surgery... and
fight in battles, too!
[small groan]
[gasp]
Hey, Choji...!
Ino! What...?
(Sakura)
A doll?  Is it an enemy?
(Saya)
[chuckle] You're
such a good girl...
...to have found me
some prey. Thank you.
[gulp]
Sakura, how are you
doing, physically?
Good, since you
let me rest.
Come on, Elder Sister,
let's hurry up and kill them
so that we can move on.
Don't be so hasty, Sana.
You'll make Saya mad.
I'm sure that Elder Sister wants
to get this over with as quickly
as possible, too.
(Sana)
Right, Elder Sister...?
[laughter] All right!
Saya, damn you...!
Lady Saya... please!
No... I shall take my time...
and curse these victims that
my doll has found for me.
Th-Then which one will we
kill first, Lady Saya?
Let me see...
...(chuckle) Oh, they're both
just so cute!  They'll
definitely be worth killing.
...But I don't want
the fatso...
Fatso! You're mine!
I am pleasantly plump!
Say it however you
want! A fatso's a fatso!
[snake hiss]
[evil laughter]
This guy's trouble!
Choji!
All right, then I'll just
take the blonde one.
No, that one is mine.
The one with the
big forehead...
She's mine as well.
[groan]
Fatso!
I said I'm pleasantly plump!
Partial Expansion Jutsu!
[chuckle] That was
almost close!
[grunts]
Choji!
She's... a Puppet User!
[grunt]
As easy as that,
you've been cursed!
Now you can no longer
escape from her!
(Thinking)
Since she's a Puppet User, if we
bring down the jutsu caster...
Sakura, guard my body...!
I'm on it!
Now, Mind Transmission--
Puppet Imitation Jutsu.
Ino?
Ino!
[grunt]
(Choji)
[screams]
Choji!
[grunt]
(Thinking)
It's up to me to
handle this... But...
Ino! Sakura!
Now's the time to worry about
yourself, not your friends.
He's right.  You're in quite a
bind too, you know.  [chuckle]
Super Expansion Jutsu!
How about I eat you guys up?!
Ino!
Wha-?!  What's goin' on?!
Puppet Imitation Jutsu!
I realized after I fell under
that jutsu; She may call it a
curse, but it isn't a Puppet
Jutsu.
It's closer to a Mind
Transfer Jutsu.
The Yamanaka Clan's reputation
is gonna be ruined!
Thanks for the rescue,
Elder Sister!
Thank you, Lady Saya!
Now curse those guys!
You don't have to tell me that!
I shall show them all no mercy.
This doll is now completely
under my control.
And I'm going use it to punish
our insolent friends and teach
them a lesson!
Uh, Ino, he's
coming this way!
Then there's only one
thing to do! We have to
get the jutsu caster!
Hurry...!
When it comes to Mind Transfer,
I'm not going to let anyone
defeat the Yamanaka Clan!
Mind Transfer Jutsu!
(Ino)
Choji!
Huh?
That's not nice.  You can't
simply barge into my doll
without getting my permission!
Now get out!
Forget that!  Choji is our
friend!  So, you get out, lady!
Hm...
As a result,  I cannot let you
perform any surgery...
Or go onto the battlefield.
(Sakura)
I need... much, much
more chakra...
(Sakura)
I need... much, much
more chakra...
Back then, I was always being
protected by those two...
...while I just watched
from behind.
But now... things have changed.
If I still have chakra, then I
can fight!
How magnificent!  I think that
you're just about ready.
Not yet.  I'm gonna need more
power to take down Itachi.
(Kabuto)
Lord Orochimaru!
The reagent we discussed before
has just been completed.
(Orochimaru)
Oh? To test on Suigetsu?
Who's overseeing the experiment?
(Kabuto)
Karin.
I believe they're both
in the eastern hideout?
Yes, I'll send a
subordinate to deliver it.
No, I'll deliver it.
Really? What brought
this on so suddenly?
Hmph. I'm just
bored, that's all.
Well, well; I guess
wonders never cease.
I can't believe you're here.
Well, don't worry. I'm leaving
the minute I'm done here.
Uh, I'm not worried!  Nobody
said they were worried!
Anyway, you're late in getting
the medicine here!
(Suigetsu)
[sigh] I'm so disappointed that
you're Orochimaru's lackey.
I certainly hope that you aren't
planning  on trying to become
Orochimaru's pet like she is.
Hey, who are you
calling a pet?!
I'm going to get ready
for the experiment!
Sasuke, don't bother
with this loser!
(Suigetsu)
Sasuke, seriously...
Will you help me?
I'm so sick and
tired of this place!
Well, it all depends on
how strong you are.
(Suigetsu)
Tsk...
Hey... huh?
[gasp]
Just great. What kind
of horrible experiment
is it gonna be this time?
Hey, you...
...what are
you doing!?
Lucky me!
You let Suigetsu escape?!
When I came to, everything
was just like you see it.
This is bad  If Lord Orochimaru
finds out about this, then he's
gonna take it out on me!
We're going after him!
Round everyone up!
Right!
(Sasuke)
What good will that
do against him?
Sasuke?! What are you
still doing here?!
I thought it might be
interesting to watch
the experiment.
(Sasuke)
What'll you do?
What's your plan?
Since I'm here I
can lend you a hand.
That way! Towards
one o'clock!
Sensory Perception?
Yeah, if it's somebody
that I know, I'm able to
track them by their chakra.
Convenient.  But there's
something I don't understand.
Since you have a power like
that, I'd think you could
get away from Orochimaru.
It's because...
[crying] Ow! Let go!
You know, I'll bet this redhead
is a remnant of a clan from the
Hidden Eddy Village...
You were right when you said
that she'd be worth something!
Let me go!
[harrumphing chuckle] She's a
pretty feisty for a kid.
Hey, little girl, did you
realize that you have a
very unusual power?
That's right.  And that means
we'll get a good price for you
on the black market. [laugh]
[painful grunts]
A shinobi without a
homeland is quite tragic.
No matter where you end up,
you're treated like an outcast.
And if you possess
unusual attributes,
they come after you...
As long as you're
living, at least.
And I should know.
I'm speaking as one
of the hunted, too.
But now... You have a
decision to make.
If you decide to come join
me, then nobody will ever
lay a hand on you again.
If I have to follow
someone, It has to be
someone strong.
So if I become stronger than
Orochimaru is, you'd follow
me instead, is that right?
(Karin)
Damn, a river!
What a nuisance!
We've gotta be careful, Sasuke.
We can't see him right now, but
he's here somewhere.
I know.
Well... I guess I can't
fool you, can I?
But, I didn't expect
you to be with her.
Sasuke follows Lord Orochimaru!
What else did you expect?!
Oh, just be quiet!
Hey, Sasuke... If you're
willing to follow her, why
not come with me instead?
What?!  What are you talking
about, you big idiot?!
I mean, I don't have any reason
to fight with you, Sasuke.
Don't ignore me!
I already answered
that question back
at the hideout.
Oh yeah, that's right. Didn't
you say that it all depends
on my strength?
It's a Water Clone!
No! Physical attacks
won't work on him!
Use Lightning Style!
Nope, I won't let
you weave any signs!
(Karin)
Sasuke!
Aw, I'm so sorry, Sasuke...
Nah, just kidding!
Hey! That's a nice
blade you've got!
Now then, You're up
next, Karin.
Just do what you're
told and come back.
Because if you don't,
you're going to regret it.
Oh, really? Is that
some kind of threat?
[chuckle]
[grunt]
What was that?!
Just as I thought. It
even worked on you.
Lord Orochimaru told me...
that this chain can even
bind a mass of chakra.
But this is the first
time that I've used it...
That's enough,
Karin. Put that away.
Sasuke... What
was that?
Put it away.
(Thinking)
In time, I'll convince
these two to join my side.
...Their powers are worth it.
(Thinking)
Ino's Mind Transfer failed?
Not yet... I don't
have enough chakra!
(Sakura)
Choji and Ino are almost out of
chakra from all these battles!
(Sakura)
Their strength and willpower
are at their limits!
(Sakura)
Back then, all I always did was
rely on Sasuke and Naruto to
protect me.
(Sakura)
Now, I should be able to
protect my teammates...
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Their Backs."
(Sakura)
I can't waste any more time
feeling sorry for myself!