[theme music]
-In the beginning,
Jiraiya boy's only goal
was to gather intelligence.
It appears that he never
intended to battle Pain,
but Pain's abilities far
exceeded his imagination.
And without knowing the
extent of his powers,
no one could defeat
Pain, no matter
how many times they fought.
Jiraiya boy pushed himself
beyond his own limits,
and he almost managed
to uncover the secrets
that Pain was hiding.
No one buy Jiraiya boy
could have gotten this far.
I'm sure of it.
He could have gotten
away if he wanted to.
Instead, he sacrificed
his life so he
could leave us
this coded message.
He bequeathed the
future to all of you.
-All right.
This frog that I'm
giving to you supposedly
contains a captured
Hidden Rain ninja.
-Yes.
I received prior
notice from Jiraiya.
All right.
Expand to full size.
-And be as rough
as you need to be.
Get everything out of him.
-Oh, I intend to.
-This is one of the three
crucial sources of data
that Jiraiya left us.
We have to discover all its
secrets, no matter what.
-Right.
-OK.
Let's begin.
-You've been really
quiet for a while.
Do you notice anything?
-Uh--
-I talked to Lady Tsunade
and Kakashi-sensei.
They had no clue.
So I'm guessing that Jiraiya
wrote this message specifically
with you in mind.
No, I'm positive he did.
I'm sure.
There's just got to
be something there.
-Please, tell us anything
that comes into your mind.
Anything at all.
It's not like we're asking
you to instantly decode
the message.
-There is one thing that's been
bothering me since I saw it.
-What?
-Well, there are all
those numbers, right?
So why is there one katakana
letter among all of them?
-Huh?
-Katakana letter?
-Where do you see that?
-See?
Right here.
-What are you talking about?
Isn't that just the number nine?
-That's what I thought
at first, but no.
Look again.
It's not a number at all.
It's the katakana
letter for the sound ta.
SHIHO: What?
-Well, yeah, I suppose that you
could interpret it that way,
but it's still a big stretch.
SHIHO (VOICEOVER): Maybe--
-Frankly, Naruto,
what makes you think
that it's the katakana letter
ta instead of the number nine,
anyway?
-Well, you know Pervy
Sage, always writing books.
I mean, he was a
writer, after all.
And I traveled
all over with him.
Wherever we went, he always made
me read his handwritten drafts,
and asked me what I
thought about them.
They were really boring, though.
Huh?
What's this?
What's nine "kitticks?"
Anyway, each time he used the
letter ta, it was hard to read,
because whenever I saw it, it
looked like the number nine
to me.
-It's a penmanship quirk.
-So it was a habit, then.
Like so.
When Lord Jiraiya wrote
the katakana letter ta,
he had a habit of drawing the
first stroke shorter than most.
So the first and third
strokes get connected.
And since he rounds
his second stroke,
the whole thing ends up
looking like the number nine.
-Found it.
Now, let's see.
This is a sample of
Jiraiya's handwriting.
SHIKAMARU: It's the same.
-Jiraiya planned this.
He knew that Naruto would
remember this idiosyncrasy
of his that he wrote the
katakana ta like a nine.
So frankly, that was the link
between Jiraiya and Naruto.
We've finally figured it out.
-What were you thinking, Naruto?
Why didn't you mention such
an important thing sooner?
-What's the big
deal about knowing
that it's the letter ta?
Sheesh.
Wait.
that's it.
It was back when you were
reading Jiraiya's manuscripts.
That was it.
That's when you found out
about his writing habit.
The code must refer to
the book you were reading.
-Book?
-Yes.
That's exactly right, Shikamaru.
It must be.
I believe that more clues
must be hidden somewhere
inside his writings, as well.
The numbers in the code
probably represent a word order
or number of lines, or--
or even page numbers.
it's got to be related
to the encryption key.
-Naruto, which book
were you reading?
-Uh, Make Out something.
What was it?
-OK, then just tell me how
many of Jiraiya's books
have been published.
-I'm not sure, but
four or five, maybe?
-Good.
That's not too many.
We'll just have to
check all of them.
KAKAHI: It's probably this one.
SHIKAMARU: Make Out Tactics!
Ta!
-Kakashi-sensei!
-It's been on my
mind, so I decided
to pop in when I
overheard your voices.
I think I caught most of it.
I'm pretty sure this is the
book you're looking for.
-Make Out Tactics.
Yeah, that's right.
That's the same
one that Pervy Sage
was working on all the time
during our training together.
-Of course.
That's something else only
Naruto would have known.
Just as I thought, Lord Jiraiya
did pass the key to Naruto.
-Mm-hm.
-This ta is the first
character in the code.
Of all Jiraiya's books,
this is the only title
with a word that begins with ta.
-When a character from a
book is used in a code,
it could signify word
placement or line number,
but the first line
of investigation
should always be page numbers.
So, the numbers
separated by a comma
are 31, 8, 106, 7, 207, and 15.
Meaning six pages
worth of information.
Let's start with page 31.
So please, flip to page 31.
-Page 31.
OK, here it is.
What do we do next?
-First, we look at
what the first letter
or word on that page is.
Please, read the first
sentence out loud.
-What?
Uh-- ah-- um-- ahem.
No.
I mean, uh--
-Look, what is the problem?
Just hurry up and
read it, already!
Come on, spit it out, would ya?
-Really?
I-- love you.
-There.
Now we have all six pages done.
-What's it say?
If I read the first character
from each page of the book
in order, the real
one's not among them.
That's what it says.
-And what does that mean?
SHIKAMARU: No idea.
-We ought to relay this to
Lord Fukasaku right away.
Perhaps it will mean
something to him,
since he fought Pain, too.
-Then l go ask Lady Tsunade to
summon this Lord Fukasaku right
away.
-May I come along
with you guys, too?
-Yeah.
Please do, Shiho.
-Great.
Thank you.
-Let's do this.
We gotta tell grandma
Tsunade what we found out.
-The real one's not among them.
-Geezer Sage, what do you think?
Does it make sense to you?
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
Actually, none of those six
really remind me of
Nagato all that much.
And yet, a completely unrelated
Pain knew of a conversation
that the Rinnegan bearing
Nagato and I shared alone.
The faces are different,
but I definitely
sense Nagato in them.
-I'm not sure.
it's still all
too unclear to me.
-But you do have some
hypotheses, though, right?
-I've already told
you absolutely
everything I know about Pain.
He seems to be able to
come back from the dead,
so I hesitate to give
you mere conjectures.
Under these conditions,
it's still mighty dangerous
to take him on.
We must first
uncover his secrets.
How are the other
investigations going?
-The autopsy and
the interrogation?
-It looks like
they're both going
to take a little bit longer.
-Like how much longer?
-I can't really say.
I don't think that
they even know.
-What?
What do you mean?
While they're goofing
around, we're losing time.
-Interrogation aside, an
autopsy requires detailed cell
and tissue analysis, and
enzyme extraction. it all
must be detailed.
Doing all those
things takes time.
-It'll be a week at the
soonest before it's all done.
-That long?
-Now, now, Naruto, you don't
have to be so disappointed.
-So what should we do in the
meantime, then, Lady Tsunade?
-Shizune is heading
up the autopsy,
so it should be
quicker than usual.
But we'll still
just have to wait.
-No.
I'll go make 'em speed up.
-Naruto.
If you get in Shizune's way,
you are so gonna get it.
-I will avenge Pervy Sage.
I can't just sit around
here doing nothing.
-But listen, Naruto boy.
Now that we've deciphered
the coded message,
there's nothing else going on
that involves you right now.
-So what about it?
What are you trying to say?
-You're definitely not strong
enough to defeat Pain yet.
-What did you say?
-You know I'm right.
Even Jiraiya boy
couldn't defeat him.
And if he couldn't,
you think you could?
-Well-- guess not.
-If you were to
fight him now, you
would merely die
a senseless death.
-So what are you
saying, Geezer Sage?
I should just totally forget
about avenging the Pervy Sage?
-I said no such thing.
Being asked to come here
was quite opportune.
You see, for a long
time I'd been planning
on coming to speak
with you, Naruto boy.
-Huh?
-Tell me, then, do you want to
come and train in Sage Jutsu
under my guidance?
-Train in Sage Jutsu?
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): I see.
Naruto learning sage jutsu.
Good plan.
-Is Sage Jutsu
really that awesome?
-Yes.
Jiraiya was the only one capable
of using it in this village.
-And remember, Pain
defeated Jiraiya,
who had summoned Lord
Fukasaku and Lady Shima.
That means that at
this point, there's
not one person from
the Hidden Leaf Village
who could possibly defeat Pain.
-I'm as furious as you.
I too want to avenge the death
of my student, Jiraiya boy.
I believe that the only one
who can do is you, Naruto boy.
-What?
Me?
-You do want to avenge
Jiraiya boy, don't you?
-You better believe I do.
-Then come along with me now.
I'll teach you Sage Jutsu at Mt.
Myoboku.
The same way I hammered
it into Jiraiya boy,
I'll hammer it into
you, if that's OK.
-Will it let me win?
Could I stop pain?
-No guarantees.
It all depends on
you, Naruto boy.
Are you all right with this?
-Yes, of course.
Naruto, go with him.
-I warn you, Sage Jutsu training
is unbelievably rigorous.
You ready?
-If Pervy Sage was
able to master it,
then I'll give it
my best shot, too.
Count me in.
FUKASAKU (VOICEOVER):
An entrusted student.
The child of prophecy.
FUKASAKU: Nicely said.
We should be moseying along now.
So, Naruto boy,
say your goodbyes.
-All right.
I'm off, guys.
Shikamaru, take care
that code for me.
-Don't you worry about us.
-If our investigation uncovers
anything, I'll send word.
I will leave a
messenger frog with you.
Send him to me if
anything happens.
-Right.
-Well then, good luck, Naruto.
-Thanks.
All right.
Now, let's go.
You guys know where Mt.
Myoboku is?
'Cause I don't.
-He's supposed to save us?
We're all doomed.
-It takes a month to
get there on foot.
It's also known
as maze Mountain ,
because if you don't
know the secret route,
you won't be able to get there.
-Why does this place have
to be so hard to reach?
-Wait, Naruto boy.
You already signed a binding
contract with the toads.
There's no need to worry, son.
-Hey.
That's the--
-I'll just be borrowing
this boy, then.
-Please take care of him.
-Hold on.
What do you mean there's
no need to worry?
-He's gone.
-It's a reverse summoning.
-What?
-Good luck on your end
of things, as well.
-Now then, let's
concentrate on figuring out
the information Jiraiya left us.
-Roger that.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): The fact
that the Great Lord Elder
prophesied Jiraiya
writing those books
may have been intended to
enable him to eventually leave
the encrypted message, meaning
that the prophecy may be real.
In which case Naruto Uzumaki
truly is the child of prophecy.
-Where am I?
No way.
Geezer Sage, where are we?
-We are in the Land of Toads.
-Land of Toads?
-Naruto!
Hey!
-Gamakichi.
-Yeah.
I was the one who summoned
you here to this place.
Welcome.
-Oh, I get it.
That's how I got here.
-Before we begin
training, we must eat.
Come along.
-Huh?
Food?
-All right!
Now eat your fill.
I've put extra effort
into making this meal.
Now now, don't be shy.
Try the caterpillars.
They're delicious.
-Uh-- thank you, ma'am.
[groan]
-Ma will have a fit if
she sees you like this.
-Hey, look.
I forced all that
food down, didn't I?
-Wel, if you're hungry enough,
your belly won't be so choosy.
I'm sure you'll get used
to it sooner or later.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I'll probably
be dead before
that ever happens.
-Snap out of it. your
training starts now.
-Right.
Yes, sir.
-First of all, I
must explain to you
that what I'm about the
teach you is not ninjutsu,
but Sage Jutsu.
And there's a big
difference between them.
-So what is it?
-Listen.
As opposed to ninjutsu, where
you utilize internal energy,
Sage Jutsu involves making
use of outside energy.
-Outside?
What does that mean?
-As you probably
know, the way one
performs ninjutsu is
by manipulating chakra
that is created
from mixing one's
mental and physical
energies together.
Now, with Sage Jutsu, it
involves taking all of that
internally generated
chakra and adding to it
nature energy from
the outside, resulting
in an even more powerful chakra.
And that leads to all
your ninjutsu, genjutsu,
and even your taijutsu getting
a really serious power boost.
Mental energy and physical
energy from within you,
and nature energy
from the outside.
The jutsu and other
techniques that
are born from the chakra created
when these three energies are
mixed together are
called Sage Jutsu.
-Hm.
-Or to put it in
other words, it's
like how adding a mint swirl
to chocolate and vanilla
soft serve makes it
even more delicious.
Know what I mean?
FUKASAKU: Quit confusing
him more, Gamakichi.
-Oh!
I get it now.
-It took that to
make you understand?
-Yep.
That's just the
kind of guy he is.
-But back to this whole
nature energy thing.
What is that all about, exactly?
-Energy that is external to you.
The energy that exists in the
atmosphere and in the terrain.
-Atmosphere and terrain.
Huh.
-By that he means in
the air and ground.
-Oh.
Now I see.
[groan]
-Enough talk.
Let me just show
you what I mean.
This should be good enough.
-Wow.
Lord Fukasaku's amazing.
Look at him gather all
of that nature energy.
-Eh?
But where?
I don't--
-Whoa.
-He-- he lifted that thing?
-Well, son?
What do you think?
What you're looking at
is the fearsome power
of nature energy
enhanced Sage Jutsu.
-But-- I don't have any
idea how you just did that.
Except that I saw
you weave a hand sign
at the beginning of it.
-Well, naturally you don't see.
You're not yet able to sense
nature energy, Naruto boy.
Nor can you take any of
it into yourself yet.
-Then how do I do it?
-What you must do is
become one with nature.
-How do I do that?
-Basically, he means that
you're gonna have to die.
-What?
[theme music]
NARRATOR: Naruto goes through
Sage Jutsu training at Mt.
Myoboku.
Since it's different
from ninjutsu,
Naruto struggles
with the training.
Fukasaku then reveals what
it takes to become a sage.
Encouraged by the path
taken by his master,
Naruto shows his determination,
and vows to never give up.
Next time on Naruto Shippuden,
The First Challenge.
-All right.
I can do this.
[theme music]