-What's going on out there?
DANZO: The Akatsuki
has begun its assault.
-Danzo.
-Are you serious?
The Akatsuki are really here?
-Yes.
And the one leading
this assault is
Pain, the head of the
Akatsuki who defeated Jiraiya.
-You mean that so soon
after killing Jiraiya,
Pain has actually
come here personally
to attack the
Hidden Leaf Village?
-Yes.
The Akatsuki's been hunting
the Jinchuriki hosts
to accumulate tailed beasts.
They have the Sand's
One Tail, and it's
believed that most
of the Jinchuriki
have fallen into their hands.
-Then that means that
their target here is--
-That's right.
The Fourth Hokage's legacy.
Naruto Uzumaki.
And yet, despite
the danger involved,
the Fifth Hokage is trying
to summon Naruto back.
-To do such a
thing-- why, it would
be exactly like pouring
oil onto a fire.
-I know.
And I know if we keep
listening to the Fifth Hokage,
the Hidden Leaf
will be destroyed.
[screaming]
-Everybody, go!
-What was that?
-Stop.
Get back inside.
-Shikamaru, what's going on?
-It's the Akatsuki.
They're here.
Kurenai-sensei, do me a
favor and step back, please.
Now you die.
Get down!
-You all right?
-Yeah.
Don't worry about me.
You need to take the underground
tunnel to the evacuation
shelter.
I'll take you part of the way.
No arguments.
If something happened
to you or your child,
I would never be
able to face Asuma.
KURENAI (VOICEOVER): Shikamaru.
[screaming]
-We've gotta get out of here!
-Watch out!
[screaming]
GAMAKICHI: Eh, where's Naruto?
-Can't you see him?
-Huh?
-Look carefully.
Huh.
Naruto.
I didn't even
notice him at first.
FUKASAKU: Impressive, isn't it?
Can you please how far he's come
in becoming one with nature?
-All right, I think
I've had enough
of this training for now.
It's time to go take care
of some other business.
-Watch out, Lord Fukasaku!
-Ah!
-Ow, ow, ow, ow.
You all right after
that, Lord Fukasaku?
FUKASAKU (VOICEOVER): Jiraiya
boy's eyes saw the truth.
He will become even
stronger than Jiraiya boy.
-Hey, get off of me, already.
You're heavy, you know?
-Damn you, Naruto!
-Choji!
-I brought some
of my food pills.
-Great.
Thank you.
There are so many.
-My stomach.
-Can someone please--
SAKURA: What's going on here?
-Oh, Miss Sakura.
You're just in time.
You're going to have
to take command.
-Huh?
What about Shizune?
-I'm afraid she's not here.
-That's right.
The autopsy.
-There are so many
wounded, the medical ninja
are simply overwhelmed.
We really need someone to
take charge and give orders.
-What?
Me?
MAN: I really need some help.
Please.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): How can I be
responsible for so many lives?
At a time like this,
Lady Tsunade would--
-I don't know.
I don't know where my family is.
-Wait here.
Take this, and do your best.
-Hey, these are for the wounded.
They're not for me.
I'll be fine.
Everyone, if you can
walk, then please
go to the evacuation shelter.
We're expecting more
wounded at any moment.
Those who are critical we'll
designate with the color red.
Yellow if they can wait,
green for minor injuries.
Go and tie colored
ribbons on the patients,
and separate them by group.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Wow.
You're amazing, Sakura.
I'm going to head back.
You've clearly got this.
-Right.
Are you all right?
Can you breathe OK?
[theme music]
-All right, then.
I'll return and call
Naruto back home.
-Good.
Hurry.
-Stop.
We must leave Naruto on Mt.
Myoboku.
-What's that?
-That's right.
We understand it's
the Akatsuki's leader
who has attacked our village.
-How did you find that out?
-Danzo is the one
who informed us.
-He also said that they're
after the power Naruto
possesses as a Jinchuriki.
-They are.
And what of it?
-Last time we gave
you wide reign,
but now conditions
are different.
Naruto is still a child, and the
assailant we're talking about
is the one who
brought Jiraiya down.
If Naruto's taken down,
and the Nine Tails
falls into their hands--
what are you doing?
-Naruto, you don't
have to protect me!
Stop, already!
Dreams don't come
true when you're dead.
-Don't you worry
about me, granny.
-Get out of the way, Naruto!
Don't do it!
-Until the day that I become
Hokage, whatever happens,
there's no way I'm going to die.
I will avenge Pervy Sage.
I can't just sit around
here doing nothing.
-We'll just have to keep
our emotions in check.
The job that we must
give to ourselves
now is to set examples and aid
the next generation, Tsunade.
To achieve that, I'd
gladly risk my life.
FUKASAKU: I can see
that this child truly
loved and admired Jiraiya boy.
It makes me hope
more than anything
that he is the
child of prophecy.
For Jiraiya boy has
clearly bequeathed his
all to his student.
-You stop this!
Unhand us now, Tsunade.
-What?
You dare to raise your
hand against us counselors.
What are you thinking?
-No!
What are you two thinking?
How long do you intend to
treat him like a child?
-What?
-The Will of Fire has passed
to him, and now it's growing.
Naruto's striving to surpass
Jiraiya this very minute!
That's right.
He's not some hidden weapon
for us to use as a deterrent
to war.
He's a true Shinobi, and
defender of the Leaf.
He's Naruto Uzumaki!
Jiraiya, Lady Chiyo of the
Sand, and Sarutobi-sensei all
had what you two clearly lack.
-Today I'd like to start
by reciting for all of you
a poem that I've written.
I expect you to remember
it when you go home.
-Eh, I can't memorized
stuff like that.
No, thank you.
-That's for sure!
-Pipe down, Naruto!
-Ah!
Iruka-sensei!
-That's all right, Iruka.
I suppose that they do
have a point, after all.
-Right.
Sorry, sir.
-Very well, then.
I won't expect you to
memorize the entire poem,
nor to understand its meaning.
However, when you have
all grown to adulthood,
I want you to think back
and recall the words
that this old man told you.
This poem is about
a way of thinking
that is sure to be useful
to you in your future.
It concerns the
Leaf's Will of Fire.
In the place where
the tree leaves dance,
there one shall find flames.
The fire's shadow will
illuminate the village.
And once again, the tree's
leaves shall bud anew.
-In this world of
shinobi created
by frivolous old people,
it's a great comfort to me
to know that new souls like
yourself have come along.
Up till now, everything I've
done in my life has been wrong.
But at least here
in my final hour,
I can finally do something
right for a change.
The Sand and the Leaf.
May the future that
awaits them be different
from the way things
were in our time.
This special power of yours that
Kakashi spoke of-- that power
will change the
future dramatically.
Become a Hokage the likes of
which has never been seen.
-Jiraiya, Lady Chiyo,
and Sarutobi-sensei,
they had what you lack.
And that's the power to believe!
Just as my grandfather, the
first Hokage, believed in you
and entrusted the Hidden
Leaf Village to you,
it is time for you to
believe in and entrust
the Leaf to the next generation.
-Do as you please.
-Lady Tsunade.
-Did you find something?
-Yes.
Look at this.
-What is it?
-They're receiver-like objects.
They respond to chakra signals.
They're embedded
throughout the body of Pain
that Jiraiya brought back.
-Receivers?
-According to what
Lord Fukasaku said,
every one of the six Pains
have these stuck in them,
studded all over their
bodies and faces.
-Does that mean the
six Pains receive
some kind of chakra signal
across their whole bodies?
Is that how they
synchronize their actions?
-That part isn't
entirely clear yet.
-A receiver.
They could use it to transmit
chakra to each other.
Or a wireless radio.
-And this thing is still
reacting, even now.
I think this must be connected
to the secret of Pain's
strength.
With data from the interrogation
core, we'll figure this out.
-Now, according to
the Intel Division,
the enemy's here
searching for Naruto.
And this enemy who
infiltrated the Leaf Village
is undoubtedly Pain.
-Pain's here?
-We should relay all of this
to Lord Fukasaku as well.
You, messenger frog,
when you recall Naruto,
relay this intel.
-Understood.
-Shizuna, take the data from
the autopsy to the Interrogation
Corps.
Find out who and what Pain is.
-Yes, ma'am.
-ANBU Black Ops, Cell
B, escort Shizune,
and then guard the
Interrogation Corps.
Don't let Pain get near them.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Meanwhile, I'll await
reports on the roof,
and I'll start healing all of
the injured through Katsuyu.
I will protect the village.
Let's go!
-I don't know why, but I got a
really bad feeling right now.
-Those two are
completely useless.
All that they've
done is grow old.
So, Tsunade has persuaded
them to her side instead.
At least now, the Nine
Tails can be kept caged up.
-I'll ask you once more,
where is Naruto Uzumaki?
-Go to hell.
-Speak.
Where is Naruto Uzumaki?
Is he in this
village, or isn't he?
Answer me now.
-I-- I don't know.
-Amazing.
He absorbed all the jutsu.
-Then we'll just have
to attack him directly.
-Summoning Jutsu!
Katsuyu, go attend to all of
the Hidden Leaf residents,
both shinobi and civilian.
Take my chakra,
and use it to treat
anyone who was
injured in the attack.
-The village is
in serious danger.
-Never mind.
Just go.
-I understand.
-I will protect this village
with all of my power.
I swear upon my title of Hokage!
-Are you all right?
-Tell me where the Nine
Tails Jinchuriki is,
or else I will kill you.
IRUKA (VOICEOVER):
That insignia-- I see.
So he's Akatsuki.
-Now, tell me.
IRUKA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
-You're wasting your time.
I have no intention of
telling you anything.
-I see, then.
I have no use for you.
-You create a loud
diversion so you
can hunt from the shadows, huh?
-Kakashi.
-Take that injured man and go.
Leave this to me.
-Roger.
Right away.
IRUKA (VOICEOVER):
Good luck, Kakashi.
-Now it's just the two of us.
-Then I shall ask you, instead.
Where is the Nine Tails?
-What you're doing is
totally pointless, you know?
The people here are
different than the ones
in other villages.
Even if it means dying,
there's not a single one of us
who'd ever sell out a comrade.
[theme music]
TSUNADE: Pain displays
his overwhelming strength
by wiping out the
Leaf reinforcements.
Despite their valiant efforts,
the shinobi of the Leaf
are gradually cornered.
Those who fight for
the village and those
who fight to protect
their loved ones.
As they fight past
their own limits,
what's possible strategy can
they come up with to win?
Next time on Naruto Shippuden,
Pain versus Kakashi!
[theme music]