‐Still nothing.
‐Do you think it
failed, Kakashi?
‐No, it was definitely
some impact.
‐But nothing's happening.
Hinata, are you able
to see anything?
‐No, I can't.
Even with my Byakugan
there's nothing.
‐Where's Naruto?
Isn't there any sign of him?
‐Maybe we didn't
reach him where he is.
What's worse, it looks like
we woke up to Three Tails.
Shizune.
‐Right, Sealing Team, get
ready for the Three Tails.
‐Got it.
‐Sai,
take Yukimaru
some place safe.
‐Right.
Come with me.
‐No, I won't.
I'm not going anywhere
until Guren gets back.
‐I'm sure she's OK.
Everyone here is
thinking about Naruto,
so I know we'll see him again.
As long as you keep
her in your thoughts,
Guren will come back
too, without a doubt.
‐Shall we?
‐K.
‐Let's go.
‐All right, then, let's begin
the Four Corners Sealing jutsu.
Four corner barrier bind!
‐This will be dicey.
We have to hold the
Three Tails at bay
until the Sealing
Team can contain it.
‐K. I guess we'll see if wood
style works on the Three Tails,
huh?
‐Well, for now, all
we can do is try.
[theme music]
‐We'll wait here, all right?
‐Um‐huh.
‐Have some.
You'll feel better.
‐How did you do that?
You know what I was thinking.
‐Not really.
I'm always terrible
at reading people.
‐That can't be true.
Thank you.
‐Dark smoke sphere.
‐I need you to stay hidden, OK?
‐Um‐huh.
‐Sticky water.
‐‐[laughing] Playing
hide and seek, huh?
Let's go, kid.
You're coming with me.
‐I've been able to ascertain
Yukimaru's potential, as well
as the limit of his power
over the Three Tails.
However, we've a problem.
The Leaf are raising
another barrier.
If, by some stroke of luck, they
manage to seal the Three Tails.
‐With every passing day young
Sasuke grows more powerful.
Our transference
is drawing closer.
Then the Leaf and the Akatsuki
can finally be dealt with
and this current endeavor
we embark on will ensure it.
‐We won't have to worry
about the Akatsuki
using the Three Tails.
But it will force
Lord Orochimaru
to alter his plans considerably.
We can't allow that to happen.
If I use these we
may lose Yukimaru,
but that's preferable to
losing the Three Tails.
Oh well, if the boy is
lost to us, then so be it.
We can use what's
left of his power
to crush the Leaf whipping
the Three Tails into a frenzy.
‐Where's Kabuto?
‐Don't worry, he filled
me in on everything.
‐(LAUGHING) so four‐eyes
isn't here, huh?
‐Too bad.
I guess there's no one to boss
us around anymore is there?
‐We're not the same guys
you've been running with.
‐Yeah, that's
right, and we don't
need to hang around
with you anymore.
‐It's been great, really.
‐Breathin' easy now, huh?
‐What was that?
‐You guys were never anything
more than pawns in this game,
and now I've got
you under my thumb.
You're just too
stupid to know it.
‐Say that again.
‐Ah, forget this.
We're through with you, buddy.
‐I say we settle this right now.
‐Settle.
[laughing]
‐What?
What's so funny?
‐Any moment now.
‐What's happening?
My body, it feels‐‐
‐Like I can't stop shaking.
‐What is this?
‐Ah.
‐Fools, obtaining
power always comes
with a certain degree of risk.
You might be feeling a
few side effects, I hear.
‐Side effects?
‐Afraid so, and left untreated,
you'll be eaten up from within.
‐No, that's impossible.
‐Please, I don't want of die.
‐Unless you get some of
Kabuto's medicine in you,
it won't be long before
your power eats you alive.
Of course, he
entrusted it to me.
Pledge loyalty to Orochimaru
and I might let you have it.
‐All right.
I pledge my loyalty.
‐Hurry, before it's too late.
‐Just face it.
Try to flee all you want
to, but Lord Orochimaru
has you within his
clutches forever.
Kabuto wanted me
to tell you we've
got the Three Tails in check.
Once again, he's in
need of your power.
‐I can't.
Taking that medicine
makes my head
feel like it's gonna explode.
‐Be quiet.
You'll do as you are told.
Guren is gone, kid,
and for all we know,
she may never be coming back.
Is that what you want?
‐Guren.
No, I don't.
‐Then quit with you're
complaining and do as I say.
‐All right.
One more time, but
only one more, OK?
‐Yeah, this will
be the end of it.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
Here it comes.
‐One of Sai's.
It seems Guren's fellow shinobi
powered up and attacked Sai.
‐What?
‐Any word from Kiba's group?
‐No, not yet.
It can't be.
‐Boy, you really saved me there.
If you hadn't gotten the idea
to dig a hole in the ground,
we would have been toast.
[whine]
‐Lee.
Tenten.
No way.
They couldn't.
Ah, ah, ah.
Don't worry, boy.
I'll be fine.
Thank goodness.
You guys made it.
‐Are you kidding me?
We barely scraped by.
If I hadn't summoned a
barrier from a scroll,
we'd have been done for.
And Lee running into battle
head first was no help either.
‐It is unforgivable, and after
all Guy Sensei's warnings,
the pride is always
enemy number one.
‐Lee's right.
They were stronger than
we thought they'd be.
‐No.
The way those guys changed
wasn't normal at all.
We got to get to the
others and warn them.
‐Yeah.
‐This mist, they've already
pulled us into their trap.
‐Protect the Sealing Team.
‐Got it.
‐Dark smoke sphere.
‐Sticky water.
‐Yamato.
‐Right.
Wood style, Tree Wall Barrier.
‐All right, out of my way.
‐Wood style, Giant Forest jutsu.
‐Parasitic Insects.
‐What the‐‐ Hey, stop.
Stop!
‐Akamura, what is it?
Hold on a minute, guys.
There's something wrong.
‐The enemy?
‐No, we're OK.
‐It doesn't seem like
there's a threat or anything.
‐You were able to tell what
Akamaru was thinking, Tenten?
‐Oh, no.
Sai.
‐So the Sealing isn't complete.
The Three Tails is still
spreading its mist.
‐It's coming.
It's coming.
‐Gather all of your chakra.
‐OK.
‐You've got it.
‐All right, cha!
‐This is it.
Take them, Yukimura.
Come on, let's go.
You want Guren to
return, don't you?
‐All right then.
I understand.
I have to do it for Guren.
She needs me to return to.
‐I made it back.
Pain is good.
It means I'm still alive.
Naruto.
Naruto, wake up.
‐Yukimaru, is he OK?
‐Stop blabbering
and get up already.
‐Huh?
Wait a sec, we're back.
‐Yeah.
‐Yukimaru.
Yukimaru, where is he?
‐Bloody smoke clone.
‐No, stop it!
Oh, my, it tickles.
‐What?
‐Oh, such a shame.
Your cute little bugs can't
seem to get a hold on me.
Well, lets say we cut
to the chase then?
‐Interesting.
I'll take a crack at this one.
Smoke dragon arise!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
Sai was right.
They're totally different
than they were before.
‐Help.
Shizune, help me.
‐She's at her limit.
Come on.
Hang in there, Ino.
You can do this.
‐Shizune.
‐Ahhhhh!
‐Oh no.
He's using his power.
‐This is bad.
[theme music]
‐Yukimaru may not forgive me
when he learns the whole truth.
‐That's still weighing
you down, huh?
‐I'm prepared to
protect him, it's just‐‐
‐Think about him and only him.
Even if he never
comes back to you.
He could push you
away, despise you,
none of that should matter.
‐You're right.
If that makes the two
of us fools, so be it.
‐Next time, "Memory of Guilt."