Naruto.
Sometimes your eyes
are even better than
mine.
Sasuke is in the
darkness.
Now get going. You
are the only person
who can save him.
Uh huh.
Trust me, I know that.
My view of being
Hokage  stands as my
response.
Itachi's life path led
me to this answer.
In order to protect
the Land of Fire and
the Village,
he sacrificed his clan and
himself
So I first needed to
know why.
What is this Land and
Village that he would
go so far to protect?
The previous Hokage
said... that the
villiage is a framework
created to stop
slaughter of many
clans and children...
...a framework that
was supposed to lead
to peace.
Itachi was trying to
sustain that peace all
by himself.
That's
what I finally came to
understand...
Suffering in darkness
as a criminal and
traitor to Land and
Village...
He was a shinobi who
took on all hatred...
...and protected the
Land of Fire and the
Leaf Village from the
shadows.
I feel that he was the true
Hokage.
It's not the one
acknowledged by all,
but the one who
accepts all the hatred
that is worthy of that
title.
And... I eventually
came to understand
Itachi's feelings
for his Land and Village
But my brother made
one mistake.
By
leaving me, his little
brother, alive
and being unable to hide
the truth from me,
he allowed the hatred to
spread.
However, I'm not
like my Big Brother
anymore.
I have no father,
mother, brother, not
even a single member
of my clan.
Which means that I
am alone.
I alone can bear the
weight
of all the hatred in
the world now.
And I alone will deal
with everything
personally.
I will handle all of
the shinobi problems.
I shall also
dispense all judgment
and punishment.
I'll concentrate all
hatred upon myself...
and bring every
single village under my control.
Hatred inside darkness
can't be destroyed.
And so, I'd
rather...
To me... the Hokage
is someone...
....who uses his own
flame...
...to sear away the
darkness of the Five
Villages.
And then keeps on living by
eating the ashes.
Do you really think
everyone'll sit back
and say, yes to
that?
I thought I told you
already...
It doesn't
matter what any of you
think of me.
And besides, I have the
power now to control
it all.
You really don't
have any clue at all
about how Itachi
lived!
There are things you
can't do alone!
Like our battle
against Kaguya,
remember?!
But it doesn't always
go well...
Like with
these two stone
statues.
And with... us two
brothers...
With revolution, the
villages
will no
longer have to bear
darkness. I will
become the one and
only darkness.
I'll dispose of the
deep darkness of the
past
and build a pure
white future from scratch.
You mean by killing
the Tailed Beasts
and taking down all of
the Five Kage, too?!
That's right.
I'm going to cast
off the past.
You're saying you
can pretend like
nothing ever happened
with Itachi? Yeah, right!
Give me a
break!
You and Itachi were
brothers,
and a lot
happened between you
two!
That's what made you who you are
today!
As of now, Itachi is
entirely in my past.
I'm cutting ties
with all past mistakes
and doubts here and
starting anew.
I'm going to begin by
cutting you down.
Your blood will be the
last that I shed
in
the memory of my late
brother.
I won't
...let you! I learned
everything I know from
the people of my past!
Especially about how
to figure out what to
do after making a
mistake!
You said that you
consider Sasuke a
brother.
That's why I know
you can stop him,
Naruto.
Only you can
do it.
You'll have to take
care of Sasuke.
That's the reason!
...why I won't let
you kill me.
Lord Sage!
It seems that it's
almost time.
So what should...?
What should I be
doing, sir?
Just continue to
maintain faith.
That
is the only thing we
can do right now.
What you do and what
shall transpire,
will be up to the two
of you from here on.
You know, Sasuke and
I...  we may not be
real brothers,
but I
believe that we can make peace.
Now that Itachi's
gone, I finally feel
truly alone.
But there's still
Naruto. He's the
one person
that I
have to cut down.
My version of the
Hokage can only exist
by severing all ties
and being alone.
Why is that?
Because
And that's because, to
me...
we're pretty good
friends.
...Naruto is still who
I'd call my closest
friend.
Naruto, Sasuke,
Show me your answer.
Show me the
shinobi's answer!
Inferno Style:
Honoikazuchi!
(battle cry)
(inhale)
(gasp)
His left eye is...
(grunt)
(battle cry)
(batle cry)
You were on your own
right from the
beginning!
You don't know
anything ABOUT it!
I'm suffering 'cause
I HAVE those ties.
How on earth could you
possibly understand
what it feels like to
lose all that?!
(grunt)
What's wrong? You're
just gonna play
defense?
(angry roar)
(yelling effort)
(grunting)
If you keep stalling,
you'll eventually
die.
(grunting)
I don't wanna kill
you!
But one thing was
worthwhile
The two of us became
best friends.
You're trying to be
alone again...
...but I'm not letting
you do that!
Especially since we
both know what
that's like!
That's why I can't let you...
(attacking roar)
...go to that place
intentionally!
Just quit all your
yapping.
We're both different
from the two boys
who fought here long
ago...
I know your heart well
by now...
...and you, mine.
Right, Naruto?
And yet, for some
reason, you still
wanna fight me?
Especially because
it's you.
I need to cut you out
of my life.
There's no guarantee
that the world
you're going to rebuild
after you go severing the past
won't end up just
like this one again,
you know.
That's the reason
why I'll keep watch
over that world.
So that doesn't happen.
You're still missing
the point!
The Five
Villages are actually
united right now!
Yeah But that's
only because they had
enemies in common.
The Akatsuki...
Madara,.. and
Kaguya...
The Five Villages had
no choice but to
discard their grudges
and form an alliance to survive.
But every last one of
those mutual foes is
gone now.
So the villages will eventually
just begin bickering again.
You're saying that
you intend on becoming
their next enemy,
is that it?
But then what?
What's gonna happen
after you're dead?
What then, huh?!
Finally, the dots
have connected into a
straight line.
I started with the
Sharingan, but now I
have the Rinnegan's
powers, too.
Including
reincarnation,
immortality, I have
many options.
I'll also be able to
control things from
the shadows, instead
of through battle.
You'd return to
that...  hell...
for the rest of your
lifetime?!
I mean for
eternity, being hated
by everyone?
Yes. To me...
that's exactly what
a Hokage ought to be.
That's not even
close to good enough
to kill me.
I told you! I'm
not trying to kill
you! Don't you get
that?!
I just want you to-
I've had enough.
(Rumbling)
At this moment I'm
the strongest in the
whole world.
And right here and
now, this will be the
first step that I take
into the shadows.
I can feel it! How'd
he suddenly gain so
much Nature Energy?
Finally decided to
kill me, huh?
We've taken a lot of
responsibilities upon
our shoulders...
But you see, I
actually do wanna
fight against you!
And I wanna win
fair and square!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Naruto and
Sasuke."
Although... not
against the current
you!