[scoff] This is a joke.
Any idiot can solve questions
like these.
[groaning]
So what question are you going
to solve, anyway?
Yeah right, like I would tell
you that?
Everyone's stuck in a dilemma
because they don't know which
one of the questions they should
solve.
They don't know which ones their
teammates are going to choose.
Neji's planning something,
I can tell.
Yeah, maybe. But why would he
tell a rival what he plans to
do? What's the point in that?
The method he plans to use
probably requires it.
You know which one you're doing?
No, and I don't know about
my teammates either.
What's that supposed to mean?
But if there's a way to let them
know just how many points I'll
get, then I'll be able to solve
the question.
[chuckle] That's a pretty big
if!
I'll communicate the number with
vibartions.
I'll send the four vibrations
through the wall.
And relay the information
without leaving or destroying
the room.
But are you sure that just
hitting the wall will actually
get your message across to your
teammates?
How would you interpret four
knocks on the wall?
Well, let me think. If I were to
hear four signals like that,
then...
[thudding]
I'd think our other teammate and
I should score forty points.
If we both get forty, that's
eighty points.
Then the one who signaled could
get...
Fifty, forty, thirty, or zero
points...
But none of those combinations
add up to one hundred.
So instead, I'd interpret the
signals to mean that the one who
sent them will complete the
forty-point question.
And the other two can do the
thirty-pointers.
Oh, I get it. That makes
sense...
I wonder if Gennai and Inaho
will think the same way..
Hope Minoki and Tanzo will
too...
Each village picked three genin
for the teams that compete
here in the Chunin Exams.
Everyone just has to trust in
their teammates.
But why would you show all of
us how to do this?
If I suddenly pounded on the
wall four times, what would you
think?
Oh. Well...
I'd be suspicious.
Of course you would. And I
simply didn't want any of you to
do something to interfere with
me.
I figured that the best course
of action would just be for me
to come clean and let everyone
in on this.
That way, we can all pass this
ridiculous paper test.
All of us?!
[gasps]
So that's his plan.
Everybody passes, huh? I guess
he really got you there,
Mr. Proctor.
Well,...even so, I got a good
look at his leadership skills.
All of us...?
I get it. And you're probably
right.
But how about letting me be the
one to pass on the info to the
other classrooms?
Okay. But why?
I can't let the Hidden Lead do
all the work. I'll even take the
blame if the classroom is
damaged.
So I just need to send
vibrations, right?
Yes.
[plonk, yell]
One! [thud]
[gasps]
Two! [thud]
Three! [thud]
Huh? [gasps]
Four! [thud]
[pound]
Hey! That was five!
What're you doing?
Everyone passes? Yeah, right.
You've gotta be kidding me!
What's the point of a test
unless someone's eliminated?!
[growl] How dare you...?!
[grumbling]
Hey, what does that guy think
he's doing?!
And it's too late to fix it!
Send four more vibrations, and
you'll just cause confusion!
It doesn't matter if you sent
five signals.
What...?!
Three times would've been fine
too. As long as the message gets
out, any one works.
Any one...?! Are you trying to
tell me that three, four, or
five would all be the same?
Yes, that's correct. Well,
it'll be slightly different.
It simply means the question I
pick will change.
What's that...?!
[gasps]
I get it...
That was some kind of signal...
And it's definitely more
efficient than just yelling
something out along with
everybody else.
But why knock five times?
I bet five signals is referring
to the fifty-point question.
So what are we supposed to do?
I see...!
Huh?
To get one hundred points using
a fifty-point question, two
members need to solve the
fifty-pointer and the third
member needs a zero.
Whoever signaled can't solve the
fifty-pointer.
That's what the message is
telling us.
What do you mean?
The remaining two have to select
the fifty-point or the
zero-point question but have no
way of knowing which to choose.
He's signaling both teammates to
solve the fifty-point question.
Whoever signaled us is supposed
to get zero points, then?
Yes, exsctly. We'll have to hope
that our other teammate will
think about the alternatives and
figure it out, too.
Who do you think was the one
that sent the message, anyway?
Honestly, I have no idea. But
whoever sent it to us got
everyone in that classroom to
agree.
Otherwise, it would've been
impossible to do.
That means everyone in the
classroom that signaled us will
earn zero points.
The reason is because the
message is telling the remaining
two members to choose the
fifty-point question.
Ah, ha! That is what it means!
Still, opting to get zero points
is pretty gutsy.
Even with three signals, my
intent would've been
communicated.
In that case, I simply would've
answered the forty-point
question.
[growl]
How do you figure?
Because if the grouping is
thirty, thirty, and forty, to
get one hundred points total...
...whoever sent the signal
wouldn't take thirty points.
That would leave the remaining
two to choose between thirty and
forty points, and that won't
work.
Whoever sends the signals takes
the forty-point question,
leaving the thirty-point
questions to his two teammates.
[sigh] Damn you. Why didn't you
just explain that to us
earlier?!
I was quite clear. I didn't want
anyone to interfere.
I thought jutsu users who can
communicate silently with their
teammates...
...would be able to foil my
plan to have everyone pass this
round.
[sigh]
You can communicate like that,
right?
[yap, thudding]
[snort]
[thudding]
[growl]
I won't let you!
[gasp]
Well, you're not gonna stop me
either!
[gasps]
NO UNAUTHORIZED FIGHTING
Proctor! Will you allow us to
fight?
If you don't reply, I'll assume
that means you will...
Ha, ha! You want to fight me?
Mr. Proctor, give us permission!
[gasp]
I made it clear Round One's a
written exam. Fighting's
prohibited!
Just keep quiet and answer the
question before the time runs
out!
There you go.
[scoff]
That Neji...He just ofrced me
into revealing a hint.
You mean that warning you just
gave?
Yeah. Until now, there was still
a possibility...
...that the participants in the
other classrooms might think
that I was actually the one
who'd caused all the pounding
on the walls to occur.
But just now, I warned them to
keep quiet...thereby increasing
the chance that it was really
someone in a classroom who made
those sounds.
So every team will score a
hundred points?
No, that's not necessarily true.
If they just think about it
calmly, then they'll all come to
agree with Neji...
But how calm can they remain?
How much faith they have in
their teammates is another
problem altogether.
What's the answer that you
prepared?
Huh? What's that?
If you were taking this test,
what would you do?
I'd just use my Shadow
Possession Jutsu, of course. But
then,...
...this entire question wouldn't
even exist if I weren't the
proctor.
That's why there's no point
whatsoever in me answering the
question.
What's that excuse all about?!
Look...it all boils down to
thinking carefully about your
teammates and the situation.
Still, there's bound to be a lot
who pass. And that'll make the
Second Round a pain.
I don't wanna make trouble for
the Hidden Sand. You see,
there's another part to this
exam.
Time's up. Everyone, flip over
your papers.
For the test's second part.
[gasps] What now? Another part!
Question...Your team is on a
mission, and the enemy spots
you.
To shake off their pursuit, one
teammate must stay behind as a
decoy. Who do you choose...
...knowing that the decoy faces
certain death?
[gasps]
Write down your answer on the
back of your paper.
To pass, all three members on
the team must have the same
answer.
And the member who's named as
the decoy will be considered
killed and eliminated from the
Exams.
What?! [gasps]
You have three minutes.
[grumbling]
You may begin!
[deep breath]
How does he expect us to
choose?!
Sand Letters!
We'll go with Mijin, huh...?
[gasp] Me?!
[whine]
Damn it...
In our old Team 7, it would've
been Naruto...
'cause he probably would've
written his own name down!
Look, Sakura, Sasuke! I'll be
the decoy, so you two can make a
run for it.
So my answer is...
NARUTO,...NARUTO,...
ME
[yowl]
You idiot! What're you doing?!
[growl] Just shut up! And thanks
a lot, you guys, for naming me
as the decoy!
What about you writing down the
word me?! We figured you'd
choose yourself, so Sakura and I
wrote down Naruto.
Like we're supposed to know
you'd just write me!
You're so mean, the both of you!
Shinobi who don't value their
friends are scum!
[gasp]
But the answer can't be Naruto.
My teammates are Ino and Choji
now...So,...
Sakura!
[gasp]
What'll we do?! I can't choose
either of you! What is Shikamaru
thinking with this question?!
Ino, please relay this to
Choji...The answer is...
[gasp]
But that's...!
[buzz]
I'll collect all your papers.
Wait in your classrooms 'til
they're graded.
Those who passed will be called
out to the schoolyard.
You rarely visit. To what do I
owe this pleasure?
We wanted to inform you of
something we discovered.
[gasp]
You don't need any proctors from
the Hidden Lead for the Second
Round?
No, ma'am.
The Hidden Sand would like to
handle everything ourselves.
Why's that?
The site of the Second Round is
the Demon Desert.
It's extremely dangerous even fo
r those familiar with it.
For the sake of security, we ask
for your understanding.
For whose security, exactly,
may I ask?
[gasp]
Naturally, for the participants.
The jonin in charge of the
entrants will accompany them to
the Hidden Sand Village.
That's not up for discussion.
Yes,...That'll be fine.
Your thoughts?
It's suspicious.
Yes. The Sand's hiding
something.
However, they are not the only
ones.
What was the response from the
Hidden Rain?
Danzo requested a meeting with
both of us earlier.
[gasp]
Even though he's confined under
house arrest right now, he still
has connections.
I trust that the both of you
are aware that I helped Hanzo of
the Salamander, the leader of
the Hidden Rain Village?
[grunt]
That was back when you were
still in charge of the
Foundation.
But I continued to communicate
with him secretly even after
I'd been ousted, as well.
Danzo, do you mean to say that
you...?
But Hanzo abruptly stopped
contacting me.
If he had stopped trusting me,
then I'm sure he would've lured
me out and killed me since I
know so many secrets.
But he did not.
Something has happened to Hanzo.
What do you suspect?
[slurp]
I think there's been some kind
of clandestine incident in the
Hidden Rain Village.
The worst case is that he's no
longer of this world...
Can't be!
To the outside world, Hanzo's
still the leader of the Hidden
Rain.
Please warn Princess Tsunade
that she must be extremely
wary.
And to keep a close watch on
the entrants sent by the
Hidden Rain Village.
That's what we are relaying.
For Danzo to ask this of you...
He may called a hardliner and
the darkness personified within
shinobi, but there's no doubt
that everything he does is for
the for the sake of the Leaf.
The Hidden Rain, huh...? We'll
have to increase our
surveillance.
And think of the Sand...
I'll inform the jonin in charge
of the entrants about all of
this.
Just the jonin of the teams who
pass the first round.
Yes.
Damn it...
[mumbling]
All right...
Those of you here have passed
the First Round.
Congratulations.
Neji, you were the one who sent
us that signal, right?
It's thanks to you that we
passed!
Truth be told, that guy from
the Sand actully did it.
How come all three of you got
through to the next round?!
That's right. Wasn't the decoy
supposed to get disqualified?
The rule just said that all
three had to have the same
answer. So our team didn't
choose anyone.
What?!
We turned in blank sheets.
Blank? All three of you?!
Yeah! There's no way that we'd
ever sacrifice a comrade.
[groans]
Just look. See how many teams
passed with all three
members.
[gasp]
[chattering]
Sorry, guys. I just couldn't
figure out that question!
It's okay!
We coordinated things with that
in mind.
Cool! I trusted you two and
didn't write anything.
More like couldn't, right?
[sigh]
[laughing] Nice one, you guys!
[crying] We passed Round One!
[groaning]
You can communicate mentally,
but that backfired on you,
didn't it?
You see...Even considering
allowing one of your own
teammates to die was the wrong
answer right from the start.
Damn you...
I'm Temari of the Sand.
I'm in charge of Round Two.
Too many teams passed the first
round, so we're going to have to
narrow things down even more.
Just what do you mean by that?!
First, Round Two is also a team
battle. Any team without its
third member is disqualified!
What?! No way!
Furthermore, the upcoming round
of these Chunin Exams...
...is to be held in the Hidden
Sand Village.
Although there's a clear route
between the Hidden Leaf and
Hidden Sand Villages, it will
take a shinobi three days,
no matter how fast they are.
We've just dispatched a
messenger hawk to the Hidden
Sand.
It's message reads, "After the
first thirty, all who follow are
disqualified."
[grumbling]
Finally, as in Round One,
fighting is prohibited en route.
You can fight to your heart's
content in Round Two.
That's all!
Lee! Tenten!...
[gasp]
As always, he's quick to assess
the situation.
What's wrong?! I just said
that's all.
[gasps]
Ino, Choji!
Um, uh, what is-?!
I get it!
This means that the
elimination's already begun!
[shouting]
Couldn't you at least have said,
ready, set, go?
This is the Chunin Exams.
Not the Academy.
Uh, what?
Hey, Yukata!
Hurry up!
Next time, we'll just use an
ordinary scholastic
test...
We should try to get there
first!
But there's no advantage in
being the first to arrive, Lee!
[gasp]
Byakugan!
There's another team up there
ahead of us.
What?! [gasp]
Lord Kazekage...Round One of the
Chunin Exams is over.
The participants are now
heading towards the Hidden Sand
Village.
Yes, I see.
Prepare for Round Two.
The people targeting you are
stepping up their efforts.
You'll just be playing into
their hands if you continue
this!
I already know. But if I quit
because of that, it would be
like declaring that I will cave
under pressure.
The Chunin Exams is where
everything began for me.
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Night Before the Second
Exam."
So I'm going to make sure these
Chunin Exams are a success.