All right! I'm going to
start the ecological
survey now!
Huh? Hey!
Wait, come back!
Huh?!
Hey, Octopops, I can't
tell whether this one's a
boy or a girl.
It's all curled up.
This armadillo has always
been shy, and if you're
trying to check its
gender, I can see why.
Who's to say if it's a
girl or a guy?
We're speaking out
against this abnormality,
which reveals your
pervert personality.
Hold on! I have to! This
is the top-secret S-rank
mission that I've been
given! I have to make the
list for the Animal Unit
we're forming!
And checking their gender
is crucial! You think
that I like doing this?!
It don't really matter
which this one is, There
isn't a quiz. Say it's a
girl and finish this biz.
[grunting]
But just look at this!
All of these markings
that are on its back make
the kanji that reads "male".
It's coincidence, just a
pattern.
I have a really bad
feeling about this
thing...
Look, could you just ask
the armadillo, please?
You're their boss, right?
Well, what's the story?
Hm! Uh!
Mm.
It says that its privates
are private! Yo!
Oh, really?! That's the
way it is?! Come on, how
am I supposed to finish
all this stuff up?!
This mission's living up
to its rank... or is it,
really?!
Well, male and female...
There are some species
that are able to switch
between them both, yo!
But check it: the heavens
and earth can't switch
places, yo! Fool, ya
fool!
Hm...
[gasping]
What's this...?!
Something is approaching
at a very high speed!
And... it's not human!
What is it?
What's wrong?
You took me a little bit
by surprise because I'd
heard that you were
already dead, Deidara.
I wasn't expecting your
clay clones.
So that was--
The Tsuchikage's stone
clone. It seems that we
were thinking the same
thing.
Brother Deidara! I
thought you blew yourself
up in a flashy explosion!
Does that mean you didn't
die after all?
Don't get excited,
Akatsuchi!
Why not?
It's merely
Orochimaru's
Reanimation Jutsu.
It seems he was brought
back to life, but he
isn't the real deal.
Damn it. Still causing
trouble, even in death!
A youngster from the Leaf
defeats you... And then you
have the gall to try to sneak
back in amongst the living!
Just shut up! I killed
that damn Sasuke Uchiha!
And because you mocked
and insulted my art, you
old geezer... You'll be
next!
It seems Deidara
doesn't know
anything...
That's enough! You're
both mine! You can't
escape me.
You actually believe that
you're stalling us here,
don't you?
I knew there was going to
be an ambush.
Do you think I'd saunter
in here without a plan?
What do you mean by that?
Inconceivable! We've
been found out already?
It can't be...
Well, Motoi?
[roaring]
"The Artist Returns"
He's found them.
Sorry, but we need to go
over there.
And why's that?
What?! My body isn't
responding to me! What
are you doing?!
No way! He's already
found them?!
After him!
Roger!
Yes, sir!
[roaring]
[groaning]
[panicking]
What's going on here?
I created a second Manda
from the cells of the
original.
His size, strength, and
sensory abilities all
surpass those of the
first one.
The fact that the island
is an animal turns out to
be its fatal flaw.
What is that?
An island? What's so
special about that place.
That's no island. It's a
turtle that's on the
move.
And the Eight Tails and
the Nine Tails are on it.
It's a turtle? The Eight
and Nine Tails are both
down there?
Yes. This is our
opportunity to capture
the both of them.
Oh, I see... Then that
damn Naruto is down
there, huh?
So... What's the plan?
First we stop that turtle
island.
Give me a big one,
Deidara.
Damn it... They're so
fast!
Do it now.
Right.
Huh!
[roaring]
Wood Style: Deep Forest
Emergence!
It flipped over. It can't
move now.
Oh, man... What is going
on today?!
I can't believe it, but
the heavens and earth
really did trade places!
Fool, ya fool!
Huh...?
[moaning]
Ha! I knew it!
[groaning]
You know, the entire
world might flip over...
but a male is still a
male!
This is no time to be
doing an ecological
survey, Naruto!
Please calm down, Yamato.
It's supposed to be an
S-rank mission.
Huh?
Something is definitely
going on out there.
However, we still have to
maintain our cover story.
We can't let those two go
outside.
We're just going to
have to handle it
ourselves.
Mmm.
Kabuto, you go look for
the Eight and Nine Tails.
Hmm.
I will fight these three
here. I owe them nothing
less.
Fine, but don't
take long.
Deidara!
You shall feel my
wrath.
Oh, great. It looks like
the geezer's snapped.
You do remember this,
don't you?
[gasping]
This just keeps getting
worse and worse! Don't
tell me that he's going
right to Particle Style!
This looks bad...
You're not getting away!
What do you think you're
doing, Akatsuchi?!
If you unleash that here,
you'll kill the turtle
island!
Uh?
Damn!
What a mess! It's so big,
it just looks like a
rock!
Now's my chance! Hmm!
Huh!
[gasping]
Old geezer!
[chuckling]
Uh!
That was Akatsuchi's
Golem, huh?
He's still attached to
the Tsuchikage's hip, I
see... How annoying!
I've got get him away
from the island.
[roaring weakly]
That damn snake!
I get it! So that's the
guy who's controlling the
giant snake!
The nerve of that wimp,
pretending to be
Orochimaru's lackey!
I see... Naruto is
actually inside this
turtle...
Now then, how do we get
inside there?
Hm?
Damn it! What's happening
outside?!
Uh...
There, uh sure have been
a whole lot of earthquakes
today, wouldn't you say so,
Naruto?
Yeah. You're right about
that!
But still, this is way
too weird. How does an
earthquake flip the whole
world?!
Well, I suppose that it's
possible here on this island
although it's probably an
extremely rare event!
Mm-hmm!
What? Quit
kidding.
You know, what...? I
think I'll take a look
outside...
Uh... You can't! Because
you have to continue your
vital S-rank mission!
So... You gotta stay
focused!
Yeah... Well, maybe I'll
just go up there and take
a quick little look-see...
But it's a ninja's
sworn duty to see every
mission through until
completion, Naruto!
And this particular
mission... is in your
hands. Only you can
accomplish it.
That's why you were
selected, Naruto.
Understood!?
We'll go see what's
happening outside. That's
honestly the only way that
we can contribute here.
But let me repeat it...
You are still right in
the middle of an
important S-rank mission!
Even Naruto's beginning
to sense that something's
not quite right. We
bluffed him into thinking
that this is an S-rank
mission...
But really, he's only
checking to see if these
animals have balls or
not.
Naruto's not a complete
idiot. He must suspect.
All right!
Gotcha!
Huh?!
I'm gonna stay focused on
my mission, then!
This is actually working!
Thank goodness he's so
dense!
You're slow!
Lava Style: Quicklime
Jutsu!
Ah, here they are, at
last...
There he is...
There should be five
people!
Aoba too, huh?
You didn't have to come!
We can take care of them
ourselves just fine!
Having said that...
Wait, you're the
Tsuchikage's
granddaughter, aren't
you?
Perfect! Now all of you
can just take me right to
where Naruto is.
[gasping]
Snakes.
That voice. That
means that you
are...
And so we meet again,
Yamato...
Gonna sweep him
your way. Get him!
Water Style: Water
Trumpet!
Nice one!
No good! He saw it
coming!
I may have told you guys
to get him, but... I got
him!
This is--
I get it.
You idiot! This means
that you can't move at
all!
My Quicklime Jutsu is
essentially like
fast-acting cement.
Water spreads it out and
helps it bond, creating a
reaction that causes it
to harden like rock.
Motoi, Aoba! Don't step
foot into that water.
And that's for
insurance!
Good! Now you're all
ours! I'll go extract his
intel!
You're even faster
than in your prime,
Old Geezer.
You've always preferred
sneaking around and
fighting from a safe
distance, Deidara.
I never liked that!
Shut up!
I'll finish him off with
my C4! Hmm!
[groaning]
They're so fast I
can't keep up!
Kabuto, how you've
fallen. You're looking
more and more like
Orochimaru these days.
Never mind about me.
You should just worry
about not falling.
Aoba! Concentrate!
Yeah, I know. Don't
worry, I'll be fine.
You remember that I'm in
the Intel Division, don't
you?
I'm going to take a look
now, and I'll see
everything that's
happened to you.
[gasping]
He's molting?!
He's gone that far?
Motoi, get back!
Uh!
Ah!
Yamato!
[gasping]
Damn!
Luckily, Kurotsuchi, I
recognized the hand signs
for your jutsu.
It helped me get all of
you to lower your guard.
Are you telling me that
you waited just for this
moment?
Damn...!
Lava Style: Quicklime
Jutsu!
Stop!
Damn! He hid inside
its nose!
Ah!
[groaning]
Uh!
This ought to be high
enough.
Don't underestimate me,
old geezer!
Prepare yourself! Now you
die, Deidara!
We'll see whose art is
greater, your Particle
Style or my Explosion
Style?
[gasping]
What is this?!
Come on! Not now!
Damn!
[grunting]
I can't move!
Hold on!
Uh!
When that kid from the
Hidden Stone returns,
she'll free you!
Uh!
You're... Lord
Tsuchikage!
Deidara got away from me.
How'd you fare?
Your companion from the
Hidden Stone went after
our assailant.
[grumbling]
Hm?
Please help me! Just get
me out of here, and I'll
go after him, too! Which
way did Kabuto go?
I can't sense the enemy
anymore. I have no idea
which direction he went.
It's useless.
Damn it. Yamato's
been--
What happened here?
It's Yamato...
The Wood Style user and
Nine Tails' guardian
was taken.
The assailant didn't go
after the Eight or Nine
Tails?
Then it's hard to tell if
he wanted Yamato or if he
was simply after any
hostage that he could
then interrogate.
Either way, we'll have to
worry about the intel
your comrade possesses.
Yamato is not that easily
broken, I'm sure of that!
That's not the issue.
[grunting]
He's up against Madara,
and his strong Visual
Jutsu.
Once someone's caught
under it,... there's no
escape!
[grunting]
I don't believe that's
the souvenir I asked for.
No, you're correct; it
isn't.
But he is the Nine Tails'
guardian and possesses
much classified intel.
And besides, I can use
him to make Zetsu and the
others a whole lot
stronger.
After I had captured him,
I elected not to take any
further risks and brought
him back.
This way's better for
you.
Then hurry up and do it.
I'm tired of talking.
This left eye of mine is
itching for battle.
Convene the Commando
Unit! Have the main
regiment run through
their formations!
Make sure the medical
unit is supplied with
ninja tools!
Find Ao and the Sensory
unit. And tell them to
hurry up!
Tsuchikage, these were
completed while you were
away. Here's yours.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Assemble!
Allied Shinobi Forces!
The headbands for the
Allied Shinobi Forces,
eh? Nice job!
"ROCK LEE'S SILLY
CHRONICLES: PART 4"
Youth shines bright, Lee!
Yes, I understand,
Guy Sensei!
But how can I shine even
brighter?
Oh, I know!
Guy Sensei, I have become
even shinier now!
Yes, your hair's so
glossy!
That is just superficial
brightness! This is true
shine!
Dazzling!
I can also cook eggs
on it, as well.
So good!
Would you guys
like some?
No!