In order to protect the
Yamanaka and Nara Clans
and the Hidden Leaf
Village, I, Choji
Akimichi swear to
transform from a lowly
caterpillar to a
powerful butterfly!
And take flight!
And it's simply this,
that I have nothing
left to say to you.
Your Ino-Shika-Cho
formation is
complete.
Thank you...
I'm going to
end this entire
battle right now.
But I'll need you,
Shikamaru and Ino.
So please help me
out, okay?
Y'know, Choji...
I've known you
practically forever
now...
But I've never
seen you take
charge like this!
You're just not
getting it. Half-
hearted attention.
And not enough
preparation.
Sorry, something's
been bugging me for a
while, and I can't get
it out of my mind!
What is it?
Well... A while
ago, I thought that I
sensed the Nine Tails'
chakra, you know?
But there's no way
that somebody else
has the Nine Tails'
chakra right?
So I don't know
what it was...
Must've imagined it.
'Cause chakra here is
entirely cut off, both
inside and out.
And Nine Tails is
only inside you.
It's a bad joke,
no doubt.
Naruto's beginning
to figure things out.
The Gold and Silver
Brothers also possess
the Nine Tails' chakra.
Which would mean that
Orochimaru's jutsu has
reanimated them.
However, he has the
power to perceive the
chakra more intensely
in this room.
We can't fool him
much longer. What'll
you do, Bee? You
have to do something.
Like what?
What do you mean?
Weren't you paying
attention to the plan?
You can't let Naruto
out of this space!
But that's what
you're here for
Eight-O!
What? Damn it.
Uh, where's
the bathroom?
The first doorway
on the left, outside.
You can't miss it.
You idiot! He'll
escape the space
go with him!
Ohh...
Don't panic!
Contact HQ!
What's that? The Nine
Tails is attempting
to escape?!
And what's Bee
doing about it?!
Well, sir, Lord Bee
wasn't really paying
too much attention
back when, you know...
But I have taken
other measures. Lady
Tsunade, please give
the order...
Right.
Stop right there,
Naruto!
Why are there so
many guards?!
I knew something
was up!
Look, Naruto, I'm
sorry but I cannot
let you get by.
Please cooperate
and go back to
that room.
I don't understand
what's going on.
Why is Shino's dad
here?
And why are all you
guys watching me?!
Enough just go
inside. We'll
talk there.
No, I won't. I don't
see why you can't
tell me out here.
Shibi, let me
talk to him.
(gasp)
I-Iruka Sensei?!
Wait, hold on...
What are you doing
here on this island?!
(chuckle)
There's a second
mission to accomplish
here. And we were
sent over to provide
some backup for you.
We've heard that
this place is quite
dangerous.
Why can't I go
outside?!
It appears that there's
a new species of animal
living here. And our job
will be to identify it.
That's because-
You know, I wonder...
I sensed the Nine
Tails' chakra. Is that
related somehow?
He could sense Kinkaku
and Ginkaku's chakra even
in here?! Where all chakra
is blocked out?
We cannot let him
go outside. It would
be too dangerous!
Do your best to
convince him, Iruka.
Oh, uh...
Maybe!
The creature does
appear to possess
the Nine Tails'
chakra. I guess
there are others like
the Nine Tails here,
although this creature
isn't a Tailed Beast.
If you go outside and
the creature somehow
responds to the Nine
Tails chakra you
possess, it's
over for you.
That's why we
want you to stay
inside and keep
hidden.
Is this creature the
reason why Captain
Yamato hasn't come
back yet?
That's right. Wood
Style works best to
suppress the Nine Tails'
chakra, of course.
You know that all
too well.
Come on, let's
go back inside,
all right?
Master Bee stands atop
the island's hierarchy
of beasts. He's tamed
every one of them.
Huh... That feeling
I had when I did
that fist bump with
Master Bee...
That was for real!
I can stop any
creatures that try
to mess with me.
Let me out so
I can see what's
going on!
We can't let
Naruto escape.
On it!
Okay! I've got him
with Shadow Possession!
(gasp)
What's happening?!
What was that?!
He sensed everything
in Sage Mode.
What's going on?!
Why is all this
happening?!
War's being waged.
Madara has
declared war.
No, Iruka!
Don't do this!
Look, Shibi, I've
had enough. The
lying stops right
now. I know Naruto
can handle it.
He needs to know
the whole truth,
and then he can
make a more
informed decision.
But why have you been
hiding all of this
from me?! My comrades
are out there fighting
and going through
all kinds of hell
without me!
Because part of this
war is to make sure
you remain protected
from Madara.
Madara has launched
an all-out assault.
His goal is to capture
you and Lord Killer Bee,
and extract the
Eight and Nine Tails
from inside you.
If he can extract
both Tailed Beasts,
then he'll complete
his jutsu. And the
entire world will end.
So by protecting you,
we'll be protecting the
future and everybody
around the world.
We're all putting
our lives on the
line, fighting to
keep you safe.
Naruto, your fight
will be with yourself.
Because you'll
have to stay here.
There will never be
such a thing as
true peace! Not as
long as we're forced
to live in this
accursed world!
Peace is impossible!
Impossible!
Well, then...
I'm gonna break that
curse one day. If
there's truly such
a thing as peace in
this world. Then
somehow, I'll find
it.
And I'll never
give up!
That's why no matter
how much pain my
own path brings,
I'll keep walking.
Because that's
who Naruto is!
War inflicts death,
injury, and pain
on everyone. The
truth is, the more
precious someone
is to us...
The harder it is
for us to accept
that they might die.
You might try to
find meaning in war,
but all there is, is
loss and unbearable
pain.
All that senseless
death, it unleashes a
cycle of violence and
hatred that never ends.
War creates
only more war.
And those are the
things you will face
in the coming days,
Naruto.
It seems that this
is finally going to
be it for me...
Naruto, I think you
of all people can
bring peace.
Nagato, what you
said to me, is this
what you meant?
Now, let's
go back.
I can stop this.
I know that I can.
You have to let me!
I'll take it all
on myself, all the
hatred and all the
pain.
Because that's
my role.
Haven't you been
listening to me at
all?! You have the
Nine Tails inside
you! This isn't just
about you, Naruto!
You know, you were
the very first person
to acknowledge me,
Iruka Sensei...
Why are you worried
about the Nine Tails
now? Why can't you
trust me and have
faith in me!
Don't act like a
spoiled brat! Do
you know what you
are to me?!
(laughing)
Why are you protecting
that freak? He's the
one that wiped out
your family.
He wants the scroll
for his own power and
his own vengeance!
I mean that is
how beasts are,
after all...
You're right...
That is how
beasts are!
However, that's not
who Naruto is, not
at all!
Naruto's one of a
kind. Works hard,
puts his whole
heart into it.
Sure, he messes up.
And gets jumped on.
But his suffering only
makes him stronger.
That's what separates
him from being a beast.
So you're wrong,
he's nothing like the
Nine-Tailed Fox.
He is a ninja of the
Hidden Leaf Village.
And his name is,
Naruto Uzumaki!
You see, to
me, you...
You remain one of
my most important
students. Also...
I think of you as
my little brother.
The enemy leader is
targeting you with
everything he's got.
How can I stand
here and let that
happen? Let you
face such danger?
And besides,
there's no reason
for you to shoulder
that burden alone.
Look, I'm not just
some little kid
anymore!
I'm strong now!
Remember, Sensei,
you are the one who
gave me that headband.
Hey, Iruka.
I can't!
I'm sorry, but I
just can't let you
leave this place.
Sensei, didn't I
tell you that I'm
stronger now?
You can't keep
me here!
He broke free!
I'll stop him!
My Parasitic Insects
can't handle the
Nine Tails' chakra!
Temui! I want you to
contact the Barrier
Corps, now. Tell them
that Naruto is coming!
Right!
And the rest of
you come with me!
Let's go!
Why?! Why,
Iruka Sensei?!
Huh?!
What is this?!
Knowing you. I'm sure
that you're going to
rush right to the
battlefield.
I also know how
determined you are.
The fact that you're
reading this means
that I wasn't
able to stop you.
Ever since Lady
Tsunade tasked me
with going to the
Cloud's secret
hidden island in
order to keep you
there, I've had
this on hand.
I've kept this
letter ready just
in case I failed.
I'm disappointed in
myself for failing.
I don't know if I'll
ever be able to give
you this note, but
still, there's
something that you
need to hear from me.
You've gone off, so
this is the only
thing that I have left
to say.
No matter what
happens, come
back alive!
Forgive me,
Naruto. I'm
weak.
I think of myself
as your big brother,
but I've never been
able to protect you.
So the little guy's
already gone, huh?
Fool, that fool.
Killer Bee? That's
who you are, right? I
need to ask something
of you right now.
Hm? Wait, who is
this guy? I've
seen him somewhere
before, haven't I?
Please, I beg
you to keep
Naruto safe!
Hold on, that's not
the way to appeal,
you see. What you
should do is raise
your fist with me.
Oh, uh...
Is it like this?
Now you got me
for real! Fool,
ya fool!
Oh wait, I get
it. It's you...
Huh?
Can you really keep
this promise, Bee?
Naruto did get out on
your watch, after all.
Hey, if he couldn't
stop the little fool's
plan. Then frankly,
no one can.
You're part of Naruto's
private clan. You're
always in his heart.
And in his mind.
What? Me?
I am?
Naruto need you.
Now, don't be stunned.
To him, it's no doubt
that you're number one.
So whatever you've
done, to Naruto you
shine like the sun and
you're just as golden.
Naruto listens to all
you say, and he's kept
it securely inside
him to this day.
What's protected
Naruto all this
time, were your
words to him.
You're really going
to chase Naruto
outside the barrier?
Yeah, of course
I am! I'm still
training him,
fool ya fool!
You'll be getting
the Iron Claw from
the Raikage for sure.
Look, a real battle
always teaches you
more than merely
training, anyway!
It's a shortcut to
power up, ya fool!
What is the meaning
of this, Tsunade?!
The Nine Tails already
got past our men?!
Iruka...
We'll just have to
use brute force
to stop him.
Is the Barrier
Corps ready?
There's a thirty-
six-layer self-
regenerating barrier
around the island.
Even a Jinchuriki
couldn't get through
that. So please, rest
assured.
It's Naruto!
He's coming!
Good! The Barrier
Corps will show
everyone what
were made of!
The time has come!
Our blood, sweat,
and tears will now
reveal just what
we can do with
this impenetrable
barrier!
We will not
let him pass!
The only message
Headquarter will
receive from us is,
"Mission Accomplished."
Do you understand!
Huh?
Ahh!
What is this?!
There's a barrier
beyond that. And
you and I are gonna
break it, stat!
All right,
Octopops!
I'll break the
barrier, ya fool!
And then Naruto,
you get the Tailed
Beast Bomb in,
ya fool!
Right!
Killer Bee the
Eight Tails is
here, as well!
What's that?!
No!
All right!
Now here we go!
Ya fool!
(powerful yell)
It's no good!
The barrier can't
regenerate quickly
enough!
Ooh, that means
that at this
rate...
Well, Chief. What
exactly do you want
me to relay to
Headquarters, then?
That our mission
failed!
Yeah, I kinda
figured that.
(powerful yell)
Damn it!
They're out!
(exhausted moans)
But there were
two of them. Two
jinchuriki! No one
told us to expect
that! W-what
could I do?!
(weary sigh)
Incredible chakra!
An immense chakra
field has appeared
on the battlefield
near Darui's First
company! What is it?
It's some sort of
humanoid monster!
It's ravaging our
troops! And it
appears to be
controlled by...
Who is it?!
We believe it's
Madara Uchiha!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Attack
of the Gedo Statue.
Gedo Statue!
Go!