Are...
Are you...
...saying I've got regrets...?!
You once told me...that you're
nobody,...that you don't wanna
be anybody.
But the truth is you wanted...to
be Hokage, just like me.
You can hide behind a mask, but
it's pointless.
You were Kakashi Sensei's
friend,...my dad's
subordinate,...an Uchiha like
Sasuke,...
...my senior,...and a Leaf
shinobi, who shared the same
dream as me.
You used to have the same dream
as me.
Now, you're the
opposite of a Hokage!
It's 'cause you're just like me
that-
No, it's...
...because of that.
That's why I wanted to see you
despair about this world.
Or I suppose I wanted to feel
again for myself...
...that the path which I've
chosen is indeed not a mistake.
There's no need to voluntarily
walk a rugged path, whose
destination isn't even clear.
And step over comrades' corpses.
So, any person who's sensible
would choose a shortcut with
a fixed outcome.
That's right...
The goal a Hokage should seek
is to create world peace.
You don't know what you're
talking about.
What I want to know isn't the
shortcut or the easy path...
...but how to navigate the
rugged one!
But,...in the beginning, how can
you tell which one is the
rugged path?
I  mean,...you never really know
until someone starts walking
down it!
A Hokage is the one who walks
ahead of everyone else, enduring
their own pain. So, that's
why...
...a Hokage never walks over his
comrades' corpses.
There's no shortcut to becoming
Hokage! And no way out for the
one who becomes Hokage!
Correct?
I just messed up a little
bit,...got some dust in my eyes
and, uh...
Ouch!
I bet I know what this Rin
person would say if she were
still alive...
Don't act tough and hide your
wounds. You know that I am
always watching.
You told me that saving you was
the same as saving the
whole world, remember?
Well then, since I'm keeping
an eye on you...
...you can't hide anything from
me anymore.
Uh-huh.
Go for it, Obito!
Become Hokage and show me just
how you're gonna save
the whole world.
And that's another promise for
you to keep!
Rin was my...
...sole light and hope in all
this dark world.
After I lost Rin...
The whole world as I saw it
changed...
It became a black hell.
This world holds no hope.
I took Madara's identity and
walked the world, but all that
did was further confirm my
belief.
Even possessing this Sharingan
didn't reveal anything to me...
'Cause there was nothing to see.
I'm sure you could've seen it,
too, if you tried.
After all, you and I have the
same eyes.
If comrades you trust gather
around you, hope can take
physical form and become
visible.
That's what I believe,...
...Obito.
Naruto's path, huh...?
"Madara Uchiha Rises"
Sage Art: Gracious Deity Gates!
[thuds]
Naruto's jutsu didn't take him
down,...but I've been able to
completely immobilize him now.
All that's left...is to wait for
the Sealing Shinobi.
[heavy breathing]
[retching cough]
[gasp]
That Tailed Beasts were
extracted from him...That means
he'll...
The Ten Tails' Jinchuriki isn't
like all of the others.
They won't die if the Tailed
Beast is extracted.
It's because the Ten Tails'
husk, the Gedo Statue,
remains.
It contains a lot of life force.
Is that true? How do you know
such a thing?
Hey, now. Who do you think
scattered us across the world
after splitting Ten Tails'
Chakra into nine pieces?
[inhale]
The Sage of Six Paths...
But with nine bodies pulled out
at once, he'll be so weak it's
like he is dead.
He won't be able to budge for
months.
Like it was for the old man,
long ago.
So that's how it goes, huh?
Kakashi....
The Nine Tails inside me just
explained it...
[deep breathing]
That's right. Rin wouldn't even
give the time of day to the
current you.
Rin wanted to watch over...
...Obito Uchiha.
So,...there's no need to worry.
Then,...his life is...
I was hoping he could atone
for all his past
misdeeds,...but...
If he can't move, it can't be
helped. You just lie there,
okay?
Sensei,...please keep an eye on
Obito.
All right.
[gasps]
What are you doing?!
[gasp]
The same...
...as the man I'd once tried to
use...
...did as a way to betray me.
No way...
Although I never imagined that
I...
...would end up doing the same
thing...
I'll use...
The Gedo Art of Rinne Rebirth.
But that jutsu...
...it will result in your...
It seems to be a jutsu that
trades life for life.
I feel as though now...
...I can finally understand
why...
...Nagato betrayed me back then.
A string of hearts...llnked
together like prayer beads...
That can be a strong power as
well...
Both Nagato and Naruto were
Jiraiya's students.
So,...it could be said that
Jiraiya defeated me.
Sensei...He was also your
teacher,...and the one who
groomed you to become Hokage.
And then, I...
...was your...
...student.
A shinobi who gave up on
becoming Hokage...And cut all
his ties.
I guess...I won't have much to
say to Rin...on the other side.
Are you really sure about this?
You could live and atone for
your sins, you know...
No...That path would be...the
easy way out.
[boom]
[thwap]
[gasps]
[crunch]
This time...I'll be helping yoou
out!
Time to switch places!
Now it will be my turn to
attack!
Cut the tough act!
This war is over, right now!
Sai!
I know!
Sealing Jutsu!
Crouched Tiger Bullet!
[roar]
Naruto...
I owe you a debt of gratitude.
You even extracted the Tailed
Beasts from Obito for me...
...saving me the trouble of
having to weaken him.
Sorry, Obito...But this was the
whole reason I was stuck onto
you in the first place.
Black Zetsu!
[gasp]
[growl and chomp]
Okay! Almost done!
Art of Rinne Rebirth!
[sizzling]
Finally, I'll be able to fight
for real!
[boom]
[gagging]
This is the form...This is the
body I've been needing!
It's just...
...not a battle without raging
blood...
...and a pounding heart!
[gasps]
Ancient relics of the past...
...should butt out!
You are only a brat nowhere
near my level.
And you stole my line, foolish
child.
Why'd he shut his eyes...?
Wait, Sasuke!
It's pointless to just lob
attacks at this guy.
He has the ability to absorb
ninjutsu!
[gasp]
It's these opposites operating
together that give rise to all
things in this universe...
Hashirama,...
Do you remember me saying that
long ago, standing in front
of the Uchiha Stone Tablet?
You said it means that true
happiness can be found...
...when two opposites - two
contrary powers - cooperate.
But I told you that it could
also be interpreted differently.
[gasp]
What's that?!
That the person who obtains...
...the power of both the Uchiha
and the Senju will be able to
attain true happiness.
Don't you think it would be
interpreted that way as well...?
...Hashirama?
It appears to me that...
...you've been doing a lot of
plotting since leaving the
village.
No...
It's something my subordinate's
comrade came up with simply by
chance.
Apparently there was another
fellow who thought quite a lot
like me.
However...
My coming back to life, as I've
now done, has gone exactly
according to plan!
[gasps]
Damn it! I can't move!
[grunts]
[whack]
[gasp]
[thwack]
[groaning]
Of course, things happened a
bit out of order. But, oh well.
So this is Sage Art Chakra...
That's it, huh? That's really
all there is to it?
This'll be easy enough to
control.
Now that you're flesh and blood
again, this will give us the
perfect chance...
...to kill you for good...
...and send you back to the
afterlife!
You'll regret that you're still
not a reanimation...
...as you go to your death!
I can sense it...
Your Mangekyo are...Choku Tomoe.
They're a straight pattern.
No wonder you have good moves.
It might not be a bad idea for
me to take your eyes until I get
my Rinnegan back.
Obito...I'm afraid you've
finished being useful.
[gasping]
What did you do?!
Madara has...
...now come back to life
completely...
[gasps]
Since you performed the Rinne
Rebirth, you will die.
All that remains is to take back
that left eye.
[gasps]
He'll likely hang on a little
longer while I'm attached to
him. Well, occupying his body,
really.
What exactly are you? You aren't
human.
I am Madara's will, incarnate.
And I will eliminate anyone who
gets in Madara's way.
Black Zetsu...
I thought that you'd been
captured!
All of you, Obito included, have
perpetually and greatly
underestimated Madara's plan.
And...you've underestimated me
as well.
[yelling]
I...can't move...! I had no idea
... that he could transform the
shape of his blade so fast...!
That's not a problem at all. You
go to where Obito is and bide
your time until I give the
signal.
I'll head over after I play here
a little longer.
I want to gauge the current
Kage's strength.
Okay, gotcha.
He's a good-for-nothing traitor
who went against Madara's plan.
Now,...until Obito dies,...I'm
going to use his body to fight
you.
It's only fair that he be useful
at the end.
Although, with an eye like that,
killing you would be sich a
waste.
How about...
...putting your blade down and
joining up  with me, as a
fellow surviving Uchiha.
Oh, please. Make no mistake...In
my mind, you're nothing but a
dead man.
Very well, then...But either
way,...you don't have a whole
lot of time left.
Fire Style! Hiding in Ash Jutsu!
[boom]
[gasps]
Madara is regaining his past
strength.
This is bad...And his next
target will be...
[boom, yelling]
[thud]
And up next...
I'll be taking possession of
every one of you...
...filthy beasts.
This taste of blood, this pain!
It's my body, all right!
Finally, I can fully experience
battle again.
He's bleeding and bearing
wounds...So he isn't a
Reanimation anymore.
How did he come back to life?
No way...
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Hidden Heart."
No way! He used Obito-