[groaning]
[groan] Guy Sensei?!
That was Guy's final move!
What happened?
[heavy breathing]
[exhale and inhale]
[laugh]
I very nearly died! You
bastard!
Seems your flame's about to go
out...But to show my gratitude,
...for the fun,
(Six Paths Madara) I'll finish
you off...
...before you turn to ash!
(Six Paths Madara) He kicked
away my Truthseeker Orb?!
(Naruto) Bushier Brow Sensei...
(Six Paths Madara) Naruto...?
You appear to be somewhat
different than before.
(Six Paths Madara)Obito
must've...
(Naruto) Yeah...
I'm still trying to figure
it out myself.
But I think I can change
everything now!
"To Rise Up"
[gasp]
(Six Paths Madara) The node's
chakra hasn't gone out?
(Six Paths Madara) What's going
on? What did he do?
(Six Paths Mardara) He stopped
the Eight Gates' endgame?!
[gasp]
(Six Paths Madara) He touched
the Truthseeker Orb?! How can
he--?!
(Six Paths Madara) Is it because
I haven't finished healing
yet?
(Six Paths Madara) No!
(Six Paths Madara) His power's
suddenly grown!
(Naruto) Son! Lend me some
chakra, will ya?
(Son Goku) All right!
(Naruto) Sage Art: Lava Style
Rasen Shuriken!
(Six Paths Madara) [grunt] This
is bad!
(Six Paths Madara) Limbo!
(Naruto) [yell]
(Six Paths Madara) What?! He
evaded the Limbo?!
[groaning]
Now!
Explode!
[groaning]
[grunt]
(Kakashi) The tree's been
severed!
(Kaguya) Take me within you.
[gasp]
(Six Paths Madara) Who...?!
(Kaguya) Take the Divine
Tree...Ten Tails...
(Kaguya) All of me...into you.
Wait, Naruto really did this?!
Guy Sensei is over there as
well!
[grunting]
The tree disappeared?!
[gasping]
[gasp]
[gasp] Guy Sensei!
Bushier Brow Sensei's gonna be
okay! So don't worry. He's not
gonna die!
Do you mean that you healed him,
Naruto? But I thought that he
had activated all Eight Gates!
(Naruto) Yeah...
(Naruto) But I feel like I'm
able to do all sorts of
things,...the way that I am
now...
Huh?
(Tobirama) He's touching
Madara's rod but isn't
affected...?
What happened to him...while he
was starting to die?
Can you teleport, Lord Second?
[grunting ]
I think I see what you
want...And yes,...
I can, since I linked myself to
Fourth's markings...But I'm
sorry...
At my current strength, I'm only
able to teleport one person.
(Sasuke) That's plenty.
Only I need to go.
But Sasuke...! [sigh]
(Orochimaru) His wind...has
gotten even stronger.
Wwll, Sasuke...I had always
wanted to see where your wind
would take you...
But I think I've seen enough.
From this point foward, I
believe that we would only serve
as a burden to you.
[chuckle] So does that mean
we're not gonna be ordered
around anymore?
Sounds pretty good to me, too!
Sasuke...
(Karin) Hey!
Why are you guys all ready to
give up? I mean, come on!
I could...
Bushy Brow, Gaara, watch Bushier
Brow Sensei.
Naruto...
You saved Guy Sensei...Thank
you!
(Gaara) Naruto...
Huh?
When you finally become the
Hokage, we should go have a
drink together, sometime.
Sure!
Huh?
(Kakashi) Is that Naruto?!
(Kakashi) Obito...Did you...?
[heavy breathing]
You are my enemy.
You hurt and killed many of my
comrades...
And I really don't like having
to say this to you, but, right
now,...
I'm going to consider you an
ally just this one time.
[heavy breathing]
And because you saved Naruto's
life, I thank you.
(Obito) I have a final favor to
ask.
Not as an ally but...
...as an enemy...
(Six Paths Madara) I see...The
Divine Tree itself is...
[laughter]
The time when all shall
become one has come.
(Naruto) Is it 'cause I met
Super Gramps Sage and got more
power from him?
(Naruto) I can feel it clearly,
even from here,...the other half
of Super Gramps; power.
You can't possibly take me down.
I've essentially become immortal
now.
Don't you see? I've obtained
eternity!
You idiot! I'm not the one who's
gonna be taking you down...
Hm.
We are the ones who're gonna
take you down!
Your time has come, Madara.
(Six Paths Madara) You awakened
Six Paths Senjutsu...
(Six Paths Madara)...and you
awakened one-eyed Rinnegan, eh?
(Six Paths Madara)
However,...I've got both of
those powers
together,...remember?!
This is the final battle between
us!
(Six Paths Madara) My powers
versus yours...
(Six Paths Madara) Let's settle
who is superior, once and for
all!
(Six Paths Madara) Sage Art:
Shadow Style Thunder Blast!
[gasp]
(Six Paths Madara) Sasuke's
gone?!
(Sasuke) This left eye...So
that's what it can do...
(Six Paths Madara)
Teleportation? Over this
distance? No... it's
not that he moved...!
You should pay attention!
(Six Paths Madara) Limbo!
[gasp]
(Sasuke) What is that?!
(Naruto) He did it again!
[inhale]
(Six Paths Madara) Sage Art!
[grunt]
(Six Paths Madara) Gale Style:
Fang of Light!
[grunt]
(Naruto) It's coming again!
(Sasuke) Over there!
[grunt]
(Sasuke) It didn't hit?!
Sasuke, it's headed your way!
Something I can't see is moving
around!
Oh, yeah? 'Cuz, I can see it
just fine!
(Six Paths Madara) Those
two...can see my Limbo...
(Sasuke) It's...another Madara.
(Six Paths Madara)The
Rinnegan's allowing him to see
it.
(Six Paths Madara) And
Naruto,...he can't see it...but
he can sense it...
Naruto!
It appears that our physical
attacks...have no effect on
this...other Madara.
(Naruto) I know!
(Six Paths
Madara) Normally,...one oughtn't
be able to sense it or see it
from this realm,
(Six Paths Madara) ...the "me"
that exists in the invisible
realm of "Limbo".
(Six Paths Madara) How'd they
both gain such power so
suddenly?
(Six Paths Madara) That Sasuke
Uchiha...He awakened the
straight pattern Choku-Tomoe
Sharingan just like mine.
(Six Paths Madara) Sasuke and I
may share some relationship that
goes beyond just bloodline.
Then,...I think that left eye of
yours wiill suit me quite well!
[gasp]
(Six Paths Madara) So, that's
your left eye's ability as well,
huh?
[gasp]
Well, then...
Go on, try it.
That's not enough to kill you,
is it?
(Sasuke) The Six Paths' Sage
Chakra can affect the shadow
Madara, too, huh?
(Sasuke) That wound on his right
arm...
(Sasuke) ...is from when he
blocked Naruto's attack earlier.
It seems your shadow returns to
your body after a fixed time.
(Sasuke) Naruto, if and when his
shadow emerges again, you go
after it.
I'll take on the visible one.
However...
[chuckle]
I always hated you ordering me
around...
I guess some things never
change, huh?
Let me finish what I was saying.
Listen,...this is our one
chance.
(Sasuke) He and his shadow will
likely stay together for a
little while longer.
(Sasuke) I don't care what is,
but get a Sage Power Jutsu read.
(Sasuke) Something that seals
movement.
(Shukaku) Well, then, why
don'tcha use my chakra to build
your Sealing Jutsu?
Great, thanks! Um, uh...
(Shukaku) It's Shukaku!
(Six Paths Madara) He's
postulating and estimating the
Limbo's duration, activation
interval,
and how to counter it...
(Six Paths Madara) He's got
sharp intuition, calm analyzing
and judgment skills,
and a Choku-Tomoe Sharingan
just like mine.
(Six Paths Madara) If he had
only been born earlier than
Obito, he'd be my...
(Six Paths Madara) No, there's
no point in reflecting on what
could've been.
(Six Paths Madara) No matter
what's happened,...I must keep
in mind that these two aren't
ordinary shinobi.
(Six Paths Madara) I need to get
my other eye back soon.
Now, Sage Art: Magnet Style
Rasengan!
(Sasuke) And I have Six Paths
Power, too...
(Sasuke) Chidori!
Naruto, send your jutsu to me!
I'll handle the rest.
It's still a bit annoying, but I
guess that there's no time to
argue!
Hm?
(Six Paths Madara) How'd I get
here?!
Naruto, the jutsu that the Sage
gave you...You know it, right?
Yeah, this is the moment!
Huh?
What?!
He moved!
(Sasuke) He substituted in his
shadow?
Right there!
Sasuke, I'll hold this one down.
You go after the real one!
[grunt]
(Six Paths Madara) It seems his
Rinnegan can't reach this far
away.
(Six Paths Madara) I'm starting
to understand your left eye's
abilities,...Sasuke.
Sasuke, hurry! Madara's heading
toward...
(Naruto) ...Kakashi Sensei!
Huh?
[groan]
Hurry up and destroy my
Rinnegan...
I can't hold off Black Zetsu any
longer.
[gasping]
(Six Paths Madara) I'll admit,
Sasuke sure is quick.
(Six Paths Madara) Kamui!
[gasp]
(Sasuke) Just his upper body,
huh?
Do it, come on!
I know!
[gasp]
No.
(Obito) The Rinnegan will fall
into Madara's hands. If he gets
both eyes, terrible things will
happen.
(Sakura) What do you mean,
"terrible things?" How much
worse can all this get?
(Obito) If both Rinnegan are
restored to their true owner...
(Naruto) Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Infinite Dream"
(Obito)...I fear no one can
stand against him.