[music playing]
[MUSIC - MOTOHIRO HATA, "TOMEI
DATTA SEKAI"]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
"Big Adventure!
The Quest for the Fourth
Hokage's Legacy, Part Two."
KAKASHI: Well, it's
starting to take shape.
-No, not yet.
I'm only aiming at
a motionless rock.
-That's true.
If only you could test
it to see if it'll
work in a real battle
in the final rounds.
-What's this?
NARUTO: Man, that giant spider
sure was a surprise, huh?
SAKURA: Why did you rush
in to attack it anyway?
That was so reckless.
-Come on.
Let's beat the Fourth Hokage's
time and get his legacy.
-Did you even hear
what I just said?
-Ow.
Sakura, my nose.
Come on, knock it off.
It hurts.
-Mm-hmm.
Shikamaru?
-Uh, the next
obstacle's up ahead.
Why don't you go on without me?
-But why?
What are you up to?
-There's something I have to do.
Just go on already.
You're in a hurry, aren't you?
-What the heck's
with him, anyway?
Hey.
Where are you going?
-Ugh.
You fool.
Why are you following me?
-I just wanted to know
where you're going.
[rumbling]
Whoa.
What's that?
-Don't focus on the rocks.
The real enemy's behind them.
[gasping]
-Now die!
-Yah!
Uh.
[sigh]
-Shadow Possession
Jutsu successful.
-Whew.
That sure was a close one, huh?
Heh.
And now I'll show
you what I can do.
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Wait.
Shadow clones?
They're better than I thought.
Retreat.
-Ha, ha.
-You're the Hidden
Rain ninja who
failed to advance
at the Chunin Exam.
What do you want from us?
-Wait, hold on.
Are you guys also trying to
get the Fourth Hokage's legacy,
the ultimate secret?
-Huh?
-Hey, don't tell
him that, numbskull.
-Huh?
-Oh, boy.
Look, don't come after us again.
You got that?
Next time we won't be so nice.
[sigh]
-Fight-- ugh.
Wait, why'd you let them go?
-Can you go a minute without
causing trouble, Naruto?
-Huh?
-Just come on.
We don't have time to deal
with those guys right now.
We have to beat the Fourth
Hokage's record, remember?
-Shikamaru?
What did you guys do?
-Just dealt with a
small distraction.
Have you found out what
the next obstacle is?
-No, not yet.
The tag came off the scroll.
-We don't have time for that.
Come on, let's just go.
-Wait, Naruto.
Argh.
We still haven't deciphered
the whole Tiger Scroll.
-Next is "offer a wildflower."
Huh.
-This sure looks like
the next obstacle to me.
-What do you think this does?
-It says, Retire Button.
I wonder what that means.
-Hey, come back.
Don't just rush in there.
-Huh?
Uh.
Huh?
-What's this?
It's like-- ugh-- sleeping gas.
-Damn.
No!
The door!
-You've got to hold
your breath, Naruto.
-Get to the ceiling.
-So are we locked in here?
-There must be some way
to clear out these fumes.
But how?
-Hey, from up here the floor
looks like a giant flower.
-That's it.
"Offer a wildflower."
Choji, use Human Boulder
and clear out this gas.
Then search the
hole in the floor.
-Gotcha.
Expansion Jutsu!
Human Boulder!
Oof.
SHIKAMARU: Is there
anything down there?
-Uh, hold on.
Um.
Uh.
Oh.
It feels like there's
some kind of switch.
-OK.
Try pressing it.
-Mm-hmm.
[straining]
-That's a whole lot better.
Can you walk, Ino?
-Yeah.
NARUTO: The exit!
Hey, it's a river.
And the path.
This way.
OK, you guys, on
to the next one.
Just follow me.
-Use your brain for a change.
-And what does that mean?
-We need to read this scroll.
We can't afford
any more missteps.
Each of these phrases
seems to give us
all the information we need
to get through the obstacles
ahead.
-Hmm.
-That way we can find
solutions before we even
reach the problems.
-And besides, you're
always jumping the gun
and putting everyone
here in danger, Naruto.
-Aw, don't say that.
I just want to help.
-Shikamaru, what's
the next hint?
-Let's see.
Be very nimble and
show determination.
That's it.
-Be very nimble?
I can do that.
-Ugh.
Naruto, what are you doing?
-Being nimble and determined.
What else?
Huh?
-Oh, you idiot!
-We have no choice.
Jump on!
-Are you even capable
of listening at all?
-I'm just following what the
Tiger Scroll told us to do.
-Um.
-Hey, does the current
seem faster to you guys?
-Uh, you think it's
because of that?
-What?
-Waterfall!
-We're gonna crash
into that big rock.
-Even if you miss the rocks,
you'll go over the waterfall.
-Why'd you say "you," not "we"?
-I'm just assessing
this objectively.
-Stop it, guys.
-At least I'm doing
something to help.
-What did you say?
-Shut up!
Damn.
What does that scroll mean
by "show determination"?
NARUTO: What's that?
-Huh?
-That big rock.
It's a tiny version of the
Leaf's great stone faces.
-What?
-Shikamaru, what do we do?
-Think fast, or
we're gonna crash.
-Huh.
Show determination, huh?
-Determination is
what I do best.
-Naruto.
-No matter what, I'm going to
get the Fourth Hokage's legacy.
-Naruto, how many times do I--
-No.
This time Naruto's right.
Jump to the right.
-Whoa!
-Yah!
Ugh!
Ack!
Oof!
SHIKAMARU: I see.
This was set up
beneath the waterfall.
A rainbow forms on the left
where the water sprays,
but it doesn't on
the right side.
If we'd chosen the left side,
then we would have fallen down.
-Would you hurry up
and move already?
You're really heavy.
-What?
You're calling me heavy?
Why don't you try looking in
the mirror, thunder thighs?
-You heard me.
I'm calling you heavy, Ino pig.
-Oh, stop kidding
yourself, billboard brow.
-This fight has
nothing to do with me.
Yep.
NARUTO: All three of
you are really heavy.
-Hmph!
-Huh?
-What?
-Naruto, you don't
have a shred of tact.
INO: I really do
pity you, Sakura.
Being stuck on a team
with a guy like that?
SAKURA: Tell me about it.
CHOJI: No doubt.
-What?
What did I do?
All right, we've reached
the final obstacle.
[gasping]
-Ino, what's this?
-Choji, knock it off.
-Sorry, Naruto, but we're
going alone from here on out.
-We're taking the Fourth
Hokage's legacy for ourselves.
-But wait.
It's just not fair.
-We're going to make sure
Shikamaru wins no matter
what it takes.
-This is our chance, Shikamaru.
CHOJI: Shikamaru?
SHIKAMARU: Go beyond hatred.
For the one who approaches,
the path will not open.
That's what the rest
of the scroll says.
And maybe what that's
trying to tell us
is that the path
won't open if you
have a falling out
with your comrades.
[chuckling]
-Now you're starting to
sound like a decent guy.
You're really becoming
a pain, you know?
-Ha, ha, ha.
A noble idea, Shikamaru.
[sigh]
-Somehow I just
knew that everything
was going to turn out like this.
-Shikamaru?
-Yeah?
Uh.
Um.
-Let's get through this
together and meet in the finals.
SHIKAMARU: Here, this is yours.
Keep it.
-You actually think you're
going to be in the finals?
-She's right.
Sasuke's the one who's
going to advance and win.
-Aw.
-Well, as long as it's
someone from the Hidden Leaf.
That's all I care about.
-Yeah.
Now, that's the right attitude.
All right, let's go!
-Too bad for you.
You guys won't make it
to the final rounds.
You won't be as
lucky as last time.
[laughter]
-Whoa.
SAKURA: All these scrolls have
secret techniques inside them?
SHIKAMARU: Uh, I don't know.
SAKURA: And we're supposed
to find the Hokage's legacy
in one of them?
-Aw.
-And time's still ticking away
on the Fourth Hokage's record
while we search.
-Ugh.
Look, we know the
Fourth Hokage's legacy
is here somewhere.
We'll open every single
scroll if we have to.
SHIKAMARU: Stop.
-Huh?
-Look at the size of this place.
And who knows what kind of
traps have been set here.
-Argh.
-Besides, look at the scrolls.
They're probably
all fakes anyway.
-They're all fake?
-That's right.
And it would take the
five of us several days
to search through
them all to find
the real one among
the forgeries.
We'd never break the Fourth
Hokage's record time that way.
There has to be something.
Something.
Some way.
-A way to do what?
-Aw, use your head, Naruto.
-Stupid Naruto.
-That's a terrible thing to say.
ACCUSING VOICE: Stupid.
That's stupid.
Stupid.
-Give me a break.
Stop saying that, Sakura.
-No, that wasn't me.
-Huh?
-Stupid.
Stupid.
Stupid Naruto.
-Hey, knock it off, parrot.
Just who do you think you
are, calling me stupid?
-Stupid Naruto.
Stupid Naruto.
-Argh!
Quit calling me stupid,
you stupid bird!
-Stupid Naruto.
Stupid.
-What?
You little--
-Ninja art, Grudge Rain.
One on one, we
can't overcome them.
But if we gather up
our grudge and use
it to put a curse on them
with this Jutsu, then we can.
[thunder rumbling]
Envelop them in
this cursed cloud
and rain our grudge
down upon them.
PARROT: Stupid Naruto.
NARUTO: Come down here!
PARROT: Stupid.
Stupid Naruto.
Rawk!
NARUTO: Stupid parrot.
-A flood?
SAKURA: Shikamaru!
-Whoa!
[gurgling]
-My chakra.
-What's going on?
SAKURA: My strength.
I'm draining away.
-This is no ordinary water.
-This rain will leach
away all of your chakra.
It's a deluge of bitter
tears from all of the grudges
that we hold against you.
SASUKE: You guys were knocked
out of the Chunin Exam.
-What are you doing here?
-I usually don't like
to do what Kakashi says.
-He's that guy.
-But I have to agree.
This is the perfect
chance to test my Jutsu.
-Sasuke Uchiha!
Be-- betrayed!
-Wait, Samidare.
-What?
-He's acting strange.
This could be our big chance.
-Forget it.
No way.
-Get him!
-Yah!
-Eeyargh!
[thumps and groans]
(PAINED) He's strong.
I knew it.
We don't stand a
chance against someone
who made it to the final rounds.
[groaning]
-It looks like
we're safe for now.
Was that part of the trap?
-Well, I'm starving.
I'd better eat.
-Gimme, gimme.
-Stop, thief!
-Thank you.
-Huh?
Naruto, get close to the parrot.
-Yummy, yummy.
Rawk.
Yummy.
-I got you.
Now's my chance to catch
that annoying parrot
and teach him a lesson.
SHIKAMARU: No.
-Huh?
-You're going to have to smile.
Look friendly when you approach.
-What?
You want me to smile at him?
How, like this?
Hello there, little parrot.
You want to be friends?
-Ah, it's stupid Naruto.
Stupid Naruto.
SHIKAMARU: Smile, Naruto.
-Ah, come on.
[straining]
Ah.
-How creepy is that?
-Just act more natural.
-Yeah, sure.
That's easy for you to say.
[giggling]
-Look, all you have to do is
think about something fun.
-Sakura.
-You know Shikamaru must
have something planned.
You can do this, Naruto.
-All right.
If you say so, Sakura, then
I'm going to do my best.
-Now smile.
Don't forget that part.
SAKURA: Yeah, just like that.
CHOJI: Good.
-Fun thoughts, fun thoughts.
Like that I'll become
a chunin and go
on a real lovey-dovey
date with Sakura.
That's the ticket.
Yeah, that's the one.
[chuckling]
-Yucky.
[laughing]
SHIKAMARU: Go beyond hatred.
For the one who approaches,
the path will not open.
SAKURA: And I guess that
meant the gate wouldn't
open as long as Naruto
kept chasing the parrot.
-Huh?
It's here, the Fourth
Hokage's legacy.
SHIKAMARU: The final
lines of the poem.
The location of infinity
falls to the anointed one.
-Whoa.
Does that mean the scroll
contains everything
that we were after?
-I guess, although there
could some unimaginable trap.
-No way.
I trust the Tiger Scroll.
I mean, that wise old
sage gave it to us.
-That's why it's suspect.
-Huh?
-Huh.
-Hmm.
-Huh?
[laughing]
-Guy Sensei?
-What are you doing here?
-Tell us!
-Shikamaru?
What the heck are you
three talking about?
Where do you guys see
bushier-brows Sensei?
-Ugh.
-Naruto still believes
that's really an old sage.
-Well, wise old sage?
So what's the deal?
Did we break the
Fourth Hokage's record?
Did we make it?
Please, I really, really want
the Fourth Hokage's legacy.
I just gotta have
it if I'm gonna
make it through
the final rounds.
-Ahem.
-Um.
-Well?
Well?
-Good job.
You five shattered the Fourth
Hokage's previous record.
-Yes!
-And now I shall present
you with the Fourth Hokage's
legacy, the ultimate secret.
-Mm-hmm?
Mm-hmm?
-OK.
Just read the first character
of each verse across the page.
Goodbye and good luck, you.
-That's so obvious.
NARUTO: Um, let's see.
Close the blade.
And then you shall
calm the heart.
Hold on.
I don't get it.
What's it mean?
-A blade with a
heart means ninja.
-Oh, yeah.
Thanks.
All right, then.
It spells out, there's no
shortcut to becoming a ninja.
-Huh?
-Aw.
-Nice work.
-Thanks.
I think it gave him some good
training for the final rounds.
-And we were able to
assess their mastery
of their techniques.
Sasuke, you're taking too
long to release that Jutsu.
You'd better not use
it in the final rounds.
-I know.
-We're leaving, Guy.
Sasuke still needs to
do some more training.
-You bet.
Just leave the rest to me.
-I can't believe this.
Was this whole thing just a
joke Guy Sensei played on us?
-I know.
I'm just as disappointed as you.
-And setting up such
dangerous traps was just mean.
Doesn't he have anything
better to do with his time?
SHIKAMARU: Don't be
so quick to judge him.
-What do you mean?
-Didn't any of you
guys notice what
happened after we went through
all of those obstacles?
-Huh?
-At first we were
all only thinking
about our own
individual team winning.
-Oh.
Yeah, that's true.
And now we just want someone
from our village to win.
It doesn't matter who.
-Mm-hmm.
-Hmm.
NARUTO: I've got it!
-Huh?
-I know what the Fourth
Hokage's legacy means.
See, "no shortcut" means we
have to take the long way.
Sakura, Shikamaru, Choji, Ino.
We have to do the
obstacle course again,
but take the long way.
-Argh!
-Boy, he really is such a pain.
-Stupid Naruto.
NAGATO (VOICEOVER):
And the very next day,
the final rounds of
the Chunin Exam began.
[MUSIC - SUPERCELL, "UTAKATA
HANABI"]
-I want to hear your stories.
Then I'll give you
my final response.
-Very well.
We'll tell you everything
about our pain.
-Nagato, it's a waste of time.
Just deal with him now.
-Wait, Konan.
I want to hear his response.
After all, he did
crush the Six Pains
and make it here all by himself.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next time
on "Naruto Shippuden," meeting.
-Two moments define
my greatest pain.
[MUSIC - SUPERCELL, "UTAKATA
HANABI"]