[Temari]
Kankuro, You're late!
[Kankuro]
Assembling my new puppets
took longer than I thought.
Goodbye Lord Kazekage!
Please take care!
Lord Kankuro, Lady Temari.
We're counting on you.
Yeah, we know.
But Gaara doesn't
really need bodyguards.
Why are we going?
Come on. Time to go.
Among all the Five Kage,
Gaara's gonna be the
youngest one.
It's our duty to make
sure the other Kage
don't take him lightly.
A Five Kage Summit.
You know, I can't help
but wonder what all the
other Kage are like.
Kurotsuchi, Akatsuchi,
good luck!
Lord Tsuchikage!
Go teach all those
other village leaders
a thing or two!
Augh! Going to summits
at my age is such a chore.
All those young'uns
romping around with no
regard for my discomfort.
They forget about
my bad back?
Well, gramps, Why don't
you just retire, then?
I mean, why bother trying to
drag out the glory?
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Here, let me carry
that pack for you.
Okay, Lord Tsuchikage?
D'rrrrgh!
Hands off, Akatsuchi!
I can get this!
[old man grumbling]
Grm... Whippersnappers..
Heh hah! It's nothing! See?
[crack]
Aa-aaah!
My back!
Listen, Gramps,
You wanna send
someone else instead?
Why you impudent little fool!
Just who do you think I am?!
I am Tsuchikage Ohnoki,
the Great Fence Sitter
of the Hidden Stone!
Hmph! I shall carry
my own pack, thankyou!
Hrr-r-r-r-r...
H'augh!
[sigh] What did you expect?
You stubborn geezer...
Very well, you may carry your
own pack if you really want to.
All right! Let's be off!
Of all the insolent...
Fine, I don't care!
Admit it, Gramps,
that's better, isn't it?
We entrust the
honorable Mizukage
to your care.
Make sure the Mizukage
doesn't overdo it.
I know; I will.
Thank you very much.
Lord Great Elder,
By my title of Mizukage,
I'll fulfill my duties
with brilliance.
Heh-heh heh
heh heh!
As one of the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen of the Mist,
Protect Lady Mizukage
well, Chojuro.
Uh, Yes, sir. All three of
us should be just fine.
Well, I hope.
You should have more confidence
in yourself. You're very strong.
After all, That's why I
chose you to accompany
me to the summit.
'kay, Chojuro?
Uh... Yes, ma'am!
I'll do my
absolute best!
Well, I hope.
She's so kind.
Yes, ma'am's all
you should say!
That spineless attitude
is useless!
The youths these
days are just all
made of weakness.
Old maid...?
Ao! Enough with the lecturing!
Now get moving or you're going
to be late!
It's too late...
for marriage?!!
My lecture's good advice!
Why, back in my day...
Shut up. Or die.
Uhh??
All right, Chojuro!
Ao! Let's depart!
I shall defend kind Lady
Mizukage's smile to the
best of my abilities!
I hope I can...
Uhhn...
What are you doing, Ao?
Lady Mizukage's leaving!
Huh?!
Oh, no!
Lady Mizukage! Please wait!
[Raikage]
Still no word
from Team Samui?!
No, sir. All communication has
been silent. But I do expect
to hear something soon.
Samui has already been informed
of the route you will be taking
to the summit, Lord Raikage.
The plan is for her to
rendezvous with you directly
or send a messenger bird.
Good! All right, then.
I'll be heading out, too!
Let's go! Cee! Darui!
Sir!
Sure.
Come along!
[sigh] Not again!
Let's go, Darui.
No, thanks. I'll just take the
stairs like normal people.
You go on ahead,
I'll catch up.
Enter the Five Kage!
Lord Danzo, sir.
I know.
I haven't seen battle
in quite a while.
This is a perfect chance to get
my muscles limbered up again.
Do not interfere.
I'll take care of them.
[sharp inhale]
Augh! Hungh! Oof!
Is your target the Hokage?
Or are you after me personally?
Please... just kill me...
Well, not that it
really matters.
Seven, eight, nine, ten...
Seventeen total, eh?
Okay! I'm ready to go!
No, this whole thing
is far from okay!
Are you serious about
going to meet the Raikage?
Of course! I'm going
to convince him to
forgive Sasuke!
But that being said,
you don't even know
where the Raikage is!
You know, I bet you
could help him with
that, Yamato.
What?!
See ya!
Kakashi, you gotta be kidding.
I'm here to challenge you,
Big Brother Naruto!
Huh? wait, I know
that voice...
Uh!
I'd appreciate it if didn't tell
the Hokage of Naruto's plans.
Oh...
Say nothing's going on.
I see. So it appears that
you still can't bring
yourself to trust me.
Well you are Danzo's
subordinate, assigned
to spy on Naruto.
But you're also a
member of Team 7,
my Team Kakashi.
So I do believe in you.
There was one
other thing he said:
he believed in me!
What is this that I'm feeling?
Catch you later!
Hm.
Auugghh!
[gurgle]
These are remnants of the
Hannya Black Ops from the
Land of Woods that we
slew in the past.
It has always
been like this.
Foe seizing a
chance to strike.
Your coming into the open
may increase our headaches
in lots of ways.
Ninja once belonged to
a world of ascetics.
To be nameless was a
source of pride.
By controlling what's
seen and what's hidden,
one can truly strengthen
village and nation.
I will make sure that this
summit is a success and that
I am acknowledged as Hokage.
Then even the Jonin Council will
have no choice but to accept me.
At last, my time
has finally come.
Hey, what's
going on?
I have no idea.
What are they doing?
Haaa!
Sexy Jutsu!
[gasps]
Sweet dreams. Enjoy those
illusions of Naruto.
Or were you interested
in their Sexy Jutsu?
So sorry.
It seems the Foundation is
beginning not to trust Sai.
Hmm.
Awww!!
Yours is way
sexier than mine!
Now...
Damn it! No way! I lose again!
You always keep widening the
gap between us, Big Bro.
We're supposed to be
rivals, you know!
Hey, I heard!
Huh?
Someone told me that you
took down one of the Pains
with your Rasengan!
Mmh.
I only pulled it off
'cause I was desperate.
Huh?
You did a good job,
Konohamaru!
You're a hero of the
Hidden Leaf Village, too!
You know, you pick up
things quicker than I do!
Next time, I'll teach you how
to do the Giant Rasengan!
Yeah!
My hand hurts from
all this writing!
What if I get
tendonitis and
it affects my
sword skills?
And that shortcoming
leads to me going
down in battle...
And despite the frantic
efforts of all the girls on
the Medical Team, then I die.
Keep moving your hand,
not your tongue, big mouth!
Hmm...
We gotta copy the Intel on
Sasuke and the Akatsuki,
Now hurry up or we're
going to be here forever!
'Scuse me, could you
please try to keep
your voices down?
Of course. My apologies.
[Karui]
Aahh! We're finally done!
Calm down. You two have
gotta be cool if you want
to call yourselves Shinobi!
All right, let's hurry
to Lord Raikage!
Got it.
Yeah!
[Yamato]
Sorry, but you are now
carrying my Signal Seeds.
Despite my demeanor,
I'm pretty good at tailing.
Now then, I'd better contact
Kakashi and Naruto.
I keep wondering if that
Naruto kid is doing okay.
Auggh!!
If you say another word
about it, I'm gonna
pummel you, too, Omoi!
Oh? So you are worried!
I told you not
to say anything!
Boy! Your hands are
as quick as ever!
Alright. It's time
to tail them.
Let's go!
[Mizukage]
Chojuro...
Your Great Twin Sword
Hiramekarei must be
quite a burden.
Are you all right
carrying it?
Oh. I'm fine.
Though I'm feeling
a bit feverish.
Let's see...
Well, it does feel
like you might have a
slight temperature.
Lady Fifth, you spoil
Chojuro too much!
This is why the young these days
get so full of themselves!
He spikes a temperature
from such a short jaunt?!
Why, in my day I--!
Ao...
It's no longer the dark
time when we were called
the Blood Mist Village.
The nightmare created by the
Fourth Mizukage is long over.
You'd do well not to
bring up the past.
Yes, I--
Forgive me, ma'am.
Now, let's stop such
depressing talk, and have
some supper instead.
I'm looking forward to the
meal this inn has made.
Ah!?
I hope you've engaged
an appetizing dinner.
Mh.
Engaged?
As in, to be married!
You have arranged
for all of our
meals, haven't
you, Chojuro?
There were just
so many choices!
So I had a lot of
trouble making up
my mind!
In the end, I
couldn't decide.
In the end...
[Ao]
You vacillating fool!
Agh! Youth these days
have voided hearts!
And no ambition!
Voided...?
Please, forgive me!
I'll make arrangements now!
My engagement.
There was a lot of trouble.
And in the end,
it was voided!
Back in my day...
Huh?
Shut up. Or die.
[Ao]
Why?!
Man, it is really
getting cold out.
The Land of Iron is just a
stone's throw away from here.
Hold on. There's
something just up ahead!
What?
This is my first trip
to the Land of Iron.
I'm really excited!
Oh, please.
It really isn't
such a nice place.
Why don't you tell us
what it's like, Gramps?
It lies among three mountains
known as the Three Wolves.
It's a neutral state
possessing powerful battle
strength as well as a unique
culture and their own laws.
(cm eating efforts)
So tell me, how are its
culture and law different from
that of the Land of Earth?
There's a long-standing
rule that shinobi shall
not engage them,
and in fact, the Land
of Iron does not have
any shinobi at all.
Instead, it is
defended by samurai.
[gasp]
Well?
They've fortified their
defenses because of the
Five Kage Summit.
Jugo, listen.
You have to use
the animals.
And scout out the
least-defended route you can
find to the Summit site.
Right, I'm on it.
We've been awaiting your
arrival, Lord Kazekage.
Welcome.
I am Mifune, the General
in this Land of Iron.
(ct shivering reax)
I'm pleased to meet you. I'm the
Kazekage, Gaara.
[Kankuro]
Man, it's cold!
The climate here's
totally different than
the Land of Wind!
[Mifune]
We can serve you some hot
tea to warm you up. Enter.
Aah, AAH--
Achoo!
Shh!
Brr! Boy, it just got really
cold all of a sudden.
Hey, we're on a
stealth mission!
So, shh!
Well, then?
There's a route that
climbs up from the West.
Not too many lookouts.
Karin, keep an eye on the
chakra positions of the guards.
It's time to go in.
What? I'm coming, too?!
Yep, it's finally time
for you to let those
skills of yours shine.
Zetsu, right?
That's right.
I need you to confirm
which one is Danzo.
You're coming too.
Looks like a
message from Sai.
What is it?
Nothing, it's just
a routine report.
Let's go.
Can't we just ambush
and off him now?
I'm pooped already.
What are you,
stupid?!
If the Hokage's arrival
is delayed, they'll know
that something happened
to him on the way there.
Then they'll send in a swarm
of samurai reinforcements.
And what if the other Kage
come, too, huh?
We don't know the enemy's
abilities, you idiot, so it's
best to bide our time and just
attack him on his way home.
Right, Sasuke?
Hgh.
Just focus on the enemy's
chakra positions, Karin.
Ha ha! Busted.
Shut up!
Wow, Sasuke, It
seems you have
your hands full.
All that matters is that
you identify Danzo before
the Summit starts.
You'd better not lie.
That's right, I'm attuned
to chakra. And a person's
chakra always becomes
muddied when they lie.
So just remember, I'll
be keeping an eye on
your chakra, got it?
There's no reason to lie to you.
After all, Danzo is a hindrance
to the Akatsuki too.
Lord Raikage, it's Team Samui.
Good. Let's descend!
My lord, We've returned from
the Hidden Leaf Village.
And how did it
go there?
Samui, you've
been tailed.
What?
Show yourselves,
you Hidden Leaf dogs!
[growl]
We need to talk, right now!
[Yamato]
Lord Raikage, your attempt to
obtain the Hyuga Byakugan is
still unresolved on our side.
[Yamato]
Do not forget the
Leaf's sacrifices.
[Kakashi]
This young shinobi is bowing
his head in affection for Cloud
and Leaf, village and nation.
[Kakashi]
Lord Raikage, as one of the Five
Kage, what do you think of this?
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden, "Naruto's Plea."
[Raikage]
Hmph.
How foolish.