Minato, you intended for
your brat to clean up
after your mess, right?
That's why you sealed my
leftover half inside him, as
if you were confident they'd
be able to work together.
Nine Tails...
Then don't regret it now.
It's not your
fault Kushina died.
And making your brat
a Jinchuriki wasn't
a bad thing either.
Because right now, he's the
one trying to change what
this world has become.
He's not that
newborn baby anymore.
In fact, tomorrow is...
Naruto...
Listen up, I've got
something to tell you.
[chuckle] Yes! I knew it!
It's just like I thought!
I can't believe that
the Ten Tails' Jinchuriki
has such a weakness!
And with Ten Tails
inside me, I can't pass
through things either!
How frustrating!
Sage moves will
work, you guys!
What is this Sage Power?
You know, toad attacks.
Those are Sage Jutsu, and
they employ Nature Energy.
Come to think of it, when I
tried to gauge Ten Tails'
power, it was
Nature Energy itself.
So maybe you can
counter nature Energy
with Nature Energy!
I mean, not that I
really understand it all...
I'm just glad that I
learned Sage Jutsu!
All right!
He'll get a frog
punch to the face!
He instantly grasped how to
use the Flying Raijin with
me and has even
mastered Sage Power.
I feel like I'm fighting
alongside Elder Brother!
It clearly
worked, but look...
He's recovered already
and is guarding his back.
If we teleport
behind him carelessly,
we might get erased.
I should start
preparing for the Tsukuyomi.
So let's tidy things up.
[gasps]
There truly is
nothing that's worth
saving in this reality.
This whole world
is already dead.
This is super bad!
Four of them?!
And all at once?!
Even if we all made an
Earth Style Wall, it-
it wouldn't work!
There's too many of them!
What do we do?
Think!
We'd need one person
to teleport each of
those with Flying Raijin.
The Fourth and I can
get two, but that
leaves two others!
It's impossible!
Where's Elder Brother?!
Madara!
Just wait a moment!
That comrade of
yours is acting up!
We are all Reanimations!
There's no need to worry!
Keep fighting!
Do not give
up, everyone!
I am with you
through my clones!
We only need to
change the trajectories
of those spheres!
The other Hokage will
also take measures
and repel them
across the ocean!
Put up an Earth Style Wall!
I'll use Deep Forest
Emergence to launch and
guide them toward the ocean!
I won't let you!
Six Crimson Ray Formation!
A barrier!
Hey!
Wait, don't tell me
that all of us...
He's trapped us inside the
barrier and made it so we
can't expel the
Tailed Beast Bombs!
This is the endgame.
All we can do is teleport
them outside the barrier
using Flying Raijin.
Lord Fourth, can
you handle two?
Since we aren't able to mark
them, I can only take one.
But there is
one other way...
We could...
You intend to teleport
the stalk itself outside?
You think I'd allow that?
You cannot save anyone now!
Dad...
I don't know if this
will work or not,
but I've got an idea.
So will you give
me a fist bump?
Hey, other half!
How've ya been?
Would you mind sharing
some of your chakra with me?
[chuckle]
You know, to be
asked a favor from
myself is a bit weird.
Naruto, face it,
Minato's useless.
He wasn't even able to
protect your mother!
Nor his subordinates.
You know what
tomorrow is, don't you?
It is the
anniversary of their deaths.
The day both
your parent's died.
In this world, it's
over when you die.
You see...
Oh, right.
Which means it's also
the day I was born!
So you see...
It's not over...
Because I exist
in this world!
Our Naruto sure has
grown very strong, Kushina!
Now, let's go, Dad!
All right!
Thank goodness for the
chakra from you two!
It's just as I thought!
Yeah, well, the two of us
used to be one, after all.
Plus...
...those two are
father and son.
He's planning to trap us
inside this barrier and blow
us up along with it!
What can we do?
The Hokage's barrier
didn't let Tailed Beast
Bombs through, either.
As far as I can tell,
this barrier's red.
I think it's accurate to say
that this one's likely on
par with the Hokage's.
With our level of strength,
it's impossible for us to
smash through it,
in which case...
Nah!
Nothing's
coming to mind, Dad!
So what's your plan, Naruto?
Just give me
some time to focus.
Let me explain what
Kurama and I came up with.
And then you tell me if
it'll work or not, okay?
Yeah, all right.
Go ahead and tell me!
Have you had a chance to
meet him already, Kushina?
Our Naruto's
really grown up.
I'm so sorry, Naruto.
I'm sure it's been
a long, hard road for
you up until now.
The real hard part is
about to start now, Dad!
[gasp]
Wait, this is Naruto's-!
So, then it
wasn't depleted?!
I noticed it when I
was healing everyone.
It seems that it
had merely shrunk.
It's actually bigger and
more powerful than before!
Have ya noticed, Eight-o?
I sense two Nine Tails,
one light and one dark, yo!
This isn't just Nine Tails.
So then you're
thinking about
protecting us all
from that attack with
this chakra, Naruto?
Jugo, what is it?
Sasuke.
This is looking bad.
Let's get
outside this barrier.
Use the Snake
Reverse Summoning.
That was my plan.
I'm going to take you
and Naruto with me.
I haven't given you two
any of my chakra yet.
Get over here, will ya?
[chuckle]
What is your chakra
going to accomplish?
There's no time!
Just hurry!
Whoa, I can't believe
he shared his chakra
with every other shinobi!
He's got almost as
much chakra as I do!
Hold on!
This has Nine
Tails' Chakra mixed in!
That won't help you
withstand the shock wave of
four Ten Tails Tailed Beast
Bombs exploding together!
Be gone!
How could--?
I guess this chakra has
protected us once again!
Not quite.
Check it out, you guys.
Choji!
Look there!
All of us are
outside the barrier!
Teleportation Jutsu!
Damn that Naruto!
He's managed to
master that, too?!
But this isn't
only Naruto's chakra.
He moved everyone
using the Fourth
Hokage's Flying
Raijin Jutsu!
[chuckle]
Well done, Lord Fourth.
By my count, this is the
second time that you have
saved all of shinobi-kind.
[gasps] But I've failed
more than that.
So I must keep...
...making amends.
What did you do?
Oh, nothing much.
Dad just teleported
every single person
outside the barrier.
Everyone?!
With that jutsu?!
I simply can't teleport
anything that I myself, or
my chakra, isn't
touching directly.
But how did?!
It's because I'd already
shared Kurama's chakra and
my chakra with
everyone earlier on.
So if Dad and our
chakra and everyone
were to, uhh, well...
Were to indirectly...
That's right!
If we were all in indirect
contact, it would work!
So, I connected Dad's chakra
with Kurama's and mine.
That's all there was to it!
He was using the
principle of Shadow Clones.
Even if you split up and
disperse your chakra, if you
keep even a little bit there
without putting it out
when the original body
infuses chakra again to
regain control, all the
individual chakra bits
resonate and link together.
In short, by joining his
chakra with the Fourth's,
Naruto effectively linked
the Fourth to the rest of
his chakra that was
residing in everyone else.
Is that right, Naruto?
Huh?
Is that what it was?
Never mind.
Old Man Second, you
sure know a lot about
my Shadow Clones!
I came up with that jutsu!
So it's my jutsu!
[chuckle]
So will you give
me a fist bump?
Yeah!
Yeah, let's try it!
'Cause we can do anything
if we borrow Nine Tails', I
mean, Kurama's power.
Right!
Then let's all four
of us join forces now!
All four of us?
You treat us like
we're human, too!
What kind of
childrearing led to this?!
[chuckling]
Naruto...
I wish there were more time
to talk to the grown-up you!
Yeah, me, too, but
guys don't need to talk!
Plus, I already know!
I...
I already met
Mom's chakra, dad...
Kushina, I'm not
gonna last much longer.
I'll start the Eight
Signed Seal, right now.
I still want to put some
of my chakra in Naruto.
We won't see him
for quite a while.
So let's tell him
what we want to say.
Naruto, don't be
a picky eater.
Just eat a lot so you
grow up big and strong.
And make sure that you
bathe every day and
that you stay warm, too.
Also, don't stay
up too late.
Make sure you get
plenty of sleep.
Don't forget, to
make friends as well.
You don't need a
ton of them, okay?
Just a few is fine.
As long as they're ones
that you can really trust.
And your mom wasn't
very good at this.
Make sure you study hard
and learn your ninjutsu.
Always remember everyone is
good at some things and not
so good at others, so even
if something doesn't go well
don't get depressed, okay?
When you're at the Academy
respect your teachers and
the upperclassmen.
Oh!
Now, this is important
regarding the Three
Prohibitions of
the shinobi.
Be extra careful about
lending and borrowing money.
Take your pay.
Put it in a savings account.
No alcohol, not
until you're of age!
Too much sake is bad for
you, so practice moderation.
And another
prohibition is women.
Remember, I am one.
So I don't know
too much about it...
Keep in mind that this world
is made up of men and women.
And so at some point,
you'll notice girls,
and that's normal.
Just be careful don't
fall for the bad ones.
Just go out there and
find someone who's like me!
Oh, uh, that reminds me.
Speaking of the Three
Prohibitions, you should be
wary of Jiraiya
Sensei, ya know.
Naruto, I'm sorry to say
there will be plenty of
hardships and
painful times ahead.
Just be true to yourself.
Make sure to have
dreams and the confidence
to make those
dreams come true!
Oh, Naruto.
There's so much,
oh so much more.
There are so many
things I wish I had the
time to pass on to you.
So much more I
want to tell you!
I wish I could
stay with you longer.
I love you!
Minato, I'm sorry!
I used up your time!
No, it's all right.
Naruto, my words to you.
Well, I guess your
talkative mom...
Said it all...
What you want to say
to me is the same as
my talkative mom, right?
See, I already know!
[chuckle]
[gasp]
Just what exactly is this?!
It's the Divine Tree!
It's Ten Tail's final form!
Chakra first originated
with this Divine Tree!
What're you saying?!
We humans stole chakra from
the Divine Tree long ago.
This thing is merely trying
to get it back, that's all.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The
Divine Tree."
Do you know how
and why shinobi
came to be, Hashirama?