Sakura.... I leave
Naruto in your hands.
...He's always been
our village's symbol
of hope...
...Ever since that
time everyone has
always...
What did Lord
Jiraya tell you?
Seems the training's
going well.
[heavy breathing]
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Giant Rasengan!
[explosion]
The power of your Rasengan
has seriously grown! And
after only 2 years of training!
Perhaps it's about time that
that we took things to the next
level...
To the next level?
Yep!
What're we
gonna do?
I think perhaps the time
has come for you to
utilize your inner power.
Wait, you mean...?
Mhm. You might have to
put your life on the line
for this training.
All right. I'm
ready. Bring it on!
Can't believe it's
been two years already.
Now the day that kid
returns home to the
Leaf may soon be upon us!
(Shizune)
Naruto is a mysterious boy. He's
been away from the village for
two whole years, and yet...
[grunt]
Inuzuka Style! Man-Beast
Transformation Combo!
Two-Headed Wolf!
Wolf Fang Over Fang!
(Shizune)
His impact on everyone
just keeps growing...
[panting]
Are you all right?
I think I'm
at my limit!
Only ten more laps! If you
stop now, then Naruto is just
going to laugh at you!
Everyone always seems to keep
Naruto in their thoughts while
they're training!
Looks like we've
got a message.
Where's it from?
Lord Kazegake!
A Shinobi Hawk has  just deliv-
ered a missive to you from the
Hidden Leaf's Fifth Hokage, sir.
Hm.
'Bout time. I was
getting tired
of waiting.
Look who they sent
for our welcome. Thanks
for meeting us.
Heh heh. Well, it is
a drag, but seeing as
it's Lord Kazekage...
Welcome to
the Leaf.
Here's the data from
the Chunin Exams two
years ago.
One hundred fifty three
entrants total. Information
about their villages,
the three rounds of exams, and
the qualifying stats have been
compiled for easy reading.
But you'd know more about the
reason behind the interruption
of the finalrounds and the
chronology.
Ahem. Because of the suspension
of the previous Chunin Exams,
the Leaf would like to sponsor a
brand new combined Chunin Exams.
Thanks in part to the Leaf's
help, the situation in the
Sand has stabilized since then.
In particular, our training
curriculum has now become
very successful.
We have more genin qualified
to take the Chunin Exams.
Then you have no objection
to us sponsoring an event?
Lady Hokage... first, what's
your true motive here?
My "true motive?"
The timing of this
whole thing, why hold
the Chunin Exams now?
If it's a personnel
shortage, you still
could've done this sooner.
All right, then.
I'll be honest
with you.
First, its to gauge the response
of each of the villages in the
Five Great Nations...
On the surface they seem
to be at peace, and yet...
Their response to holding
the combined Chunin Exams
will reveal their true feelings.
And the second reason is
to probe the movements
of the Akatsuki.
Our intel says that they're
seeking the Tailed Beasts
from each village,
but they've been awfully
quiet for these past 2 years
you want to open the
Village and use the Chunin
Exams as some kind of bait?
you want to attempt to
lure the Akatsuki out?
That's right.
I'm betting the Akatsuki have
grown impatient and are getting
ready to make a move soon.
That is a risky
proposition...
Hold on.
The Sand would like to host
these Chunin Exams alongside my
introduction as Kazekage.
[gasp]
Hm.
That will not do.
The Hidden Leaf must be
the one to sponsor
these Chunin Exams
so we may finish what
we previously started.
Absolutely.
Lord Kazekage cannot decide
this all by himself, of
course.
He must talk with
the village advisors.
That's right. So we're going to
need some time to contact them.
Let's come back to this.
We'll discuss it again
at the next meeting.
All right. We'll
settle this during
the next meeting, then.
This whole thing has
become a real drag.
Yeah. I didn't expect
Gaara to make an
announcement like that.
He really didn't tell
you anything at all?
No, it came out
of nowhere!
Well, Gaara has his own
ideas about the way
things should be done.
(Gaara)
I leave it to you.
If the Hokage's right and
the Akatsuki make a move,
you know you're going to
be their target!
If the enemy wants Tailed
Beasts, they'll come for
me sooner or later.
So I'll simply act as
bait and just take
them down.
What are you saying!?
The Village welcomed
you as their new Kazekage
...but things are
still unstable!
I am aware.
I know some aren't
happy that I've
become Kazegake.
And I have no doubt there
are those who would welcome
an opportunity to kill me...
Then why'd you even
consider hosting the
event?
That's why I want the
Chunin Exams in the Sand.
You must be joking!
You don't want the Akatsuki,
you want to lure out the
conspirators in our village!
That's way too
dangerous, Gaara.
In regards to the combined
Chunin Exams,
it's Lord Kazekage's wish
that we host the event
in the Hidden Sand Village.
And he also intends to introduce
himself as Kazekage to the other
nations.
Is that a
wise choice?
Though things have been
quiet for a while now,
it doesn't change the fact that
Gaara's a military weapon to be
feared.
To be honest, as long as Gaara
continues to live, this village
can never  truly be at peace.
For the second round
of the Chunin Exams
Lord Gaara intends
to offer up the Demon Desert
as a suitable arena.
And we, the Hidden Sand,
will do our utmost to
support him!
I'm sure that Yuura
is onto us by now.
No, everyone's
just uneasy about
Gaara.
Still, that isn't enough to
build a coup d'état around,
and I--
Well now, if it isn't my
seniors. Of all the places
to find you three.
What do you want now?
All of us have already
agreed to give our support
to Lord Gaara's plan.
It's nothing, really.
I just forgot to tell you.
Lord Gaara plans to
personally supervise
the exam site.
We'll have to be very
careful with our
preparations.
The second round is a survival
test, and--- there are always
some fatalities.
So who's to say that nothing
will happen to the supervisor
himself, our Kazekage, Lord
Gaara.
Now, if you'll
excuse me...
This is the perfect opportunity
to get rid of the Kazekage
and make it look like
it was an accident...
But... he is a
Jinchuriki.
There's a way.
The first Jinchuriki, Sir
Bunpuku, was able to temporarily
seal Shukaku in a teapot.
Maybe we can use that.
What's your decision,
Lady Tsunade?
Hm...
...Two years ago, Jiraya's intel
said the Akatsuki would target
Naruto in three of four years.
We tried to learn their plans
with no success. It's now
two years later.
I'm fully convinced that by
this time, they're practically
itching to make a move.
You're not thinking
of using Naruto as bait!?
No, as Fifth Hokage of
the Hidden Leaf, I could
never do that.
You mean, Lord Gaara
will assume that role?
As luck would have
it, he's the one
who proposed it.
But... will the
advisors agree
to that?!
Well, I'll just have to
placate them by suggesting
a joint sponsorship.
We can't negotiate
any further.
(Tsunade)
I reviewed the plans
that you submitted,
Lord Kazekage.
What do you think about the idea
of a joint sponsorship with the
Hidden Leaf?
We'll hold round one,
the written exam, in
the Leaf Village...
...and the Hidden Sand will host
the site of the second round,
the survival test.
The Forest of Death
really has become too
familiar as a test site.
I was just thinking
recently that a new
site would be needed.
I agree as well.
We've no objections
to that proposal.
All right, then. I guess we'll
see you again at the Chunin
exams.
Yeah...
Just let us know if any
trouble arises, all right?
We'll handle it, Mr. Crybaby.
Heh, she hasn't
changed a bit.
The Hidden Sound
probably won't take
part this time around.
Should we just send out
invitations to everyone else who
attended the last Chunin Exams?
Send invitations for
the introduction of the new
Kazekage to every village in the
Five Great Nations.
I see. That way we
can monitor each
village's response.
That's right. In addition
to the Akatsuki problem,
that's the other reason for
reopening the combined Chunin
Exams.
Okay. I
understand, M'Lady.
These invites are for the
Chunin Exams. Go and
deliver them to every Village.
(Anbu Ops)
Yes ma'am.
Well, we've set
out the bait...
Now we just have to wait and
see how they react to it.
Lady Tsunade! The
Hidden Sand send their
reply right away.
Ah, they'll be sending
nine teams, twenty-seven
genin in total.
Last time they
sent thirty in
ten teams...
It may be one team fewer, but
considering the Sand's current
situation,
one has to commend them
for nurturing this many genin.
Right...
Oh, and- Any word from
the other villages that
we sent invitations to?
No, not yet.
I wonder how the
other Kage will
respond to all this.
(Raikage Ay)
What!? Chunin Exams!?
Damn Princess Tsunade!
She's getting carried away!
She probably coaxed the Kazekage
into cooperating and plans to
get the jump on us within the
Five Great Nations.
What should we do?
Ignore her, that's
what! We'll just
ignore her!
And don't mention this, or
the past to anyone! Especially
Bee! He can't find out!
Whenever an event like this
is getting planned,
he gets worked up about live
concerts and other nonsense.
Actually, I kinda
already told him.
What!?
Well, he kept asking
questions... Sorry sir.
Bee! Where are
you, Bee!?
Don't tell me that
he... Find Bee immediately
and bring him here to me!
Understood, sir!
This is so dull...
Gonna have a concert at the
Hidden Leaf Village, yo!
Turning up at the Chunin
Exams, showin' what I know!
And I'll take a lesson
from Kinchan Sensei, too!
That one's fo' sho'! Yeahhh!
Lord Bee! Lord Raikage
wants to see you.
Please return!
What!? No way,
fool, ya fool!
Did Lord Raikage
say no?
He said that unfortunately
they're swamped with Village
business,
so they don't have
enough time to prepare now.
Now why would the Hokage
and the Kazekage send
a message?
Well, it appears they are
looking to resume the Chunin
Exams. What shall we do about
it?
There's still the matter of Lord
Fourth Yagura. I think we should
focus on rebuilding the village
now.
You very well may have
a point, there.
Yes, that's right. A
ceremony for the Kazekage
is only a waste of our time!
A wedding ceremony....
is... a waste of time!?
Shut up, or die.
What!?
Perhaps it would be best
if we forego the Chunin
Exams this time.
Yes, let's
do that!
It seems that the Hidden
Mist Village is currently
tied up as well.
Listen, we have just
received an invitation
from the Hidden Leaf Village
to attend the new
combined chunin exams.
Hmm.
Their ulterior motive's
crystal clear!
They're looking to test the
strength of the villages
in  preparation for the next
battle that erupts between them!
I say we just throw it
right back in their face!
Yes, I intend
to do so!
[pleased grunts]
I'll give you my
answer, right here!
Ahhhhhhh!
My Back!!
I want you
to go here.
To the Hidden
Rain Village?
Yes, to that most
troublesome spot.
Every person who enters the
village is checked & kept under
surveillance during their stay.
It's said Hanzo of
the Salamander,
whom even blood relatives can't
approach,  rules with an iron
fist.
Yes, so I've heard.
Even if I'm carrying an
invitation to the
combined Chunin Exams,
I doubt if they'll
let me in easily.
That place remains unstable.
There are rumors of a coup
d'état.
But since it's closed
off, no one knows the
true state of things.
While I'm there should
I also look into
their internal affairs?
Yes, but don't take
any chances.
(Kankuro)
Are you actually
going to supervise?
(Gaara)
Yes, I'm going to oversee the
finals of the second round.
(Kankuro)
You think you'll solve something
by outing the rebels?
(Gaara)
No...
(Kankuro)
Then why do this? Why would
you face danger head on?
(Naruto)
Next Time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Chunin Exams Begin!"
(Gaara)
Naruto is working hard to
forge bonds with others...