[groaning]
Impossible!  He took all of us
out with one attack?!
It really was a blessing that
this gang of thieves escaped
into our territory.
Our leader's the lieutenant, the
most skilled in the organization
and the pride of our clan.
You had no chance of escaping.
You were brilliant
as usual, sir.
So what do we do with them now?
What we always do.
Understood.
Teach them a lesson and make
an example out of them!
Yeah!
[villagers crying out]
(Villager Man)
Do they have to beat
them up so much?
Lately, their methods have
just been so extreme!
(Villager Man 2)
They say it's to maintain public
morals, but they're just
throwing their weight around.
Did you say something?
We'd better watch what
we say, or we're gonna
get the same treatment!
Heh.
Oh, Sasuke...
♪
At first I thought we were going
too far, but these results speak
for themselves!
If we hurt them enough, bad guys
won't resort to crime anymore.
And the same thing goes
for the villagers, too!
It's a deterrent, two
birds, one stone.
No... We get to let off steam
too. It's three birds with one
stone!
[laughing]
Y'know, honestly, until Sasuke
came, everyone was getting fed
up!
We were making no progress on
the big problems, but our work
load just kept on increasing!
All Captain Fugaku said was
just to listen to the
Hokage, and keep waiting!
If things were going to change
just by waiting, then they
would've changed a long time
ago.
Absolutely! We have to
apply pressure, too!
Lord Fugaku's
ways are too weak.
Yeah!  We're gonna do things
your way, Lieutenant.
Hm.
It's very easy to just
run your mouth.
Now here's your chance to
demonstrate your skills in a
real mission.
Humph. None of this... has
been difficult at all!
The recent activities of
the Leaf Police Force are
indefensible!
I admit, there's no doubt
that crime has gone down,
but the villagers are growing
more and more uneasy every day!
I believe that this
is a form of protest.
They're annoyed because their
situation hasn't changed...
They're losing patience.
It takes time for things
to truly change.
My father understands that.
However, some others feel
frustrated by it.
Especially the younger
generation.
And the one at the center of all
this is the clan's most gifted
member, Sasuke.
Sasuke, you're back!
Perhaps they're being rather
rough, but they're still
fulfilling their duties.
I believe my father would like
to keep observing them.
Besides... if we make the wrong
move, then we'll only invite
more resistance.
Man, what a drag... Everybody in
the village is so high-strung
because of those guys...
Yeah, it's so annoying.
It wasn't that long ago that
this place was filled with
people and food stands!
They're so strict about
the regulations. So
it's all deserted now.
I know.  You're right.
I mean, what could
Sasuke even be thinking?!
I really wish that I could just
go ask him, but he's so
unapproachable these days.
So you think it'll ever
go back to how it was?
(Naruto)
This is weird...
Huh?
(Naruto)
Weren't there lots of food
stands here before?
I know that voice!
Could it be...?!  Naruto?!
Huh? Hey, Sakura! You guys!
Hold on... when did
you get back here?
Just this minute!
Pervy Sage said he had to make
a stop along the way,
so I figured that I'd
just come home first.
You know, you look a
little more distinguished!
Really?  You guys haven't
changed at all!
What're you talking about? Here,
just take a look at this...!
See?
Huh?? What the--!?
While you were away from the
village, the rest of us became
chunin.
Not only that!  Neji, who's a
class ahead of us, is now a
jonin.
So I'm... the last one from our
class who's still a genin?!
Well... actually, Sasuke's
still one, too.
He was at the Feudal
Lord's office till now.
What happened? What's
going on with Sasuke?
Uh, yeah, Since you've been
gone, things have gotten a
little complicated...
(Taiko)
Hey you!  Who gave you
permission to open up shop,
huh?!
I'm sorry, but until now I-
Shut your mouth!
Come with me!
Stop! She's just a grandma!
There's no need for that!
Wait, you're-!
Oh no, look! That kid...
Yeah, you're right. He's back!
So you start breaking the rules
the minute you return?
Seems you haven't
grown up at all.
That may be, but you
sure have changed.
Choji, get her to safety.
You got it.
Hey!
I'm sorry. I can't
let you pass.
What now? Huh, Lieutenant?
We won't back down from anything
obstructing our duties.
You're still stuck on that?!
I've been waiting
for this day...
[roar]
This feeling... What the
hell is it?
Stop it, both of you!  Aren't
you aware that this is a public
road?
No way, you're...
We're just two friends having
a friendly fight.
You're not involved,
so leave, old man!
You idiot!
Sakura?! What's the deal?
What's going on?
Look, just be quiet!
Let's get out of here!
Hey, they're running!
Leave them alone. Drop it.
But, sir!
That's an order.  Just continue
your rounds. You all understand
me?
[groans]
That Naruto Uzumaki... He seems
to have gained a lot of strength
in the past three years.
His master Jiraiya must have
done a very good job teaching
him.
What are you trying to say?
I'm just posing a question.  You
should be much more than you are
right now.
How long will you remain
confined where you are?
That's all.
Naruto, you can't just go
calling someone like Lord
Danzo "old man."
Well, I didn't know! Who
the hell is he?
One of the Leaf's top officials!
What's more, he's always at odds
with Lord Fourth and Lord Third.
Yeah, and Lady Tsunade gave
me a very strict warning.
She told me never to get
involved with him.
You're so clueless you don't
even know you're clueless!
Thank you for
your help earlier.
Oh, uh... sure!
It's really no big deal.
We're happy to help.
It was simply the
right thing to do-
Well, I must be going now.
That's the kid right there.  I
hear that he's always been on
bad terms with the Lieutenant.
I just hope he doesn't make this
situation any worse than it
already is.
Hey, you!
Leave it. Or it'll
just keep going.
More importantly, about
Sasuke...
Pervy Sage told me that... if a
friend wanders off the path, you
have to pull them back onto it.
So next time, we have to
make sure we stop Sasuke.
Yeah.
Lieutenant... You want us to
leave them be?  Really?
It's just, that kid's bound to
give you more trouble!
Shut up!
Lieutenant!
I have work to do now.  Listen,
you're members of the Leaf
Police Force.
Solve it.  Stop depending on me.
That Naruto Uzumaki... He's
seems to have gained a lot of
strength in the past three
years.
I don't know how he trained...
But he's nothing like how he
was in the past.
I'm still not strong
enough.
How do I...?
[barking]
[whine]
In truth, that child
Sasuke...possesses fine eyes.
[clock ticking]
Hey, you know what I heard?  The
Police Force had a run-in with
the Hokage's son yesterday.
What?! I just saw them!
They were walking around
like nothing happened!
They act all big with us
commoners, but their hands are
tied when it comes to the son of
a powerful official, huh?
They're just the Hokage's
lapdogs, after all.
There's been a lot of
gossip going around...
I know... Letting him
go was a big mistake!
We've clamped down
on everyone until now.
So when we make an exception,
they all drag us through the
mud!
But the Lieutenant said
to leave him alone!
He also told us to think
for ourselves and handle
things on our own!
For the sake of our clan,
we have to make the
right decision now...!
I'm gonna go all out and whip up
something really special today!
[door slamming open]
What's going on?!  You can't
just barge into someone's house!
Especially with your
dirty shoes on!
Bring us Naruto Uzumaki!  We
want to question him about
interfering with our duties!
I don't know what you're talking
about!  Interfering...?
Look, I know my son, and he
would never, ever do anything
like that!
Hey, wait a minute! Who gave you
the authority to do this?!
I'll tell Minato and you'll
get an earful, y'know!
Protect him, and
you'll come, too!
(Naruto)
What's the big idea...?!
...barging in like this?
(Fugaku's Henchman)
Excuse me.
What is it?
The captain wants you.
Lieutenant, please come
with me right now.
[gasp]
I had some misgivings, but I
never expected this!
The Police Force raiding the
Hokage's home without
authorization!
My sincerest apologies.
At least... there was no one who
got hurt in this incident...
What will Fugaku do?
He'll investigate... and
take the appropriate
disciplinary measures.
I just hope that they ease
up a little bit now.
What the hell?
Lieutenant!  We're sorry!  We
just did it for the Uchiha!
Enough. Just throw all
of them into a cell.
Sir!
You told me you were going
to take a different path.
And you did become stronger.
But after all the boasting you
did, I had hoped there was some
substance behind it.
I guess it was
for nothing, though.
All you really ended up doing
was empowering fools to
indulge in idiotic behavior.
Nothing good has
come out of this.
You will never
measure up to Itachi!
Someone like you doesn't
belong in my unit.
You are now relieved of all
your duties as lieutenant.
You're dismissed from the
Leaf Police Force.
The Leaf Police
Force really did that?
So what's gonna happen
to Sasuke, I wonder...
I'm not sure.
But, you know...
Even if this incident does
get him fired rom the
force, who really cares?
We'll just give him a slap on
the back and welcome him right
back onto our team again.
Yeah!
What the hell... have I been
doing...  for the past three
years...
Why is he so different from me?!
It's power... I need power.
You've come.
You wanted to see me. You must
have something up your sleeve.
I only came to see what
exactly you're offering.
Oh, is that so?  You only came
here to see that, did you?
I want to take advantage of you,
too. I thought that we'd have a
nice chat.
Well, then...? What is
it that you want?
I want power...
Enough power to beat him.
Yes, of course. I
predicted as much.
But...  are you sure?
Not only is Naruto Uzumaki
the son of the Hokage...
...he's also the Nine Tails'
Jinchuriki, which is essential
to this village.
If you reach your goal, it's
quite possible that the Uchiha's
standing in the village will
become even worse.
I don't care.
Beating him's all
that matters to me.
I don't care about the
Uchiha or the Leaf.
What's so funny?
[chuckle]
I remember a shinobi who
deserted the village long ago
saying something just like
that...
He betrayed everyone, committed
numerous crimes, and in exchange
obtained frightening power.
The name of that shinobi
is Orochimaru...
He's one of the Three Legendary
Sannin, like Jiraiya, Naruto's
mentor.
The Legendary Sannin.
I'm listening...
He has knowledge of the myriad
jutsu in this world, including
forbidden ones.
I can't think of a single person
better than him to learn from.
However... he is a man who has
lived within darkness.
Remember that's the price you'll
pay.
I'm looking forward to it.
Very well, then.
Before sunrise, go to the tower
at the border. And I'll take
care of the rest of it...
We aren't done here yet. I
want to know what you're
getting out of this.
It's your choice whether
you believe me...
But I am one of the many who do
not look with much kindness upon
that creature, the Nine Tails.
It's nothing but a monster. It
could rampage at any moment,
and I doubt that it's wise to
leave such power unbridled...
I feel that we need the power to
be able to fight against it.
Humph.
Now, go...
The contract has been fulfilled.
And now the rest of
it will be up to you.
[dog whining]
Shiro...
You take care now.
[bark]
If you're gonna have a
midnight snack, you gotta have
something rich and heavy!
That's Sasuke... Where is
he going at this hour?
Five orders of karaage!
And some extra!
Oh! Awesome!  Thank you!
All right, shift's over.
Time to close the gate.
We weren't notified about any
departures at this hour...
Hey, the gate's about to close!
[grunts]
Wait...
(Sasuke)
I really am grateful to you, but
this isn't enough for me.
(Sasuke)
I'm not satisfied with the
mediocre level I'm stuck at.
(Sasuke)
So I'm going to go and get
power... at the side of that
other Sannin.
(Sasuke)
Three whole years... I can't let
those three years end in the
blink of an eye!
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Leaving the Village"
(Naruto)
Sasuke!