[baby crying]
[heavy breathing]
[gasp]...
He's really here.
[baby crying]
[joyful laugh]
Today I am a father!
Yes, you've got a
healthy baby boy,
Minato.
Naruto!
Hands off, you!
Mother first,
father, second.
Okay...
[gasp]
So Naruto...
We finally meet.
Now, you'll have
more time later.
There, there
my child!
Kushina... are
you feeling
alright now?
I'm okay.
Thank you.
Minato.
Alright! Now I
realize what
you've just
been through...
...but we need
to reseal the
Nine Tails!
(Biwako & Taji)
[screams]
[gasp]
Lady Biwako!
Taji!
Fourth Hokage
Minato... Step
away from the
Jinchuriki.
[gasp]
Or else this
child will die
in it's first
minute.
[thinking]
How the hell
did he get past
the barrier?
[thinking]
Who... is he?
[groaning in pain]
Kushina!
No... The Nine
Tails seal isn't...
Get away from the
Jinchuriki...
Don't you care
what happens
to the brat?
Wait! Please!
Just stay calm!
Speak for yourself.
I am as calm as can
be, Minato.
Naruto!!!
[baby cries]
Leave it to the
Yellow Flash
of the Leaf...
...but what about
the next one..?
[gasp]
Minato! Naruto!
[crying]
Thank goodness
Naruto wasn't
injured...
[gasp]
[thinking]
He forced me to
use the Flying
Raijin Jutsu.
His target was
Kushina... and
he succeeded in
separating us.
Gotta hurry...
[exhausted breaths]
Alright, what
do you want!?
I'm going to
extract the Nine
Tails from you, and
crush the Leaf.
No... you can't.
Minato's Teleportation Jutsu
allows him to move instantly
between locations that are
marked with Jutsu Formulas.
Those markings are
incorporated into the
Sealing Formula.
That way, Minato
can protect you at
all times. But he's
far away now...
Nine Tails' Seal
has weakened due
to childbirth.
Do you have any idea
how long I've waited
for this moment?!
You'll be safe here.
Naruto, please be
patient, okay?
I have to go
and rescue your
mother right now.
[Thinking]
It's you.....
[snarling]
[roaring]
Now then, come
on out...
Nine Tails!!!
[roaring]
Good. Now we'll
head to the Hidden
Leaf Village.
More hate...
You Uzumaki are
just amazing.
You don't die right
away when the Tailed
Best is extracted...
[growling]
You were the Nine
Tails' Jinchuriki...
[growling]
So I'll let you
die by his hand.
[gasp]
[roaring]
You really are
quick as a flash...
...but you're
too late.
Minato...
Naruto.... is he...
alright then??
Yes. He's fine.
He's in a safe
place for now.
[sigh]... good.
Minato, that masked
man is with the
Nine Tails.
(Kushina)
They're headed to the
Village. Stop them.
He flew away.
Hm. That's fine.
Let's get to the
Hidden Leaf Village.
But... why?
Nevermind. Just...
be with Naruto.
[quiet sob]
Naruto...
Thank you...
Minato.
And good luck.
I'll be right back.
Look! Another
shooting star!
Did you remember
to make a wish
this time, buddy?
Oh, I forgot.
[meow]
Are you serious?
What do you mean
you're going out?!
The guys are getting
together! I'm allowed
to go out sometimes,
you know!
"Sometimes?!" It's been
every night lately!
(Husband)
I'll come home
early, alright?
(Shop Owner)
Thanks for
coming!
(Customer)
Sure! I'll be back!
I know. Come on.
Let's go home.
[sigh] Look, why
don't we just do
rock-paper-scissors
again?
Oh come on! There
must be something
more exciting we
can do!
(Guy)
...and you call
yourself my rival!?
We have to get an
early start tomorrow.
So let's just take a
pass on tonight.
A mission is
no excuse!
I have all this
pent-up energy
inside me!
So there's no better
time than right now
for some really
rigorous training!
Honest to goodness
discipline and hard work
will lead us to success
in future missions!
Are you even
listening to
me!?
Forget that
for now...
Do you sense something
strange? As if there was
suddenly a dark chill in
the air..?
The only thing that's
chilly is your attitude!
You must be much more
hot-blooded!!
I feel something
ominous...
[baby cries]
There there,
it's okay.
[thinking]
What a strange
feeling...
Of all the times
for mom and dad
to be out...
[crying]
Don't cry, Sasuke.
No matter what happens,
your big brother will
protect you. I promise
you that.
Hm?
It can't be...
Summoning Jutsu!
[panting]
Huh? Is that..?
[growling]
No! No way!
[huge roar]
(Villager)
The Nine Tails!
[frightened cries]
Go Nine Tails!
[growling]
[roaring]
[fearful cries]
Lord Third! It's
the Nine Tails!
The Nine Tails is
inside the Village!
Yes, I know that.
I'll go restrain him.
You and the others
go protect all the
people of the Village.
Yes sir!
[Thinking]
Was Kushina's
seal broken?
We failed even
with all the
safeguards we
put in place?
Biwako...
Damn you,
Nine Tails!
It's time to
realease all my
pent up energy!
We don't know
what we're up
against!
Come on!! I'll
be your opponent!
Wait!
Huh?
Gather immediately
in the guardroom!
Why?
The Third Hokage
ordered it!
What? Lord
Hiruzen did?
Well, you heard
him. Let's go, Guy.
[grunting]
Now is our chance!
All of you, go!
Evacuate the Village!
Ohhh noo!!
Are we ready!?
Yeah!
Over here,
Nine Tails!
[angry growl]
Right here!
Your battle's here!
...with me!
[angry roaring]
Do not falter!
Even if we can't
defeat the Nine
Tails, we must allow
villagers to escape!
Don't take action
on your own!
Assemble around
Lord Hiruzen.
Carry out
your orders!
As Hokage, I must
protect the Village-
my family...
This is what
I have to do
right now.
[Thinking]
I won't let you
destroy my home.
[growling]
So you noticed
me, huh?
[roar]
I won't let
you do this!
[thinking]
With this much power, I've
got to carefully chose where
to redirect his attacks.
The Jutsu deflected
Nine Tails' attack.
That's a Transpiration
Barrier!
It's Minato.
Alright! Let's
move in too!
I've got to alert
Lord Third right
away about what's
going on.
I'm your opponent!
And you're done for!
He got away...
So fast...
Next time I'll
take him a lot
quicker... as
soon as we touch.
[grunt]
My attack passed
right through him...
...but a moment later,
he made himself
solid and tried to
pull me inside him.
What was that Jutsu?
[gasp]
Ha. You shall
not escape.
[thinking]
He uses the
Transportation
Technique too?
That's how he was
able to grab Kushina
and move so quickly!
He defeated the Anbu
Black Ops assigned to
Lord Third...
...got past a
highest-level
classified barrier...
...and knew Nine
Tails' seal would
weaken during
childbirth...
Even more than that, he
undid the Nine Tails'
Seal and tamed him...
He slipped in and
out of the Village
barriers without
triggering any alarms...
..As far as I know,
there's only one
shinobi who can do
all that...
Are you...
Madara Uchiha?
No... That would
be impossible. He
is dead, after all.
Hmm. I wonder
about that.
In the end it
doesn't matter
who you are...
...but why attack
the Hidden Leaf?
What would you like
to hear? I could say
I did it on a whim, or
that I planned it.
...or that it's
for war... or that
it's for peace.
[gasp]
[thinking]
Either way, he's
not ordinary. He can
control Nine Tails.
His Transportation
Technique surpasses
both Lord Second's
and mine.
And he's got some
dangerous ideology.
If I don't settle
this now, we'll have
even bigger problems
than the Nine Tails...
If I transport myself
to the Village, he'll
come to the battlefield
with me...
It'll be chaos...
If he's anything like
Madara, he can't keep
the Nine Tails under the
Summoning Jutsu for long.
I have to entrust
the Village to
Lord Third...
...and just take
this guy down right
here, right now.
Now that I've freed
the  Nine Tails, there
is no hope for any of
you!
[grunt]
My physical attacks
have no effect on him.
But he makes himself
solid when he attacks
me....
I have to aim for
a mutual strike,
precisely timed...
But he knows that
he's vulnerable
when he attacks...
And considering the
time remaining on the
Nine Tails' Summoning
Jutsu...
...he won't want
a lengthy battle,
either.
Whoever attacks an
instant quicker than
the other... will win
this match.
I win.
Damn it! He
transported
himself to
his Kunai!
Flying Raijin,
Level 2!
[exhausted breaths]
You got me! You
really are a
slippery one!
I never should have
let my guard down
around you!
[gasping]
[Madara thinking]
Flying Raijin Jutsu!?
Of course! He must have
marked me somewhere!
A Contract Seal?
Trying to separate
Nine Tails from me?!
The Nine Tails is
no longer yours!
[angry roar]
(Minato)
Naruto... our
newborn son...
I wanna stay
with you longer!
(Minato)
Our family is shinobi. We
sacrifice our lives to
protect what we believe in!
(Kushina)
Don''t forget us,
Naruto. Remember we'll
always love you.
(Kushina)
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Thank you.
(Minato)
I'm going to seal
the Nine Tails
inside Naruto!