The longer you live,
the more you'll realize
that the only things that
truly exist in this reality
are merely pain,
suffering, and futility.
Listen...
Everywhere you look in this
world, wherever there is
light, there are
always shadows to be
found as well.
These are nexuses,
causal relationships
that cannot be separated.
Normally, that is.
He means tossing the
real world's bad stuff
and escaping inside
of a dream that's
entirely full of
good things!
Since it's a dream,
everything is just
how you want it!
Even those who are dead
can be alive again!
A world of only victors...
A world of only peace...
A world of only love.
I will create such a world.
Rin... Once again...
Let's create a world
where you can exist again.
I shall...
...sever the nexuses
of this world!
That's the reason
why I've come back.
[chuckle]
Well, I certainly hope
that no one observed you.
I'm pretty sure I'm the
only one who saw him.
Obito slaughtered all of the
enemy, so I think we should
still be perfectly safe.
He didn't seem to want
to kill his former
teammate Kakashi,
though.
But then again, Kakashi
didn't see anything anyway.
When reinforcements from the
Hidden Leaf Village arrived,
he was screaming, "Who
killed the enemy?!"
You still felt loyalty
to your one-time
teammate, did you?
Not at all. I didn't
care either way.
It doesn't really matter to
me anymore whether he's
alive or dead, in
this world, at least.
Kakashi will exist in
the world we'll create.
Rin, too...
I want you teach me
how to create this world
of dreams, Madara.
[chuckle] I don't
need your thanks now.
Just come over here.
Starting today, you
will be the savior.
Look into my eye.
You are inside my
genjutsu right now.
It is still a blank canvas,
but I can project my will
upon it to create
whatever I want.
I can control
everything in here.
Anything that I wish is
possible, since I'm linked
to and borrowing the
power of the Gedo Statue.
Just like this.
We'll use this genjutsu
to create the ideal world.
And then we'll cast the
genjutsu on everyone else
and bring them here.
The scale of this jutsu, an
entire world of dreams is
achieved by using the
moon instead of our eyes.
You make it sound so simple,
I still don't quite get it.
Let me explain,
starting with the
Sage of the Six
Paths and the Ten Tails.
Wait, isn't the Ten
Tails just a legend?
Legends are always derived
from something real.
The Tailed Beasts that roam
the world resulted when the
Sage of Six Paths split
up the power of Ten Tails.
What, seriously?
Do you have any proof
that story's true?!
I do.
After I'd obtained Hashirama
Senju's cells, I implanted
them into the wound
that I had received.
At first, nothing
at all happened...
It was only when I was
beginning to die of old age
that my Rinnegan awakened.
And it also simultaneously
led to the undoing of a
certain seal.
I could then summon and
extract the husk of the Ten
Tails from a Seal Stone.
The husk of the Ten Tails?
Yes, I call it the Gedo
Statue and the Seal Stone
is what you now
know as the moon.
I immediately used the
statue as a catalyst and
medium to culture
Hashirama's cells into
what you see
before you now.
Really, one could say that
these artificial beings are
clones of Hashirama.
Although they're quite
reduced in quality.
The Rinnegan cannot be
awakened without possessing
both Uchiha and
Senju powers, and
the statue cannot
be controlled easily.
You have Senju
cells attached to the
right half of you.
Even if you never awaken
the Rinnegan, you ought to
eventually be able to
control the statue.
Hey, can you see them?
That redhead's eyes?
So they're Madara's
Rinnegan, huh?
They're Madara's
actual eyes.
He secretly transplanted
them without anyone knowing
back when that boy
was very small.
Nagato is of Senju
bloodline and the only
other person in addition
to Madara who can
summon the Gedo Statue.
As Madara said, first we win
over and groom Nagato,
then everything else
will fall into place.
Huh?! Hey, what are
you going to do?
I'm going straight for him.
But wait, shouldn't you
plan a strategy first?
I don't need to do that.
Obito, I shall teach you the
Uchiha Forbidden Jutsu...
The Six Paths Jutsu,
and the Shadow
and Light Style Jutsu.
I've implanted my
will into this one.
Think of him as
being half of me.
Though he will be
degraded, as well.
Use these beings
made with Shadow and
Light Style Jutsu
as your soldiers.
That Black Rod was
created as a physical
manifestation of my will.
Use it when performing
the Six Paths Jutsu.
[grunting]
Now go on. Until the time
when I will be revived.
You shall be...
Who're you?
I am Madara Uchiha.
Madara?
To claim Madara Uchiha's
name as your own means
you're either a criminal...
Or a total idiot.
Now, why have you
approached us?
The Rinnegan...
[gasp]
To guide those who
awaken it is the mission
our organization
has been entrusted
with since long ago.
You mean that you
know about my eyes?
You are the reincarnation of
the Sage of the Six Paths,
who dreamed of world
peace and stability.
Only the villages of large
nations are showered in
light, leaving your
small country's village
in their shadow, dying.
That is why your eye
has awakened here.
Wherever light strikes,
there are always shadows.
So long as there is a
concept of victors,
the vanquished
will also exist.
The selfish intent of
wanting to preserve peace
initiates wars. And hatred
is born to protect love.
These are all nexuses,
causal relationships that
cannot be separated.
Normally, that is.
However, a world made
up of only victors,
peace, and love. Such a
world can be created, too!
If you allow all of
us to collaborate,
you can learn how.
As soon as you attain the
true power of the Rinnegan,
your very own world can
be actualized immediately.
Now...
No, we can't do that.
I think you're just
trying to use us.
This offer of yours
sounds way too convenient.
One finds the true world
only after knowing another's
pain and shedding
tears alongside them.
Shedding tears alongside
them? You mean in revenge?
No, I don't mean
that at all.
In mutual understanding.
Stop talking so
idealistically.
No such thing exists
in this world.
Let's go, Konan, Nagato.
We can't trust these guys!
Don't you dare
approach us again.
I shall wait here at the
same time each day.
You will eventually
realize it, too.
Who are you?!
We are the guardians
of this village.
This is a warning.
Leave here now!
[growl] To hell with
them! Kill 'em all!
Water Style: Raging Waves!
Wind Style: Gale Palm!
Damn! We can't get near 'em!
[attacking yell]
One move, and
I'll skewer you!
We won't let you take a
single step into this village!
Just give up!
[grunting]
[gasp] The rain!
Now's my chance!
[attacking yell]
Sorry! You okay?
[screams]
Damn! There's no end
to this! I didn't want
to use this, but...
Why you! Do you three
belong to Hanzo's gang?!
We wear his headband, but
we are not his subordinates.
But just like Hanzo, we hope
that one day we'll be able
to bring peace to
the shinobi world.
Oh, so in other words,
you're only copycats of him.
We're not copycats!
But we will keep the
peace in this village!
Not through violence,
but through dialogue!
Through dialogue?!
You're mad!
This village is between
two great nations!
As long as they're at war
with each other, the
fighting will never end!
The strong just take
everything they want from
the weak! That's
how the world is!
We're fighting in
order to change that
very way of thinking!
Every one of you must
secretly wish to find peace!
Listen, a piece of
straw is weak...
But when you put three
of them together...
It's much--
Damn it!
I'm just trying to say, that
the more you have, the
stronger they become!
Yahiko...
You're so bad
at speeches.
Whatever! Look, we're
not going to kill you.
Negotiate or leave!
I can't guarantee you that
we won't attack again!
That's just fine. We can
do this dozens of times
until you give up.
A hundred times!
However! Just remember,
it'll be more painful for
you the next time!
Let's go.
Earlier...
When you attacked...
You spared those kids.
Thanks. We're war
orphans, too.
Such strange kids...
You appear out of
nowhere and ask to
protect this village.
We want to
change this land.
War will never leave this
land. That won't change.
Nothing will change.
Yahiko...
Seems like little by little
things are changing.
All three of us are shinobi
who left our village because
we don't have too
much faith in
Hanzo's ways anymore.
But to tell you the truth,
we've all been getting
pretty sick of this
lifestyle, as well.
And when I looked into
your eyes earlier...
I began to feel like
starting over again.
But I don't feel like going
back to Hanzo is the answer.
So please, take us in
as your subordinates!
No way!
What?! But before you--!
Not subordinates,
but as comrades.
I'm Yahiko. And this is
Nagato and Konan.
My name is
Kyusuke the Swift.
If you need intel gathered,
just leave it to these legs.
Then go and seek out
other villages that are
suffering like this one.
Yahiko...
What?
You should name
our group.
There are more of us.
It'll be necessary soon.
A name, huh?
How about The Akatsuki?
This nation weeps because
of the suffering of war.
So we will change
this nation--
No, the whole world.
And we shall usher
in a new dawn!
Akatsuki...
That's a great name.
Akatsuki. Great,
then it's decided!
Yeah!
I can't believe how much the
Akatsuki's suddenly grown.
Incredible.
They've all come to believe
in your dream. Although
perhaps more than anything,
they're tired of war.
If everyone unites, we
can achieve peace.
Say, where's
Konan right now?
She went out a
little while ago.
Why's that?
["I dunno" grunt]
This is...
It's Konan's.
It says, "My dear Konan..."
"From the first moment
I laid eyes on you..."
Is this--?!
It's a love letter.
"I've wanted to ask you how
you feel about me. I'll be
waiting anxiously on the
back terrace for you."
"Kyusuke."
Don't tell me...
Konan's gone there?!
I dunno...
[chuckle]
Yahiko, didn't you
have something to do?
Huh?! Oh, yeah,
that's right!
Almost forgot! I need to go
to the bathroom! [laughter]
I'm gonna wet myself!
That guy!
Guess running isn't
all he's fast at!
Well when we get more
comrades, it seems we get
more competition
in love, too!
Yeah, no kidding...
Oh, Nagato!
Do you like
Konan, Yahiko?
Dummy! It's
nothing like that!
Well, you know, I
think Konan likes you.
Huh?!
Oh, he's leaving.
I know you're there...
Yahiko, Nagato.
Konan, what did
you tell that guy?
I said I don't have time
for a relationship till
we make the Akatsuki's
dream come true.
Isn't that right?
Konan...
Yahiko!
Can you help me out
with some training?
This jutsu...
...doesn't work in the rain!
Oiled paper, huh?
Great idea.
I experimented.
If you hesitate,
I'll leave you behind!
Like I'd let you!
Hanzo is setting an example
for the rest of us shinobi
by fighting to try to bring
peace to this world.
We will prove that one day
the Akatsuki will surpass
him in that quest!
I approve of a group that
resolves issues through
nonviolent means. It
will help me realize
my dream of uniting the
Five Nations without force.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Creeping Shadow."
So they're the apprentices
of that brat! [chuckle]