[distant fighting]
[grunt]
Thanks, Hinata!
Are you doing all
right now, Neji?
My eyes have recovered
a lot, but I still have
some blind spots.
Then rest assured, until
your eyes have healed
completely, I will be
sure to protect you!
...just as you
protected me
back then...
When I...
protected you?
Yes... Lady Tsunade
had just become Hokage.
It was when
Sasuke was still
in the village...
[punching]
(Neji)
Hinata.
Oh, Neji.
I've come here to
act as your training
partner.
Huh? But... I'm
getting ready for
Senbon Sparring now.
I'm aware of that.
Senbon Sparring is an
important ritual of
the main family.
During one's thirteenth
summer, one must drill
daily until reaching a
thousand sparring exchanges.
Then the head of the
family becomes your
sparring partner and
passes on jutsu secrets.
That's why today
Father and I are
planning to--
Lord Hizashi is away
on business regarding
Lady Hanabi.
[gasp]
The soonest that he
could return is a
month from now.
I was told to come
here and to become
your training partner
until he can join you.
But, that's so...
Are you
dissatisfied
with me?
Oh, no! I didn't
mean it that way.
Let's begin.
Uh, yes!
(Neji)
The First!
Right!
[gasp]
[sigh]
The Second!
Yes!
[loud striking sound]
(Neji)
Next!
(Hinata)
Okay!
[grunt]
Tenth!
Alright!
Now! Twenty-Third!
(Hinata)
Yes!
Now, the Thirty-sixth!
(Hinata)
Right!
(Neji)
Fifty-fourth!
Okay!
(Neji)
Seventy-fifth!
(Hinata)
Right!
(Neji)
Ninety-third!
(Sakura)
Hinata...
[whimper]
Whoa, are you all
right? I barely
touched you just now.
I'm just kinda
bruised all over,
that's all.
What? WHere'd
you get those?!
Oh, I was training...
[groan]
Why are you
training
so hard?
Its really no big deal!
I've just been training
with Neji for a clan ritual.
Oh, I get it. Tough
growing up in a
noble family, huh?
But if you're going
at it that hard, I
wonder if you'll be
able to join us...
Hm?
You know they're having
a fireworks display
this weekend, right?
What? Fireworks?
Yeah! To commemorate
Lady Tsunade becoming
the Fifth Hokage!
I bet it'll be fun.
I was going to go...
And I wanted to see
if you'd join me!
To tell the truth, I was hoping
to use this chance to sneak
Sasuke out of the hospital
so we can be alone together!
But he insists on
tagging along
everywhere I go!
[love-struck gasp]
Hey! Hinata!
N-...Naruto...
You see, unless he has
someone to keep him
company, I won't get to have
any time alone with Sasuke!
Getting to watch a
fireworks display
with Naruto...
[squeaky freak out]
Hinata, wait! Are
you gonna come or
not!?
I'm coming.
Absolutely.
[swoon]
Whoa, what's up with
Hinata? Did something
happen?
(Neji)
Eight hundred
thirty-eighth!
What's the matter
with you? Your chakra
flow is all over
the place!
Sorry!
You're too hung up
on each individual
jutsu...
Focus on your
accuracy!
It makes no sense to
do one well if your
overall flow is poor!
Okay!
So you say, but are
you really listening?
Your side!
Elbow!
[wince]
I juggled my schedule
around to make time
for you, and for this?
Neji... I'm sorry.
Stand up! And get
focused! Don't waste
any more of my time!
Yes. Right!
The eight hundred
and thirty-ninth!
Gentle Fist Technique!
Eight Trigrams! Two Palms!
Four Palms! Eight
Palms! Sixteen Palms!
Thirty-two Palms!
[muffled]
Eight Trigrams!
Sixty-Four Palms!
Hinata! Are you--
[gasp] Hinata!
Hinata!
(Doctor)
It's eyestrain. Probably
from sudden or excessive
use of her eyes.
Will she recover?
Ys, of course. That
isn't a weakened that
the Byakugan possesses.
Given time, her eyes
will simply recover
on their own.
You really don't
remember at all?
No, I don't
have a clue.
Huh?
Hey! Neji!
Hi!
Excuse me, Neji. Can
I ask you a question?
Have you seen Hinata?
Yeah, neither one
of us has seen her
around for a couple
days...
We figured you of all
people would know.
I'm sorry, but I am
not Hinata's guardian.
Yeah, no kidding! We
didn't say you were!
Look, we just want
to know if Hinata's
okay, all right?
You know, I'm not
obligated to answer
your questions.
[angry growling]
Is that so? Fine!
Come on, Sakura! Let's
just go to Hinata's house
and find out for ourselves!
[Tsk]
No, don't! Hinata's
recuperating there now!
She's recuperating?
What happened? Did she
get hurt or something?
(Sakura)
Wait, she did tell me
that you were helping her
train for a clan ritual.
Don't tell me...
(Naruto)
You injured Hinata,
didn't you!?
It was due to
Hinata's lack of
skill, it wasn't
my fault.
Why, you--!
Watch it, Naruto!
And you watch it,
too, Neji! That's
no way to talk!
Too bad. That means
she'll miss the
fireworks display.
Fireworks display?
Really?! You didn't
know about that?
We're putting on a
fireworks show this
weekend to honor Granny
Tsunade becoming Hokage!
Anyway, that's not
all! Sakura's gonna
be my date--
Ooof!!!
Like I'd ever go
on a date with you!
Hinata seemed really
excited about seeing
the fireworks!
Ridiculous!
Man! That guy is
so inconsiderate
it's unbelievable!
Ugh... huh?
Sakura?
Hey! Sakura! Wait
up, would ya!?
Ugh, what am I
going to do
with him...
Heeey Sakura!
[small grunts]
Oh...
[sipping]
Is someone there?
Must be my
imagination...
Well, it's going
to take a little
more time...
Oh, uh, how
much more time?
Try not to be
impatient. It's
important that
you rest.
Oh, all right...
Doctor! Please wait!
Hey, that's Neji.
Hide!
Why exactly are
we hiding?
It just seemed like
the right thing to do.
You have to heal her!
Hinata's eyes must be
better by this weekend!
Huh? Did she injure
her eyes or something?
She was looking forward
to seeing the fireworks
display this weekend!
I want her to go,
whatever it takes!
I understand, but
something like this
isn't that simple.
Hm. If I only had
access to some Eyebright.
And what is
that? Eyebright?
It's an extremely
rare medicinal plant.
And it's said to be
very effective in
treating eyestrain.
But Eyebright only grows
in remote areas, and even
there it's exceedingly
difficult to find.
Although, now that
I think about it...
That's right!
I heard that someone
recently saw some growing
in the Valley of Judgement.
The Valley of
Judgement...
Now, hold on...
Don't think of
looking for it.
Even jonin have been
known to get lost in
the Valley of Judgement.
If you go, you
won't come back.
If Hinata rests
quietly, then she'll be
fine in a week or so.
She simply needs to
be patient a little
longer.
But one week
is too late!
There you are! I
figured you'd show up!
Naruto... Sakura...
You're going to the
Valley of Judgement,
aren't you?
So you do have a
soft spot inside
you after all!
Yeah, um, we didn't
mean to eavesdrop on
what you were saying
earlier... Right?
Yeah! But we were
right in front of
Hinata's house and
listened anyway!
So we're gonna
come with you to go
get some of that
Eyebright stuff!
No thank you.
Ugh. Do as you
please. But don't
expect my help if
you lag behind!
Yeah right, like
we'd want your help.
You should focus on what
really needs help: That
annoying personality of
yours.
You know, Neji, if you
weren't going, then Naruto
and I would've gone anyway.
I wanna make sure
Hinata gets to see
those fireworks!
I'm gonna make sure she can
see so she'll come along and
keep that infuriating Naruto
out of my way!
[swoon]
[embarrassed sigh]
[giggles]
What is this place...
That mist is
totally creepy!
Are we even going
to be able to find
that medicinal plant?
Even Jonin have been
known to get lost in
the Valley of Judgement.
You two stay here. Since
you don't have the Byakugan
you'll only slow me down.
Neji!
Hey, what are you
doing, Naruto?
Tying us together, of
course! That way we won't
get separated walking through
all that mist down there!
This is perfect!
It's our red
string of destiny!
You annoying
little...
All right! Come on,
Sakura! Let's go!
[screaming]
Does that medicinal
plant actually grow
here?
Without my Byakugan, I
doubt I could even walk
through here...
No way! This is
supposed to be a
demilitarized zone!
They must be very skilled
to navigate through this
mist so effortlessly.
Or, are they adept with
visual Jutsu like the
Byakugan or Sharingan?
(Naruto / Sakura)
[screams]
Naruto! Sakura!
[gasp]
This string is nothing
but a nuisance! It's a
huge pain in the butt!
Just hurry up and
cut it off already!
No, I'm never gonna cut
that red string or any of
the ties that bind us
together Sakura!
For once could you
not be a total idiot!?
[grunt]
Eight Trigrams
Palm Rotation!
Neji!
Nice one! You
saved us!
It's too soon to celebrate.
There's even more of the
enemy out there...
Argh! What do you
think you're doing!?
You cut our red
string of destiny!
Neji... Damn you!
(Neji)
Isn't destiny something
you make with your own
hands?
Huh?
You helped me see that,
Naruto. Don't tell me
you're putting your faith
in a piece of string!
Right, okay then!
That's what I'll do!
I'll forge my destiny
with my own two hands!
Fine. But that destiny
will still never happen.
Sakura, punch Naruto!
My pleasure!
(Neji)
Naruto! Strike with
your fist to the left!
All right!
You got it!
Yeah! That's the
first enemy I've
punched here!
Heh--! Huh?
So that's it...
I get it now...
How can we block
them all!?
Stop this
fighting at once!
(Naruto)
Bushier Brow Sensei!
Leaf Hurricane...!
Whirlwinds!
(Kakashi)
Lightning Blade!
Kakashi Sensei!
(Sakura)
What are you
two doing here?
Hm? Oh! Surveillance.
For, what?
Well, since it was a
false alarm I guess
we can tell you...
(Kakashi)
A medicinal plant for
treating eyestrain is
said to be found here.
Yeah! That's
why we're--
(Kakashi)
...and Orochimaru
might be after it.
Huh!? Did you say
Orochimaru!? Where?!
Where the hell is he!?
Like I said, it was
just a false alarm.
Alarm?
Idiot! It was a false
alarm! You know, "false!"
As in, what they were
worried about happening
didn't actually happen!
Oh! So what's
the big deal?
(Kakashi)
Orochimaru is fixated on
Visual Jutsu, especially
the Sharingan.
That plant would be
extremely helpful in
Visual Jutsu research.
That concern came up at
one of our meetings, so
Guy and I came out here
to investigate further.
And? What about
you guys?
(Guy)
Youth! Ah, yes! This
is what youth is all
about!
All your passionate
devotion to a comrade
who's in need..!
That's true friendship!
I just couldn't be more
impressed with every one
of you!
Bushier Brow Sensei, your
words may mean one thing,
but your actions say
something totally different!
[laugh]
Well, I guess it's
time for us to go.
But, Sensei!
Neji... you saw
what they looked
like, didn't you?
Huh?
What does he
mean by that?
Uhhh...
Those things...
didn't have eyes.
Huh?
(Kakashi)
It's said that fish living where
light can't reach stop relying
on their eyes...
...and eventually they
lose them entirely.
How long do you think it
would take humans to reach
the point where their
bodies changed like that?
A hundred Years?
A thousand...?
In any case, they've
adapted to this valley
and have thrived here.
Who knows, maybe they
can't even survive
outside this place.
You know who's valley
this is., don't you, Neji?
Yes.
(Kakashi)
Fighting a futile battle to
obtain medicine that will
heal her eyes--
--that wouldn't
make Hinata happy.
[happy crowd murmuring]
[awe reactions]
Back then, before the
fireworks show, Naruto
and Sakura came to tell
me what happened.
They explained everything
that you went through to
try and help me.
So, you knew...
I've always wanted to
tell you this... to say...
...Thank you, Neji.
Okay, Neji. Are you ready
to do this? After all, compared
to Senbon Sparring, this is
practically nothing!
(Neji)
Sounds good!
And this is your chance
to show me just how
much you've progressed
since then!
(Hinata)
Until Naruto comes, we'll
do everything we can to
hold our position!
(Hayate)
You're Kabuto Yakushi.
I see... You're still an
enemy of the Leaf...
(Kabuto)
Yes. And right now, you're
on the same side as me, I
reanimated you to be my pawn.
(Hayate)
Just, what am I?
(Kabuto)
Well, there's no doubt
that the body count has
increased by this point.
(Kabuto)
I guess I'll begin
the next stage...
(Sakura)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Fade Into the Moonlight"
(Hayate)
This... is war?