"Hopes Entrusted to the Future"
He's not on the northern route.
Or the southern or the western!
[groan] Where could Lord Gaara
have gone?
The massive sandstorm seems to
have passed.
Lord Gaara?!
What's the commotion about?
Please, try to focus and resume
the Second Exam.
Uh, yes, sir!
Go on! Restart the Second Exam!
It's unusual for Houichi not to
send a message. Could he have
failed?
Hmm?
Lord Gaara!
Fugi...
I've been wanting to speak with
you.
Well, then...
What did you want to talk about?
I have always considered you to
be a highly-regarded citizen of
the Hidden Sand Village.
I still do, even now.
Thank you for your kind words.
In the past, words like
"citizen" and "friend" were just
that, mere words that held no
real meaning for me.
For a long time after I was
born, I understood those words,
but they were not part of my
existence.
I see...And when did these
concepts become real to you?
When I infiltrated the Hidden
Leaf to destroy it. There, for
the first time, I met someone I
could call a friend.
Ironically, he was an enemy who
belonged to the Hidden Leaf
Village.
Although the two of us shared
comparable circumstances,
unlike me, he was always able to
empathize with others.
...He could share in others'
pain. He could sympathize with
their happiness and with their
tears.
Through him I realized how
precious and important the
concept of "friend" really could
be.
And, it made me want to become
more like him: a human being who
is valued and needed by others.
Lord Gaara, there's little doubt
that you will always will be an
individual who is indispensable
to the Hidden Sand Village.
All this time, I've been
considered a military weapon to
be feared.
And that fact continues to
instill fear even in the hearts
of the people of the Sand
Village.
But that's not-!
Yes, it's true.
If it were not so, then my own
father would not have tried to
kill me six times.
I'm aware that many oppose me.
When I was asked to be Kazekage,
it was a hard choice.
To accept or not...? It was a
real dilemma.
But I thought of my friend, the
Leaf shinobi who had taught me
about frienship, and I
decided...
...I wanted to try to heal the
hurt I'd caused everyone.
But, it's been difficult to get
the people of the Sand to truly
believe me.
There was a time when I felt
that the wounds I'd inflicted on
my people would never heal.
I thought I should just
disappear from the Sand because
then the fear would finally
disappear, too.
But, I found that despite my
past, there were some who,
without prejudice, accepted my
feelings and believed in me.
This happened because you're
frightened of yourself.
When using a weapon, you must
suppress your feelings and
become emotionless.
[exhale] Right!
I've met someone like you. He's
a shinobi that comes from the
Village Hidden in the Leaves.
Through sheer perseverance, he
has become a fine shinobi.
And Shira,...I think you will be
as impressive a shinobi as he
is.
These shinobi who trust me have
come to accept and rely on the
guidance I provide them.
They're maturing steadily.
We're almost there!
But we still need to find one
more scroll!
Well, a whole lot did
happen...
Why don't we just forget about
passing the Chunin Exams until
next time.
Well, then,...even if we're not
gonna worry about getting the
other scroll that we need to
finish this...
...just once, there's still
someone I wanna fight.
[gasping]
It's someone just like me, who
received guidance from Lord
Gaara and developed into a
shinobi.
There's something I wanna
confirm by fighting someone who
received the same training as
me...
We did it! We made it!
We may have reached the tower,
but we still only have the
"Heaven" scroll...
There's nothing we can do. We've
simply reached our physical
limits!
If I hadn't stopped on the way
for a personal fight...
Don't say that, Shira!
That's right. We've done all we
can for now.
I'm sure we'll get another try
at it.
Thanks a lot!
Huh?
[gasp] What do you want?
Shira, I wanna face you in
battle.
You can have this "Heaven"
scroll if I lose.
It's senseless for Sand to fight
Sand.
Besides, we've already made a
decision.
Huh?!
This scroll is useless to us!
Take it!
What?! Oh, wow! You're a real
lifesaver! Thanks!
Uhh...Huh?
To tell you the truth, we don't
even want the scroll.
I just wanna use this as an
opportunity to fight you.
Fight me?
You and I...
...learned almost all we know by
studying under Lord Gaara.
We are the ones who are going to
carry out Lord Gaara's will.
We are the ones who are going
to support the Hidden Sand
Village in the future.
I wanna make sure we truly
deserve that right.
All right.
Let's do it.
Okay?
If this is what you want,
Shira...
Uh...yeah.
Thank you, Shira, really.
So who are your supporters?
The promising power of the
young, the future of the Sand.
I believe in them. They have no
preconceptions and can see with
clear vision.
Those who wish to kill me may do
so...
However, they shouldn't let
those youths become involved in
it.
I don't want them tainted by
hatred and vengeance.
Now! Go!
Right!
[grunt]
There have been many times where
I doubted myself as the
Kazekage.
But after meeting them and
coming to know them, I realized
that perhaps even someone like
me can accomplish something.
I've been reborn. I want to
erase hatred from the Hidden
Sand and create bonds with
people I can call friends who
understand and share each
other's pain.
If you object to that, then you
can take my head.
But leave them out of it.
[gasp]
Come on.
Huh?
[chuckle]
Thank you very much, Shira.
[grunting]
Take this.
[gasping]
Huh?
Well, that's not gonna work!
[laughing]
Seriously?! Oh, come
on, I can't believe this!
[laughing]
Lord Gaara has indeed matured.
It seems the worries that we old
soldiers carried were baseless,
after all...
We must let the horrible
memories of the past fade into
darkness
and leave it to the
next generation to build a
new future.
I take responsibility for
everything.
...That's crazy, right...I hear
that...
[loud exhale]
Please, sir, I beg you to accept
these scrolls!
I'm sorry, two "Heaven" scrolls
are not acceptable!
[yell] But we-!
No! Absolutely not!
I cannot reveal the details, but
extraordinary circumstances
stopped us from getting both
scrolls.
Please, just go ask Lord
Kazekage!
Circumstances don't matter! No
means no!
Meanie!
Now, now...
Give it up.
No! Never! I cannot just give
up!
You wanna cancel the Third
Exam?!
I'm sorry.
I'm afraid I can't give details,
but it's because of a domestic
matter within the Sand.
So how do we know who passed,
then?
We know because we've prepared
deatailed reports about every
team's performance in the Second
Exam.
I'd like the respective villages
to use them to determine who
should pass.
But this isn't just about making
a choice; these exams were to
test their ability to carry out
missions as Chunin!
It can't be helped that things
turned out like this...
But will this satisfy the
participants who put their lives
on the line to survive the Demon
Desert?
I'll address that.
Looks like the Third Exam's
going to be cancelled.
What?! So what about the Chunin
Exams?
I did have a bad feeling about
this whole thing...
[scoff] So does that mean all
the effort we put into this was
for nothing at all?!
We continued to the end and
didn't give up, so we should be
okay.
But those who dropped out
midway are the ones who shouldbe
worried.
I kinda feel bad for them...
It seems like all that we really
got out of this was hunger and
exhaustion.
Yeah, it was all pain and no
gain!
Well, at least we gained some
confidence.
What? Huh? What?
Exam entrants! I commend you!
Just as times change, this
shinobi world of ours needs to
develop a new system with new
laws.
Before, shinobi were required to
sacrifice even the lives of our
comrades for our laws and our
rules.
But I have come to realize
there's something far more
precious than rules and laws.
I'm speaking of friendship with
other villagers and shinobi.
And the bond with those who
understand the same pain.
I believe that every one of you
who stands before me, now, knows
exactly what I'm talking about.
Therefore, I deem the Third Exam
unnecessary.
And, I'm rescinding part of the
Second Exam's requirements.
So what does that mean for us?
The villages of every one of
you, who is standing here right
now, will receive a report of
how you did in the Second Exam.
And then your Kage will make the
final decision on whether to
promote you or not.
[growl] We have to wait longer
to find out?!
Yes, but it also means that we
still have a chance to become
Chunin, correct?!
Listen, when you reach the
northern border, you be careful.
Thanks, I will.
Yome, since you're going, too,
you be nice to him!
What?!
We just got assigned to the same
place by chance, that's all!
Yeah, sure, of course you did!
Go get 'im!
Wha-?!
Yome, let's go!
Oh...
Hey, wait up, Shira!
I hope they're gonna be okay...
We've gone through the report
from the Hidden Sand on the
Second Exam. And your protion to
Chunin has been approved.
Thank you, Lady Angel.
And also,...I'm going to assign
you an S-rank mission right
away.
The corpse today is light.
I've developed a knack for this
over the years. I can tell this
one's probably a woman.
The tallest tower in this whole
village...You know, where we
always deliver the bodies...
You know what it's for?
In a village like ours, towers
are usually where the ashes are
enshrined.
They were originally built as
memorials to honor the fallen.
If that's the case, then why
aren't their relatives allowed
in there anymore?
How should I know?
But actually, there is a rumor
going around about that tower,
you know...
that Lord Pain lives there.
Really? Interesting...
But there's no way.
Well, it is just a rumor,
nothing more.
Never mind.
I'm gonna confirm my theory...
You were right! It's just like
you said...A woman.
Ajisai, a chunin.
She just recently passed the
exams.
Her first mission as a Chunin,
and this is how it ended?
Thank you.
Oh! Lady Angel!
Now quickly...Go and bring the
next one in here.
Yourou!
I know. We're being followed.
Fuu, let's stop at that rocky
area.
Huh?
Aww, if you say so.
We might not know who you are!
But you can bet we're on to you!
I told him to stop! I mean,
after all,...if we didn't get to
kill you, it'd be a real pain!
[gasp]
Wait! Say, mister! Aren't you
from the Hidden Waterfall?
Huh?
What's that?
Yeah! I know you! After you
failed to assassinate the
Hokage, you stole the hearts of
the village elders and escaped!
You're Kakuzu Senpai!
Kakuzu?!
Impossible! He'd be too old!
You know,...I've always thought
if I ever got to meet you, I'd
like to be your friend!
Kakuzu...Is she stupid?
I wouldn't know. I deserted the
village long ago.
How about we start out with some
tea and get to know each other?!
I didn't come here today to
become your friend, you fool...
Well, that really is too bad...
I've thoroughly gone over the
Second Exam reports that we
received from the Sand.
And:...Hinata, Shino, Kiba,
Choji, Ino, and Sakura...You six
passed with flying colors and
are promoted to chunin!
[cheering]
Well,...after all, we were not
able to get the second scroll...
Komugi, Gennai, Inaho...
You will have another chance in
the next Chunin Exams.
[whining gasps}
Finally,...even though they
weren't able to collect both of
the scrolls,...
...they performed admirably, and
they are more than qualified for
promotion.
Lee and Tenten, you are now
chunin.
[giggling sigh]
Lady Tsunade!
Team Guy is one for all, all for
one! So, how can Neji be left
out?!
Let me finish!
[scream]
Neji Hyuga is given a special
double promotion and will become
a jonin!
The Kazekage himself said that,
"Neji's performance was most
impressive and that is reflected
in this report."
He's already proven himself more
than capable of being a
chunin.
Yes, way to go, Neji!
Hey,...Congrat's!
Thank you all, very much!
And thanks to both of you as
well!
I made it to chunin because of
the great teamwork of Team Guy!
Sure thing! Our three-man squad
is forever, right?
Yes. I hope that's true.
And I finally overtook Naruto!
Oh, man. He's gonna be seriously
upset that he missed the Chunin
Exams.
I wonder if Naruto is busy
training, right now...
Soon it'll be time to wrap up
our training and return to the
Hidden Leaf Village.
[sharp inhale]
Guess that chest wound of yours
still hurts, huh?
Well, listen, you just rest up
for now!
I'm gonna continue my training
on my own!
Hang in there, Naruto!
But why?! My jutsu's not
working!
It's because Nine Tails was
extracted! But there's a way to
save him! And that's why we're
hurrying, right now!
There's someone else where
Sasuke is.
You recognize the chakra?
No, but this chakra has a real
nasty feel to it.
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"On the Brink of Death"
Is this where his wind ceases to
blow?