Shikamaru?
Got a sec?
Yeah, what's up?
Ino needs you. What are
you guys doing?
Just sorting these
photographs.
Photos? What for?
They were all salvaged
from the debris.
I'm sure they're
important to someone,
so, frankly, we want to
return them to their
rightful owners.
You want to look through
them and see if you
recognize anyone?
Sure! I'd be happy to
help you out in any way I
can!
Hm. I don't think I
know any of these
people. Huh?!
Wait, is that-?
I just remembered
something I've gotta do!
Mm?
I need to take this photo
with me!
Wait! Naruto!
Oh! That's right...
Do you know if there are
any tulips blooming
nearby?
Oh, you're looking for
tulips? You know, that's
an exceptionally romantic
flower, Naruto.
Flowers often have
symbolic meaning, and
tulips stand for "eternal
love".
I really don't like that
look she's giving me.
I'm pretty sure that the
flower garden on the east
side of the village is
still intact.
Great! Thanks, Shikamaru!
Sure.
What's all that about?
What do you think he
needs tulips for?
Eternal love, huh?
Huh?
[grunting]
Great, it's starting to
rain!
Better get back as fast
as I can!
[screaming]
[grunting]
Man, that hurt...
Huh?!
[screaming]
Whoa. What is that?!
Oh, it's just a rock...
Wait... What is this?
Some kind of tag?
It says... "Kisuke..." I
can't make out the rest.
[gasping]
Uh, oh...
[howling]
Eh!
I'd better get out of
here!
[moaning]
Hey, what's up, Sakura?
Uh, listen, Sakura...
You're kinda hugging me a
little too hard, there...
Sakura, when'd you
get so heavy?!
[screaming]
Who in the heck are you,
mister?! You sure scared
me!
You're the one who scared
me, screaming at me like
you did!
Hey, hold on! Just what
are you doing sneaking
into my house?!
Huh?! I don't know.
Strange... I came to, and
here I was.
What?!
I don't get it. What do
you mean you just "came
to"?
That's ridiculous...
[screaming]
G-G-G- Ghost!
What?! Where?!
There's no ghost or
anything in here! You're
gonna give me a heart
attack!
Mister...
Look in the mirror...
Hm?
Come on, don't be so
sad.
Though I can't say I
blame you.
So, Mister... you
seriously don't remember
dying?
Wait, that's right!
What is it?
I don't remember
anything.
What?!
Actually... I can't even
remember my own name.
That's weird. I've never
heard of a ghost with
amnesia before!
Me, either.
Did you do something that
would make me haunt you?
And why would I do
something like that?!
I mean, I don't even know
you, so why would I have
done anything to you?!
It just doesn't
make any sense!
Wait!
What?!
Come to think of
it, last night...
Back in the hills, I
peeled off this weird
tag...
A what?
Just hold on...
You really think that
turned me into a ghost?
Here, this is it!
Kisuke...?
Kisuke? Is that me?
Well, okay, let's say
that my name is Kisuke...
Who am I? And where did I
come from?
How would I know
something like that?
[sighing]
I guess you're
right.
But if I'm dead now, then
why aren't I able to rest
in peace?
You know, I've heard that
ghosts stay behind
because they have
unfinished business they
need to take care of.
They do? Unfinished
business...
I wonder what...
What am I supposed to do
with this dead guy now?!
"The Man Who Died Twice"
Since no one's freaking
out, I guess I'm the only
one who can see you.
It's probably because you
destroyed that seal.
You're the only one I can
rely on now, Naruto, I
guess.
Yeah, I know... I'll just
have to ask around about
you!
Who? Kisuke? No, don't
know him.
Never heard of the guy.
Sorry, but I don't know
him.
[meowing]
[groaning]
Nothing!
Nobody around here seems
to know you, Mister.
[sighing]
It's no use, huh?
Wait!
I know!
Sorry, you can't see
him, now. Lord Third
Hokage's out.
Why, did something
happen?
He's in a big
meeting. Not that
it's your business.
[groaning]
Boy, that's too bad; I
was certain that Gramps
would know something
useful.
All right, then We'll
have to try someone else.
And as soon as we put
this new security network
in place, we'll be able
to triple the strength of
the Hidden Leaf's defense
system.
Personally, I believe
that this measure is
absolutely essential for
our safety, and I
recommend that you adopt
it.
Yes, duly noted... You
know... This is quite
an excellent plan,
indeed!
We'll make our final
decision this afternoon.
Until then, we'll take a
recess.
Lord Koharu! Lord Homura!
Oh! Sabiru.
Thank you for your time
today.
Excellent proposal.
You've really come up in
the world. It's a
testament to your hard
work.
Thank you very much!
I've dedicated my whole
life to this village.
He's so young, yet he came
up with a whole new security
plan for the entire village.
I'm impressed.
Agreed.
If the measure is
approved when we
reconvene in the
afternoon, then it should
greatly increase the
peace and safety of the
Hidden Leaf Village.
Our luck has
gotta turn around.
[sighing]
I wonder if I'll ever be
able to get my memory
back...
Aw, cheer up, Mister! I'm
sure we'll figure
something out!
Hey! Naruto!
Oh, Sakura!
You missed today's
training exercises! And
just what are you doing
dawdling here?!
Oh, uh, I forgot!
Forgot, huh? That's no
excuse!
Listen! I'm dealing with
a serious situation here!
Oh, yeah; like what?
Just look! See!
Oh, right; I'm the only
person who can see him...
You're not making any
sense, Naruto!
If you keep missing
practice, then I'm going
to tell Sensei!
Okay, okay; I got it!
Yeah, you'd
better.
Aw, come on. What have I
gotten into?!
Sorry about that, Naruto.
Hey! Wait up, Sakura!
What?
By any chance do you
happen to know anyone
named Kisuke?
Kisuke?
No, I don't think so. He
doesn't sound familiar.
Oh--
Wait a sec, maybe I have
heard that name...
You have?!
Please tell me where, and
fast!
Oh! I know!
I had gone to the
hospital to visit a
friend of mine, and
there was a patient in
the back room...
[gasping]
[gulping]
Can't be...
That's me!
Yeah... No wonder you
can't rest in peace,
Mister.
It's 'cause You're
actually still alive!
Alive? How could this
happen to me?
[sighing]
Mister. Mister!
Uh!
Oh. Naruto.
Guess what? I got your
address from the nurse.
Let's go check it out.
Hello? Did you
hear me?
Huh? Oh, right...
So this... was my
house...?
A tulip.
Your neighbor... He told
me your house burned down
a while ago.
I'm sorry to tell you
this... but your wife...
died in the fire as well.
Mister...?
[gasping]
[screaming in pain]
Mister! You okay?
[panting]
I remember now...
What?!
It was... that man...
He sealed me up in that
rock.
What man?
The Anbu Black Ops
assigned me to
investigate if spies had
infiltrated the Leaf
Village.
As I did, I came to
suspect a man named
Sabiru.
He was an exceptional
ninja in the Tactical
Division for Village
Defense. It was thought
he'd guide the Hidden
Leaf into its future.
I couldn't simply accuse
him, not without having
solid evidence first.
In secret, I continued my
investigation without a
word to anyone.
And then...
You can come out now.
Or did you think that I
hadn't noticed you there?
I guess that means you're
on to me, then.
Our little game is over.
[gasping]
So you are a spy!
Uh!
No, you don't!
[grunting]
What?!
What's this?!
It's over.
Damn it.
Fooled you.
Uh!
[gasping]
[screaming]
[gasping for air]
You're pathetic.
You know... I hate
to tell you this, but I
got rid of your wife
right before I came here.
What did you say?!
You monster!
I'll seal your soul here,
and when they find your
body, everyone will
assume that you simply
drowned.
The stress of your
mission, proved too
much, so you got rid of your
wife and threw yourself
in the river.
Such a tragic end for
a husband and wife.
Goodbye!
Soul Detachment Jutsu.
[struggling and screaming]
Hah!
Sabiru's security network
is about to be put in
place, all over the
Hidden Leaf.
And that means, he'll
have complete control
over the Village's
defense system.
That can't be allowed to
happen; we have to stop
him.
But how can we do that?
Uh!
His temperature's
dropping!
And his blood pressure!
Uh!
Nothing's working!
We're losing him!
Losing him? What's
going on?!
You have to go; you're in
our way!
I won't! Not until you
tell me happened!
The life support system
just suddenly stopped.
I'm not getting a pulse!
It's no use...
No way...
No, Mister! You can't
just die now!
[crying]
Mister...
Naruto, don't cry.
[sniffling]
Mister!
Someone turned off my
life support system and
killed me.
What?!
The culprit must be
someone who saw me as a
threat.
Sabiru!
And now, we will vote on
whether to approve
Sabiru's security network
measure for the Hidden
Leaf Village.
All those in favor...
raise your hands!
Well...
Then with a majority
vote, the measure is
approved, and-
I object!
[gasping]
Hear me out before you
decide this!
And who are you?
Kisuke?!
Why have you barged in
here like this?!
I'm Kisuke, and I'm with
the Anbu Black Ops.
I was on a secret mission
to investigate a spy who
had infiltrated the Leaf
Village.
And what does that have
to do with the resolution
that we just voted on?
More than you'd imagine!
Stay calm! If you don't,
the Transformation fails.
Right. Don't worry; I
know that.
[clearing throat]
What I mean is they're
directly connected.
Because the one under
investigation was none
other than Sabiru!
A very serious
accusation!
Please! A moment!
Now, Kisuke... You have
proof of this accusation?
You sealed away my very
spirit! This body right
here is all the proof I
need!
Perhaps... If you are the
real Kisuke, that is...
[gasping]
I received a report that
Kisuke died earlier.
Confirm that!
Right!
[grunting]
Is it all over...?!
Damn!
[gasping and chattering]
That man is an impostor!
Arrest him, now!
[grunting]
Lost track of him.
Uh!
Who are you, really?!
Pretty clever, trying to
surprise me like that.
But, still. If you're
helping Kisuke...
That means you have to
die as well!
So you actually admit
that you killed him and
his wife, too?!
Who are you, brat?!
Answer the question!
And so what if I did!
Then you'll pay!
Looks like you were
right about everything,
Naruto...
Release!
Kakashi?!
Yep. And that "brat"
happens to be one of my
students.
Now talk. Tell us what
you planned to do after
taking control of the
Hidden Leaf's defense
system.
[grunting]
It's over, Sabiru!
Kakashi Sensei, wait!
Mister! This is your
chance to take your
revenge!
Yeah!
Transformation Jutsu!
Now prepare to die! Multi
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Let's go!
Sabiru!
Now take this!
[screaming]
What the--?
Hey!
[grunting]
What is this? Kakashi
Sensei!
He was eliminated!
Thank you, Naruto.
Because of you, the
Hidden Leaf is safe
again.
I didn't do anything!
We're only safe now
because your spirit
hung around.
Oh, don't be so modest.
Yeah, but, Mister...
You're really dead now...
It's okay. I can reunite
with my wife and find
happiness.
But I do have one favor
to ask, Naruto.
Sure! Anything!
If you should ever find
yourself thinking about
me, can you go place some
tulips on our graves for me?
They were my wife's
favorite.
Of course!
Well, Naruto...
Goodbye...
Live a full life for the
both of us!
Wait, Mister!
Okay! I will, Kisuke!
Goodbye!
What is this?! Sasuke,
what is going on?
How should I know?
Besides, whose fault do
you think it is that
we're in this
situation in the
first place?!
You're one to talk!
It's your fault
Sakura got captured!
Quiet! The longer we
argue, the less of a
chance Sakura has of
surviving!
But how can we do
anything like this?!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden, The Worst
Three-Legged Race.
Nothing good ever happens
when you're around.