[panting]
[thunder]
[gasp]
[weeping]
-(VOICEOVER) Huh.
Was I really ever that young?
-Congratulations on delivering
the Feudal Lord safely.
-What do you disapprove of now?
I protected the Feudal
Lord as you asked.
I saved the King's life.
Why won't you acknowledge
what I've done?
-The King, eh?
-You refuse to give me
even a little credit, Dad?
-You still don't understand
how long and difficult
it will be-- the struggle
to protect the King.
You still don't see
how important it is.
-I admit we lost many
men on the mission.
But such sacrifice is
part of being a Shinobi.
-Huh.
It will be a long time, I
foresee, before you understand.
Before you grasp what it really
means to protect the King.
[gasp]
-You refuse to acknowledge me.
I grasp that much.
[door opening and closing]
[birds calling]
-And now, I think
I'm finally starting
to understand what you meant.
I'm sorry I used to duck
out of the village the way
I did, going off on my own.
Not that I regret any of it.
Maybe it wasn't
so bad, after all,
being born into
the Sarutobi clan.
You fulfilled your duty
as leader of the village.
I see that now.
I see how good a
father you were.
[theme music - in japanese]
[construction noises]
[panting]
-Hauling lumber's as good
a mission as any, I guess.
Come on!
Let's show them what we can do!
Here we go!
Oh!
Ahhh!
Hey, what is going
on back there?
[groan]
-Can we-- can we maybe
take a little break now?
-Yeah, we're not used
to this kind of work.
-You guys are lame,
you know that?
-Huh?
-I can't believe I'm hearing
this from you after what we
just went through.
Naruto and the others just
put their lives on the line
to save our village
and the Fifth Hokage.
Don't tell me you're tired now.
We've got a mission to finish.
It's our job to serve this
village, too, any way we can.
-Well said, Konohamaru.
-Hmm?
-You guys are the
next generation
of defenders of the Leaf.
Just like it was Naruto
and his generation who
saved the village this time.
-Iruka-sensei!
-It makes me so proud to
think you're my students.
[weeping]
[nervous laughter]
-OK, Konahamaru.
I'm ready to go now.
-If we all work together,
and do our best,
the village will always
be OK, no matter what.
-Mmm-hmm.
-Next.
Next.
-Next!
-Here.
-Next.
Next.
You're too slow.
Next!
-Huh?
-What's wrong?
Where's the rest of them?
-Uh, my lady, that's it.
You're finished.
-I see.
-Well, this isn't
like you, my lady.
You never used to take your
work quite so seriously before.
-That's true.
-All this trouble and
commotion over a couple
of wretched grave robbers.
-It makes us look
pathetic, Princess Tsunade.
-Yes, indeed it does.
Word of our recent
troubles has spread
to neighboring lands
and the Feudal Lord.
We're a laughing stock.
And it's all because of you.
Your orders were
slow and confused.
-Your lack of
leadership jeopardizes
the safety of the Leaf village.
Along with the title of
Hokage comes responsibilities.
It's time you started
taking them seriously.
-(VOICEOVER) Those
two old geezers.
How dare they talk
to me like that?
Who knows what they would have
said if they'd walked in here
and seen all that work
piled up on my desk.
-Damn!
-Ah!
Almost forgot.
A report just came in
from the-- uh-- man
you sent to look
for Master Jiraiya.
Here.
-Huh?
His report?
So he's back?
-Look at you.
Sneaking out like that before
your injuries had healed.
And what did it get you?
Right back in the hospital.
[laughter]
-It says here, that's
what friends do.
They rush to each other's
aid in times of crisis.
-Huh?
You're reading manga now?
Oh, boy.
You're acting really
random these days, Sai.
Here.
-Hmm?
What's wrong?
-It also says, when
a woman feeds you,
it's a sure sign
that she likes you.
It's not like I'm
testing you, or anything.
-For goodness' sake.
Give me a break, will you?
-Ahh, Sakura.
-Huh?
-I'm already stuffed.
I couldn't eat
another bite, really.
Oh, well, if you insist, Sakura.
OK.
For you, maybe I can--
-I hope you choke on it!
-Hey, guys.
Huh?
[muffled shouting]
-The manner in which Sakura
fed Naruto that apple--
it must mean that she--
-Aaaah, help me!
Why do I have to be on a
team with these morons?
-Huh?
Uh-- what's going on?
-I've confirmed that attacks
on seven different villages
in five neighboring lands
have been carried out
by the same pair of Shinobi.
While there's been no incursion
into the Land of Fire as yet,
I have to believe that
it's only a matter of time.
-Lady Tsunade?
-Hmm.
(VOICEOVER) So the Akatsuki
have finally shown their hand.
-Let's finish it.
-Not yet.
Before doing that, you know that
I have to confer with my lord.
-You can be such a pain
in the neck sometimes.
-It's a pain in the neck
for me as well, you know,
but the commandments are
strict, so I have no choice.
-Ha.
You idiots.
You think you have me
trapped, don't you?
Well, you haven't.
In fact, I'm the
who's trapped you.
Ha.
Now that I know you're both
members of the Akatsuki,
I can't let you escape.
-Well, look at that.
We walked into a trap, Kakuzu.
-No matter.
This makes things even easier.
-I'm Yugito Nii of
the Hidden Cloud.
And you're dead.
-Hey, hey, careful.
You want to watch making
threats like that.
When people get all
full of themselves
and start throwing around
a lot of tough talk,
it really gets me annoyed.
And when I get annoyed,
pretty soon I get mad.
And then I lose my temper!
-Shut up, Hidan.
-OK, OK.
I'm just saying.
When I lose my
temper, I sometimes
get an overwhelming urge to
forget about the objective
and smash everything in my path.
-Knock it off.
Our mission is
clear and absolute.
-Heh.
Yeah well, this whole mission
goes against all my beliefs.
The way of Jashin
is total slaughter.
There's even an
actual commandment
that prohibits half-killing.
I don't really feel
like doing a job that
requires me to
break a commandment.
I may not look it, but
I'm a very pious person.
So to have to resist killing
you is a huge struggle for me.
Perhaps we can resolve
this through negotiation.
-Through negotiation?
(VOICEOVER) Is he insane?
-Hmm.
[laughter]
-Come on.
Why don't you just
surrender and come with us?
-You must be joking.
-I guess I'll take
that as a no, then.
-Are you an idiot?
[roaring]
-Oh, come on.
Are you kidding me?
[growling]
-What kind of
Jinchuriki is this?
She's completely turned herself
over to the tailed beast.
[growling]
-Oh!
-Uh-oh.
Ah.
This stupid thing.
It must like its supper hot.
[growling]
-So that must be the Two-Tails
Cat Spirit, also known
as the Wraith.
Well, I guess this means I'm
the mouse in the trap, huh?
Ha, ha.
I am not amused.
-So.
I hear you guys did all
right for yourselves
while I was gone.
-Speaking of which, where were
you, anyway, Kakashi-sensei?
-Eh, nowhere special.
-Asuma-sensei.
-Huh?
-I thought you'd be here.
I need to talk to you, Kakashi.
-Really?
-I mean, if you've got a minute.
Oh, Naruto, Sai.
I brought a get-well present.
-No, no, no!
I don't even want to
see another apple.
-So.
I hear you went out to
get a look at what's
going on out there.
-Something like that.
-Beautiful day, huh?
-Hmm?
Yes, it is.
-Naruto and Sakura are
certainly coming a long well.
-Yeah, they are.
But so are Shikamaru,
Choji, and Ino.
The next generation
is growing up fast.
They'll be leaving us in
the dust before you know it.
-Hey, wait a minute.
I'm not ready to
pack it in just yet.
[laughter]
-Still, their progress is
good news for the Leaf.
-Hmm.
Well, what did you
want to talk about?
-Eh-- well, it's like this.
-There you are.
Just who I was looking for.
-Hello, Kunani.
What's going on?
-I just came here to find Asuma.
-I see.
So anyway, what
was on your mind?
-Oh, that's all right.
It's something that can wait.
No big deal.
-(VOICEOVER) Now he's
really got me wondering.
-Huh?
What do you think
you're doing, Naruto?
-I don't have time to be lying
around here in a hospital bed.
I've got to get
back to my training.
The clock's ticking.
-Well, that may be,
but you're still not--
-You don't have to say it.
I'm still not strong enough.
But that's why.
That's my whole point.
I have to make
myself strong enough
to master this power
of mine so that I
can use it to protect
people, not hurt them.
-Naruto--
-Woah.
Hold your horses.
-Hmm?
-For right now, healing those
injuries is your training.
-Oh, come on, sensei.
-Listen up.
And this goes especially
for you, Naruto.
-Huh?
-The next phase of your training
will be so severe, so intense,
that if you leave this
hospital before you're ready,
you'll wish you hadn't.
[gulp]
-I was only-- OK, OK.
I understand.
-(VOICEOVER) Hmm.
There.
That ought to make him stay put.
-Sakura.
-Um, yes?
-I have some things
to take care of,
so I leave their
supervision to you.
-Uh--
-Just make sure they
don't overdo it.
You know what I mean.
See you.
-He's so slick, the
way he does that.
-I've read your report.
Are you sure that Naruto
can learn this new jutsu?
Well, Kakashi?
-No.
I'm not sure.
-What?
-I can't say for certain.
But I think he probably can.
The new training
regimen is working well,
and more importantly, he'll have
a clear and powerful objective.
-Sasuke Uchiha.
-It's been 30 minutes already.
Aren't you done yet?
-Will you shut up?
You're interrupting the ritual.
Ow.
Ugh.
-You perform that vulgar
prayer each and every time.
Can't you abbreviate it at all?
Let's get going.
-I find it tedious, but a
commandment is a commandment.
It must be obeyed.
And how dare you
suggest I abbreviate it?
Blasphemous unbeliever!
-We still have one
assignment left.
It's like finding a
needle in a haystack.
The Land of Fire is next.
[theme music - in japanese]
-Good grief.
Naruto has gone back
into training again,
even though he's still not 100%.
Well, no surprise.
He always was headstrong.
But he doesn't get that
willpower isn't enough anymore.
Even if he's not
physically ready,
this training could
have the reverse effect
of what's intended.
On top of that, because
of his special abilities,
he's always in danger of pushing
it to the limit, and beyond.
I've got to do whatever
I can to help him out.
-Next time.
Akatsuki's Invasion.