[roar]
[growl]
[angry roar]
I don't want to believe that
Lord Third planned all of
this in order to
return to power...
[gasp]
Kakashi...
Kakashi!
Hm?
Huh?
[sigh]
So he's back to
ignoring me, huh.
[street chatter]
Wood Style!
Giant Forest Jutsu!
Who's that boy who
can use Wood Style?
Maybe I'll find some
information there.
"The Works of the
First Hokage."
Aha! Found it!
Hashirama Senju.
The leader of the Senju
Clan of the Forest.
He brought peace and
stability to this bloody,
war-torn world. He
and he alone mastered
Wood Style Ninjutsu.
He and he alone mastered
No. There's another.
What does this mean? How is
he able to use Wood Style?
"Top secret?"
Where are the files?!
Is this what you
are looking for?
[gasp]
Professor!
It's all right. I
give you my permission.
Go on, read it.
Yes, sir.
Long ago, the First Hokage,
Lord Hashirama, after his
death match with Madara,
used the Wood Style
to suppress the Nine Tails.
After that, there was
no one else to carry on
the Wood Style Jutsu.
Either the Sharingan
or Wood Style is needed
to suppress Tailed Beasts.
Now, there was a period
of time in the Hidden Leaf
Village when researchers
tried to revive the First
Hokage's Wood Style Jutsu.
However...
Despite the dedicated
efforts of many, the tests
to transplant Lord
Hashirama's cells all
failed, one after another.
The number of lives
lost kept increasing.
And so, unfortunately,
that jutsu...
...was deemed a Forbidden
Jutsu and sealed away.
But, as of late...
There have been some genin
and chunin, and even members
of the ANBU that have
mysteriously gone missing.
What is even more
disturbing is that
we've also had reports
of incidents in which
newborn infants
have been kidnapped
from some of the smaller
hamlets that surround the
Hidden Leaf Village.
[gasp] Infants?!
All told, we've confirmed
sixty kidnappings, and
those are just the
ones we know of.
Who would?!
Indeed...
Now, what I'm about to tell
you is merely hearsay...
But I believe that
someone is continuing the
experiments and trying
to implant the cells of
Lord Hashirama.
Even if they're rumors,
why would anyone--
There are those who
want to obtain every
jutsu that exists.
At times, even I've wondered
how things would be if there
were only someone who
knew Wood Style.
Had that been the case,
then perhaps the Fourth
Hokage need not have
sacrificed his life.
But...
[gasp]
To be frank, isn't
that one of the reasons
why Lord Fourth lost
his life that night.
Mind you, all of this is
nothing more than hearsay.
Hmm, but if...
But if Lord Hashirama's
cells actually had been
implanted into
those infants...
Implanting any cells
into infants is strictly
forbidden, of course.
And even if someone were
to do so, the possibility of
success would be low.
However, perhaps
if one of the
first infants who
were kidnapped
somehow managed to survive
such a procedure,
they would be approximately
ten years old by now.
Ten years old...
Are you all here?
Yes, sir!
Now then, tomorrow morning,
the Third Hokage and five
ANBU under his direct
command will depart
the Leaf for the Feudal
Lord's prefecture.
The objective he's after
is to retake his post
as Hokage now that
Lord Fourth's gone.
If we allow this to
happen, the Hidden Leaf
Village will once again
be forced to accept a
weak and indecisive leader.
For the sake of the
village, we must prevent
that at all costs.
Therefore, your mission is
simple. Somewhere along
the route, take the life
of Lord Third quickly
and discreetly.
But remember, this must be
kept secret. It must appear
that it was the work
of rogue shinobi.
Understood?!
Yes, sir!
Lord Third?
Are you ready?
I am. Let's depart!
Enemy attack!
Wood Style Jutsu!
What?!
[groaning]
A Substitution?!
Agh!
Wood Style! Giant
Forest Jutsu!
Chidori!
[grunt]
You! Where did
you learn Wood Style?
I didn't expect
an answer anyway...
Go.
Huh?
Leave! Quickly! That jutsu
of yours will be critical to
the Leaf Village one day.
It appears that they were
after Lord Third and Lord
Third alone. And it
seems that their
purpose was to
separate us from him.
They all scattered
somewhere.
Were you all right here?
Yes.
Did you recognize
the enemy?
No... I don't
know who it was.
Well, that's all right.
I'm sure Lord Third will
take care of the rest.
I regret to inform you
that I won't be giving
up that seat just yet.
It seems like you want to
ask me why I'm still alive.
Of course not! I just
thought that you'd left this
morning for the Feudal
Lord's prefecture.
A certain someone
betrayed me.
No, instead, he
came back to me
in order to warn me and
the others that we would be
targeted on the way
to the prefecture.
I could easily find out
who was behind this.
And that person
would be executed.
That is as clear as day.
However, it's against my
principles to bring about
any more death.
If I could speak with that
person, I'd tell him...
That I will overlook his
actions this one time.
But in exchange, he
must do everything that
is within his power.
For the sake of
Hidden Leaf Village.
[growl] You and your
absurd ideals of peace.
Your lukewarm naiveté
is certain to be your
undoing one day, Hiruzen.
Hmm. Perhaps you're right.
We've always been this way.
You are the light
and I am the darkness.
Wherever there is light,
there is also darkness.
But losing either one
causes disruption and
imbalance in the world.
[harrumphing chuckle]
Professor, I don't think I'm
qualified to be in the ANBU.
Why is that? It is thanks
to you that I'm still alive.
Still, I nearly
betrayed you once.
Hmm...
I wasn't able to protect
the Fourth Hokage.
I wouldn't blame you if
you hate me for that.
You know, when Minato was
still alive, he came to talk
to me about you.
[gasp]
I had hoped that he
could forget the pain
in his heart, even
just a little bit...
That's why I assigned
him to the ANBU.
But based on the rumors that
I've heard about him lately...
I'm afraid that I might've
just made his wounds deeper.
So now, I'm regretting it.
Unfortunately, no one
can mend another's
wounded heart.
Time is the only thing that
can truly heal all wounds.
Yes.
Well.
There may be a solution...
Perhaps you could give
him the assignment
to guard Kushina.
If he leaves his ANBU
duties to watch over
someone who's about to
bring a new life into
the world, perhaps it will
trigger a change in him.
You're right!
When Minato died...
For one fleeting moment, I
considered releasing you
from the ANBU.
But right now, I am in
great need of your strength.
Yes, sir!
So, will you cotinue on as a
member of the ANBU, but one
who reports directly to me?
Yes!
I just hope that Minato
will forgive me, as well.
Lord Third, there's
something I need to tell you.
Hm?
A Wood Style user's
in the Foundation.
It's just as I
thought, then...
I have a good idea
of who it must be...
Leave this situation
to me; I'll handle it.
Yes, sir.
Ah, I see! So once
again, you will be
filling the post,
Lord Third.
I am relieved to hear that.
You already have the
experience and knowledge.
Is that man not
here today?
You know who I mean,
that angry-looking
one who has the
fearsome eye.
Are you speaking
of Danzo, sir?
Yes, that's it!
He's the one!
He had an urgent matter to
attend to, so he wasn't able
to be here with us today.
Oh- oh, I see, good!
I just don't feel very
comfortable around him...
We have to avoid any direct
contact between the two of
us for the time being.
Did something happen?
Kakashi has betrayed
me, and I believe
there's a possibility that
Hiruzen knows about us.
That would not
be good at all.
In time, he might
learn all about this
place and its secrets.
Well, it is Lord Third;
he'll be on to us
eventually. He's probably
already guessed.
He must never
find out about us.
Kakashi...
[grunt]
It won't come off!
I heard that Lord
Third is reassuming
the title of Hokage.
I thought that this whole
changing of the guard thing
was gonna mean a
new era for the Leaf.
I know what you mean, Genma.
I thought the same thing.
Hey... It's not going to be
easy for Lord Third, you
know! Not at his age!
Well, we just have to
do our best for the
village, that's all.
I say that we celebrate the
return of Lord Third by
having some more
yummy dumplings!
Yeah!
Huh?
[nervous swallow]
Wait! It's just me!
It's Guy, Kakashi!
Agh!
You were really
out to get me!
I thought you were
gonna kill me!
Yeah, me, too. What the
hell were you thinking?!
I was just- I just
wanted to lure you into
continuing our
rivalry showdowns.
[sigh] I'm sorry.
This emergency summons
has been issued for the
immediate capture
of Orochimaru, who
escaped during the
previous mission.
The knowledge, data, and
jutsu he possesses are
valuable assets to the Leaf.
If he's allowed to leave the
Land of Fire, it would be a
dire or fatal blow
to the Leaf!
Therefore...
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Rogue
Ninja Orochimaru"
You... I like the
look in your eye.