-There's no presence of anyone
around the Tenchi bridge yet.
-Well, I guess that
rules out one thing--
there's no Akatsuki ambush.
All right.
Then that means we'll proceed
according to the plan.
NARUTO: Right.
-Here, Naruto.
Could you take this picture
and hold it up in front of me?
Yeah, yeah.
That's right.
Just face it toward me.
Wood Style Transformation.
Well, did it turn out OK?
-Yeah.
It's amazing.
You look exactly like
Sasori's puppet, Hiroko.
-Excellent.
Now I have to match the voice.
Let me know when it
sounds close to Sasori.
-Yes, sir.
[singing in different pitches]
-There.
You've got it.
That's Sasori's voice.
-All right.
If you're all ready, shall
we begin the operation?
-Hold it.
Your tone's too polite.
Try to sound more--
oh I don't know.
Way more aggressive
or something.
-Oh.
Yeah.
You're right.
I'm supposed to be cranky
and irritable, and more
than anything, I hate
to be kept waiting.
We're starting
the operation now!
-You nailed it.
That's exactly what
he sounds like.
-Listen up.
Our opponents will
be on the alert,
so I want us to split up.
We'll have to work as a
team, especially you, Naruto.
No one makes a move
before I give the signal.
Let's go!
OK.
This is it.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
The wind's strong here.
Good.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sakura.
-Yeah.
This spot should be fine.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
It's almost noon.
-That lousy spy.
Why isn't he showing up?
SAI: He's here.
[theme music]
-That must be the guy.
SASORI: Go to the Tenchi
Bridge in the Village
Hidden in the Grass.
Ten days from now at noon,
one of Orochimaru's henchmen
is working for me
as a spy, and that's
where I'm supposed to
rendezvous with him.
However, I don't think I'll--
YAMATO (VOICEOVER):
So, that's him.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Good
luck, Captain Yamato.
-It's been a long
time, Lord Sasori.
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): That's--
-About five years, right?
YAMATO (VOICEOVER):
Kabuto Yakushi.
-Were you followed?
-It's just you and me.
-How do you feel?
-Well, I still haven't
shaken that strange sensation
from when your jutsu broke and
I remembered who I was again.
My head still feels
clouded and heavy.
-No way.
He's back?
-It's crazy.
So the Akatsuki spy
was actually Kabuto.
-I have a few questions for you.
-I don't have much time,
so please keep it brief.
I risked my life
sneaking out to meet you
without Orochimaru finding out.
-I want information
about Sasuke,
as well as the location
of your boss's hideout.
-Orochimaru has
several hideouts.
We keep moving to a
different one every week
to avoid being
discovered by the enemy.
Of course, many are in
the Hidden Sound Village,
but some hideouts are
in other lands too.
He has spies everywhere
acting as his eyes and ears.
There are so many ways a
person could get around.
It's not easy to track them.
-The current hideout?
-Right now Orochimaru's holed
up on a small Island on a lake
just to the north of here.
We'll be moving
again in three days.
Sasuke Uchiha is there as well.
NARUTO: The wind
is so loud I can't
hear a word they're saying.
SAKURA: Ugh.
You're such an idiot.
That's why we were able to
sneak this close in first place.
The wind blows away our
scent and hides our sound.
Why do you think he
hasn't noticed us?
-Oh.
By the way-- it was nothing.
Just a wild rabbit.
As I was saying,
we should discuss
the orders you gave
me, Lord Sasori.
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): Uh-oh.
I still had a few
more things I wanted
to ask him while
I had the chance.
If the conversation goes on
much longer, I'd be discovered.
-Even after
re-animation, Orochimaru
uses a Protection
Jutsu on the specimens
from his discarded
vessel, so I was
unable to analyze their cellular
structure as you commanded me.
-I see.
NARUTO: What's he waiting for?
He should just grab the
guy while his guard's down.
-Have you forgotten
that's Kabuto?
Playing it safe is the
right way to handle it.
Besides, if he
manages to escape,
this was all for nothing.
SAI: But if he
takes too much time,
then the spy might
get suspicious.
And then our whole plan
would be put into jeopardy.
-Maybe.
But we have no choice but to
trust the captain's judgment.
KABUTO: Now, I trust you brought
the item you promised me.
Let's do the hand-off.
I've spent too much
time here as it is.
If I were to be discovered
speaking with you like this,
Orochimaru will
certainly kill me.
-I'm aware.
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): I
can't stall any longer.
I have to take him right now.
OROCHIMARU: Your conversation
sounds intriguing.
I hope neither of you would
mind if I joined in the fun.
-Huh?
YAMATO (VOICEOVER):
He was just followed.
-Orochimaru!
SAI (VOICEOVER): So that's him.
-Lord Sasori, if you hadn't
pulled out the kunai,
I wouldn't have gotten
away from him in time.
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): Lucky.
Looks like he misunderstood.
I guess my cover
hasn't been blown yet.
However, now that Orochimaru
has shown up-- now what do I do?
-I remember that garb.
It sure brings back
memories, Sasori.
-So you followed
Kabuto, did you?
-Oh.
I just wanted to
thank you in person.
After all, you're the one
who sent this kid to me,
and he's come in very handy.
The development of any new
jutsu usually eats up well
over a hundred
human test subjects,
but thanks to your spy's
Medical Ninjutsu skills,
I've been able to reuse my
test subjects again and again.
For some reason it's always
so hard to find volunteers.
-Sakura, what are we gonna do?
-Until we see him
give the signal,
we'll just have to stand by.
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): Taking
on Orochimaru by myself
would be virtually impossible.
And even if I work alongside
Kabuto to beat him back,
Kabuto would tell
by my fighting style
that I'm not really Sasori.
I could summon my
three teammates,
but my identity
would be revealed,
and Kabuto would flee
before we captured him.
Either I call in the others and
try to defeat both these guys,
or maintain my cover
and retreat right now.
OK.
Time to decide.
Did he know who I was?
No.
He couldn't have.
Then what's going on here?
-Multiple Striking Shadow Snake!
-That was a Wood
Style substitution.
Interesting.
You must be--
-Lord Orochimaru, is that
form Sasori's real body?
-Sasori?
Definitely not.
Oh, Kabuto.
You mean all this time
as his faithful servant,
and you've yet to see
the man's real face?
-Hm.
Well he always hides it behind
those weird puppets of his.
The man is such
as dreary fellow.
-What is the
meaning of all this?
Kabuto, you were supposed
to be an Akatsuki spy.
Shouldn't you have
been controlled
by Sasori's jutsu
this whole time?
-Not any longer.
Lord Orochimaru broke
that jutsu long ago.
-So you pretended to
be under Sasori's jutsu
all the while having
turned traitor?
Or did Orochimaru use
his powers to turn you?
-Oh no.
You've got it wrong.
The fact of the
matter is I empathize
with Lord Orochimaru's ideals.
Who are you anyway?
The plan was to come
take care of Sasori,
but your presence
changes things.
OROCHIMARU: Kabuto, I can fill
you in about this child later
on.
For now, why don't you signal to
the three baby rats behind you
to come on out.
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): So he
must have known all along.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
There's the signal.
-Well, it's you again.
-Mm.
I know that face all too well.
And it looks like the
Nine-Tails tagged along.
Well, we might as well
have a little fun together.
OROCHIMARU: Let's find out
who's gotten stronger--
you or Sasuke?
[theme music]
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER): My, my.
You're starting to act like a
jinchuriki, aren't you, Naruto?
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): Is he--
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): What
kind of chakra is that?
SAI (VOICEOVER):
The air, it stings.
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): It's got
to be the Nine-Tails' Cloak.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): The
jinchuriki host's power.
This must be it.
I can tell just by feeling it.
This chakra, it's horrible.
It's not a chakra that
can be controlled.
SAI (VOICEOVER): So this is
Naruto's power, the Nine-Tails'
power.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next time--
The Nine-Tails Unleashed!
[theme music]
-Lord Orochimaru has been
re-animated three times
thus far.
Details about the
first time are sketchy.
When the Leaf Village
was destroyed,
it was already his second body.
He wanted the body
of Itachi Uchiha who
possesses the Sharingan,
but he could not get it.
Instead, he tried to entice
Itachi's younger brother,
Sasuke over to his
side with some help
from Kimimaro and
the Sound Four.
But in a battle with
the Third Hokage,
both of Orochimaru's
arms were sealed,
and his body reached
its limit too quickly.
The situation was dire, so I
had the remaining test subjects
battle each other, and
chose the last one standing
to serve as the next host.
That would be his
current form, Genyumaru.
It's been three
years since then,
and I'm proud to say that his
next vessel is nearly complete.
But I'm just thinking out loud.
Don't pay any attention.
[chuckling]