[music playing]
TSUNADE: It's been a
long time, you two.
Your training proved
to be fruitful, I hope.
-You think we would
have come back
without producing any results?
-Mission accomplished, Grandma.
-Huh.
I'm glad to hear it.
Show me what you got, kid.
-What, right now?
TSUNADE: I have someone
I'd like you go up against.
I've kept him off
missions the last few days
so he'd be ready for
just this moment.
Your opponent will be--
[knock on door]
TSUNADE: Come in.
[creaking]
-Huh?
SHIKAMARU: Hey.
-Hey, Shikamaru, Temari.
Look what the cat dragged in.
-Hmm?
Is that-- it is!
Naruto, it's you.
-Hey, Shikamaru.
TEMARI (VOICEOVER): Is that
the same little squirt?
-Well, well.
You're back, huh?
-Yeah, got back today.
-Look at you.
Who'd ever believe you're
the same idiotic-- well,
I mean to say, you've
changed, haven't you?
[chuckling]
-He hasn't changed at all.
-I didn't think so.
[sigh]
-Give me a break, Sakura.
[laughter]
-Huh?
Hey, wait-- does this mean
you're my opponent, Shikamaru?
-Opponent?
What are you talking about?
I just came over here to
drop off some paperwork.
-Oh.
Well, if it's not
you, then is it,
uh-- what's your name again?
-You don't remember me?
-Naruto, you won't find
your opponent in here.
He's out there.
-Eh?
-So, Naruto-- you went
and got all grown up.
[gasp]
-Kakashi-sensei!
[MUSIC - NOBODYKNOWS+, "HERO'S
COME BACK"]
-Well, you haven't
changed a bit, sensei.
Oh, wait a sec.
Hang on, I got something
for you, sensei.
A little present.
KAKASHI: Hmm?
-Just like old times, huh?
-Yeah.
-No way!
[thunder]
-Is that-- is that really--
[trumpets]
-The first new issue
of the "Make Out"
series in three years.
Pretty boring, if you ask me,
but I know you like this stuff,
so--
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): Hmph.
Little idiot.
But you can't expect a kid to
appreciate great literature.
People would kill for a copy.
Hasn't even been released yet.
[heartbeat]
-Whoa.
[giddy laughter]
-Calm down.
This is no time to be
fooling around, Kakashi.
-Hmm?
So I guess-- are
you my opponent?
-Well, you're half right.
Hmm.
Been a long time
hasn't it, Sakura?
-Yes it has, sensei.
KAKASHI: So as to who
my opponent will be--
-Hmm.
- --it's Naruto and
Sakura, the two of you.
[gasp]
-Huh?
Both of us at once, sensei?
-That's right.
Kakashi will put
you to the test.
How well you do against him will
determine your future status.
-Huh, their future status.
-Sakura, it's time to show
that your training with me
wasn't a waste of time.
-Right.
KAKASHI: So, shall
we get started?
OK, you're right.
You've just got back, Naruto.
You must be tired.
We'll give you a
chance to rest first.
-I'm not tired.
I'm ready to go right now.
-No, you take it easy.
I'll meet you later at
the training grounds.
So long.
-Well, that's odd, isn't it?
He seemed in a hurry.
-Yeah, and I have a
pretty good idea why.
-Can't wait to read that book.
-Eh?
-That explains it.
That gleam in his eye.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): Of
course he wants to read it.
Who in his right
mind wouldn't want
to read my book before
anyone else does?
NARUTO: Kakashi-sensei-- I'm
sorry I ever gave it to him.
That stupid book's
more important to him
than our training.
-No accounting for taste.
At least now, we'll have
time to discuss strategy.
-Ooh.
Hey, are you two
going out or what?
-Not even close, idiot.
-Hah, you've got to be joking.
Like I would ever even.
The chunin exams
are about to start.
I've been busy running back
and forth between your village
and mine getting ready for them.
-Yeah, that's right.
And I'm her escort.
It's a drag.
And don't ask how it
happened, but I've
been put in charge of
organizing the chunin exams.
-The chunin exams, huh?
Man, that takes me back.
-Yeah, well speaking
of which, what
are you going to do, Naruto?
-About what?
What do you mean?
-What do you think?
About the chunin exams.
You're the only one in our
year who isn't a chunin.
Everyone is but you.
[music playing]
[scream]
-Sakura, you've
been made a chunin?
-(CHUCKLING) That's right.
-Oh, you haven't even
heard the half of it.
Kankuro, Neji, and
Temari here, they've
even taken it a step further.
They've already been made jonin.
-Jonin?
What are you talking about?
Huh?
What about Gaara?
What's he?
-Lord Kazekage, the
meeting is about to begin.
-Very well.
-I see.
So Gaara was named Kazekage.
That's great.
-Huh?
-Hmm.
Well, I'm not about
to be outdone by him.
-Mm?
-I'm still gonna
be Hokage one day.
Just you wait, Gaara!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Funny, I
think he has grown up a bit.
JIRAIYA: What do you think?
Not bad, huh?
If you ask me, it's the
best one I've ever written.
[chuckling]
-I'm delivering Naruto into
your hands as promised.
-I can see he's grown all
right, but has he grown up?
-Huh, you implying I
haven't done my job?
Oh, go ahead, underestimate him.
You'll be sorry.
-Well, that sounds encouraging.
-The ones we've been watching
are about to make their move.
-Over the last few
years, our village
has enjoyed stability and
prosperity, largely due
to our dealings with the Hidden
Villages of the Allied Lands.
To give one example
of this, our recruits
are better trained thanks
to new training methods,
methods learned from
the Leaf Village.
-We'll see how much
better they are.
The chunin exams
are almost upon us.
-Correct.
And that's why these nasty
rumors are specially troubling
right now.
-Rumors, Yura?
-Yes, sir.
Have you ever heard of a
group called the Akatsuki?
-I see.
So they're finally coming
out of the woodwork.
-It's no surprise.
Bound to happen sooner or later.
-The Akatsuki.
-The Akatsuki is a
mysterious organization
comprised of a
dozen or so shinobi.
Every one of its members is
listed in the "Bingo Book"
as ruthless S-rank criminals.
Of those who have
been identified,
one is Itachi Uchiha
of the Village Hidden
in the Leaves, a
man who annihilated
his own clan in a single night.
Another is Kisame Hoshigaki, one
of the seven ninja swordsmen,
the Phantom of the Mist Village.
Then there's Orochimaru, the
assassin of our late Kazekage,
who came so close to
destroying the Leaf.
It is said that even he
too was once a member.
-So why do you think they're
finally showing their hand?
What are they after?
-There ultimate objective
is still unclear,
but I know one thing-- they
want the fox spirit that Naruto
carries within himself.
As to why-- well,
you can be sure
they have some evil
purpose in mind.
That's why I've been
going around spreading
the word to all our allies.
Something's coming, so they'd
better boost their security
and keep on their toes.
-I see.
Yes, I've heard something
of this myself recently.
So they're finally
making their move.
-We have this information from
one of the legendary Sannin,
Master Jiraiya himself.
So before this
meeting was convened,
I took the liberty of ordering
the village to be secured
and I've stationed ANBU
Black Ops at key points
on the perimeter.
No matter how clever
these shinobi may be,
if they hope to take us by
surprise, they're mistaken.
We've heard that they often
wear distinctive black cloaks
emblazoned with red clouds.
If our lookouts
spot such a cloak,
they've been ordered by
me to attack at once.
[murmuring]
BAKI: Very well, then.
This meeting is adjourned.
-Well done, Yura.
We're all impressed by the
promptness and prudence
of your actions.
-Hm.
Well, I have had a seat
on the Council of Advisors
for four years, and I've
learned that I must--
[grunt]
-(STRAINED) --be able to
make decisions on my own--
-Huh?
-(STRAINED) --while always
considering the best interests
of the village.
[grunt]
-What's wrong?
-Nothing!
It's nothing.
I'm just tired, that's all.
-Careful.
You push yourself too hard.
-Thank you for your concern.
[groaning]
YURA (VOICEOVER): I see.
So that's what's--
[bell jingling]
-The one who's in place here
will be the first, it seems.
The one we sent to
Orochimaru will have to wait.
This one's turned
traitor and has
been talking about
our movements.
Hmm.
-Can't be helped, I suppose.
But even I don't know what will
happen once the jutsu is cast.
Are you sure what you've got
in that pouch will be enough?
Our enemy possesses
the jinchuuriki host.
-Every one of my jutsu
is a work of art.
But just to be sure, I brought
along of my masterpiece.
Hmm.
We can't take any chances when
our opponent is the One-Tail.
[chuckling]
-Oh, come on!
Is Kakashi-sensei gonna keep
us waiting here forever?
-Well, he's always
been like this.
-Yeah, I know, but I thought
he would have grown up by now.
[chuckling]
-Huh?
-Sorry to keep you waiting.
I, uh, ran into
this poor old lady
who needed help carrying some--
-(IN UNISON) Would
you give us a break?
-Oh wow, does this
bring back memories.
-Your assignment is very simple.
You just have to take
these bells from me.
That's all there is to it.
If you can't get 'em by
noon, you go without lunch.
-Waa!
-You'll be tied to
those posts and you'll
watch while I eat my
lunch in front of you.
[bells jingling]
-Oh, that's right.
This was the site of your
very first training lesson,
wasn't it?
-It was Squad 7.
-The three of us together.
-That's right.
We had Sasuke with us
back then, didn't we?
-Don't leave me!
If you go, I'll scream and--
-Sakura.
Thank you for everything.
[sobbing]
[thump]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Sasuke.
-Sasuke!
-So it's you.
Hopeless little knucklehead.
-Huh.
-Hmm?
Whoops.
-Remember that
time with Sasuke--
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
I guess Sasuke's name
is taboo to these guys.
[bells jingling]
-Huh?
-All right.
Show me how far you've come.
After all, you haven't given
up on your Sasuke, have you?
-Not a chance.
-What the heck do you
think I put myself
through all this training for?
-Hm.
The rules are the same as
they were that first day.
I don't care how you do it, just
get these bells away from me.
And remember--
-If we're not
prepared to kill ya--
- --we won't get the bells.
We know.
-You can use any weapons,
including shuriken.
If you're not
prepared to kill me,
you won't be able
to take the bells.
[bells jingling]
-(CHUCKLING) Exactly.
Show no mercy if you ever
hope to get these bells.
You've got till
sunrise tomorrow.
[music playing]
-OK, shall we get started?
-Heh heh, are you gonna be
reading that stupid book
the whole time, Kakashi-sensei?
-No he won't.
I bet he already
finished reading it.
-Not quite, but I'm going
to save that little pleasure
for later.
Besides, I've got a feeling
I'd better keep on my toes.
It's a whole new ball game.
This time, it's serious.
[bells jingling]
-Hmm?
-What have we here?
[music playing]
[gasp]
-Black cloaks with
red clouds on them.
It's them!
Must be.
Captain Yura must
be told at once.
Captain Yura, the ones you
were waiting for, they're here.
-So I see.
-No need to worry.
This won't take long.
[bells jingling]
-Good work, Yura.
You remember me, I presume?
-How could I
forget, Lord Sasori?
[music playing]
[bells jingling]
-What are we waiting for?
[MUSIC - HOME MADE KAZOKU,
"SHOOTING STAR"]
[music playing]
JIRAIYA: The time
has finally come
to unveil my latest masterpiece.
The world has had to wait
three years since my last tour
de force, "Make Out Violence,"
but the wait is over.
"Make Out Tactics" is here!
You'll laugh, you'll
cry, you'll forget
to eat or bathe or breathe.
And you'll be swept up in
this stirring, soulful saga
full of deep meaning
and pretty girls.
Order your copy today!
NARUTO: Pervy sage, stop
pluggin' your stupid book!
Next time, "The
Results of Training."
[MUSIC - HOME MADE KAZOKU,
"SHOOTING STAR"]
[school chimes]
-All right, it looks
like everyone's here.
Today, we're going to be
learning about the chunin
exams, so I want you
all to listen up.
Twice every year, the allied
nations of the Land of Fire
select their most
outstanding genin.
These genin are then
brought together
to participate in
the chunin exams.
Not only is it an opportunity
for these young genin
to be promoted to chunin, it
is also an opportunity for them
to defend the honor and status
of their respective nations.
In other words, they compete
not only for themselves,
but for their homelands.
All right, here's a
question-- in the exams
in which Narrator and
the others competed,
which Leaf ninja was it who
earned promotion to chunin?
[beep]
IRUKA: The answer
is Shikamaru Nara.
Yeah, it's hard to believe, but
he's now a full-fledged chunin.
This shiftless, lazy,
constantly complaining kid
is the same rank as me.