-Sakura!
-Lady Chiyo.
How are you holding up?
Can you still move?
-Oh?
Still worried about her even
with a sword through your gut?
CHIYO (VOICEOVER): Sasori.
But how?
No, it can't be.
Of course.
So that's it.
-If you're a medical
ninja, then you
should understand exactly
how dire your situation is.
-Shut up.
-You're quite a courageous
girl, but how much longer can
you really hold on?
SASORI (VOICEOVER): What?
She's stopping the bleeding
while my sword is still
through her?
She's got skill.
-Listen to me, Lady Chiyo.
Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine.
I want you to take the antidote.
-But Sakura.
-It appears the poison is
starting to take effect.
You see, my sword was also
coated with poison, just
in case.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): My body's
getting numb from the point.
I'm losing control of my chakra.
[theme music]
-I see.
So that's the antidote.
-Why?
Why did you-- Lady Chiyo.
You OK?
SASORI (VOICEOVER):
I can't believe
these people would choose death
to save someone else's life.
They're so stupid.
-I won't give up.
SASORI (VOICEOVER):
I don't get it.
How can she be this strong?
-Come on.
Hang in there.
SASORI (VOICEOVER): If
it's a battle of strength,
there's no way I'll outlast her.
Fine.
-Now you die!
What?
Bu-- How?
-You lowered your guard at
the last moment, Sasori.
-What?
-And now you can't move anymore.
Even though your body
is now that of a puppet,
you still need a human
element to control chakra.
That's your weakness.
I couldn't help
noticing that part
from the left side of that
puppet's chest is gone.
-Take this!
CHIYO: You must have
done it quickly.
Right before the
jutsu was completed.
A simple switch to
a different puppet.
All of these puppet bodies.
They're just a
collection of dolls.
But your true nature is
the part inside your chest
that produces your chakra.
Sakura.
CHIYO (VOICEOVER):
She doesn't look good.
I've got to try and close her
wound while I simultaneously
pull out the sword.
-Stay with me now.
Just a little further.
-That won't work.
There's too much damage.
She'll die even without
the effects of the poison.
She's lost too much blood.
I'm well aware that you're
a medical ninja, which
is why I aimed for a spot
that is impossible to heal.
-I've already finished
the first aid treatment
with medical ninjutsu.
What I am doing for her now
is something very different.
-What?
I'm harnessing my own life
force and conducting it
into her body.
-No, it can't be.
-A reanimation ninjutsu.
-A reanimation ninjutsu?
-This jutsu of mine.
I spent many years creating
it especially for you,
and I'm the only
one who can use it.
Using this jutsu, life can
be breathed into anyone.
Even puppets.
That is, in exchange for the
life of the one who uses it.
CHIYO (VOICEOVER): Sasori.
-Ah well.
But after all that's
happened, I suppose
that's an impossible dream now.
SASORI: Nonsense.
-Have a safe journey!
-No!
It can't be.
Curse you.
Curse you, White Fang
of the Leaf village!
-Grandmother Chiyo.
Are they here?
Have mother and
father returned yet?
They're not home?
-Well, no dear, they're not.
You see, your parents were
sent on another very important
mission and it looks
like they won't
be back here for
quite some time.
I'm terribly sorry.
-Oh.
-But I just received
word from them
saying for you to stay
with me until their return.
Well, Sasori, is that OK?
-Yeah.
-What utter nonsense.
Tell me, grandmother.
When did you become so senile?
-Sakura.
Are you all right dear?
-Yes.
How are you, Lady Chiyo?
-Hm?
Peculiar.
That reanimation ninjutsu,
or whatever it's called.
I thought the
caster was supposed
to die after bringing
someone else back to life.
-Sakura's injuries were
severe, but she wasn't dead
when I used the ninjutsu.
So, even though I took a
risk, my life was spared.
-How very unfortunate.
That's pointless.
This puppet body of mine
can't feel any pain.
When you strike me,
the only thing you hurt
is your own fist.
But come to think
of it, you both seem
to love doing such
pointless things.
Even if a relative, my own
grandmother, died right here,
I wouldn't feel a thing.
My heart is just like this body.
Over the years, I've killed
hundreds, thousands of people.
She's be no different
from the rest.
Things are much simpler
than you might think.
-You monster.
What do you think human life is?
What is family to you?
-Hey.
Is that really how a
shinobi should talk?
-How dare you?
How can you treat
people this way?
CHIYO: Sakura.
That's enough.
-But he--
-The teachings and customs
of the Sand village did this.
We all share the blame for
making him what he is today.
-But, Lady Chiyo.
-Deep down inside, don't
you want to be like me?
If you do, then I'm sure
you'll understand just a little
of what I'm talking about.
This body won't
fall apart or age.
I'm not bound to a
limited lifespan.
A puppet can be
recreated over and over.
With puppets, you can make
as many people as you want.
If you want to, that is.
It's not just about quantity.
Don't get me wrong.
A serious collection
is based on quality.
-What the hell are you?
-I would describe myself
as a human being who
could not become
a complete puppet.
Yes, I am an unfinished
puppet whose lifeless frame
still contains a beating
heart at its core.
I am neither dead
nor am I alive.
The end is near.
But first, I'm going to do
something pointless too.
Think of it as a reward
for defeating me.
You wanted to know about
Orochimaru, didn't you?
Go to the Tenchi Bridge in the
Village Hidden in the Grass
10 days from now at noon.
-Why?
What's there?
-One of Orochimaru's henchmen
is working for me as a spy,
and that's where I'm supposed
to rendezvous with him.
However, I don't think I--
-Well, Lady Chiyo.
It's really over.
You did it.
-No, dear.
The wrong person was
defeated in battle today.
It should've been me instead.
Just like he had
done before, Sasori
anticipated my final
attack, but for some reason,
he didn't even
attempt to dodge it.
He chose to let
his defenses down.
-You mean that he wanted this?
-Kakashi-sensei.
You about ready yet?
-My preparation's complete.
-So that's what you
were telling me about?
-That's right.
My new Sharingan.
Now let's go, Naruto.
-Right!
[theme music]
TENTEN: They're getting
stronger the more we fight.
It looks like we have
no choice but to unleash
our hidden methods.
NEJI: Hidden methods?
GUY: Allow me to explain.
Up against a critical
situation, Team Guy
can fully activate
the one time only,
the hot blooded youth
at full power power!
For an instant, we obtain an
explosively destructive energy.
All right, Lee.
Time to let her rip!
LEE: Yes, Guy-sensei.
TENTEN: Now hold on a second!
NEJI: We don't have
any methods like that.
NARUTO: Next time,
Beasts, Alive Again!
[theme music]
-Rivals of love.
-Oh wow.
Lately Sakura's been
kicking some serious butt.
-Tell me about it.
Look at her.
She's a pretty awesome girl.
LEE: Strong, smart,
and beautiful.
The day that I met Sakura, I
could not take my eyes off her.
It was instant love
at first sight.
NARUTO: Ha.
Then she tried to get
away from you, remember?
Let's face it.
There's just no way she was
ever gonna give a guy like you
the time of day.
Not fair.
We did not know each
other very well back then.
And besides, you are the one
who transformed into Sasuke
to get close to her.
Talk about a pathetic attempt.
-Come on!
That was ages ago!
Ha.
Well, next time I'll get her.
She'll be blown away by
my amazing new abilities.
We are on the same team which,
means I actually have a chance.
-Argh!
You might be on the
same team, but do not
forget who you had your
memorable first kiss with.
-Ah!
No, no, don't watch.
Turn it off!
Don't watch it!