Stand...
We're leaving.
What about your mission,
Kakashi? Weren't you
supposed to search
this location.
It's suspended
because of you.
Don't let me stop you.
You just tried to kill me,
so stop joking around!
I'm not joking
around at all!
Just move!
I hear Foundation agents
are trained to discard
all their emotions. Is
that true of you, too?
Not just our emotions.
Shinobi of the Foundation
have no names, past, or
future, either. We only
have our missions.
Well, you failed
your mission.
Don't move from that spot!
Huh?
[screaming]
Snakes?!
What are they?!
And what's that?!
They're not
snakes, they're...
Orochimaru's
experiments!
[gasp]
[grunts]
What the?!
Kinoe!
[attacking yell]
Dead...
Everyone's dead...
I'm going to die, too.
In here, like this...
I don't want to...
You alive?
You all right, Kinoe?!
[groaning]
Are you okay?
I think so... But why?
Why what?
Why did you save me?
I couldn't just let you die.
But if you did, I
would have deserved it.
Did- Did you want to die?
No, I didn't.
I... definitely didn't
want that to happen.
Then be grateful that
you're still alive.
That I'm alive?
[gasp]
The fluid from the snake...
This is...
Don't inhale it; it's
poisonous! Run!
Right!
Kakashi!
[grunt]
[grunting]
I didn't find Orochimaru.
Nor did I encounter
a strange clan...
Nor anyone from
the Foundation.
All I can really do for
now is live by the rules.
But that's okay.
Beause now I know
that I'm capable
of protecting someone.
Procure a replacement for
this right eye of mine.
Kinoe, where's Kakashi?
Did you do it?
Yes.
So, you didn't need me...
Where's his body?
I made it appear like he
was killed by one of
Orochimaru's traps.
Lord Hokage's ANBU
will find him.
Good. Let's return before
they get wind of us.
[groaning]
Kinoe?
"To Kakashi..."
"I've become confused about
this mission, where I'm
supposed to kill a friend."
"So I'm going to abandon
it, and I'll report to Lord
Danzo that I failed."
"Please... take care."
Kinoe...
Kakashi, sir, your wounds!
I must report in first!
What's wrong?
Lord Third, it's regarding
the Foundation.
The Wood Style user just
targeted me, likely on Lord
Danzo's orders.
Hmm...
But he defied Danzo and
abandoned his mission midway
through, even going so
far as to save my life.
He should've returned
to the village.
Who knows what's
happened to him by now...
What?! What's the
meaning of this?!
Kinoe?!
I beg your pardon.
I failed my mission.
If Kakashi was able to
defeat you, then there is no
one to blame for
that failure but me.
It appears that I
have underestimated
Kakashi's strength.
But what is much harder to
forgive is you abandoning
your mission and
making a poor
attempt at faking
his death!
And I sent two men
to do the job.
What were you hoping
to accomplish?!
Answer me! Tell me
why you've done this!
Please, sir, go to Lord
Danzo and save Kinoe.
[sigh]
Lord Third!
It was agreed upon that I
would not interfere with the
Foundation. But...
That is not possible
in this case.
So, Yugao...
Sir!
Go and take this missive to
Foundation headquarters.
It's an order
from the Hokage.
It summons Danzo here to
speak with me immediately.
Right!
I'm counting on
you, Yugao.
Rest assured, my lord.
Kakashi...
Sir!
Go to the infirmary and
tend to your injuries.
Yes, sir.
Huh?
Sir?
I'm coming, too.
Kakashi is a shinobi of the
Hidden Leaf. He's a comrade
from the Village. Isn't it
wrong to kill a friend?
To be frank, you should
only consider those in the
Foundation to be
your true friends.
Isn't the Foundation
the Leaf's friend?
The Foundation's a unique
organization that supports
the tree of the Leaf
from deep underground.
Just as a tree is divided
into what is above and below
ground, the Foundation
has its own existence.
Kinoto, what is a
Foundation shinobi?
Our shinobi have no names.
We've no emotion.
We've no past. No future.
We have only our missions.
I'm the leader of
the Foundation!
The missions I give
you are absolute!
No past?
No future?
No emotion?
No name?
Tenzo! Welcome home!
Are you listening, Kinoe?!
No! Don't call me that!
My name is not Kinoe!
What?! What do
you mean?!
You are Kinoe of the
Foundation!
What other name could you
have besides that one?!
I am a shinobi of the Leaf!
A shinobi not just of the
Foundation but the whole
Leaf and its branches!
They're all my comrades!
Damn you...
What has made you
turn on us like this?!
[gasp]
Take him away to
the treatment room.
Bind him with
a Curse Mark.
Yes, sir!
Lord Third has sent this
communiqué to Lord Danzo,
summoning him
to an audience.
Notify Lord Danzo that he
is to appear immediately.
Lord Danzo isn't here.
What did you say?
We will let him know just
as soon as he returns.
Where is he now?
We have no idea.
We aren't privy to
the details of Lord
Danzo's schedule.
Go back and report
this to Lord Third.
What about you, sir?
I'll stay here and
wait for him. Go.
Right.
[gasp]
Stop!
This is Foundation
jurisdiction!
[gasp]
Where is Kinoe?!
Damn that Kinoe! What
ideas has Kakashi fed him?
Lord Danzo, we're ready.
Release!
Let's get out of here!
Kakashi?!
Agh! Kinoe!
Wood Style!
Hey! Wait!
Found him! Over there!
[gasp]
Wind Style!
Vacuum Bullets!
[gasp]
Wood Style: Domed Wall!
[groan]
How good of you to
come over from your side
to see us here, Kakashi.
You entered Foundation
jurisdiction without
authorization and tried to
take one of our own.
Don't think you'll
get off so easily.
Lord Danzo, Kakashi-
Just shut up!
You won't be getting
away with this either.
Neither shall you...
Hm?
[gasp]
Who is that?
Hiruzen...
I am well aware that
you harbor a grudge
against Kakashi.
But still, that does not
give you the justification
to target one of the
Leaf's finest shinobi.
What are you talking
about, Hiruzen?
I couldn't care less about
Kakashi. But he chose to
trespass into
Foundation territory.
And that is quite serious.
He chose?
You're wrong. In actuality,
I dispatched him here with a
summons from me.
Then, in order to complete
his assignment, he went
looking for you to
deliver that message.
All on my orders.
It seems there was a
miscommunication.
This is the first
I've heard of that.
Well, then that settles
things with Kakashi.
However, it's
regarding this next issue
that I sent for you.
It has to do with
another exceptional
shinobi of this village.
You're aware that a Wood
Style user has long been
sought in the
Hidden Leaf Village.
There was even a period when
we conducted questionable
tests to acquire that power.
I understand there is now
such a Wood Style user, so
why keep him hidden
in the Foundation?!
I was the one who found him,
and I protected and raised
him, too. I wasn't
hiding him from anyone.
I just didn't feel there was
any need to report it to you.
Hear me, Danzo...
The Jinchuriki child has
now entered his fourth year.
Wood Style Sealing Jutsu is
becoming more and more
crucial to the village.
Because of that...
I ask you to entrust this
Wood Style user to me.
To the ANBU under
my direct control.
I can't...
Please do this, Danzo.
I know he is valuable
to you. But for the sake
of the Hidden Leaf,
transfer him to me.
Should you choose to
do so, everything will
be settled amicably.
Members of the Foundation
bear a Curse Mark so they
don't reveal secret intel.
I will not remove
it from him.
That is fine.
Very well, then.
He is in my care now.
So henceforth, you
will be an ANBU under
my direct orders.
Uh, sir?
Thank you, for everything.
Um, hello? My name's Kinoe.
I just transferred here
from the Foundation.
Oh, hey there, Tenzo!
Tenzo?
Kinoe's your
Foundation codename.
In the ANBU, you
should go by Tenzo.
But that name is kinda...
Wasn't there even a
time when you called
yourself Tenzo?
All right, everyone! This is
Tenzo. He's the new guy!
And I can vouch
for his skill.
[chatter]
So, I'm Tenzo now, huh?
Tenzo, you'll be on
my team, Team Ro!
I'm counting on you.
[chuckle]
Okay. Yes, sir.
As usual, your
Lightning Blade is as
brilliant as ever, sir.
There's no such thing as
brilliant or inferior in
assassination. Killing
is killing, that's all.
By the way, what ever
happened with the
replacement? Our team
is still short a member.
There isn't really a rush.
We're not in the
middle of a war now...
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "An Uchiha ANBU."
Someone'll show
up soon enough.