-This time there's no escape.
-Get ready.
-[together] Right!
-He's fast!
-Ahh!
CHOJI (VOICEOVER): I can't move!
-Kakashi, I had
intended to replace
the hearts I lost with yours,
but I've changed my mind.
After all, I can find more
hearts any time I please.
Now die!
-Wind Style Rasengan!
-Water Style Ripping Torrent!
--[together] Hurrican
Vortex Jutsu!
[music playing]
-Sorry we're late, but
better late than never.
-Perfect timing.
-Yeah, let's hear
it for the cavalry.
-Sakura, Naruto, and Sai.
YAMATO: I've never seen you
looking so disheveled, Kakashi.
KAKASHI: One of those days.
YAMATO: The enemy must
be powerful indeed.
[theme music]
[wind blowing]
-Perfect.
Another weirdo to deal with.
Though this one's
already bruised up a bit.
Naruto, are you sure you're OK?
-Where's Shikamaru?
-He's dealing with
the other enemy
by himself a little
further away.
-Two of you head over an
assist him, a long distance
fighter and a medic.
He's going to need you.
-Leave it to me.
-All right.
Sai and Sakura, I want
you to go with Pakkun
and help out Shikamaru.
Hurry, now!
-Yes, sir.
-On it.
-Huh!
Ragtag bunch of misfits.
You people are nothing but
potential heart replacements
for me.
[laughs]
-All right, pal.
This is my show now.
-Naruto.
-Come on, we better go.
-Naruto, we're
counting on you, OK?
-He's perfected it?
-No.
It only works half the time.
-I see.
-Although-- well,
just keep watching.
Trust me.
He's come a long way.
-This way.
-I know this was
personal for him,
but he shouldn't have
gone to face him alone.
It seems reckless.
Do you think he's OK?
-Shikamaru will be fine.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
He's the smartest person
in the Land of Fire.
And besides--
-All right, then.
Come on, we might
as well get going.
-Uh, OK.
-That guy, he has no
motivation whatsoever.
I can't believe
he's a subcaptain.
It's so out of character.
-Oh, come now.
He's just not big on
showing his enthusiasm.
In fact, I'd say he loathes to.
You'd be surprised.
He's burning an
awful lot of calories
trying to look bored these days.
-I don't really get it, m'lady.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
I like Shikamaru.
But don't you think
you're overestimating him?
-Just the opposite.
I've probably
underestimated him.
-Hm?
SAKURA: What's this?
-We received an offer from the
Land of Fire's Feudal Lord.
They want Shikamaru to be a
member of the feudal lord's
official guard division.
It seems he made quite
a good impression
when he was running
the last Chunin exam.
The Lord's inner circle thought
he showed a lot of potential.
-You mean that he--
-That's right.
He'd be taking that
important first step
toward being a member of
the Guardian Shinobi Twelve.
It's quite an honor.
-Amazing.
Ah!
Then did Shikamaru-- did
he accept their offer?
-[laughs] Well, you know him.
-Hm?
ASUMA: I heard you rejected
the Feudal Lord's offer.
SHIKAMARU: Yeah.
ASUMA: Wouldn't be so bad for
you to see the world a little.
Honestly, I don't think I'd be
the same man that I am today
if it wasn't for the time I
spent among the Guardianship
Shinobi.
-This is me we're talking about.
I don't want the extra hassle,
and I probably never will.
-Huh.
-I just-- how do I put it?
With Choji and Ino here in the
Leaf, the guys in my new squad,
and even Naruto, I
guess I'd rather just
stay close to home
in case they need me.
-I see.
So you carry the Will
of Fire in you too.
-The Will of Fire?
The Third used to
talk about that.
-That's right.
It's an uncompromising desire
to protect this village.
-I don't really know
if mine runs that deep.
-What are you, shy?
You worry about your friends,
so you want to protect 'em.
I know where you're coming form.
-We're all Shinobi of the Leaf.
It's a drag, but I'd feel this
way whether I wanted to or not.
-The Will of Fire
illuminates this village.
At least, that's what my old
man always used to say say.
-Maybe someday I can shed
a little light on you.
You never know.
-Hm.
[laughing]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): No need
to worry about Shikamaru.
He's fighting to
avenge Asuma Sensei.
Besides, if anyone has the
perfect plan, it's him.
-[insane laughter]
Hate to break it to you,
but I can still move.
Damn it!
If only you believed in Jashin
you'd still have a chance.
He could step in and
save you right now.
It might not be too
late to convert, though.
To change your ways.
Nah, just kidding!
You're dead, kid!
Huh?
-Thanks, anyway, but
I can save myself.
-What the hell!
-Shadow Pull Jutsu!
-You-- you little--
-Hm!
Well, well.
Guess I'm not out of chakra.
Go figure, huh?
-You're kidding, right?
Kid, what are you doing?
-See for yourself.
[music playing]
-What!
What is this?
When the hell did
you set this up?
-A while ago, long before we
caught up with the two of you.
HIDAN (VOICEOVER): No way!
He didn't just randomly
separate me and Kakuzu.
He lured me here deliberately!
Which means this was all
part of his calculations.
-When you curse someone,
you dig your own grave.
You know why, don't you, pal?
-Enlighten me!
-If you curse someone
and take them out,
you'll also be defeated
in retribution.
And that's why you end up
digging your own grave.
-Ah!
-You cursed my Sensei dead.
Can't just let you keep
living, running around free.
-[gasping]
-That's your grave
you're hanging over.
HIDAN: [laughs] I won't die even
you if you dismember my body
and bury the pieces
six feet deep.
I'll just chew my way out
and come seeking your throat!
Huh?
What the-- deer?
-These woods are a special
place in the Land of Fire.
Only members of my Clan
are allowed in here.
Anyone else is forbidden.
Once you set foot in here, we
can watch you for eternity.
-You did well here, Shikamaru.
-Thanks.
-Hm?
Huh.
[music playing]
My Will of Fire I
entrust to you now.
-[sigh]
-Hey, what were you
just doing what that?
I'm talking to you!
-It's the Will of Fire.
The will to protect our village.
Farewell, Sensei.
-Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Shadow Clones, huh?
So, you're the
Nine-Tails jinchuriki.
-Kakashi, bring us
up to speed on what
we're dealing with here.
What's the rundown?
-Both our opponents
are Akatsuki.
Shikamaru splintered
off with one
of them leaving the rest
of us to handle this guy.
He's able to split
into multiple entities.
See those two masks?
Not only can they
detach, but each one
has its own beating heart
and can act autonomously.
He originally started
out with five in total,
but now he's down to three.
-So two of them have been--
-That's right.
We've killed him twice already,
and he won't go down for good
until we get the other three.
Plus he's a mid-distance fighter
using several different changes
in chakra nature.
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): No wonder
Kakashi's had his hands full.
Naruto!
-Yeah, Yeah, I heard.
-Naruto, don't!
-A head on attack
won't work on this guy!
-Only Shadow Clones?
You'll never win that way.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Based on his
assault speed and battle style,
I'm going to need three clones
for the diversion alone.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
He's at least
learned to tap into
his clone's experience
now and use that knowledge
to his advantage.
His mastery of them is evolving.
-[breathing]
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Hm?
Another trio of clones.
[music playing]
-What is that?
He's--
-Listen, that sound.
So-- so much chakra!
-Interesting.
Now what?
-This is as far as
I've ever gotten.
What am I supposed to do now?
-Well, let's see
what happens when
it collides with my Rasengan.
You ready?
-Huh?
Are-- Are you sure
that's a good idea?
What'll it do?
-If your jutsu is
near completion,
my Rasengan will
be canceled out.
All right, let's do it!
[music playing]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): The Fourth!
KAKUZU (VOICEOVER):
What is that jutsu?
I can't let it hit me,
or I'll be finished.
-Wind Style Rasen Shuriken!
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Look, I
know my teamwork is important,
but right now this is a bridge
I need to cross alone no matter
how dangerous it is.
If I don't work my
way to the other side,
I'll just be a kid forever.
So don't take away my chance
to prove what I can do!
Next time, "Wind
Style Rasen Shuriken!"