According to that stone tablet.
When the one who possesses the
power of Rinne should draw near
the moon,...
...the eye that can reflect off
the moon and grant the infinite
dream shall open.
Shine upon the world...
...Infinite Tsukuyomi!
"The Infinite Tsukuyomi"
[heavy breathing]
[gasp]
I've used up my chakra and can't
release my jutsu!
[yelling]
[yells]
[gasps]
[gasp]
[yelling]
[grunts]
What is going on?!
It's finally started...[titter]
Then my job is done.
[gasp]
(Swirly) And we don't need this
interior anymore, either...
[yells] Not again!
What is going on now?!
At four o'clock! Meteorites!
(Raikage) So many!
Brace for impact!
[groan]
Just what in the heck could be
happening over there? This isn't
normal!
[growl]
Tbhe chakra Naruto gave all of
us has disappeared...And that
giant tree vanished abruptly.
(Shikamaru) Something big is
happening over there, that's for
sure.
(Shikamaru) Most
likely...something bad.
[shouting]
[growl, barking]
What's wrong?!
Huh?
What? What is it?
Shino...The moon! Look up at the
moon!
[gasp]
This can't be! Is that...?!
What is happening now?!
(Sasuke) This is really bad!
I'm gonna pulverize all of the
meteorites with these, so don't
worry, you'll be safe!
Just stick close to me and stay
still!
Okay!
(Naruto) Gotta make sure not to
hit Sasuke!
Go!
[gasp]
(Naruto) Sasuke, watch your
angle of descent! I could've hit
you with the Rasen Shuriken!
[gasps]
Hey, come on! Land more softly,
would ya?!
Look, just shut up and stay
still, all right?!
Huh?
[frightened shouts]...What is
happening?!
[growl]
Harrumph! Now! Become one!
[exhale]
Wait, those eyes...!
So, Madara's launched his
jutsu?!
[snoring]
My lords, this is terrible!
Please, wake up! My lords,
quick, you have to wake up!
What is it? We are all very
tired from playing mahjong all
night.
What? All night? But you were
asleep a minute ago!
Uh?! Oh...Never mind! It isn't
important!
Something terrible is happening!
It's night out, but it's bright
as day-!
This light can penetrate and see
through even shadows,
...so no one can hide from it.
And next...
Divine...Deep Forest Emergence!
Get hold of yourself, Tsunade!
What is happening here?!
(Hinata) I can't move...
(Hinata) Naruto...!
[gasp]
Huh?!
Naruto, don't move an inch!
(Black Zetsu) Huh? The light
isn't able to penetrate that
Susan'o?
(Black Zetsu) His Rinnegan...can
deter even this jutsu?
Don't go outside.
Without this Susan'o's
protection, you'd be bound up in
his genjutsu, too!
And besides that, his shadows
are still outside...
If you fall, it's all over!
(Sasuke) We have to wait!
[sigh]
(Hashirama) This is the Deep
Forest Emergence! He's binding
people using the Divine Tree's
life energy!
Why am I not affected?!
Huh?
[shout]
Yamato!
[exhale]
[gasp]
What is...? Where am I?
[groan]
What...happened to me? [groan]
You all right, Yamato?!
Lord Third, you're...?! Well,
I... [groan]
Motoi, get back!
[gasp]
Yamato!
[groan]
That's right! Kabuto captured
me...
The war...! What's happening
with the war?!
(Yamato) And Naruto?! Is he all
right?!
Control yourself, Yamato!
[exhale]
Wait, this is--! [groan]
[groaning]
[groan]
And, now...Let the world of
dreams begin, a world without
abysmal chakra!
(Yamato) I was Orochimaru's
guinea pig...I was all alone...
(Yamato) I had no family,
nothing...
(Yukimi) Tenzo...! Tenzo!
[gasp]
Where am I?
[giggling]
Hm?
Tenzo! Come on, hurry up!
Yukimi?
[gasp]
Tadah!
Tenzo! What do you think?!
I met Yukimi and I also got to
know Kakashi...
(Yamato) And then, the place
where I belonged became the ANBU
Black Ops.
(Kakashi) Hey, Tenzo.
[gasp]
(Yamato) Kakashi?!
(Kakashi) Hurry up and get
ready. We have a mission.
Right! I'm sorry!
(Yamato) If I'd stayed in the
ANBU, I wouldn't be alone. The
missions were difficult, but...
(Yamato) I had no family,...so,
for someone like me, it was the
best place.
(Yamato) No, that's not right!
The place where I belong
changed.
(Yamato) Where I belong is...
(Yamato) But that place belongs
to Kakashi...
(Kakashi) Tenzo, what's the
matter?
[gasp]
(Yamato) Oh, uh,...Kakashi?
Uh...What am I supposed to...?
(Kakashi) Have you finally
realized it? That there's no
doubt that this is where you
truly belong.
What does that mean? Why are you
saying that right now?!
[chuckle]
[gasp]
[exhale]
(Yamato) You're-!
(Kabuto) It's been a while,
Yamato. I'm going to be taking
Kakashi's Sharingan, now.
[gasp] Wait! [gasp]
[growl]
(Naruto) Captain Yamato!
(Yamato) Huh?
Come on, we gotta go after him!
Yeah! It's up to us! Only Team 7
can save Kakashi Sensei!
(Yamato) You guys!
Everything's ready to go! But we
have to hurry up!
Captain!
Captain Yamato!
(Sai) Captain!
Hm.
(Yamato) We can do this! Are you
ready?
(Yamato) Yes...This is where
I...
[heavy breathing]
[chuckling]
[roar]
[yell]
Damn!
[gasp]
(Sakura) Captain Yamato!
[groan, heavy
breathing]
[chuckling]
[gasp]
[gasp] Captain Yamato, are
you...!
[gasping]
[gasps]
[gasp]
(Yamato) Who are you?!
[gasp] It's Sasuke!
[gasp] No way! Sasuke?!
(Sasuke) Chidori Stream!
[pained yelling]
[groaning]
But why...?! Why are you--?
That isn't any of your business.
[shout]
Watch out!
(Kabuto) [groan]
Damn it! I was careless.
(Yamato) You all right?!
Yeah, I'm okay now. Thanks to
you.
[groan ]
Kakashi!
You're all right!
[groaning]
You seem to be in one piece.
(Kakashi) Yeah, thanks. I'm just
fine. You saving me, imagine
that.
Actually,...I wasn't the only
one.
Truth is, I had a lot of help
from Naruto and Sasuke...
[chuckle]
Now I can rest assured and leave
things to you.
Huh?
[exhale]
(Kakashi) You're the only one
among my subordinates that I can
trust with this...
(Kakashi) So from here on out,
you're officially the new
captain of Team 7.
What?! No way, you're...! But
Kakashi, Team 7 is...
Yamato, Kakashi is correct.
[gasp]
(Tsunade) You have performed
admirably, and there's simply no
one else that I could imagine
entrusting Team 7 to...
Lady Fifth...!
Awesome! Way to go, Captain
Yamato!
I'm so happy that you're in
charge now!
I've always thought of you as my
first friend, Captain Yamato.
(Sai) No one else will do!
(Yamato) You guys...Thank you!
(Yamato) And on top of all this,
Sasuke is back. I'm so happy for
you...Naruto...Sakura...
[chuckle] Approved by Kakashi to
lead his old team. Nice,
Captain Yamato.
Sasuke...Hm.
(Yamato) Yes...
(Yamato) I can stay...right
here.
(Yamato) This is...where I
belong from here on out...
This is...where I belong from
here on out...
So is this the Infinite
Tsukuyomi?
[gasp]
Just what exactly is going on
here...?!
[gasp]
[groans, gasp]
Huh?
(Minato) Wha-...What happened?!
(Tenten) I don't know how, but
this is my room, right?
(Tenten) The Hidden Leaf
Village...
(Tenten) Does this mean I was
somehow transported here from
the battlefield?
(Tenten) Hold on,...what is this
feeling...?
(Tenten) I may not be on the
battlefield anymore, but
still,...it's way too peaceful
here...
(Naruto) Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "To the Dream World"
Why?! What is going on?!