[panting]
Is he still
behind us?!
[gasping]
[struggling]
I'm getting accustomed to
these powers. It's going
well, not bad at all...
I think it's about time
to put my plan into action.
"Storage"
Well, what's the matter?
Just press the Storing
Square!
Feeling unsure, eh,
Naruto? I can't say
that I blame you.
But why?
Lord Fukasaku, The way
that the Nine-Tails gets
its power is by mixing
two things together:
its chakra and
its will.
[grunting]
To control this power,
you must extract only the
Nine Tails' Chakra,
convert it into your own
chakra, and thus make it
your own power.
But that's not as easy as
it sounds.
[laughing]
When you pull out the
Nine-Tails' chakra,
his will tags along.
The Nine Tails' will is a
mass of hatred that's
bound tightly to his
chakra by strong forces.
No matter how hard you
try to shield yourself,
it will find some hatred
buried deep inside you
and try to take over.
In other words...
You must have a strong
will of your own,... one
that's completely empty
of hatred...
... One that's capable of
completely separating
Nine-Tails' will from his
chakra.
The Fourth Hokage made
Nine-Tails' seal so a
little bit of its chakra
leaks out of its cage,
hopefully to naturally
become one with
Naruto's own chakra.
It's known as the
Eight-Trigram Sealing
Formula and creates a
double-interface
Tetragram Seal.
If Naruto uses this key
to open the Tetragram
Seal, he could pull out
all of Nine-Tails' chakra.
And that means that
all of the Nine-Tails'
Will would tag along with
its chakra!
And as soon as Naruto's
will loses to the
Nine-Tails' will...
The Nine Tails will be
fully resurrected!
How terrible.
And tell me... has the
key ever been used to
open the seal?
Actually, the Tetragram
Seal is always getting
weaker.
To restrain Naruto, who
started a Nine-Tails
transformation in
training, Jiraiya used
the key to tighten the
seal.
[roaring]
Uh!
There. That should hold
him for a while.
Only for "a while,"
huh? Man...
Hm?
Hmmm...
What's going on?
Something wrong, Pervy
Sage?
Jiraiya was greatly
concerned. The seal was
still loose. If the
Fourth Hokage's Sealing
Formula was beginning
to weaken,
there's no telling when
Naruto might undergo a
Nine-Tails transformation
again.
All right. I guess I'll
have to try it.
Hm?
[screaming]
A toad just came out of
your mouth!
Give me a break, would
you, Jiraiya? You just
summoned me a little
while ago, you know!
What do you want?!
Look, I need a favor.
Just hear me out, all
right, Gerotora?
It won't
take long.
Huh?!
It's about Naruto's
Tetragram Seal.
Come on! You just
tightened it, didn't you?
Do you want it even
tighter now?! Sheesh.
Not quite. Just the
opposite.
If it's not too much,
I wanna loosen it up
just a little bit.
What?!
Jiraiya wanted to
deliberately open the
seal for just a short
while.
...to drill Naruto into
developing the power to
resist the Nine-Tail's
Will.
Well... It failed
miserably.
I didn't mean to hurt
Pervy Sage; things just
got outta control.
[panting]
Are you kidding me?
You're giving up
already?!
Ahhhh!
[panting]
This training...
... It's impossible!
I'm disappointed in
you, kid. Callin' it
quits so quickly.
[grunting]
Listen, do you remember
when I told you that you
reminded me of the Fourth
Hokage?
You're the shinobi who
inherited the Rasengan,
the jutsu developed by
the Fourth Hokage
himself. So shape up!
You have no idea... Just
how happy I was then.
Back when I first learned
the Rasengan... I mean,
it's the Fourth Hokage's
own jutsu!
It's almost like I'd
taken over the work of
one of my idols!
But--
As hard as it was for me
to learn the Rasengan,
that was nothing compared
to this training!
Hmph!
I guess you think
mastering the Rasengan
was a miracle and not
due to hard work!
Maybe I was just
expecting too much
out of you.
Look, I know the Fourth
Hokage was a great shinobi.
You don't have to remind me!
Yeah, that's
for sure.
He's totally different than
someone like you who gets
stupid excited about mastering
one measly little jutsu.
Unlike you, my most
foolish apprentice, he
was a true prodigy.
The jutsu he developed
was simply extraordinary.
Even I couldn't grasp the
ninjutsu that he came up
with.
What? Even you?
Mm-hmm.
And not even the Hokage
that came after him,
either.
His jutsu was that
amazing?
I knew he was in a class
all by himself! How can
I ever become Hokage?!
Listen, okay?
There's only one shinobi
now who has the potential
to master such
extraordinary jutsu.
Huh?
I'm talking about you,
Naruto!
Uh! You are?!
That's right. Only you
possess the Nine-Tails'
chakra and can master
that jutsu!
It's a jutsu that only I
can master? Do you mean
that...?
Yeah. The Fourth Hokage
left it solely for your
sake.
He meant it as his legacy
to you.
It's his legacy...?
[gulping]
A jutsu just for me, huh?
Naruto! Will you train to
master your chakra control
and live up to the
expectations of the
Fourth Hokage?!
Yes, sir!
[panting]
It seems the harder I try
to become strong,
the tighter the grip
of the Nine Tails will
on me becomes.
He just ignores my own
will and tries to hurt
everyone near me.
And that's what happened
from only opening the
seal a tiny bit.
So that's the reason for
that scar... The one that
was on Jiraiya-boy's
chest.
So, tell me, what's
happened since then?
It hasn't gone well.
Long ago against
Orochimaru,
I relied on Nine-Tails'
power on purpose. I gave
him my will.
Don't you talk about
Sasuke like you own
him!!!
Especially in front
of me, you rotten
bastard!
Hearing him talk about
Sasuke made me furious.
Before I knew it, I lost
myself.
[roaring]
That's when Captain
Yamato told me I needed
to stop relying on the
Nine-Tails' chakra... and
to fight using my own
power.
Everything was fine in
training under Captain
Yamato, 'cause he can
restrain Jinchuriki.
But in real battle,
feelings of hate are
bound to come out.
So I thought I didn't
want Nine-Tails' power
anymore.
I knew if my own will
wasn't able to suppress
the Nine-Tails' will...
... that I didn't want
power that would hurt
the people around me.
I made up my mind to put
it aside.
But then...
When Pain took down
Hinata...
I was so angry. I lost it
again.
My heart linked itself to
Nine Tails' Will all by
itself.
Right now, I feel safer
because the Fourth Hokage
rebuilt the seal.
It could fall apart at
any time, though.
But I need Nine-Tails'
chakra in order to fight
Sasuke.
I am the Nine Tails'
Jinchuriki, after all.
I can't hide from that
forever.
I sealed half of the
Nine-Tails' chakra inside
of you.
Because I believed that
you could master this
power.
I'm going to conquer this
control thing, Dad! No
more hurting my friends.
No more giving in to
hatred.
Well... no use getting
depressed.
Now I see just how
dangerous it is to
release the Nine-Tails'
chakra....
But he has the Fourth
Hokage's love and that
sheer gutsiness instilled
in him by Jiraiya-boy.
Contract complete!
Storage time!
Huh? What do you mean,
what's "storage?!"
Relax, you don't need to
do a thing. Just open up
your mouth nice and wide,
you got it?
Mouth...?
Just say "Ahh!"
Ya understand?
Ahhh...
No, wider! Open up!
[grunting]
Ahhh!
All right! I'm going in!
[freaking out]
Hey! Open wider! Are you
going to let me get
inside you or not?!
Why by mouth? He's all
slimy. This is gross!
Hhh'yah!
Uh!
[gagging and coughing]
Storage is now complete!
I'll be returning Naruto-boy
to the Hidden Leaf.
And then we'll have to
find the octopus.
Oh, that's right... the
prophecy said I was
gonna meet an octopus.
Mm-hmm!
So where is this thing?
Can't you give me any
more clues?
It's not clear, but
it's an island. avoided
by people. A creature's
paradise.
It seems a veritable
pleasure resort to me!
[happy reacting]
I believe that is where
the octopus will
cooperate with you.
In any case, you'll
receive guidance there.
Yes, sir!
There's no mistake
about it, this is
Kabuto's doing.
This method of killing...
Kabuto is becoming more
and more like Orochimaru.
But still, why is he leaving
a trail? If he wanted, he
could erase it easily.
Do you think it
was deliberate?
What is he plotting?
I suspect that he's taken
on Orochimaru's will.
Now the big question is:
is he going after the
Hidden Leaf or the
Akatsuki?
Let's start with
greetings, Tobi. Oh,
that's right...
I hear you're going by
Madara these days.
I'm impressed you found
me.
You shouldn't
underestimate my volume
of intel, from criss-
crossing the land
a spy and as an Akatsuki
member.
That's right. You were
one of Sasori's spies.
You're a traitor to the
Akatsuki.
This is...!
The Reanimation Jutsu.
A Forbidden Jutsu known
only to the Second Hokage
and Lord Orochimaru.
Now, I'm the third one to
know.
I've surpassed the two
of them in other ways,
as well.
This show was for your
benefit.
So you'd believe in my
power and trust me.
Rest assured. I did not
come here to fight you.
Then what do you want?
I want us to
join forces.
Join forces?
And what would be in it
for me?
I hear that you're
starting a war. I can
offer you more strength
in battle.
In the form of...
Itachi.
Sasori.
Deidara.
Kakuzu.
And Nagato.
They're all stalwart
warriors. Also... They're
not the only pawns that I
possess.
And in return...?
Sasuke Uchiha.
What are you plotting?
Nothing in particular...
I'm just interested in
finding the pure truth
behind ninjutsu.
Sasuke is merely
necessary for part
of my research.
I need a young, living
Uchiha specimen.
And if I refuse?
Summoning Jutsu:
Reanimation
Th- That's-!
Surely you didn't think
that I'd come unprepared
to a meeting with you?
See? You cannot refuse
me.
Why you-- where
did you get that?!
Oh, I have
my means.
But don't worry. I
haven't told anyone
else about this.
[chuckling]
Did I say something
funny?
Kabuto Yakushi. I never
imagined that you would
become such a...
formidable vessel.
Quarreling with you now
would only lower my
battle strength.
You came here at the
perfect opportunity. You
are very clever.
So what's your answer?
Very well. We'll join
forces.
But I'll only hand over
Sasuke after you've both
completed your roles in
the war.
Until then, you
can't even see
him.
You comprehend quickly.
As expected from Madara.
Your vessel's unique.
And you're insolent.
I'll reformulate my
strategy after I confirm
your battle strength.
Come along.
[chuckling]
He left corpses lying
around this remote area?
Judging by how these
bodies are strewn about,
I'll bet there's
something up ahead.
Originally I thought this
chase would lead through
the Hidden Waterfall
then back to the
Hidden Leaf.
But this... It's like he
wants us to follow him.
I don't get it.
It could be a trap.
What's the plan?
Uh!
Tokuma! Two o'clock.
Byakugan.
Right!
Byakugan!
Captain Mitarashi!
It's--
What is it?
Kabuto isn't alone! He's
with a masked member of
the Akatsuki!
It looks like they're
going into some kind of
underground entrance!
Are you sure?!
Wait, a masked Akatsuki?!
Could it be he's the one who
claims to be Madara?!
Does this mean we
finally found his hideout?!
But why are he and Kabuto
together? Are those two
allies?
Wait a minute. Could it
be possible that Kabuto
deliberately led us here?
In order to show us
where Madara's hideout
is?
But why? If they've
joined forces, why betray
him?
I don't know just yet.
But we need to notify the
village right away!
Hide them away? Naruto
and Bee can lend battle
strength! Why hide them
away?
The Five Great Nation's
aim in this war is to
protect those two.
Your sole dissent as
Hokage is not enough.
Majority will rule.
Listen, you stripling!
Naruto is-
I know him quite well.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: The Five
Kage's Decision.
All right! Fine!