Scatter!
Morale continues
to remain high.
Everyone is ready
to leap into action
when the order is
given, Lady Tsunade.
Good.
You guys, we can't
just stand around
doing nothing!
-Huh?
(Konohamaru)
Moegi...
Udon...
Alright! Let's
do this!
Hiya!
[grunting]
No, Udon!
There!
Fire Style:
Burning Ash!
-Woahhh!
[coughing]
Hey, stop
Konohamaru!
Yeah, you're really
overdoing it.
Look guys, the
entire Village is
gearing up for
war as we speak!
And everyone has to
be ready to answer the
call to arms when it
comes, including us!
We're still Genin,
so I doubt they're
gonna send us into
battle right away.
And besides, aren't
there still things kids
like us are supposed
to be doing Konohamaru?
How can you guys be
so relaxed!? We're
not just kids! We've
grown up a lot!
The time's come to
make our mark and
become heroes of the
Village like Naruto!
[groans]
[determined grunt]
Anyway, now it's
our turn to achieve
great things for
the Hidden Leaf.
But, Konohamaru,
how are we gonna
do that?!
That's right.
It's way easier
said than done.
Uhhh...
Lemme think...
Hmm... Huh?!
Oh! That's it!
We'll just use
the Leaf News!
Huh?
What do you mean?
(Konohamaru)
We're from the
Leaf news, and
we're collecting--
(Konohamaru)
--data about the coming
war, so we can figure
out how we can help!
During the last
major incident,
we just helped
everyone evacuate.
But do you think
there's anything
else we can do
to help out?
There is! Hold
out your hands...
[groaning]
Okay! Take those to
the storage room.
[groaning]
Thanks a lot!
That was a
big help!
Yeah, but
Sakura!
...hold on!
Hm?
You didn't tell us
what we can do to
help during the war!
We really wanna
do our part!
Yeah! We wanna
do something big
to help out the
Village!
Mhm!
Hm, [gasp]
but you're already
doing something big to
help the village out!
-huh?
All these boxes! They
contain medicine for
the ninja who will be
fighting out there!
No! That's not
what we mean!
We wanna do
something
really important!
Like the kinda
stuff Big Brother
Naruto does!
What are you
saying!? War
isn't a game
you know!
[gasps]
A lot of people
out there could
get hurt or die!
So don't speak
lightly of it!
Man! I can't believe
she was looking down
on us just because
we're still only genin!
But what Big Sister
Sakura said really
is true!
Mhm.
Listen, maybe we
should just stick
to--
No way! We are
not gonna give
up that easily!
(Shikamaru)
What's the matter?
You sound kind of
upset.
(Konohamaru)
Big Brother
Shikamaru!
How do we get on
the front lines and
fight the Akatsuki!?
I brought down Pain!
And that means I'm a
full-fledged Leaf
Ninja now!
(Shikamaru)
Tsk...
Alright, I have a
question for you,
full-fledged Leaf
Ninja...
Uh, okay.
What's the identity
of the King that
you must protect?
Answer that.
The King...?
Heh...
If you don't
know the answer
to what I'm
asking...
...then I'm afraid
I can't acknowledge
you as a "full-fledged
Hidden Leaf Ninja."
Heh, look at me
talkin' all big.
I only got the
answer recently
myself.
Anyway, there's
no need to push
yourself so hard.
We'll talk again
some other time.
Here!
What's that?
Why'd he write the
symbol for "ball?"
It's "king!"
(Konohamaru)
I wish everyone would
just stop giving us
the run-around!
Fine. If that's
the way it is.
What now?
Who are we
gonna interview?
No one...
We're gonna demand
to be allowed to
take part in the
war!!!
(Lady Tsunade)
You fool!!!!!
Why am I a fool!?
I just wanna fight
for our Village on
the front lines!
That's no place
for you, trust me.
I brought down
one of the Pains
by myself!
I am fully
qualified to
fight in the war!
[groan]
You're interfering
with my work!!!
Get out!
Woahh!!
Konohamaru!
Are you okay!?
Ugh!!!
Why is this
so hard!?
[sigh]
(Young Tsunade)
Nawaki, I can't believe
you're twelve! Happy
Birthday!
[gasp]
Sister, is this
what I think
it is?
Yep! It's
grandfather's!
That necklace belonged
to the First Hokage!
I love you!
[sigh]
Damn... Ugh!
-Hm?
(Moegi)
Someone's coming!
We'll get
yelled at!
Ahhhhh!
This way. Lady Hokage
is expecting you.
Thanks!
Hey, don't we
know her?
Temari, the older
sister of the
Sand's Kazekage.
Kazekage!?
Oh...
I've got a
great idea!
What are you
thinking about?
Here's the secret
missive from the
Kazekage.
Yes, thank you. I
confirm receiving it.
What a time! To
come this far,
just for that?
Not at all! It's to
assess the situation
here as well.
I mean, we're both
in the same alliance
after all.
It's been a
while, hasn't it?
The past shadows
are gone, so please
stay and rest.
Thanks, I
would...
...however I have
to get back to the
Hidden Sand Village
as soon as possible.
Excuse me,
[panting]
Brother Shikamaru!
What's going
on you guys?
Did you finally
figure out who
the King is?
Uh, no! Konohamaru's
in big trouble!
Hm? What is it?
(Konohamaru)
Hidden Sand
Jonin Tamari!
You will accept my
challenge to fight
here and now!
Huh!? Get lost...
or get hurt!
Will I get
hurt..? Or you!?
My name's Konohamaru
Sarutobi! Lord Third's
grandson!
And Naruto's
favorite student!
Naruto's what!?
Running away from this
challenge will mean that
you fear me, and you'll
be known as a coward!
Say that again, brat!
Okay, let's
do this!
[grunt]
Alright! Fire
Style: Burning Ash!
First Star...
[grunt]
[screaming]
[coughing]
How'd you manage
to do that!?
(Temari)
Give it up, kid!
You're all talk!
Just admit it!
[growling] I'm
not a kid! I'm
Konohamaru!
(Konohamaru)
Shuriken!
Now! Shadow
Clone Jutsu!
Second Star...
[grunt]
[gasp]
Hmm, it seems
that the Sarutobi
Clan  doesn't have
any decent heirs left!
[growl] You give
me no choice then!
Multi Shadow
Clone Jutsu!
Now, here we go!
[charging grunt]
[dying gasps]
Third Star!
Ahhh!
Had enough!?
You're a hundred
years away from
being a challenge
to me!
Thought you were
Naruto's favorite
student?! But you're
only a dissapointment.
Of course, I shouldn't
have expected a guy
like Naruto to have a
decent student anyway.
[grunt]
You did a good
job, Konohamaru!
You're a hero of the
Hidden Leaf too!
[giggling]
That's it!
You can say
whatever you
want about
me....
...but I won't let
you say anything
bad about Big
Brother Naruto!
What!?
(thinking)
What is that!?
[attack cry]
Rasengan!!!
Ninja Art! Wind
Scythe Jutsu!
Shadow Strangle
Jutsu!
[shouting]
What?
What was that Jutsu?
(Shikamaru)
The one he learned
from Naruto.
It's the Rasengan.
That brat's managed
to master a Jutsu
this powerful?
Konohamaru!!!
Are you alright,
Konohamaru?!
[grunt] Damnit!
What do you think
you're doing!?
If you'd just let me
finish the Rasengan
I would have won that
fight no problem!
[gasp]
Ow! Hey! What
was that for?!
Because...
because...
...you keep going
on and on about
distinguishing
yourself and winning!
Konohamaru! It's
like you're happy
war is coming!
No... That's
not...
(Moegi)
Konohamaru...
...do you remember
the day that Pain
attacked!?
Huh?
(Moegi)
I got separated from
you, so I headed
towards District C...
(Moegi)
But then...
[gasp]
[crying]
(thinking)
He's in big trouble!
I have to get help!
(thinking)
I'm the only one
here... I have to
help him!
(thinking)
Somehow... I
have to help him!
(Child)
[crying]
[gasp]
Huh?
[panting]
Huh!? Sota!
Mommy!
Sota!
[crying]
Going to fight on
the front lines isn't
the only way we can
help the Village!
When war breaks out
for real, all the Jonin
and Chunin will have to
leave to fight...
...but what
happens if the
enemy attacks the
Village itself?!
(Udon)
She's right...
We will have to
take the place of the
ninja who are out
on the battlefield...
...and protect all
the elderly and
children at home.
[gasp]
What's the identity
of the King that
you must protect?
Answer that.
I swear... that I
will protect them...
...all the grannies
and the grandpas...
...and the
children too.
All of them!
Hm.
(Shikamaru)
Protecting the
Village is a huge
responsibility too.
But boy, are you
every lucky.
If you'd kept on fighting,
I have no doubt that you
would have fallen to
Temari's Wind Scythe Jutsu.
Among all the Shinobi,
she's probably the
cruelist one you'll
ever meet.
[gasp]
Heh. But still, kid,
you're really somethin
else making me have
to go as far as I did...
Uh, I...
thanks!
Now I can report back
to Gaara that there are
some fine young ninja
coming up in the Leaf.
In a few years,
I'm sure you'll
be an incredible
Shinobi.
Heh!
Well, Konohamaru...
What do you think
we should do now?
What else...?
This Village was my
grandpa's... the
Third Hokage's
greatest treasure!
I'm gonna
protect it!
'Cause I'm the grandson
of the Third Hokage, who
kept the Village hidden
in the Leaves safe!
And because Big
Brother Naruto
made me a promise...
...that we would
fight for the title
of Hokage!
(Konohamaru)
I'm gonna train harder than
ever, until I can pulverize
Big Brother Naruto!
Because my dream
is to become Hokage!
Huh, really?
Konohamaru actually
said that?
Yes, those were
his exact words.
I see. I'm glad
to hear it.
I'll take care of
it! And not just
the necklace...
...the entire
Village meant a
lot to our
grandfather!
I'm gonna take
good care of all
of it!
After all, I'm the
grandson of the Hokage
who built the Village
Hidden in the Leaves!
[laughing]
Remember, like you
always say, a man never
goes back on his word!
That's right!
And I give my word
I'll follow in our
grandfather's footsteps
and be just like him!
To become the Hokage!
That is my dream!
I wonder how he's
doing right about
now...
(Guy)
Ha! A marriage proposal
just like that!? You're
quite popular Naruto!
(Naruto)
It's not like that!
I'm telling you!
(Naruto)
Just because Pervy Sage
made some careless promise
I have to pay for it now!
(Yamato)
We are on a secret mission.
We can't get involved in any
foolish distractions!
(Aoba)
We must avoid
unnecessary conflict.
(Aoba)
So let's go to bed
early and leave first
thing in the morning.
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: The Kunoichi
of Nadeshiko Village.
(Naruto)
Stop following me!
Leave me alone!