[Tsunade]
They should be arriving soon.
Do you mean Naruto?
Yes.
The Raikage wouldn't disclose
the location, but he said it was
the ideal place to lay low.
Now if only Naruto will
do as he's told and stay
hidden during the war.
But knowing his nature, once he
learns that fighting has broken
out, he's going to want to rush
right onto the battlefield.
I told Naruto he was going
on a highly classified
S-rank mission.
Don't worry, the others
will follow along and
play their parts.
Octopus, octopus, octopus!
[Yamato]
Octopus?
Yeah, it's supposed to give
me guidance, remember?
Giant Gramps Sage foretold it!
Now, Naruto. I've had a
prophecy about you.
Soon you will be
meeting an octopus.
So where is this thing? Can't
you give me any more clues?
It's not clear, but it's an
island. avoided by people.
A creature's paradise.
It seems a veritable
pleasure resort to me!
I believe that is where the
octopus will cooperate with you.
In any case, you'll
receive guidance there.
Oh, yeah.
That octopus.
I mean he's right about
this place being an
isolated island paradise!
So he must be right
about meeting someone
that'll help me!
Good. It looks like Naruto
hasn't caught on yet.
All right! Please get
ready to disembark now!
Hey! The island's
coming into view!
Paradise, here I come!
That's...
a paradise...?!
It's like the
Hidden Leaf's
Forest of Death.
Although perhaps
a whole lot flashier.
No resort?
Don't worry. It's safe here.
Just remember: as long
as you don't provoke
them, the creatures here
will leave you alone.
Well, except for...
"Except for...?"
Except what?!
What part of this
place is a paradise??
You stink, Giant
Gramps Sage!
It lives along the shore.
Hm?
Yeeah!
Octopus tentacles!
Uhh...
Okay, octopus!
I made it here!
So come on and guide me!
Naruto,
that's actually...
A squid!
"Land Ahoy! Is This the
Island of Paradise?"
Huh.
It's him! I was just about
to warn you that he's the
only one that you have to
be careful of!
What's that?
What?
One, two, three, four...
You don't need to
count its tentacles!
You can tell just by
looking, Naruto!
I don't know; I think
we should make sure.
A squid has ten legs.
An octopus has eight.
If this is the octopus who'll
guide me, I gotta know!
Uwhaaa...
Yaaah!
Naruto!
Whoaaaaa!
Hm!
Gyaah!
[Killer Bee]
Squid go deviate!
The rest I abbreviate!
What is this?! Here
comes another one now,
spouting off weird rhymes!
All of us are
done for!
That's six. And seven.
And eight...
It's an octopus!
This one's
an octopus!
It is?
You sure?
It's Lord
Killer Bee!
It's Killer Bee?
This octopus is...
All y'all are late!
Ya hear, fools, ya fools?
It's really
a person?!
Hey, Octopops!
Thanks, ya know!
"Ya know" huh?
What is he..?
Hmm?
Killer Bee...
That's me...
ya know!
I don't want to be rash,
but will we clash
or be a smash?
If I dare say,
it'll be a no-go,
whee!
I'm a brat-hating
outlaw, yeeeeeuhhh!
Who the hell is this
shades-wearing meathead
with the weird rhymes?
This geezer is my
octopus mentor?!
They're not
weird rhymes.
This is his own original
style, a combination
of Enka and rap.
It's Enka Rap!
That doesn't make
sense at all.
Glad you made it in one piece.
I've been waiting for you.
I am Supervisor Motoi. Welcome!
I'll show you your rooms.
Follow me.
Unhh. Have we
finally arrived?
Yes, we've landed.
So get yourself
together.
Ohh...
Bushier Brow Sensei...
Are you okay?
He never really found
his sea legs, did he?
We were at sea
for quite a while.
It sure was long.
[hurf]
And so painful.
this is not
exactly what I'd
call "paradise".
Huagh. I still
feel woozy.
Raaaaah!
Aaah!
[retching]
Stand down, there, King!
These guys are with me.
Huh?
Mmm!
A giant
gorilla?!
That's...
a gorilla?!
Master Bee stands atop the
island's hierarchy of beasts.
He's tamed every one of them.
So as long as he remains here,
this place will offer
you no danger.
Also, preeminent Hidden Cloud
shinobi maintain a barrier
around the island.
We'll know immediately if
anything suspicious approaches.
Which is why this place was
selected to hold them...
What the heck is up with that
shades-wearing pops, anyway?
He's the Hidden
Cloud Village's
hero among heroes.
Hero?
He's someone who not only
tamed these beasts, but also
has the Eight-Tails
perfectly under his control.
[Naruto]
Huh?
[Motoi]
He is a Jinchuriki
just like you.
of Eight-Tails.
The Eight-Tails' Jinchuriki?
And... he can control it?
That old Octopops?!
He's Master Killer Bee.
Yo!
This island is also
where he trained in
order to gain control
over the Eight-Tails.
Huh?
You Hidden Leaf ninja can
use this entire floor.
There are rooms enough
for all of you.
the dining hall is downstairs.
You can eat whenever you want.
Well, pick whatever room
you'd like, I guess!
We'll adjourn until the
meeting tomorrow at seven.
I just want to
rest a while.
[Motoi]
This island is also where
he trained in order to gain
control over the Eight Tails.
In any case, you'll
receive guidance there.
It's the "ya know" brat.
What's up?
Do you want my
autograph or something?
No, I want you
to train me.
You want me to what?
I'm like you.
I'm a Jinchuriki, too.
But I can't control the
Nine Tails inside me yet.
So please, I need you to
teach me how to control
my Tailed Beast!
No way.
Huh?
I came here 'cause my
brother the Raikage ordered
me to take a vacation.
Why would I ever want to
give up my rare R and R
for the likes of you, kid?
Ya hear me?
Fool, ya fool!
'Cause you're a
Jinchuriki just like me!
I don't understand!
Why won't you help
me out, here?
Ya got a big 'tude,
now change my point
of view, dude.
Huh?!
Hehh!
Your shades are hip,
your facial features are thick.
You're just so sick!
Yeeeeah!
Hee hee...
You know something, kid?
You've got pretty good style.
Yes! He's starting
to like me!
Yo!
Huh?
First comes the greeting!
So we start it all off with
a fist bump.
And then you
keep rapping.
Uhh...
Octopops with sun-spects,
ya seem suspect-
Ahh?
Oh, crud! Shouldn't
have said that!
Oh well, what the heck!
Harem Jutsu!
See, I'm begging on my
knees, full of respect.
I'm a good prospect!
Let's put the
training to effect!
So... help me, please...
What do you think?
Best jutsu ever, right? Eh?
Aahh!
Hey, Octopops!
What gives?
Meanie!
What's his deal?!
Making up weird
rhymes all the time!
I bet some other octopus
is the real one!
What is it?
I want you to teach me all
the drills that octopops
used to gain control over
the Eight-Tails.
He trained on this island,
didn't he?
Oh. You mean Master Bee.
Yeah! That guy won't
give me the time of day,
so I decided to come to
you instead!
To me?
I don't care if he's some big
hero of the Hidden Cloud!
He's mean and stubborn, and
all he does is talk in rhymes.
We're both Jinchuriki,
so you'd think he'd be
more understanding
about my situation!
You don't know a damn
thing about Master Bee!
Now I suggest you shut
your mouth before you say
something you regret!
[stunned]
If you're also a Jinchuriki...
you know what it's like to
live with that burden.
Tell me, isn't that true?
Yeah, I do know
all about it.
And he should be able
to understand what it's
been like for me, too!
So I don't see why won't he give
me a break and help me out!
I just...
Don't worry, Master Bee's
been watching over you.
I'm sure there's a
reason he did this.
Huh?
Listen; did you
exchange greetings?
Exchange wha?
First comes the greeting!
So we start it all off
with a fist bump.
Well, we did this, uh,
whatchamacallit...
fist bump?
Good. Naruto, right?
Come, follow me.
Uh... why?
I'll take you to Master
Bee's training grounds.
All right!
[Yamato]
Then I'll tag along.
Huh?
[Naruto]
Captain Yamato?!
I'm a Wood-Style user, and I'm
supposed to look after Naruto.
Oh! Yes, I've
heard of you.
Very well.
[Aoba]
I brought you
some water.
Oh... thanks for that.
Are you feeling any better?
Kinda. I do feel like I'm
starting to recover though.
But it's as if I can't quite
seem to shake the feeling
that I'm still at sea.
Is it my imagination?
Hmm. Yep, it's
in your head.
Is this it?
Yes. This place is
called the
Waterfall of Truth.
The Waterfall
of Truth?
He learned to control
his Tailed Beast here?
Not quite.
It is just the
first step.
[Naruto]
Huh?
Sit down here and close
your eyes, Naruto.
And you will see
your true self.
See my true self?
That's right.
Why?
Hmm?
[Dark Naruto]
Why didn't you give them
your autograph at Ichiraku?
What's that?
Can't blame you, you know.
I mean, after all,
they came kissing up
to you like that.
[gasp]
They were completely
disgusting, weren't they?
He looks just like me!
Don't you remember?
Everyone in the village used
to treat us like outcasts,
and then they try to pull that?
Oh, that's right!
Can I get your
autograph?
And if you don't mind, could
you make it out to my kid,
please? He's a real big fan!
Autograph?
You're the hero of
the Hidden Leaf!
Naruto, the kid who
makes miracles!
Can I please have
your autograph, too?
What? Can't you do it?
No, it's not that;
I'm just not used to
this celebrity thing.
I've never given an
autograph before!
Who the hell are you?
Isn't it obvious?
Come on!
I'm you!
What? That can't be.
I haven't made any
Shadow Clones!
I'm no clone;
I'm the real you.
The one that exists
inside your heart.
You see, I am you!
What are you even
talking about?
I have no idea who you are.
Now just stop making stuff up!
Naruto. Hey!
No, quiet!
So they call this place
the Waterfall of Truth?
I never thought I'd be able to
emerge completely like this.
I like this place.
Rgh.
Anyway, I'm the truth that
you're supposed to face.
I'm the real you,
your true self inside.
The real me? But...
Yeah. I'm the hatred
that's inside you.
I'm the dark part of you.
[gasp]
The only difference
between us,
Is that the Nine Tails has taken
a really serious liking to me.
Then you...
The Nine Tails' will is a mass
of hatred that's bound tightly
to his chakra by strong forces.
No matter how hard you try to
shield yourself, it will find
some hatred buried deep inside
you and try to take over.
So he's the one working
with the Nine Tails.
Yeah, you got
that right.
Just face it: I'm
the real one here.
And I'm not going to let
you kick me out, you fake!
So that's how it is, huh?
You're the fake one.
And I'm gonna prove it!
[growling]
[growl]
Come on; any time, now.
[roar]
On this island, I'm top dog,
taking y'all down like a
whirlwind clearing the fog!
Yea-ah!
You've still got a
ways to go, Kintoki.
Mraaah.
Hey, Bee. If you have the
time to play around, you
could have looked after that
Nine Tails kid, you know?
After all, Jinchuriki ought
to stick together, right?
I don't really care for
the Nine Tails, but that
kid's got potential.
I was crazy wild too, once.
But we met, and look at me now.
Plus, he kinda
reminds me of you--
My rap says shut your trap!
And I ain't acknowledging no
rap-mocking "ya know" fool!
And besides, he...
[panting]
Damn it!
We have the exact same strength.
This is never going to end!
Accept it, there's no way you
can beat me. Not ever.
Egh!
Then I'll overwhelm
you with numbers!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Aw, what the hell?!
I can't believe this!
We even make the same
amount of Shadow Clones!
Hey, you're pretty sharp,
figuring that out.
That's it!
Go!
I don't understand.
What's going on?
When one sits before
the waterfall,
one can focus and enter
one's own mental sphere.
And the waterfall
becomes the mirror that
reflects your true self.
It is a truly
mystical place.
So right now,
Naruto is battling
against himself.
Rasen...!
...gan!
Huuh?
Aagh!
Naruto!
You all right?!
What happened?
This guy...
He looks
just like me.
And he...
What...?!
I think he was my dark half.
[gasp]
We're both just the same.
The same strength,
the same jutsu...
The same fighting style,
same tricks-
everything is
identical with us!
We'd fight forever!
How can this be?!
You must defeat him.
Or you won't be able
to handle the Tailed
Beast's power.
Huh?
I told you...
The Waterfall of Truth
is merely the first step.
[Motoi]
Master Bee and I were
close friends once.
[Naruto]
Wait, that's it!
I've got it!
Motoi! You can go ask
Octopops for training
hints on my behalf!
[Motoi]
I'm sorry, I can't.
[Naruto]
What? Why not?
[Motoi]
I am not worthy of
such an errand.
I once tried to.
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
Killer Bee and Motoi.
I wonder what happened
between those two...