Stone Golem!
This should
pulverize Madara!
Wood Style...
Deep Forest Bloom!
Agh! Damn it!
[gasp]
[growling]
As expected!
It's getting closer...
What now?!
Hold on... That's
Grandfather's!
Kazekage!
Yes, I know!
What is that?
Just look at the
sheer scale of it!
To create a forest
in an instant!
Everyone, beware of the
pollen! Don't inhale it!
Not just the Deep Forest
Emergence...
... but the Deep Forest
Bloom as well? How dare
you, Kabuto!
There's no shinobi alive
today who's as powerful as
the First Hokage,
Hashirama Senju.
Everyone says that.
In fact, many doubt that his
power was as strong as
legends say, just like they
think the Sage of the
Six Paths' power
was a fairy tale.
It's time to show them that
all the myths were real!
Wait, you bastard!
[gasps]
You're all too distracted
by the flowers!
No! No way! Raikage!
[chuckle] Seems that it's
time to burn things up now...
Fire Style!
Majestic Demolisher Flame!
[painful groaning]
Mizukage!
Water... Water Style.
[groan]
I guess I'm too old...
to do anything.
Hey now, the left
side is dirty!
That's a precious
stone of the Hidden
Stone Village!
You need to learn to
be true and sure.
And scrub until
your hands blur!
His rhymes and puns
are killing me.
Wha-?!
Listen, symbol of our
village or not, this thing
looks like nothing more than
a plain old ordinary
rock if you ask me!
I mean, why don't we have
Great Stone Faces just
like the Hidden Leaf
Village does?
Seems like you're being a
real cheapskate, Lord
Tsuchikage.
Ohnoki, I can tell the worth
of any stone I see just by
taking a good look at
it for a moment or two.
This rock is... a symbol! It
carries inside of it our
village's Will of Stone!
It is our bedrock!
Aw, even a cheapskate with
your words! Don't be using
our symbol in your puns!
Well...
Actually, you're right. This
is just an ordinary rock.
What?!
Agh!
What do you think you're
doing, you stupid old man?!
I can't tell which
one it is now!
You see... if you simply put a
new one of them on here like
this, no one would
ever even know it.
What?!
What's really important is
the Will of Stone inside
you.
Just as I can with an
ordinary rock, I can also
tell the worth of someone's
will just by looking at them.
Ohnoki...
Hidden within the will you
possess is the power to
change the entire world.
But if you aren't careful, I
worry that precious will of
yours may disappear...
Disappear?
What?! But why?!
That wasn't the agreement!
Lord Hashirama said...
There is no alliance now.
You will merely bow down to
the might of the Hidden
Leaf!
And also... never mention that
shinobi's name in my
presence again!
Susano'o!
Barriers!
As you keep running into
barriers, you may abandon
your will, make excuses, or
perhaps even replace
it with hatred.
Listen well, your will...
Never abandon it and always
stride with pride!
It seems that you still want
to keep dancing...
But there's no strength
remaining in your step
anymore!
No more excuses!
Particle Style: Atomic
Dismantling Jutsu!
Look at me being pitiful
about my age...
There's no excuse for making
such an excuse! Let's go!
What is this?
Nice job, Ohnoki!
Good, you're all awake! All
right, then! Let's get on
with our counterattack!
There he is now!
You dance well.
However your step
is still too weak.
Is that?! The First
Hokage's face?!
I didn't want to believe it,
but that's why he can
use Wood Style!
[chuckling] And this is far
different from what Lord
Orochimaru developed
with Danzo.
The First Hokage was even
more powerful than Madara
is. So, now this fusion of
both will be my
ultimate weapon!
No one can stop this
Reanimation!
Wait!
Is that you, Itachi?!
I told you to wait!
A Susano'o!
That Susano'o. You
definitely are Itachi!
I'm impressed. I didn't know
you had been able to master
it as well, Sasuke.
But what are you even doing
here?! You are dead!
Kabuto's jutsu...
I have become a
Reanimated shinobi.
No time to talk right now.
There's something important
that I have to do.
So what?! I don't care!
You're here, right in front
of me, right now!
And I have
questions for you!
Ask me later...
But you probably
won't listen...
You're the one who told me.
To come and find you once I
had the same eyes as you!
Now you want to run away
from me?! Are you running
out of guilt for being a
liar?! You don't have the
courage to tell me the truth!
I already know everything
about you anyway!
That's why I'm going to
destroy the Hidden Leaf!
I told you before when we
fought against each other...
We each live inside
our own fantasies.
I asked you to think
about it that way.
And about how one's reality
might be an illusion.
However, my truth is real.
I no longer live inside an
illusion! And I can see
through your genjutsu!
These eyes...
...are your eyes!
Sasuke understands all your
pain and your resolve to do
what you did!
But Sasuke isn't like you.
He's really going to destroy
the Hidden Leaf!
He's going to kill everyone
in order to avenge the pain
that the village caused
his older brother!
I can tell part of you is
still the same, but I've
heard from others
what's happened to you.
I know how much
you've changed...
You're wrong! You were the
one who changed my world
long ago!
I was supposed to die, too!
You were also supposed to
kill me along with both our
parents!
But, no!
So he made up his mind. He
himself would drop the
curtain on his own
clan's history.
Of course he did not hate
the Uchiha. He simply did
what he had to.
The discrimination by the
village... And the object of
their antagonism...
He shouldered all
the blame himself...
No one should ever
question Itachi's decision
and the sacrifices he made.
[gasps]
What is going on?
Big brother! Father and
Mother are both-
I don't... Understand! Just
who could do something like
this?! [stunned breath]
My foolish little brother.
Mangekyo Sharingan!
Now explain it! Why me?!
Why?! Why did you spare
only me?!
He just couldn't bring
himself to kill you.
Do you understand
what that means?
Why me?! What's different
about me versus our father
or mother?! Why only me?!
Because you didn't
know anything.
You had no part in the
Uchiha Clan's folly. You
were just a child.
And do you think I
did it just for you?
I wanted you to grow
up and judge me.
I deserved to be
dealt with only by
another Uchiha.
And so I took advantage of
the hatred inside you.
That's why I failed.
Ultimately I only filled
you with hatred and made
you go rogue.
I turned you
into a criminal!
Chidori!
[battle cry] Elbow Bolt!
Even though all I ever
really wanted was for you
to walk the right path.
Back before I died, I--
I tried to lead you down
that path to righteousness.
Down a path without
any forks or turns...
I changed the
signposts on it...
...with lies and my
Visual Prowess.
What? I was supposed to
happily walk that one path,
ignorant of everything?!
I couldn't!
I never could have
walked that path!
Yes...
You're completely right.
You ought to decide your
journey for yourself.
No matter how you try to
obscure the signposts, my
eyes can strip away
all of your lies!
[harrumphing chuckle]
What's so damn funny!
Nothing...
Just realizing that the
signposts were not your
only guides.
Properly speaking,
I'm dead now...
There's no point in
talking any further.
When you were alive, you
never paid any attention
to me.
Always flicking my forehead,
saying "forgive me," and
running off.
And even now that you're
dead, you're still running
away?!
I'm not running
away from you.
As I told you, There's
something important I
have to do.
I must stop the
Reanimation Jutsu.
You there, female
medical ninja.
You have it. His blood
runs through your veins,
doesn't it?
And what if it does?!
Then I will take
you down first.
Taking out a unit's Medical
Ninja first is a
well-established tactic.
Surely, you don't think we'd
let you do something like
that so easily...
You're wrong...
The reason that she's first
is that she's a descendant
of Hashirama Senju.
Your Medical Ninjutsu is
only strong enough to defer
death for what essentially
amounts to a meaningless
period of time.
It's pathetic compared to
what Hashirama Senju was
able to accomplish.
He could heal wounds without
even weaving a single sign.
In every jutsu he attempted,
he was in a class by
himself.
Everyone viewed him as
the ultimate shinobi.
And I once fought a battle
against him, putting my own
life on the line.
Compared to that,
this is nothing!
So even if you
are his descendant...
What do you really have to
offer? Just what can you
hope to do in this battle?
You cannot use Wood Style,
your Medical Ninjutsu
doesn't even
come close to his.
And most of all, you're
merely a weak woman!
Weakness of any kind
completely revolts me.
A weak Senju disgusts
me even more!
I think you've rambled
on for long enough now!
Hm?
I am a descendant of First
Hokage Hashirama.
I don't use Wood
Style, that's true.
My Medical Ninjutsu is
pathetic compared to the
First Hokage, who
didn't need hand signs!
And it is also true
that I am a woman.
A woman...
But I am not a weak
woman-- far from it!
Physical strength
isn't everything.
There's something else,
something passed down to
me from the First Hokage.
And that gift is what
my true power is!
Don't dare underestimate...
...the Will of Fire!
This Reanimation jutsu
will not come undone
even if you kill me.
But I am the only
one who can stop it.
In other words, you
cannot simply kill me.
I will make you stop the
Reanimation Jutsu.
This jutsu has neither
risks nor weaknesses.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Risks of
the Reanimation Jutsu."
Every jutsu has a weakness.