I told you,
you fool...!
...You're way too
old for this kind
of thing now...
[shocked grunt]
[grunt]
Oh my! Thank you
for that, Kazekage.
[grunts]
And eye of sand...
You were watching over
Ohnoki with that this
entire time, weren't you?
You switched him out
with a San Clone when
he took out the Giant
Clam!
[groan] My back...
[chuckle] This
kid is gonna be
seriously big...
...And he's
browless!
Alright! We've
got him!
No! It's not
working..!
That slime's keeping
the sand from
sticking together!
Not good. I'm
starting to
enjoy this fight.
Grand Sand Mausoleum!
Quickly! Throw all
the Sealing Tags
we've got at him!
There's no way his
slime can keep up
with this much sand.
Now attach the
Sealing Chains!
Good! Looks like we've
got this fight won!
[bracing against blast]
[grunt]
What..!? This
can't be...
What the hell's that?
Could it be
another genjutsu?
Genjutsu...?
No, that's no
genjutsu...
...that's the
Infinite Explosion
Ninjutsu of the
Misukage!
It gave my
predecessor Lord Mu
some real trouble.
It's the Steam Imp!
[gasps]
Hail...?
All the moist air that
was forced upward by the
steam explosion earlier
must have been cooled
in the upper atmosphere
and turned into hail!
It's shirking!
(Gaara)
What is this?
It's a clone comprised
of oil and water taken
from the Misukage's body.
The exterior surface of
its childlike form is
composed of oil, while
the interior is water.
It's special feature is
that it can both heat up
and cool down easily...
When it moves around, the
oil on its surface increases
in temperature precipitously,
which in turn causes rapid
vaporization of the water
inside...
...resulting in a
steam explosion!
And when the hail cools
it, it shrinks back down
to its original size and
is ready to explode again!
It's coming!
It's faster than
I imagined...
[grunts]
Are you alright!?
Damn it! This
clone's a wily one!
The real Misukage should
be nearby. Don't bother
with the Imp. Just go
after the original!
Another feature of
this jutsu is that it
greatly weakens the
caster while in use..!
The brat Ohnoki! He
sure knows a lot...
Mu must've told him.
If it's not a mirage genjutsu,
and he can't make himself
disappear, then I should be
able to sense him...
[gasp] He's
behind that rock!
Oh! Damn my back!
Of all the times
for it to go out!
I can't move at all!
Oh, found me, huh?
Before it stops
hailing...
I shall seal you!
What's happening!?
Is it just me, or is
he getting bigger!?
It's just as Lord
Tsuchikage said..!
The more it moves around,
the faster the oil heats
up and vaporizes the water
inside...!
The hail's
stopped, too!
Another explosion of
steam is imminent!
We've trapped
the original!
[gasp]
Hey there!
Damn!
Uh oh!
This really is a
perfect hidey-hole!
I was once one of
the five Kage, too...
As long as I still have
my oil, your Sand Jutsu
simply won't be able to
touch me!
Unless, of course,
you can seal me up
real quick!
That does seem
to be the case...
Now...! How are
you going to take
me down, then?
Honestly I was hoping
you'd tell us!
[groan]
Nah, I've changed my
mind, I'm done with
that...
Sorry, everyone!
You were cooperative
until just now!
What, have you decided
to help the enemy!?
Nope! Wrong!
I mean I am a former
Kage after all...
And actually, I am still
helping you out! Only in
a different way...
Which way is
that exactly!?
If you can't beat me using
all of your abilities,
then you're worse off
than I am you old fool!
You'll never win against
the enemy boss this way!
It's gonna explode!
Run!!
Retreat!!
Just when I'd thought
that I'd found the
Golden Child of the
Five Kage...
Kazekage! You're just
an ordinary child!
[gasp]
Over there!
Hold on, guys! I'm
on my way there!
[coughing]
That's... a Sand Shield!
Lord Kazekage has
protected us!
But where is
Lord Gaara?
I'm impressed! You attacked
knowing you'd get hurt,
while protecting everyone
at the same time!
But if you don't stop
this, the same thing
will keep happening!
Heh. THe hail's stopped.
Here comes the next round.
You mistimed getting
your guard up because
of its sudden expansion!
Another Sand Clone,
huh? Well, that's
within expectations...
The real one was hiding
below, just as I'd
guessed! What'll you do?
But what now..?
It's going to
explode again!
The speed of your sand
is no match! You'll
never catch him! So-- huh?
How did he do that?
Is his sand getting
faster...?
But either
way... Ka boom!
Even more smoke!
that's gotta be where
they are! Let's go!
It stopped moving...
Is that...
Gold...?
Did he mix in that Gold
Dust his father left
behind and do something
to the Imp?
There was Gold Dust
hidden away within
that Sand Clone from
earlier...
I took advantage of that
thing's heat to melt and
then bond the gold to it.
Gold is about 20
times heavier than
water....
...which is why
its movements has
become sluggish.
(Second Mizukage)
And why the sand
trapped it so easily...
But still, why didn't
the Imp explode, then?
The sand that I mixed
with the hail was
enough to cool this
thing down...
Gold also has good
thermal conductivity
...which came in
handy for chilling
its water vapor
and steam.
That was well played.
Truly an act befitting
a current Kage!
I'm impressed you
came up with such
a strategy!
Wait a minute...
I guess you really
are.. a golden child!
[hiss]
(Kabuto)
I didn't think I
could get this
off course...
Still, I'm glad that
clone was sealed
before he could say
too much.
Although, given Naruto's
power, it'll take some
time for him to regenerate.
Even with a Reanimated body.
How naïve of you, Ohnoki.
You were my student...
...You completely
missed me fragmenting.
[gasp]
[attack yell] This
is... a violently
rotating... Rasengan!
Earth Style:
Weighted Boulder
Jutsu!
Don't let your
guard down yet...
I'm still...
Nice!
Guess I can't remove
these tags after all...
What an impressive
Sealing Jutsu!
If I remember correctly,
Mu's Jutsu is not cloning,
but fission...
Because the real body
splits into two, it's
fast and he doesn't
need to use hand signs.
But his power
is halved.
It's going to take this
one some time to summon
that one...
...given his
weakened state...
I'll have to buy
more time with
another tactic, then...
Are you all
right, Gaara!?
What's the news
on your end?
We sealed the
Third Raikage.
I saw something had exploded,
so I raced here faster than
Temari and the others to see
of I could help out.
I see.
We're almost done, too.
Good. But hold on,
where is your enemy?
Look at that! So you
really do have friends!
Huh? What!? What
is he!?
He's got a really
weird body!
No, no, that's
my jutsu.
[chuckle] Kazekage!
Well I see that you're
the smart one out of
your friends...
(Second Mizukage)
You make a
good pair.
Oh really?
It's been a while
since I've had
this much fun...
Relay our current
battle status to HQ!
Yes, sir!
You fought well against
the former Five Kage,
everyone.
The victory is ours
on this battlefield.
Okay! Extract the
wounded! Get them
to the medical teams!
All those who can still
fight, stand by for
further orders from HQ!
Lord Tsuchikage, you
should seek medical
attention, too...
No, I'm totally
fine. All right!?
[grumble]
Listen, make sure you
don't overdo it, old man.
Don't you treat me
like some doddering
old fool!
I can still take
on you young
ones! Argh!
Here we go.
We'll take you to
the Medical Corps
to get you all
checked out.
Let go of me,
you dolt!
I can walk fine
on my own!
You really should just
accept that you're
old! There isn't
any shame in it!
How dare you! I am the
Tsuchikage, you know!
Yes, I heard you say
that yesterday, too.
Lord Gaara, why don't
you come by and visit
later, okay?
Let me go I said!
Didn't you hear me!?
This way...
Argh! My back!
(Yukata)
Please stop squirming!
(Matsuri)
Seriously!
(Ohnoki)
Owwww...!
So, Naruto... You're
a clone, aren't you?
Yeah.
Where is your original
to be found right now?
[taken aback]
We can't take in any
more patients for a
while...
We just received orders
to focus on the wounded
that we have here already.
But, they keep bringing
in new casualties from
the battlefront. What
do we do about them!?
I know. But there's
no way for us to
distinguish between
who's an ally...
...and who's an
enemy in disguise.
[gasp] But that's...
Even our chakra has
been copied perfectly.
Which means I have to
consider everyone besides
myself an enemy...
Man, what a drag!
But... we have to
figure out a
solution soon...
Where did they hide
that Bashosen fan,
anyway?
It'd be really
handy, and I can use
it really well!
Is there any
sign of them?
No. Nothing yet.
But then, White Zetsu
could be disguised
as any one of us...
Please be
careful, Hinata.
I will. You do
the same, Neji.
It's still blurry...
The Sealing Corps just
reported in. They weren't
able to seal Pakura and Gari.
I see...
Two of the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen remain...
Fuguki Suikazan, and
Mangetsu Hozuki.
Hang in there,
everyone!
I'm coming!
(Kidomaru)
It seems we get to
play with you again!
(Tayuya)
We're way more than
mere reanimations!
(Tayuya)
Our curse mark's power has
been intensified far beyond
what it was, you damned rat!
(Jirobo)
Enough, Tayuya! Women
should speak properly.
(Tayuya)
Shut up, fatso!
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Ghosts from the Past"
(Kidomaru)
It's game over
for you...!