[music playing]
-This is the place?
-Gaara's on the other
side of that boulder.
-It won't be easy getting
past that barrier.
-What's the plan?
-We smash our way in.
-No, Lee.
Late as usual, Kakashi.
-Well, you see, we ran into a
little trouble along the way.
-Naruto!
Sakura!
-Wait a minute.
By a little trouble, you don't
mean me, do you, Kakashi?
-Well?
-Naruto.
-Well then.
Let's do this, Kakashi.
-Right.
-(THINKING) Hang on, Gaara.
Just hang on.
[theme music]
NEJI: Inside, it looks like
there's a large cavern.
But--
NARUTO: But what?
NEJI: I just can't quite make
out what's going on in there.
I see several people.
NARUTO: Neji, what about Gaara?
What's happening?
Is he one of the people you see?
NEJI: Back off a second.
I'm trying to locate him now.
NARUTO: Negi!
NEJI: Take it easy.
I don't-- what is that thing?
-What is it?
What's going on?
Neji, what's in there?
-Let go of me.
-Well, what did you see?
-It's hard to
describe with words.
Wait, so that would mean--
-Yes.
It means that whatever
it is, we will
have to go see it for ourselves.
-That makes things
easy, doesn't it?
[roaring] Coming through!
Yah!
Quite a barrier.
-Hmm.
It's getting noisy out there.
-It looks like we've got
ourselves some expected
visitors.
-But which group is it now, hmm?
The one that my man Kisame
was stalling, or perhaps--
-Both.
It's both groups.
-So they all arrived
at the same time.
Interesting.
But what a pity.
They're too late.
-It seems one of them
is also a jinchuriki.
[evil laugh] Oh, don't
be jealous now, Itachi.
[evil laugh]
-What is your plan?
-Well, Lee, it's
pretty obvious we
need to get rid of that barrier.
-And how do we do that?
-Before we can even think
about breaking through,
we should know what
kind of barrier it is.
-That's right.
So, figure out the
type of barrier.
That's step one, right Kakashi?
KAKASHI: Yeah.
-What do you think?
-Hmm.
It could be a five seal barrier.
-I agree with you.
-Five seal barrier?
-It's a strong
layer of protection,
in which five tags with
the word forbidden on them
are fastened around the
area that's being guarded.
One forbidden tag
is in front of us.
And four more must be
in other locations.
GUY: Can't we just
pull them off?
KAKASHI: It's not that easy.
The tags are in five
different places.
But they have to be taken
down at the exact same moment.
-So we'd have to remove
them simultaneously?
-Right.
The barrier won't budge unless
all five tags are pulled off
simultaneously.
It's a tall order.
That's only one tag.
-Which means there's
four more out there.
-All right, then.
Let's do it.
How do we figure out
where the other taxes are?
-Neji.
-I understand.
Byakugan!
I found them.
NARUTO: Awesome, Neji.
Point 'em out.
NEJI: One is on a boulder about
500 meters northeast of us.
The second one is
on a tree trunk
beside a river bank 350
meters south-southeast.
The third you'll don't find 650
meters northwest, on a cliff.
And the last one is in the
woods, less than 800 meters
to the southwest.
That's four.
-If that's the case, each one
of them is pretty far apart.
How will we signal each other?
-I think I can handle that.
We should just be
in range for these.
They're wireless radios.
-Whoa, that's amazing.
-Good thinking.
-Yes.
-Ha!
OK.
So we'll stay in
constant communication,
and follow Neji's
directions to the tags.
-Well, shouldn't we get
this show on the road?
We got company
outside to deal with.
And there's still
the small matter
of a mission we
have to complete.
-Yes.
Let's get going.
-What about the intruders?
-I wouldn't lose too
much sleep over them.
We don't even know if
they can get in here.
-Don't underestimate them.
You should know better, Kisame.
--[laughing] Well, they do have
brute strength going for them.
I'll give them that.
-Sasori, [inaudible].
-Hmm?
-Take care of our
new friends outside.
-I had a feeling you'd say that.
Hm.
-But I want the
jinchuriki alive.
-Understood.
-Everyone else is dismissed.
-Let's go.
-Right.
-Well, I suppose
we'll be leaving, too.
-Itachi, this nine-tailed
jinchuriki, what is he like?
-Go on.
Tell him.
-He's the one who bursts
in and barks first.
-Huh?
What do you mean?
-Doesn't he have any identifying
characteristics other
than barking, hmm?
Huh, guess not.
-Well, that's it, then.
-[grumbling]
-You OK with this?
He was your target, after all.
-Let's move.
Right.
-OK, let's find these
tags, and get rid of them.
Team Guy is the
faster team, so we'll
be the ones to
handle this mission.
-We're all counting on you.
GUY: All right, Lee, you head
northwest into the woods.
-Yes, you got it.
GUY: The northeast boulder
is all yours, Neji.
-I can handle that.
-Tenten, you'll get
the south-southeast.
-Right.
No problem.
-And I'll take care of the
one on the northwest cliff.
That's the one in the
trickiest location,
and should be the
hardest to eliminate.
KAKASHI: What's the frequency?
-174.
-Copy that.
-Testing, do you read me?
-[wailing]
[feedback]
-Lee, your microphone's
up too loud.
-A thousand apologies.
-Lee, the mic.
-Huh?
Sorry, guys.
-My wireless settings
are good to go.
-My radio's set, too.
-All right.
Team Guy.
Hmm?
-Oh, right.
-[chuckling]
-Uh, OK.
-Hm.
[chuckling] Hmm?
Hmm!
Hmm?
[chuckling] Onward with
the power of youth!
Atta!
-Yeah!
-Atta!
-And one more for good luck.
Atta!
-Yeah!
-Scatter!
-Oh man.
That was so cool.
Hey, we should do it, too.
I would rather die.
-Me too.
-Not a chance.
-Well, guess it's about
time for me to shove off.
There's no real reason
I should stick around.
I'd just be getting in the way.
-Thanks, Pakkun.
Good work.
-All right, then.
See you guys later.
-The rest is up to you two.
-Not a problem.
-I'll be waiting
for your report.
-Now let's recap the mission.
The members of Team Guy are to
find their tags, and stand by.
After all four have
reached their positions,
we'll remove the scrolls
together on my signal.
Got that?
-Got it.
GUY: Team Kakashi will take
out theirs at the same moment.
And just like that, will
break the five seal barrier.
-And the moment
the barrier's gone,
Sakura will destroy the
boulder at the entrance.
That will be our signal to
charge inside, and rescue
Gaara.
-(THINKING) Gaara!
-What's taking them.
Hmm.
I wish they would just
hurry up and get in here.
Hmm.
Sasori, what's the
matter, my man?
I thought you didn't
like to be kept waiting?
Hm.
-Yes.
I hate it.
-(THINKING) Sasori, it's absurd.
I never imagined a day
like this could come.
-This is Neji.
Ready, and in position.
GUY: I found my tag as well.
I'm almost to it.
-Got mine too.
LEE (ON RADIO): N-Neji?
-I understand, Lee.
Byakugan!
It's just south of you.
A little further.
There.
Look up.
-OK, I have it.
Lee to Guy Sensei, in position.
-Well, Kakashi,
you guys all set?
-Ready when you are.
We'll make our assault
using the button hook entry.
-Sounds like a plan to me.
-Yeah.
-All right, everyone.
Get ready to remove the
tags on the count of three.
On my mark, one, two, three!
-Now, Sakura!
-Right!
[roaring]
-(THINKING) Sounds
like it all worked out.
Huh?
-What is that?
-Huh?
-[gasp]
-We're too late.
-Oh.
[chanting]
-(THINKING) Sasori.
-Finally.
Well then, which one of you
would be the jinchuriki?
-You!
You bastards!
I'll kill the both of you!
-The one who bursts
in, and starts barking.
That would be him, then.
-Sasori, my man, I
think you're correct.
Hmm.
[music playing]
NARUTO: I'm going to
take a normal scroll you
can find anywhere.
And when I count to three,
a huge shuriken appears.
-Hey, you can't steal
somebody's abilities.
NARUTO: Pipe down.
I'm practicing
for a talent show.
SAKURA: What did you say?
LADY CHIYO: Enough with
this ridiculous bickering.
Listen.
I'll show you both
my best skill.
Now watch these wonderful
kunai knives in midair.
SAKURA: Oh, whoa, the
kunai knives are floating.
LADY CHIYO: I can
teach you for 300 ryo.
NARUTO: I can't do it without
the puppet master Jutsu anyway.
Next time, traps activate.
Team Guy's enemies.
[music playing]
-Kisame, my man.
-What is it?
-The guy you're teamed
up with, Itachi,
what can you tell me about him?
-Well, let me see.
Itachi was born into
the Uchiha clan.
He's good with fire style Jutsu.
But his scariest technique by
far is the Mangekyo Sheringan.
-Oh, what's that?
-The ultimate visual Jutsu,
combining powerful hypnosis
and penetrating sight.
It allows him to
use advanced Jutsu
like Amaterasu and Tsyukuyomi.
-Sounds like he's got himself
a pretty artistic Jutsu.
-Now I've got a
question for you.
Can you pick out which
Sheringan is Itachi's?
The answer is A.
-Pretty handsome guy.
And he seems quite
popular, unlike you.
-Hmm?
Something the matter?
-I'm just a freakshow, aren't I?
-Yikes.
That bothered you
more than I thought.