This time you won't
reach the other side!
[growl]
I am still standing. It is
the opposite of last time.
I just wanna
protect the dream
that I realized. We
have fought enough.
You look pretty depressed
right now, Hashirama.
Cannot just perk
back up this time, eh?
It's impossible to
show what's inside
us to each other?
The first step is to not
give up on our ideals.
And we're gonna have
to get stronger, too.
Let's build our
settlement right here!
It's often said that
wherever there's a will,
there's a way, and yet, I.
That dream's now
becoming reality.
A Wood Style Clone!
I cannot believe my
back was taken.
I will protect our-
no, rather, my village.
Whatever it takes...
I still believe that
protecting the village
will in turn lead to
the protection of all the
people, shinobi
and children!
I won't forgive
anyone who would dare
to threaten the village.
Be they friend, sibling,
or even my own child.
You have changed,
Hashirama.
I made a resolution that
day that I would endure
in order to wach
over the present.
You have got your
priorities backwards.
It will someday lead
the village to darkness.
And thus my battle with
Madara came to an end.
I don't have any idea how
Madara returned to life now,
but I know I definitely
killed my friend.
For the sake of
the village...
That's right.
The village is--
The village that Madara
and I envisioned in the
beginning is something that
joined one clan to another.
It was an invaluable
cornerstone that created
order out of chaos and
then maintained it.
It protected the children,
averted pointless conflict,
and made peace a
reality. However...
It gave rise to darkness,
the kind your brother Itachi
was forced to bear.
Perhaps what Madara said
was correct after all.
Maybe he foresaw
this state of affairs.
Still, I am the shinobi who
created these circumstances.
What's more, I
considered them acceptable.
And I believe...
That shinobi are those
who endure for a purpose.
But depending on what
that purpose is,
a shinobi can change.
As both Madara and I did.
So shinobi are defined
as those who endure in
order to achieve their goals.
The goal that I was pursuing
was building a village.
But it appears that Madara
found something else.
About this plan of Madara's
that Orochimaru mentioned.
to erase all the shinobi
in this world, I don't know
what that means
in literal terms.
The Infinite Tsukuyomi,
where village shinobi,
everything is irrelevant.
He'll put everyone under
genjutsu and manipulate
them as he sees fit.
To negate it all. To
nullify everything...
My older brother, Madara's
little brother, and
all of you have
striven to protect.
It turns out my brother
inherited your will without
you ever having
exchanged words with him.
Big Brother.
Itachi, you also serve as
the Uchiha Clan's pipeline
to the Village nerve center.
You know that, don't you?
Even as he shouldered
that heavy responsibility
for our Clan.
We cannot condone
this any longer.
If they're going to start a
revolution and use it to try
to usurp our power.
Then we have no choice
but to judge the Uchiha as
traitors to the Hidden Leaf!
Please wait, Koharu.
Don't rush to conclusions.
However, Hiruzen, the Uchiha
Clan will not be dissuaded.
And since that is, in
fact, the case, we must take
measures to
avoid any mayhem.
That includes
innocent children, too.
Don't say such things
in front of Itachi!
Besides which, a battle
against the Uchiha will be
far from an easy task.
We must plan our
strategy very carefully.
We're in a race
against time, here.
We ought to strike them
preemptively, before they
can make their first move.
If we join forces, and use
our respective Black Ops to
launch a surprise
attack from behind,
we'll end this fast.
The Uchiha are
comrades in arms.
I would like to use words
first before violence.
I will come up
with a strategy.
Itachi.
It doesn't have to be
long, but buy me as
much time as you can.
He stood between
the village and the
clan amid their strife.
I see, so you've aligned
with the other side?
Father...
Mother...
I just...
We already
know, Itachi.
Itachi, just
promise me this.
That you'll take
care of Sasuke.
I will.
Do not fear it.
This is the path
you have chosen.
Compared to yours, our pain
will be over in an instant.
Our philosophies may differ,
but I'm still proud of you.
You are truly a kind child.
He even killed
his own parents.
We've received intel
that Itachi, Uchiha of the
Akatsuki, has died.
You should mark his entry in
your Bingo Book, and remove
him. Just cross him out.
So that traitor has
finally died, has he?
I'm surprised. Who was
able to kill someone that
powerful, do you know?
His little brother,
Sasuke, apparently.
Poetic that someone who
killed his clan got taken
down by his own kin.
Yeah, well, it serves
him right after all the
atrocious stuff he did!
Not only did he join
the Akatsuki, but he also
attacked the Leaf!
He's the most
notorious criminal in
the Village's history!
But damn it all. I
wish that we'd got our
hands on him first!
He killed his own clan
and endured being branded a
Rogue Ninja. Yet he kept
watch over the group that
wanted to harm the Leaf.
And even in death...
But I will have protected my
village. I'm Itachi Uchiha
of the Leaf once again.
My brother endured
longer and harder than you.
When he died he
still said that he was
proud to be Leaf Shinobi.
[chuckle]
Ironic, the one who
understood you most
was a shinobi from
the Uchiha Clan.
Your brother
wasn't the only one.
One of my subordinates
was Kagami Uchiha, a
man a lot like
your brother.
Second Hokage, I thought
that you hated the Uchiha.
That's not the whole truth.
Whatever clan they
belonged to, if someone
posed a danger to the
village, I viewed them
with extreme caution.
And there's no doubt
that the Uchiha Clan
warranted my suspicions.
The Uchiha happened
to be a clan disposed
to be considered warily.
But because they could feel
deep love, there have been
several Uchiha like your
brother and Kagami who could
transcend the boundaries
of the clan and devote
themselves to the village.
My elder brother thought the
village was something that
could eliminate the
framework of clans.
Well the reality of it is
that it wasn't so simple.
Elder brother's naiveté
and the potential risk
that Madara posed.
It was my role as Second
Hokage to mediate between
the two of them, to
protect the village,
and to fortify it.
Shisui Uchiha was a
descendant of Kagami Uchiha.
And he was a friend of
your older brother Itachi.
There've been many,
including myself, who
inherited Lord
First's Will of Fire.
But perhaps I was the most
naïve shinobi of them all.
I couldn't maintain Lord
Second's village-building
skillfully enough.
Which is how I ended up
burdening Danzo with the
village's darkness.
And I killed Danzo
out of revenge.
To the end, he professed
that he would protect the
village, no matter what
dirty means were required.
It seems that I failed
miserably time and time
again as the Hokage.
Even the things that led to
the current circumstances
are in part my
responsibility.
No, it's not your
fault, Lord Third.
You devoted yourself to
the village completely
and respectably.
However, I am the
one who died during the
Nine Tails' attack!
You had such high
hopes for me as Hokage.
And yet I couldn't
live up to them.
And to think I was skipped
over in favor of you.
We were all so
disappointed.
Lord Orochimaru. You
sound like you're pouting!
[chuckle] A bit, since
the Third Hokage is here.
If I hadn't died perhaps I
could've helped to foil the
Uchiha's plans for a coup
d'état a whole lot earlier.
Now then Sasuke.
What next?
Will you crush the village?
Or...
Aww...
Sorry 'bout that,
Sasuke. But we'll do
it some other time.
Sorry, Sasuke.
Maybe some other time.
Ow!
You probably
hate me, huh.
[gasp]
But with us it's
different because you and
I are flesh and blood.
I'm always going to be there
for you, even if it's only
as an obstacle for
you to overcome.
Even if you do hate me.
That's what big
brothers are for.
You believe I had a
hand in this, don't you?
You're not even
worth killing.
Foolish little brother.
If you wish to kill me one
day. Foster your hatred and
despise me. Surviving
in such an unsightly
manner as this.
It's just as you
said, brother.
I've fostered my hatred
for you all this time.
I've lived my life for
one single purpose.
To see you die!
It ends here.
You don't interest
me at the moment.
You're still too weak...
You don't have enough hate.
And you know
something? You never will.
I have always lied to
you and asked for your
forgiveness while
keeping you at a distance.
Because I wanted to
keep you out of this.
But now, I think...
That perhaps you could have
changed Father, Mother, and
the rest of the
Uchiha as well.
If I had only come to
you from the start, looked
straight into your eyes
and told you the truth.
Then I wouldn't have to
stand before you as a
failure, telling
you all of this.
But I want to
impart at least this
much truth to you.
You don't ever
have to forgive me.
And whatever you do from
here on out, know this...
No matter what, I
will love you always.
I'm going to head to the
battlefield! I won't let the
village and Itachi
become nothing!
It's decided!
Tobirama!
Prepare to
fly us outside!
I'd love to use
Flying Raijin, but I'm
bound right now.
Orochimaru, was it?
What will you do now?
I believe you said
earlier you'd stay with
Sasuke, didn't you?
Of course we
shall accompany him.
What?!
Jugo, are you?
I'll go with them, too.
After all, it's my duty to
protect Sasuke.
Four mighty zombies
and three monsters.
If I tag along, I'm
gonna die for sure!
I'm making a break for it
when I get the chance!
This view sure
brings back memories!
It's now or never!
What the hell?!
So, it really was
you, huh, Sasuke?!
I'm--
I sensed your chakra, and I
could hardly believe it, so
I backtracked here,
and look what I find!
Karin?
Oh my so many of my best
experiments, all gathered
here in one place!
Jerk!
I'll never forgive you!
I'm sorry, Karin.
Bastard! You think an
apology will actually get
you off the hook for
what you did to me?
Good for nothing.
I see you still have a
weakness for Sasuke, Karin.
Just listen,
Lord Orochimaru!
Sasuke had the gall to
stab me! You believe that?!
Me too, dear.
Quite a coincidence.
But now, I'm
cooperating with Sasuke.
This is perfect. You
can come help us, too.
What?!
Well, I guess I have
no choice! [giggling]
Who's she?!
From the chakra and
red hair, she's of
the Uzumaki Clan.
Four mighty zombies, three
monsters, and now an idiot.
I bet Madara'll
be shocked, too!
Orochimaru, why have
you decided to cooperate
with Sasuke now?
You've been trying so
hard to destroy the village.
After spending
time inside Kabuto,
I have come to
realize something.
He copied me,
tried to possess
everything, and failed.
Now I'm curious about
the different path
Sasuke has chosen.
That boy, unlike Kabuto,
didn't try to copy me.
My fellow Hokage!
From atop these Great Stone
Faces watching over the
Leaf, let's burn this
view of the village
into our eyes!
[weary sigh]
I'll finally meet my son.
Naruto, I'll make up for not
being there for you as your
father by bringing you
a huge present now!
Now, then, it's been a
while since my last war!
I must focus and
brace for battle!
Madara! We will defeat you!
It's foolish, I know, but
I'm kind of looking forward
to seeing a
familiar old friend!
Just you wait, Madara!
There's always conflict,
no matter what the era, but
this shall be
the end of wars!
Let's go!
Obito, your dream long
ago was to become Hokage.
I'm certain you
must understand
Naruto's feelings!
You can still go back!
[laughter] It's because I
understand Naruto mind...
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Hole."
...that I want to
negate every last
thing that he does!