(NARUTO) I've got dreams, too!
I'm gonna be an even greater
Hokage than you, Dad! I swear I
will!
Tell mom when you see her over
there...
...that she doesn't have to
worry about me even a bit!
[weeping]
Tell her I'm doin' my best!
[sobbing]
We are leaving the rest up to
you now, Kakashi, Sakura...
Plus Sasuke and Naruto.
Lord Third!
Elder Brother, you've now
finally settled things with
Madara. As Saru just said to
them...
...let's leave the rest of it to
the next generation.
(HASHIRAMA) Naruto Uzumaki...
Sasuke Uchiha...
You two will probably find a
different conclusion that we
did. No... make sure that you do
so.
(FOUR TAILS) And now all the
rest of us are free, too!
I'm going back to Suirendo!
[chuckle]
I believe I'll just hunker down
in a forest.
All of us are finally going to
be able to go back to our homes
now. I can't believe it's
true. It's like a dream!
Eight Tails, and what will you
do?
Who, me? I was thinkiing...
Hmmm?
I think I'm gonna go back to
being partners with Bee.
Even that annoying rapping that
he does has ended up growing on
me.
So, what's your plan?
Huh? Hmmm...?
(EIGHT TAILS) What will you do?
Hm.
Well... I'll...
(HAGOROMO) A little piece of
each of your chakra... is
already inside of Naruto.
In short, Naruto is like a
gathering place for you Tailed
Beasts.
If you want to discuss
something, you can speak to each
other through your chakra within
Naruto. Kurama...
Huh?
I'd like you to stay inside
Naruto as the overseerof the
gathering place.
Wha-?!
You no longer mind, right?
Well... I guess I'll do it if
you insist, old man...
[laughter]
What is it?! What the heck is so
funny?
You still can't be honest
about your feelings! You haven't
changed, Kurama.
[chuckling]
It's finally finished. The
Fourth Great Ninja War is over!
Yeah. All that's left is...
Alright, Naruto and Sasuke...
About what I asked you two
before...
Having battled my mother
Kaguya... is there any change to
the answers you gave me?
My answer's the same. And I'm
sorry, Super Gramps, but after
fighting Kaguya...
...there's just one thing I feel
strongly about...
I'm just really happy that my
mom was Kushina Uzumaki, y'know!
Kaguya was different from anyone
else I've ever fought against...
It's like she didn't even have a
heart at all...
Long ago, it was said that my
mother Kaguya started off as a
beloved goddess of the people.
I'm not certain what made her
transform into a being that was
called a demon.
I suspect that the process, or
something, started after she
devoured the Chakra Fruit.
In any case, you are not like my
mother. I trust you not to
become like her, even if...
...you have all the Tailed
Beasts' Chakra in you.
Now then, all that's left... is
to undo the Infinate Tsukuyomi.
But how, specifically? Are you
going to need our powers, as
well?
No, all of you are just fine.
Naruto possesses the chakra of
every Tailed Beast.
And Sasuke posseses the
Rinnegan. If they both weave the
sign for rat simultaneously, the
jutsu will be undone.
What? That's it? It'll really be
that easy?
Believe me, I researched
thoroughly how to undo Mother's
Infinite Tsukuyomi.
There's no mistake.
Very well, then. Now, Sasuke,
the rest... is up to you.
Yeah, alright...
But before that, I'm executing
the current Five Kage inside the
Infinate Tsukuyomi.
[gasps]
What did you just say, Sasuke?!
Huh?
What about the Five Kage?
And you Tailed Beasts...
I'm putting all of you under my
control, and eventually, I'll
get rid of you as well.
What did you just say?
[roar]
Huh?!
[struggling]
Kurama!
He put the Tailed Beats under a
genjutsu...
And with just a single glance,
too...
Naruto, it's ended up as I
feared. I've no choice but to
trust you to handle this.
I can't stay in this world any
longer. I shall soon fade away.
Yeah. And I'll apologize for
this too, Six Paths Super
Gramps, but it ain't gonna go
like it did with your kids.
That's because I'm not Ashura.
And Sasuke... isn't Indra
either.
(KAKASHI) Sasuke! Is this what
your current dream is? Are you
saying that you're still seeking
vengeance?
Why, Sasuke?!
I admit...
...at one time, all that I
wanted was to seek vengeance and
destruction.
But now, things are different.
I want to destroy but then I
want to rebuild.
A village without darkness. I'll
reform the shinobi world.
[straining]
(SASUKE) Do you understand? What
I'm talking about...
...is revolution!
Revolution, you say?!
My dear Sasuke...
What do you want to do? What is
it that you seek for the
aftermath of this war?
I would like to hear your
honest thoughts and opinions.
The previous Kage caused these
circumstances.
So I will become Hokage...
...and change the Village.
This title of "Hokage" that you
mentioned... Just what do you
mean by it?
If you want to know so badly,
I'll tell you.
Catastrophic Planetary
Devistation!
[gasps]
[growl]
It's up to you, Naruto!
I swear I'll rescue you all!
I'll save you!
Just hang in there a little
while longer, okay?!
Because of this war...
...I've already become quite
adept at using my Rinnenegan's
abilities.
And all those who were in my way
are gone.
Except for you... Naruto.
Things just don't go as planned.
When I decided to bequeath power
to just one side, I ended up
with Indra and Ashura.
This time, I bequeathed it to
both, yet it still ended up the
same way...
[exhale]
No way... All this stupid
squabbling... is gonna end right
here and now!
First off, let the Tailed Beasts
go. I mean, they just finally
got their freedom back!
I'm friends with all of them, so
I can guaruntee you this... They
aren't gonna cause trouble any
longer.
Naruto... you don't seem to
understand at all.
As it stands, you're now the
Jinchuriki of all the Tailed
Beasts.
And what that means is that I
plan to eventually get rid of
the Tailed Beast Chakra in you
too.
[gasp]
What?! No way...
In short, you're going to die,
Naruto. Out of necessity.
If what the Sage said is
true...
the Tailed Beast power
inside you isn't necessary in
order for me to release
the Infinite Tsukuyomi.
I can just use the Tailed Beasts
themselves that I captured. I'll
let them live until then.
I'm not gonna stand here and let
you hurt the,. You know that,
don't you?
As expected, I'll have to deal
with you first, Naruto.
Let's move this elsewhere. you
understand, of course?
Wait, Sasuke!
[pained grunt]
Sensei!
[heavy breathing]
The Sharingan's aftereffect is
still...!
[quivering]
I... I know in my heart that
there's nothing I can do, even
though I love you!
Even though I care so much about
you, Sasuke!
I can't get close to you or
exchange blows with you.
I can only whine, beg, and cry,
yet again.
It's so pitiful, isn't it?
Sakura...
I thank you.
But... but please, Sasuke!
If there's even a little corner
of your heart that still thinks
about me, don't leave again!
Please!
If we just stick together... I
know that it can be like old
times again... someday...
You really are...
...still incredibly annoying.
[gasp]
Sakura!
You didn't need to put Sakura
under genjutsu!
If I didn't...
...then she would've just chased
after us and gotten in the way.
Sakura... Sakura just wanted to
help you. All this time...
You're suggesting that I enjoy a
romance?
Too bad I have no reason to love
her or to be loved by her.
The only time that you need a
reason like that is when you
want to hate someone! Don't you
understand?
Sakura isn't even trying to make
you hers!
She only wants to save you! She
almost died by your hand, but
even now... She still spills
tears for you!
She suffers from loving you!
Uh, hey Mom...
Hm?
I was wondering... It's about my
brother and me... What does
father really think of us?
Hm? What on earth makes you ask
that?
The other day, down on the dock,
father said to me, "That's my
boy."
That's something he's only ever
said to Itachi. So it made me
really happy to hear it.
[chuckle]
I see... that's great to hear.
But then I started to wonder,
now that Father and Itachi
aren't getting along...
Am I just...
...someone to replace my older
brother?
[sigh]
Your older brother's your older
brother, and you're you.
Believe me, your father has
always cared very deeply about
the both of you.
He's only thought of Itachi
before now!
If it seemed that
way...
...the reason for that's simple.
It's because your father is a
leader of the Uchiha Clan...
and he has to make sure that
it's kept safe and secure.
What's that got to do with it?
Your brother is the first born.
He's older than you are.
So, since it's your father's job
to look after the clan...
it's only natural he'd want to
be sure that Itachi's ready to
take on his role.
But I'll let you in on a secret.
When we're alone and no one's
around, the only one that he
talks about is... you, Sasuke!
He's so serious, and he has a
hard time showing his feelings;
it's how he is.
Got your lunch ready.
Time to go.
And after you get home today,
I'll watch you practice your
shuriken jutsu. Okay?
It's not "practice." It's called
training.
See you later!
Have a great day!
Well, perhaps, those are merely
the ties to a failed past.
Sasuke...!
(NARUTO) I made a promise...
To Sakura a long time ago...
Don't you worry one bit. I'm
gonna bring Sasuke back.
I promise that on my life
Sakura!
Well, Sensei... You already know
my Ninja Way, right?
I'm gonna go!
Alright... We're counting on
you.
(HAGOROMO) Love and affection
are difficult things...
I too, had two children at one
time.
I loved both of them, and they
both loved and revered me.
But I entrusted everything
only to the younger brother.
That became the impetus for the
older brother to begin hating me
and his brother. Love had
transformed into hate.
What molded the current
Sasuke... is none other than his
loss of love in the past.
Madara was the same.
Are you saying that Sasuke... is
going to suffer the same fate as
Madara?
No, I'm not at all.
I also want to make the future a
better place, in my own way.
Having learned from my past
mistakes...
This time I gave both of them
the power instead.
The past insn't there to
remind the present that the
future can't change.
The past is supposed to exist
for the future.
Why exactly do you see potential
within Naruto?
Somehow, that boy was able to
save and befriend Kurama, who
had become a concretion of
hatred.
I think I shall let Naruto
handle this...
...since I hope that hate can be
transformed into love this
time...
Or rather... I have hope that
love can be regained.
Since, unlike my mother...
Naruto, as well as Sauke...
knows what love truely is.
This place, huh? Should've
figured. Brings back memories,
right, Sasuke?
This place was where we battled
against each other. Seems so
long ago...
It'll be the same now. Just like
the last time... you're going to
lose here.
But you aren't gonna be able to
hit me with the same punch as
last time!
There's no way I'm gonna let you
get away with whatever you want.
And trust me, Sasuke you're not
gonna be Hokage, either!
You don't even seem to
understand what it means to be
Hokage.
I told you, being Hokage means
revolution to me.
It's totally different than what
you believe.
Your big brother once said
something to me. Lemme tell
ya...
Becoming Hokage isn't all about
getting people to acknowledge
you.
Only those already acknowledged
will ever become Hokage.
Well, I learned not from
Itachi's words, but by the way
that he lived his life.
You and I simply arrived at
different conclusions. Let me
clarify this before we fight...
I'll teach you exactly what
being Hokage means to me now.
[scoff]
(NARUTO) You really don't have
any clue at all about how Itachi
lived!
(SASUKE) As of now, Itachi is
entirely in the past. I'm
cutting ties with past mistakes
and doubts.
I'm going to begin by cutting
you down. Yours will be the last
blood that I shed in the memory
of my late brother.
(NARUTO) Next time of Naruro
Shippuden: "The Final Battle."
I won't let you!