[sniffing]
I just caught a whiff...
Are you
telling me you finally notice
what you smell like?
No, not me...
You don't get it...When you deal
with smelly things, your nose
becomes sensitive to all kinds
of scents.
So what do you smelling?
That loudmouthed Leaf guy.
I'd pick up that canine smell
anywhere.
Those guys?!
Are you saying they climbed
outta the sand?!
Relax. It's more fun this way.
We get to go back to the chase
and play a nice game of tag!
It's no fun for me--
(Kazami) I was hoping that no
matter how hard they tried, they
wouldn't be able to catch up to
us...
All right, guyss, let's do this!
[cocky chuckle] Poor Hidden
Leaf...
[sniffing]
[[gasp]
Buuuuurami!
All right...Three cheers for
Burami!
Hip hip, hurray, Burami! Hip
hip, hooray, Burami! Hip hip,
hooray, Burami!
[long inhale]
[loud chewing and exhale]
Oh man, I hate doing this so
much!
[whinning]
[chuckling] There, that'll
completely neutralize our scent.
We're odorless!
[panting and sniffing]
I don't smell them anymore!
[barking]
You too, Akamaru? Damn it!
So now what?
(Shino) Don't worry. The reason
is because even without our
sense of smell, we have our
sense of sight.
Yes, but they're out of the
Byakugan's range!
Then, we simply have to
get within range.
We're counting on you, bugs!
Looks like they found those guys
up ahead, a bit.
All right, then! We're getting
our scroll back-no, I mean,
we're gonna get both the Heaven
and Earth scrolls!
"Unwavering Gutsiness"
[gasp]
There they are.
Uh-huh!
And now, it's those guys' turn
to sink into the sand!
Wait!
I don't see their chakra.
What? What do you mean by that?!
It's just a mirage...
Damn it!
They're fakes?!
[gasp]
The tower...
Can you use your insects again?
Maybe, but there's no guarantee
we'll find the real guys.
Plus. there's a chance that
they'll reach the tower while we
wait for my insects to finish
their reconnaissance.
Damn it!
[gasp]
Why'd I just see his face?!
[growl]
What Kiba?
I ain't givin' up!
Let's do this. Let's find them!
Even if we have no clue where
they are right now?
C'mon! Of course we have a clue!
It's guaranteed they're heading
for the tower. And they'll wanna
avoid that bottomless sandpit
that almost got us!
Yeah, that's a huge area, but
it's still contained!
Well, Hinata?
Huh?!
Can you try to get us a
direction to search in?
Yeah, I'll try.
Byakugan!
Looks like there's a lot of
quicksand in the northeast.
In comparison, the
north-northeast route would
appear to be safer...
I'm in favor of heading for the
tower. There's also the chance
of finding other teams that have
Heaven and Earth scrolls.
We don't have to target that
Hidden Grass trio.
Of course we do!
[gasp]
Those guys stole our scroll!
And I would...
Naruto would take it back from
them, there's no doubt about it!
Naruto...?
Uh...
I mean...Never mind about
Naruto!
You're right. Naruto would do
it.
He'd pursue them to the ends of
the earth!
Forget I ever mentioned Naruto,
okay?! I'm the one who's not
gonna give up!
Yes, Naruto wouldn't give up.
I said I'm the one-
No...So we won't either.
Shino...
The reason is because Team 10,
with its sensory perception
powers, must never be beaten.
Shino!
All right!
It's time for us to show those
guys what we're made of!
We're not letting them get away,
no matter what!
Huh...?
I think we gave 'em the slip.
[buzz]
Huh? What's wrong?
Those pesky guys...I just caught
another whiff of 'em...
I thought that you erased our
scent.
Yeah, I did...But, I guess that
they can still track us by
instinct or something.
Then, we'll just have to take a
little detour. What's the big
deal?
Look, we'll stop 'em. But don't
underestimate 'em.
You're right. Their persistence
is extraordinary. I'll say
that...
Plus, they're extraordinarily
confident in their tracking
skills, as well.
So, what are we gonna do?
You have me, so just relax!
Hip, hip, hooray, Burami!
[big inhale]
[chewing and belch]
[gasp]
Here we go!
[barking]
You too, Akamaru?!
What is it, Kiba?
It's that blubber guy's scent!
[sniffing]
This way!
Heh. Try all you want, but you
can't hide your scent from me!
We're gonna find you. You just
wait!
[gasp]
[sniffing]
What, Kiba...?
A trap, as expected.
This whole area...reeks of that
guy's scent...
Here we go!
But, which of these schents
is...
...that bastard's real
scent...?!
Seems like they're onto us.
Damn it!
[whine]
Why was I able to keep laughing?
And keep getting back up?
What enabled me to do that back
then?
Naruto...
Just when I thought UI caught up
to him. he takes off to train
with Master Jiraiya...
Damn it...
I'll train, too!
Listen, Akamaru...We're going
to surpass our Two-Headed Wolf.
So, we'll have a whole lotta
heads, and we'll call it...
...the Multi-Headed Wolf!
[whine]
Now, to do that...
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
[barking]
Oh man, I guess that...
I don't have enough...chakra
to...
[moaning]
[barking]
[licking]
Okay, I get it...
I guess you were right...
Looks like I found out the hard
way that the more Shadow Clones
you try to make, the more chakra
you use up...
Just how much chakra does Naruto
have?
Damn it...
It's no use. I'm just gonna have
to start with one and, then,
steadily increase the number.
[bark]
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Let's do it, Akamaru! With you,
we'll have three bodies to
make...the Three-Headed Wolf!
Inuzuka Style! Man Beast
Transformation Combo!
Three-Headed Wolf!
[roaring]
I'm not even able to sustain my
jutsu when my chakra level drops
to half...
Steadily increase it? Who am I
kidding?!
Can I even do a Three-Headed
Wolf at all...?
[sigh]
No, I have to do it! I'll do it,
I'll do it, I'll do it!
If my chakra's too low, I'll
increase it! I'll work on my
stamina and taijutsu to build up
my strength!
[yell]
What is this...?
[sniffing]
[gasp]
Naruto...!
Blood...sweat...
This place reeks of Naruto's
scent...
[yell]
[boom]
[whine]
Can you tell by the scent, too?
It's as clear as day...I can
tell just how hard Naruto
trained out here.
It's my turn...
I'll cover this place with our
scent!
[bark]
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
[roar]
[thud]
C'mon, again, Akamaru!
[barking]
I won't give up! I'll never give
up!
[growl]
[roar]
No way am I going to lose...Not
to that bastard!
Three-Headed Wolf!
[sniffing]
[bark]
That's right! It's my...
I mean, our scent!
Damn it...
I can almost hear Naruto...
He's laughing at us again...
asking if we're gonna give up!
Well, we're not giving up!
It's okay...
Just give up!
[thud]
[pow]
[smack]
You guys-
How-?!
...did you-?!
[chuckle]
Nothing wrong...
...with prey becoming the
predator, am I right? [chuckle]
[groan]
They totally caught us by
surprise...!
At this rate...
[inhale]
Hip, hip!
Hooray, Burami!
Hip, hip, hooray, Muyami! Hip,
hip, hooray, Muyami!
Is it...all over...?!
[gasp]
Wait...
Hey, what's up...?
He stopped moving all of a
sudden...
Huh?
We did it! We defeated those
Leaf guys! And, it's all because
of me!
No, Burami! Like I always say,
it's 'cause of our teamwork!
It doesn't matter. Let's just
hurry up and finish this.
Let's go.
But it was all 'cause of me!
Yeah! There's the tower! We did
it!
Huh?
What?! You?! How...?!
We fooled you guys really good!
You didn't think we were dead,
did you?!
Too bad for you, we're still
alive!
I used the insects inside me to
make it seem like I was dead.
And, Kiba and Hinata switched
places with Insect Clones.
No way! We've been had!
Yeah, but even so...How were you
guys able to track us?!
And, why didn't you catch their
scent before now?!
Our scent was contained. The
reason is...
You used your insects to make
airtight suits?!
[chuckle]
Like that?!
[gasp]
But, but, but, but...I made sure
that I'd erased our scent, too!
I still don't get how they were
able to track us!
We didn't follow your scent!
[gasp]
The scent that I followed was
this one right here!
You see, there's this guy named
Naruto...
I've never heard of him! Who is
he?!
I'm just saying he exists!
Anyway,...he kept on popping
into my head.
I thought it was strange...But,
then I remembered...
Scents have a powerful ability
to stir up the various memories
that they're connected to.
[sniffing]
[roar]
[thud]
Back at the training ground, at
home, some grass got rubbed into
my elbow.
This scent reminded me of that
training,...
...and it even brought back
memories I didn't want to think
about, like Naruto...!
[chuckle] But in that memory, he
told me not to give up, no
matter what.
All this has nothing to do with
us...
You're wrong! It does!
The stain on my elbow,...I
rubbed it on Blubber Man's
belly, earlier.
[gasp]
You could erase your own scent,
but you weren't able to erase
the scent of the grass!
This is your fault!
No, it's the fault of the whole
team...
Well,...we caught you, so give
it back! No...
We'll tale it back from you!
That Heaven scroll is ours!
Summoning Jutsu!
Moguranmaru!
[roar]
Infestation...complete...
Fang Over Fang!
[thump}
[eaager roar]
Devour! Parasitic Gigantic
Beetle!
[cry]
[yelling]
8 Trigrams: Air Palm!
[whoosh]
[crying]
Now, I'll take down all three of
you at once!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Inuzuka Style! Man Beast
Transformation Combo!
Three-Headed Wolf!
[roar]
Burami!
Uh, it's okay! I'll
just...uh...!
Hip, hip...!
Tail Chasing!
...Hooray!
Rotating Fang!
Kiba!
Naruto saved us...That's
because...
That's because Naruto reminded
us never to give up, is that it?
Come on!
[sniffing]
I'm the one who thought of
Naruto and tracked that guy with
this scent!
It was all 'cause of me!
Well,...I still think that
Naruto-
No, you're wrong. It was me!
[bark]
Yeah! You did great too!
[howl]
It is so convenient having you
around, Tenten!
What's that mean?! I may have
convenient tools, but I am not a
convenient tool, okay?
No, no , Tenten! You are
absolutely convenient!
Seriously?!
Hey, Tenten...
Don't follow me!
What just happened?!
I've no idea...
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Tenten's Troubles."
[sigh] Guess I just needed to
vent a bit...