(Hokage) Iruka.
(Iruka) What is it Lord Hokage?
[growls]
(Hokage) I know how you feel.
You grew up just like Naruto,
without knowing the love of a
mother and father.
Hmm?
Now who could that be
at this hour?
(Iruka) Mizuki Sensei?!
What? What is it?
You need to come to Lord
Hokage's.
It's Naruto! It seems he's
pulled a prank and stole the
sacred scroll!
No!
It's been over half a day since
the Scroll of Sealing was taken.
Bring Naruto here at once!
Naruto!
You've gotta hurry up and give
the scroll to me!
Mizuki's coming to take it!
[grunts]
[grunting]
[groaning]
It can't be. Naruto?
How'd you know I wasn't
Iruka?!
[laughs]
Because I'm Iruka.
Uh!
Naruto's one of a kind. Works
hard, puts his whole heart
into it.
Sure, he messes up sometimes,
and everyone jumps on him.
But his suffering only makes
him stronger.
(Iruka) So you're wrong, he's
nothing like the Nine-Tailed
Fox.
He's Naruto Uzumaki of the
Village Hidden in the Leaves!
A dream?
(Konohamaru) Huh?!
What's this all about, anyway,
Iruka Sensei?
Do you remember that
congratulatory message that you
recorded me delivering before?
Huh? Oh yeah. You mean that
boring message without style
or enthusiasm?
C'mon, now, don't say that!
Can't you just use that one
for your video?
But you told me that you wanted
to redo it.
So I've been waiting around this
whole time for you to come up
with something else!
I'm sorry about that.
But the more I think about it,
the less sure I am about what I
should say to Naruto.
But you held out for so long,
and now you're the only one who
hasn't finished theirs!
Look, don't over-think it.
Just make up your mind and send
him a cool, heartfelt message,
okay?!
Please forgive me. Tell you
what, I'll treat to you some
ramen next time, okay?
Hey! Tsukune, Sansho, Mibuna!
(Iruka) You messed around with
the Third Hokage's statue again,
didn't you?!
I can't believe it's almost
here! Naruto's wedding is next
week!
So, Iruka, are you going to
give a congratulatory speech?
Uh. Oh no. That's Lord Hokage's
job! I'm pretty sure he's gonna
be taking care of that.
(Ayame) Hey, Iruka!
Huh? Oh, Ayame!
Is something the matter? You
haven't been around much at
all lately.
Oh, I just wanted to hold off
until I figured out what to
say...
for the message that Konohamaru
asked me to record.
I'm trying to practice some
self-restraint.
Oh! So did you get your
message all finished up, then?
Uh, well, uh.
I'll stop by again in just a
little while. Please say hello
to your dad for me!
(Kid) Oh, come on! That's too
easy!
All right, can you jump this
far?!
[leaping yell]
[grunts]
Ha! I knew it!
Oh, boy.
(Kid) Shut up! I still beat you
at fence jumping!
(Naruto) It's all thanks to you,
Iruka Sensei.
That night, you acknowledged
me. Do you remember?
It was the first time ever!
And that's the reason why I'm
here today.
(Naruto) Your words changed me.
Naruto was able to express his
feelings so clearly and directly
to me. What am I doing?
[grunting]
[groans] I really shouldn't do
things I don't know how to do!
Hmm?
Yes?
Oh!
(Iruka) Naruto?!
Uh, hey there, Iruka
Sensei.
Um, is something the matter?
No, it's nothing. It's just,
um.
Well, I was just thinking about
you.
And so I thought that I'd
stop by here to you know, see if
you were still alive!
What the hell does that mean?
The thing is, I'm gonna be
getting married soon, and with
you still being single...
and all, I was worried about you
being alone. Anyway, I'm gonna
come on in!
Hey, wait! I'm in the middle
of...
What happened here?!
It's really nothing at all, just
some stuff.
But more importantly, what about
you? What's going on?
Oh, uh, well, uh.
Oh yeah! Ramen! Do you want to
go and get some ramen with me?
Some ramen? Actually, I was just
in the middle of making dinner
right now.
Oh, that explains this crime
scene.
Uh, yeah.
You really should hurry up and
find someone to get married
to, Iruka Sensei!
Oh, shut up! What about you?
Should you be neglecting
Hinata right now?
What are you talking about,
"neglecting?"
Besides we aren't even married
yet, so don't worry about it.
Don't worry about it?
You heard me! My single days
are numbered! I gotta have
all the fun I can till...
You stupid fool!
Are you kidding?! Do you even
have a clue about exactly how
hard...
Hinata has been working to
prepare for your wedding?!
Hey, what's the matter, Iruka
Sensei?
Hmm. It seems there are a lot of
things I failed to teach you...
about how to be a good human
being!
I take full responsibility for
that!
Come with me! I'm gonna knock
some sense into you!
(Naruto) Where are we going,
Iruka Sensei?!
(Iruka) To Hinata's!
(Iruka) I'm gonna have to
apologize to her for raising
you...
as such a thoughtless,
inconsiderate man.
C'mon stop! Please, if
Hinata's around I can't tell
you what I wanted to say!
What exactly did you wanna
say?
That's why I thought that you
and I could have some ramen, and
then, while we're still out...
you could maybe have a
drink or two and we could have a
nice conversation and...
you know, have a little fun!
(Iruka) Enough.
[sighs]
I guess that I didn't need to
spend as much time as I did
mulling it all over.
Thinking what to say and how
to congratulate you.
I have a favor to ask.
A favor?
Do you think that you might be
willing to take on the role of
my father at the wedding?
Naruto?
(Iruka) Is that what you wanted
to talk to me about?!
You can leave it to me!
[happy chuckle] Iruka Sensei!
Thank you.
Come on, what are you talking
about, Naruto? That's my
line! Thank you!
[chuckles]
Okay, that's enough of that!
I'll see you later, Iruka
Sensei!
All right!
[choked up crying]
Hey, good evening!
Oh, hi!
Hey, there!
Welcome back!
So, what's going on?
Are you wrestling with some
kind of problem again?
Huh? Oh, no.
I was just thinking about how
truly glad I am that I chose
the profession I did.
Oh, I see! Well, what can I
get for you today?
Uh. A large miso char siu
ramen topped with naruto
fishcake, please.
(Teuchi) One large miso char siu
ramen!
(Ayame) You got it! Coming right
up!
(Iruka) Hinata!
Huh? Iruka Sensei!
How are all of the
preparations coming along?
They're good! Now, we just
have to wait for the big day.
Well, I'm very glad to hear
that! Anyway, I have something
to say.
I'll just dive in. It's about
the wedding ceremony.
Oh, you've accepted Naruto's
request to attend as his
father, haven't you?
So you already knew about
that, huh? Yeah, of course you
would! [laughing]
I think it's something that's
been on Naruto's mind for a
long time, now.
There's no doubt that you're
Naruto's teacher, Iruka Sensei.
But he didn't really think of
your bond as just a...
student-teacher or mentor
relationship.
[taken aback]
(Iruka) Thing is...
I kinda feel like this shouldn't
be coming from the point of view
of a teacher to his student.
Naruto was thinking the same
thing as I was!
And so his answer to what he
was thinking was to ask me to
attend as his father, huh?
That's right. I hope that you'll
continue to support him just as
you always have, Father!
[gasps]
Uh, yes, of course!
[chuckles] But it's kinda
embarrassing to be asked so
formally!
[giggles]
Anyway.
I don't get it. What is this?
It isn't very much, but please
put it toward the cost of the
wedding.
What?!
Naruto asked me to stand in as
his father, so I have to!
If I tried to give it to him,
he wouldn't take it.
I'm not going to take it
either! Listen, please! Don't
worry about that!
Oh. I see.
Guess I don't have much of a
choice...
but to accept your answer
and wait for the big day to
arrive.
I wish that I could've done
something fatherly to help you
out more, though.
[giggles]
Uh! What is it?!
[giggling] With that expression
on your face, you look just like
my father!
So in a way, you are acting
like the father of the groom.
Really? You think so?
[laughing]
(Konohamaru) Three, two...
One! And we're rolling!
Naruto, Hinata, congrats on
your wedding day!
Naruto.
[chuckles]
What's the matter now, Iruka
Sensei? You at a loss for
words again or something?
No, sorry, sorry. Don't worry,
I'll do it right, I promise!
Can I start over again, just one
more time?
[weary sigh]
Naruto and Hinata!
Congratulations on your wedding!
Please create a home that is
as bright as the morning sun!
May you always be happy!
Cheers!
Congratulations!
Do your best!
Don't eat too many tasty
homemade meals!
Congratulations.
Yeah, congrats!
Congratulations to you both,
Mr. Naruto and Miss Hinata!
Congratulations on getting
married!
Stop by once in a while for
ramen, okay?
Congratulations, you two.
Congratulations!
Naruto, Miss Hinata, a lot's
happened, but congratulations.
Big Brother Naruto, you did
it! And I'll do my best, too!
Naruto Uzumaki,
congratulations.
Dear Naruto, do your best.
Yeah!
Naruto, Hinata,
congratulations on your
wedding!
Be there for each other, and
may you have everlasting
happiness!
Naruto! Hinata! Congrats on
your wedding!
Hinata, as you know, Naruto's
absentminded and reckless. He's
gonna need all your support.
So I ask of you: please take
good care of him!
Naruto, I just have this to
say.
You'd better do everything to
make Hinata happy!
[mild chuckle]
That was great! I'd even say
it was perfect, Iruka Sensei!
[relieved sigh] It went off
without a hitch, huh?
Great.
Could you get the receiving
desk set up, too?
Lord Kakashi!
[groans] Like I said about a
hundred times, drop the "lord"
part.
The Lords Kage have just
arrived in the Village.
Huh? They're here
already?!
Shall I escort them in, then?
Yes. It's rude to keep them
waiting.
Hmm? Hey, Kazekage entourage!
We're here from the land of
Lightning, delivering our
wedding blessings.
Let's forget the past and all be
friends till the last!
Yes, of course! I don't feel
like fighting like little
brats anymore.
Yo, now direct your eyes, see
my gift and be surprised. Even
the couple will be rapturized!
(Raikage) Enough!
[grunts]
(Shizune) The reception desk is
now open. Please come and sign
the guest book...
Hey, where's Temari run off
to?
I haven't seen her since we
got here.
Between you and me, how much
are you giving them, Ebisu
Sensei?
Well, etiquette says that
working adults are supposed to
give about.
Huh?!
You can give that little? Man,
I put five bills in my
envelope.
What?! Did you say you
put five in?!
Oh, no! I'll lose face as a
teacher!
Oh, this is the gift table!
Hold on a second. Here's our
gift!
No, dad, not that one!
Oh, yeah. Good catch.
This one!
Oh, seriously!
Now listen up, Lee! When we
honor people, we hone our mind
and spirit.
That's what a wedding
celebration is for!
What you are saying is to
never forget to train, even
when at a party!
[grunts] Naturally!
Look, people are starting to
stare, so will you cut it out
already?!
We'll start with dumbbell
juggling!
Yes, Guy Sensei!
Hah!
What a day! What a joyous day
this is!
This training especially so!
You have way too much joy in
your heads!
(Kurenai) So? Did you get ahold
of the honey wine?
(Kiba) Of course!
And we're gonna tell Naruto
all about the history of the
Senju Clan along with this!
Are you really well versed
enough in their history to be
able to do that?
Huh?! Well, kinda. I, uh...
I'll tell you what, why don't
you run it by me first?
Oh, uh, thanks, but...
(Mirai) Giddy up!
Run! Go!
What are you doing,
Mirai?
I'm playing horsey-back!
Akamaru is a dog. You can't
ride a dog and call it
horsey-back riding.
Then I'm doggie-back riding!
That's true, it is doggie-back
riding. But Akamaru looks a
little tired now.
So why don't you just come on
down from there? The reason
is...
No! Wanna ride!
I guess there's no choice.
We'll go Shino-back riding,
then.
That seems new to me. Was
Shino always this good with
the little kids?
He seems to think that he
might be suited to teaching in
the future.
Just what are you smiling
about?
What? Who ever said that I was
smiling?
Yeah, whatever.
I know what the deal about
weddings is.
Men go to them to meet single
friends of the bride, isn't that
right?
That's not it! Man, this is
such a drag. Come on, let's go
over there.
[gasps] So sweet!
It's definitely going to be
sweet.
How long has that been going
on? When did those two get
together?!
Just who do you mean?
Shikamaru and Temari.
Did you know they were like
that?
M-hm.
Anyway, you know that everyone's
probably thinking the same thing
about us right now.
[sighs]
[gasps]
Sasuke.
Hey, what's the matter, Iruka
Sensei? Is there something
that's still worrying you?
Well.
It'll all be fine.
Thanks to you we have enough
shinobi to cover guard duty and
anything else we might need.
Oh no, all of that was really
your doing, Kakashi.
[chuckles] No, I hardly did
anything at all.
Maybe I managed to help things
along a little.
(Kakashi) But it's really all
thanks to the bonds that Naruto
forged.
Everyone's here today, all
because of Naruto.
I'm sure that he's going to
make Hinata very happy.
So what exactly are you
worried about?
Well, I never really got around
to preparing my toast for the
reception.
Huh?! [laughing]
Big Brother Neji. I'm about to
get married.
(Hanabi) Elder Sister! It's
time!
Right!
Wow! You look so
beautiful!
Don't you think so, Father?
Okay, are you ready?