The Ten Tails vanished?!
What's going on up there?
Have they taken it down?
No...
Hinata!
Did you see it?
Yeah...
Can you explain what
exactly happened?!
The Ten Tails has
been completely
absorbed into that man.
Based on its chakra.
Don't tell me.
That guy is Ten
Tails' Jinchuriki?!
What's this I feel?
Jinchuriki, huh?
This is bad.
He looks even
creepier than he did before!
Obito...
Naruto, how can you
tell he's a Jinchuriki?
I made friends with
the other Tailed Beasts.
Earlier, they all gave me
some of their chakra,
so I can totally feel it.
I felt the Tailed Beasts'
chakra get sucked inside
Obito one after another.
And besides that, I saw
Nagato do that Six Paths
Rebirth Jutsu before.
But the signs that this
guy was weaving were
completely different!
He was performing the jutsu
to become a Jinchuriki
this whole time.
I see...
Eight-o!
Is that its final form?
No, it's not.
It's difficult to
explain, but that isn't it.
It seems Ten Tails was
used to create a Jinchuriki
before it reached
its final form.
[grunt]
Even if you've become a
Jinchuriki, the Gracious
Deity Gates are
still in play.
Whoa!
Awesome!
Not quite...
Wha-?!
The Sage Art Seal that
even suppressed Ten Tails.
Such power...
[gasp]
No way!
The Four Crimson
Ray Formation!
Is he stronger than
when he was gigantic?
Or is it me?
Before, it was just throwing
its brute strength around.
But now, it's apparently
learned to focus it.
Everyone, keep
your guard up!
He's made The Ten
Tails' power his own.
There's not telling
what he might do!
He's broken the barrier!
Enough, Obito!
Stop this now!
O...
bi...
to...?
Look, I'll be blunt.
This guy is
stronger than I am!
No offense intended,
but it appears to be true.
Even if you absorb your
remaining clones, you're no
match, Elder Brother!
Yes, I know.
However...
Though it would be quite fun
to watch the Hokage beg for
mercy, I simply
cannot wait any longer.
Obito is now just like
the Sage of the Six Paths.
I can't let him
take the lead before I
use my trump card.
Huh?!
What happened?
So fast!
Fourth!
Saru!
Scram!
This is Lord
Second's attack plan!
Brother!
Minato, get away now!
Lord Second, you
sure work fast!
Flying Raijin Jutsu!
I suspected that might
not be enough to kill you.
I created the
Reanimation Jutsu,
and its ancillary jutsu.
Though it's the first
time I'm using it on myself.
Here it comes!
Lord Second's special,
Tandem Explosive Tags!
And this is how it's done!
Each tag summons more tags,
resulting in concentrated
and focused
consecutive explosions!
[grunt]
This is way too much!
What's going on?
I can't keep up!
Now don't freak out!
Always watch
what's happening!
I don't care if
that's The Ten Tails'
Jinchuriki or whatever!
Our Lords Hokage are
engaged in battle!
Let's join them!
Don't be hasty!
We need to take our-!
All of you!
You must not
approach him carelessly!
Damn it!
What is he?!
He's solid and swift.
And has an attack that turns
all to dust in an instant!
Shuriken Shadow Clones!
It's like Ohnoki's Particle
Style, but can change
shape, be offensive or
defensive, and be
continuously maintained.
I suspect it's a combination
of more than four Changes in
Chakra Nature!
This is more than a Kekkei
Genkai or even a Kekkei
Touta...
But there seems to be
a time limit to how long
he can use each one.
Gramps, no!
Hey, Dad!
You couldn't teleport
Grandpa Third
with your jutsu, too?
I couldn't.
I simply can't teleport
anything that I myself, or
my chakra, isn't
touching directly.
Calm down, Naruto.
The Hokage are
Reanimations.
They intentionally attacked
head-on, knowing full well
they wouldn't die to
assess the enemy's powers.
Stop worrying and
analyze the battle instead.
That's Sasuke.
He's bright.
But it still takes a little
while for a Reanimation
to regenerate.
I'll go first and
create an opening!
At this point, I
feel the need to.
I'm done waiting!
Let's go, Hashirama!
Wh- What the-?!
I see, Ten Tails hasn't
completely synched
with its Jinchuriki yet.
This is our chance
to take it down!
I'll summon my
original here, then!
It's been a while, but
time for my Rasen-Flash
Super-Circle Dance
Howl Stage Three!
[gasp]
Gamakichi!
Below!
He passed underground!
But just his upper body!
Damn it!
Sasuke...
You're not the one...
...who will sever the past.
I am!
[gasp]
Be in time!
Flying Raijin Jutsu!
My markings on
Obito disappeared?!
Damn it!
I really thought
we were done for!
I simply can't teleport
anything that I myself, or
my chakra, isn't
touching directly.
[chuckle]
Looks like my kid is as
accomplished as Sasuke.
Now, then...
He's just like a snake!
What is that?!
We have to take him down
while he's still unable to
use his body well.
Was he after your
clone just now, Dad?
No.
I don't think that's
what he's going for.
Hold on.
What just happened?!
He hit himself
with his own attack.
His attack
missed its target.
Seems Obito's consciousness
is merely clinging on to The
Ten Tails' great power.
He barely has
any control of it.
Well, I'm certainly glad
he missed us because
otherwise, we'd be dead!
We can't
carelessly approach him!
Now I'll get in the
Rasen-Flash Super-Circle
Dance Howl Stage Three!
I'll create an opening.
Then you two
immediately hit him with
your strongest combo!
Rin- [discomforted yell]
[screaming]
Of course I'm
gonna become Hokage!
Rin!
Then...
I'm not gonna have any
time for girls at all!
Am I right, Sensei?
[screaming]
Here I come, Obito!
Who are you?
[screaming]
It's about time, Sensei.
Damn it!
Dad, no!
Naruto, focus!
He may have gotten
me, but I'm still okay!
I escaped with
Flying Raijin.
Are you sure?
When did he?!
Ah, he attached it to
me so it would teleport
along with me!
Even a small power can
be helpful, depending
on how it's used.
There might come a time
when we'll be needed.
Our power could change
the course of this world.
We can't afford to relax
and let our guard down,
even for one second!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "An Opening."
Shikamaru, you would
make a great Hokage.