[theme music]
[owl calling]
[wind rushing]
[diabolical laughter]
[owl calling]
MALE SPEAKER: This'll stop them!
[thunk]
-Huh?
Nngh.
[explosion]
[clay clattering]
-Nngh!
They might hit Lord Kazekage!
Tell them to cease
fire immediately!
Nngh.
Sir!
Hold your fire!
All units cease fire at once!
MALE SPEAKER: Cease
fire, cease fire!
MALE SPEAKER: Gaara.
MALE SPEAKER: What the
devil is he up to now?
-Nngh.
Don't tell me he's
leaving the village.
-I've kept my man, Sasori,
waiting long enough, I think.
Hmph!
-Nngh.
Is he going to
carry him off alive?
-I'm going after him!
-Kankuro, no!
Don't go by yourself!
Wait for a back-up squad!
-By then, he and Gaara
will be long gone!
-All right, but don't engage
until we catch up with you!
-Right, understood!
-Damn.
KANKURO: So, he was
after Gaara all along.
-Lord Kankuro, we're here!
-We can't let that guy get away!
BOTH: Right!
KANKURO: He's landing.
He doesn't realize we've got
a security unit stationed
right there.
-Well, I've cleared my mission.
Hmm!
-You're late.
I told you, don't
keep me waiting!
-Aren't we grumpy!
This one was rather
strong, you know.
Hmm.
-Yes.
Perhaps next time
you'll listen to me!
-Everything ready here?
-Well, of course it is!
I had plenty of
time to see to it.
Unlike you, I know
what I'm doing.
-Hmm.
Well, then.
Let's get going.
Hmm.
SASORI: I'm never
coming back here again.
[footsteps]
-Wait, hold it!
-Why, what's the matter, sir?
-It's way too quiet.
[gasping]
-We have a whole squad guarding
this entrance to the village.
He landed right on top of them.
We should be hearing
the sounds of fighting.
So then why is it
as quiet as a grave?
On top of that, they
never replied my message
asking them to confirm
their position.
What's going on out here?
-[gasping] Lord-- Lord Kankuro!
-What have you found?
[footsteps]
-Ahh!
Wha-- what happened?
It's a bloody massacre.
This didn't just happen now.
It might have been before
Gaara's battle started.
-There were ANBU Black
Ops in this unit.
Their attackers must have
heavily outnumbered them.
-Or maybe not.
-What do you mean?
-Nothin'.
Forget about it.
(TO HIMSELF) When Gaara
was named kazekage,
I investigated everyone!
There's no way we could have a
traitor among the Sand Village
shinobi.
Whatever happened, the ones
who took Gaara passed this way
and they're getting
farther away every second.
Let's move!
EVERYONE: Yes, sir!
-Here, sir!
One of them is still alive!
-Wait!
Be careful how you handle him!
-Hunh!
-A paper bomb!
[explosion]
-Ahh!
-Aaugh!
-Sounds to me like someone just
for your trap, Sasori my man.
Hmph!
-Well, of course.
It wouldn't have been much
of a trap if they hadn't.
-Well, I guess
that's true enough.
Hmph.
[door creaking open]
-Finally!
Home sweet home!
The old place hasn't
changed a bit.
[floor boards creaking]
-Whoa.
Well, bound to be a little
dusty, being closed up
for a couple of years.
[door opening]
-[gasping] You see?
I finally made it
back here, Sasuke.
(TO HIMSELF) So I
can bring you home.
[rock dust falling]
[labored breathing]
-No!
Can't be!
Do you think Kankuro
and the others
were caught in that trap?
-No, I-- I can't believe it.
Watch out!
It's gonna collapse!
What in the--
[poof]
[growls]
-Nngh.
Kankuro!
-I was only able to
save two of them.
[labored breathing]
-These men need
medical attention.
Hurry!
-Wait!
What are you going to do?
-What do you think?
I'm gonna bring Gaara back.
-Are you insane?
Didn't you see what
he did to Gaara?
Do you really think you
stand a chance alone?
-What are you suggesting?
That we just let him go?
-No!
Of course not.
We'll find out
where his base is,
then assemble a large,
fully equipped squad.
-It's no use.
-Very well.
Go on and follow them,
but you're not to engage!
-I'll try, but no promises.
-(TO HIMSELF) Damn you, Kankuro!
-Huh?
So they're playing with me, huh?
This is Gaara's sand.
Nngh.
(TO HIMSELF) Hang on, Gaara!
I'm coming.
-You finish up here.
-Sir!
[footsteps]
-Assemble a full pursuit squad
and send them after Kankuro
at once!
-Sir!
Send word to the
Hidden Leaf Village,
apprising them of the situation.
Tell them we have an emergency.
Now!
-Sir!
(TO HIMSELF) As bad as
things are, I have a feeling
they're about to get
much, much worse.
[footsteps]
-It's up to you, Takamaru.
Fly!
[bird calling]
-What's going to happen?
-Don't worry.
I'm sure Lord Kazekage
will be back soon.
[wings flapping in the wind]
[footsteps]
-Nngh.
[growling] That way!
-[sighing] Brilliant!
It's even better reading
it a second time!
But I guess I should
get some sleep.
Huh?
It's morning already?
Oh no, that's not good.
I still haven't made
up that personnel list
for the new squad.
That's not it.
No.
Not that.
Where did I put it?
-All right.
[door opening and closing]
-Well, you're up awfully early.
[yawning] Everyone in their
right mind's still asleep.
-Why are you-- I
have my own village
to think about, you know?
I've been gone too long,
so since I'm finished here,
I thought I'd head back.
-Yeah, but without
having any breakfast?
-Oh, I'll find it tea house
or something along the way.
Come to think of it, what
are you doing up so early?
-Believe me, I wish I wasn't.
But I'm supposed to be
your escort while you're
in our little village, remember?
It's a drag, but
it's my mission.
--[chuckling] Sorry to
be so much trouble.
Your mission's done.
-So I guess we'll meet again
at the chunin exams, huh?
-Yeah.
I'll see you then.
-Huh?
-You ask me?
It's time you became a jonin.
You won't have any
problem if you just
stop complaining about
what a drag everything is.
-Huh?
Hmm.
-Man, what a drag.
-All right!
-Let's go to work.
[wind gusting]
-(TO HERSELF) I don't like
the feel of that wind.
-Hmm?
Sasori?
What's the matter?
-I wouldn't have
thought it possible.
We're being followed.
-Hold it right there.
We meet at last.
Hand over Gaara now!
-Heh.
-Deidara, you go on ahead.
-Huh?
--[sighing] (TO
HIMSELF) The tall one.
He's the one riding
that strange bird,
the one that carried off Gaara.
Which means his
companion's the one who
set the trap in the village.
-Huh?
[scrolls unfurling]
-Are you two ready
for a puppet show?
Grow!
Black Ant!
Salamander!
I'm
[explosion]
[wood clacking]
[growls]
-I'll say it again.
Hand over Gaara!
Now!
-There you are!
You're late!
-Finally, Sensei.
-Yeah, uh, sorry about that!
It took me a lot longer
than I thought to,
uh, finalize the
new squad dossier.
-Hello!
This is our first new
mission as a good team!
Couldn't you be just
a little excited?
Kakashi-sensei, you haven't
changed a bit, have You
--[growling] Already
you're annoying!
Shut up!
Don't waste your breath.
You know he's always
looked un-enthusiastic,
like he doesn't care.
-(TO HIMSELF) Hmm.
I don't seem to be inspiring
a lot of respect here.
Hmm?
[wings buffeting wind]
-(TO HIMSELF) That looks
like one of the Hidden
Sand's carriers.
-The Puppet Master Jutsu, eh?
-Heh.
I'm going on ahead.
Enjoy the show!
-Think again!
Huahh!
[wood clattering]
-Aaugh!
What?
-I don't like to wait,
or keep others waiting.
So I'll make this
short and sweet.
[theme music]
MALE SPEAKER: With his
brother's life on the line,
this is a match that the
challenger cannot afford
to lose!
MALE SPEAKER: He can
stand the pressure.
He's a puppet master
of the Sand, after all.
MALE SPEAKER: Yeah, but
the champion Sasori's
a tricky opponent with a lot
of moves we haven't seen yet.
Oh, Kankuro opens the
fight by bringing out Crow.
MALE SPEAKER: Oops!
Looks like that didn't work,
but the challenger still
has a salamander up his sleeve.
MALE SPEAKER: Whoa!
And there it is!
The salamander!
Yes, indeed!
It looks like we are in
for a heck of a fight!
NARUTO: Next time,
"Team Kakashi Deployed!"
[theme music]
NARUTO: A word from the
Society for Leaf Tourism.
Today, we'll look at
the 44th Battle Training
Zone, the second of
the chunin exam sites,
also known as The
Forest of Death.
This training ground
is a circle with radius
of 10 kilometers,
surrounded by a fence.
Each team of chunin
candidates enters
through one of the 44
gates in the fence.
The gates are
locked behind them,
and the teams race
to see who could
be the first to reach the tower
in the middle of the forest.
This isn't just any forest!
The trees are huge!
And it's got giant centepedes,
enormous leeches, and tigers!
Don't even let me get
started on the snakes!
When I think of how we
had to deal with all that,
and find the scrolls, and
fight off all the other teams,
man, I get that creeps
just remembering it.
Anyway, the point is, if you
could survive that place,
you might one day
be as good as Gaara.
Or who knows, even me!
This is Naruto
Uzumaki, reporting
from the lush and
lovely paradise
that we like to call
The Forest of Death.