[whoosh]
[grunt]
-Whenever facing an opponent
with superior abilities,
make sure you have the
advantage of superior numbers.
You taught us that lesson.
[chuckle]
-You've gone to all
this trouble for me?
Is this any way to
treat an old man?
-By order of Lady
Tsunade, we are
to detain you and escort you
back to the Leaf Village.
[whoosh-clink]
-What's this?
He's from the Hidden Rain.
[japanese theme music]
-If you find a friend's mood is
suddenly changed for the worse,
cause might even be something
as simple as a subtle change
in his diet, much like
differently colored noodles.
[growl]
-I have no idea what
they're talking about.
-Well, I don't either, really.
-That's my point.
Come on.
There's gotta be a better
way than this to understand
why people behave
the way they do.
-Sakura has told
me that I should
try learning through
real life experience.
-Careful.
With Sakura, that can mean a
lot of butting horns and locking
heads.
I mean, she's into violent,
real life experiences.
Listen to her and
you're liable to, um,
end up back here
in the hospital.
-All the same, it seems
to me, butting heads
is the way you and Sora have
chosen to try and understand
each other.
[growl]
-Well, in any case, I'm not
very good at that kind of thing.
I guess I'll just
have to keep studying.
-What's up with that guy?
I don't get it.
I thought he was
finally settling
in here in the village.
What happened to him?
-(VOICEOVER) Lord Donzo.
-Asuma and Yamato?
-Yes, they've been summoned.
-Explain yourself, Donzo.
With tensions running so
high with the Hidden Rain,
why would you choose
this, of all times,
to try and make
contact with shinobi
from a neighboring land?
I want an answer.
-Wait.
Just a moment, my lady.
I've seen this person once
before, when I was in the ANBU.
He went missing while
he was on a mission.
His name is Totsji.
-So you're saying
this man was the spy
that Lord Donzo sent
to the Hidden Rain.
-You thought you'd sniff
around on your own, did you?
I have no idea what you were
looking for in Hidden Rain,
but you are going to tell
me what you found out.
Was the Hidden Rain responsible
for those earlier attacks?
[chuckle]
-You really are badly
informed if you don't even
know that much.
Princess Tsunade,
while you pursue
your policy of moderation,
your complacency
is destroying this village.
-I take it, then,
you refuse to talk.
Very well, then.
In that case--
-Don't bother.
You're just wasting
your time if you
think you can get him to talk.
-There's more than one
way to go about this.
-You summoned me, my lady.
-I'm counting on you , Ibiki.
-Leave it to me.
Give me 10 minutes and I'll
have him singing like a bird.
-Huh?
-Tsunade, where
is your patience?
A hokage is supposed to be
above this sort of thing,
going so far as to
drag Ibiki into it.
Really, such tactics.
They're unacceptable.
-There, there, now.
I'm sorry about all of this.
-Poor Danzo.
Tatsugi wasn't only
spying for you, you see.
All that time he was sending
information to us, as well.
[chuckle]
-He is no traitorous spy.
He's a loyal
citizen of the Leaf.
-According to Tatsugi's
reports, the Hidden Rain
was not involved in the
attacks on the border villages.
More significantly, it appears
that the mission assigned
to him by Donzo was
to track and monitor
the movements of those four
grave robbers, the ones who
violated the hidden tombs near
the Temple of Fire recently.
-Well, what did he find out?
-It is just as you all
feared, I'm afraid.
What those four were
really after all
along was that boy, Sora,
from the Fire Temple.
-Tsunade, you know
about the incident
the boy caused in the past at
the Fire Temple, don't you?
-Yes.
-I don't know how it
came to be, but there's
no doubt the boy possesses
a great power of some kind.
Power equal to, if not greater
than that of the Guardian
Shinobi 12, whose
tombs were ransacked.
-And you welcomed
him with open arms.
You brought this strange
and dangerous power
into our own village.
Since you are supposed to
be the village's guardian,
you must act quickly.
You must decide
what is to be done.
-Yes, I understand.
But we can't just send him
back to the Fire Temple.
Perhaps if we kept him
under lock and key.
-No, no.
The seedling must be
torn out by the roots
before it can spread and
threaten the village.
-Elimination?
-I wanted to show
you your true power.
SORA (VOICEOVER): Why?
Why must my power
make me an outcast?
Not this time.
Old man Asuma.
-Tsunade, you are the hokage.
The decision is yours.
You must decide what is
best for the Leaf Village.
-I won't--
SORA: Let go!
Let go of me, you masked monkey.
-Quiet down.
-Sora.
-We caught him hiding
in the rafters.
-I heard everything.
Elimination, huh?
Is this power I have really that
much of a threat to you people?
You're no different than those
fools at the Fire Temple.
-You carry the seeds
of disaster in you.
-Donzo!
-You're all cowards and
fools, everyone of you.
Comrades, huh?
To hell with Team Kakashi.
-Sora.
-Well, I guess that's what I get
for trusting in people again.
This is what I get for
believing in all of you.
-Quiet, Sora.
That's enough.
-Asuma, there's something
I need you to tell me, now.
Was it you?
Are you the one who
killed my father?
-The one who killed your
father is none other
than ex-guardian
shinobi Asuma Sarutobi.
-Who murdered my father?
Was it you?
-It was me.
I'm the one who finished it.
Well, and by that, I
mean I, I killed Kazuma.
-Asuma.
-Kazuma.
-Now, I understand.
[growl]
-What's happening?
-How dare you.
You had no right.
How dare you.
-Stop.
[growl]
[gasp]
ASUMA (VOICEOVER): That
right hand of his-- Sora.
What kind of power is that?
-Who gave you the right
to kill my father?
You had no right.
-Are you all right, Sora?
-Naruto, why did you--
you little idiot.
When are you going
to stop butting in?
-Don't blame me.
You said it yourself.
-I've come to back you up.
-Funny, I don't remember
calling for backup.
-Well, as long as I'm here,
I guess I'll give you a hand.
-As long as I'm here, I
guess I'll give you a hand.
Hey!
Who's the jerk who
attacked Sora, anyway?
-The Foundation.
-Sora!
Naruto.
Are you OK?
[grunt]
-Don't worry.
I'm all right.
-And as for you, you
betrayed your comrades.
You stabbed my
father in the back.
And I will have my revenge.
-Sora.
-No.
-That stupid jerk.
-Naruto!
FIRE TEMPLE MONK:
He mustn't get out.
No matter what.
All the gates have
been closed and locked.
-We have to restrain
him with the destruction
of the evil seal.
Hoo.
-Too much.
But not even he
is powerful enough
to destroy the sealed
Iron Walls beyond.
-What?
-The same dream,
just like before.
-The real problem is
there are two great kings.
The Land of Fires feudal Lord
and the hokage of the Leaf.
There will always be
distrust and confusion,
as long as there are two
kings of equal strength.
Two can never decide
as quickly as one
how to react to a crisis.
Kazuma's ultimate
goal was very simple.
To unite all the factions
of The Land of Fire,
and make them one.
But his efforts to bring the two
kings together came to nothing.
In fact, that was
the very thing that
ended up tricking
him in the end.
The people of this
village, like most people,
always stick with
their own king.
That's what Asuma did.
He preferred his own hokage.
He doesn't understand what
makes this village shine.
It's only catching the reflected
light of the true king.
It's the Land of Fire
that makes it shine.
Ultimately, The Land of Fire
was Kazuma's only cause.
And it was for
that cause that he
had entrusted you
with your powers.
-My only cause is
avenging my father.
-And that's all right.
But try and look beyond
your personal objectives,
and see the greater revenge
that Kazuma envisioned.
Join me, Sora, in
fulfilling Kazuma's dream.
Join me and I'll see you
get as many opportunities
as you like to deal with Asuma.
-The other king, the hokage.
-Sora!
Sora.
-Man, this guy.
What a pain in the neck he is.
So I guess that's as far
as the scent goes, huh?
-Boy, your recuperative powers
never cease to amaze me, Naruto.
We've had everybody
looking for him everywhere.
He might have left the village.
-No way.
I've got a strong
feeling Sora's still
here in the village somewhere.
-Maybe so.
Anyway, try and get
some rest tonight.
-Right.
Sora.
That chakra.
I sense chakra that's
full of-- full of rage.
No doubt about it.
It's Sora.
-Grandma Tsunade.
Sorry, but-- you OK?
-Yeah.
-Sora.
-What sort of chakra is this?
-No.
-Stay out this.
-Why-- why are
you attacking her?
-Just get out of my way.
-Leave, Tsunade.
-Wait.
-Sora.
Naruto.
-Wait.
Sora.
[MUSIC - NICO TOUCHES THE WALLS
- BROKEN YOUTH]
-Hey, look.
All the lights have
gone out in the village.
MALE KID: Maybe
everybody's gone out.
FEMALE KID: Nah.
It must be a power outage.
Just our luck.
MALE KID: I really don't
like the dark much.
FEMALE KID: Don't worry.
The lights will probably
be back on soon.
MALE KID: Yeah.
What if they're not?
FEMALE KID: Well, good question.
What do you think, Konohamaru?
KONOHAMARU: I've
got a bad feeling.
FEMALE KID: You do?
KONOHAMARU: Things have been
crazy in the village lately.
I just hope nothing
bad's going on.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time, Lockdown of Darkness.