Everyone! Let's join
together and fight as one!
[cheering]
Thanks, Hinata!
Time for you to recover!
You guys...
A futile display.
[growl]
It's transforming again!
No, just reverting
to its original form.
That was only
its attack form.
However, it's only
one stage short of
its final transformation.
Naruto's still recovering,
and Nine Tails is infusing
chakra. It's all up
to us right now, Bee!
I heard that! We'll
show everyone the way
and where it's at!
Listen Bee, if we let
it undergo its final
transformation, we've lost.
We have to stop
it right now!
Ten Tails isn't
holding back.
He must have gotten
irked after seeing his other
Tailed Beasts inside Naruto!
The fun is just about to
begin, but it appears that
I'm going to
need to move soon.
Whoa. It's still
growing bigger.
Yeah, is that
meant for Naruto?!
Honestly, how're we
supposed to deal with that
without Naruto's chakra?
We have to remain strong,
everyone! We can't waver
after coming this far!
Naruto is putting
his all into doing
what has to be done.
But still, it's even more
painful for me not to have
my comrades in here!
The words Naruto just
said made it clear!
Yeah, he's been going
out of his way even
to protect shinobi like us.
That's not what I mean!
He's told us he considers
all of us his comrades from
the bottom of his heart.
Comrades.
We're...
Yeah, we're all...
Comrades!
I'm going to fully
heal Naruto now!
We must each
do what we can.
If we're going to die
anyway, we might as well go
down fighting to the very
best of our abilities.
[chuckle]
Ino!
I want you to link
me with someone!
You have a plan, huh?
I knew you'd come through!
There must be something
we can do, right, dad?
I'm low on chakra.
Master Kitsuchi!
Please, hear me out!
You're
Shikaku's child, right?
Teach me the signs to an
easy Earth Style Barrier
ninjutsu that even
non-Hidden Stone
shinobi can perform!
One that anyone could
instantly master would be
too feeble! It'd
be better to-
No, it's crucial
that everyone be able to
reproduce it. If the
enemy has quality,
we've got quantity.
But these walls'll get
blown away immediately.
Then we just
keep building more.
They'll act like a shield.
We'll slow that thing's
momentum with many
weak walls, rather than
try to stop it with
one powerful wall!
Of course, I also plan to
have all of you Hidden Stone
shinobi build me
a super wall.
I see, your idea might
indeed be worth a try.
All right, these
are the hand signs!
Before that...
Master Bee!
Huh?
While everyone else is
building barriers, I want
you to hit that thing with
tons of Tailed Beast Bombs
and shift its
trajectory upwards.
Ino...
Next thing I want you
to link me with every
shinobi on the battlefield.
Can you do it?
That doesn't
matter! I'm gonna do it!
[chuckle]
What's your issue
with a Genjutsu World?
Reality is cruel.
This hole is just
going to get bigger.
Things don't always go the
way you want them. Nor does
help always arrive in time.
Just like how
it was with me!
How I couldn't
get there in time!
Right, Kakashi? Don't you
agree? How will you seal
this hole by living
in a world like this?
I may be scum as a shinobi,
but I've still learned a
thing or two.
The hole in one's
heart gets filled by
others around you.
But people won't flock to
someone who abandons the
memory of his friends
and gives up on the world
just because things don't
go the way he wants them to.
That will do nothing
to help fill the
hole in your heart.
And people don't help those
who run away and do nothing.
As long as you don't
give up, there will
always be salvation.
No matter what
you say or do...
It's over!
Earth Style Barrier!
Here it comes, Bee!
Yeah! Let's go!
Its power is
off the charts!
It's more powerful than I
thought. At this rate...
The last barrier!
[grunting]
Lord Bee!
Tedious whitewashing.
True happiness is only
achieved by abandoning
reality and purging the
memories of your comrades!
In the ninja world, those
who break the rules are
scum. That's true.
But those who abandon their
friends are worse than scum.
And those who don't cherish
their comrades' memory are
even worse scum than that!
It vanished?
I won't abandon my
memory of the old you.
Even if it's the current
you who's repudiating it!
Am I too late?
No way.
You got here
right on time, dad!
Huh?! Who's?!
Whose dad?
I'm Minato Namikaze.
Brace for an explosion.
Huh?!
[gasp]
Huh? What is that?
Whoa, what-?!
I sent Ten Tails' attack
over there into the sea.
Whoa, watch out!
What the hell's
going on now?!
What's to stop it?!
Oh, come on! That shockwave
came out of nowhere!
What's up with that?!
Look, quit complaining!
Honestly, we're
lucky. We got off easy.
Reanimation eyes!
So? Talk! Who are you?
It's okay, don't worry.
I'm an ally of yours.
It looks like I owe you
thanks for healing Naruto!
So, uh...
Are you
Naruto's girlfriend?
Huh?!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! I
guess you could say that!
You shut your trap!
Don't waste your
energy talking!
You're supposed to be
healing me, not hurting
me even more!
Oh, I'll just heal
the extra damage, too!
[chuckling]
She kinda reminds
me a bit of Kushina.
So, uh. Please, could
you go easy on my son?
[chuckle]
This is such a
sudden surprise.
Although, it
seems like you knew.
Yeah, I sensed his
chakra in Nine Tails Mode.
The others should be
arriving soon, too.
[gasp] Something's coming!
Well, Minato...
It seems you're
as fast as ever!
[gasp] L- Lord
Third Hokage?!
And also aren't they--?!
Well, Lord Fourth...
I must say you're
even better at
teleporting than I!
All right, then.
Let's do this!
No way!
I don't believe it...
Lord First, Lord
Second, Lord Third,
and even Lord Fourth!
It's really Minato!
Oh, so you're the ones
who stopped the attack
just now, Lords Hokage!
But who reanimated you?
Orochimaru's the
one who summoned us.
We need to put a stop
to this war quickly.
What?!
Orochimaru died, didn't he?
Amazing! The previous
Hokage joining us in battle!
Now that's reassuring!
[sigh] I'm totally lost.
The other reinforcements
are coming, too.
But I guess they're
lagging behind a bit.
It's about damn time!
I've been
waiting, Hashirama!
I'll deal with you later!
First I have to
stop the Ten Tails!
[chuckle]
He hasn't changed a bit.
We were never on
the same page.
After all...
...he's charging
right towards us.
Naruto, you've done
really well today.
Why don't you
take a little break?
That friend of yours
will be here soon.
He's our ally, too.
[gasp] He is?
[gasp]
This presence... It's
Minato! What's going on?!
Fellow Hokage...
Let's go!
Please, Lord Second
and Lord Third
stand in front of me.
That's exactly
like Naruto's...
I never imagined
that Minato would, too!
See?! See?!
Is my dad totally
amazing or what?!
I know that even
better than you do!
Reaper Death Seal!
Let's believe in him!
After all this
child is our son!
Seal!
[angry roar]
He's the one who split me
up before sealing me away!
Have you already
placed your markers?
I have.
It appears that you're
quick at striking, too!
They vanished!
Let's go! Ninja Art...
Four Crimson
Ray Formation!
And I think. I'm
going to add on.
Sage Art:
Gracious Deity Gates!
Ten Seals!
A red barrier?!
It is said to be more
powerful than the Four
Flames Formation!
It's a barrier that
requires four Hokage-class
shinobi working
together to create!
[angry roar]
Now it won't be able to
move about so easily.
You sure took your time
getting here, Sasuke.
[gasp] Sasuke?!
Sakura, huh?
S... Sasuke?!
Why?!
[gasps]
[angry growling]
Huh? S- Sasuke, you-?!
Hey, Ino! Stop!
He's still an enemy!
Yeah, Ino! You probably
shouldn't go near him. Just
keep your distance!
You guys are still
as annoying as ever.
Why the hell are you
here, you bastard?!
He's right.
What are you
doing here, Sasuke?
A whole lot has happened.
But I've decided to protect
the Hidden Leaf Village now.
Then, after...
I will...
...become Hokage.
What?!
Long-time-no-see Rogue
Ninja, you can't come back
suddenly and crack lame
jokes! You even get what it
means to be Hokage?
I don't know everything
that's happened to you, but
that's just an
impossibility.
I mean, do even know
what you're saying?
Do you really believe
we can forgive and
forget all you've done?
I know. I realize
you probably can't.
But then it doesn't
really matter what any
of you think of me.
The previous Kage
caused these circumstances.
So I will become Hokage
and change the Village.
Becoming Hokage isn't
about getting people to
acknowledge you.
Only those already
acknowledged will ever
become Hokage.
You'll have to
take care of Sasuke.
Leave it to me.
I'm going to be the
one who'll be Hokage!
It does please me to see
you guys so infatuated with
becoming Hokage,
but speed it up!
Start infusing chakra!
We'll take down Ten Tails
with an all-out attack!
Thanks, Sakura.
For healing me!
Now it's your turn
to get some rest.
Let's go, Sasuke!
Sakura?
You think I'm some
weak woman who can't
keep up with you two?
Is Lady Tsunade the only
Sannin to give inadequate
training to her student?
I'm almost there...
I'll be at full capacity in
a little bit. Then I can put
out my true power.
I'm a part of Team 7,
too! And a student of
a Legendary Sannin!
[chuckle]
All right!
Team 7 is finally back
in action once again!
Sakura! Sasuke!
Let's go!
Right!
Yeah!
That sight sure brings back
memories! Right, Shikamaru?
Well, okay. I guess that if
he's willing to help us take
down the enemy, I
won't turn him away.
But I don't accept him...
It's been a while since
our whole class was together
like this. Kinda feels
like the Chunin Exams!
I'm the one who's
gonna be Hokage!
Hey, are you
even listening?!
Kiba, no one's
paying attention.
Frankly, it's
pitiful. Quit it.
The reason is because the
impact of Sasuke showing up
suddenly and declaring his
intent to become Hokage is
much too great.
Um, Kiba? Well, I
heard you loud and clear!
All of us should
aspire to be Hokage!
All right, come
on, you guys!
Let's show 'em what
we're made of, y'know!
Back during the Chunin
Exams, I thought I was a
full-fledged kunoichi.
But I ended up hiding
behind Sasuke and Naruto.
I hated the way I was.
I swore that next time,
I would make them
stare at my back!
And now finally, I...
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Team 7,
Assemble!"
Cha!