[stretching yawning]
Huh!?
Wha?!
Agh!
What the hell is this?!
Huh?
[Naruto]
[mischievous chuckle]
Naruto Uzumaki, that's me!
One day, I'll be Hokage!
Hey!
-Get back here!
-Get him!
-Don't let him get away!
Damn! It's that kid again!
Thanks to him,
we have another big
mess to clean up!
Yeah, and he doesn't even
have any parents that we
can go and complain to about it!
What'll we do?
Who's going to
pay to get all of
this cleaned up?
Ha ha ha ha!
Hee hee hee hee!
Who can we complain
to, you know?
It was him again,
wasn't it?
Yeah, the boy we're not
supposed to talk about.
That kid's
a nuisance.
He's so
unpleasant.
More like
useless.
Mmhh...
[door opens]
See you later!
Huh?
Wait! Your lunch!
Oops! Thanks!
What did you put in
there for me, anyway?
I said I
wanted an
omelet!
Well, good, 'cause
that's what I
made you both!
Yeah!
You be careful!
-Okay!
[door opens]
May I come in?
Here's this
month's allowance.
Make sure you
spend it wisely.
Hold on.
Hmm?
Tell me about them.
Tell me all about
my mom and dad.
Hmm.
I'm certain that I
told you before.
Although it was
quite some time ago.
I don't mean that!
You're talking about
when the Nine Tailed Fox
ran amok, aren't you?
I already know plenty about
how it attacked the Village
and killed tons of people,
including my parents.
But that stuff isn't what I'm
asking you to tell me about now!
What I want to know is...
Just who were my
parents, really?
What kind of
people were they?
There's no use in
asking such questions.
It won't bring
back the dead.
Now... for the next lesson.
Instead of just
introducing yourselves,
I want each of you
to demonstrate your
skill with ninjutsu!
[kids]
Awww!
Okay, don't worry, we're
just gonna start with
a basic Clone Jutsu.
And the first up:
Uh, is
Sasuke Uchiha.
[giggles]
You ready?
Whoa, he's from
the Uchiha clan?!
Yeah! He's an elite
among elites.
Heheheehe!
Sasuke~!
Hmph.
Why do you always
have to act so smug?!
It's annoying!
If you think that you're
so hot, then prove it!
[Sasuke]
I just did.
Hmm??
When did--?!
Wow.
Impressive.
"Ooh, Sasuke's so great!"
Bah! With this jutsu,
if you attack the real one!
Huh??
Yauugh...
Ugh. He's hopeless.
Ahh! Hnggh!
[kids laughing]
Damn!
Today I'll get him!
Dagh!
[girls cheering]
Hmph.
Damn it!
Damn it! Damn it!
Damn it damn it
damn it!
Hmph.
[girls shrieking]
Oh man! Come on!
Aaaggh!!
Choji, too?!
Hmf.
Hm.
Hmph.
Damn it! Today is gonna be
the day I beat him, for sure.
Definitely! Definitely!
Definitely!
I will beat him!
[Iruka]
Next up, Naruto Uzumaki,
and Sasuke Uchiha!
You've got
this, Sasuke!
You're totally
going to win,
I'm sure of it!
Damn it! Why does he
get all the attention?
Let's go!
I'm gonna win!
[Iruka]
Begin!
Whoa! He's so cool!
Oh, Sasuke,
you rock!
Ahh!
Sasuke.
That look in his eyes.
It's the same look that
everyone gives me.
No.
No, it's stronger
than that.
Wait...
...it's not for me.
Man, he pisses
me off!
Hm.
- Hey!
- Not him again!
- Get back here!
- You gotta be kidding!
Hee hee hee hee hee!
Damn it!
Where'd that little brat
run off to this time?!
There!
- Hey over there!
- We found 'im!
- Let's go!
Hee hee hee!
Serves you right!
Huh?
[panting]
I have acted like the
older brother you
desired for one reason:
Because I wanted to discover
how powerful you were.
[gasp]
Huh?
Hey, did you know that
everyone in the Uchiha
clan was killed?
Yeah, I heard my
father talking about
it a while ago.
Sasuke's the only
one who survived.
[yawn]
Today's the day!
I finally get to
wear this!
Hee hee hee!
Looks perfect!
All right!
Starting today,
I'm a genin!
Alright, why don't you
introduce yourselves.
One at a time.
Okay, I'll go first!
My name's Naruto Uzumaki!
I like instant
ramen in a cup!
I really like the ramen
that Iruka Sensei got
for me at Ichiraku.
But the thing I hate is waiting
until the ramen is done.
And my future
dream is,
to be Hokage!
Then the whole village will
stop disrespecting me and start
treating me like I'm somebody!
Somebody important!
Hobbies?
Huh?
Hmm.
Playing pranks.
Last one.
My name's
Sasuke Uchiha.
I hate a
lot of things.
And I don't
particularly
like anything.
My dream... isn't really a
dream at all, because I'm
going to make it a reality.
I'm going to restore my clan,
and destroy a
certain someone.
[Kakashi]
Good! you're each unique and
you have your own ideas.
We'll have our first
mission tomorrow!
Hup! What kind of mission
are we going to have?
It's a task that the
four of us are going
to do together.
What? What?
A survival exercise.
I'll be your opponent,
but it's not just a drill.
And the chance that
you'll fail is at
least 66 percent.
Hey, wait up, Sasuke!
Wanna walk home together?
No, thanks.
I finally made genin,
and there's no way that
I'm going to get dropped now.
I'm going to train by myself.
Yeah...
Guess that makes sense...
That jerk!
Always acting so cool!
All right!
If Sasuke's going to train
by himself, then so will I!
I've had enough!
I'm not going to
lose to him anymore!
Now grade this,
Professor Kakashi!
Yahhh!
I'm gonna become a genin,
no matter what!
Damn it!
I had to get stuck in a
three-man cell with Sakura and
that loser, of all people!
I will pass, all on my own!
I just have to stay
focused on my goal.
[Kakashi]
Here we go.
It's set for noon.
Hmm?
Your assignment is very simple.
You just have to take
these bells from me.
That's all there is to it.
If you can't get
'em by noon, you
go without lunch.
At least one of you will end up
tied to a post and ultimately
disqualified for failing to
complete the mission.
That one goes back
to the Academy.
Rrrgh!
Get ready.
Annnd...
start!
You n' me,
right now,
fair and square!!!
Let's go!
Fool.
I'm gonna crush youuu!
Aaaaaggh!!
Rrrgh! I'm not going to
let it end like this!
I'll attack
from the water!
Uuagh!
Whooa!
Yah! Uagh! Hey!
Fire Style:
Fireball Jutsu!!
Ha ha ha ha
ha ha ha!
Sensei said that no
bell means no lunch.
But if I eat it right now,
then there's nothing he can do!
It's chow time!!
Hi there.
I was just...
joking sensei.
Nice try.
[alarm]
[stomach growl]
It's too late now,
but if all three of
you had come at me,
you might have been
able to take them.
Mmmmhh.
All right. I'm going to
give you one more chance.
But I'm going to make
it much harder on you.
You'll have three
hours to get a bell.
Eat lunch now to
build up strength.
But, Naruto
doesn't get any.
It's your punishment for
breaking the rules and
trying to eat by yourself.
And if anyone tries to
feed him, that person
will immediately fail.
I make the rules, and you
follow them. Got it!?
[stomach growl]
This is no big deal.
I can go without
eating for days.
For weeks!
Unnhhhh...
I have to get one of those
bells from Kakashi Sensei.
But as much as I hate to admit
it, I can't do it alone.
What's the best move?
Combine the strength
of three into one.
Here.
What! No, Sasuke,
you can't do that!
You heard what the
Sensei said.
Kakashi's gone.
We need to get those
bells as a team.
If Naruto's hungry,
he'll be weak and
ineffective.
That would hurt the entire team
and jeopardize the mission.
[gulp]
Sakura!
[chuckle]
Thanks.
Yahhh!!!
You pass.
[chuckle]
Huh!?
Huhhh!?
In the ninja world,
those who break the
rules are scum.
But, those who abandon their
friends are worse than scum.
The exercise is over.
Everyone passes!
Okay, it's picture time!
Look sharp, everyone!
Yeah, but I still
don't understand why I
have to be in the same
picture as this guy!
Hmph. I should
be asking that,
you loser.
Say that again!
[Kakashi]
Come on, you guys, quiet down.
This is a tradition!
[Kakashi]
Squad seven starts its first
mission tomorrow!!
What!?
Do it!
Ahh!
[gasp]
Kakashi Sensei!
Ah!
Ahhh!
Now, it's
your turn.
Whoa. Cool.
Ahhh!
[Naruto]
Kakashi-sensei used the
Substitution Jutsu.
I was useless!
And Sasuke was so cool!
On our first mission!
Didn't he feel scared at all?
He looks so calm.
Not a scratch on him.
And I was so lame;
he had to come and save me!
Why can't I keep up with them?
Hey.
Yeah!?
You're not hurt are ya?
scaredy-cat?
Rrrgh!
Why am I so different!?
Why am I always... Aaagh!
Damn it!
Ngh!
Huh??
[gasp]
I'll never back down again and
let someone else rescue me.
I will never run away.
Upon this wound,
I make this pledge!
[Sasuke]
Listen, if you really don't
want to owe me anything,
Then just become
stronger than me.
...Loser.
[Naruto]
Agh! I'm gonna catch
up to him in no time.
And then I'm gonna become
even stronger than he is!
Just you watch!
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
Rivals. The story of how Sasuke
and I got started continues.
[Sasuke]
When did he get this good?