"Neji's Judgment"
I'll give this to you...
...if you'll only help me!
[gasping]
Don't worry about that
now! Listen to me. Can
you show us the way?
[gasping]
Yes!
Right over there.
Byakugan!
Found them!
What is the plan, Neji?
We can't ignore them.
You do realize this could
mean we won't pass the
Chunin Exams.
I'm really sorry, you
guys...
No, it isn't your fault. I
was the one who decided to
get involved.
Right...
But you're correct,
Tenten. This decision could
very well mean that we're
not going to pass the Chunin
Exams.
But in a situation like
this, he wouldn't...
Naruto wouldn't hesitate
for a moment to act.
That's for sure!
You are right! Naruto would
give us all a serious
scolding if we ignored
anyone in need, especially
if it is just to pass the
Second Exam.
Naruto and Gaara both
challenged their destinies
and were able to overcome
many hardships.
They wouldn't ignore this
and say it's someone
else's problem.
[struggling]
Damn it, Fuu. I told you
to stay away.
But how could I ever do
something like that?! If
that friend of yours were
here, I bet that he'd do
everything in his power to
try to save you!
[gasping]
My friend would--
Yes, but that's only
because he's a fool!
♪♪
[struggling]
[yelling]
♪♪
[roaring]
[struggling]
[gasping and grunting]
[grunting]
Ninja Art: Cocoon.
[gasping]
What is that?!
What's this?!
It's a power that I have.
But unfortunately it's not
enough to break
this Chakra Chain.
But at the very least... it
should be enough to buy
us some time.
♪♪
Huh?!
This is--
The flow through the chakra
chain is becoming
sluggish.
That cocoon actually has the
power to suppress the
absorption of chakra?!
How did you...?
I just wove a cocoon
together for us.
It's no big deal! It's
basically just like a giant
tangle of super-fine
Chakra threads.
I thought it'd slow that
chain down from draining our
chakra.
But didn't stop it.
Both the chakra flow and
discomfort have been
reduced, but eventually...
...our Tailed Beasts will be
extracted, and then...
...we'll die.
[chuckling]
Negative thoughts aren't
helpful, you know! Besides,
I'm sure that someone's
gonna come along to save us!
How can you stay so positive
about this situation?
You know, there was someone
else who praised me for
being positive too!
Nobody is coming to save us.
Don't say something like
that!
Hey! Is anybody out there?!
Can you hear me?!
Your voice can't travel
through this cocoon.
Uh--
Dang it, I forgot...
All right, then! I'll just
have to pull this out with
brute strength.
[grunting]
[straining]
So, listen... we might have
to wait to be rescued, after
all...
However long we wait, no one
from the Sand will help us.
There you go again! More
negative thoughts!
Would you still say such
things if you knew our enemy
is from the Sand?
What?! Are you serious?!
How useless. All you did was
throw away any avenue of
escape.
Just how long do you think
you'll last in there?
♪♪
In the past, the only way
that I could relate to
others was with hatred and a
desire to kill them.
[struggling]
Now that I have become the
Kazekage, some believe that
I will rule through fear...
And so, they're trying to
eliminate me.
I suppose it can't be
helped...
[struggling]
I'm the one who brought it
on myself because of my past
actions.
If I have any regrets, the
biggest...
...is that I wish I'd been
better able to show people just
how much I'm trying to change.
That friend of yours you
talked about showed you,
right?
That you can share and
understand the pain,
suffering, and happiness of
other people!
Uh--
You're right. Yes, he did...
But still, it's difficult
for a Jinchuriki to find
acceptance.
That doesn't have to be
true! I'm sure it'll all
work out!
If you're a Jinchuriki you
can still make a hundred
friends. I know it!
'Cause my Village Chief told
me so!
They really are a lot
alike...
Judging by the panic within
the Hidden Sand... I'd say
we can assume that they no
longer have Gaara under
their protection.
Yes. It's exactly what we
feared might happen...
He's set himself up as bait
in order to lure out the
faction that's planning a
coup d'etat.
In the worst-case scenario,
there's a chance that he
could've already been
assassinated.
The Leaf has very close ties
to Gaara...
If something happens, it
would greatly affect our
alliance with the Sand.
We can't allow anything to
happen to him.
I know, but as long as we
don't know who's behind
the coup d'etat, we
can't request any
assistance from the Sand.
We'll just have to
something ourselves, then.
Well, that said, we don't
know where he went, and
don't have any clues about
his enemies.
What is that?
Hmm?
Hm. They're Sand genin.
♪♪
You hear that
lute playing?
[gasping]
What is that thing?!
It appears to be a giant
cocoon!
And who is that man with
the lute up on the ridge
there?
You are entrants from the
Hidden Waterfall!
That's right. We're
looking for Fuu. She
wandered off.
She did?!
What?! Chakra is being
extracted from Gaara and
Fuu.
What is it, Neji?!
Just what do you see in that
cocoon?!
Uh--
I can see two Jinchuriki
inside.
One of them has to be Lord
Gaara. But who's the other
one?
From the Hidden Waterfall.
I believe it's your teammate.
To be sure, at this rate,
both of them will perish.
[gasping]
It's the Sealing Jutsu of
that lute player.
He's extracting their
Tailed Beast Chakra.
Ultimately, he'll extract
the Beasts themselves.
But if the Tailed Beast is
extracted, then Lord Gaara
will die!
Please! You have to
help him!
So? What do you intend to do
about this?
You abandoning your
teammate?
Let us call a truce. And we
can fight together!
If we act quickly, we can
still save them!
[exhaling]
All right...
Please, help us with saving
Fuu.
Sure!
I see...
From what I can tell, that
priest is vulnerable to a
strike from his back.
So, this is my plan. First,
we'll divide into two
groups, an attack team and a
rescue team.
The attack team will sneak
in close and approach him
from behind, and then, while
he's distracted by them...
...the rescue team will move
in and free both our
friends.
Lee and Matsuri, accompanied
by you two, will attack.
Understood.
All right! We will go
pulverize him!
Can I be on the
rescue team?
No. I'm sorry but I need
Tenten for that. The two of
us will go.
You got it!
Scatter!
Shuriken Shadow Clone
Jutsu!
Water Style: Water Shuriken!
Deadly Shell Meteorite!
Leaf Hurricane!
Dharma Barrier: Celestial
Pillars!
[gasping]
What is that?!
Some defensive jutsu?!
There is something else
going on here, too. We have
to be careful!
Hm?
[gasping]
Tenten, I need a Chakra
Sword.
I'm on it!
Ha!
I just need to find a
weak spot in the cocoon.
Right there!
[grunting]
Huh?!
This means... we
can't get close to him.
That barrier is impregnable!
At this rate, we'll be
useless! No help to Lord
Kazekage!
No, this is fine.
Huh?
Just drawing the enemy's
attention away will make
Neji's job easier, and
that is what we
came here to do!
Are you all right,
Neji?
Are you two doing okay?
You see?! Someone came to
help, after all!
I gave very strict orders
not to tell anyone.
They were just worried about
you. Please, don't be too
angry with your
subordinates for that.
It's just as I suspected.
Those chains have penetrated
your Chakra Points. And
they're disrupting your
Chakra Networks.
They're controlling the
flow of chakra through your
Chakra Points... and
siphoning off your Tailed
Beast Chakra.
That's right. And as the
Tailed Beast Chakra weakens,
he'll be able to extract the
Beasts themselves.
Can you do something to
help?
Whether it's Tailed Beast or
not, chakra is chakra.
If we block the Chakra Point
being used to siphon the
Tailed Beast Chakra...
...then we just might be
able to staunch its flow.
Is that possible?
It is. It's sure to be
tricky, but it's still
worth a try.
Do it.
There it is! Gentle Fist...
...Chakra Point Needle!
[gasping]
[grunting]
Uh?!
What happened?
I think that...
...the Tailed Beast Chakra
is so powerful that it
repelled me.
I had no idea that it would
be as unbelievably strong as
that!
Like that time before. The
force of the Nine Tails
Chakra inside Naruto was
almost unimaginable.
It appears that the Tailed
Beast Chakra inside Gaara
and Fuu... is just as
powerful as Naruto's.
You've just gotta keep
trying! Please, we're
counting on you!
I know, Fuu.
I'll try again!
Huuuuuuh!
All right! It's stopped!
You're right!
Get ready, Fuu.
You're next!
Okay!
[grunting]
What?! The flow of chakra
has stopped?!
But why?! Why isn't the
Tailed Beast Chakra
flowing?!
That guy with the lute is
acting weird.
I know... that means
something must have
happened!
Did that Byakugan user
actually stop him?
Well... the enemy definitely
looks flustered...
What's happening now?!
They look like they're
moving on their own!
Creepy!
Careful, everyone!
Unless I do something, the
chain will continue searching
for Tailed Beast Chakra!
It'll find the Tailed Beast
Chakra that's already been
stored in me and start
siphoning off that chakra...
...until it destroys me.
[grunting]
The barrier has been broken!
[gasping]
[yelling]
May I ask you a favor, Neji?
Please spare him.
Of course. Understood.
[struggling]
Neji...
Ah, I see... it's the same
idea as before. The Chakra
Points are closed.
There are more Chakra Points
here, though...
Everyone, please stand
back.
We can save him.
Get him to a Medical Team.
Right! I understand!
I thank you, Neji. Never
thought you'd rescue me.
Hm.
So are both of you all right
now?
Yeah! We're totally okay!
Lord Gaara!
Oh, thank goodness you're
safe!
Matsuri and the others did a
great job!
Yes.
There they are...
And in the end, it appears
they didn't need to have any
help from us after all.
Yep! I guess we got here a
little too late.
I'm Fuu of the Hidden
Waterfall!
And my goal for right now is
to make one hundred friends!
So please, you just gotta be
my friend! You can't say no,
okay?!
Okay, okay, yes!
I understand, just let go of
me!
[laughing]
Neji! This is great news!
(chuckling)
Woohoo! Woohoo! Finally,
I'm on my way to making a
hundred friends!
There was a time when I felt
that the wounds I'd inflicted
on my people would never heal.
I thought I should just
disappear from the Sand
Village.
But I found that despite my
past, there were some who,
without prejudice, accepted
my feelings and believed in
me.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Hopes Entrusted
to the Future"
The promising power of
the young. The future
of the Sand.