[unearthly roar]
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
How about it, Kakashi? Can
your borrowed Sharingan
extinguish power like this?!
Now I'll show you the
difference between the
real thing and a fake!
Nngh...
Augh!
Huh.
Yagh!
Damn it!
No! My sight!
Sakura! Why are you here?!
Don't!
I won't let Kakashi Sensei
bear this burden!
I'm not the same as you.
I'm traveling a path the
rest of you can't follow.
I know that the four of
us have worked together,
And for a while, I
thought I could take
that road instead.
But in the end,
I've decided on revenge.
That's always been my
reason for living.
Sakura, I will never be
like you and Naruto.
I'll do anything
for you, Sasuke!
So please...
I'm begging you,
don't walk away!!
I'll even help get your revenge!
I'll do whatever it takes to
make it happen, I swear!
So stay here...
with me...
And if you can't,
Then take me with you, Sasuke!
[sobs]
You haven't changed.
You're still annoying.
[gasp]
Don't leave me!
If you go,
I'll scream and--
[gasp]
Sakura...
Thanks for
everything.
Sakura!
A-Aah!
Sasuke! Don't!
Two Fates
You've got even better
timing than I do, Naruto.
I never imagined you'd
come here, but it's a
good thing you did.
You're a lifesaver!
Yeah. Thank you, Naruto.
[Sakura]
Sasuke... really tried
to kill me just then.
[Sakura]
If Naruto hadn't come,
I'd be dead now.
[Sakura]
By Sasuke's hand.
Sasuke, c'mon.
Sakura's a comrade from
Team 7, remember?!
You mean former comrade.
I'm off your team.
Now do you understand,
Naruto? Sakura?
His intent to kill
is undeniable.
Sasuke is no longer the
person we once knew.
Listen, Sasuke.
What do you want?
I know the truth about
Itachi. That guy Tobi
told me everything.
Huh?
The truth about Itachi?
Then again, maybe he was
lying. I guess I can't
really know for sure.
But it doesn't matter.
What you've been doing,
I get it, Sasuke.
Huh?
Naruto.
Just like I told you before,
You never had a family or
siblings in the first place.
You couldn't possibly "get it",
So all you outsiders
can just shut up!!
Do you know what Naruto
has gone through for you?
No matter what we hear
you've done, he still
considers you a comrade.
When everyone wanted to turn on
you, Naruto alone stood up for
you and wanted to rescue you.
Even now...
Rescue me?
From what?
Oh. Well, from--
From revenge, Sasuke.
Huh?
I swear I'll save you from
revenge and from all of the
chaos that it causes.
Heh!
But I don't want you to do that.
The stage has already been
set for my vengeance!
Huh?
Not long ago...
I finally got my revenge
on the one behind
Itachi's betrayal.
How many Uchiha did you
have to kill to get that
right arm of yours?!
It was all thanks to Itachi.
You made him do it!
Agh!
It's a Reverse Tetragram
Sealing Jutsu!
Sasuke! Get away from Danzo!
I took down a high-ranking
Hidden Leaf elder right here.
The one called Danzo.
[gasp]
What?! Sasuke killed Danzo?!
All by himself?
I 've never felt
like this before.
I can feel the tainted Uchiha
name becoming cleansed.
I feel the Uchiha at last
being freed from this
rotting Shinobi world.
You couldn't even begin
to understand it.
And besides, isn't what I'm
doing exactly what you Leaf
Shinobi have wanted all along?
You've always snubbed and
put down the Uchiha clan.
So I'll simply help
erase the Uchiha
from your memories,
By killing all of you.
And then destroying...
The Hidden Leaf Village!
Severing all bonds with
the Hidden Leaf will be
the ultimate purification!
And that shall lead to the
Uchiha's true restoration!
My god, Sasuke.
Hatred. The cycle of
hatred begetting hatred.
[Kakashi]
That's what created
the Sasuke before us.
They may not realize it,
but Naruto and Sakura are
seeing with their own eyes
that Sasuke is a victim
of the times we live in.
Which is especially why,
This is my responsibility.
Naruto, Sakura.
Go on, get out
of here.
Kakashi Sensei! No!
If you stay, you'll see things
you'll wish you hadn't.
Now go!
Sensei, I--
Sakura, the poison-laced
kunai Shizune taught you how
to use won't kill Sasuke.
He still has Orochimaru's
immunity to poison.
What's more, you also
know how you feel.
No, Sasuke!
I know I just healed you,
but you shouldn't...
Ngh!
You can't withstand
another battle yet!
Please, Sasuke...
Don't move, Karin. Hold still.
He hit a vital point...
right through the hostage?!
[chuckle] Now that's my boy.
One down...
Soon the rest, big brother.
Actually, what am I saying?
Why should I still care
about Sasuke?
Kakashi Sensei,
This "something"
you don't want
us to see...
Are you going
to kill Sasuke?
Go! Both of you!
Now's my chance!
And I'm not going
to hold back!
Wait, Naruto!
Naruto!
[Naruto]
You know, Sasuke...
...there's a chance...
...our roles could
have been reversed.
[Itachi]
By all means, flee.
Cling to your
wretched life.
And one day, when you
possess the same eyes.
Come back and face me!
Rasengan!
Chidori!
Sasuke, you remember,
don't you?
Back in the day,
The entire Village
used to hate me.
Because of the Nine-Tails
that's inside of me.
And I hated
them right
back.
I thought about getting
revenge on everyone, too.
And keep wiping until
every speck of that
graffiti is gone!
Look, it's that...
that kid.
Why do they even let
that boy stay in the
Village, anyway?
Lord Hokage should have
more consideration for us!
Shut up!
Haaa!
Hmm?
Hey, you little brat!
Get outta here!
Hmf!
Hey, what's the
big idea, buddy?!
Here, is this
what you want?!
Ah!
Then just take it and get lost!
And don't come back!
There it is again!
I don't understand it.
Everybody, even you,
my own teacher.
Why does everybody look at me
like that all of the time?!
I'm not just a nuisance or some
kind of germ; I'm a person, too!
I am!
I'm Naruto Uzumaki!
Don't forget it!
One bad move, and I could
have been like you, and
devised some terrible plan.
I used to think I didn't have
any bonds with anyone, either.
Till I met you and
Iruka Sensei as well.
[kids giggling and playing]
Daichi! Dinnertime!
Let's go home,
everyone.
Mom!
What do you think
you're doing?
I told you not to
play with that boy.
Come on, let's go!
Hmf!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Oh, I'll tell you
who's really lying.
They've been lying
to you your whole
life, Naruto.
Since the decree
12 years ago.
What decree is that?
Everyone knows it!
Iruka's trying to hide
it from you even now.
He'd do anything to
shut me up!
What is this decree?
Why does everyone
else know about it?
The decree is:
no one can tell you the
Nine-Tailed Fox is inside you!
[gasp]
The Fox Spirit that
killed Iruka's parents
and destroyed our village
has taken over YOUR body!
You are the
Nine-Tailed Fox!
They've all been sneaking
around, hiding things from
you your whole life.
Didn't you think it was
strange how they
treated you? Like dirt!
Like they hated you
just for being alive?
That's why you'll never be
accepted in this village!
Die, Naruto!
Naruto! Get down!
However...
Nngh! Agh!
Why?
[sniffle] I know how
you feel, Naruto.
You feel lonely, and it hurts
inside. And I could have been
there for you more.
[sniff] I let you down.
I'm sorry. No one should have
to suffer that much. No one
should be alone like that.
I almost gave in
to my despair.
But you and Iruka Sensei,
you saved me!
Back then, I always knew
that you were alone, too.
I felt better knowing
there was someone like
you- like me- out there.
We were just brats,
but dealing with stuff
no other kid had to.
Me, the Nine-Tails.
You, the fate of the Uchiha.
We had such similar burdens.
Pretty ironic, huh?
To be honest, nearly every
time I saw you, all I really
wanted to do was come up to
you and start talking.
I'd get sort of giddy.
Because I felt like
maybe you of all people
could understand me.
But I never did.
'Cause I was jealous.
You were so good
at everything!
So I decided that instead,
I'd make you my rival!
And, Sasuke,
From that day on,
...you've been my goal.
[Naruto]
Hey. Sasuke, do you remember
what you said to me long ago
at the Final Valley?
The thing about
high-level shinobi?
We learned things right now from
trading blows with each other.
So, Sasuke. Can you tell me
what I'm thinking right now?
Can you read my mind?
[Kakashi]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
High-Level Shinobi.
[Sasuke]
Why are you so fixated on me?!