[music playing]
[groaning]
-How's it going?
Are you able to control the
Nine-Tails' chakra easily,
Tenzo?
-Everything seems to be
under control so far.
But Kakashi, please
don't call me Tenzo.
I'm Yamato right now.
Remember?
-Oh right, right.
-Almost.
Hey, there's a tear in mine.
It's finally working.
-Ah, no fair.
I can't get mine to
do anything at all.
-Ha.
Ha.
Well, I guess that just
means I'm better than you.
-What do you mean
better than me?
You are me.
NARUTO CLONE: Yes!
Hehe.
-Ah man, how'd that one
of me get to be so good?
I think I need a change of plan.
Kakashi Sensei, I was wondering,
can I ask you a question?
-What is it?
-Is there anyone
else in the Leaf
Village who's got a wind
chakra nature like mine?
-You want their advice.
Is that it?
-Mhm.
-Hm.
Well, there is one
person I can think of.
Knowing him, he's probably
playing shogi right now.
[theme music]
-Checkmate.
-[groan] Lost again.
-Looks like you're
going to be treating us
to the dinner and party after
our next assignment, Sensei.
-Yeah, I know.
NARUTO: Hey!
-(BOTH) Huh?
-Asuma Sensei.
SHIKAMARU: Oh, it's you, Naruto.
ASUMA: What's up?
-There's something I really
need to ask you about
if you've got a minute.
-Hm.
-Tricks for mastering wind
change in chakra nature, huh?
-Come on.
Don't tell me
you're really doing
change in chakra
nature training.
-Yeah.
-You sure you're up for it?
You gotta be pretty darn
sharp to master that stuff.
-I know.
That's why I came to get
some tips from Asuma Sensei,
because you've got the
same wind chakra as I do.
Right, Sensei?
-Huh.
I never would have pegged
you for a wind nature.
What do you know about that?
-Please, Sensei.
I need you to teach me how
to master it right away.
-Well, let's see now.
I might be inclined to do
it if you agree to pick up
the tab for Team Asuma's next
post-mission barbecue dinner.
-Hey, that's not cool.
-Well?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I can
probably just cover it,
but it'll clean me out.
I'll be totally broke.
Well, all right.
If it will get you to help me.
-OK.
It's a deal then.
See these.
They're my chakra blades.
They're forged from a special
type of metal that can actually
absorb the bearer's
chakra nature.
-Whoa.
Sweet.
-Here take one.
OK.
Now try sending your
chakra into the blade.
-All right.
I did it.
But my chakra comes
out looking a lot
different than yours, Sensei.
-Now, listen up.
To activate it, imagine
your chakra splitting in two
and grinding against each other.
-Grinding them?
-Just as if you were
finely sharpening
the blade between the two
halves of your chakra.
-Sharpening the blade
between the two halves, huh?
-Exactly.
Finely and sharply.
That's the trick.
-OK, but you know, there's
something I don't get.
-What?
-What's the point of using
this wind change of nature
when the ninja tools we have
are already sharp to begin with?
I mean going to all
the trouble and effort
of pouring your chakra
into these special blades.
What's wrong with
the ones we've got?
Seems to me it'd be better
and a whole lot easier
just to use them.
-You think so?
Maybe if I let you
see for yourself.
All right.
Let's you and me both try
hitting that tree over there
with our chakra blades
at the same time.
-Why do that?
-Just do it.
You'll see.
Ready.
Go.
-Whoa.
Amazing.
Yours not only went
right through the tree,
it penetrated that
boulder right behind it.
-I held back a little
just to be safe.
I could've made it go
through the boulder too.
When two shinobi
of equal abilities
face each other with
blades, the sharper blade
will often decide the outcome.
The wind change in
nature is best suited
to close and medium
range combat.
Got it?
You know, there aren't too
many wind types like us around.
-There aren't.
Really?
-Drop by anytime if there's
anything more you want to know.
As long as you're willing to
pay for dinner, of course.
-You got it.
Thanks a lot, Sensei.
-So that was a Shadow
Clone the whole time?
-Poor Naruto.
He'll be sorry when he remembers
that Choji's on our team.
-You're cruel, Sensei.
He doesn't have much time.
You really think he can
master a new ninjutsu
before the Akatsuki show up?
-Well, we'll see.
Won't we?
-Don't you think
it would be better
to just hide Naruto
safely somewhere, now
before the Akatsuki
try to make contact.
-That's a decision for
the Fifth Hokage to make.
-So that's how you do it.
I get it.
-Right.
Here we go.
-Let's do it.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
Looks like he
got some useful tips from Asuma.
And he's already
learned how to profit
from the individual experiences
of his Shadow Clones.
Hm.
-Uh.
Naruto.
It says here when a friend
is engaged in strenuous work
or play, the thoughtful thing to
do is to bring him refreshment.
Lack of refreshments is the
least of his worries right now.
[grunting]
-Come on.
-My lady, we've
received disturbing news
that a village near the
border of the Land of Fire
has come under attack.
-Was it the Akatsuki?
-Always a possibility,
but evidence
suggests the attack came from
the Village Hidden in the Rain.
-What?
Why?
What could their motive be?
Don't they realize
this could lead to all
out war between the
neighboring lands?
-Perhaps.
Perhaps, they're trying to
take advantage of the fact
that the Akatsuki
are after Naruto.
-They couldn't really be so
shortsighted, could they?
Whatever the case
may be, we have
to get to the bottom of it.
Summon Asuma.
-My lady.
But uh, that will mean
fewer jonin in the village.
And what if the Akatsuki
come for Naruto.
We'd have a hard
time protecting him.
-Hm.
-All right.
Lock your clones'
cumulative experiences
into your memory bank.
-Huh.
-Now break the jutsu and
reflect on the exercise.
-(CROWD) Yes, sir.
-Right.
Here we go.
-I'm close.
I've almost got it down.
-Trouble is, along with all
that cumulative experience,
there comes cumulative
fatigue as well.
-I know.
I knew from the start
it wouldn't be easy,
but I'm so close.
I'm almost there.
-Why don't we take
a break, Naruto?
-This is not the time
to be taking it easy.
I'm OK, Kakashi Sensei.
Really.
Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu.
-Huh.
Hey, hold on.
Wait a second.
[groaning]
-Wow.
Incredible.
Your work ethic is
impressive, Naruto.
-Well, I guess he can handle it.
After all, his stamina
is off the charts.
-Here you go.
-Perfect.
Thanks.
-Who are they for?
-Oh, no one in particular.
Well, uh, see you later.
-Say hi to Kurenai
Sensei for me.
-Oh.
How, how did she know?
[giggling]
-Oh look.
There he is.
-Sorry to interrupt you on
your way to see Kurenai Sensei.
-How do you guys
know where I'm--
-Come on.
Don't try to hide it.
Everyone--
-Shikamaru.
-Oh yeah, right.
We just received the word.
The Fifth Hokage wants the whole
Team Asuma, Choji, Ino, you
and me to assemble
on the double.
-She does?
-Really?
She wants to see all of
us from the old Squad 10.
-That's right.
-Let's go then.
-The four of you, Asuma
Sarutobi, Shikamaru Nara,
Ino Yamanaka, and
Choji Akimichi are
to investigate what's behind
this attack on the border
village.
-(ALL TOGETHER) Right.
-We know the Akatsuki
are on the move again,
so handle this with great care.
-In the meantime,
what about Naruto?
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): A
nice safe D-rank mission
is just the thing.
Grave-robbers, huh?
-(ALL TOGETHER) Yeah!
-All right.
I nailed it.
Whoa.
I really am awesome, aren't I?
At this rate, I'll have this
new jutsu down in no time.
-If it's coming quickly, it's
because of this new training
method, which-- let us
not forget-- was my idea.
-Oh, and by the way,
I'd like to think
that I helped out a
little bit, Kakashi.
-OK.
Whatever.
Can we just get on to
the next exercise now?
-Of course, none
of it could have
been done if you
weren't you, Naruto.
-Naruto.
-Yamato, we'll take a short
break until he recovers.
-Understood.
-Is Naruto all right?
-A little rest, and
he should be fine.
This kid is really
something else.
-Sensei.
-Hm.
What is it, Sakura?
-Lady Tsunade needs you.
-Huh.
Asuma Sensei.
-All right.
Looks like everyone's here.
-Hey look.
What do you think?
-Hm.
About what?
-Come on.
Don't you notice
anything, Sensei?
-Huh?
-Come on, Sensei.
It's the first time you've
seen us all gathered together,
wearing these
earrings you gave us.
ASUMA: Congratulations,
Choji, Ino.
Well done.
Since Shikamaru
passed last time,
that means all the
members of Squad 10
are now officially
chunin, and it also
means that I will no longer
be in charge of you guys.
From here on out you're
leaders in your own right.
Each of you will be
given a new team to lead.
These earrings are my gift to
you to celebrate your success.
Whatever the future
holds, never forget
you were members of Squad 10.
Yes, of course.
It's the first time we've all
been together for a while,
isn't it?
NARUTO: I can't believe I
have to stop my training just
to go on some lame mission.
-A mission's a mission.
We have no choice.
-Yeah.
But it's not like this
mission is an important one.
Who cares about a
bunch of grave robbers,
and why's Grandma Tsunade
wasting our time on them?
-Hey, Naruto.
How you doing?
What's up with your training?
-Suspended on account
of some stupid mission.
-Ino, are you guys
heading out now too?
-That's right.
We're all together again.
KONOHAMARU: Hey, what
are you all doing here?
-Konohamaru.
-So what?
You off on another
mission, Naruto?
-Unfortunately.
Still looking for lost cats?
-[laugh] That's right.
This is the seventh
one I've found.
If you ask me, I'm getting
to be a real expert at it.
-Good work.
You hang in there.
-Will do.
Well, I guess I better
go file my report.
-See you later, Konohamaru.
-Bye, Uncle Asuma.
Good hunting.
-Did he call you Uncle Asuma?
I don't get it.
What's up with that?
-What are you talking about?
He called him "uncle,"
because Asuma's his uncle.
What do you think?
-Say what?
Then he's--
-Yeah.
He's the son of
the Third Hokage.
You didn't know that?
-I had no idea.
-No.
Me neither.
-Well, what of it?
NARUTO: I never knew you
were the old man's son.
And to think we have
the same chakra nature.
Amazing.
It makes me feel like we've got
a special bond or something.
-Well, just make
sure to keep training
even while you're
on your mission.
And don't forget what I told
you, finely and sharply.
-Don't worry, I won't.
All right, Team Yamato.
Let's get this mission started.
-OK.
Hey, wait up.
-Naruto.
-So you're leading the team?
-Yes.
It seems Kakashi has a
different mission right now.
-Protect Naruto.
Look after him.
-Yes, sir.
-Hey, Captain Yamato.
Come on.
We're ready.
-I'd better go.
Coming.
-All right.
It's time we were off as well.
-He's progressing
phenomenally quickly,
but he's still got a ways to go.
A new jutsu like this one
isn't mastered easily.
-Yes.
I know.
Listen, I'm sorry
about this, Kakashi,
but it's essential you
rendezvous with Jaraiya
and keep tabs on the Akatsuki.
I wish we had time to let
Naruto focus on his training,
but it can't be
helped right now.
-He wants to get it
over with quickly,
so he's pushing
himself to the limit.
My worry is that
the result could
be an eruption of
the Nine-Tails' power
that not even Yamato
would be able to control.
I don't think I'm
making a mistake here.
[crying]
-Look at them.
See how they grieve,
their tears, their anger.
The Land of Fire has
no need for neighbors.
Words are wasted when people
cannot understand each other.
At last, the Land of
Fire will rise and assume
its place on the tallest
mountain top for all the world
to look up to.
But for that to happen,
the decayed and rotten Leaf
must be torn away.
The time has come to
awaken the Land of Fire.
-Let's wrap this up quick,
so I can get back to training
already.
-Better be careful.
Don't go taking
this lightly just
cause it's a D-rank mission.
-Huh.
Don't worry I won't.
[theme music]
-I can't believe
Grandma Tsunade's
got us chasing
after grave robbers.
What a waste of time.
SAKURA: Hey, it's our mission.
Complaining about
it doesn't help.
NARUTO: Yeah, but--
YAMATO: Besides, there's
something different going on
here.
Your typical grave robber is
nothing but a thief plundering
buried coins and
jewelry from the dead.
However, these
grave robbers seem
to be after something
other than buried loot.
NARUTO: What do you mean?
YAMATO: I don't know
for certain yet,
but there's definitely a
different motive at work here.
NARUTO: Next time,
"Deprived of Eternal Sleep."
[theme music]