[bird calls]
-Ah, there you are.
-Huh?
-Every once in a while
you disappear, Naruto-boy.
Where do you go?
-Oh, uh, nowhere in
particular, really.
I just kind of wander around.
Well, no matter.
-We're going to practice
that merging I talked about.
Why don't you come on down?
-I hope they're OK.
-What do you mean?
-I know that the
Akatsuki are after me.
Well, I've been
worried that they'll
come looking for me
in the Leaf village.
-You're a fool.
-Huh?
-There are many distinguished
ninja in the Hidden Leaf
village, so stop all of
this unnecessary worrying
and concentrate on
the work at hand.
Besides, if something
were to happen,
they'd send a messenger
frog to let us know.
-Hm.
All right.
Then let's try
this merging thing!
-I can't believe the damage.
[theme music]
[singing in japanese]
-The era of Lady Tsunade
shall come to an end.
However, we cannot allow the
Akatsuki to get their hands
on the Nine-Tails, so I've
removed that possibility.
We will lay low underground
until the chaos above
dies down.
-Should we not provide support?
With all due respect, even
if you do assume power,
it would be meaningless if the
citizens of the Hidden Leaf
are dead.
-The princess is now Hokage.
As long as she has
Katsuyu's jutsu,
the village will not perish.
Certainly there
will be lives lost,
but those are necessary
sacrifices-- in order
for me to become
the next Hokage.
-Ha!
I win.
-Ah.
Nothing tastes better than
a drink of sake after work.
-It's no good.
-Tonbo.
Were you able to
find out anything?
-Not yet.
Or at least, no clues
that are directly related
to Pain in any way.
-The corpse today is light.
-I've developed a knack
for this over the years.
I can tell this one's
probably a woman.
-The tallest tower in
this whole village.
You know, where we always
deliver the bodies.
You know what it's for?
-In a village like
ours, towers are usually
where the ashes are enshrined.
They were originally built as
memorials to honor the fallen.
-If that's the case, then why
aren't the relatives allowed
in there anymore?
-How should I know?
-Heh.
-What?
You think you're better than me?
-But actually, there is a rumor
going around about that tower,
you know.
That Lord Pain lives there.
-Really?
Interesting.
Ugh.
But there's no way.
-Well, it is just a rumor.
Nothing more.
Never mind.
I'm going to confirm my theory.
You were right.
It's just like you said.
A woman.
-Thank you.
-Oh!
Lady Angel!
-Now quickly.
Go and bring the
next one in here.
-Inoichi, you
really are amazing.
Scanning half a day
of this guy's memories
in less than 30 seconds.
I can barely keep up.
-Fool.
If you have time
to talk, then you
should be looking harder for
anything related to Pain.
-Sorry for interrupting.
It's me, Shizune.
I was ordered to report here
to you guys by Lady Hokage.
-Did you discover something?
-Yes.
I'll share my findings.
By combining my information
with the intelligence you're
extracting, we'll
figure out who Pain is.
-Summoning Jutsu.
-Each of the Pains
had black rods
like this one embedded
in their bodies.
We believe that this is the
key to explaining their power.
-So then, are they transmitting
chakra to each other?
That would make it something
like our Yamanaka clan's
secret ninjutsu technique.
-Ninja with the same eyes
as the sage of Six Paths.
The legendary Rinnegan-bearing
forefather of all ninja.
It they truly exist,
it's no surprise
they could use all
kinds of jutsu.
-Oh!
-What was that?
-It seems they've
shown up here as well.
[growling]
-We'll stop them.
-Wind Style.
Wind Blade Jutsu.
-Lightning Style.
Four-Pillar Trap.
-Earth Style.
Bhudda Fuda.
-Did we get it?
-All right.
This is the final
step of sage mode.
We'll now begin merge training.
-Ah, OK.
So, basically, you're just
going to sit on my shoulder
and attach yourself
to me, right?
-Correct.
While you're in motion,
I'll stay still.
And I'll draw in
nature energy for you.
This training will help us
to hone that merging process.
-Mmm.
-Now, let us begin by
synchronizing our breathing.
-Right.
-Ah.
Ahhh!
-Oh-- oh-- are you
OK, Geezer Toad?
-How very strange.
All right.
Let's try it one more time.
Sage Art, Amphibian Jutsu.
[growling]
[scream]
-Huh?
-Well, Naruto-boy, it
seems it's impossible.
-What do you mean?
-I suspect that the
Nine-Tails inside of you
is rejecting me and
casting me out, Naruto-boy.
-No way!
Come on!
Then what was all
that training for?
What are we going to
do now, Lord Fukasaku?
[laughter]
[roaring]
-What?
It's grown more heads.
-Seems like a special
type of summoning.
We need to take on the caster
rather than face this thing.
-So what should we
do now, Shizune?
-Leave it to them.
-Summoning Jutsu.
-Huh?
-Ah!
[roaring]
-What is that?
-As I thought.
This is it.
-It seems I made it in time.
-Lady Katsuyu,
thank you so much.
-Please forgive
me, Lady Katsuyu.
I'm not used to you.
-Oh, that's all right.
-They are powerful summonings.
Everyone, please be careful.
-There's no mistake.
I saw her inside the memories
of that Hidden Rain ninja.
But how can this be?
-What is it?
-When I saw her,
she was a corpse.
-(VOICEOVER) And that corpse
is now using a summoning jutsu.
But each of the
Six Pains is only
supposed to be able
to use a single jutsu.
Something's wrong.
According to Lord
Fukasaku, the only Pain
that can do summonings
is the one I autopsied.
What does this mean?
Lord Jiraiya already
defeated the only Pain
with this ability.
Inoichi, please give
me more details.
We might be able
to figure this out.
-Right now?
But we can't.
-Leave this to the ANBU and me.
Get out of here.
-But Ibiki--
-Quick.
Let's go.
Inoichi, we must uncover
Pain's true identity.
We have to hurry and get
to the Cipher Division.
We should bring
Ino with us so she
can support your
jutsu, Master Inoichi.
-All right.
-(VOICEOVER) Ino.
It's me.
Listen closely.
We're going to go to
the Cipher Division.
-Let's move out!
[growling]
-You have to get
through us first.
[growling]
-So, you have
nothing to say, huh?
You're no fun at all.
Huh.
Well, if that's your
attitude, then I'm
just going to have
to make you talk.
-We'll deal with the dog.
Combination B.
-Right.
-Wind Style.
Wind Blade Jutsu.
-Lightning Style
Four-Pillar Trap.
-Earth Style.
Mud Fall.
-Lightning Style.
16-Pillar Trap.
-Fire Style.
Biscuit Firing Jutsu.
-Summoning.
Iron Maiden.
-Summon.
Torture Chamber.
I'll make you
loosen your tongue,
and you'll tell us
all your secrets.
Pain.
Nice name.
Pain is the most reliable
form of communication.
Let me feel your pain, too.
Yes, that's right.
Pain simply cannot tell a lie.
And through pain,
we are all equals.
I'm going to share your
pain, and through it I
shall learn all about you.
Now, you'll show me
who the real you is.
Grr.
Now.
(VOICEOVER) This one
isn't feeling any pain.
Ugh.
And, so cold.
Like a corpse.
-Tell me.
Just what is this pain
you presume to speak of?
The likes of you
could never understand
what true pain really is.
[grunt]
-Summoning Jutsu!
[shouts]
[roaring]
-Summoning Jutsu.
-Huh?
[roaring]
-Ah!
Impossible!
[theme music]
[singing in japanese]
-No, Konohamuru!
Why didn't you run when
you had the chance?
-Long ago, I made a promise.
-Huh?
-To fight big brother Naruto
for the title of Hokage one day.
He is my rival, so I'm not
choosing an escape route.
Because Naruto won't be waiting
at the end of that shorter
path.
-Next time on Naruto Shippuden.
Surname is Sarutobe.
Given name, Konahamuru.
-Remember me!
-The documents are really
piling up around here.
Oh, well.
I guess I'll have to
cancel tonight's date.
Yeah, right.
Like I'd even have a date!
Better get back to work.
-Oy!
-Ninja registration forms.
A lot of this hasn't been
updated in a long time.
Ah!
They're all so young!
All these are photos from
back in their Rookie 9 days.
And look at how
much they've grown
in only a few short years.
Huh?
Ooh, boy.
That troublesome child.
Now I have to have Kenzo
retake that picture.
Huh?
Give me a break.
Quit copying such silliness.
Ai-yeeee!
[theme music]