So..if that guy up
there is the real
Madara...
That means the guy who
we thought was Madara...
isn't actually him?
Yes, so it seems.
You used to utilize
the Akatsuki.
So can't you speculate
on what the identity of
that masked man might
be, Tsuchikage?
There's no one
I can think of
right now.
But honestly, it
doesn't really
matter who he is.
Whatever his name,
we still need to
stop him!
Their headbands say
shinobi, but I see them
wearing clothing from each
of the five great nations.
Is this some new
united army?
Well, it does appear
that we're at war.
So that's what
he's up to.
But I wonder what exactly
he's got in mind now.
It doesn't look as if
things are going the
way he originally
planned them.
Or else why would he
revive me in this
strange way.
Who is the caster
of the Reanimation
Jutsu?
I have no idea.
My name is Kabuto.
I'm his collaborator.
Speaking to me through
a Reanimation Link? What
a sneaky one you are.
Your reanimation is
quite special.
You're now even
greater than during
your glory days.
Is that so?
You know what I was
like during my glory
days, do you?
No. That's one of the
reasons I brought you
here now.
To show me your
legendary Uchiha power.
Guess we can't take
him that easily.
Very well then.
[nervous swallow]
Here he comes guys!
Whatever happens, don't
look directly into his eyes!
[battle cries]
[grunting]
You can't use Particle
Style now, not with half
your normal chakra.
Sensory Ninja! Make
sure you watch
Lord Mu!
[grunt]
Wait.
Gaara, you and the
Tsuchikage have to
recover first.
Naruto, use that mode
instead of your
shadow clones.
The truth is I can't
right now. I used up
my chakra in the
earlier fight.
[worried reaction]
[painful cry]
[painful grunt]
[scared reaction]
[painful yell]
[painful reactions]
[choking sound]
You want to dance
with me as well?
Do not underestimate me!
[frustrated reaction]
Fire Style! Majestic
Destroyer Flame!
His Jutsu is enormous!
Water Style! Wall
of Water!
Here he comes!
[shocked gasp]
[yelp]
Hm?
You will go
no further!
Massive Rasengan!
Earth Style!
Mobile Core!
[battle cry]
[struggling sounds]
[shocked gasp]
[painful yell]
[painful grunt]
That's a Susano'o!
He's already activated
the Mangekyo Sharingan?!
Naruto, how
much longer?
Just hold on a second,
I'm almost done.
[yelling in pain]
[scoffing]
[shocked breath]
Sorry about that.
Okay! I'm
all ready now!
I'm gonna need
everyone to get back!
Go, Kazekage!
Earth Style!
Lightened Boulder
Jutsu!
I've made all the sand
around here lighter
as well.
With sand this light,
there's no limit to
what I could do.
Naruto!
Alright! Here I go!
If it's like Sasuke's,
external attacks are
ineffective. So I should use
the sand at Madara's feet!
[surprised reaction]
Go!
Naruto!
Rasen Shuriken!
Why did that man
in the mask claim
to be Madara
specifically?
Why him?
Well, it is as if
a presence like
Madara's does already
exist in this realm.
So even if one is full
of deceit, if you can
convince the world then
it will quake in fear.
Just the name
itself is power.
It made us throw
caution to the wind.
It drew our attention
and then the lie fooled
all of us into embarking
on a war!
We've been had. We were
trapped, hook, line
and sinker.
Too much energy.
He...he absorbed
that Jutsu!
But-But that's...
How come that Madara
guy posseses Rinnegan
eyes?
It appears that my
guess was correct.
The natural progression
following the Sharingan
is the Rinnegan.
I managed to awaken
the Rinnegan just a
little prior to my death.
You said Kabuto, right?
What exactly did you
do to this body?
Like I mentioned
to you before...
I made you even better
than at the peak of
your power.
You bastard.
You know the secrets
within my flesh!
You aren't even able to
read the Uchiha Stone Tablet
but you still managed to
decipher it.
I'm just testing out a
hypothesis suggested by many
years of experiments that Lord
Orochimaru and I conducted.
And now, you are proving
that hypothesis to be
true after all.
You are able to achieve a piece
of that God's power. The power
of Sage of Sixth Paths.
Thanks to the might
that I built into you.
Do not misunderstand it.
This is not power of your
creation!
[soft chuckle]
Man...
It's so unreal.
What...What the
hell is that?
[nervous reaction]
Whoa...This is way
out of our league.
Is this the power
of a God?
[surprised reactions]
Is this ninjutsu?
We can't outrun it!
[scared reactions]
It is still far too
early to consider
giving up!
Never quit without
even trying!
Always do something. However
small an effect it may have.
Lord Tsuchikage!
Everyone! Get as far away
from here as you can!
[panicked reactions]
Run!
You're taking us out, too?
Yes, of course I am!
That was the original point
of the Reanimation Jutsu, to
take the others out with you.
The two of us will
be restored presently.
A shinobi that can fly?
Is that really the little
Fence Sitter Brat from the
Hidden Stone?
What's Grampa Tsuchikage
gonna do up there anyway?
He's gonna make that
meteorite lighter
and stop it!
[struggling efforts]
Earth Style! Super
Lightened Boulder Jutsu!
[struggling efforts]
[powerful yell]
Just a little...
Need just a little
bit more to stop it!
[struggling yell]
Who would've guessed that
Fence Sitter lad...He's
become quite a capable shinobi.
Yes!
The old man did it!
[sighs and groans of relief]
[relieved sigh]
But now...Just what
are you going to do
about the second
one, Ohnoki?
[shocked gasp]
[painful yell]
What?!
[startled grunt]
What happened out there?!
From our Relay
Intel Unit...
A giant boulder big enough
to block out the sky's
been dropped on our Fourth
Company's battlefield.
It's the source of
this tremor!
Any further reports
from the Fourth Company
since the attack?!
The sheer scale of it...
To kill so many enemies
all at once.
[overwhelmed reaction]
There's no mistake...It's
Madara's Jutsu or close to
it. Lady Tsunade, at this
rate...
That's it! I'll go!
What...What in the
world happened?!
[painful grunts]
[struggling efforts]
Bendy guy! Why'd
you bother saving
a clone like me?
I feel bad about the
others...But whether
you're a clone or not you're
still sorely needed here.
...if we hope to win.
[upset reaction]
[startled gasp]
What about Grampa
Tsuchikage?!
Grampa
Tsuchikage!
It's okay, don't worry.
He is still alive.
However...He's
seriously injured.
So this is the power
of the Sage of Six
Paths, huh?
Magnificent.
[satisfied hum]
This landscape brings
back so many
memories.
You said that your
name was Kabuto...
How much do you
really know about me?
Tell me the truth.
This is only a
guess, but...
Back when you battled the
first Hokage Hashirama at
Final Valley, you didn't
actually die on that day.
Instead, in
that skirmish...
You may have lost to the
First Hokage...But you
gained a portion of Hashirama's
power for yourself in return.
Am I mistaken?
Ah, then that's why...
I'm able to see
what's coming so well.
Then you are also
aware of our plan?
Not really; not in detail...
But please remember that
I am your ally.
However, when it comes to
whether that fake Madara
intends to carry out your plan
exactly...I don't quite know.
Oh, by the way...Seems
there are still some
survivors here and there.
The Tsuchikage and Kazekage
are especially persistent.
What should we do?
Before anything else, there
is something I want to
check first.
Summoning Jutsu!
[struggling in pain]
My stomach!
It feels...so hot!
This chakra that summons
me...Is it Madara's?!
It appears that the
Nine Tails still
remains uncaptured.
In fact, that's the
entire purpose of
this war.
The Nine Tails remains
sealed inside a Jinchuriki.
For right now.
Just look, he's
right over there.
That boy is the Nine
Tails' Jinchuriki. His
name is Naruto Uzumaki.
Uzumaki...?
He's from Mito's
Clan, eh?
He attacked me earlier.
Nothing but a little brat!
Yes, but he's actually
quite the shinobi.
We will need to capture
him, although that one
right in front of us is
only a clone.
Shall we go and capture
the original one now?
Not yet. There's still
a jutsu I'd like to try out.
And I think that it will
make a prettier picture
if I do it where there are
still people around.
Huh?!
It's them! They're
toward four o'clock!
Wood Style! Deep
Forest Emergence!
He's able to use
Wood Style?!
I guess this is it
for us, then.
[nervous reaction]
Damn it! I don't
have much chakra
left at all!
I'm at my limit!
I'm gonna disappear
at any moment here!
What am I gonna do?!
Naruto, that's enough.
I'll take over the battle
from here on.
I have a chance to
reclaim myself now!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Five
Kage Assemble."
I'll help you
reclaim yourself.