I see...  Sasuke and Naruto are
in an alternate Time-Space...
...as are Sakura and Kakashi.
Naruto and Sasuke are the core
participants in the battle.
I really wish that we could've
received this advice a bit
earlier.
This lower body is a piece of
Madara after he became Ten
Tails' Jinchuriki...
...which means, in short,
contained within it is Ten
Tails, Madara and Hashirama.
No, Nine Tails, Indra,
and Ashura.
I can only emerge like this now
because their chakra is finally
one.
And... going back to the jutsu
you just mentioned to us...
How exactly are we
supposed to execute it?
I'll weave the signs for the
jutsu.  But this jutsu requires
a vast amount of chakra...
...which I don't have right now
... since I've given it away.
We don't have much time, either.
So I just ask you
to do as I say.
♪
This man lent me his power, and
that's why...  we were able to
get here.
He did, huh?
[grunt]
[gasp] This is bad.
Damn it, I can't!
Not till I
bring them back...
Just hang on!
Will I... break my
promise again...?
...Rin?
Hey, you know, Rin, if you
really think about it,
you saving me is pretty much the
exact same thing as you saving
the whole world!
Huh?
'Cause, I mean...
...I'm gonna become Hokage and
I'll bring this war to an end,
right?
And for me to do that, I have to
stay alive and healthy.
It's like... how do I put it...
I mean, if you... don't stay
close and keep a watch over
me...
Well...
It's just- [gasp]
Argh!
Y- You got so close
to me all of a sudden!
Don't scare me like that, Rin!
You said to stay close
and keep watch over you!
Yeah, I guess I did.  Heh.
So watch over me!  'Cause I'm
gonna wear the Uchiha crest.
And become Hokage!
Right!
Oh man, oh man, oh man! This is
the one day I can't be late!
[panting]
[chatter]
[sigh]
You're even late to the
entrance ceremony?!
Someone like you has no business
being in the Academy at all.
You'll fail out.
It's okay.
Huh?
Since you weren't there, I
picked this up for you.
Uh, for me?
Yeah! Just submit this packet,
and you'll be able to enroll!
Wow, thank you!
You're a lifesaver!
(Kakashi)
You know, if you keep pampering
him, then he'll never get over
his tardiness.
(Obito)
Hey, shut up!
Now begin!
(Teacher)
Stop!
[excited chatter]
Hey, what's with the headband?
That means that you passed it!
Congratulations!
Thanks.
Well? Aren't you going to
congratulate me?
Yeah, right!
I'm gonna catch up
with you in no time!
Just you wait!
[gasp]
Obito...
Class is going to
start soon. Let's go.
Rin...
[gasp]
Please, just... Just keep
watching over me, okay?
[gasp] ...What?
(Obito)
I...
I'll catch up to him... And then
I'll surpass him... and... I'll
become Hokage, no matter what!
Hm! Don't worry,
I'll be watching.
[heavy breathing]
[big exhale]
[rainfall]
[grunts]
[grunting]
There you are, Obito!
Huh? Rin!
Argh!
Obito...! Are you all right?!
[embarrassed laugh] Yeah, I just
slipped, but it's nothing.  I'm
okay. I'm okay.
Now...  Here's the graduation
certificate for Obito Uchiha!
This attests that you've
graduated from the Hidden
Leaf Ninja Academy.
You are hereby commended for
persevering through the elements
in order to reach this
impressive milestone!
Here! Congratulations, Obito!
Rin...
Thank you, Rin.
No one may be here to see it,
but this makes me happier than
receiving it from Grandpa
Hokage!
We've been assigned to a
team! This is our first
step as shinobi!
[excited chuckle]
I still have a long way to go,
but I'm closer to becoming
Hokage now! Right, Rin?
What... the hell!?
[gasp]
"I'm always watching you."
[gentle string music]
I'll make you pay me back
in full for the last time
that we fought!
The last time we fought...?
Do your best! Obito!
[gasp]
All right! Just watch me!
Begin!
[gasp]
[attack grunts]
The winner is Might Guy!
What was he doing?
[sigh]
So this is where you've been!
[gasp] Oh, it's you!
[gasp]
It's only natural that
Kakashi would pass.
But we can do it,
too, I know we can!
We'll just practice
hard for next year!
But... it's hard to
get motivated after
watching Kakashi.
What are you saying?!
Huh?
You're gonna be Hokage, right?
[gasp]
Obito, I'll always
be watching you.
[happy gasp] Okay!
[gentle string music]
[gasp]
Obito...?
[laugh]
I did it! I'm a Chunin now!
(Kakashi)
You're late again, Obito!
A lot happened on my way here,
okay?! I mean, I got lost...
How come every route you take
always seems to be the
roundabout one, huh?
They're not falling into
line at all, are they?
That's for sure...
But, you know, Sensei?
Hm?
You just let me handle this!
I'll watch over the two of
them... always!
Let's go! Both of you!
(Obito)
I was so stubborn... and most of
the time I felt ill at ease...
But you never failed
to come to my rescue.
[crash]
(Zetsu)
Since it's a dream, everything
is just how you want it!
(Zetsu)
Even those who are dead
can be alive again!
A world of only victors, A world
of only peace, A world of
only love. I will
create such a world.
Rin, once again, Let's create a
world where you can exist again.
[gasp]
Yes! You came back to us!@
[grunt]There's still
something that I must do...
We're going back, all of us.
Now hang on tight to me.
Right.
[grunt]
[grunts]
I'm sure of it...
Those things...!  They took down
that Shadow Clone earlier.
[grunts]
(Zetsu)
The Clones are frantically
protecting that one.
There's no mistake, Mother.  The
one with the Truthseeker Orbs is
the real Naruto!
[grunts]
There's no end to them!
(Thinking)
Am I powerless to do anything
but sit here and watch?
Sakura and Obito are battling as
well...
I... I really couldn't do much
for you as your teacher...
Nor for you... Obito and
Rin,... as your friend...
I just put on airs that I was an
elite and yet kept making
mistakes.
It's not over!
Ya hear me!? There's no
way I'm gonna lose!
[attack yells]
What am I doing... wallowing
like this... when Naruto is
fighting so hard?
There should be something
that I can still do!
Obito!
[gasp]
What?!  Sasuke?!  Impossible!
He's here!
[grunts]
[gasps]
There's nothing to
worry about now.
No!  No way!
No, no way!
Naruto!
[gasp]
Why you...! He passed the
Truthseeker Orbs to a
clone? And we fell for it?!
Thank you, Sakura and
Obito! I owe you one!
Hold on! So you're really okay?!
You sure scared us there!
Sasuke! Have you properly
thanked Sakura and Obito?
Just focus on the enemy!
Well, Naruto was always
unexpectedly clever...
Mother, if they've reunited, we
have no other choice.
We can't afford to save our
chakra right now.
Yes, I know.
[grunt]
[shouting]
[heavy grunts]
[gasp]
(Thinking)
My body's so heavy. And this
terrain... is digging into me!
[grunt] What happened!?
I can't levitate anymore!
(Thinking)
A heavy gravity
plane this time...
Except...She's affected, too.
[weary grunt]
[gasps]
[gasp]
Oh no...!
(Thinking)
Damn it! My left eye
hasn't recharged yet!
Quick!  Dodge 'em, Sasuke!
[gasp]
[grunts]
Did the heavy gravity distort
your aim?
I'll make the adjustment now.
I won't miss them again.
I'll stop you! [grunt]
[grunts]
(Thinking)
There's still something
that I can do.
I can at least be a
shield for them!
Please make it in time!
[gasps]
Rin...!
Again, you.
Thank you, Rin. Obito and I will
be joining you shortly.
We can catch up then, all three
of us together once more.
[gasp]
(Thinking)
Rin. This time, let's, spend
some alone time together,...
just you and me.
[angelic music]
Kakashi would just be in the
way.  So I'll leave him here.
That was Kamui!
[gasps]
Obito!  What did you-?!
Kakashi... you stay
here a little longer.
[gasp]
Don't you rush to follow us.
♪
(Obito)
After fighting you, I
feel like I've woken up.
When I was a kid, I'd imagine
myself as the Hokage so often...
I think you brought back... that
indescribable feeling of
exhilaration and uncertainty.
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"You Better..."
(Naruto)
Don't laugh at Obito!
♪