Good.
Naruto!
Stop, Madara! Enough!
[grunting]
Honestly, I gave you plenty
of time.
And I even warned you that
you didn't have a whole lot
of it left.
[panting]
Obito...
It seems that he's fighting
to prevent his Rinnegan from
falling into Madara's hands.
Stubborn fool. You're almost
dead. Just give up!
Hang in there! Don't give
up!
You are so strong! You'll
make it! I know that you
will!
Uh!
My chakra's almost all...!
[straining]
At this rate... Sa- Sasuke
is--!
...really gonna...
At this rate, Naruto is
going to...
...die!
"On the Brink of Death"
[gasping]
The Nine Tails' Chakra...!
No heartbeat or pulse!
Can't be!
Just hang in there, Naruto!
But why?! My Jutsu's
not working!
Because the Nine Tails was
extracted.
Impossible!
Madara attacked him.
But there is a way to save
him! And that's why we're
hurrying, right now!
To where?!
Where the Fourth Hokage is.
Hey, Kazekage! Do me a
favor!
His father...
One half of me's sealed
inside Minato.
So you just take that other
half and transplant it in
Naruto.
That will save his life.
Hurry to the Fourth Hokage!
He has the Teleportation
Jutsu. Why don't we just
have him come here?
Not possible.
His Teleportation Jutsu's
tied to my Sealing Formula.
However, once I'm extracted,
it'll disappear.
Just rush Naruto over to the
Fourth Hokage! You got that,
Gaara?!
[grunting]
I'm counting on you,
Kazekage!
That's what the Nine Tails
said to me.
As of right now, there isn't
any other way for us to save
Naruto!
Then let's go! How much
farther?
Several kilometers!
[grunting]
I'll do whatever it
takes...with what little
chakra I've got left!
Uh--
Mm!
There!
As long as I'm here, I am
not going to let you die!
Mm.
[grunting]
Going full speed!
Right!
[groaning]
If I could just save his
soul with my Forbidden
Jutsu...
I can't sense any chakra in
him anymore...
I can't move at all now,
much less teleport.
Damn you, Madara!
[yelling]
What?! Karin really just
went charging in there like
that?!
Let's go back her up!
Shouldn't we wait for an
opening, or, you know, some
kinda plan?
[grunting]
Now, just hold on, there!
You're not getting past me!
No one's answered my
question yet!
You'd better get out of my
way!
I've gotta get to Sasuke!
Move, you bastard!
No way... Impressive,
Karin...!
What's that?
It's tThe same power as
Kushina Uzumaki...
She's finally attained
it....
Oh, no... Well, that's just
not nice. You broke my
little toy!
Do not underestimate
me--ah!
[chuckling]
Double Blast!
Not bad.
I can't move...
A Curse Mark!
That's too bad-for you!
A- Amazing...
Orochimaru's team... they
got past it!
Oh, well... No biggie. It's
too late even if you make it
there, anyway.
But, as for you guys, I'm
going to take you down!
Well, don't just stand
there, ogling! We must move
in, too!
Still... just who is he...?
Are you all right, Karin?
I'm fine. But never mind me.
Sasuke is...!
I can't sense Sasuke's
chakra anymore!
So this is Six Paths
power...
Now to collect that left
eye...
[inhaling]
I'm one of the greatest
ninja ever! Some day I'm
gonna be Hokage and you'll
look up to me! My name's
Naruto Uzumaki! Remember
it!!
And my future dream is...
...to be the greatest
Hokage!..
Those silly dreams you once
had no longer seem so silly.
I won't... I won't let you
die!
You're not going to die...
No matter what!
Not when we're so close!
Your dream...is right before
your eyes, now!
Who's there?!
Depending on the situation,
Orochimaru might try to
steal Sasuke's body.
It's what Kimimaro had
wanted... But I doubt Karin
would allow it.
[gasping]
There's someone else where
Sasuke is.
You recognize the chakra?
No! But...
But what, Karin?
This chakra...
...has a real nasty feel to
it!
Then we're going to need to
hurry even more.
After all, we have
absolutely no idea what this
stranger might be planning
to do to Sasuke.
Is this where his wind
ceases to blow?
[growling]
Wha--?
Karin! If you don't pace
yourself, you're going to
collapse.
All right... Let's head out
to join the others at youth
power max!
Lee! Tenten!
Yes, sir! But you are...
...clearly falling over, Guy
Sensei!
It seems your body isn't
keeping up with your spirit,
too well!
Uh--
That looks like Gaara's
sand... And I think that I
saw Sakura, too...
But I wonder why they would
be retreating...
Kakashi hasn't... overtaken
and passed us yet, right?
Right.
The Nine Tails' Chakra
from Naruto is gone.
And seeing that Sakura, a
Medical Ninja, is on the
move...
I have a feeling that
something is going down
where Kakashi is, right now.
We're heading back, Lee!
Tenten...!
My red-hot blood is boiling
right now!
You are feeling super
uneasiness?
What?!
[sighing]
There's simply nothing good
that can come out of being
stuck with this hot-blooded,
air-headed duo!
Neji, why did you have to go
and leave me here alone with
those two guys?
Come on... let's just head
back.
You do want to go back,
right? Let's just go.
Neji... I'm never gonna
forgive you for this.
Wait for me! I'll be there
as fast as I can, Kakashi.
Kakashi...! Hurry up! The
left eye.
Obito's conscience is clear.
Now's our chance.
Yes, but the problem is how
are we going to tear that
guy away from Obito?
And we can't let him hand
over that left eye to the
enemy...
[inhaling]
[exhaling]
I'm feeling a little bit
heavier than I ought to,
now. It seems something's
catching in my chest.
[spitting]
The Sage's Ninja Tools, huh?
Useless.
But now, I'm lighter.
Exactly what are we
going to accomplish by
returning now, anyway?
Tenten! Stop your grumbling!
I just have this feeling,
deep in my gut, that some
unknown horror is
approaching!
Yes, sir.
[yelling]
What was that?! Are you two
all right?!
Yes...!
[groaning]
No way... Are those...?!
They are!
[panting]
You two guys sure
are stubborn.
Obito's consciousness... is
no longer stable.
Kakakshi... Let's go!
Hold up, Minato!
Uh!
Quick, switch your chakra
into Sensory Mode! Now!
Uh!
No way!
We were distracted, here...
There's no mistake. My other
half's been extracted!
Sensei?
Huh?
Uh--
Kakashi Sensei!
[gasping]
What happened, Sakura?!
The Nine Tails was extracted
from Naruto! It doesn't
look good.
Naruto...
A message from Naruto's Nine
Tails!
Listen, Fourth Hokage! He
said to transplant the other
half of Nine tails within
you into Naruto.
It's the only way to save
him!
Hmm...
Kakashi, he's all yours.
Understood.
I'll help!
Well, I'm going.
Be careful.
Of course! There's no way
I'm going to die before I
see my child's face.
[sighing]
Once this child is born, I'm
going to have two things to
worry about...
Hey, don't worry!
I can take care of the kid!
No matter what happens, and
no matter what it takes!
Mm.
But you're so busy being the
Hokage, and I think he's
going to be mischievous, and
incorrigible, and say he
wants to become Hokage, too!
And he's gonna be clueless
about girls... defy his
teachers--
Hold on!
[gasping]
Calm down. I mean, the kid
hasn't even been born, yet!
You're worrying too much!
Besides, how do you know
that it's a boy? Or that
he's going to want to be the
Hokage, even before we lay
eyes on him?!
Easy!
Because I'm his mother.
Uh--
[chuckling]
Anyway, I'm the Hokage. I'm
not going to die easily.
And as Hokage, I'll protect
that child no matter what!
Don't worry!
You're awfully confident
when it comes to this baby!
Well, of course...
I am his father.
The current me can...
This time for sure!
Uh--
[gasping]
That was-!
[growling]
Nine Tails...
Now... you're finally...
mine!
[grunting]
What happened?!
How is Naruto?!
What was that?!
No way...
Lord Madara...
Black Zetsu...
You're taking too long.
So I decided I should
come to you, instead!
I need to ask you something,
Madara. What am I to you?
[chuckling] You have to be
kidding, right? What kind of
a stupid question is that?
You have always been only
one thing to me.
He who rejects this world,
all who hold that thought in
their heart... And strive
toward achieving the
Infinite Tsukuyomi...
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Two
Mangekyo"
Yes... you are...