-Can it be that you're--
-You finally
remembered, have you?
-Have we met somewhere before?
-It's no wonder
you're called a beast.
Your intelligence is
certainly subhuman.
Well, don't worry.
I'll refresh your
memory soon enough.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Itachi.
-So.
That's the one.
The child who wiped
out his entire clan.
-Kakashi.
Naruto.
It's been awhile.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
His Sharingan.
It's the same as Sasuke's.
So this is the guy who's been
hounding Sasuke and Naruto all
this time.
-I wasn't enough for you, huh?
You had to go after
Gaara as well.
I'll destroy every
last one of you.
-Everyone.
Whatever you do, don't
look him in the eyes.
[theme music]
-So he's an Akatuski.
-Water Style, Exploding
Water Shockwave!
-Get ready.
-All right.
-Ready or not, here I come.
-Itachi's genjustsu
is a visual jutsu,
which means, avoid
eye contact with him
and his jutsu can't take effect.
-Yeah, that I know.
-OK, but then, how are
we supposed to fight him?
-That's the tricky part.
Guy.
How did you fight Itachi?
-Hm?
There's only one way.
-You have to
anticipate his moves
by watching his feet, his body.
-But that's like fighting with
one arm tied behind your back.
-The Uchiha clan, eh?
It's been a long time since I've
gone up against the Sharingan.
Don't look so surprised.
I've been around, and I know
there's more than one way
to fight a visual
jutsu like that.
-Yeah?
Like what, then?
-If one against the
one, abandon the field.
If two against one, take
the rear, and he'll yield.
-What's that mean?
-Well, the first part
of it is pretty self
explanatory, isn't it?
The Sharingan can never be
beaten in single combat.
But, if you outnumber
the Sharingan user,
if the battle is two against
one, then even if one of you
is caught in his
genjutsu, the other
is free to strike from the rear,
breaking the genjutsu's spell.
Even if your attack from the
rear should fail somehow,
you're still free to strike
your comrade yourself
and break the genjutsu that way.
So, while one of us fights him
face to face as a distraction,
the rest of us will
mount a series of attacks
from the rear, where his
Sharingan can't reach.
-Good plan.
-I guess you learn
a lot of stuff
like that if you
live long enough.
Let's go.
I'll take the rear.
KAKASHI: Wait.
-Huh?
-You guys!
Look out!
-How about it?
Like it so far?
-Huh?
-Ah, you remember me now?
-Where in the world is all
this water coming from?
-This technique of his requires
a huge amount of chakra.
An incredible amount.
-OK, Sensei.
We're waiting, but what
are we waiting for?
-Do you have a problem with my
way of fighting the Sharingan?
Are you suggesting my
methods won't work?
-No.
They work fine against
ordinary genjutsu,
but what we're
dealing with here is
something much more complicated.
-Meaning what?
-He uses Mangekyo Sharingan.
It's far more powerful than
any other visual jutsu.
It only takes a second, but if
he hits you with that jutsu,
it'll be the longest
second you ever lived.
Time itself gets warped.
What seems like a
second in the real world
can be hours or days to
someone trapped in his jutsu.
I know.
I wandered around
in it for three days
and lost consciousness
for more than a week.
It's not a genjutsu that can
be broken just like that.
-That does sound tricky.
What a troublesome
fellow this is.
-Very good, Kakashi.
I see your sojourn
in my Tsukuyomi.
Wasn't wasted.
-Oh, believe me.
I learned something
else as well.
There's a price to pay
for using that Sharingan.
It exhausted you, didn't it?
You had to quit before
the battle was over.
-Itachi.
You've risked
overusing your eyes.
You know that's dangerous.
-We're not here to fight
a full scale battle.
Tempting as it may be, it's
not the way to do this.
Let's go.
-So in addition to using
up a lot of chakra,
you risk permanent
damage to your eye
every time you use that
jutsu, don't you, Itachi?
-You seem to have learned
a great deal from our one
brief encounter.
-I wonder just how
much damage has already
been done to your eyesight.
ITACHI (VOICEOVER): Kakashi.
Could it be that you--
-Where do you think he is?
Guy-sensei!
Tenten.
-It was only a water clone.
-I guess you'll never get
the chance to remember me.
-It appears Itachi has made
contact with the enemy.
And I see that Kisame
is engaged in combat.
-Lee!
-Leaf Rising Wind!
-What?
-Eight Trigrams, Air Palm!
KISAME (VOICEOVER): Paper bomb!
-Damn he got away.
-Where's he hiding this time?
-Neji.
Any sign of him?
-In front of us,
and coming closer.
-I have found him.
-I'll grant you brats this much.
You're more trouble
than I thought you'd be.
In fact, you're
incredibly annoying.
-Wait a minute.
The water jutsu and
the massive sword.
Are you--
-Don't tell me a
memory is finally
stirring in that
tiny brain of yours.
-I feel certain
we've met before.
-I'd think this guy would
be pretty memorable.
-Listen to that.
Even your own
followers are beginning
to wonder if you can
remember anything.
Well, let's see what we can do.
Enough pain and maybe
then you'll remember.
-I underestimated you back then.
I admit it.
But I am not the
fool I used to be.
Things aren't gonna go
the same way this time.
I promise you that.
-Yeah, and don't go thinking
I'm the same kid either.
A lot of things have
changed since then.
-Naruto.
Leave him to me.
-Huh?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): This
is just like the last time.
-Now, quick.
Manji formation.
Protect the bridge builder,
and stay out of this fight.
-Huh?
-I taught you teamwork.
Now it's time to use it.
-Not again.
Not that kind of teamwork where
we sit back and do nothing!
-No.
This time, you cover me.
I wish I could say
you guys go on ahead,
I can handle this alone.
But I never make the
same mistake twice.
-Let's see now.
-All right.
Time to launch a counterattack.
Let me go in against him first.
As soon as his guard
is down, you move in.
-Yes, sir.
-Are you fool
enough to think you
can get me to lower
my guard that easily?
I won't try to
talk you out of it.
I'll let you learn the hard way.
-Gentle Fist!
He has a point.
He swings that huge
sword with such ease.
And getting through his
guard is just impossible.
-If close range combat won't
work-- How'd you like that?
-I missed it.
Did you do something?
-That sword's
getting on my nerves.
-Of course.
That sword of his.
-Ah, do you remember at last?
-That weapon.
It's yours, right?
-Whose else could it be?
-A-ha!
But there's a big
difference between knowing
and being absolutely certain.
-Wise words, Guy-sensei.
So simple and yet so
full of profound meaning.
Oh, give me a break.
Do you get this excited
about everything he says?
LEE: Forget it, Tenten.
-I said you had the intelligence
of a subhuman beast,
but a beast could run
circles around your brain.
Let's go.
Dynamic Action!
-It's time you came
with me, Naruto.
-Me first.
A shadow clone.
-Rasengan!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Another shadow clone.
-What the-- Sakura?
Granny?
Sakura.
Are you-- I--
-Attack!
-Water Clone Jutsu!
-Watch out.
-Water Prison Jutsu!
-Leave him alone, you swine!
Lee!
Neji!
Tenten!
No.
-Kakashi-sensei!
What's going on here?
What is this?
[theme music]
WOMAN: Greetings,
kids of all ages,
and welcome to the
Kisame Shark Tank Show.
We've got a really
exciting show for you
today, as Guy-sensei
and his team
go up against five ruthless
predators of the deep.
Now, before we get
started, we ask
those seated in
the front rows who
don't want to get wet to please
move to the seats farthest away
from the tank.
OK, kids.
Here we go!
Now, all together.
1, 2, 3!
ALL: Watch out for that shark!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next time.
Naruto's Growth!
[theme music]
LEE: Notable People
of the Leaf Village,
where you meet our most
popular personalities!
Today, our guest is a
personal hero of mine.
That passionate warrior
and teacher, Guy-sensei!
GUY: Dynamic Entry!
Greetings.
Yes, it's me, the Noble
Blue Beast of the Leaf.
It's Might Guy!
-First question, Guy-sensei!
What is the power of youth?
GUY: One part talent,
two part sweat and tears,
a dash of passion.
That is the
indescribable ecstasy
I call the power of youth!
-And just how much
is a dash, exactly?
GUY: It also helps to
have a worthy opponent.
A rival you can compete against.
LEE: Like you and
Kakashi-sensei.
GUY: Exactly.
We're eternal rivals,
perfectly. matched.
Well, not quite.
I have 51 wins,
and he has only 50!
LEE: That you can beat him
is an inspiration to me.
Like a mighty flame
burning inside of me!
-Let it burn!
-To the power of youth!
-Hot.
Hot.
Hot!