There we go.
Right.
Storage is now complete!
I'll be returning Naruto-boy
to the Hidden Leaf.
And then we'll have to
find the octopus.
The time has come! Just
like Giant Gramps Sage
prophesied. I'm going
to go look for an octopus
and train to control the
Nine-Tails' power.
And meet Sasuke once
again.
Naruto, are
you--oof!
Now, my young
one, time to go!
"The Young Man and the
Sea"
Whoa! Check it out,
it's the ocean!
Yeah! Nothin' like
the salt air.
This is the Land of
Fire's one and only
port.
From here, we depart for
the Hidden Cloud Village
in the Land of Lightning.
So uhh... What's this
top secret mission that
Granny Tsunade was
talking about?
It's called a top secret
mission because it's
secret, Naruto.
Aw, come on! What's the
big deal-you can tell me!
I won't blab, I promise!
You'll be filled in
later.
Boo.
Oh, boy. I guess
Yamato hasn't come up
with a good cover story
yet.
Lady Tsunade? Why did
you assign Naruto an
S-rank mission at such
a critical time?
And as if that weren't
risky enough, you sent
him to the Land of
Lightning by Sea!
Oink.
Yes. But with the
Akatsuki still aiming
for him...
I decided a long and
arduous voyage at sea,
would be just the
thing to throw his
pursuers off the
scent.
And then to the Hidden
Cloud Village in the Land
of Lightning. What will
he be doing there?
I'll leave that up to
the Raikage to decide.
Wow!!!
That's a first rate
ship you lined up for us!
Actually... The ship
the Hidden Leaf arranged
for us is the next one
over.
Yeah, it's the smaller
one over there.
Huh?
Aww...
that tub?
Well, we are on a top
secret mission. A big
ship would attract
attention, right?
This one'll be perfect
for our trip to the
island. More low key.
Doesn't look like
there's anyone on
board. When's the
crew showin' up?
About that... They
refused to set sail
into the open sea.
What?? Why the heck
did they say that? You
didn't try to low ball
them, did ya?!
No, it's not that...
Well...
Go on, tell me. I
won't get upset.
'Kay... they said
something about a
huge monster?
A creature attacking
anything that attempts
to set sail.
A monster?
Aw, man. Looks like
I drew the short
straw on this one.
Don't know what we'll
run into, but whatever
it is, I'm gonna crush
it into bits.
Hahahaha!
I don't think Guy
should be making any
promises,
we don't even know
what kind of monster
we're dealing with yet.
Ah Guy-Sensei'll be
fine. Look at him!
He's already warming up
he's so pumped!
[groaning]
Guy, you sure you're
doing alright?
Wh-what are you kidding,
this is nothing.
I just didn't know the
boat was going to sway
so much.
My stomach's a little
off, but I assure you
it's only temporary.
How are you supposed to
crush a monster in that
condition?
Please! I may not look
it, but when the time
comes-- [heaving]
Well, we're in the
open sea, now.
[gagging]
I--I don't
see anything.
Damn monster! It must
have spotted the Leaf's
Burning Hurricane and
turned tail!
[gasping]
Muh-muh-monster!!
Hold on, is that a
sword?!
Some type of Summoning
Animal?
How though? I don't
sense a jutsu user
nearby...
Could it be a Wild
Summoning Animal?
It's doubling back!
Get clear!
Not enough time!
[gasping]
You stay back, Aoba!
I'll stop it!
Guy! behind you!
What?!
Awwwwoooooooo!
[gasping]
Huh?
I'm not gonna make it!
I gotcha!! You damned
monster!
Huh?
Ahhhhh!
That was a pretty
reckless move ya pulled
there!
My name's Yusuke. Thanks
for the help. Who are you
and how the hell are you
standing on the ocean?!
Well, I'm Naruto, a
Ninja from the Hidden
Leaf Village.
Now, why don't you
leave the rest to me?
Uh? Huh?
Ah! I can't make
signs like this!
Aaaaaahhhhh!
Wood Style! Giant
Forest!
[grunting]
It's gonna pull you
in! Release the jutsu!
Quickly now Naruto, take
him and go!
Scattering Crow Jutsu!
I don't get it. Why
would there be a summoning
animal in a spot like that?
Hard to say. It could be
it survived the Third
Great Ninja War, I
guess.
Well at least now we know
why everyone working this
port is so scared.
That thing has been
living around these parts
for about 15 years now.
I see.
Normally when its ninja
summoner has fallen, an
animal will return to its
own world.
So what's the deal
then, why is this one
acting up?
Maybe it doesn't know
that its war has ended,
following its orders even
after its summoner is gone.
Yeah.
Your ninja wars have
never been anything
but a nuisance.
Because of that damned
monstrosity, every coward
in town refuses to go to
sea anymore.
They're not cowards,
they're being smart. What
were you thinking doing
something so dangerous?
A fisherman's job
is to catch fish.
I thought I was gonna get
rid of him once and for all.
Only to have you interfere.
If I hadn't interfered,
you'd be fish food by now.
Hmph.
Seriously, just leave
that thing to us. It
was reckless of you
to get involved.
Shut up already. If
anyone beats that thing,
it's gonna be me!
Mm.
I'm not asking for all
that much.
If I only had a sturdier
boat that could withstand
that stupid marlin's body
blows,
I might have
a chance.
And I could probably use
an internal-combustion
engine too, to match that
thing's power.
And maybe some sort of
super strong fishing rod
with a good lure that
won't snap on me!
Actually, that's
asking a lot.
Hmph!
Tell me. How come you're
so determined to get that
marlin?
Is that your dad?
I'm dead serious about
fighting that fish. Anyone
who'd give in so easily...
... Is no real
father or son!
[grunting]
[gasping]
Captain Yamato, isn't
there anything we can
do?!
Like what?
I dunno, like lending the
guy a hand? Yusuke should
be able to avenge his dad!
Come on! We can't
just stand by and
do nothing!
You're in the middle of
an S-rank mission, Naruto--
The boy's passion has
moved me to tears,
Yamato!
Let's give this fellah
a helping hand! Come
on, man, if you will,
so will I!!
As long as that
monster's out there, we
can't set sail. Kinda
have to deal with it.
Ya see? Anyway, if that
Marlin's a summoning
animal, then shinobi
like us are to blame
for all that poor
guy's misfortune.
Mm-hmm. And as far as
we can tell, that creature
isn't here because it wants
to be.
All right. All right,
you guys have convinced
me. [chuckling]
All right!
Huh?
Yusuke!
We got ya a
fishin' rod, too!
Naruto...
What do you think? I
designed everything with
that wish list you
rattled off.
No quarrel with the boat
or the rod, but there's
no motor.
Without internal
combustion that can match
the marlin's power, all
this is useless.
Don't worry! You can leave
that to me! You want power?
The Noble Blue Beast
got you covered! I've
got energy to spare!
So what do you say?!
Hmph. I can't believe
you people. You couldn't
mind your own business
if you tried,
could you? You're taking
all the thrill out of
the fight!
Man, that guy
sure is stubborn.
Heads up, giant marlin
spotted 30 degrees to
starboard!
Hey, pull the ship
around in front of him!
Roger that, on the
double!
Stroke! Stroke!
Stroke!
Okay, we're
ahead of it!
All right, I'm going to
release the lure.
Hey! What is that?!
It's a special lure I
built for our oversized
prey.
That's not what I meant.
Why's it have to look
like me?!
Come on. A showboat
like you will make
for the perfect bait!
Nooo! I'm gonna get
eaten!
Pick up the pace!
We have to make it think
this lure is nice and
fresh!
I'm on it!
Eight Inner Gates! Second
Gate of Rest!
[grunting]
Faster, Bushier
Brow, Sensei!
Fourth Gate, Gate of
Pain, Fifth Gate, Gate
of Closing, Open!
Open! Open! Open!
Come on... come on...
Come on!
Huhh?!
Bullseye!
Well, it looks like my
bait did the trick,
doesn't it?!
Huh?!
That hurts
my heart.
Yusuke, come on,
we have to reel
it in!
What're you, stupid?
If we do that, the
line'll just snap!
We'll let it play and
wait until it tires out.
At this rate, we're
gonna run out of line!
I know that. I'm gonna
let it pull the boat. You
think you can keep up
with it?!
Nothing on earth is
impossible for me!
Aaauuhhhh!!!!
You don't need to row
anymore. Just follow
his lead and steer the
boat now, okay?
Gladly. I think I had
just about reached my
limit.
Yeah, keep going. Use
up all that strength
of yours.
It's got amazing
stamina, keeping this
pace up. I can't believe
how fast it is.
But it will eventually
use up all its energy to
resist. That's when the
real fight begins.
This is it! It's
finally showing signs
of exhaustion.
[grunting]
Yusuke, you okay?
Stay outta my way! I
don't need your help!
This fight is between
him and me!
Don't worry,
I know that.
Here we go. This
time. This time
for sure.
[grunting]
Maybe it's time for
us to step in.
No, don't help him!
Yusuke's gonna avenge
his father with his own
two hands! We can't take
that away from him!
Oh, dear.
Guess we have no
choice. You heard
the man.
[grunting]
All right, a
little more...
Give it up you damn fish!
Ugh!
He still has so much
strength!
[struggling]
Not good!
[gasping]
Yusuke!
Damnnn yooooouuuuu!!!
Heh.
[grunting]
[panting]
You finally did it,
Yusuke. You avenged
your dad.
Yeah.
I still don't get it,
though. Why hasn't the
animal returned to its
home already?
Mmm.
Easy there. I'll get it
out.
This is--
A Demon Wind Shuriken
from the Leaf.
Well, I guess there's
no question, then.
Looks like it was
a victim of the Third
Great Ninja War after
all.
If it's possible,
we'd like to send
the beast home.
Yeah sure, whatever you
want. As far as I'm
concerned, our feud was
settled today.
No grudges on my end.
I can't take it
anymore! Get me
off this ship!
Get a hold of
yourself.
But these waves are
rather hard to take!
Then what do we do?
Get me off!
Please!
It's a little out off
our way, but there should
be an island up ahead!
That's it, we'll stop
there! Set a course,
North by Northeast!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden, The Ninja
of Benisu!
Naruto? What are you
doing here?