It is true that our nations
have never gotten
along in the past.
But we each did what we
had to do to protect our
brethren and our clans.
Perhaps at times we
had no other choice.
And now, today, even
if our Five Nation
Treaty comes to be.
I honestly can't say how
long it will last or even
if we can hold onto it.
But I've got this dream that
at some time in the future
there will come a day when
shinobi will collaborate,
and help each other, with
one heart, regardless
of their affiliation.
That is my dream
of the future.
Seems like our generation no
longer needs to talk about
that dream, 'cause
it's happening right now.
Am I wrong?
No, you're not.
That goes without saying.
However...
If we don't win here,
then it won't come to be!
The Tsuchikage is correct.
Defeat is not an option.
All right!
Let's spread out and
take command, then!
We'll draw out the
Allied Shinobi Forces'
greatest power!
For that is our primary
duty as the Five Kage!
Now go!
[attacking yell]
Sasuke!
I'll synch up!
Incredible...
But what just happened?
Naruto and Sasuke
are attacking as one.
Did they do it?!
You better be prepared.
I'll never let
my comrades die!
No matter what happens!
This is!
Naruto!
Even while you fight, you're
also healing your comrades.
Naruto!
Just focus on what
only you can do!
Leave the healing to me!
You don't
understand, Sakura.
He's doing this
unconsciously.
Huh?
His chakra is acting on its
own, merely from his deep
desire to help Shikamaru.
With my Mind Transmission
Jutsu I can sense it!
Damn it, Naruto.
You're always going
above and beyond, always
sticking your neck out.
You'll go to any
length for us.
Since before the war,
you've never held back or
compromised when
it came to us.
You even made me get off my
butt and stop being lazy.
What a drag...
I'm sorry, Dad.
Naruto doesn't want
me to join you yet.
Shikamaru, stop
talking right now!
I am not going
to let you die!
Naruto!
No, everybody
needs you!
Dad...
I only found out later
that Naruto had persevered
through a ton of
painful and bitter
things all on his own.
And I don't want him
to ever have to go
through that again.
Or at least that's
how I feel when I'm
hanging around him.
I told you once.
Remember, Dad?
He's going to become a
very important shinobi
for this village someday.
I'm sure of it.
When I'm with Naruto.
He makes me want to
follow him to walk by
his side no matter what.
Unlike Lord First, that
dumb Naruto doesn't have
an adept brother like Lord
Second to be his advisor.
Well, then...
That's why, even more so,
I need to stick around
so that I can stand
next to that idiot when
he becomes Hokage.
So I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm afraid I can't join you
on the other side just yet...
Because there's no one
more qualified than
me to be Naruto's advisor.
[chuckle]
Thank you, Naruto!
Your chakra, as well
as the power of your
heart saved him!
He's back!
Thank you, Sakura.
And thank you, Naruto.
Don't go
overboard, Shikamaru.
You just might become
my advisor instead!
[anxious whine]
No need to fret, Akamaru.
That's because a Kage can
have up to three advisors.
I want to stand
beside Naruto, too.
I'll have to work hard!
Shikamaru!
Lady Tsunade!
You did well!
Forgive me, Grandfather.
Don't apologize, Tsuna.
I dragged this mess into
my grandchildren's era.
My cowardice is to blame.
However, your heart and
your dreams have been passed
down even beyond your
grandchildren's era!
Yes...
...your Will of Fire!
[attacking yell]
You get back here!
All right!
Now let's get this giant
tree cut down while he's
distracted by his battle!
No matter how tall or thick
this tree may be, it's still
quite tiny compared to
the great earth itself!
And this earth, this
entire land is on our side!
[eager yell]
Look, I'm begging you!
I don't want us taking
each other down for
vengeance anymore!
Shinobi shouldn't lower
their heads so easily!
Action and power are
the things that a
shinobi should respect!
It seems those who
become Hokage like
prostrating themselves.
But as an act that relays
one's heart, perhaps it can
lead to strength and
be meritorious, too.
Let's go, everyone!
Okay!
That means it's
Double Lariat time,
brother of mine!
As a woman, I mustn't
start late on battle like
I have with marriage!
All right, then!
Let's move out!
[cheering]
[attacking yell]
Come on!
Naruto...
You have truly become a
necessary existence
to this world.
What the two of us
always wanted to be.
And you shall now
save the whole world.
Follow me, everyone!
[cheering]
This should do.
I should get going now.
The springtime of my youth
has not faded just yet!
Tenten! Lee!
Let's go!
-Right!
-Yes!
Your past is filtering
into me through the others.
Naruto Uzumaki, you are
the one who is uniting
everyone right now.
Your tempestuous history
made you who you are.
And your way of life
has brought hope into
everyone's hearts!
For our future!
Come on!
[cheering]
Let's go!
Let's cut down
that giant tree!
Samurai, do not waver!
Now go forth!
We should go, too.
Are you okay,
though, Shikamaru?
Yeah.
Don't worry, I'm
completely recovered now.
But what if that tree
tries to rob us of
our chakra again?
Now we know, we'll
just be careful.
Listen, Fourth, I'm
going to use the link
between your chakra
and Naruto's chakra.
I can't move everyone
simultaneously like you, but
I'll protect them with
my Teleportation Jutsu.
Orochimaru...
Are you just going
to be a spectator?
I have no interest
in this war at all.
But, this dream Obito's
pursuing would ultimately
lead to the elimination of
all of this, my precious
laboratory, so I suppose
that I cannot support it.
Well, then lend a hand!
All right, I shall.
I'll revel just a bit in
nostalgic memories
and in some
student-teacher partnership!
I'll shift to a
more offensive form!
What is it?!
Don't panic!
It's coming!
I'll teleport away
those who seem in danger.
So go forth without fear!
It's the voice
of Lord Second!
We can give it
our all, then.
-That's because--
-But still, don't get
careless, all right?
With two 100 Healings
adepts, we can likely summon
a tenth of Katsuyu's
actual body here from
Shikkotsu Woods!
We'll mold her into the
Allied Force's footing, a
Healing Area where one
can be restored just
by standing on her.
Are you ready, Sakura?
Yes!
Summoning Jutsu!
Ino!
Have you told everyone?
Yes!
Huh?
What is that going to do?!
Is this it?!
This way, we can
fight without our
chakra being stolen!
Oh, this is simply great!
So this is the
Healing Area?!
Now that you get it,
quit playing around
and get going!
Where's Naruto?
Damn it, he really is fast!
But I'm starting to
sense him better and better!
Right there!
It's about time
for you to sleep.
Now I'll guide
you into the dream.
There's no time left!
Obito...
I bet that you really
did want to confirm...
[roar]
...whether a heart that
never bends and a Will of
Fire that does not
waver, no matter what,
are truly possible.
You gave up on them once...
But after fighting Naruto
and hearing his words.
I think you've stopped being
able to deny, deep down,
that they might
really exist after all.
Isn't that right, Obito?
And yet you still search and
test everyone and everything
in an attempt to
prove yourself wrong.
Which is why even
now, as you stand
at the precipice.
What's that?!
[screaming]
What happened just now?!
Naruto and Sasuke are--!
Wait!
You keep pushing Naruto,
trying to get your answer.
Why do you get up?!
And what exactly are you
fighting for, anyway?!
For your comrades?
Or do you fight
for this world?
Listen...
Comrades
eventually betray you.
And this world
transforms love into hatred.
You should know!
You've experienced it!
The people of the Leaf
and Sasuke betrayed
you in the past...
...and Jiraiya's love
conferred hate upon you.
You and I are both the same.
Cumulating anguish and pain
will change you in time.
And very soon, even
more pain and suffering
shall assault you.
How can you claim you will
never change because of it?!
You don't know when comrades
might betray you again.
Or if the Allied
Forces will go back to
fighting each other.
You don't even know if you
can defeat me right now!
There should be no
reason to keep fighting
for a world like this.
No matter, it's coming to
an end in a few minutes.
So why do you
keep on fighting?!
Because it's my Ninja Way.
No matter what, I
never go back on my word!
That is and always
will be my Ninja Way.
I thought I told
you to go to sleep.
Let's end it with
our next move, Naruto.
Yeah!
We'll sleep tomorrow and
we'll dream our own dreams!
Obito, when people see
someone trying twice as hard
as others, they
instinctively start
wanting to lend a hand.
That's because people
eventually learn that they
only have each other to fill
the holes in their hearts.
And he who possesses a heart
filled with comrades...
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "A Heart Filled
with Comrades."
...is truly powerful!