Massive Rasengan!!!!
[gasp]
[growl]
Wahhh!
[thinking]
So fast!
[snarl] Do you
really think that
you can beat me?
Yeah! Of course
I do! That's why
I undid the seal.
And besides...
Gotcha!
Arggghh!
[angry snarl]
Wind Style:
Rasen Shuriken!
Now hurry!
[struggling grunts]
You bastard!
[growling]
[Thinking]
He's weakening!
Now's my chance!
[grunt]
(Dark Naruto)
Hate you...! It
hurts... Wanna
kill you!
Huh?
(Ghostly Voices)
I hate you! This hurts!
I just wanna kill you!
[moaning]
(Ghostly Voices)
You'll never have
the respect you
desire!
Those voices...
What is this?
(Thinking)
No. This is bad.
Don't give in, Naruto!
Fool! Ya fool!
[gasp]
Just give up! You
will never be able
to control my power!
You are only a
tiny little piece
of my hatred!
[heavy breathing]
(Ghostly Voices)
[moaning]
Just shut up!
The Nine Tail's
hatred is even
greater than I
imagined...
Yo! This is bad
for real, it is
quite the ordeal!
I can stop him!
[struggling]
Go away! And don't
...come... back!
(Woman's Voice)
No, it's alright.
You can stay here.
[gasp]
Naruto...
What is this?
Who are you?
Where did you
come from?
Wait... how do
you know my
name, anyway!?
Oh! Right. You
don't know yet...
Well then, why
don't you try to
guess who I am,
Naruto.
[gasp]
[giggle]
Don't tell me...
You figured
it out, huh!?
Yeah, you bet!
You're the Nine
Tail's true form!
Huh??
[laughter]
Oh man! That sure
is one scary laugh!
You're tryin' to
trick me by taking
that form, huh!?
Wrong, ya know!
[painful shouts]
Huh? You said,
"you know."
[giggle] Sorry!
I just couldn't
help myself!
(Woman)
I was born impatient, so,
I talk fast. and sometimes
weird expressions come out!
I try to control
it, but I slip
up, like when
I'm excited.
But let's talk
about you!
I really hope you
didn't end up with
any of the weird
quirks that I have!
Then...
That Minato! He
didn't say
anything to you?
[giggle] Shame
on him!
Anyway. That's
right! I'm your-
[happy sigh]
I've wanted... I've
wanted to meet you
for so long now, mom!
You know?
You just said,
"you know..."
There's no doubt
you're my child.
The Nine Tail's
transformation
stopped!
But how!? What did
you do, Yamato?
Nothing! It seems
like it just stopped
on it's own.
[thinking]
What happened?
Where to start!?
There's so much that
I wanna ask you!
You can ask
me anything!
But first things
first... we need
to tame the Nine
Tails.
[struggling grunts]
[angry roar]
What is this
chakra!?
Kushina..?!
Minato embedded my
chakra into the
sealing formula.
So I'd appear when
you try to gain
control over the
Nine Tails' power.
That way, I
could lend
you a hand!
[gleefull giggle]
Are you even
listening?!
I can't get over
how beautiful
you are, mom!
Oh! Thank you!
You know, you have
your father's hair,
but it looks to me
like you got my face.
I'm sorry about
that, Naruto!
Why sorry? I mean,
if I got my good looks
from you, that just means
that I'm handsome, right?
Actually, if I could
have it my way, I'd even
wish I'd gotten your red
hair, too! It's awesome!
[giggle] Which means
that you're now only
the second man who's ever
complimented my hair.
I am? Seriously?
So, who was the
first one, then?
[chuckle] Who do
you think? It was
your father, silly!
Ohh! Right! That
makes sense!
What is it...?
Hey, can I tell
you something'?
There's always been one
thing that I really wanted
to ask if I ever got the
chance to meet you...
Just how did you
and dad meet and
fall in love anyway?
[gasp]...[giggle]
Well, it's a bit
embarrassing, you know!
Hey! You just said,
"you know!" I guess
you're excited!
This whole experience
has me all kinds of
shaken up, you know!?
You said it again!
[laughing]
[chuckle]
Let's see...
(Kushina)
It was the first day of
school after I had moved
to the Hidden Leaf Village.
Your father and I
were both still
little kids when
we met.
Alright! We have a
new transfer student
joining our academy
today!
I'm Kushina
Uzumaki, you
know!?
Do you guys see
the color of her
hair!?
Yeah! Who would
ever want hair
like that! Ha ha!
(Students)
[laughing]
That's enough! Be quiet
everyone! Settle down now!
I'm gonna... I'm
going to become the
first female Hokage of
the Hidden Leaf Village!
Me too! I wanna
become a great
Hokage the whole
village respects!
A Hokage that's
respected by everyone
in the Village, huh.
My first impression of
your dad was that he
wasn't very manly or
dependable...
So I didn't take him very
seriously or believe for a
minute that he could
actually become Hokage.
Why not? Dad seemed
really powerful to
me...
Yes,  you're right.
But back then I was
young, and I was
simply too ignorant to
recognize the truth.
[giggle]
Hm?
It's pretty snotty to declare
that you're going to become
Hokage after just moving from
another village, doncha think?
So, after that, all
the boys in class
began to tease me.
And they gave me
a mean nickname.
Tomato!
From now on, your
new name's "Tomato!"
With that chubby round
face of yours, and your
read hair, you look
just like one!
No Tomato's ever
going to become
Hokage, and besides,
I hate tomatoes!
Me too! I always
pick em outta my
salad!
A bright red tomato
that everybody hates
is never gonna be
accepted as Hokage!
[laughter]
Wait, I know!
I bet that dad stepped
in and totally put a
stop to those bullies
who were picking on you!
That's what happened,
right!?
Oh no! You couldn't
be more wrong about
that!
(Kushina)
Tomato... I grudgingly
accepted being called
that name...
It was embarrassing,
but it was pretty
accurate...
Look! Ha ha!
You're getting
redder and riper!
It looks like it's
harvesting time at
the tomato festival!
Who are you
callin' "Tomato?!"
Now you listen to
me... I hate tomatoes
just as much as you,
ya know!?
Ow ow!
Arrghhhhh!!
Ooof!
That's it! You keep
on calling me "Tomato"
and you'll keep getting
more of this, ya know!?
And what are
YOU looking at!?
Anytime a bully called me
"Tomato" I beat them at their
own game! I turned them into
SMASHED tomatoes!
[nervous laugh]
I was the girl with
the long red hair
who beat the boys
that dared to cross me!
That's how I earned
a new nickname for
myself...
They called me...
The Red-Hot Habanero!
[gulp]
Now I know why Kiba and
Shikamaru always say that
moms can be really scary...
I was always
fighting everyone...
Naturally, the Red-Hot
Habenero won all those
fights, but still...
Heh.
[gasp]
Alright, fess up!
Are you the one
who's been making
my kid brother cry?
It's only because
he's always messing
with me, ya know!?
And because he's
such a wimp!
[gasp]
Uh...
I made Genin!
Cool, huh?
Uhh...
If anyone bullies my
kid brother, then I
get to teach them a
little lesson in manners.
Hmf!
[grunt]
[thinking]
A real kunai?
Huh?
[gasp]
[gasp] Argh!
Oof!
Ahhh!
You can't recognize
a Substitution
Jutsu? You're only
a little kid!
Boy, that is some
red hair... and
it's as stiff as
straw!
I don't think i've
ever seen anything
so ugly!
Heh heh heh!
Serves you right!
[surprised gasp]
I hate my hair,
too. Are you
happy now!?
Leave me alone.
Let go!!
[grunts]
[struggling grunts]
[gasp]
Ow! Oof!
Guhhhh...
But still...!
You know, this
hair's a part
of me! I can't
change that!
...It's just me!
Ahhh! It't the
Red-Hot Habenero!
Outsider!
[gasp]
As if an outsider
like you could ever
become Hokage!
[gasp]
You didn't want to
help me, because I'm
an outsider, huh!?
[gasp]... no,
that's not it!
I bet you agree
with them attacking
me, too! [angry sob]
[small sobbing]
[thinking]
It's because I
don't want to be
an outsider...
...it's because I
want this Village to
be my home! That's
why I said that.
Who'd wanna be
Hokage, anyway!?
Back then, I
used to hate
my hair...
But then, there was a
certain incident that
completely changed the
way I felt about it.
What happened?
(Young Kushina)
I'm home!
I'm home...!
Anyone here?
Where is everyone?
Huh?
[gasp]
Someone! Help!
(Young Kushina)
[screams]
(Kushina)
I have a special
kind of chakra...
...and because
of that, agents
of the Hidden Cloud
kidnapped me.
[gasp]
Hey...!
I knew I had to do
something. In order to
leave a trail behind while
I was being led away...
I pulled out strands
of my hair and dropped
them carefully, so the
enemy wouldn't notice.
However, since I was an
outsider, new to the Village, I
didn't hold out much hope that
anyone would come to rescue me.
Before long, we'd almost
reached the boarder, And
I thought I was done for.
[grunt]
-Huh?
[grunts]
Are you okay?
[weak sigh]
I came to
rescue you.
[happy sigh]
[gasp]
Everything's
gonna be fine!
Hey! Wait!
Wha...?
(Young Kushina)
That's...
Your hair's beautiful.
So I noticed it right
away.
Then how come
you're always
ignoring me?
It's because I know
that you can take care
of yourself. And I
Know that you're strong.
Both in body,
and in spirit.
But still, this
isn't your fight,
it's a fight
between villages.
It's different
than all your
other battles.
So I came.
...Why?
Simple. Because
I didn't want
to lose you...
But, I'm an
outsider...
No, you're not.
You live in the Hidden
Leaf Village. That means
no matter where you came
from, you're one of us!
(Kushina)
From that moment on,
Minato was a great
ninja in my eyes.
I realized he could
make all my dreams
come true.
He changed me.
The red hair that I used
to hate and that gave me
so much trouble, had this
time brought me love.
It became the
red thread of
fate,
Since then, I've
liked my hair!
And, most of all...
I fell in love with
Minato.
[gleeful chuckle]
There are certain precious
words... that I only bestow
on the men who compliment
my hair...
Naruto, will you
accept them?
Uh huh!
I love you...
[gasp]
[happy sigh]
I wonder what happens
when you put the Yellow
Flash of the Leaf and the
Red-Hot Habenero together.
Hee hee hee...
Then you get the
Hidden Leaf's
Orange Hokage!
Naruto! That's
so cool, you know?
[pleased chuckle]
Hokage...
Your dream is the
continuation of
the dreams Minato
and I shared.
Yeah! And I won't
ever let your
dreams down, no
matter what!
Thanks, Naruto.
But first, I have
something to do.
Hm.
(Nine Tails)
[roaring]
(Kushina)
Naruto, listen
closely. We're
out of time.
(Naruto)
What do you mean
out of time?
(Kushina)
I need to tell you the
reason why Nine Tails
was sealed inside you.
(Kushina)
It's about the incident
sixteen years ago...
(Naruto)
Sixteen years ago?
(Kushina)
That's right. It was on
October 10th, sixteen years
ago, the day you were born.
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Target-
Nine Tails."
(Naruto)
What happened!?