[running footsteps]
-Well, they sure
haven't been here yet.
-Not yet.
We should set up a
perimeter and keep watch.
-Argh.
-I don't know anything.
And I couldn't tell
you, even if I did.
-No use.
What do we do with him?
-Ahh!
-Let's let Ibiki squeeze
some answers out of him.
-I can't find any sign of
the Akatsuki in this place.
-No, same here.
It doesn't look like anyone's
been through this place
for days.
If they're coming,
they haven't come yet.
-So what now, Aoba?
[choking]
-Well, there haven't been
any requests for backup
from the units sent to the
other four collection offices.
-Meaning none of them has
made contact with the Akatsuki
yet, either.
-Unless one of them is in the
middle of a fight right now.
-Oh.
-Oh, I wouldn't worry.
Especially not if
it's Asuma's team
that's made contact with them.
You guys know better than
anyone what a tough old warrior
Asuma is.
-We certainly do.
-Yeah.
And he's got Shikamaru with him.
-All right.
Let's get out of here and
figure out what our strategy is.
-Hmm.
-Let's go.
[soft grunt]
-First of all, let's go over
everything we know so far.
The Akatsuki are headed for
one of five collection offices,
and there's been
no call for backup
from the other four teams.
And it's clear they haven't
been anywhere near this one yet.
-Which means that they're--
-Mmm.
-Yeah, you've got a point.
There's always a chance that the
Akatsuki are still on their way here.
-So we wait, then.
And when they show
up, we strike.
Got it?
[eagle cry]
-I want a man covering
every possible approach
the enemy might use.
So, like we discussed, fan
out, take up your positions,
and wait.
-Right.
-Where the hell
are the Akatsuki?
[theme music - in japanese]
[birds calling]
-Kakazu.
It took you long enough.
[grunting]
[knives clashing]
-Way too slow.
-That's one of them down.
-Hmm.
-Ow.
That hurts.
Who are you people?
-What the hell?
We both hit his vital spots.
-Quit sticking it in like that.
I said knock it off.
That hurts.
-What is this?
Is he immortal?
-Isn't that obvious, you fool?
Now, then.
Once again.
Who are you people?
[grunt]
-That symbol.
That's from the Guardian
Shinobi something-or-other.
Oh, terrific.
Looks like I'm going
to have to go back
into that stinky
collection office.
Awww.
-(VOICEOVER) Chiriku.
-Hmm.
We are Shinobi of
the Leaf village.
Our orders are to capture
or eliminate you Akatsuki.
We already know you
usually operate in pairs.
My original idea was
to take down one of you
first, then capture the other.
But I guess that plan's
going to have to change.
-(VOICEOVER) So he's one
of the Akatsuki, huh?
His powers are incredible.
My Shadow Stitching is
not going to be enough.
[laughter]
-Not your lucky day.
I'm afraid you chose the
wrong one of us to start with.
-Your partner.
Where is he?
[gulp]
-I'm free of his jutsu.
-Hmm?
-Kotetsu.
Izumo.
Retreat!
-That fellow in front.
Well, well.
For once, you
struck gold, Hidan.
-Kakazu.
Just stay out of
this, all right?
I want these three
for my ritual.
You can have them after.
-(VOICEOVER) Kakazu, huh?
And Hidan.
-Very well.
But don't get careless,
or you're dead.
-Not that again.
Knock it off, will you?
Believe me, I wish
someone would kill me.
But that's not possible.
-(VOICEOVER) What's he
doing with that diagram?
-I'll attack alone.
Try to trap Mr. Immortal
with your Shadow Stitching.
Capture him, even if
it's only for an instant.
That's all the time I'll
need to take his head off.
-This kind of move
is crazy risky.
It's not like you.
-I'll go in with you.
-Don't you guys get it?
It's the only move we've got!
[gulp]
-(VOICEOVER) I've never
seen Asuma like this.
-Look.
These two are
stronger than I am.
Izumo and Kotetsu.
You two will provide
Shikamaru with backup
against the other Akatsuki.
-Now that we have an idea
of the enemy's strength,
wouldn't it be better for
us to fall back and regroup?
-You think they're going
to let us just turn around
and walk away?
If we don't stand and
fight them right now,
we'll be slaughtered.
And the Leaf village will
be in even greater danger.
To penetrate the enemy's
line, sometimes you
have to risk a bold move.
-But I thought you always
hated risky moves like that.
just like me.
-To defend your King
from a superior opponent,
one must make some sacrifices.
-(VOICEOVER) He's not seriously
thinking of sacrificing
himself, is he?
One of these guys has
untold powers and abilities.
The other is immortal.
It's true, we don't stand
much of a chance, but still.
For Asuma to make himself
a sacrificial piece?
-Shogi?
But it's such a drag.
-I know you're a lazy
bones, Shikamaru.
But that's what makes
you so good at thinking
of clever stratagems to get
around trouble or hard work.
-Mmm.
-You see, Shogi is a game
of countless variations,
all determined by
how you utilize
the characteristics of
the individual pieces.
It's a perfect game
for someone like you,
who's always trying to
out-think the other guy.
This book will give you
all the basic rules.
The rest you'll
learn as you play.
-What a pain.
Give me 10 minutes,
and I'll have it down.
-You-- you beat me.
-You know, you don't
have to go easy on me.
Really.
-You went with the
Climbing Silver.
-It's a move from the book.
You use an advance unit to break
through your opponent's lines.
-Heh, heh.
-You're not upset because
you lost the game, are you?
-No.
Sacrificing your
vanguard in order
to make a
breakthrough-- it's just
the sort of logical shortcut
I'd expect from you,
but I can't say that
I like it very much.
-Hey, it's just a game.
-I suppose, but the
Climbing Silver,
while it may break
the enemy's line,
ends with you
sacrificing your piece.
Inflicting damage
on your opponent
is certainly one of the
objects of the game,
but to throw away your
own man on a risky gambit?
Frankly, that worries
me a little bit.
-Mm-hmm.
-You know, I'm not nearly as
logical as you think I am.
-Ha ha.
-Want to play again?
This time, I'll go
nice and slow, OK?
And no more Climbing Silver.
-(VOICEOVER) You sacrifice
a piece only when
your opponent's so powerful
that you have no other option.
But which piece
do you sacrifice?
We three Chunin
aren't strong enough
to make such a move worthwhile.
On the contrary, Asuma would be
at an even greater disadvantage
having to fight them
while worrying about us.
He's right.
We'd all be slaughtered.
What's the best move then?
Our opponent has major
pieces on the board.
In order to capture
a major piece,
you need to dry him
out by baiting a trap.
But the bait has to
be tempting enough
to make him take the risk.
We're not strong enough,
not tempting enough,
to act as bait.
We can only fight with
the pieces we've got.
-Climbing Silver.
It's not a role that suits you.
-Heh.
Don't sweat it.
I'm not going to be
the sacrificial piece.
I've got you with me, after all.
-(VOICEOVER) Ugh.
I can't attack the major pieces.
And I'm useless as bait.
Well, I can try and
distract them, I guess.
-Have you finished strategizing?
Oh, that really hurts.
What pests you are,
poking me right and left.
[gulp]
-They gods shall
punish those who
don't understand
the pain of others.
Ha.
-Mmm.
-That's a nifty little
weapon you've got there.
-Asuma!
-Come on.
Get to him.
-(VOICEOVER) Hmm.
I don't want to
get caught by that.
-(VOICEOVER) I'll just
keep on coming at you.
-Grr!
-(VOICEOVER) Yes.
That's it, Shikamaru.
As long as he has to
fight while watching out
for your Shadow Stitching,
it lessens his advantage.
-Damn it.
-(VOICEOVER) It's working.
My Shadow Stitching is
throwing him off enough
to give Asuma a chance.
But what if this whole
gambit's a mistake?
I mean, what's the point of
gaining the advantage when
you're fighting against
a guy who's immortal?
When we've got limited
chakra and only one life.
Oh, well.
It's too late to
think about it now.
This fight doesn't really
start 'til I grab him.
-No, you don't.
-Oh, no.
-Hmm?
-There's that stance again.
[singing voices]
-Ahhh!
-Yes. Chiriku's jutsu.
Of course, Chiriku is better
at it than I am, but--
-Ahhhh.
-Hidan.
Don't underestimate them.
-You stay out of it.
Just keep your mouth and watch.
-Yeah. Nice move.
-(VOICEOVER) The two of them
are acting in perfect sync.
-(VOICEOVER) So far, the other
guy really is staying out
of it.
But we can't depend on him
to stay out of it forever.
-You almost got him
that time, Shikamaru.
Keep at it.
-All right. Listen up.
-Hmm?
-I may need you guys
to back me up, OK?
-Ha.
It's always the way
with you nonbelievers.
You're so desperate
to escape your fate,
you choose the obvious
line of attack.
You're so transparent.
-You play around too much
when you fight, you know that?
-Now!
You've got nowhere
to run this time.
-Then I won't run.
-Immortal jerk.
-I guess I'll just take
care of the weak ones first.
[gasp]
-No! Leave them alone.
It's me you want!
-Captain Asuma!
[grunting]
-(VOICEOVER) All right.
If targeted attacks aren't
going to be effective--
-Ha ha ha ha.
-Burning Ash!
-Huh.
-(VOICEOVER) What's he doing?
He's not moving.
[theme music - in japanese]
-What's going on?
-I don't get it.
He's the one who was
nailed by the jutsu.
Why's the captain-- Oh, no.
Don't tell me--
-What?
What is it, Shikamaru?
-I don't know exactly
how the guy's done it,
but it looks to me like
his and Asuma's bodies
are connected somehow.
-What?
Connected?
What does that mean?
-Next time.
The Judgment.