[theme music]
-Good.
You're awake.
-Hm?
Great Lord Elder?
-I thought your life would be in
danger if I left you like that.
-I'm beholden to you.
-Can't wait even though
you're still ailing.
-This actually helps
me heal faster.
But tell me, what of the boy?
-Naruto's presently
speaking with the real Pain.
-Hm?
Speaking with Pain?
-The two children of prophecy
have come face to face.
How will they settle
this, I wonder.
-I need to hear your stories.
Then I'll give you
my final response.
-Very well.
We'll tell you everything
about our Pain.
-Nagato.
It's a waste of time.
Just deal with him now.
-Wait, Konan.
I want to hear the
response he comes up with.
Besides, I doubt I could
take him down too easily.
After all, he did
crush the six Pains
and make it here all by himself.
Two moments define
my greatest pain.
The first of these was
the death of my parents.
The Hidden Rain village had been
caught up in the great nations'
war and became a battlefield.
MAN: Found anything yet?
MAN: Yeah, some canned food.
Our first meal in four days.
MAN: No, three days.
MAN: Whatever.
Let's just eat.
I'm starving here.
MAN: We should search the
rest of this place afterward.
We might find more stuff.
-Let's get outside,
while they're distracted.
-But what if they
see us, father?
I'm scared.
-Don't worry, now.
Let's just go and
be completely quiet.
MAN: Man, that's good.
-Who's there?
Damn.
enemies!
-Run now.
Get out of here!
-Nagato.
Go!
Nagato.
Hurry.
Run.
-Run, Nagato!
Run, and don't look back.
Hurry!
-He-- He's just a kid.
-Oh no.
These people weren't shinobi!
-What do we do?
How did this happen?
How could we mistake
them for the enemy?
Damn it.
We didn't know.
We didn't have any idea
that there were still
any civilians left out
here in the war zone.
I'm so sorry, kid.
-What is-- What happened here?
Father?
Mother?
Oh no.
[scream]
-My parents died all
because of the shinobi war
that your Hidden Leaf started.
I have never forgotten the
searing pain of that moment.
I've endured it
to this very day.
That pain transformed
into hate, but it also
brought my powers into bloom.
It was only much
later that I realized
that I was the one who
killed those two Leaf ninja.
-Well mother.
Well, father.
Goodbye now.
NAGATO: Food was so scarce, I
was forced to leave my home.
-That's the last of it.
YOUNG NAGATO: I'm
too hungry to walk.
-Thank you.
If you hadn't just woken me
up, I'd probably be dead.
I'm sorry.
You shouldn't be following me.
I have nothing to give you.
I don't have anything
to eat for either of us.
Excuse me, do you have anything
to eat you could share with me?
I-- Thank you.
It's just been so long
since I've eaten anything.
-I'm sorry, son, but I've got
nothing I can give to you.
These times are tough.
We barely have enough
for ourselves right now.
I'm very sorry.
Try somewhere else.
-But this was my last stop.
Let's go.
[whimpering]
YOUNG NAGATO (VOICEOVER):
I can't go any farther.
Am I going to die here?
-Go on.
Eat this.
-Really?
-Mm-hm.
[whimpering]
-Here.
But eat slowly.
-Konan, who are
these two, anyway?
-Sorry, but he was almost dead.
-And a dog, to boot?
What's your name?
-Chibi.
-Boy, you sure
have a weird name.
Chibi?
-Not me.
That's the dog's name.
-And that's how we met.
How I was introduced to Konan,
and also to a boy named Yahiko.
They were war orphans just like
I was, but they were strong,
and they were fighting
desperately to stay alive.
And so, with nowhere else
to turn, I joined them.
-Wow.
There's so much food here.
-If you're gonna
stay with us, then I
expect you to help find
provisions too, small fry.
-OK.
But how?
-We steal.
YOUNG NAGATO: You steal?
But isn't that wrong?
-Don't be ridiculous.
These are hard times.
We gotta fend for ourselves
by any means necessary.
Naive ideals won't cut it.
-No, you're right.
-We'll do whatever
it takes to live,
even if that means
we have to steal.
Got it?
-I understand.
Could you please give
us some food, sir?
-Just a little will do.
-Please help us out.
-I'm not just gonna
hand out fish for free.
Go on, scram.
-Stingy bastard.
-Hey, you, watch your
tongue, you rotten brat.
-Wha-- Hey, you.
Come back here, you mutt!
Stop!
That's just great.
Hey!
Drop that!
You kids.
I'll find out!
-Good dog.
-Score.
-If you're not buying,
then get out of here.
-Ow.
Uh oh.
-Ignorant kids.
And next time, you're not
gonna get off so easily.
Hmph.
NAGATO: There was no
system for helping orphans
in that small,
chaos-ridden nation.
Thievery became the only
way for us to survive.
We had no other choice.
But even under such
harsh circumstances,
Yahiko never abandoned hope.
Yahiko was always optimistic.
-You guys OK?
Listen, don't feel
too bad, all right?
These things just
sometimes happen.
NAGATO: I guess.
-Nagato.
Tell me.
Do you have any dreams?
-A dream?
-Sure not gonna live in
a dump like this forever.
I got big dreams
to make come true.
-Huh?
-World domination!
-World domination?
What?
Seriously?
-You better believe it.
Once I rule the
world, we'll never
have to go through this
kind of suffering again.
-Yeah, that'd be nice.
-And, if I die like this without
trying to reach my goals,
then my mom and dad's soul
will never rest in peace.
Ain't that right, Konan?
-Mm-hm.
-If we rule the world, then we
can do whatever we want to do.
-You know, you're right.
It'd be just like
we were all gods.
Think we could get
rid of war, too?
-Everyone OK?
Dammit.
Not now.
-Battling shinobi
right on top of us.
Hanzo against Hidden Leaf ninja.
-It was Jiraiya-sensei
and his two teammates
that were fighting.
The three who would become
known as the legendary Sannin
of the Leaf.
Their opponent was Hanzo,
leader of the Hidden Rain.
The battle was
extremely intense, and--
YOUNG NAGATO: Chibi!
Chibi!
-Yahiko, what do we do?
Chibi's not breathing.
-Worry about him later.
We gotta get out of here, fast.
-Chibi.
-Damn it.
Damn it, damn it.
Damn it!
Why is it always like this?
If all of this useless
fighting doesn't stop,
then I'll become the god of
this world and make it stop.
NAGATO: That's when Yahiko's
dream became my dream.
-Nagato.
Quit crying all the time.
If you only cry when
you're beaten down,
then nothing will change.
Just like this nation.
But I'm going to
change this nation.
And for that, I will need power.
Not just words.
-What kind of power?
-We're going to learn ninjutsu.
-Ninjutsu?
From who?
-The Hidden Leaf ninja who
were fighting against Hanzo.
I just checked out
the battle site.
I didn't see a single
one of their corpses.
They all went up against
Hanzo, and they survived it.
Those guys must be
incredibly powerful.
-Maybe.
I hate Hanzo.
He's made the entire Hidden
Rain village into a warzone.
Anyway, I'm going to
become their student.
I've got to find them.
-But what if you go after
them and you find out
they've been killed?
-Then I'll find
whoever did them in
and become their
student instead.
My mind is made up.
Take only non-perishable foods.
-Just toss the rest?
-No.
-Chibi.
Rest in peace.
-What are you kids doing here?
-All this stuff is
for you to share
with the grocer and
the fruit stand lady.
I figure, in some
ways, we owe you guys.
Anyway, take care.
-We're sorry.
-What the--
NAGATO: However,
we soon discovered
that pursuing the Leaf's
Sannin was far from simple,
and was very dangerous.
Following ninja meant going
deep into the battle zone.
Even though we
were just kids, we
had no choice but
to throw ourselves
into the horrors of war.
-Don't ever take off your mask.
Thre are toxins in the mist.
It'll be the end of us.
YOUNG NAGATO: Are you OK?
-Stop!
-A booby trap.
Hey, look!
How cool am I?
We're gonna become strong.
I know it.
TOGETHER: Right.
NAGATO: No respectable ninja
would ever leave tracks behind,
so the Leaf's Sannin
were not easy to find.
But Yahiko refused
to give up hope.
We headed even deeper
into the battlezone.
We believed that the greater
the intensity of the fighting,
the more likely we'd
find the Leaf's Sannin.
-Here.
Give me your hand.
You can do it.
There you go.
-Well, At least the
explosions have stopped.
-We're in danger.
[whistling]
-Yahiko.
Yahiko!
-Where am I?
-We found them.
NAGATO: Fate had led
us right to them.
The Leaf's Sannin.
We finally found him.
Jiraiya-sensei
[theme music]
YOUNG NAGATO: All I want
to do is protect those two.
No matter what kind of pain
I may be forced to endure.
JIRAIYA: I understand.
YOUNg NAGATO: Sensei.
What are you always
thinking about?
-There's so much war and
hatred in this world.
I want to do something
about it, and I'd really
like to know what the answer
to finding true peace is.
NARUTO: Next time on
"Naruto Shippuden."
Origin of Pain.
-And finally, we grew up.
[theme music]