"Record of the Gutsy
Ninja Master and Student"
Lord Kandachi!
Looks like the big guy is
finally making his
appearance.
Lord Kandachi... We
captured one of the
suspicious men we found
trespassing in our village.
Well...
And you're the one who
caught him, huh, kid?
Uh, yes, sir.
Hmm.
You actually caught
Jiraiya, one of the
Sannin of the Hidden
Leaf...
Wait... I'd know that
ugly mug of yours
anywhere! - - You're
Kandachi! You were the
right-hand man to Hanzo
of the Salamander!
Imagine, running into you
out here... Did you
desert your village?!
As it stands, the Hidden
Rain Village has no
leader. But more to the
point, it's no longer the
village we call home.
Really?
If we hadn't left there,
we probably would have
been killed as rebels
like so many others.
Good work, kid! You'll be
rewarded for bringing
Jiraiya to me.
Just tell me whatever you
want, and it's yours.
Huh?
That boy isn't me! He's
a fake!
Huh?!
[gasping]
There are two
Tanishi's?! What's
going on here?!
Who are you really?
[grunting]
Why'd you have to show up
now of all times?!
You're that kid!
I thought so. I knew
there was more to this
than meets the eye.
Kid, you let Jiraiya into
the village, didn't you?
[gasping]
You'll pay the price
for your defiance!
[screaming]
Mom, no!
What are you going to do
to them?!
I'm merely going to keep
my promise...
Huh?
For your disobedience,
I'll now feed everyone to
the Conch King!
[gasping]
My... What a beast!
Ninja Art! Conch Whip!
[gasping]
Don't do this! Please
just stop!
I've had enough!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Mm?
What's that? You're
using quite an unusual
jutsu.
Here it comes!
Rasengan!
What the-?!
Naruto!
That's why I told you
guys to stay out of this!
I beg you! Please, you
have to spare the villagers!
No. Not gonna happen.
I promised I would do
this if you broke the
rules.
[grunting]
Please! Leave them alone!
Spare them, I beg you!
[chuckling]
Stop, Tanishi. You're
just wasting your time
trying to get him to do
the right thing.
Huh...?!
Whether we came here or
not, this was inevitable.
Did you actually believe
that he would ever
release the hostages?
Mmm.
Don't forget what your
dad Sukune did.
Think about why he chose
to fight back!
If you keep on believing
that your father died a
senseless death, then
this village will never
be saved!
Mmm.
[gasping]
Pervy Sage! Get everybody
out of the cages!
Right, leave it to me!
No, you don't!
You're fighting me, now!
Fire Style! Flame Bombs!
There. Done. Now finish
your side of things!
Got it! Shadow Clone
Jutsu!
Are you still trying to
fight me?! I guess
you're nothing but a fool
who doesn't know his own
weakness!
Just shut up! I'll never
rest when it comes to
pulverizing bullies like
you!
Hm. Fine, you
want some more?
Conch Spear! Ha!
Rasengan! Go!
Go! Conch Whip!
[grunting]
You can't defeat me! Give
it up, Leaf brat.
This is bad.
[gasping]
[struggling]
No way. You haven't
won this yet.
Until I bring down your
entire gang here, I'm
never going to stop
fighting you!
If I ever give my word
and go back on it, then I
wouldn't be true to
myself!
It's useless...
Ah!
[grunting]
No, damn it!
Conch Spear!
[grunting]
That won't stop me...!
[groaning]
No. Not yet. This fight
isn't over!
But why?
Why is he...
This village...
Does not and will not...
...belong to you!
[grunting]
[coughing]
No! Just stop!
Uh!
Desperately charging at a
foe you have no chance of
beating. You truly are a
fool.
Yeah, okay. If that's the
kind of thing fools do,
Well, then, I guess I'm a
big one.
I'm proud to be a fool,
and once I've made up my
mind, then I never quit!
[gasping]
If you keep on believing
that your father died a
senseless death, then
this village will never
be saved!
[grunting]
Damn it...
Uh, hey!
I can't do this! Not
again! I can't!
Tanishi, quick! Go and
get all of the villagers
to safety!
You can do this, I know
it!
[gasping]
And don't worry about
this guy, I'll take him
down!
What are you waiting
for?! Go!
Oh... Right!
Tanishi, what are you
going to do?!
I'm gonna save
everyone!
You're going to defy Lord
Kandachi?!
Obeying him only keeps us
alive while it's
convenient for him.
Uh!
Now you're talking! That
was spoken like the true
son of Sukune!
I'll leave the rest of
this to you!
Right!
Okay, everyone...
Time to get you out of
there!
[grunting]
Huh?!
I'll help, but... don't
blame me if things get
worse!
Heh!
Okay, pull!
[grunting]
Sorry to keep you
waiting, Kandachi.
I thought this kid might
keep things entertaining,
but he's useless!
Hmph!
Are you all right,
Naruto?!
Oh, yeah. I could keep
this up all day long!
Now let's do this!
Hurry! This way!
Huh...?!
Ninja Art! Needle Jizo!
He blocked it?!
I'll back you up all the
way. It's time you
finished this guy off,
Naruto!
He's got some payback
coming his way...
You got it!
That little brat has no
chance of stopping me!
I guess that means the
both of you are big
fools! All right, then,
I'll take care of you
two with this jutsu!
Huh?
Water Style Genjutsu!
Mystic Fog Prison!
[gasping]
What's goin' on?
Huh?!
What's this?! What's
happening?!
Pervy Sage, what's going
on here?! Huh?!
No, damn it!
My hand!
Pretty hard to make hand
signs , isn't it?!
It's no use...
I'm completely frozen! I
can't move at all!
We're almost there. Just
keep moving, everyone.
Something's wrong. What's
happened to them?
Lord Kandachi?
They were touched by the
breath of the Conch King
and have now fallen under
a genjutsu.
We'll finish them for
you.
Don't be so hasty.
But my Lord--
We chose this site
specifically because the
special magnetic field
that's created by the
trees surrounding this
area greatly increases
the genjutsu power of the
Conch King.
Even someone as strong as
Jiraiya cannot break this
genjutsu.
Once they realize their
paralysis is complete,
their feelings of
helplessness will turn to
fear and overwhelm them.
Then it's just a matter
of time before they
mentally breakdown.
[struggling]
Damn. I can't
move an inch.
So don't worry about
these two, just go get
the villagers back.
Sir!
I'm sure they won't
find you guys here. Just
stay put until I come
back, all right?
But where are you going
to go, Tanishi?
I can't let you go. You
could be killed if you go
back!
I get it now. Finally.
You can't run away from
your problems.
But facing those
monsters...?! You're
acting like a fool!
A fool?
I'm a fool, and once I've
made up my mind, then I
never quit!
That's right... I guess I
am a fool...
If I ever give my word
and go back on it, then I
just wouldn't be true to
myself!
I learned that from
the guy from the Hidden
Leaf... And I bet that
dad felt the same way, too!
If we just do whatever
they tell us, then we'll
lose who we are.
Well said, Tanishi!
Thanks, mom!
I agree. You sure are
Sukune's son!
Please keep everyone
safe.
I promise.
Just be careful.
Right.
[gasping]
Huh? What happened?!
Until just now, we were
both caught inside a
genjutsu.
Achoo!
[gagging]
Naruto, it was a pepper
gas ball, so keep your
eyes closed!
Impossible! They broke
out of the genjutsu?!
Hot! Spicy!
Yech.
Naruto, are you awake?!
Huh? What are you doing
here?! Why didn't you
run away?!
Because I decided to
become a big fool just
like you, Naruto!
Ha! Happy to hear that.
I think I'll be able to
finish this, now!
Well, then...
I should let you know
that you're going to have
to take care of that big
guy without me.
What?!
A Shadow Clone?!
You're free?! But how did
you two escape from my
genjutsu?!
Easy!
It was never me; it was
just a shadow clone that
was under your genjutsu
from the beginning...
Nice, Pervy Sage!
Naruto! Do you still have
any chakra left?
You kidding?! I have
loads and loads of it!
Well then, let's begin
with the creature.
But Rasengan isn't going
to work on that weird
thing! I tried that
already!
Just one failed attempt
doesn't mean your
training won't work.
You should be able to
release a huge Rasengan,
like the one you made
that sent Mr. Gamariki
flying the other day!
Of course! All right,
then...
Now, Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Let's go!
Right!
Is this some kind of lame
joke?! That jutsu won't
work on the Conch King,
and you know it!
Come on... Just like
during training. But
rotate it quickly
outside my body.
You don't know when to
give up, do you?! I'll
take you down first!
Well, Naruto? You about
done yet?!
Yeah, almost! But I still
need just a little more
time...
Fine. I'll keep this guy
busy...
Art of the Raging Lion's
Mane!
Uh!
Do you really think
you can hold me back?
Hurry up, kid...
Getting tired already,
are you?
Naruto!
What?! What is that
thing?!
It's enormous!
Pervy Sage, I'm
good to go!
Right!
Damn it!
Move in and stop him,
now!
[yelling]
Here goes nothing...!
Giant Rasengan!
[yelling]
[panting]
Not bad at all...
[groaning]
Tell me! Why'd you take
over the village and make
those people hostages?!
Why didn't you guys just
ask them to take you
inside and hide?!
[struggling]
Yeah, right; like I'd
trust strangers.
I'm Kandachi of the
Hidden Rain. And I'm not
a fool.
Yeah? Too bad.'Cause
things would've been
easier for you!
[gasping]
We did it!
Sukune, our village is at
peace once again.
The power of the forest
will be used to protect
us instead of being
corrupted by evil men.
Father...
I'll keep Mom and the
rest of the village safe,
just like you did. I promise
I won't let you down.
Now that we've uncovered
their scheme...
I doubt those other
Hidden Rain ninja will
ever return to trouble
this village again.
I can only hope that
I've been able to repay
Sukune for the hospitality
that he showed me.
Thank you so much for all
that you've done for us.
Actually, we owe you our
thanks, too!
If Tanishi hadn't come to
help us out when he did,
then we would've been
finished off by that
genjutsu.
Yeah, you're right.
Don't get carried away;
you're such a little fool
sometimes!
[chuckling]
[laughing]
Minato...
Naruto is growing up so
fast. Faster than I ever
thought he would.
He's just as gutsy and
tenacious as the both of
us ever were. Maybe even
more.
You were more than just a
teacher to me, Jiraiya
Sensei; you were like a
father.
And I know that Naruto
will love you like
family, too.
Hey, you know...when I
think about it, I guess that
makes Naruto something like
a grandson to me!
What was that? What are
you muttering to yourself
about back there, Pervy
Sage?
Huh? Oh, nothing. Nothing
a grandson like you would
understand.
What?! What the hell?! A
grandson like me?
Are you goin'
batty or something?!
Now, come on. No need
to be so mean!
Give your grandpa a hug!
What do you think you're
doing? I mean, besides
being really creepy! Cut
it out!
Get off of me!
Aw, don't be like that!
Fine, then you can go
this way, and I'll take
another road, Pervy Sage!
What? We're going to
catch another cat?!
Not quite. You're
actually after Nekomata.
And your mission is not
to capture him, but to
get a paw print from him.
Whatever it is, this is
just a D-rank mission, so
no thanks! Right, Sasuke?
You don't have to come
along if you don't want
to. This is an Uchiha-
No, wait; it's my
mission.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Sasuke's
Paw Encyclopedia.
I will complete this
mission, no matter what!