-Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu.
Damn.
-Look, don't be so impatient.
You're doing well here.
At this point, it's
only a matter of time.
Trust me.
-Well, if it's only
a matter of time,
then we should be training
every chance that we can get,
shouldn't we?
-Hm, I know that you can
take a licking, but uh--
-Huh?
[wheezing]
-I'm good to go
whenever you're ready.
Let's do it.
[coughing]
-You could be really creepy,
you know that, right?
[theme music]
-You carry him for a while.
-Are you kidding me?
You're the one who keeps
going on about money.
You can carry him
there yourself.
He's your precious
bounty, isn't he?
What's the matter with you?
Why the hell are you
looking at me like that?
-I swear, one of these
days, I'm going to kill you.
-Oh please, not
that again, Kakazu.
-Hmph.
-Look at that.
Guess he's doing all right.
He might not need my food
pills after all, huh?
SAI: Don't be so sure.
-Oh, Sai.
I didn't even see you.
How long have you been there?
-Before you got here.
You didn't notice?
-You're kidding.
I really had no idea.
I swear, it's like
you're invisible.
-Oh, well, uh, I'm sorry.
Like I was saying though, he's
certainly got his work cut out
for him.
From what I've observed so
far, Naruto hasn't much skill,
yet he has to sustain
absolute focus
while using Shadow Clones
nearly to his limit.
It really is amazing.
The degree of fatigue
must be extraordinarily
compared to that
of normal training.
-Yeah, you're right.
-That's-- that's what it
says in this book anyway.
-You don't have to
hide it, you know?
SAI: But weren't
you fed up with me
turning to books for everything?
I thought so.
[chuckle]
-Sorry, that's not what I meant.
It's totally fine.
You were only reading up
on it again because you
were worried about
a friend, right?
In the end, when all else fails,
that's what books are for.
Turns out you do have
a nice side, huh?
-Huh?
A nice side?
-Come on, we don't want
to interrupt his training.
Let's head back.
-Guess they shaped up into a
decent team during my absence.
Well, that's
certainly encouraging.
-Naruto.
-Hm?
-Concentrate on everything
you've learned so far,
and then break off the Shadow
Clone Justu, all right?
Time to tally up for the day.
-You got it.
-How about it?
Starting to sink in yet?
-Still not there yet.
Come on.
I'll just have to
train until I--
-You can't keep pushing
yourself this hard.
-What's that?
-Sakura brought it for you.
It's a basket of food
pills and a note.
-Eat some of these
and train hard.
They're my special food pills.
Cha.
Good old Sakura.
I bet her homemade
food pills will help.
This'll hit the spot.
[gagging]
Bleh!
Sakura, what did you
put in these things?
They're inedible.
OK, let's dive back in.
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu.
[music plays]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): I can't
believe Naruto's still at it.
Good thing he had my food
pills to keep him going.
[splashing]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Wow.
KAKASHI: Naruto, why don't
you take a little break?
-If I don't give it
everything I've got,
I'm never going to be able
to catch up with Sasuke.
IRUKA: Well, if it isn't Sakura.
-Huh?
Oh, Iruka-sensei, hey.
-Boy, that Naruto sure is
something else, isn't he?
He really came through for the
village in its time of need.
-Thanks a lot.
What am I?
Chopped liver?
I'm only kidding.
-I'm sorry about that.
You are Lady Tsunade's
apprentice after all.
My students have all
turned out so well.
It makes me proud.
But that adorable
little knucklehead
has really grown up.
Even now, he's tackling
training no one else could even
dream of taking on.
Amazing, isn't it?
-Well, I had my act together
right from the beginning.
Guess I should have been
working on being more adorable.
-What gives?
You're in a mood
today, aren't you?
-He really has grown
strong though, hasn't he?
-He's changed all right.
Everyone's changing.
All of my former pupils
are finding their way now,
getting stronger.
-Hm?
what's that?
-I see.
They even got Chiriku.
-I was out on patrol
when the temple was hit.
By the time I got
back, they were all--
-It has to be the Akatsuki.
They're probably scouring
every inch of the Land of Fire,
hunting down all
of the Jinchuriki.
Finally, they've returned.
-And here they're going to stay.
We have 20 new platoons ready.
Tell them they're a go.
That's all I have to say.
If anyone has any
questions, now's the time.
Asuma.
-Chiriku is one of the
Guardian Shinobi Twelve.
They would have had
to get past him.
Was he not there or something?
-Lord Chiriku faced the two
Akatsuki all on his own.
They cut him down.
ASUMA (VOICEOVER): Chiriku, no.
It can't be.
-For the pride of the
Hidden Leaf Village,
and above all, the safety
of the Land of Fire,
we must not allow
them to roam free.
I want to learn what their
motives are, but be warned,
these enemies are formidable.
Do not allow them to
leave the Land of Fire.
If you cannot detain them,
they are to be slain.
That's it.
You have your orders.
Go!
INO (VOICEOVER): We
will never disgrace
the name of Team Asuma.
CHOJI (VOICEOVER): We'll do our
best, Shikamaru, Asuma-sensei.
-Now then.
-Right.
Let's start at the
Fire Temple, shall we?
ASUMA (VOICEOVER):
Somebody's gotta do it.
-Let's go.
-Asuma-sensei.
-Yeah, what's up?
-It sounded to me like
you knew that Chiriku guy
from the Fire Temple
pretty well, huh?
-That's right.
Didn't I ever tell you?
I fought with him as a brother.
Remember, I left
the Leaf when I was
younger to be a member of
the Guardian Shinobi Twelve.
The temple's nearby.
Let's hurry.
-Such a beautiful moon tonight.
[clank]
-Huh?
-Yeah, you did it.
Way to go, Sakura.
I always knew you were awesome.
-Everyone's changing, Sakura.
-It's true, everyone is.
Naruto's embarked on
training no one else
could even think of doing,
all in pursuit of Sasuke.
-Ow ow ow.
-Hmph.
-Oh, Naruto.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): I can only
ever do little things for him.
YAMATO (VOICEOVER):
It doesn't matter
whether the things you do
for him are great or small.
What matters most is
how much you care,
really care about Naruto.
-A shooting star.
Sasuke.
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Damn it.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sasuke.
But as long as I don't give in.
If I just keep going
without bothering to rest,
I'll get there.
-All right.
Here we go.
I did it!
-Huh?
Boy, this training method
really is something.
I can't believe he
succeeded so quickly.
-No, it's not just the training
method spurring him forward.
-Huh?
-His driving force is Sasuke.
-We did it!
We cut the waterfall!
Yeah!
We got it good.
-Phew.
-Well done.
Now we can start developing
your own signature jutsu.
-Yeah, sure, you got it.
-Naruto, you OK?
I guess he overdid it a little.
-G-- gotta get--
-What?
What's that?
-Gotta get something to eat.
-Naruto, you never
cease to amaze.
[theme music]
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Shizune,
have we tracked them down yet?
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): Our
platoons are in the field
now, Milady.
They're searching everywhere
within 150 kilometers
of the Fire Temple.
But so far, no one
has encountered
any of the Akatsuki.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Why not?
An ant couldn't slip through
the perimeter we set up.
Where the hell are they?
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): Well--
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): And why
hasn't Team Asuma reported
in from the Fire Temple?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time-- The Old Monk's Prayer.