Where are you
trying to go?
The Kazekage's quarters
are beyond here.
[glass shatter]
Hold it!
Who the hell are you!?
One who seeks to reform
the Land of Wind!
I won't let you escape!
There's nowhere
to run to now...
[grimace]
The Divine...?!
Punishment!
(Temari)
Take cover!
[explosion]
So, you're back?
Damnit...!
You gotta be more careful!
(Gaara)
You wanted to talk to me?
Please, Gaara...
forget about supervising
the Chunin Exams.
The people targeting you are
stepping up their efforts.
You'll just be
playing into their hands
if you continue this.
I already know...
But if I quit
because of that...
...it would be like declaring
that I will cave under pressure.
Yeah, maybe so,
but still...!
...It's just the
Chunin Exams!
(Gaara)
The Chunin Exams is where
everything began for me.
Thanks to him, I've
made it to this day.
So I'm going to make sure
these Chunin Exams are a
success.
(Shibire)
We've finally reached
Hidden Sand territory.
And now on to the
second round's site!
[hard breathing]
Sarutobi Sensei!
Yuhi Sensei!
I'm sorry to say you
will go no further.
Those who arrived
late are disqualified.
If you're from the Hidden
Leaf, return to the village.
The rest of you can
disperse from here.
But we all had to run
nonstop for three whole
days to get here!
Complaining? Then perhaps it's
for the best that you're being
eliminated at this stage.
[gasp]
'Cause beyond this point is hell
And who knows if you'd even be
able to get out of there alive.
(Lee)
Sakura! Everyone!
We made it!
(Sakura)
I gotta admit, Guy Sensei's
team sure has a lot of stamina!
Team Asuma, Team Kurenai...
It looks like the main
players from the last time made
it through this time, too.
Yep! You guys have
given this your all!
The fortitude you showed me
running three days and
three nights without sleep
has made me
so proud that I can
hardly stand it!
Why, it takes me back to
the time when I took the
Chunin Exams...
Sensei... If this
is a long story...
Please, just let us rest
already. Plus, I'm starving!
Seems so...
We have never been to
the Hidden Sand before&
It really is nothing
but desert.
Although, to be accurate,
this isn't the Hidden
Sand Village.
In fact, we're actually
quite far away from it.
Are you saying you have
been to the Hidden Sand
Village before?
Once on an errand
for the Hyuga.
This is called the Demon
Desert checkpoint.
Really? No kidding?
So this is what they're
gonna use.
You know, taking the
Exams in a different
village is a bit stressful.
I wonder what the Second
Round is going to be like.
It'll probably be just like
the last Chunin Exams.
So we compete against
the other teams?
There's a good
chance of that.
Then we are going to have
to be cautious of some teams.
We went at full-speed, and
yet we were not the first
to arrive here.
Yeah, the Hidden
Waterfall was the first.
And not only that, but
they also arrived here
long before we did.
So just what kind of
opponents are they...?
(Fuu)
{grunt] Hey! What's going
on? This door won't open
for some reason!
I'm sorry, Fuu.
You'll just have to stay
in there until tomorrow
morning.
(Fuu)
What?! How come?!
'Cause we never know what
you're gonna do next!
Please, just give us a break
and let us rest up for the
next round, all right?
(Fuu)
What?! But that means I can't go
and have fun with the others!
That's just the kind of
thing that worries us!
Ugh!
(Loudspeaker)
Dinner is now ready. Entrants,
please assemble in the
cafeteria.
(Sakura)
So that's the Hidden Sand...
(Kiba)
Yeah, just look at
them over there...
... giving everyone
the stink eye!
Those guys sure
do look mean...
Yeah, but&You look
pretty mean, too, Kiba!
And over there is
the Hidden Rain...
...I guess the other side
is the Hidden Grass.
(Choji)
That guy is amazing...!
I would say so, too...!
Compared to him, even
our slightly chubby
Choji looks normal!
(ino)
But the way he's sweating&
Seriously, that's gross.
(Tenten)
Hey... I'm getting a
bad feeling here.
Hm? Bad feeling?
It's just all that sweat! If
he gets too close to the
food on the tables...
[horrified gasps]
All right! It looks like it's
just about time to eat dinner!
[grunt]
[nervous gasps]
Left foot... Right
foot... Left foot...
[squeamish groan]
[grunts]
[grossed out groan]
[sweat dripping]
At this rate...
Our whole dinner's
gonna be...
[shouts]
Ahhhh!
Whoa!
(Kiba)
Damnit!
[screaming]
Eight Trigrams
Palm Rotation!
Thank goodness!
We're saved!
Uh&No, I do not
think that we are!
Huh?
What did you guys
do to our dinner?
Yeah, what were
you thinking?
Why are you guys
disrespecting our friend?
(Rock Lee)
Please, do not misunderstand!
We only wanted to
protect our food!
So you were just gonna save your
food and forget all about the
food for the rest of us?
What're you
talking about?!
We'd never
stoop to something
as low as that!
Your suspicion just shows
that Gaara hasn't trained
you right!
Did I hear you right?
Did you just criticize
Lord Gaara?
That is absolutely
unforgivable!
[fighting grunts]
Please stop this! Everyone,
please stop now!
[fighting grunts]
Ow!!!
Hey, come on!
Knock it off!
Neji! Aren't you
going to stop them?!
Sorry, but I'm
busy right now.
Burami!
Hey, don't go eating
food off the floor!
Muyami! You help too!
I'll pass&I'm way
too shy to do that...
Calm down, every- -  Argh!
We must not fight- - ARGH!
Why, you...!
[groan]
Will you stop and
listen to me!?
[gasp]
This room is too small for
a flashy move like that.
I was not using my full
strength, but still, to
stop me with one hand&!
What's that sound?
Fuu!
Yaa!
Taa-daa! Well, well! Looks
like the party's already
started, huh, guys?!
...Am I about to make
a hundred friends?
Who are you?
I'm Fuu from the
Hidden Waterfall Village!
Uhh...
She's...
I came to the Chunin Exams
to make a hundred friends!
and there's no better
time than right now!
So tell me, guys, what's
the plan for after dinner?
Cards? Backgammon? Musical
chairs? You name it; I am
up for it!
Or, how about all of us
just take a bath together?
What the hell...?
[exasperated sighs]
Oh well, I guess that's it
for dinner, then& I'm going
back.
Huh? Hey, wait! Come
back! Hey, hold up!
Come on, don't go! You
guys, stick around and
play with me!
Well, it took an idiot like that
to stop all that ruckus& Hm.
Sort of  reminds me of someone.
Yeah... Naruto.
Don't you think
so too, Lee?
Huh? Hey, Lee?
(Lee)
Excuse me,
please wait!
I realized when we made
contact, that you are quite
different than all the others.
You were able to stop my
attack so easily back there.
It may sound arrogant
to say this, but
it takes someone
extraordinary to do
something like that!
That is how I can tell. that
you have had to overcome
great odds like me.
What are you saying?
Well, that you
and I are alike.
I know about you, too.
You're Rock Lee
of the Hidden Leaf.
I'm Shira of the
Hidden Sand.
Shira... Huh?
I don't know what you
sensed back there, but...
...dwelling on the misfortunes
of birth is meaningless.
For all the flaws and
suffering, we have just
one life, this one.
And to my mind, there
is only one truth to
be found in life.
There is only
one truth in life?
Determination
never betrays you.
Shira, you&
(Kakashi)
Lady Tsunade? I've returned.
I'm glad you're back.
How did it go?
As I reported, I wasn't able
to see Hanzo in person.
...I tried to sneak back
in and investigate...but...
The infiltrator must be
around here! Find him!
[Thinking]
What? They've discovered
my presence already?
They were on to me
right from the start.
It was almost as though...
a ghost was watching me.
Well...
I expected just the
usual Chunin Exams.
But now that they're
underway, we're discovering
some some interesting things
about each village.
Interesting...?
[stomach growling]
[groan]... Hungry...
(Ino)
Choji...?
What are you doing?
Hey, Ino&What's that
building out there?
Huh?
Oh! That's the
Sensei's quarters.
The Sensei?!
Uh- Hey, Choji!
(Choji)
I'll bet they'll give us some
food if we go over there!
But we're not supposed to
wander around at night!
e's so hungry that he's not even
able to think straight anymore!
I'm going after him!
[crazed laughter]
Hey, Choji! Where are you?!
(Choji)
What the-- Ahhhhh!
-Choji!
-Choji?
[sigh] So much for
making friends.
[screaming in the distance]
Huh?
Byakugan!
What is that shadow?
Who was that?! No
way... Did somebody
go outside?!
What? Oh! Cards?
Backgammon?!
Giant scorpions come out
at night to hunt during
this time of year!
You were told not
to go outside&!
Really?! You have
things like that here?!
Hey! Don't go out there!
[screaming]
Somebody help!
Choji! We're here
to help you!
Ahhhh! What is
this thing?!
Hidden Waterfall Hurricane!
[screaming]
Wooo-hoo! [laughter]
This is fun!
What's happening!?
(Choji)
No! Stop!!!
Hey stop fooling around
and take this huge thing
down, would you!?
Aww, I gotta
stop already?
(Sakura)
It's dangerous!
Aww, guess I have
no choice...
(Lee)
Sakura! Talk to me!
Are you alright?
Yeah...
(Lee)
But, you are bleeding!
I'm okay...
(Ameno)
Just hold still.
[Thinking]
This girl... She's a
Medical Ninja like me&
That should do it.
Thanks for that.
[Thinking]
And she's skilled, too...
Oh yeah! Awww
Yeah! Woo, woo, woo!
Oh, come on...
She's a lunatic!
[Thinking]
That girl again&
How'd she show up so fast?
And she brought
down that enormous monster
in no time at all!
(Guy Sensei)
W-What's going on?!
Just what exactly
happened here?! Huh?!
Going outside at
night is prohibited!
The Second Exam
begins before dawn!
Hurry up and return
to your quarters!
I'm sorry...
Guy Sensei! Oh, please!
We are starving, here!
What...? Seriously,
you're starving?!
Just go back. Clear your
mind of mundane thoughts and
even that fire will go out!
[happy sobs]
Missing a single meal
won't kill anyone.
Think of this as
part of training!
Ugh...
(Fuu)
Huh...? What?!
Seriously, you're
all just gonna leave?
Oh, I'm so sad&
You're a very good
person to help your rivals
from other villages.
If you'd ignored them, you'd
have fewer opponents.
I don't care about that
stuff! Not about rivals
or allies!
I wonder if I'll still
be able to make a hundred
friends! Woo-hoo!
Hey, wait, maybe all
of us can be friends!
Wanna play cards
or backgammon?
Or we could take
a bath together!
Whoa!
(Yourou)
Hey! That's Lord Kazekage
and the jonin supervisors!
(Yourou)
You have to be more careful
about what you say to them!
You guys!! But I want
a hundred friends!
(Gaara)
She doesn't care about
rivals or allies, huh?
Sounds just like somebody
else I know.
(Temari)
Gaara...
Sorry... Just thinking...
Now I have more to look forward
to in the Chunin Exams,
thanks to a few interesting
characters taking part in it.
All right, now I'll explain...
the second round of the Chunin
Exams!
The Second Exam will be a
competition for scrolls and will
be held in the Demon Desert.
It's the ultimate
survival battle!
There are two scrolls,...
Heaven... and Earth.
Half the teams will be given
Heaven scrolls.And the other
half will get Earth scrolls.
The objective of this exam
is to obtain both the
Heaven and Earth scrolls
and bring them back to the base
located in the center of the
Demon Desert.
You have seventy-two
hours. And you must find
food on your own!
There will be fatalities from
here on. So each participating
team member will sign a consent
form!
When you turn in the
team consent forms, you
will be given a scroll!
Furthermore, to avoid any
confusion, each team will start
from a different location.
So all of you...get to your
starting points quickly!
(Rock Lee)
It is finally starting! The 2nd
round of the Chunin Exams!
(Neji)
We don't know what lies ahead.
So make sure that you stay on
your toes.
(Tenten)     (Lee)
Right!       Okay!
(Neji)
Our priority is to acquire
the other scroll quickly.
(Tenten)
To do that, we'll have
to battle another team.
(Neji)
Yesterday's brawl in the
cafeteria was a fortunate turn
of events.
In my opinion,...the teams to
watch are the one with Shira,
who stopped Lee's kick. And...
(Neji)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Demon Desert Survival."
(Neji)
...the team from the
Hidden Waterfall!