[music playing]
-This is my ultimate art.
This time I'm going
to detonate myself.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): He's insane.
-In death I shall
become art itself.
No one's seen an
explosion like this,
one that shall leave behind a
scar on the very earth itself.
And then I'll receive
more admiration for my art
than anyone has
ever seen before.
Sorry Tobi.
-Hmm?
-But while I will
be admired, you'll
almost definitely be dead.
This explosion will
cover 10 kilometers.
You can't run away
from this one.
Tremble, be afraid, recoil
in despair, cower in awe.
Cry your heart out.
Because my art--
is an explosion!
[rumbling]
-Whoa, what is that?
-What's that?
What is it Kakashi?
-From the feel of that
Chakra, it's that Akatsuki.
-What do you think is going on?
-Come on, let's go check it out.
-Good idea.
-What is that?
I've never seen that.
I don't know what it is.
KARIN (VOICEOVER):
Sasuke, no, it can't be.
[gasps]
I can't sense Sasuke's
Chakra anymore.
-That blast is near
our rendezvous point.
Wait, is he-- Oh no,
it's just as I feared.
That fool, Deidara,
he blew himself up.
-And what about Tobi?
-Probably got caught up in it.
It was within the blast
radius, after all.
[theme music]
-Deidara is dead.
At least he went
out with a bang.
KISAME HOSHIGAKI
(VOICEOVER): Oh dear, it
looks like we've lost yet
another Akatsuki member.
And I really thought he was
one of the stronger ones too.
So who did him in then?
Was it Sasuke?
or the nine-tails Jinchuuriki?
-It was Sasuke.
However, it appears that
Sasuke has died as well.
-Deidara took him with him?
-You should feel
grateful Itachi.
Deidara sacrificed his life
to save you a lot of trouble.
-Hmm, it's funny.
I feel like we've
forgotten about something.
-It looks like Toby
is dead as well.
Deidara had no regard
for his partner.
-Tobi, that's what
I'd forgotten.
Must've been quite a Jutsu
that Deidara set off,
if that escape artist,
Tobi, couldn't run from it.
-No matter.
We can easily replace
someone like Tobi.
But losing Deidara
is unfortunate.
Don't get me wrong.
I like Tobi.
He managed to lighten the
mood of this rather gloomy
organization.
We was really quite talented
if you think about it.
-I must go.
Let us try to mourn
Deidara quietly.
-And I shall mourn
for the loss of Tobi.
-You're that bored, huh?
-OK, when the crest of the
snake vanishes then I do this.
Add a drop of Sasuke's blood.
All right, summoning Jutsu!
So, this is Orochimaru's
summons, Manda.
Orochimaru could
barely control him.
So how did Sasuke g-- huh?
I see, he used Genjutsu.
[grunting]
-Whoa, you're a mess Sasuke.
Who were you fighting?
-You, you used me, insolence!
You damn brat.
How dare you do
such a thing to me?
-Those eyes, you hypnotized
me with those damned eyes
of yours.
Me, you did this to me.
How dare you?
-Oh, boy, well, he's dead now.
Hey, wasn't Manda supposed
to be Orochimaru's favorite
pet or something?
You know, you really ought to
treat animals better Sasuke,
and not force Genjutsu
onto them either.
-There wasn't any time
to think about it.
I had no choice but to do this.
There you are.
I thought you'd be here.
Your Chakra suddenly
disappeared.
So I wondered what happened.
Did you transport
yourself or something?
You hid yourself inside Manda
and used the transportation
technique to escape to another
dimension, is that right?
Then why are you so beat up?
-Just before we
jumped, Manda and I
were hit by the blast wave.
That Akatsuki, it was
stronger than I expected.
KARIN (VOICEOVER): Even
all cut up and bruised,
Sasuke's still pretty sexy.
-Well, in any case, you'll
need some time to rest up.
Isn't that right Karin?
-Huh?
[clears throat]
-How pathetic!
I can't believe you're the
man who killed Orochimaru.
-Orochimaru was already
weakened to begin with.
That's all I'll say about that.
-It doesn't show any
signs of stopping.
Strange, there usually
isn't this much rain
around here this time of year.
You'll catch your
death out there.
You're so cold.
I have no idea what's going
on in your head right now,
not one little clue.
Yet from here it looks
like you're crying.
It's really too
bad, what happened
to your younger brother.
It looks like you're the sole
surviving member of the Uchiha
clan.
-No.
KISAME HOSHIGAKI
(VOICEOVER): Mm-hmm?
-Sasuke's not dead.
Besides--
-What are you talking about?
-The rain has finally stopped.
-Naruto!
-It looks like that explosion
caught everyone's attention.
-You guys, what happened?
-There's evidence Sasuke was
here just before we arrived.
-Huh?
-It's very faint.
But his scent is
definitely here.
Also, I can detect several
other scents as well.
-What does that mean?
-By the look of this crater,
a battle was fought here.
-Thought so.
As I suspected, one
of the other scents
is identical to the one
I detected in the city.
Sasuke isn't traveling
by himself now.
He has three companions
traveling with him as well.
They must be his accomplices.
-Then in the town--
-Yes.
Sasuke's probably formed a team.
Also, I know that one
of the five scents
here belongs to Deidara,
a member of the Akatsuki.
-Wasn't he the one who
self destructed and was
sent to another
dimension by your Jutsu?
-I thought so, but
it seems that he
faked his own death to escape.
Now, the Akatsuki
operate in two-man teams.
So there should be three left.
And Sasuke is in a
four-person team.
I don't care how
many of them there
are, let's just get moving
and track down Sasuke's scent.
-Sorry, I'm afraid
we can't do that.
-What?
Why not?
-The trail goes cold here.
-And what does that mean?
-I'd say, in this
case, either Sasuke
was completely annihilated
in that explosion
or he used the
transportation technique
to escape before it went off.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Transportation technique?
-It was probably the latter.
I've made my sense of smell
even keener than a dog's.
I think I found Sasuke.
-A nose sharper than a
Ninja Hound's, impressive.
Just what I'd expect
from the Inuzuka clan.
-Right Kiba, show us the way.
KONAN (VOICEOVER): Come
in Pain, it's time.
He's arrived.
-Well, so how is Sasuke?
-Coming along nicely.
His Sharingan is at full power.
His eyes will surpass
even Itachi's.
Then, the time has come.
I'm sure his mind
is made up, since he
doesn't have much longer.
-And what about the Nine-tails?
-You will hunt it.
And as leader, I will
not tolerate failure.
-Ha, you said you'd
take down Itachi.
But in this condition, you're
barely even able to move.
-Look Karin, we've been
going nonstop lately.
We need the rest.
-Give me a break!
That's all you've done
is rest, you punk!
-There, it's all done.
-You didn't do a thing
at the northern hideout.
So don't start
saying that I'm lazy.
-What did you just say?
Do you want a piece of me?
Well come then, bring it on!
-That's enough you two.
Suigetsu, Karin, have you
gathered data on Itachi
like I asked you to?
-You're not in any shape to
boss the rest of us around,
you know?
-Well, I picked up some
intel about the Akatsuki
here and there, but nothing
specific about Itachi,
I'm afraid.
-I've got nothing.
-It appears that they're
targeting specific people,
or at least,
they're after people
who have very special Chakra.
-Special Chakra?
I see.
-I've been conversing
with the animals.
And I've pinpointed a
few Akatsuki hideouts.
It seems they sense powerful
unpleasant Chakra coming
from those places.
That's what the animals told me.
-Wow, so what you're
saying, is even
lowly animals have the
ability to sense Chakra.
Or maybe it's because they're
so lowly, just like you Karin.
Uh--
-What did you say?!
Suigetsu, I'm not going to let
you get away with it next time!
-Hey!
Hey wait!
Stop!
Just relax Karin!
It was just a joke!
-I must kill.
[growling]
-Oh no, Jugo's
impulses have started!
-Sasuke, hurry.
-Calm down now Jugo.
[gasps]
[breathing heavily]
-Sorry, sorry about that.
-Screaming and making a
fuss, this is your fault.
-What?
-It's yours too.
-Karin, you're always
trying to provoke me.
Just what are you up
to, trying to do that?
I thought I already
made it clear to you,
I don't intend to leave
Sasuke's team for any reason.
-Look, I'm not up to anything.
You always make
it sound like I'm
playing some huge scheme
to get you or something.
I'm just trying to test your--
-I-- I need Sasuke beside me.
He can replace Kimimaro.
And he's the only one now.
Sasuke, he said that he
would become my cage.
And right now, only he
can stop my impulses.
like he did for me just now.
-Yeah, well, I don't
know about her,
but my own cage is
unlocked and the door's
completely wide open.
We can leave any time
that we might want to.
But then again--
-It's this way.
I'm sure.
From his scent, I can tell
that he's stopped moving.
I think that he's
resting after his battle.
-This is our chance.
-Sasuke, our paths are finally
going to cross once again.
(VOICEOVER):
Naruto Uzimaki
is no longer just
some troublesome brat.
He's acquired some
formidable Jutsu
and has many powerful allies.
it won't be easy.
He even destroyed
two of Kakuzu's lives
in a single blow.
-Spare us your words
of warning and of fear.
They are wasted on us.
Pain's never lost
a single battle.
[laughter]
Tobi (VOICEOVER):
Well, that is true.
We're done here.
Be certain to tell the
other members to hurry
with the remaining Jinchuuriki.
-I know I will.
Tobi (VOICEOVER):
Soon, very soon, all our goals
shall be achieved.
When that happens,
then everything
will be restored to
its rightful place.
The true power of
the Sharingan that
belongs to me, Madara Uchiha.
-Once again, the sky is weeping.
Pain, are you--
[theme music]
-I'm coming in Tsunade.
-Jiraiya, have you
learned anything?
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
Yes, I've located
the leader of the Akatsuki.
-You have?
Tell me everything!
-If it pans out, we can
use that information
to plan a surprise attack.
-Now, now, don't be hasty.
-This isn't like plotting
a sequel to your novel.
We have no time to waste.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
Haste makes waste.
We can't afford that, not with
the stakes as high as they are.
-Next time, Twilight.