(Kakashi) Hmm. What a dilemma.
What's the matter, Lord
Kakashi?
Please, just drop the "lord"
part.
Remember the mission I gave to
get wedding gifts?
Do I really have to assess
every one of them?
Of course you do!
Oink oink.
(Kakashi) The honey wine is a
great gift. It's perfect for a
special occasion like this.
(Shizune) You can tell that Team
8 really went all out.
And this hot springs honeymoon
and the gift certificates for
dinner are very thoughtful, too!
(Kakashi) I wasn't expecting
this from Choji and Shikamaru.
They outdid themselves.
(Shizune) You can really see the
girls' tastes reflected in these
choices.
Yes, they're very cute, but
take a look at this.
Hmm?
[comically horrified]
Unbelievable, right?
Also Konohamaru hasn't turned
in the video he was making
yet.
Uh. Well, I guess that it all
worked out!
Now they can be the ones given
assignments on the day of the
wedding!
It's true that if I'm supposed
make my selections based on the
gifts...
then these three should
be the candidates.
But is this really the right
way to do this?
(Hinata) Kakashi Sensei?
Hmm?
Oh, Hinata! It's been awhile,
hasn't it? What's up?
I'm meeting Sakura and the
girls. It's been so long!
Last girls' get-together as a
single woman, huh?
How are your wedding plans
going, anyway? I take it
Naruto's doing well?
Huh? Yes, he's fine.
He's doing really well!
Where are you headed, Kakashi
Sensei?
Oh. I'm hoping to take a quick
nap.
I see.
I'm sorry to have bothered
you.
If you'll please excuse me.
Oh, yeah sure.
[sighs]
Hey, what's the matter, Iruka
Sensei? Was the ramen not good?
Oh, no, no! The ramen was
delicious, as always! It isn't
that.
I knew that you'd be here,
Iruka Sensei!
Konohamaru!
(Konohamaru) No more delays! I
need your congratulatory
message!
'Cause otherwise, I can't turn
in this video as my wedding
gift!
I'm so sorry!
Oh, is that what you've been
agonizing about?
It is. I can't think of what
to say.
Well, you're agonizing about
it too much! Now get ready!
'Cause I'm recording!
[gasps] Hey, wait!
Ahh!
[groans] Get it together, Iruka
Sensei!
I have to agree with Konohamaru.
How can anyone not know what to
say in a congratulatory message?
You're Naruto's teacher, well
aren't you?!
That's the reason why!
That is?
Back when Lord Kazekage came
in to Ichiraku...
I'm going to honor Naruto not
as Kazekage, but as a friend.
When I heard him say that, I
began to wonder...
in what role exactly I should be
celebrating Naruto.
And what does that mean?
But how else would you do it?!
You're his teacher!
I realize that almost everybody
probably thinks of me as being
Naruto's "teacher."
That's right! So, hurry up and
let me record you, or I can't
finish this video!
(Iruka) But.
Hmm?
Thing is, I kinda feel like
this shouldn't be coming from
the point of view...
of a teacher to his student.
(Iruka) I don't even know if
it's right to do this as his
teacher or not.
But I feel that Naruto's a
little different than my other
students.
And that's why it feels wrong
to do it as instructor.
But I also don't think it's
really right to call us
friends...
in the way Lord Kakashi spoke
of.
So you see...
the more that I think about it
all, the more unsure I become
about my message for him.
Hmm, I think I see what you
mean now.
Saying that you and Naruto are
friends doesn't quite feel
right.
(Teuchi) But anyway, I am gonna
have to charge you for that bowl
you broke.
[groans]
And, Is all the prep for the
wedding done?
Yes! Well, most of it.
I have to say, I'm really
surprised that the first ones
out of our entire group...
to get married are you and
Naruto!
How's Naruto doing, anyway?
Is he even helping you at all
with the planning?
[chuckles] Of course! But
actually, more than Naruto...
it's my father who keeps
telling me what I should do.
It's true what they say about
the father of the bride being
a real pain.
I guess that planning a
wedding is a huge task, huh?
Yeah, of course it is! Even for
us! Like how Kakashi Sensei gave
us...
[loud scream]
Hey! Sakura!
What's the deal?! [gasps]
Even for us, like how Kakashi
Sensei gave us... Damn that was
close
[yelling]
Uhh?
What was that about Kakashi
Sensei?
Uh!
Oh, uh...
He's just going through a lot.
Trying to wrap up all the
missions before the wedding,
that's all!
Yeah! And unlike us, you already
have someone like Naruto, so
you're really lucky.
Uh, yeah, that's right!
Well, I guess so!
So, tell us everything! Are
you gonna wear a kimono for
the ceremony?
You're gonna look really
pretty as a bride no matter
what you wear!
Yeah! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
(Kiba) Hey, Hinata!
[chuckles]
Long time no see, huh?
Kiba! Shino!
Are you doing okay?
M-hm. You two seem great!
Well, we're going to be
celebrating your wedding soon,
so of course we are!
The reason is because...
How is Naruto doing, anyway?!
We hardly ever get to see him
anymore these days.
Oh, I guess he's probably
busy getting ready for the big
day, huh!
M-hm.
Although, he's been busy with
missions.
But I can still count on him to
help with the wedding, too!
Oh, yeah?
We just completed a mission
ourselves, and I'm sure that
it's gonna make you happy.
Kiba!
Huh?
Oh, oops!
Uh.
Huh? What about me?
Uh, well...
What I meant is just that you
and Naruto are definitely gonna
make a happy home together!
And, uh, we're looking forward
to the wedding!
Oh thank you!
Hmm.
Hmm? Oink oink!
Huh?
[gasps] Lady Tsunade!
[sighs] It's been a while, huh,
Shizune?!
So how've you been?
Just great, thank you! What
about you? How has your
betting been going these days?
With Naruto and Hinata's
wedding coming up, I've been
keeping it in check.
That's probably a very wise
decision.
So, what did you want? What's
up?
M-hm. Right. Actually, it's
about Lord Kakashi.
Kakashi?! Really? What's the
matter with Lord Sixth?
I really don't have any choice.
I may not have footage of Iruka
Sensei...
but I have to turn this in as my
wedding gift, at least for right
now.
(Tsunade) Wedding presents?!
Yes. We have that rule on the
books about assessing the gifts
the invited shinobi will...
(Shizune) present in order to
determine who will be allowed to
attend the wedding, right?
Oh yeah. I remember.
(Shizune) Lord Kakashi has been
having a real dilemma about how
he's going to judge the gifts...
and therefore who he's going
to have to eliminate from the
wedding ceremony.
When you think about it, if
anyone's excluded...
that's probably going to make
Naruto and Hinata very sad.
At the same time, we need to
have people to go on missions
and be on guard that day.
That's what he's stressing out
about?!
Damn it.
This is really bad!
[marketplace buzz]
Everyone's acting really weird
around me lately.
(Konohamaru) No, it's true! I'm
not lying!
(Ino) Our gifts are going to be
judged to determine who's
allowed to attend the wedding?!
What's the meaning of this?!
I don't get it! Why?!
Hey, come on, stop! I mean,
it's not my fault!
[grunts]
[groans] This is the worst!
I get it. It's like this.
(Shikamaru) Most of the shinobi
in the village...
will want to attend Naruto and
Hinata's wedding ceremony.
However, there are still gonna
be missions that day.
We'll need people on duty.
Plus, there are gonna be a
lot of VIPs attending.
It'll be crucial to have enough
security for the event.
That's right. And a lot of
Naruto and Hinata's friends...
are now top-ranked jonin, so
they'll be in demand that day.
(Kiba) What does that mean?
Are we just gonna have to draw
lots or something like that...
to see who can go to the
wedding?! How lame!
No way!
(Lee) Then we cannot truly
celebrate with the couple!
I didn't think that our wedding
would cause so much trouble.
This whole thing's been
bothering Kakashi Sensei, too.
That makes sense.
Why'd it have to turn into
such a big thing?
Well, because Naruto's bond is
with the whole village, not
just us. It had to.
So we just sit and wait to be
judged?!
I don't think there's gonna be
any need. I'll take on the dirty
work, and that'll be that.
Me, too! I want everyone to
attend the wedding, so I will
volunteer for duty!
(Choji) Yeah! I'll do it, too!
(Kiba) Fine, sign me up!
(Akamaru) [barks]
No way! If Team 8 isn't there,
Hinata's gonna be really sad.
But still I don't feel okay
about somebody else missing the
wedding just so we can go.
We definitely feel the same
way.
All right, lounging around
won't solve this. Better get
back.
Kakashi Sensei!
Hmm?
Hm! Kakashi Sensei! I'm so
sorry!
Huh? What? [gasps] What's
wrong, Hinata? What happened?
I heard about the dilemma
you're facing. And it's all
because of our wedding!
Huh? What? What's that, now?
You haven't decided who can
attend our wedding, right?
What?! You found out?
Yes!
And the mission?
Yes.
Everything?!
Oh. I see.
Listen, I would never want to
put anyone through trouble just
to celebrate our wedding day.
Huh? No, no, no, no, no, no,
no!
We are going to have a
ceremony for you two, there's
no doubt about that!
Well all right, but about the
security...
can't we have the Hyuga Clan
handle the missions and guard
duty that day?
Uh, no, that won't work.
Huh?!
The day of your wedding is a
happy day for your clan too,
isn't that right?
As Hokage I have to make sure
your whole family can be there
for you. That's my duty.
Okay, I see.
I'll figure out something
about the missions.
Don't worry about anything.
Right.
So for now just focus on
yourselves, that's all.
Actually, I'd better get back!
See you!
What?! What's this all about?
We all know. About Naruto and
Hinata's wedding. And that we
can't all be there.
And that the mission to find
wedding gifts for them...
was so you could assess them to
see who goes.
Oh, I see. So, you guys found
out, too.
And that it's all been
troubling you.
Don't mind that, it's part of
the job.
So what about it? Are you here
to voice your opposition?
No, the opposite, in fact!
What?
Everyone here will handle the
assignments that day.
But if you do that, Naruto and
Hinata are going to be sad
that you aren't there!
And that's why we're going to
the wedding as well!
What do you mean?
It's simple. We'll schedule the
missions and guard duty, and
we'll all just work in shifts.
If everybody puts in a little
time...
then all of us can still be
there to wish them well!
After all, helping each other
out is something that Naruto
taught us.
Well? This way you won't have
to bear the whole burden.
You guys.
Thank you all!
One thing, if we do this, we
gotta change that rule.
Don't you worry. Come hell or
high water, I'll think of
another solution.
(Tsunade) You'll just drown!
What?!
Besides, there's no need for
all that.
Lady Tsunade?!
Look, Lord Sixth, the thing
is, that rule was made...
(Tsunade)...back during a time
when there was a sudden upswing
in shinobi weddings...
and while there was a serious
shortage of manpower.
Plus it was during the Great
War.
The situation's different now.
Also, and perhaps most
importantly, the Hokage is
you.
You don't have to be bound by
old rules. Choose the path that
you believe is fair and just.
So then you will choose to let
us all volunteer to work,
right?
Sorry, I can't.
What?! But why not?!
My job is to find a way for
everyone who wants to
celebrate...
alongside Naruto and Hinata to
be able to attend the wedding.
No one leaves early or comes
late.
(Sakura) But it's the only way
to make it work!
I'll think of something.
Hinata? Well, well! If it
isn't Hinata!
Iruka Sensei.
What's the matter?! Did Naruto
do something?! He did, didn't
he?! I knew it!
Huh?
[distraught yell]
Forgive me, Hinata! This is my
fault! I never taught him how
to treat women!
Uh! I mean, not that I even
really know about that kind of
thing, of course!
[grunting]
[groans] I don't know what
happened, but as a favor to
me, please, forgive Naruto!
Please! I'm begging you!
[chuckling]
What is it? What's so funny?
[laughing] Iruka Sensei.
I didn't even tell you anything,
but you decided that Naruto
must've done something wrong...
and started to apologize.
Oh. So he didn't?
To be honest, it didn't even
cross my mind...
that having a wedding would
cause so much trouble for so
many people.
Looking back I guess I
should have known all along.
Because this wedding isn't
really just for us.
After all, Naruto's a hero who
connects every village.
I was probably just being naïve.
And only thinking about marrying
the man that I'd loved for so
long.
You're wrong about that,
Hinata!
Huh?
No matter how great he might
become, no matter how big a
hero he may be...
to me and to everyone else,
Naruto will always be Naruto.
Iruka Sensei.
(Iruka) Nothing will change our
desire to wish you both the
best.
So, don't think of this as a
big fuss.
[giggles] Yeah!
(Kakashi) I see.
I feel really bad for
everything I put Hinata
through. I'm sorry too, Iruka.
Oh no. Although I do
understand how Hinata feels.
Naruto's become someone that
connects everyone in every
village together.
Did you say every village?
Oh! Humph!
Thank you so much, Iruka! I
know what the solution is now!
You what?!
But what does that mean?
Forget it! I'm just gonna have
to bow my head a little,
that's all.
(Konohamaru) Iruka Sensei!
I know you're in there! I
heard you!
C'mon, now! I need to record
your message or I won't have a
wedding gift!
What's up?
Now that Hinata's found out
about the wedding gifts from
everyone...
it's no longer a surprise. Which
means there's nothing to keep
hidden.
Well, then! Konohamaru, I
think it's time you got to
work!
Huh? I, uh, what now?
In short, would it be possible
for you to dispatch some...
Hidden Sand shinobi for the
day of the wedding?
I sincerely implore you.
Please raise your head, Lord
Sixth.
(Gaara) The Raikage, Tsuchikage,
Mizukage, and I have talked
about what we can do.
We didn't want to overstep our
bounds.
I still plan to celebrate with
them as Naruto's friend...
but want to do something as
Kazekage, as well.
He means that we'd be happy to
cooperate with you.
This is all possible because
of the peaceful bonds...
that were forged through
Naruto's strength.
Therefore, I think it only
fitting that we help to make
his wedding a great success.
Thanks so much, Gaara.
Actually, may I be so bold as
to ask for one more favor?
You only have to ask.
[chuckles] Uh.
Come here, Konohamaru!
(Konohamaru) Yes, sir!
[giggles]
Oh! A video message, huh?
Gaara, say something!
What should I say?
Just make up a proverb or
something!
I can't! Not just like that!
Oh, come on! What Kazekage
can't come up with a proverb?!
[gasps] Hey!
[grunts]
(Iruka) I didn't have any
parents either, and no one
acknowledged me.
I did a lot of stupid stuff to
get attention. Naruto, I think
you and I were very much alike.
I was your teacher back then,
and at times, it felt like we
were brothers.
But now, you're a true shinobi
hero. You really have come
far.
(Naruto) Next time on Naruto
Shippuden:
"Hidden Leaf Story, The Perfect
Day for a Wedding, Part 7: The
Message."