No! Stop! Why are
you doing this?!
[painful grunting]
[screaming]
Now to test these
outside...
I already know
these eyes...
See the darkness
quite well...
I wonder if Sasuke
and Karin are okay?
I wouldn't waste any
time thinking about
that if I were you.
What? Why's that?
Because even if Karin and
Sasuke are alive and still
together.
Do you really think if we
found them, we'd have
some kind of touching,
emotional reunion?
Just listen... Karin
wants to get hot and
heavy with Sasuke.
Which means that to her,
the two of us will just
be in the way.
I see...
So what do we do? Just keep
collecting blades, then?
Nah, no way! We're going
to meddle, of course!
After all, that's my second
favorite pastime after
collecting blades.
So, are we going to look
for Sasuke and Karin?
Let's check out Orochimaru's
hideout first!
Kakashi Sensei! Bushier Brow
Sensei! You both came!
You know that I can't just
sit back and relax not while
my student from Team 7
is working so hard!
Oh! Right! Him! He's got
a Sharingan and a Rinnegan
that are linked,
left eye to right eye,
and there's a rod sticking
out of the left side of the
chest, and, and, uhhh!
Just calm down! You aren't
making any sense at all!
His right eye holds a
Sharingan and his left a
Rinnegan. And he has the
same rods that Pain
used. So I see, at least...
Well, your deductive
skills are as impressive
as always, Kakashi.
Here it comes!
I count Five Tails!
Leaf Rock Crush!
Hey! Thanks! That's
way better!
He's after the Eight Tails!
I'm real sorry,
Eight-o! You okay?
We share pain, remember?
So are you all right, Bee?!
Wait, was it trying
to attack him??
[angry roar]
So painful!
I can't believe,
I'm letting him...
Why, you!
There! He's done it!
But why is he bottling up
the Tailed Beast's power?
I don't know... He doesn't
seem to have the Tailed
Beast completely
under his control.
Maybe that's why...
[angry growling]
Hey, did you hear that,
Naruto? That voice?
Yeah. I did.
That was the Tailed
Beast... Five Tails' voice.
[growling]
We Tailed Beasts
have emotions.
It pains me to see
one of my kind treated
like that!
Agh! Now you get mad?!
It's always been the same
with every single shinobi
who has kept us as pets!
Eight Tails, you and that
brat Bee are a special
exception.
[harrumphing chuckle]
I wonder about that
Nine Tails...
Huh?! Wait, Nine Tails
can talk directly to
Eight Tails?!
I know you, Nine
Tails. You-
You talk too much!
By the way, given the number
of tails you have, aren't
you the next most powerful
after me, Eight Tails?
Hurry up and finish this!
I'm going to take a nap!
Don't decide who's
stronger or weaker based
on the tail count!
You've always been like
this! That's why that Tanuki
One Tail really hates you!
Hey, are you even listening
to me, you fool?! Don't you
dare play possum, you fox!
[growling]
[chuckling]
Eight Tails and Nine Tails
are actually fighting!
Tailed Beasts can talk to
other Tailed Beasts
mind-to-mind, but it's a
real rare thing, of
the amazin' kind.
[chuckling]
You're babbling again,
Naruto. The enemy's
incoming!
Remember, don't let
your guard down
just 'cause I'm here!
Right!
We need to confirm which one
performs which of Pain's
jutsu! Got it, Guy?
Listen, I have enough
trouble remembering
people's faces.
These guys all look
the same to me!
Lightning Blade!
Eight Inner Gates! Sixth
Gate of Joy, Open!
Three headed your
way, Naruto!
Right! Incoming!
Three is better than what we
faced before, and I'm more
serious now too, hard-core!
[attacking yell]
Chakra Absorption Summoning...
Magnetic Pull and Repulsion...
Chakra Extraction...
Puppetry...
What's going on? They're
not using any of those!
[grunting]
Why?!
They're not using
Pain's jutsu!
Maybe they or he can't.
Or maybe just he's shrewd
enough not to divvy up his
chakra and waste it...
in order to make them
perform Pain's jutsu,
which we already know
and are able to counter.
Yeah It's got to take an
enormous amount of chakra to
completely control seven
Tailed Beasts with just
one's Visual Prowess.
Gotta hand it to you,
Kakashi Sensei!
There you go using that big
brain of yours again!
Kakashi Hatake... He's
got very discerning eyes.
Well then, let us just
power it up a little
bit, shall we?
[angry roar]
Two of them this time!
[screaming]
[attacking roar]
Damn it.
We'll distract them
with Nine Tails Chakra
Shadow Clones,
while we go after this
masked guy head on!
You can't make any more Nine
Tails Chakra Shadow Clones!
If you do, Nine Tails will
take all of your own chakra,
and you'll be done!
And you don't have to
guess: that is no fun!
Bee, have you still
not noticed?
I thought you bumped
fists with him!
Given the number of clones
he's produced, Naruto
should have been
half-dead long ago.
That he's not means Nine
Tails stopped taking
Naruto's chakra
a while back!
Right, Nine Tails?
I don't know what happened
between you two, but...
Hey! Ya know what,
Nine Tails...
[chuckle]
I believe I'm gonna come
after all of that hate
that's inside of
you, too, someday!
And just who the hell
are you to decide...
...that having a Tailed Beast
makes me feel despair like
that?!
What the heck is that?!
Whatever you do, don't let
that stuff touch you, Guy!
[gasp]
[grunting]
Naruto! We gotta help him!
Guy, we've got our own
problems! We need to
help ourselves first!
We're surrounded!
[angry growling]
That tree wilted instantly!
Is it a corrosive gas?
I'm worried about how much
chakra I have left, but
there's no choice.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
All right, We have to guard
each other's backs and focus
on what's in front of us.
So, any problems?!
Nope!
Lightning Cable!
Sixth Gate of Joy: Open!
Asakujaku!
Here comes the next wave!
Over here, too.
Let's wrap this up quickly
and go help Naruto!
[grunting]
Hey! Let Naruto
go, monkey!
Nine Tails... it seems that
you're helping out Naruto's
clone, who's fighting the
other Madara, by giving
him some of your chakra.
You ought to lend this one
strength, as well before
it's too late.
I'm not like you, Eight
Tails. I don't keep wagging
my tails at my Jinchuriki
time after time.
Are you saying you don't
care what happens to Naruto?
[angry growling]
Nine Tails...
This transient form is
nothing more than a nodule.
You're only a piece of
yourself, a pittance
of your true power.
Quiet.
You are merely an ignorant
and unstable power...
Shut up!
The ones who shall guide
you are the Uchiha.
You Tailed Beasts are
simply servants of those
with Visual Prowess!
Shut the hell up!
Now, obey me!
Nine Tails... Your power is
too great, too destructive.
I'm sorry, I can't let
you run around loose.
No matter what
words they use...
Whenever you exercise
your power, you always
draw hatred to you.
Please, just stay
quiet inside me.
Humans are always saying...
This is an unfortunate
situation for the both of
us, so please listen.
You're here to keep the
world in check, but I'm
here to keep watch over you.
...the same thing.
And now, this brat? How
dare these shinobi...
I'll bet even he's the same...
Hey, ya know what,
Nine Tails?
I believe I'm gonna come
after all of that hate
that's inside of you,
too, someday!
[groaning]
[screaming]
Naruto!
What?!
I suppose that now you want
to take my power, too?
Coming all the way in
here... You obnoxious
little brat!
Hold on, are you
Four Tails?!
Don't you dare call me "Four
Tails!" I have a proper
name, you know!
I am the handsome Monkey
King of Suirendo, The King
of Sage Monkeys, bestowed
with the priestly title "Son"
from the Sage of Six Paths!
The Great Monkey Equal
of Heaven, Son Goku!
[screeching scream]
Huh? What? So... Which
part's your name?
Is it [screeching scream]?
It's Son Goku!
Hmph! You humans
are all stupid!
Can't even remember
names! You all are
less than apes.
I really don't want to give
my power to the likes of
such...
So, where are we? This is
like where Nine Tails lives...
Do you not pay attention?! I
just told you my name!
How dare you ignore me!
You are far too rude!
Heh? Oh, uh...
Sorry about that...
Hm?
You seem rather genuine for
a human. You're the first
one I know of who's ever
apologized to a
Tailed Beast.
I guess you didn't
come to steal my
power after all, eh?
You have one inside you,
as well. So that's
how you got in...
It seems that Kurama
has trained you well.
Kurama?
Who's Kurama?
Huh?! You're his Jinchuriki
and you don't even know
his real name?!
You humans disgust me!
What?! You mean Nine
Tails has a name, too?!
[growling]
Oh, I see! His
name's Kurama, huh?
You humans only see us as
sources of great power.
You don't even care
if we have names.
You show us no
respect whatsoever!
You imprison us and you
deny us our true status.
Look, it's that child.
Ignore him and keep walking.
Who is that kid, anyway?
You don't need to know.
[chuckling]
What is this?!
Why you annoying
little brat!
I may not be the same
as you, but I understand
how you feel.
I used to misbehave
all the time...
Just so I'd get noticed.
Huh?
I'd do anything to get
people's attention! Because
even having people get upset
with me was better
than being invisible.
I'm a Jinchuriki...
But, still I've got a name
I cherish, too! Naruto!
It's a memento from my
parents and master!
Hmph!
That's why...
Nobody. I don't want to be
anybody. I just want to
fulfill Project Tsuki no Me.
That will be enough.
I hate that he doesn't even
care enough about who he
is to have a name.
It is not worth living in
this world where only
despair exists.
But despite that, he's still
forcing you to do whatever
he wants!
Well, then, what would
you want to do with us?
I guess I'd be
like Octopops...
Yeah, that's what I
want. To be like Octopops
and Eight Tails.
Huh?
Whenever I watch them
together, they're always
joking and fighting
and playing...
I can't really explain it
well, but I can see it when
I'm with them.
They're like-
They are true friends.
And seeing them together,
it always makes me feel...
Hm?
I guess kind of jealous!
[laughter]
Come on! Are you telling me
that you, a human, really
wants to be friends
with a Tailed Beast?!
[hysterical laughing]
This human...
Is completely serious.
So that's the reason I
want to help you, too...
But, uh, what was
your name again?
[sigh]
Just call me Son...
By the way, I ate you.
What're you going to do now?
Oh, yeah! I forgot about
that! What do I do?!
Uh...
At least he's better than
the guy in the mask...
There is a way to stop me.
Huh?!
Just undo these chains and
I'll tell you what I mean.
[chuckling]
Son!
I don't trust Jinchuriki
humans on principle.
Especially not fools like
you that claim they want to
be friends with Tailed Beasts!
Don't assume that even if
you do set me free from
these chains I'll
automatically become
your ally.
That's the kind of
response I'd expect.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Nine Tails."
All that humans want
is to imprison us!