-Hey.
He's not moving.
He's still down.
-Naruto!
[grunt]
-Hmm.
-Naruto.
You all right?
-Hold him steady, Choji, OK?
Just like that.
Right now, I can only give
him emergency first aid.
That was something, Naruto.
Who would have ever thought
that the real you was
hidden among the clones?
[laughter]
-You know, you're not
as dumb as you look.
Not in Shikamaru's
league yet, but--
-Please, don't
compare me to him.
-I'm impressed that
you could pull off
that jutsu three times in a row.
You were only able to
do it twice in training.
-(VOICEOVER) Such confidence.
And the wit to turn failure
on its head and quickly
plan his next move.
Naruto has become strong.
Truly strong.
Jutsu that were beyond
the Fourth Hokage
are well within his command.
I guess it's time to
finally pass the torch.
He's surpassed me.
Can you sense it?
You're the one who's
always before his eyes.
Inspiring him.
It's you who makes him strong.
You know that.
Don't you, Sasuke?
-Kakashi.
Time to move.
-Yeah.
[groan]
-Think you can make it?
-OK, everyone.
We're heading back
to the Leaf village.
-Where's Kakashi-sensei?
-Tying up loose ends.
-Defeated by a pack of brats.
Ugh.
Incredible.
-You did fight the First Hokage.
It's no wonder you
see us as brats.
But it cuts both ways.
To our eyes, you're just an
old geezer whose time is over.
And so here you are.
Dying.
Hugging the earth like a worm.
One by one, the new generation
will catch up to you.
And in the end,
they'll surpass you.
[theme music - in Japanese]
[birds calling]
-Well done, everyone.
But it's not time to
celebrate just yet.
Not when there are still more
of the Akatsuki at large.
Naruto.
Those wounds of yours.
-Yeah.
Kind of like a
badge of honor, huh?
-We gave him some
preliminary treatment,
just to stabilize him.
-Make sure he gets
to the hospital
for a full examination.
-It's OK.
Really, I'm fine!
-Shut up.
No, you're not!
Don't you worry, my lady.
Leave everything to me.
I'll make sure he gets there.
Right, Naruto?
-Ow!
-All right, then.
And as far as the rest
of you are concerned,
I order you all to
take a few days off.
Give your minds
and bodies a rest.
Got it?
Dismissed.
Did you notice?
-If you mean that
wound of Naruto's, yes.
What do you suppose it could be?
I've never seen
anything like it.
-Is there any news
regarding the corpse
of the Akatsuki
Kakashi brought back?
-Yes.
I've been told that it's being
examined at this very moment.
-Tell whoever's in charge
there, that examination's
to be their top priority.
[background chatter]
-I can't believe
it's finally over.
-Yeah.
See you around.
-What?
-I'll, uh, catch up
with you later, OK?
-But your house is this way.
-There's something I got to do.
Well, what was that all about?
-Calm down, Ino.
-Should you really
be up and about?
-Oh.
Shikamaru.
You've lost a Shogi
partner, haven't you?
You were always Asuma's
favorite student, you know that?
You must miss him too.
-When I begin to think of all
the things Asuma taught me
over the years, some
things being more
important than others,
Shogi was only one of them.
If I said I didn't
miss him, I'd be lying.
But I'm not a kid anymore.
I'm expected to
act my age, right?
I'm not allowed to do
the self-pity thing.
Hmm.
I used to complain about
what a drag everything was.
I made a lot of
mistakes that way.
And every time I did,
Asuma came to my rescue.
He was an odd teacher.
Kind of elusive,
hard to figure out.
But to me, he was a
terrific role model.
Well, looks like it's
finally my turn now.
When that baby arrives,
it'll be my turn
as guardian and teacher.
Guess I've got some
growing up to do, huh?
Thank you.
[birds calling]
-You know, Dad, you're a lot
better at this than Asuma was.
-Hmm.
Climbing Silver.
-In defending the King
against a stronger opponent,
some sacrifice is unavoidable.
Look.
If you retreat that way,
my knight moves here.
-Ensuring that your bishop
gets promoted no matter what.
Yep, that's certainly
one devious knight
you've get there.
-If you were picking pieces
to represent Leaf Shinobi,
the knight you just
mentioned would be me.
-What are you talking about?
-It's something Asuma said once.
[laughter]
-Oh, he did, did he?
Good old Asuma.
I guess he knew
you inside and out.
So then.
Who is represented by the King?
-Done.
Do you know which
one the King is?
-Huh?
Um, well, the Hokage, right?
-Yeah.
That's what I used
to think, too.
But, it's not the case.
-Then who is it?
-You'll know the answer
when the time comes.
-Hmm.
The children who
carry the future
of the Leaf on their shoulders.
They're the King.
-Ha.
You do get it, don't you.
Very good.
And checkmate.
-Wha-- huh?
-You're not quite good enough
yet at protecting the King.
You'll need to work harder.
-Awww.
Damn it!
-You're too darn reckless.
That's your problem.
-Why are you getting
so upset, anyway?
-Shut up.
Don't talk back.
-(VOICEOVER) Abrasions.
Contusions.
None of these wounds
is very serious.
The real problem is this arm.
It's broken in several places.
[gasp]
-(VOICEOVER) His body just
isn't up to using this jutsu.
-I see.
So these are the examiner's
conclusions regarding Kakuzu?
-Yes, my lady,
though the autopsy
isn't totally complete yet.
-In any case, the supervising
Jonin will have to be informed.
-Kakashi and Yamato?
-Go and find them.
Bring them to the
coroner's office.
[wind howling]
-Well, well.
So, Hidan and
Kakuzu are dead, eh?
-Yes.
It seems they were defeated
by Naruto and his team.
-Ah.
-We thought that they might take
out some more of the Akatsuki
if we allowed them to live.
Looks like we made
a wise decision.
-Yes.
Not bad at all.
I'm sure the Akatsuki never
imagined in their worst
nightmares losing two of
their members in one blow.
It must be very
disappointing for them.
[laughter]
-Still, they do
possess the Two-Tails.
We really must do
everything we can
to thin out their
ranks even more.
And what about the boy?
Is he coming along well?
-Yes.
I've planned the final test
for a few days from now.
But judging from all my data,
there should be no problem.
-Hmm.
I look forward to it.
(VOICEOVER) It won't be long
now before the final step
can be taken.
But for that, it's essential
that we have one more pawn.
[laughter]
-That woman, Kabuto.
You know the one I mean.
Would you be good enough to
find her and bring her here?
[gasp]
-You mean that woman?
-The examination
isn't complete yet,
but we've already found out
something about this new jutsu
of Naruto's.
The damage this man
sustained didn't just
come from a barrage
of individual blows,
no matter how many
there might have been.
-Hmm?
What do you mean?
-As impossible as it may seem,
his entire chakra network
has been severed.
-His chakra network?
-Yes, that's right.
I know it's difficult to
imagine, but it's true.
-I didn't know the Wind-Style
Rasen Shuriken was so thorough.
-The effect on the body
is more like a poison
than a physical trauma.
It's an incredibly precise
attack, doing its damage
on the cellular level.
I believe it shapes
the wind chakra
into a blizzard of
miniature swords,
and systematically attacks
every cell in the body.
-That is some jutsu.
-Poison, indeed.
So it would be more
accurate to speak
in terms of concentration,
rather than in number
of attacks.
-And Naruto?
How about the one
who used the jutsu?
-Well, there lies the problem.
-I see.
-Kakashi.
Whatever happens,
don't let Naruto
try to use Rasen Shuriken again.
[gasp]
-It's that serious?
-I saw those same symptoms
in Naruto's right arm.
Not as severe, but the same.
If he keeps using that
jutsu, sooner or later,
he'll lose it-- the
ability to wield chakra.
[sigh]
[loud ringing]
I
-It's a powerful jutsu.
It comes with risks.
-Once any cell in the
body has been disconnected
from the chakra network, it's
beyond my ability to heal it,
even with my medical ninjutsu.
Make sure Naruto
understands that.
-Of all things, wanting
to summon that woman.
[gasp]
-Not a very friendly
greeting, Guren.
[laughter]
-Oh.
It's only you, Kabuto.
I thought it might be an
enemy intruder or something.
-Right.
You did that on
purpose, didn't you?
-Of course not.
Besides, anyone who could
have been killed that easily
is unworthy to stand at the side
of Orochimaru, don't you think?
-All right.
Done.
Now, you just take
it easy, will you?
-Thanks a lot, Sakura.
-Hey, Naruto.
This new jutsu of yours is
only a last resort, right?
Promise you'll think
before using it.
-Haha, what's the big deal?
Long as you're here
to patch me up.
-That's not the point.
Medical ninjutsu's
not a miracle.
There are limits to
what I can patch up.
-But still.
I kind of like things this way.
The way they are now.
[gulp]
-It's sort of like you and I are
on the road to finding Sasuke
together.
[gasp]
-Oh, well--
-Hehehe.
[theme music - in Japanese]
-We've received a message
from the ANBU Black Ops
reconnaissance mission.
-It says-- where
Kakashi right now?
-I believe he's
working with Naruto.
-Fine.
But tell him to report to
me the minute he's finished.
-Is it a lead on
Orochimaru, do you think?
-Yes.
Seems the ANBU Black
Ops were getting
close when they were attacked.
We've got to assemble
a search team
to be dispatched as
soon as possible.
-Next time.
A Shinobi's Determination.