[theme music]
[water running]
INO: Ow!
‐Bear with me.
This ought to ease
the pain a little bit.
[sigh]
‐Thanks a lot, Sakura.
‐This wound's a deep one.
There's only so
much I can do here.
‐Sakura‐‐
‐Huh?
‐How's Yukimaru doing?
‐Shizune's in the other room
tending to him right now.
[music playing]
‐It's worse than I though.
His chakra network‐‐
SHIZUNE: Yes, it's
suffered a lot of damage.
Even with treatment,
he will never
get back to the
way he was before.
The strain was too
much for his body.
The effort of restraining
the Three‐Tails
took an enormous toll on him.
‐You think that jutsu might
have shortened his life?
‐Yes.
I won't know for sure until
I conduct a full examination.
Nevertheless, I'm fairly
certain that Yukimaru's powers
will never be the same.
‐This boy was the
only hope we had
of handling the Three‐Tails.
‐Maybe it's best this
way, for his sake.
‐Well Shizune, how is he?
‐All I can tell you
is that he'll live.
At the moment he sleeping.
[sigh]
‐He's going to make
it, thank goodness.
‐Yeah, but no thanks to me.
I was no help to
him all, in the end.
‐Huh?
‐I'm the one who told him,
wherever someone's still
thinking of you, that place
will always be your real home.
Then, right before
his eyes, he lost her.
The one person he finally
felt at home with‐‐
‐Come on, this
wasn't your fault.
‐I'm not so sure.
‐After all, we
have a connection.
You're the one I can return to.
And don't you see?
I'm the one that you
can return to, Guren.
‐Do you mean‐‐ I promise,
for as long as I live,
I will keep thinking about
you, and I will never
leave your side again.
‐Hm.
And you'll never leave my
thoughts either, Guren.
That's my promise, from
today forward, forever.
[crying]
‐Naruto‐‐
NARUTO: I'm sorry, Yukimaru.
I'm sorry.
‐And that's the
situation, Lady Tsunade.
TSUNADE: Hm, I see.
Katsuyu, order them
all back at once.
‐Huh?
Are you sure, my lady?
[sigh]
‐We have no choice.
They're in no condition
to continue their mission.
Besides, now that the
boy has lost his powers,
Orochimaru will never
control the Three‐Tails.
The wisest choice now is to
regroup, reassess, and come up
with a new strategy.
KATSUYU: But, Orochimaru's
not the only one
after the Three‐Tails.
‐Yes, I'm well aware of that.
But if we couldn't
tame that tailed beast,
I sincerely doubt
that the Akatsuki
will have any more luck.
I'm sending a team
to relieve them.
As soon as their
replacements arrive,
they're to pull out
of there at once.
‐Right.
And those are Lady
Tsunade's orders.
‐Yes, understood.
‐I'll inform the others at once.
The Hokage has
sent us new orders.
We are to return to
the village as soon
as a relief team has arrived.
We're scrapping this mission.
[gasps]
‐That's a bit sudden, isn't it?
We just pick up and leave with
the Three‐Tails on the loose?
‐That shouldn't be a problem.
The team that's coming, the
one that will replace us,
will keep an eye
on the Three‐Tails.
‐Yeah, but‐‐
‐The fact is, if
anything were to happen,
we're in no condition
to deal with it.
We've all been injured,
some of us severely.
Lady Tsunade has wisely
decided that the best course
is for us to bring back the
intelligence we've gathered
so far, and then
decide what to do next.
‐Hm.
‐The relief team will be here
first thing in the morning.
So, everyone get a good night's
rest before we move out.
[snore]
[whimpers]
[water running]
[music playing]
GOZU: Guren, Guren‐‐
‐Gozu, why are you here?
Why are you trying to save me?
GOZU: Do you remember that
day, when you came to me.
Orochimaru had locked me up
after I failed his experiment.
He allowed me no food,
scarcely any water.
I was on the verge of dying.
Then, one day, you came and
gave me a drink of water.
Just a ladle full,
but it was enough.
Because of it, I survived.
‐Hm, I must have been
feeling generous.
I don't remember it.
‐But I remember it.
I can never thank you enough.
I will cherish what
you did for me forever.
[gasp]
[music playing]
‐Guren‐‐
[heavy breathing]
‐Oh‐‐
[sigh]
‐Huh?
Yukimaru‐‐ damn it.
Uh‐‐
‐Hm‐‐
[sigh]
‐Kakashi?
[heavy breathing]
‐Give me a break.
I close my eyes for one second,
and he gives me the slip.
He must be out of his mind.
Someone in his
condition‐‐
Yukimaru.
Damn it.
What's that?
A grass flute, could that be‐‐
stay where you are Yukimaru.
I'm coming!
[music playing]
[grunt]
‐Hey, Yukimaru.
Where are you?
Can you hear me?
[sigh]
[music playing]
[wind blowing]
‐Damn it.
You blew it again, Naruto.
[sigh]
‐Where has he gone?
[whoosh]
‐Hey it's‐‐ why
would he leave this?
It means so much to him.
[music playing]
‐There's not a single
crack in it now.
I see, so that's it.
‐He just disappeared?
‐I don't see how he could
move at all in his condition.
‐Naruto, you were right here
in the room with Yukimaru.
You didn't see anything?
‐I'm afraid not.
‐Huh, some ninja you are.
But what do you
expect from a genin?
‐Shut up.
You slept right through it, too.
‐Hey, I'm not the one who
claims to be Mr. Super‐Stamina.
And I wasn't sitting
right next to him.
‐Stop it.
Arguing about it won't help.
‐Hm.
‐Forget how it happened.
I'm worried about him.
Yukimaru doesn't
have anywhere to go.
‐We must go and look for him.
We cannot just
leave him out there.
‐I agree.
‐There's no need for that.
‐Huh?
‐Our only interest in
the boy was his ability
to control the Three‐Tails.
Now that he's lost his powers,
he's no longer our concern.
‐His powers are
not the issue here.
‐I'm afraid Shino's right, Lee.
It's not our job to go
chasing after runaways.
And besides, we have our orders.
We're to return to
the village at once.
‐Yes, but‐‐ Naruto, do
you agree with them?
‐Yep, nothing we
can do about it.
Don't worry, the kid
will be all right.
‐Naruto?
‐All right, it's time
we were on our way.
‐Sorry to keep you
waiting, Kakashi.
OROCHIMARU: I was
hoping we would
strike a blow
against the Akatsuki.
‐Yes, forgive me.
I wasn't expecting the
Hidden Leaf to interfere.
‐And so, the woman, Guren,
you're sure that she's dead.
‐Yes, my Lord,
I'm afraid she is.
It's a great pity.
She had remarkable abilities.
‐Hm, don't pretend
you didn't detest her.
Are you sure it wasn't
you who killed her?
‐Of course it wasn't.
‐Well, not to worry.
She's easily replaced, even
with her remarkable abilities.
‐As for the boy, Yukimaru‐‐
‐Never mind him.
At this point, it doesn't‐‐
[choking]
‐Lord Orochimaru, hang on
while I fetch your medicine.
[choking]
‐That host body of his has
reached its limit already.
[choking]
[laugh]
‐At this point, none of
it will matter much longer
because soon I will have
a new host body, his body.
[whoosh]
[wind blowing]
‐Hm.
‐Huh?
[gasp]
‐What is it?
What's wrong?
‐Nothing, there's nothing wrong.
[giggle]
[birds chirping]
‐You're finishing our report?
‐Yeah.
‐There's a fog forming.
‐The squad we're
relieving says it's
created by the Three‐Tails.
And it induces
hallucinations, so be careful.
‐Interesting, I
didn't know that.
Ha.
‐A black cloak with red clouds‐‐
[gasp]
[explosion]
‐Hm.
‐Bravo, Deidara.
As expected, that was awesome.
Well, so much for the look‐outs.
‐Looks like your information
was a little off.
Hm.
You specifically said the
leaf ninja weren't involved
in the battle for
the Three‐Tails.
Isn't that right?
‐Yeah well, that's how
it was supposed to be.
It's really weird.
[laugh]
‐Anyway it's not like these guys
gave us much trouble, is it?
Hey, let's fill our
quota right now,
while we've got the chance.
‐You're 100 years too
young to give me orders.
Hm.
‐Huh?
[explosion]
‐But, wait.
Remember what they said
about that fog causing
hallucinations.
‐Who do you think you're
talking to, you fool?
I can handle it.
‐Ah, his temper
hasn't improved any.
‐It would take a
long time to search
this whole lake for
the Three‐Tails.
Much easier if I make
the beast come to me.
Hm.
[explosions]
[explosion]
[roar]
‐Whoa, look at it.
It looks a little like a turtle.
A huge, really dangerous turtle.
‐So, that's the Three‐Tails.
‐But you've done such
a good job so far,
I think I'll just
leave the rest of you.
‐Tobi, you wanted to be
a part of the Akatsuki,
and now you are.
You handle it.
Hm.
‐You're j‐‐ joking, right?
[whimper]
[screams]
‐Help, it's gaining on me.
‐But this thing's
a water creature.
I'm totally the wrong
man for the job.
Shouldn't we have assigned this
to somebody else, like Kisame,
or anybody else?
[scream]
[water bubbling]
[roar]
[screams]
[music playing]
‐Truly pitiful.
[screams]
‐[shout]
[scream]
KATSUYU: Is something
wrong, my lady?
‐Nothing.
‐Oh.
I can report that
everyone is safely back
within the land of fire.
‐Excellent.
Good work, Katsuyu.
You may go now.
‐Right.
‐I did it.
Victory‐‐ victory!
Did you see that?
Did you see me knock out
this giant monstrosity
with my jutsu?
I have to admit, at
first I had my doubts.
But I think I did pretty
well on my first assignment
as an Akatsuki, don't you think?
‐No, I don't.
We both know that it was
my detonating clay that
neutralized the Three‐Tails.
If it weren't for
my artistry, you
would still be thrashing
around underwater.
Since you're an Akatsuki
now, stop jabbering so much
and learn how to be cool.
That's the secret.
You've got no cool,
you've got no art.
You see, that's what art is.
It's passionate
emotions recollected
in cool tranquility.
‐Ha, talk about jabbering.
[laugh]
‐Oh, I was kidding!
[scream]
‐What is it?
‐It's just that‐‐ the ones
headed for the lake should have
been in contact by
now, don't you think?
‐Hm, we'd better send
a report, just in case.
[water rushing]
DEIDARA: Just make sure you
don't get too complacent there,
Tobi.
The Three‐Tails
was easily defeated
because it doesn't
have a jinchuriki host.
It has great powers, but not
the intelligence to control it.
[sigh]
‐Hey there, Tobi.
When I said be cool, I
didn't mean be comatose.
I'm talking to you.
TOBI: Oh, yes.
Hm, now just a little lower.
Ah there, that's the spot.
Hm, perfect, hm.
DEIDARA: Fall
asleep on me again,
and I'll make sure
you never wake up.
[scream]
‐Woo, I feel like I haven't
seen the old place for ages.
‐It has been one
mission after another.
‐All right everyone,
dinner tonight at Ichiraku.
[laugh]
‐Wait, Naruto.
‐Huh?
‐There's something I don't get.
You worried so much
about Yukimaru.
I'm surprised you would have
just left him like that.
‐He's OK.
Besides, where
he's gone, we would
have had a heck of a
time finding him anyway.
‐What are you saying?
‐I think what Pervy
Sage told me is true.
He said that, wherever
someone's still thinking of you,
that place is your home.
And if you just keep
thinking about a person,
then sooner or
later, your thoughts
are going to reach him.
‐Is that what I think it is?
‐Uh‐huh.
So I say, we've got to keep
sending our thoughts out there,
so that we can create a place
for Sasuke to come home to.
[music playing]
[theme music]
‐I always knew you
would come from me.
SASUKE: I'm stronger than
you, so at this point,
I don't see a reason to
hand my body over to you.
‐A bold statement from
a nursling Uchiha.
‐That's the only kind
Uchiha you can handle.
‐Silence!
‐Anyway, I don't
like your style.
The way you toy with people,
all for this vain, and frankly
stupid, cause of yours.
You disgust me.
Next time, "The Serpent's Pupil"