[water flowing]
[fapping]
-Now, regarding the Akatsuki.
We intend to continue
pursuing them,
with assistance
from all our allies.
-With everything that's
happened to your village,
those of us from
the Land of Fire
shall provide full support
in your rebuilding efforts.
First, we'll put
together a budget.
Then we'll ease tensions
between the other--
-More importantly, there is a
more pressing matter at hand.
I speak of the selection
of the new hokage.
(TO HIMSELF): Here it comes.
I knew it.
-Would not be possible
for us to simply bide
our time until Tsunade recovers?
-Respectfully, my Lord.
That's impractical.
Tsunade remains in
a comatose state.
The village is still
in ruins and we just
don't know when Tsunade will
awaken, if she ever does.
We are unable to steer
the village forward
as it currently stands.
Hmm.
Besides, she is
the one who allowed
the Leaf Village
to be destroyed.
-I'd really hoped that
Jiraiya would follow us
as the next hokage.
I liked him very much
and it saddens me
that he's no longer among us.
So who else is up for
consideration then?
In that case, I--
-I nominate Kakashi Hatake.
-Oho!
How interesting.
The son of the White Fang.
Yes, why not?
Sounds good to me.
And what do the rest of
you think about that?
-He's renowned,
powerful, and virtuous.
He'd do well.
-But perhaps he's just a bit
too young for such a position.
-I believe that Minato,
the fourth hokage,
was even younger when
he took the office.
-I can't quite remember.
Who was Kakashi Hatake's master?
-The fourth hokage.
-Oh, is that so?
If I'm not mistaken, Jiraiya
was the fourth hokage's master
and the third hokage
was Jiraiya's master.
It would seem that the matter
practically settles itself.
All right, then.
-But the third hokage's
teachings led to the village
being virtually annihilated.
-Oh.
Mmm.
-The Akatsuki's leader, the
one who flattened our village,
he was a former student
of Jiraiya's as well.
This is what happens when one
sympathizes with foreigners
and teaches them ninjutsu.
They were too naive,
every single one of them!
That naivete has
continued for generations.
It alllowed our ally,
The Sand, to betray us,
set Orochimaru on a campaign
to destroy the Leaf, allowed
the Akatsuki to rise up.
And now Sasuke, the
last surviving Uchiha,
has become a rogue ninja
and is working underground.
What sort of hokage
do we need now?
Someone able to clean
up this entire mess.
Someone who can reform
the shinobi world
and who will enforce
all our shinobi laws.
The answer is simple.
That hokage should be me.
-My Lord.
Why don't we allow Danzo to
handle the situation for now?
-Hmm.
-An aggressive and one-sided way
of doing things is not how we
of the Leaf--
-Yes, I've decided.
Danzo, I hereby name
you the sixth hokage.
-She used Lady Katsuyu's
jutsu to protect everyone
in the village and she's
been unconscious ever since.
We don't know when she'll
regain consciousness, if at all.
-Granny.
-Hey, Sakura!
Here, let me go fill these
up with water for you.
-Why don't we go together?
-[chuckling] Sakura.
-Don't get the wrong idea.
It's just that if I
left it up to you,
who knows where you'd
get that water from.
--[sighing] You can trust
me a little more than that,
you know.
-(TO HIMSELF): Naruto.
Who would've imagined.
SAKURA: We're gonna
be late, you two!
NARUTO: Aah!
I'll get you for this!
SASUKE: Hmph.
-The genin that are
assigned to Team Seven
are Sakura Haruno, Sasuke
Uchiha, and Naruto Uzumaki.
-(TO HIMSELF):
Sasuke and Naruto,
both of them on the same team.
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER):
I will be placing
Kakashi Hatake in
charge of this team.
IRUKA (TO HIMSELF): Kakashi?
-You know what I heard?
That Kakashi has
never passed a genin
that he's been placed
in charge of before.
-Is the hokage trying
to prevent Naruto
from advancing or something?
-And Sasuke, too?
-Huh?
Hmm.
(TO HIMSELF) He couldn't be.
-Understood, Kakashi?
-Yes, sir.
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER):
Team Eight will
be Hinata Hyuga, Kiba
Inuzuka, and Shino Aburame.
Kurenai Yuhi will be in
charge of those three.
-Nngh.
Yes, sir.
-Now, Kurenai.
This is your first time being
in charge of genin, isn't it?
Keep in mind that
the jonin in charge
will decide their future.
-Right.
I'll be careful with them, sir.
-The genin of Team 10 are
Ino Yamanaka, Shikamaru Nara,
and Choji Akimichi.
I'm placing Asuma Sarutobi
in charge of them.
-Roger.
-What do you think?
-Hmm.
This is a difficult predicament,
even for someone like you,
Shikaku.
-You think so?
I doubt it.
-All right.
Well, it looks like I'd
better start attacking again.
-Huh.
Sometimes it can be very
tough for soldiers like us
to accomplish anything when
our generals are running amok.
-Now how about a time-out?
-There are no time-outs
on real missions.
-Hnngh.
-I'm just a pawn.
You're like a silver
general in Japanese chess.
I can only do my duty if
I have your protection.
-What are you talking about?
If you're a pawn, then I'm
just a sacrificial piece.
-No, you're wrong about that.
Pawns like me are only
able to do their work
because you're there for us.
-Well, you got me there.
-Speaking of which, were you
able to find a suitable answer?
-Huh?
And answer?
Oh.
You mean to that
riddle from before.
First I thought the king was
the feudal lord or the hokage.
But now I get the
feeling that answer
doesn't tell the whole story.
-Huh.
Yeah (TO HIMSELF) Take
good care of my son.
[theme music]
-So this is where Naruto lives.
-Yes.
-This milk is way past
its expiration date.
He's a fool, but it would be
best if you looked after him.
You have good
instincts, Kakashi.
-Sure.
-And also, Sasuke Uchiha is
going to be on your team.
Well, Kakashi.
You studied under
the fourth hokage,
and you also possess
the Sharingan.
Who ever would have
thought that you'd
end up looking after those two.
[door opening]
-I'm not naive enough
to go easy on them
because of personal feelings.
-Yes, I realize that.
I wish you good luck.
-Understood.
This looks like it's
going to be troublesome.
-Sakura's completely infatuated
with that Sasuke kid.
What's the big
deal with this guy?
I just don't get it.
-Stop, Naruto!
Quit glaring at
Sasuke, would you?
[zapping]
-Get lost.
-Hmm.
-Get him, Sasuke.
You show him who's
the boss here.
-Just get him.
-What?
No way.
[thwogg]
-Sorry.
[kissing noises]
[door sliding open]
-We've been waiting for you.
-It shouldn't have taken this
long to designate team leaders.
[door sliding shut]
-You're right.
I was busy showing Naruto's
apartment to Kakashi.
-That's why you're here.
-You placed both Naruto and
Sasuke on the same team,
and I hear you've put Kakashi
Hatake in charge of them.
-Yes.
I think he's right for the job.
-It doesn't matter
if he's right or not.
What do you plan to do
if Naruto is on a mission
and that thing inside of him
suddenly goes wild and attacks
again?
-And that's not
the only concern.
There's a danger that
outsiders might target him.
-The wisest course
of action is to keep
Naruto confined to the village.
And you must explain why
you would team Naruto up
with Sasuke.
DANZO (TO HIMSELF):
Are you plotting
to give the Uchiha control
over the Nine Tails?
[inaudible], you're
quite the sly one.
-Next is Team Seven.
Sakura Haruno, Naruto Uzumaki--
[cheering]
[grumbling]
-And Sasuke Uchiha.
[cheering]
-Iruka-sensei, I don't it.
Why does a great
ninja like me get
stuck in the same group
as a slug like him?
-Sasuke has consistently
had the very best scores
of all the graduating students.
Naruto, you had
the worst scores.
To create a balanced group,
we put the best student
with the worst student.
[sniggering]
-Heh.
Just make sure you don't
get in my way, understand?
Loser.
-Gah.
Hey, what'd you just say?
Aah!
-Knock it off!
Naruto, sit down!
-Ow!
Aah!
Come on, Sakura!
Stop it!
Ow!
[jingling]
-You're right.
In the ninja world, those
who break the rules and laws
are regarded as scum.
But those who would abandon
even one of their friends
are worse than scum.
-Now, before we part, let
me see this one more time.
For shinobi, the one thing
that's important above all else
is teamwork.
[jingling]
-Nngh!
Aah!
[thud]
-Hmm?
-Aah!
[breathing heavily]
-(TO HIMSELF): So that
other one wasn't Sasuke.
It was Naruto.
-Sakura?
I want to ask you
something that I've
been wanting to ask for awhile.
Oh, well, what do
you think of Naruto?
-Naruto?
Hmm.
He knows about my feelings and
he purposely gets in the way.
He likes interfering
and making me feel bad.
Naruto doesn't understand
one single thing about me.
He's annoying.
[stomach roiling]
-Doh!
-All I really want is for
you to accept me, Sasuke.
That's all.
[gasps]
-It's true.
I'm desperate.
-Anyway, that's how I feel.
I'd do anything for that.
And it's all because I love you.
-Aah!
(TO HIMSELF) Sa-- Sakura,
I-- [farting] Aaugh.
[farting] Nngh.
-Hey, what's the matter?
-I'll be right back.
Aaugh.
-(TO HIMSELF): That
look on his face.
So he drank that milk.
[labored breathing]
[poof]
-Oh no!
I'm not gonna make it.
[door slamming]
[shoes skidding]
-Close.
Really close.
-Aah!
Oh, Sasuke!
You're back!
Don't be so shy, you bad boy.
Are you ready now?
You know, mentally prepared?
Because I am.
I'm raring to get started.
-It's nearly time to go.
Where's Naruto, anyway?
-Oh, see, now there you go,
changing the subject again.
Look, just forget
about Naruto, OK?
Anyway, Naruto just
picks fights with you.
You know why he's so annoying?
It's because he wasn't
raised right, that's why.
Actually, he doesn't have
a mother or a father.
He does what he wants because no
one taught him right and wrong.
If I did that?
Forget it.
My parents would get mad
and I'd get in trouble.
It must be nice to be
alone like that, not
having any parents pester you.
He's so selfish and bratty
'cause he's all alone.
-Loneliness.
It's not like that.
You have no idea what
it means to be alone.
-Sasuke, what's the matter?
Why are you saying that?
-Because you're annoying.
[footsteps]
-Aah!
You're here?
How'd you get loose?
-I used the escape jutsu.
It's a very basic technique.
Remember that next time, loser.
-What?
[growling] Huh?
-(TO HIMSELF): Sakura?
-(TO HIMSELF): Sasuke's words
must have hurt her pretty
badly.
-(TO HERSELF): Now I get it.
This is how Naruto must feel.
-(TO HIMSELF):
Sakura looks so sad.
What happened?
Nngh.
Sasuke!
-(TO HIMSELF): Naruto doesn't
understand what really
happened.
-Hey!
Sasuke!
[breathing heavily] You jerk!
You said something mean
to Sakura, didn't you?
-Hmph.
Not really.
-You big liar!
If you didn't say
something, then there's
no way that she'd
be as sad as she is.
All right, listen.
I hate to say it.
All Sakura wants is for
you to accept her, Sasuke.
-Like I care.
-[gasping] What!
[growling]
[thwogg]
[thud]
-Oh boy.
There they go.
-What do you think you're doing?
-Nngh.
What does it look like?
I'm taking you down!
Its pay-back for
making Sakura feel bad.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Aah!
-Nngh.
[thwogging]
-What's wrong?
You afraid to come
at me one on one?
-What?
Hey, let go!
-[laughing] Ha!
You totally fell for it.
Take th--
-It's me!
[thwogg]
-Aah!
[poof]
-Don't you think that was
a little over the top?
--[laughing] Got a
little excited, I guess.
Wait a minute.
How did you get over there?
Hey, get back here!
[footsteps]
-You're annoying,
too, you know that?
[shing]
[poofing]
-(TO HIMSELF): Damn it.
Talk about annoying.
I've got to do something
about Sasuke's speed.
It's time to use my trump card.
-(TO HIMSELF): That sign.
Another Shadow Clone Jutsu?
-Ha!
Sexy Jutsu!
-[giggling] Hiya, Sasuke.
-(TO HIMSELF): Ha!
Sasuke's so shocked,
he's speechless.
Now's my chance.
-I've got you!
[shing]
-Oh!
Aah!
[poof]
-Ouch.
That hurt.
[kring] Ow ow ow ow ow ow ow!
-Heh.
-Sasuke, come back here!
We're not finished yet.
-Naruto!
-Huh?
Hi, Sakura.
-We've got to get to class.
-Right.
Hey, wait for me.
Aah.
-They're amusing, but
they lack any sense
of teamwork whatsoever.
[jingling]
-I have serious doubts
that they can pass my test.
SAKURA: We're gonna
be late, you two!
-Aah!
I'll get you for this!
-Heh.
-Sasuke.
Looks like it's going to be
my job to stop you, then.
[jingling]
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
That's weird.
Where on Earth could
Inari have run off to?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): [sighing]
I don't know, but thanks to you
I'm stuck in this mess, too.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Shut up.
Will you just quit complaining
already and help me look?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Why do you think
I'm here with you right now?
Show some gratitude, loser.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): What?
Damn you, Sasuke!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Wait a second.
What is that?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time on "Naruto Shippuden,"
"Inari's Courage
Put to the Test."
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Inari!
[theme music]