[music playing]
-Lady Tsunade,
couldn't you please
reconsider this, one more time?
-Reconsider what?
-The Naruto issue.
[sigh]
-Allowing Naruto to take
part in a mission like this,
it's far too risky for him.
My lady, just
imagine if something
were to happen to him.
-Hm, I won't say it again.
Naruto and Sakura are
part of Team Kakashi,
and that's who I've
assigned to this mission.
I already explained
my reasoning.
-I understand that, my lady.
But still, it's not
really Team Kakashi
if Kakashi Hatake can't
even go with them.
The situation is different
from when we sent them
to the Hidden Sand Village.
[music playing]
-That's true.
-I doubt that you
want to hear this,
but I'll just go ahead
and say it anyway.
I think I'll take care
of the jinchuriki, ha.
SAKURA: (VOICEOVER):
In the last mission,
the enemy was clearly trying
to get their hands on Naruto.
-Just where the hell do
you think you're going?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): The only
reason they couldn't was
because Kakashi
Sensei was there,
and he knows how Naruto works.
-Naruto!
-But if we won't have Kakashi
Sensei on this mission,
of course Shizune
would have concerns.
-Don't be so worried, Sakura.
On that point, I've already
come up with a solution.
I'll be giving you
two substitutes
to fill the gaps left
by Kakashi and Sasuke.
Make sure you tell Naruto.
-Yes.
[wind blowing]
[music playing]
-Ninja Art, Super Beast Scroll.
[roars]
[gasp]
-Naruto, go straight for him.
Ninja Art, Shadow Stitching.
[music playing]
-I can't.
Who are you?
-Lady Tsunade--
-Yeah, I'll be there soon.
-Tsunade, I need to
discuss something with you.
It's rather important.
[theme music]
-So, what did you
want to talk about?
Since both of you
advisers are here,
I imagine this isn't
a social visit.
-Now that you mentioned it--
-Shizune recently
paid us a visit,
seeking our advice on something.
[sigh]
-What is this all about?
-It's Naruto Uzumaki.
-Hm.
Henceforth, regarding
Naruto, he must not
be dispatched on missions
that might bring him
into contact with the Akatsuki.
-Can we assume you
understand our reasoning?
-Yeah, I've been hearing about
it from Shizune, ad nauseam.
-Well then, find two
accomplished shinobi.
They will remain at
Naruto's side at all times.
Not only will this
protect him, it'll
restore Team Kakashi to
the requisite four men.
-Furthermore, you should
decrease the number of missions
you assign Naruto
as much as possible
and limit the scope of
his responsibilities.
-That is all.
Understood?
[sigh]
-If Shizune had come to
beg for your intervention,
then you should already know
what my answer's going to be.
-Lady Tsunade--
-Impossible.
-Huh?
[grumble]
-Tsunade, Naruto is not
just an ordinary child.
He is a jinchuriki.
-Normally, we would never even
send him outside the Village,
and we'd keep him under
surveillance at all times.
So you see, we're
offering a compromise.
-Well, I'm in favor for using
the four-man squad model
for his team, but you cannot
impose any more restrictions
on him.
So long as Naruto remains in one
place, the Leaf is in danger.
Sooner or later, the
Akatsuki will come for him.
In the Hidden Sand
Village incident,
they headed straight for
the jinchuriki, Gaara,
even though he was
supposedly in the safest
location in the Village.
And if they come
after Naruto, you
can bet the Akatsuki
will be just as
brutal as they were then.
And at the end of the day,
that would put the Leaf Village
in danger, as well.
But if Naruto stays
on the move, the enemy
will have a tough time
figuring out what he's up to
and how to get him.
Let's not forget, he
is a boy with talent.
He's a fine ninja and a
great asset to the Leaf.
-I expected much more
from you, Tsunade.
You call yourself Hokage.
-Look, I'm trying to find a
compromise here too, damn it!
-Correct me if
I'm wrong, but you
can't ensure that Naruto won't
be taken by the Akatsuki.
And if they do get
control of the Nine-Tails,
tell me what
guarantees you can make
that such a horrific tragedy
will never come to pass.
[sigh]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Get
ready to pay up on our bet.
That cursed necklace of
yours is about to be mine.
TSUNADE: Enough Naruto, you
don't have to protect me.
Stop already!
-I warned you not to be
stubborn, now you die!
You've just thrown it all away.
Dreams don't come
true when you're dead.
-Just get out of
the way, Naruto.
No, look out!
-Ha, don't you worry about me.
[music playing]
-I--
-Until I become Hokage, I
don't care what happens.
I'm not gonna die.
-A magic charm, to make
your dream come true.
[music playing]
-He won't fail.
They won't get Naruto.
If there's anything I
believe in, it's him.
-And if your judgment turns
out to be mistaken, well,
what then?
[music playing]
-Look, if I've endangered the
Leaf, or the Land of Fire,
then I swear as
the Fifth Hokage,
I will protect them with all
my might and, if need be,
my very own life.
[music playing]
-Very well, then.
If you feel that strongly about
all this, do as you see fit.
However, as a
compromise, you will
use the shinobi we select
for the additional members
of Naruto's four-man squad.
[sigh]
-Agreed.
-Danzo, please enter.
[door opens]
[music playing]
-Wait, aren't you--
-It's been a long
time, Princess Tsunade.
-Oh well, if it's you,
then I understand.
It can only mean one thing.
One of the new team members
is from The Foundation
within the Black Ops.
[music playing]
-Funny, you're pretty
weak, aren't you?
-Huh?
-The way you fight, do
you have any balls at all?
-Wha-- uh, what was that?
You never answered me.
Spill it!
Who are you?
[music playing]
-In due time, Naruto.
In due time.
-Hey, wait.
[groan]
-Who was that guy?
INO: Choji, I knew I
would find you here.
Oh, for crying out loud.
Asuma Sensei's
getting pretty mad,
and he told me to tell
you to get a move on.
-Oh hey, sorry, Ino.
Some weirdo just came and
attacked us out of nowhere, so--
-Huh? What weirdo?
You mean that guy?
Hey wait, isn't that Naruto?
-Uh, no.
When I said weirdo,
I didn't mean Naruto.
[laugh]
-You see--
-Hey Naruto, down here!
-Don't even bother, Choji.
This whole situation's
such a drag.
[music playing]
-So, these two
additional members,
you'll be providing
both of them?
-No, just one person.
-I understand.
Kakashi, their team leader,
he's out of commission.
But nobody told
you that, did they?
-Um, see, the team
needs one more member.
They have to start the mission
before Kakashi Hatake will have
finished recuperating, and
we don't have much time
until they set off.
This decision should
belong to Lady Tsunade.
-Well, I wasn't
expecting Kakashi
to be missing from
the team, either.
I had only just started
to figure out what to do.
-It's clear.
What you require is an
exceptionally distinguished
commander, someone
from the Black Ops,
assigned directly to the Hokage.
-Yes, that choice would be wise.
-I trust you have no
objections, Tsunade.
-You'll leave the final
selection up to me.
Is that OK with you?
-Well Danzo, what do you say?
[music playing]
-Fine then, I'll
pick whomever I want.
[sigh]
-Uh, Lady Tsunade--
-I am not happy.
-Uh, I-- I'm sorry, ma'am.
I know you feel betrayed,
but please, believe me,
that wasn't my intention.
-I'm not talking about you.
-Huh?
-I'm talking about that man.
I had the same idea,
appointing an ANBU Black Ops
under my command to
fill in for Kakashi.
I even had someone
specific in mind,
but I never thought they'd
suggest the exact same thing.
I totally thought
they were going
to force another one of
their subordinates on me.
Hm, does this mean they
think one person is
enough to keep tabs on Naruto?
Or maybe they're after
something else entirely.
-Uh, excuse me, Lady Tsunade.
-Oh, I've got a thing or two
that I want to say to you!
[shriek]
-But right now,
reorganizing Team Kakashi
is much more pressing.
You've got a lot of
work ahead of you.
-Uh, oh yes, ma'am.
-Well, that was fast.
ANBU AGENT: I heard it was
a matter of great urgency.
-I assume you know why
you've been summoned here.
-I have a general idea.
[music playing]
-Kakashi's out, and I want
you to take over his team.
-It would be an honor to work
in Kakashi's stead, my lady.
-Now, this isn't an
ANBU Black Ops mission.
You're going on a
regular assignment,
so you can take off the mask.
I'll give you a code name.
During the mission, you
will be known as Yamato.
-Yes, I understand.
-One more thing.
Team Kakashi will be getting
a new face in its ranks,
from The Foundation, the
Black Ops training division.
-Really, The Foundation?
-However--
-Yes, my lady?
-Keep a very close eye on him.
Study his every move.
-And the reason for this?
-This additional
recruit was recommended
by a man named Danzo.
Not only is Danzo a member
of the Hawk Faction,
a group that once
opposed the Third
Hokage, he was behind a separate
detail within Black Ops,
a training division know
only as The Foundation.
Danzo was the one who
founded the division.
I'm sure you've at least
heard his name before.
Though The Foundation
has since been dissolved,
and Danzo removed
from power, I--
I can't help but be
suspicious of his motives.
-Perhaps you're worrying
too much, my lady.
[music playing]
-Never mind.
Meet up with the rest of
your team, immediately.
-Right away.
[birds chirping]
-Hey, Sakura.
-Hey.
-Wait, this is the
place, right, where
we're all supposed to meet up?
-Yeah, that's what I was told.
-Yeah, me too, but
I don't get it.
Nobody's here.
What's up with that?
I mean, did Grandma
Tsunade really find us
some new members, or is this all
some kind of elaborate prank?
-Hey, don't freak out.
The two of us just got here a
little bit early, that's all.
There's still a bit of
time before the others
are supposed to be here.
-Well, I sure hope
hope they aren't always
late all the time, like
Kakashi Sensei was.
-Oh?
-Huh?
-Hello.
-Hey, what are you doing here?
-Huh?
-You're that guy from
the roof, earlier.
-What?
-Uh, it's a pleasure to
meet the both of you.
From now on, I'll be
taking Kakashi's place.
[music playing]
This is going to be
tougher than I thought.
[music playing]
[theme music]
YAMATO: Our mission is
to go to Tenchi Bridge
and capture the
Akatsuki spy who's
infiltrated Orochimaru's
organization.
This is an opportunity to obtain
intel on both Orochimaru and
and Sasuke Uchiha.
If we succeed, we'll
have information
that could lead to taking
Orochimaru, as well as bringing
home Sasuke.
The operation will
require the utmost focus.
And above all else,
be careful out there.
NARUTO: Got it.
NARRATOR: Next time, "An
Unnecessary Addition."
[music playing]
CHOJI: Society for Leaf
tourism-- all right, today
we'll be introducing you
to the BBQ restaurant.
This is the spot
where we celebrated
Shikamaru's promotion to chunin.
[sizzle]
-Oh man, that looks goo--
-Hold it, Naruto.
It's very tricky to grill
the meat so it's just right.
You better let me taste it.
Hm.
-Wha-- hey!
Stop, Choji.
You can't hog all the meat.
-Don't be so naive, Naruto.
Barbecue is war.
-Say what?
-Calm down, Naruto.
-Tell that to Fatso!
-Oh, that word is taboo.
-Uh-oh.
-I am not fat.
I am chubby!
[screams]
-Oh, man.
Can't you guys even
eat barbecue in peace?
You're both such a drag.
-I want meat.