[scream]
[gasp]
They're too strong!
Just how are we
supposed to--
Yes, you're right. At
this rate, we'll...
[battle cry]
Hokage! You're getting
sloppy with your fighting!
[grunting]
You keep it up, and soon
you'll have no stamina left.
I've put my life on the line
here! No saving strength;
I'll give it my all!
[wet cough]
Hokage!
No!
Damn! How could I have let
this happen?! I've fallen
prey to the Sharingan's
Genjutsu?
Release!
Thank you, Tsuchikage.
Damn Ohnoki...
His wisdom in battle is
beginning to show...
He stopped the Susano'o
with the Weighted Boulder
Jutsu...and managed to
save the Raikage.
Get up, fellow Kage! We
fight a battle to the end,
no whining, no complaining!
We are the Five Kage! So
choose final words that will
not shame the title you
hold!
We entrusted Naruto
to fight his battle!
And we swore to win this
fight that he entrusted to
us, no matter what! Don't
forget that!
And there is one more thing...
Each and every shinobi has
entrusted us with one duty.
All of us have to be worthy
of the title of Kage!
So Ohnoki is the
problem, after all.
I have no choice but
to break his will.
Princess! I need more!
You don't have to tell me!
There's not much chakra in
me! This could be our last
stand.
Particle Style! Boundary
Dismantling Jutsu!
My Susano'o kept me from
absorbing the Particle Style
properly!
I told you that only
physical attacks will work
against me.
You think you've eliminated
my clones and distracted me
with Particle Style?
You can't hold us
off for long!
If you don't like the
sand, just stop absorbing
the jutsu! Although then,
you'll be zapped by
the Lightning Water Dragon
and be immobilized.
Once that happens, I'll get
you with Particle Style for
sure! And that'll give us
enough time to
seal you away!
Don't you see?!
This is the full power
of the Five Kage!
I see... Indeed, this is truly
worthy of the shinobi who
bear the name Kage.
Then I, Madara Uchiha, shall
also respond with full
power!
Even the Five Kage are
nothing compared to the
power that I wield!
This is it! Meet the
Perfect Susano'o!
It's huge!
Is- Is this...?!
...the True Susano'o?!
Not quite...
Settle!
The big one's chakra has
stabilized... [gasp]
He's just so strong! I can't
believe Grandfather fought
someone like him!
I already explained this to
all of you... Only Hashirama
could stop me.
And he is no longer with us.
Though in a way you could
say that actually works out
better for you. Because...
[screaming]
It's just me...
So after all this, the maps
will only need to be redrawn
a little bit.
Impossible! He split
the mountain!
This is... Madara
Uchiha's strength?!
Then why earlier?
Why did you hold back
against us?
What adult would go
full-force when fighting
mere children? But anyway...
Are you finished now?
It may be true that we're
stumbling in the dark right
now, but we're also close to
the light at the
end of the tunnel!
Here, of all places!
My Susano'o is destruction
incarnate.
A single stroke of the blade
contains enough power to
smash all things in this
universe.
It rivals even the
Tailed Beasts!
Be crushed and begone, Kage!
You and your pathetic
philosophy!
Ne Ushi...
Saru...
Tora...
Tatsu...
I...
That's it, huh?
All right... Ne...
Ushi...
Saru...
I guess... it won't matter
what I say, will it?
As soon as I saw you... I
tailed you because I wanted
to confirm whether or not
Tobi and Danzo
told me the truth.
But that wasn't the only
thing that I was able to
verify.
When I'm with you, I
remember things.
Childhood feelings, of
adoring my big brother....
That's the reason why...
...the closer I get to you,
the closer we become to how
we were before, as brothers...
...And the more I
understand you.
The more that I come to hate
the Hidden Leaf Village for
causing you so much pain!
I hate it more now than I've
ever hated it before!
I know what you want me to
do, how you want me to be.
You're my big brother,
so I know you're going
to disapprove. But it's
because I'm your
brother that no matter what
you say, you're not going to
stop me!
Even if you protect the
village now...
...I will still
destroy it someday.
Tora...
Tatsu...
So it's goodbye...
I...
Reanimation Jutsu, Release!
Big Brother!
Lord Tsuchikage...It's
unfortunate, but I think
this is the end.
Silence, Mizukage!
I'm not going
to give up yet!
What is going on?
Something has happened
to the jutsu caster.
There is still time.
I can feel myself slowly
losing consciousness now...
I must tell you everything
before I say goodbye and we
part for good.
There is no need
to lie anymore.
The night I left you...
I did everything Danzo and
Tobi told you I did.
[gasp]
I'll show you...
the entire truth.
These are Itachi's
memories!
It seems we can't prevent
the Uchiha coup-d'état.
And if civil war erupts in
the Leaf, the other villages
will invade for sure. True
war will break out.
When I tried to
stop all this with
the Koto Amatsukami,
Danzo stole my right eye.
That man doesn't
trust me at all.
He intends to protect the
village his way, no matter
what it takes or how it
looks.
I suspect he'll come after
my left eye, so I'll give it
to you before he has a
chance.
Shisui...
You're the only one I can
count on, my best friend.
Protect the village. And the
Uchiha name. Both of them.
We cannot condone
this any longer.
If they're going to start a
revolution and use it to try
to usurp our power.
Then we have no choice but
to judge the Uchiha as
traitors to the Hidden Leaf!
Please wait, Koharu.
Don't rush to conclusions.
However, Hiruzen, the Uchiha
Clan will not be dissuaded.
And since that is, in fact,
the case, we must take
measures to avoid any
mayhem.
That includes innocent
children, too.
Don't say such things in
front of Itachi!
Besides which, a battle
against the Uchiha will be
far from an easy task.
We must plan our strategy
very carefully.
We're in a race against
time, here.
We ought to strike them
preemptively, before they
can make their first move.
If we join forces, and use
our respective Black Ops to
launch a surprise attack
from behind, we'll
end this fast.
The Uchiha are
comrades in arms.
I would like to use words
first before violence.
I will come up
with a strategy.
Itachi...
It doesn't have to be long
But buy me as much time as
you can.
Despite what Lord Third
said, he will move to
protect the Leaf if push
comes to shove.
That's the kind
of man he is.
In which case...
As the Hokage, even Hiruzen
will have to take decisive
measures.
Whether it starts a war or
not, once the coup d'état
happens, the Uchiha will
lock themselves
into a fate of getting
annihilated.
Including your innocent
little brother, who knows
nothing.
However, there is a way to
spare just your brother
prior to any revolt.
If things come to pass, your
brother will likely come to
know everything.
And if he witnesses a Leaf
Shinobi slaughtered his
entire clan, he will develop
a vengeful heart
towards the Leaf.
And then I'm afraid that he,
unfortunately, he will have
to die as well.
Is that a threat?
No, I'd just like you to
make a choice...
Either align yourself with
the Uchiha, launch the coup
d'état, and die along with
the rest of your clan...
Or side with the Leaf, save
your little brother before
the revolt, and then help us
eliminate all the
other Uchiha.
But no matter what happens,
to protect the Leaf, this
must be quelled before
mayhem arises.
The only one that can handle
this mission is you, a
double agent for both the
Uchiha and the Leaf.
Itachi...
There is no one else...
Itachi this will likely be
the most painful mission for
you...
But on the other hand, it
will allow your little
brother to be spared.
I know you care about the
village as much as I...
Will you accept
this mission?
How did you know about me?
You slipped through
the highest level of Leaf
Security and went to
examine the Nakano
Shrine's secret
stone tablet.
Only the Uchiha are
aware of its location.
After that, I studied your
movements, and looked into
what kind of character you
are and what your ideology is.
Well, that saves
me much time.
For then you already know
that I am an Uchiha myself
and bear hatred toward both
the Leaf and my own clan...
I have terms...
I'll help you exact revenge
upon the Uchiha Clan. But
you are not to harm the
village itself.
Nor...
Sasuke Uchiha.
Now I regret not telling you
everything before it had
come to this.
I see... So you've aligned
with the other side?
Father...
Mother...
I just...
We already know, Itachi.
Itachi, just
promise me this.
That you'll take
care of Sasuke.
I will.
Do not fear it.
This is the path
you have chosen.
Compared to yours, our pain
will be over in an instant.
Our philosophies may differ,
but I'm still proud of you.
You are truly a kind child.
There's nothing more to say.
I have told you
the whole truth...
I won't have to ever again...
I have always lied
to you and asked....
...for your forgiveness while
keeping you at a distance.
Because I wanted to
keep you out of this.
But now, I think...
That perhaps you could have
changed Father, Mother, and
the rest of the Uchiha as
well.
If I had only come to you
from the start, looked
straight into your eyes and
told you the truth.
Then I wouldn't have to
stand before you as a
failure, telling you all of
this.
But I want to impart at
least this much truth to
you...
You don't ever have
to forgive me.
And whatever you do from
here on out, know this...
No matter what, I will
love you always.
Naruto! The Jinchuriki are
gonna quit it! Looks like
Itachi did it!
Thanks, Itachi! Then this
means that the other battles
are...
Curse Kabuto. He has failed.
Hey, what do you think
you're looking at? We're
still fighting!
It looks like the
Reanimation Jutsu
has been released.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Reanimation
Jutsu: Release!"
And? What of it?