It appears that Fate
has decided you and
I would fight again.
After the last
time, I owe you
one!
My own puppet,
huh?
However, I no
longer care for
that body anymore.
Because at long last,
I'm finally a true doll
that will never, ever
rot away!
What I always
longed to be.
[gasp]
Run away, Sai.
Captain!
The Foundation
agent!
He swallowed
the clay!
Huh?
Using Lightning
Style can neutralize
Deidara's detonating
clay.
I still have
some chakra left.
Ittan, surround the
injured with protective
rock. Kiri, focus on
getting them healed up.
Too late!
Hearrrgh!
Now!
Secret Black
Technique!
Salamander!
Brother!
"Sai and Shin"
An explosion?!
But we must
reinforce. And
crush our enemy.
Zaji! How's
it going?
Good, I think.
I can still sense
their chakra.
Everyone's alive!
[struggling]
I can't believe
we survived that.
Huh? Sai!
The Salamander, huh?
He surrounded the
bomb with a defensive
puppet he'd hidden
underground.
Because of that,
the blast didn't
have much force.
Hmph.
He's just...
a bomb...
...to you?
Hmph! You got something to
whine about?! You're just
garbage! You're not good
enough to replace Sasuke!
Shut the
hell up
weakling!
As long as his soul's
bound to this world,
he'll keep coming back
to life!
I can make him
into a bomb over
and over!
[laughing]
But Shin...
My brother.
I just...
I really don't
want to have to
hurt you, Sai.
I died...
...and when I did
I was freed from
the foundation.
I have heard rumors about the
Leaf's Foundation. You're
raised together from the time
you're young, like siblings.
And then forced to
fight and kill one
another in the end.
A training system
that destroys
emotions.
Where there's no
feeling, there is
no doubt.
And that makes for
a truly powerful
shinobi.
You of the Foundation
are just like me.
Don't call yourself
an artist just because
you can draw a little bit!
True art is an explosion!
And I think it's time for
another big one!
Just you try it!
There's a drawing
I want to show you,
Brother.
Oh? Well, then,
let me see it!
No, I can't; it's
not finished yet.
I'll show you
when it's done.
[grunt]
Secret Black
Technique.
[grunt]
Damn it!
How annoying!
I knew I should
have detonated
myself a long
time ago!
It's tasteless to exhibit
one's ultimate art over
and over, but if I must!
Fine! Hmph!
[grunt]
Lightning Style?!
[gasp]
Triple Iron Maiden!
[heavy breathing]
[struggling]
Excellent job, Omoi! You
don't have to worry about these
two anymore. I'll use my Puppet
Jutsu to keep them restrained.
Now go help
Sai's brother!
Roger!
I always knew... in the
Foundation, I was going
to have to face you in
battle one day.
So let's settle now
what we couldn't
back then.
My kunai is
in the target.
I guess I win.
I'll bet that mine
collided in mid-air
and was knocked off
course.
I'm so unlucky.
Luck is a skill too,
you know. Well, it's
decided: you're on
meal duty today.
Yeah.
[struggling]
[wet coughing]
Are you
all right?
Stay back!
Huh?
It's nothing.
Oh...
Okay, then.
(Sai)
Hey
Huh?
Just how long has
it been since both
of us came here?
Dunno.
Why?
Oh.  Well...
I was wondering
how long we're
going to stay.
And I was thinking that you
and Lord Danzo are the only
people I ever see in this
place.
I'm starting to
lose track of
time here.
Of course,
I don't really
care!
That's because Shin,
I'd stay with you
forever if I could!
Me, too.
What is this?
Go on,
open it!
It's...
It's a sketchbook.
Yeah.
I know you've wanted
one for a long time.
So I bougt  last time
I went into town.
Thank you
so much!
You know what...
I think I'm going
to draw pictures of
you and me in here.
Huh?
I'm gonna make this
into a picture book
that tells the story
of you and me.
Sounds great.
And you'll show it to
me when it's finished?
Seriously! I want you
to promise that you'll
show it to me, okay?
Mhm.
Huh? Lord Danzo..
what did you say?!
Could you repeat that?
The order I gave you is not
complicated in the slightest:
the two of you are going to
fight each other, to the death.
But that's...
This is your final test
and your fate. You are
members of the Foundation.
After three days,
if you two are still alive
and you make any attempt to
descend from this mountain..
..Then the both of
you are going to be
killed. Understood?
No, this...
can't be.
I can't kill
my brother.
Then...
I'll just have
to kill you
instead!
[gasp]
Brother!
Are you
serious?!
[gasp]
Brother!
Huh?
You are far too
kind and naïve
to survive this.
Brother.
Still you are the
one who will live.
Huh?
[wet coughing]
[gasp]
[struggling]
I'm... sick.
We have to get
you some help!
[struggling]
It's useless.
I've already looked
into my illness.
There's nothing
we can do. It's
completely incurable.
No. That's...
Lord Danzo doesn't know anything
about this. So when you report
back to him just tell him that
you got rid of me.
No! I can't.
I knew all along
that the final test
of the Foundation
is to kill acomrade.
[gasp]
That's why I didn't
tell you that I was
sick before today.
I tried to live
with this secret.
So that I could
lose to you in
our fight.
[groan]
But...
[pained groan]
I don't think I even
have enough strength
left to pull that off.
Brother, I also knew
one day I was going
to have to battle
someone.
But never did I
imagine it was
going to be you!
[small chuckle]
So, you knew
all along.
Kill your emotions, Sai.
Because otherwise, your
duty is going to absolutely
destroy you.
Now go.
Go and live life
for the both of
us.
Brother.
I'm still capable...
[struggling]
...of ending my own
life.
[gasp]
Go!
[heavy breathing]
[small whimper]
Don't cry! Didn't
I tell you to kill
your emotions?!
[struggling]
I understand.
[wet coughing]
But I really do
wish that I could
have seen your
finished drawing.
You want to settle
our last match?
Hey, Sai.
You doin'
all right?
Sai, I see.
So that's what
your name is now,
is it?
But you know.
It's not necessary.
[gasp]
Brother.
I'm really glad
that you finished
it.
I finally got to see
the drawing that I
longed to see.
And it's as though...
Your drawing has
freed my soul from
all of its bindings.
[gasp]
Sai...
These comrades
who call you by
your name...
Cherish them.
Thank you.
What's going
on out there?
My threads just
went slack.
Sasori, Sakura once
explained to me all
about the way you
do battle.
The girl who was
with Granny Chiyo
back then.
Get over here!
[attack punch]
[gasp]
I forbade even
myself use of
this jutsu.
I never imagined
I would use it
again.
But against
you I must.
[grunt]
It's time that
we finish this,
here and now!
There's so
many of them!
It's said the ability of a
puppet master is measured
by the number of puppets
they can use.
I'd expect no
less from you,
Grandmother.
Granny Chiyo's Secret
Multiple Digits. I've
heard tell of their glory...
You once destroyed
an entire fortress
with it...
Secret White Move:
Chikamatsu's Ten Puppets.
Ten Masterpieces.
All created by the
first Puppet Master
Monzaemon.
An exquisite
collection.
However...
I used these to
destroy an entire
nation.
[gasp]
Secret Red Move:
Performance of a
Hundred Puppets.
The true source
of your power
lies in your soul.
You tried to erase
your soul by becoming
a puppet, but you
didn't fully succeed.
I can still feel it,
inside this puppet
that you made, where
your undying soul dwells.
You may inhabit living
flesh now, but that's
only a shell, nothing
more than a mere puppet.
You were a first-rate
shinobi puppet master
at one time.
Not just some
lowlife that allows
another person to
manipulate him.
And if I'm not mistaken,
you were using Kabuto as
your spy back then.
But the tables have
turned now; he's the
one using you.
A puppet master
controlled by
another is done
for.
Whether it's you or whoever
might be controlling you,
there's no way that I'm
going to lose here.
Because now I am
the ninja puppet
master of the real
Sasori puppet!
Your art, the puppets
that you've created,
will live on forever.
As long as future generations
of puppet masters still remain
to inherit the soul that resides
within them.
[chuckle]
So that is precisely
the true form of art
I sought.
Hey, quit messing
around, would ya?!
Don't listen, Sasori!
Don't pay any attention
to that jerk at all, do
you hear me?! Hmph!
Art is a solitary
flash of light!
True art is an
explosion!
You hear me,
Sasori?!
The soul of the
creator dwells
within, huh?
You're right.
Kankuro...
What is it?
I entrust you with
the "Father" and
"Mother" puppets.
When you pass, give
them to another, so
that they may live
forever, too.
Because those
two are...
Of course. Yes,
I understand.
[grunt]
Hey! Sasori!
No!
It was a sacrificial
victim. What's going
on here?
We were told that no
one who's under the
Reanimation Jutsu
could be killed.
Maybe Kabuto
released a jutsu?
(deidara)
Let me out of
here, you bastard!
No, it doesn't seem that way.
Sasori is gone but that loud
one is still here, clearly.
All along we thought that
the Reanimation Jutsu had
been perfected, but it
seems to have a flaw.
Apparently it isn't
quite so easy to
control someone's
emotions.
Looks like
it's over.
No.
It's just
starting...
Sai, Omoi, Zaji!
Set up an ambush!
Yes, sir!
Roger!
Yeah.
What is it?
Oh, It's
nothing
at all.
The Reanimation Jutsu...
There are still so many
mysteries behind it. But I
think that I've figured it out.
Madara, you head out to the
front line. I'll stay hidden
and concentrate on the jutsu
for now.
This woman...
She got this close
to the hideout...
And Kabuto was
aware of it. Did
he purposely lead
her here?
That snake Kabuto.
He's pitting me against
the Allied Shinobi Forces.
[chuckle]
That will never happen.
I'm the one who will
use him.
The Reanimation Jutsu. Prove
to me right now that it really
requires living bodies. And
tell me all its secrets.
And if I say no?
You will surely not reach what
you desire, and what you desire
will become something else. It
will be your life!
Next time on
Naruto Shippuden:
"Secrets of the
Reanimation Jutsu."
Very well,
I'll explain.