You actually tailed Samui.
You guys are pretty impressive.
But, but you--
How dare you, Naruto!
You tailed us here?!
What's the big idea?!
Hey, boss. That guy?
The one standing
there on the right?
It's Kakashi Hatake.
Come on. I know that much!
You the Hokage's errand boy,
Kakashi Hatake?!
No sir, today I've
come to ask a favor.
Naruto Uzumaki of the Leaf
would like to petition you.
Naruto Uzumaki, huh?
[Kakashi]
I was hoping you could
hear his supplication.
Don't you think
this is a bit rude?
To interrupt us on the
way to the Summit without
any prior notice at all?
Yes, we're quite
aware of that.
Enough of this.
All right, you there, boy!
Start talking!
It's Sasuke.
I want you to cancel the
elimination of Sasuke Uchiha!
[gasps]
Hey, Naruto, This
isn't really the
time or place--
Are you still going
on about that?!
Pretty brave.
Just what are you
talking about?
I know what I'm asking may
sound ridiculous to you,
But this is the only way that
I really know how to say it!
Sasuke is my friend!
And I can't just stand around,
and watch my friend get killed!
And besides, I don't want
Leaf and Cloud ninja killing
each other because of Sasuke!
I don't want my
friends or yours,
To get lost in their
need for revenge!
Look, I'm begging you!
I don't want us taking
each other down for
vengeance anymore!
Sasuke has always been
all about vengeance!
He's obsessed with it.
It changed him!
Vengeance... drives you mad.
It turns you into someone
you don't even recognize.
I don't want anyone else
to become like Sasuke!
I don't want the Leaf and
Cloud to kill each other!
And that's why...
[sobs]
All right, I have work to
do so I'm going back.
Would you mind taking
the mission report to
Kakashi Sensei?
Yeah! Sure, no
problem, Sakura!
See ya!
I have a question, Naruto.
Mmm?
You like Sakura,
don't you?
What?!
I saw it in a book,
that one tends to
smile when they're
with someone you love.
Around Sakura, you're like that.
Have you told her?
How can I? After all,
I'm the guy who couldn't even
keep a promise to her.
She's right. Just stay
out of this, Sai.
No. I won't. I can't just
sit still either, Naruto.
[sobbing]
No matter what,
we will dispose
of Sasuke!
You all ought to hold
your ground afterwards!
That's right.
You're a fool!
We're in a rush, so, sorry.
Your time is up.
Lord Raikage, please.
The incident in which you tried
to obtain the Hyuga Byakugan is
still unresolved on our side.
[Yamato]
The Hidden Leaf swallowed our
tears of blood to avoid war,
a war whose seeds you
of the Cloud had sown.
Because of those
noble sacrifices,
your people still exist.
Do not forget that.
[Kakashi]
Right here and now, this young
shinobi, no matter how awkward,
is bowing his head with respect
and affection for the Cloud and
Leaf, village and nation.
So, Lord Raikage.
As one of the Five Kage,
Tell me, what do you
think of this?
[sobbing]
Shinobi shouldn't lower
their heads so easily!
Action and power are the things
that a shinobi should respect!
Concessions are forbidden in
agreements between shinobi.
The history of mankind
is a history of war.
Since the Three Great
Ninja Wars, every nation
has tried to obtain
powerful ninjutsu.
Those who are weak
are trampled!
That is the truth of
the shinobi world.
We'll brand the Akatsuki
as wanted criminals.
Once we do, not only I,
but the whole world
will hunt Sasuke down.
You bow your head for a
criminal and beg mercy to
keep your comrade safe.
In the shinobi world,
that is not friendship!
You Hidden Leaf brat!
think more deeply on what
it is you ought to do.
The shinobi world is not so
indulgent as to suffer fools.
Let's go!
Hmf.
Naruto, enough.
Raise your head.
[frustrated sob]
Sir, we've been
waiting for you.
[White Zetsu]
That's him.
The geezer in the middle.
So that's...
Danzo!
[Mifune]
Place your Kage
headpieces before you.
You, the Five Kage, assemble
here today in response to
Lord Raikage's summons.
I, Mifune, will preside
over these proceedings.
And now, let the Five
Kage Summit commence!!
Naruto's Plea
I, Mifune, will preside
over these proceedings.
And now, let the Five
Kage Summit commence!!
Then allow me to begin.
Listen--
[Tsuchikage]
Heh! My, my...
How the Kage have changed.
To be named Kage at
your young age is
quite impressive,
Lord Kazekage.
Yet despite your father's
obviously brilliant guidance,
He seems to have not
taught you any etiquette.
Tch!
Yes, probably.
That's why I was
chosen as Kazekage.
Bah hah hah hah!
You cheeky young rascal!
Lord Tsuchikage, Please
don't interrupt any more.
Please continue,
Lord Kazekage.
I am a former Jinchuriki.
The Akatsuki captured me.
What's with that
Tsuchikage?
Just be quiet!
And that's why I consider
the Akatsuki to be an
extremely dangerous group.
I sought the aid of the
Five Kage many times,
but was ignored.
Except for the previous Hokage.
Jinchuriki from all your
nations have been taken.
To collaborate at
this point is simply
too little, too late.
Hah.
The Five Great Nations'
Hidden Villages can't
afford to alert others
that their Jinchuriki
were taken; it's an
embarrassment!
Covert rescue and
recovery is the norm.
No one seeks aid from other
lands when Jinchuriki disappear!
Appearances, and status.
Such foolish,
outdated concepts.
Hmph! How dare that
stripling...
Setting aside whether those
beliefs are outdated or not,
I will acknowledge that as
Mizukage, I refrained from
acting on this issue.
However, I don't believe that
having our Tailed Beasts stolen
is cause for immediate alarm.
After all, it still takes
significant skill,
knowledge, and time to
achieve control over them.
A Jinchuriki needs to mature
along with their Tailed
Beast to adapt to it.
And even then, control
remains difficult.
It's not a simple task.
Wouldn't you agree with that,
Lord Kazekage?
Very few have achieved
control over Tailed Beasts.
Madara Uchiha and
First Hokage
Senju Hashirama.
And of cousre the
Fourth Mizukage Yagura,
as well as Lord
Raikage's brother,
Killer Bee.
However...
Chojuro!
Yes, sir!
Enough...
...of this nonsense!
[sigh]
This Summit is a
place of discourse.
So, please refrain
from any more behavior
that lacks civility.
Stand down, Foo, Torune.
You too, Kankuro, Temari.
Ao, Chojuro.
It's all right.
Yes, ma'am.
Mmm.
Now let's continue
our discussion.
The Hidden Leaf. The Stone.
The Sand. The Mist.
The Akatsuki's membership
is composed of Rogue
Shinobi from your villages!
That's not all, either!
From our investigations, we
know that among you and the
earlier Kage, there are those
who've even used the Akatsuki!
The Kage used them?!
And that's why I don't trust
any of you! I have no
interest in any discourse.
But the reason I've
summoned you all to
this Summit,
is to ultimately
question your loyalties.
What do you mean, that
they used the Akatsuki?
You're the Kazekage,
and yet you don't
know anything?
Just ask your village
elders back home!
You of the Sand have previously
used the Akatsuki in battle!
Currently, all Five Great
Nations are equally stable.
They're moving from military
expansion to disarmament.
As strained relations
between nations ease and the
threat of war diminishes,
Hidden Villages, considered
military powers by their nation,
merely become costly hindrances.
And yet at the same time,
completely eliminating
such villages poses its
own risks, as well.
What if war suddenly
breaks out?
Relying on ninja with
no battle experience
would be problematic.
You'd lose the battle,
without question!
The Kage would realize that
one way to avoid that risk,
is to use mercenary soldiers.
Namely, soldiers
from the Akatsuki?
It takes effort and money
to cultivate accomplished
ninja from within one's
own Hidden Village.
The Akatsuki makes war its
livelihood and is made up of
experienced professionals.
Furthermore, they can
be hired quite cheaply.
Best of all,
Their solders have always
delivered superior results.
Don't be pompous,
Tsuchikage!
Hmf.
The Sand once used the
Akatsuki to try to destroy
the Hidden Leaf.
I'm talking about Orochimaru!
Though he may have already
left the Akatsuki by then.
But as a result, your father,
the Fourth Kazekage, and the
Third Hokage, Hiruzen, perished.
It's also hard to dismiss the
possibility that this was all
part of an even larger plot.
That crafty old badger.
But the most
suspicious of all
is the Hidden Mist!
The Mist never
engages in diplomacy.
And it's rumored that the
Akatsuki started there!
Since it's come to this,
I'll be honest.
Don't tell me Lady Fifth
is going to mention--!
We suspect,
that someone from behind the
scenes was secretly
manipulating Yagura, the man
who was Mizukage before me.
There's a possibility that
that someone was the Akatsuki.
And that, is exactly why I
didn't want to talk big and...
[trails off]
Each and every one of you!
You just watch your
tone, Raikage!
In fact, it's because you
of the Cloud went around
collecting ninjutsu.
...seeking more power in
this era of disarmament!
We had no choice but to hire
the Akatsuki in order to try
to counter your growing power!
What was that?!
Mgh.
[Danzo]
Before you start arguing
each other's merits,
I would like to state
the point that I was
about to make earlier.
What's that?
It's probable that the
leader of the Akatsuki,
is Madara Uchiha.
Are you sure of that?!
But how could that
even be possible?
Hasn't he been dead
for several decades?
The Kazekage's right!
Madara has been dead
for a long, long time.
Well, I don't know
all of the details.
But the information is from
quite a reliable source.
Are you saying
he's immortal?!
Perhaps.
So, then, he really is some
kind of inhuman monster.
[ahem]
I'd like to say this as the
leader of a neutral nation.
The leader of the
Akatsuki has been able
to read the times well.
Despite stabilizing,
the Great Nations harbor
suspicions about each other.
And the Akatsuki seized on that
weakness to amass its power.
Would you just
get to the point!
Now, please just stay calm.
We can turn this misfortune
into a blessing.
It's very rare for all five Kage
to convene in one location.
What do you all say to this:
Until the Akatsuki
are disposed of,
why not establish the world's
first Allied Shinobi Forces of
the Five Hidden Villages?
An allied ninja force?
That's a splendid idea.
We're practically in a
state of emergency.
Cooperation will be crucial now.
This is going perfectly.
Moving forward with this plan,
a standardized chain of command
would also be ideal.
Further chaos must be avoided.
All right, and whom do you
propose handing the reins of
these allied forces to, then?
If the choice were left to
you, you'd all just argue.
Therefore, since you have deemed
me to be a neutral party worthy
of presiding over you, I would
like to make this suggestion.
I will decide who among
you five Kage is the most
suitable to lead.
This spells the end
of Tsunade's era.
The Leaf has the last
Jinchuriki, the one
containing the Nine-Tails.
I feel that how he is
guided will be the key.
I say, why not allow the
Hokage to lead the
Allied Shinobi Army?
Grr.
Wha?
[gasp]
Mh?
[Ino] [crying]
Why'd it have to turn
out like this?!
[Kiba]
Stop crying, Ino!
[Temari]
Don't talk to her like that!
You know how Ino's felt
about Sasuke.
[Kiba]
It can't be helped!
Things are different now.
[Shino]
You sure about this?
If that's Ino's reaction,
how will Naruto and Sakura feel?
[Neji]
Leave it to Shikamaru.
He always knows the
right thing to say.
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden,
"A Painful Decision."
[Sakura]
Wait, Shikamaru!