(Madara)
This place was known
as the "Training Cave"
Hey, tell me about
this new jutsu.
What exactly does this
Limited Tsukuyomi do?
And experimental version
of the Infinite Tsukuyomi.
First, we need to
understand the true
desires of our target.
Hm.
(Naruto)
I can't believe it's the
last day of my R & R!
All right!I need to
re-energize for tomorrow
so it's time for me to
but out that limited
edition premium ramen
that I've been saving for
a time just like this!
[goofy happy laughs]
Man, am I bored.
Wait..!
Ha! Tadah! Guess
what this is!
Whoa, no way! It's
that premium ramen!
Every store's sold out
of it! You can't find
it anywhere anymore!
Well, today's your
lucky day, 'cause
you get to have some!
Are you in, or what!?
-Yeah!
Do ya really want some!?
Really, really
want some--?
-Yeah! C'mon!
Cook it up!
Well then, let's
play some cards!
And whoever wins
gets to have the
ramen as a prize!
Yay! Awesome!
[sigh] I'm so tired.
But, at long last,
the mission's over
and I finally get
a break tomorrow!
Oh, Kakashi! Please
do me a favor and
take over, okay?
Sure, sure.
Roger that.
I really need
to go unwind.
How about the
bathhouse?
Hm. Lee, are you
coming with us?
Thank you,
but I cannot!
Now that the mission
is over, I must get
back to training!
That's admirable.
But listen, don't
overdo it, or your
body won't be able
to keep--
[happy sob] That's my
dedicated boy, Lee!
You're brimming with
youth! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Whaddaya say we
train together!?
(Guy)
Let's go!
(Lee)
Right!
Are they okay?
Follow me! We'll rush
forward with the full
power of youth!
Ahhhh!
Nope. Just as
I thought...
Ahh! Guy Sensei!
Get up! Please!
You have to get up!
You must face tomorrow!
Lee... his body simply
won't do what he tells
it anymore.
Please do not die!!!
No! Guy Sensei!!!
You made me a promise
that you would make
me a fine shinobi!
[sigh] Lee, listen.
I'll take over looking
after Guy, but can you
take a message from me
to Sakura and Naruto!?
Huh..?
Do you have to
be so messy!?
Why can't you line
up the seams when
you fold laundry!?
Do it yourself
if you're going
to complain!
I really don't need
to hear a bunch of
useless lectures from
you on my day off!
The only time you're
ever home is on your
day off!
(Sakura)
Duh, of course.
(Mebuki)
Don't you talk
back to me--!
[groan]
(Kizashi)
Sakura, you need to
listen to your mother.
She's absolutely correct.
So stop arguing with
her, and don't be so
salty!
Salt... get it!?
[groan]
Lee, what's up?
Uhh, sorry to
interrupt but, I
have a message...
about your mission.
Ohhh, you must mean
the prep meeting for
our next mission!
I'll be right there!
Sorry. I did not
want to bother you--
But the message is for
you to meet tomorrow
morning at six.
It's okay. You gave me
a good excuse to leave!
[stretching] I really
just wanted to take
it easy today, ya know?
So, thank you, Lee!
Now... the next stop!
Yes!! I win!!
I'm not having
any luck at all!
Oh boy, that was
a close call! I
almost went in!
Listen, you! You
better not be cheating!
It's always the weak
ones who complain!
What was that--!?
Cut it out, ya
know? You're all
me, so get along!
Hey, who's side are
you on, anyway!?
Well now that
you ask...
I demand we start
the game over!
The loser sure
knows how to whine!
All right that's
it! Let's go outside!
[groan]
Huh!?
Wait, I have no
idea if I won or
lost that game!
[weary sigh]
What am I doin'
hangin' out here by myself
on my last day off?
Boy, it sure does
get lonely around
here sometimes...
(Thinking)
Naruto...
(Choji)
Please, let's go
to Barbe-Q's!
They're doing this all-
you-can-eat special for
fifteen hundred ryo per
table--
--So even if we split
it between the three
of us, it's only...
Let's see... it's uhh...
Five hundred ryo.
We just completed a
mission. I'd rather have
a soak than food right now.
Yeah, I vote
for a soak, too!
(Kiba)
Akamaru, You're more
dirt than dog, now! I
should call you "Chamaru!"
Get it? 'Cause
"cha" means "brown"
[whimper]
Actually, Akamaru should
never be called Akamaru,
because his name means "red."
So instead, Akamaru should
be called "Shiromaru" because
"shiro" means "white."
I don't have any
idea what you're
yapping about!
All I was saying
is that Akamaru is
filthy and that I
need to clean him up!
Ever heard of a
sense of humor?
Then you ought to
bring him to the
bathhouse with the
rest of us!
Impossible... Dogs
are never allowed
in the bathhouse.
(Kiba)
Well I'll just have to
figure something out!
[gasp]
I really need to
go unwind. How about
the bathhouse?
Ahhh!
Naruto! Listen! Let us
gather everyone and
go to the bathhouse!
Everyone! We should all
go to the bathhouse
together and unwind in the
company of true friends!
I don't get it. Lee's
the one who suggested
this. Why isn't he here?
He;s not done training
yet. He still has to
walk three thousand
steps on his hands.
He said he'll come
once he finishes.
He sure is
dedicated...
(Thinking)
Bushy Brows was being
thoughtful because he saw
that I was all by myself.
I just really hope
he gets here soon!
(Thinking)
Just when I thought
I could relax by myself.
Oh well, whatever!
[sigh] Nothing like
a hot soak to warm
your tired boned
after a mission..!
Tenten, you sound like
an old man or something!
[giggle]
[embarrassed gasp]
Hinata! Just relax.
Don't be embarrassed
and try to hide yourself!
We're all women here.
(Sakura)
Just sink in and
enjoy the bath!
Oh... Umm... I...
[gasp]
But... they just
keep floating up!
[groan]
(Thinking)
Is it wrong that I'm
jealous of Hinata..?
...of her chest
that is...
I must hurry!
One thousand eight-
hundred fifty-two!
hundred fifty-three!
One thousand eight-
hundred fifty-four!
I wonder if Bushy-Brows
is still at it...
He's a hard worker,
but he can't read
people too well...
That's not unusual.
And why is that, you
ask? Because he's a
worker ant.
And boy, do I ever
love ants like that.
You must look at
your comrades in a
more generous light.
(Thinking)
I can't believe
this guy...
He's actually still
bitter from the time
that he was left out
of that mission!
Wow, Shino! What a
nice thing to say!
You sure have a big--
Ahhhhh!
That's so disgusting!
Shino! Don't look now,
but there's a giant
larva near your groin!
He's an insect user,
of course some of them
will end up on his body!
Oh!
Shino, you're one of the
guys that I really look up
to... in more ways than one!
Hm? Really?
Hey, did ya hear
that, Kiba?
Huh?
[barking]
Huh!?
That's Akamaru!
They don't allow dogs
here, so I used Man-Beast
Transformation to get him in.
Argh!
Yoooow!!!
Ahhhhh!
[whine]
Got a strike!!
Or something...
Hey, watch it,
would you, Choji!?
The water level dropped!
Ugh, just great.
Now what...
(Neji)
How can we soak
with no water!?
They're being
so noisy!
(Choji)
Sorry, guys...
I'm really surprised you were
able to meet us here. Your
mother is usually so strict.
Yeah, she's
such a pain...
My mom always piled
on the chores when
I'm off, too...
If I complain, my
dad says, "Mind
Destruction Jutsu..!"
[gasps]
But, I am a
bit jealous...
What!?
Choji, use your
Expansion Jutsu.
Huh? What for?
Just do it.
Yeah, sure,
why not?
Expansion Jutsu!
Whoa, where'd all
this water come from?
Sure, there's more
water, but there's hardly
any room to move..!
[laughing]
(Thinking)
Man, I always have fun
with them! It's way
better than being alone!
I wonder what he's
doin' right now...
He's the only one
who's really changed...
If he hadn't, he'd
be here too...
Huh? Sasuke?
But, how..?
Something wrong?
What's with that look,
Naruto? You're not
planning some kind of
mischief, are you..?
What are you talking
about, Neji? I was
just lost in thought,
that's all!
Well I hope that's
true! You'd better
not be up to your
old tricks again!
What!? What tricks?
Peeping, perhaps?
Whaaat?
[girls giggling]
Oh, right. On the
other side is...
There's a whole
different kind of
fun to be had...
Aaah. Yeah, that bath
sure felt good, didn't it?
Hey, wait! Did
you even soak?
Two thousand nine-
hundred and ninety-eight!
Wait, Naruto. I
am coming soon!
Two thousand nine-
hundred and ninety-nine!
Ahhh!
Now, the real trick
about peeping is to
not get caught..!
[crash and screams]
What just happened?
Naruto...!
[groaning]
Lee..!?
What are you
doing here!?
[gasp]
Rock Lee, you creep!
You were just trying to
peep on us, weren't you!?
N-no!
I was passing by while
training and got caught
on something--! It was
only and accident!
Oh, really? You
just happened to be
on the bathhouse?
I don't buy it!
I'm gonna take
care of you..!
No..! No!
Bushy Brows...
(Neji)
Naruto! I knew it!
No! It wasn't me!
(Ino)
Don't act all
innocent, Rock Lee!
[gasp] Rock Lee?
What happened here!?
[embarrassed shriek]
N-Naruto..!
Rock Lee's been
peeping on us!
He did what!?
How improper!
See? See!? SEE!?
Now stop pretending!
Bushy Brows...
Did you...
[sobbing]
[gasp]
Hey! He's running
away!
Argh!!!
Running makes
him look even more
suspicious!
Let's get him!
That pervert!
Don't let him
get away!
[gasp]
We should all go to the
bathhouse and unwind in
the company of true friends!
Naruto, listen! Let us
gather everyone and go
to the bathhouse!
This is our day off!
Do not stay inside by
yourself... let us go
have fun...!
I have some training that
I need to finish first,
but I will rush over as
soon as I am done!
It is because I
cannot lie to myself!
(Thinking)
Bushy Brows went out and
rounded everyone up, just
for me!
He'd never do something
like this..!
(Neji)
I thought you were
above this...
You have it wrong! I was
jumping between roofs, my
sleeve caught on something
and then, well...
You see!? It is torn!
I got knocked off balance
unexpectedly, and then I just
fell in there by accident!
No more excuses!
Stay calm, everyone.
Maybe it was just an
accident!
Thank you, Sakura!
Eh, shut up! You're
suspicious enough to
get a beating!
Wait! Stop!
Huh?
Bushy Brows isn't
that kind of person.
Naruto..!
He's our friend! So if
he says that he's innocent,
then I believe that he's
innocent!
Don't judge him when
you don't have any proof
that he's guilty!
Trust in your
comrade!
Maybe you're
right, Naruto...
I got caught up in the
moment and lost it...
Uh, Naruto...
Have a big heart,
and an open mind!
[gasps]
A piece of underwear
as small as that one
is, must belong to...
Hey, that's mine!
Oh, Naruto...
You're gonna get
it, Naruto..!
What?
You underwear thief!
What?!
Sureee... you act all
innocent, but we know
it's just an act!!!
Ahhhhhh!!!
(Naruto)
All I did was try to
take a little peek!
...and I didn't even
actually do it!
Ugh, this may be
the worst day of
my life...
[groan] Why does this
stuff always happen to me?
I knew that I shouldn't have
tagged along with those
so-called friends of mine, no
matter how lonely I was feeling
You know what?
Forget those guys...
[knocking]
Lee insisted that we
all come over and visit
you, so here we are!
(Kiba)
Now come on!
Open up!
[happy chewing / humming]
Maybe he went out, he
doesn't seem to be
answering the door.
Too bad. Let's
go, then.
Now, I can tell by
his scent that he's
inside there.
He must be upset...
about earlier.
Damn it! I can't believe
you guys came here! What
do you want, anyway?
I see, we must have
showed up here at a
bad time. Well, let's go.
Hee hee!
I guess we can
hang out...
(Neji)
What!?
Neji? You lost again!?
You're horrible!
I'm out, too.
I can't get a
good hand!
You guys had better
not be trying to cheat!
I am out!
(Kiba)
That's the howl of
a losing dog...!
(Shino)
Not true. The
reason is--
(Neji)
I can't stand this!
Deal another round!
(Shikamaru)
Oh, are we gonna
keep playing?
[laughter]
Ya know, you can stay
longer if you want.
Sorry, my mom gets
on my case if I'm
home too late.
Me too, I can't
miss dinner--
Ah-hem!
Wha..?
See you!
Yeah!
[village bustle]
[tea kettle whistle]
(Thinking)
Huh, that's funny. My
room looks bigger than
it usually does.
...I wonder if it's
because I had so
much fun here today...
I wish everyone could have
stuck around to eat...
...Times like these...
(Madara)
The time is ripe...
I have seen what lies
inside your heart,
Naruto Uzumaki!
Now... let the Limited
Tsukuyomi begin!
(Lee)
Old Master Chen! It is
an honor to see you again!
(Guy)
He died before you were
even born! So how could you
have possibly met him!?
(Lee)
The Old Master did not
die when you think he did.
(Master Chen)
You're that brat
from back then!?
(Lee)
There is no way that I could
ever forget you.. . or the
Dragon's Eye!
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Old Master and the Dragon's
Eye."
(Master Chen)
I see that you are
still a shinobi!