-You're telling me you want to
master a new jutsu right now?
It just can't be done.
It's impossible.
-I don't care if it is.
I don't have any other choice.
-Right.
This'll be a bit on the
harsh side, but we'll try it.
-You mean it?
You have some kinda idea?
GAMAKICHI: You.
Hop into Gamatatsu's mouth.
-Uh--
-Well, then, what do we do?
Thanks to the bats, the enemy
already knows our location.
They could take action
against us at any moment.
-The enemy will
either pull back,
knowing that a confrontation
with the four of us
would waste a lot of time,
or they'll hit us hard.
-In any case, our mission
is to capture the bad guys
and extract information out
of them, no matter what.
If we lose track of
the enemy, something
tells me they're going to become
a big problem for the Hidden
Leaf Village.
HINATA: We have
to keep searching.
-Right.
-Now, listen up, people.
Lord Orochimaru has given
us a very important mission.
We have to deliver this boy
to a specific lake safely.
Mistakes will not be tolerated.
However, a group of
strangers have followed us
from the hideout.
-That's pretty
perceptive of you, Guren.
Just what I'd expect from you.
The enemy has four ninja
and one ninja hound.
Right now, three of them and the
dog are a couple of kilometers
away from our position.
-What do we do?
-I know just the thing.
And when I'm through, they
won't be following us anymore.
Bring them to me, and
I will crush them.
[theme music]
-Right!
OK, guys, I think
I can do it now.
-That's the spirit, Naruto.
-All right, Gamatatsu.
Let me in there one more time.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): OK.
Feel it, now.
Gamatatsu's chakra.
I can feel how he builds it
up, before he spits it out.
[scream]
-Sorry.
-Oh, no!
Naruto!
Are you OK?
Talk to me.
-Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
And I think I just finally
figured something out.
-Did you, now?
GAMAKICHI (VOICEOVER):
Well, well.
Things are getting interesting.
-OK, don't stop now.
Let's keep working on it,
while it's fresh in my mind.
SAKURA: Naruto!
-Huh?
-Hm?
Uh, hi, Sakura.
-Come on.
Enough wasting time here.
We've got stuff to do.
Whoa, you smell terrible.
What happened to you?
And how come you're all slimy?
-Actually, believe
it or not, we've
been working on something
really important.
-Yeah, yeah, tell me later.
Everybody's waiting for you.
Let's go!
-Hey!
Hey, Sakura, come on.
I'm in the middle of training.
-I'll give you training.
-Sorry, Gamakichi.
Sorry, guys.
I guess I gotta go
now, but I'll call you!
Don't worry!
-All right, but keep training.
-Hey, big brother, do
you have any mouthwash?
-I can see it.
And it looks like the
chakra of shinobi!
Watch out!
-So, you must be
their leader, huh?
-Kakashi-sensei!
-Sensei!
-No!
Kiba, don't!
-What?
-Huh.
I missed.
Oh well, what can you do?
Now that Gozu's got their
leader out of the way,
the rest of them shouldn't
be too difficult.
Since you found us, you must
have great tracking skills.
You're gonna wish you
didn't by the time
we're finished with you.
-Are they-- are they the ones--
-Yeah.
Must be.
They've gotta be the
ones in that hideout.
No question.
Better watch your step, Hinata.
-Right.
Taking on three of them.
What's our strategy?
-Akamaru's jutsu
and mine are linked.
If we can take out one of
them, reduce their numbers,
that ought to improve the odds.
-And after that?
-I'd like to say we wipe
the floor with them,
but I guess the
safest plan is just
to hold them long enough for
Kakashi-sensei to get back
here and help us out.
-Got it.
-We should target one
of the two in front.
This masked guy's
hiding something.
I wanted to know what it
is before I took him on.
Which leaves-- now, Akamaru!
Fang Over Fang!
-Smokescreen, Kigiri.
-Kiba!
-Poison gas?
[barking]
-Cool.
Thanks, Akamaru.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): If it's
not poison, what is it, then?
Some kind of diversion?
What?
Hold on.
I'm not getting
their scent anymore.
I can't smell
anything at all now.
I get it.
This fog's more
than a diversion.
They're using it to
cover their movements.
This is bad.
I can't see 'em.
I can't smell 'em.
Hey, wait a second.
What's true for me must
be true for them, too.
So how come these guys
know exactly where I am?
-Nurari, go on.
-Uh-oh.
They're coming.
-Duck!
-Hinata?
-Fal back, Kiba.
I'll handle this.
-Be careful, Hinata.
I don't know why
it is, but this fog
doesn't seem to affect
their movements,
or their ability to see us.
-Well, they can take away
my sight and sense of smell,
but I've still got my Byakugan.
-OK.
Come on, Akamaru!
-You're facing me now.
Just try it!
-How can you-- impossible!
You can't!
Not in this smokescreen.
-Oh, yes.
I can see every attack
you throw at me.
Right here!
[scream]
-Just kidding.
-What?
Did I miss?
It's not possible.
How?
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): His
strength is incredible.
-Huh?
Now die!
Ha ha ha!
A shadow clone.
-That's right.
I'd be crazy to take on someone
as strong as you in a stand up
fight.
Your muscles have been
enhanced beyond their limits.
Did Orochimaru do that for you?
Run around all you want.
You can't beat me.
Your assets are your speed
and incredible strength,
but I can anticipate
your every move.
That's my asset.
It's pointless to keep this up.
Just come along quietly.
-I think not.
-So, it's begun.
It's a good way to test the
strength of friends and foes
alike.
Meanwhile, I have my own
business to take care of.
-Such a shame.
Even though you can see
me, you're still helpless.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
There's something--
some force surrounding his body.
That's why he's not affected.
No matter how much
chakra I hit him with.
[laughter]
-You use the Gentle Fist, I see.
That jutsu is
useless against me.
You sure you don't
want that smiling boy
to come back and help you?
HINATA (VOICEOVER): No.
I won't call Kiba back.
That would be just
what he wants.
[scream]
-Hinata!
Damn.
There's gotta be
something I can do.
[whine]
-Huh?
That might work.
Yeah.
It just might work.
Come on, Akamaru.
[bark]
GOZU: Over here!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): He's
even faster than before.
But his attacks are
unsophisticated.
They're easy to read.
What?
Do I have time?
-Go on, Nurari.
Finish her.
-With pleasure.
[crashing]
-What?
What is this?
KIBA: One more time.
Fang Over Fang!
I
-Kiba!
-What's going on?
-Hinata!
[bark]
-Hi.
Sorry we're late.
What is it?
Are you all right?
-How-- Kiba?
How did you ever--
-Heh.
It was easy.
I just used my Fang Over Fang
to stir things up a little.
I made a mini windstorm
and got the air moving.
Next thing you know, goodbye
annoying smokescreen.
Now that I can see and smell
again, we've got the advantage.
No more fun and
games for you, buddy.
Get ready, 'cause
you're going down.
-You're the ones who
should get ready.
[coughing]
-Idiot.
How could I have
forgotten the other guy?
-Yeah, that was stupid.
Well then, now that we know all
their strengths and weaknesses,
this time we finish them!
-Right!
-What the-- no, it can't be.
We're being surrounded.
I can sense it.
-Renji, what is it?
-Quick!
Another smokescreen!
Retreat, now!
-What the-- But why?
I don't get it.
SHIN: It would seem the
enemy's senses are very acute.
KIBA: Shino!
-It's very disappointing.
Just when I had almost finished
weaving my net around them.
-Heh.
-Is everyone all right?
-Kakashi-sensei.
-Well, at least
we're all together.
-Yeah.
But Hinata--
-How bad is it?
Can you move?
-I'm fine.
I think.
[whine]
-Sensei, did you wrap things
up with the big fella?
KAKASHI: No.
I couldn't finish the job.
KIBA: I see.
Ours got away from us, too.
-Then this battle's
far from over.
And whoever it is
who's using that jutsu,
they're still out there.
GUREN: Well, how interesting.
I never expected to be pursued
by Kakashi, the famous copy
ninja.
Poor Renji and Gozu.
They never had a chance.
So far so good.
All the groundwork's been laid.
Now it's my turn.
-Mother.
[theme music]
NARUTO: Captain
Yamato, shouldn't we
be getting close to
Kakashi-sensei's squad by now?
YAMATO: Yes.
According to
procedure, he should
have left signs
for us to follow.
SAI: Has anyone seen any?
I haven't.
NARUTO: Great.
Did he forget that we're
supposed to be following him?
SAKURA: Don't be an idiot.
He didn't forget.
We have to assume that something
happened to him and his team.
NARUTO: What?
YAMATO: Sai, get airborne
and take a look around.
I'm getting a bad
feeling about this.