Here we go, Lee!
I am ready!
Haaaa!
Ha!
Hm!
Hyaaaaaah!
Primary Lotus!
Yah!
How is that?
It's heavier than you
can handle, right?
Gyaaah!
Lee!
Lee! Come up for air!
Come on! You never
give up remember!?
Lee!
I dreamed about it when
I was a little girl.
[kids playing]
Her name is
Lady Tsunade!
Oh?
They say she's
really strong!
Yeah, Lady Tsunade's
a legendary kunoichi!
Wow!
[Young Tenten]
I've decided!
I'm gonna be like
Lady Tsunade!
As of today, all of you
are genin. So tell me.
Just why have you done it?
And what are your goals?
I'd rather
not say.
Sensei!
I want to show I can be a
splendid ninja as well,
even if I do not have any
ninjutsu or genjutsu!
I want to prove it
to the whole world!
Hm.
What?
What is so funny?!
You nitwit. Without Ninjutsu or
Genjutsu, you can hardly call
yourself a ninja, can you?
What are you, stupid?
[sigh]
[Guy]
Listen up!
If you've got the passion,
that isn't necessarily the case!
Eh?
[gasp]
With the right
amount of passion,
and some healthy competition
to spur each other on,
you'll all be great ninja!
You'll still have to work
your butts off though.
Right!
[Guy]
And you?
Ah!
I want...
...to walk in the footsteps of
the legendary Lady Tsunade!
Uh...
Heh heh heh...
Ah, My Hero
Lady Tsunade!
We fight with the
power of youth!
We fight!
Lady Tsunade.
Her taijutsu was
just amazing!
And she has monster strength!
It's rumored she almost
killed her teammate Master
Jiraiya, who's also one of
the Legendary Sannin.
So what am I gonna have to
do to become that strong?
Use sheer determination!
Fight on!
[Guy]
Eleven twenty-one!
Eleven twenty-two!
Eleven twenty-three!
Eleven twenty-four!
Eleven--
Eleven fifty-four.
Eleven fifty-five.
Eleven fifty- six.
Eleven fifty- seven.
Eleven fifty- eight.
Eleven fifty- nine.
Eleven sixty...
Haaaa!
Ah!
[Guy]
Okay, Lee! Go!
Right!
[fighting]
[Tenten]
[sigh]
Hm?
I'm really trying
my best, Sensei,
but I'm not getting
any stronger.
How will I ever become as
strong as Lady Tsunade?
Hmm.
Well, keep in mind that
Lady Tsunade inherited the
talents of the First Hokage.
Are you saying that
talent is more important
than determination?
No! Not at all! But...
I just mean that shinobi
have different strengths
and are suited for
different things.
No one can say whether
you'll develop superhuman
strength, Tenten.
[big hit]
Yaaagh!
Enough!
Rrrgh...
Lady Tsunade has more than
just monster strength, right?
Mm-hmm! She's a Medical
Ninjutsu specialist.
They say that there isn't
a single illness or
injury that Lady Tsunade
isn't able to heal.
Oh, please, then I want to
learn Medical Ninjutsu, too!
Well, what I teach is
really quite different than
Medical Ninjutsu, you know.
Please, teach me, too!
How do you do it?
[Guy]
Huh? Oh...
Uh... Okay!
You use...
Energy and guts!
That again...
Still, I can see you have
a passion for wanting to
learn Medical Ninjutsu!
That's the right spirit!
I'll speak to the
Medical Corps for you.
Yes!
[Medical Ninja]
That completes the lecture on
high-level Medical Ninjutsu.
Now we begin the
hands-on training.
Great!
As its name suggests,
Medical Ninjutsu is
ninjutsu that uses chakra
control for healing.
Right.
You use your own chakra
to stimulate the chakra
network of your patient.
Nn... Right...
Now revitalize the cells.
Mmm...
Haaaa!
Aw...
Eh...
[Medical Ninja]
I think perhaps...
[Tenten]
He said I wasn't
suited for it at all!
[Guy]
Ah, ha!
Don't worry about it!
There are many fine
kunoichi who cannot
perform Medical Ninjutsu.
Yeah, but I really want
to become just like the
legendary Lady Tsunade.
Isn't there some other
kind of skill that
makes her so legendary?
Hmmm.
There is Summoning Jutsu.
There's that.
She's able to summon a giant
slug. That's why she's also
called the Slug Princess.
[Tenten]
The Summoning Jutsu?
Mm-hmm.
Then teach me!
Just how do you do
this Summoning Jutsu?
Well, let's see.
It's a type of
Transportation
Technique.
First we have to test
your aptitude for it.
[Guy]
All right! Whenever
you're ready to begin.
Go for it.
Hah!
It worked!
Huh.
Wow!
Seems you have the
Transportation
Technique down pat!
Hm.
You'll need to sign a
contract with the one
you'll summon.
Summoning Jutsu!
Hmmm??
Guy, are these three
your new students, then?
It can speak?!
A ninja tortoise?
Nicely done,
Guy Sensei!
Oh...
So you don't
have a slug?
Mmm...
Don't you think a tortoise
is better than a slug?
What's the matter,
little girl?
Do you have something
against me?
Oh. No. It's just that
you aren't legendary,
I guess.
What insolence!
You'll sign no
contract with me, girl!
Ah!
Bleh!
Tenten!
Don't be so
self-centered!
It isn't very easy to
find a partner for a
summoning contract,
you know!
What? Are you serious?
Anyway, for now,
just keep up with
your training!
Okay...
is there anything
else Lady Tsunade
is legendary for?
Mm?
Hmmm.
I suppose you could say
her love of sake and
gambling is legendary.
But of course,
you can't emulate that!
I mean, you're still just
a little girl! It just
isn't proper! Ha ha ha!
[Tente]
Gimme sake!
You're too young
to be in here!
Meow!
[Tenten]
Hey! Stop it! Let me go!
Meow meow!
You'll see! I'm going to become
just like the legendary
kunoichi, Lady Tsunade!
Like Lady Tsunade, huh?
Then you'll have to come
back when you're much bigger!
Lady Tsunade's big
chest is really what's
legendary about her!
Legendary...
Big chest...
This is it! Today is the
day I will beat you, Neji!
Hmh.
Yaaaah!
[sigh]
Huh?
Something troubling
your youthful
heart, Tenten?
Daaagh!
Lee! You just never
learn, do you?
Face it, you can't
defeat Neji!
[Tenten]
He's not like you.
Ah!
Hm.
He's a genius.
Lee! Come up for air!
Come on! You never
give up, remember?
Lee?!
Bleaagggh!
Lee! Stop!
[Neji]
The enemy's controlling him!
[Guy]
Neji, find the jutsu user!
I'll stop Lee!
[Neji]
If you can't use ninjutsu or
genjutsu, you're susceptible
to an enemy's jutsu.
Mm-hmm.
It makes me uneasy to
be on the same team
with someone like that.
Mmm.
One thousand one
hundred eighteen!
hundred nineteen!
One thousand one
hundred--!
Agh!
[Lee]
I keep thinking all of my
efforts will pay off...
But what if I do
not get stronger?!
It scares me; I do not
know if I can take it.
All the effort is pointless
unless you believe in yourself.
[gasp]
You say you want to
show the world you can
be a splendid ninja,
even if you don't have
all the gifts that
others are blessed with.
That's your nindo,
your ninja way, right?
Well, I think
that's a fine goal.
[Guy]
If you plan to take on ninjutsu
and genjutsu with only taijutsu,
you must perfect it so that
it's superior to them both.
[Guy]
I'm going to have you open the
fifth of the Eight Inner Gates,
the Gate of Closing.
The Eight Inner Gates!
A Forbidden Jutsu one
can die using...
I am prepared for this.
Please, teach me the
Forbidden Jutsu!
[Lee]
Whatever it takes for my dream!
Hyaa! Yoo! Choo!
Yaaa!
Ah!
[laughing]
[Tenten]
Ah... Sensei...
[Guy]
Ha ha ha!
Rules are rules,
after all.
Right?
I said that if I lost,
I'd walk on my hands for
five hundred laps around the
village while carrying you.
Ahm... In the future, I
really wish you'd just keep
me out of your silly rules.
[Guy]
By the way,
if you didn't win,
my punishment for failing to
train you properly was going
to be to carrying Neji around
for eight hundred laps!
Ah ha ha ha ha!
You were amazing!
Even if you did have a
handicap, you beat Guy Sensei!
Thanks. I just tried to
figure out what my strengths
were and do my best with 'em.
Ah ha ha ha!
You found your place, Tenten!
You're a Ninja Tool specialist!
Yes! Out of all the ninja
I know, only Tenten can
battle like that!
Ninja Tools?
Huh!
[laugh]
I am a Ninja Tool specialist!
[Tenten]
Me, a Ninja Tool specialist?
Yeah, right.
[Guy]
Please! Examine my
student Lee next!
Come, come.
It's right this way.
I'll show you, Lady Tsunade!
That was the day.
[Tenten]
The first time I saw
the person I'd admired
since I was little.
And she said...
[Tsunade]
It's best if you give
up being a Shinobi.
[Tenten]
Those words were like a
death sentence to Lee.
Hmm.
No.
This can't...
No! It just can't!
This simply
cannot happen!
So then...
[Tenten]
Does determination
mean nothing?
So it means if you
don't have talent...?
Tenten!
Huh?
Don't take Lee's
resolve lightly.
And trust your own.
It got you this far and will
take you even farther.
[sobs]
The chances of it
being successful are
fifty-fifty at best.
And if it
should fail,
...he'll die.
[heavy breathing]
[Tenten]
But Lee, you went through
with the surgery...
[Tenten]
And right after,
you went to
save our friend.
Guy Sensei!
Tenten!
Lee! Lee, my boy!
You've recovered!
I knew that you'd
bounce right back!
Good job, Lee!
Yes! Thank you,
Guy Sensei!
Thank you so much!
Oh, Lee!
[Lee]
Thank you!
Lee!
Ah!
You never, ever give up,
no matter what!
You never give up!
That's why I promised myself
I would never lose you,
that's why I was able
to give it my all too!
Don't give up now, Lee!
You can't let this be
the way it ends!
Lee! Lee!!
Lee!
Eeeaaaahhhh!
[Lee]
[heavy breathing]
I was right at my
absolute limit, Tenten!
You mean that it
actually worked?!
Uh-uh. It was no
different than before.
To open more of the Eight
Inner Gates, I must train
even more rigorously!
I could really use Guy
Sensei's guidance right now,
but that is impossible.
If you want me to,
I'm happy to help.
One... two...
three...
Uh, Lee...? What in the
world are you doing now?!
six... seven...
Do not mind me!
This is just a
rule that I have
made for myself.
When intensive training does
not work, I make myself do
ten thousand push-ups!
Seventeen.
Eighteen.
And how long is
this gonna take?
Just ignore me.
Twenty-three.
Twenty-four.
Twenty-five. Twenty-six.
Twenty-seven. Twenty-eight.
Twenty-nine. Thirty. Thirty-one.
Thirty-two.
Dyaaaaagggh!
Glaagh!
Please! Tenten!
Heavy! So heavy!
Hey! Watch it! You're making
it sound like I'm the one
who's heavy here, Lee!
What you should be saying is,
"The metal statue that you
brought is heavy, so heavy."
So start saying it.
Eeeyaagh!
You're really rude,
you know that?
I don't want to be like Lady
Tsunade anymore. I've moved on.
But I haven't given up my dream.
I still want to become
a legendary kunoichi...
in my own right.
[Sai]
I was taking a walk to
see how things were
going in the village.
Your argument reminds me
of Naruto and Sakura.
Sakura's hit me like
that before, too.
Huh? Well, they're more like
comrades than friends...
What's the difference between
a comrade and a friend? Hmm.
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
Sai's Day Off.
That's a difficult question.