[construction]
Huh??
Hi there Big Brother
Shikamaru! What's goin on?
Huh?
The first round of the
Chunin Exams is going
to be held here,
so we're making
a few upgrades.
The Chunin Exams? It's
sure been a while since
they held them!
Yep, two
years now...
That means we get to
participate this time!
That's so cool! We're all
gonna get to become chunin!
Hold up. You three are
still Academy students.
You're not even
genin yet so you
can't participate.
That's kind of a
disappointment, but
also a big relief...!
Hold on! That means
Big Brother Naruto's
coming back, right?!
Huh, Naruto?
Isn't he coming back to
take the Chunin Exams?
He's not coming.
What!?
[Groan] Who knows what kind of
training he's  doing now...
Nobody even knows where he is.
I don't even know if he's even
heard the news that we're gonna
hold the Chunin  Exams again...
They're really gonna
go ahead without
Big Brother Naruto?
It's not like the
village plans things
to fit his schedule.
Big Brother's gonna
get left behind...
Yeah! Our boss is
gonna be disqualified!
We're here to represent
the Hidden Sand! We've
just gotta become Chunin, OK!?
It's too soon to
get all worked up.
She's right. Just
calm down, Yukata.
[annoyed grunt]
It seems that Shikamaru's
going to be a proctor
for the exams.
That isn't surprising.
That's because he's
already a chunin.
Then I say we should just
buckle down and get
promoted to chunin, too!
[happy bark]
Let's do this!
We'll give it
our all!
Mhm!
Okay, so you three
are taking the Exams.
You're all registered.
There's no trick this time, like
preventing us from submitting an
application, is there?
Well, the exam's
details are up to the
proctor in charge.
Okay, pull
lots, please.
Three...?
Two?
One, huh?
Please return the lots and go
to the classroom matching the
number that you picked.
(Choji)
They're so polite,
it's almost creepy.
(Sakura)
I bet Shikamaru
planned this.
(Ino)
I wonder what
he's thinking...
Next group in
line, please.
You're from the Hidden
Waterfall Village, right?
I'm Fuu!
All right, please
pull lots.
We have waited so
long! We definitely
have to become chunin!
Hiya!
Do you have to
be so loud?
(Naruto)
This where the Chunin
Exams are being held?
[gasps]
Hey! I'm back and
ready for action!
(Lee)
Naruto!
No way! Is that
really you?
You're back!?
Are you real?
You bet I'm
real, ya know?
(Tenten)
Seems you haven't
changed much.
What?! Of course I have!
Just look at the results
of my training.
Hiiiiya!
This is my
sexy jutsu!
Ya see? Pretty
sweet, huh?
Well, he's
still stupid...
And that is why
Naruto is Naruto!
Byakugan!
I'm gonna take part
in the Exams with
you guys!
(Lee)
But you need to be
part of a team of 3!
Well I just got to the Village
and there's no one left,
so I'm simply gonna
have to ask them to make
an exception for me!
Oh man...
[groan]
What's the big idea?
(Moegi)
Don't get mad
at Konohamaru!
You all right,
Konohamaru?
We only did all
of this for Big
Brother Naruto.
(Neji)
Naruto...
Because Big Brother
can't join in the
Chunin Exams...
He won't be able to
become a chunin.
So you were trying
to take it for him?
A stand-in
test taker?
(Neji)
You don't need to
worry about him.
-Huh?
Because Naruto will continue
to strive to become the Hokage
even if he's not a chunin.
That is right! And, when
he returns, we will welcome
him with a big smile! Ha!
I get it now...
(Kotetsu)
Next in line...!
One.
Three.
Two.
Leave the lots and go
to the room with the
number you drew.
Room One is the classroom
straight ahead. Rooms Two
and Three are up the stairs.
Huh?
We're being
split up!?
We will be
on our own
for this?
I'm in Room One.
[gasp]
Big Brother Neji!
So why were we split
from our teams?
[annoyed sigh]
I have no idea...
[grunt]
It won't open!
I wonder what
is happening!
Isn't the
proctor coming?
I bet they're
planning something.
Heh! That's fine!
Bring it on!
(Komugi)
A stack of papers...
Hey! Don't go
around touching
stuff!
(Shikamaru)
Uh... Ahem.
[loudspeaker interference]
I'm Shikamaru Nara. I'm the
proctor for the first round
of the Chunin Exams.
Please take one sheet from the
stack on the teacher's desk and
then take any seat.
So Round One's a written
test, after all?
Oh. Good... it's
the same as usual.
(Shikamaru)
Is everyone seated? This is a
drag, so let's get right to it.
-This is a drag for him?
-It's serious business
for us!
Heh! You guys are lucky 'cause
I'm the one in charge this
year.
He might be right.
Why's that?
'Cause he's not
gonna do anything
unreasonable.
This is a written
test. Read the
questions closely.
There are only
three of them?
..The three questions are
worth,  from the top down, 30
points, 40 points, and 50 points
One hundred twenty is
a perfect score?
Shouldn't it
be one hundred?
(Shikamaru)
Each of you will  answer only
one of  the three questions.
Your team's total will determine
whether you pass.
But if your total exceeds 100,
then the whole team will be
disqualified.
[confused chatter]
So, for example...
If a team has thirty, thirty,
and fifty points, for 110 total
...thirty, forty, and forty,
for one ten total...
...or 40, 40, and 40 for
120 total, those scores would
disqualify them, right?
Then we'll average out the
scores of the teams that remain,
and any who fall below the
average will be disqualified,
too.
(Shikamaru)
Those over the average
will pass.
Average score?
You'll average out
the totals of all
the teams' scores..?
Just a minute...!
How are we
supposed to--?
The exam starts now.
[buzzer]
I don't know
which question
I should solve!
[groans]
I do not understand
this test! At all!
This exam isn't only about
solving the questions on
it. The test's a test.
Quit saying things
that'll confuse me more!
None of the three questions
are that difficult...
unless you're really dumb.
...anyone can solve
even the fifty point
question...
Don't underestimate me!
I don't quit and I
don't run! No way!
I don't care if I'm stuck as a
genin for the rest of my life,
I'll still be Hokage some day!
[Neji Thoughts]
Come to think of it, there
was a guy like that.
He couldn't answer one question
in the first round exam, but
he passed.
Which means They're not testing
our problem-solving skills.
It's the same as last time!
Now then... 100 points is
either 30, 30, and 40, or
50, 50, and 0.
So what's the
point of this
first round?
The point of it is to try to
think of the score that the
other two team members
are going to get.
Or rather, how to make your
fellow team members get a
certain score.
Although that gives an advantage
to any of the teams who might
know jutsu that enable them
to contact each other.
If that's their solution to
this, then that's fine.
That just means those teams that
have those skills will get a
hundred points.
And the rest have to suck it up
and figure something out, huh?
The last Chunin Exams'
first-round was just
like this, wasn't it?
The point count isn't
what's important.
The Chunin Exams are
intended to illuminate who's
team-captain material.
If the point was to test
strength, I wouldn't be a
chunin.
That's for sure.
Thanks for having
my back...
[buzzing]
[gasp]
[thinking]
It's completely
sealed off...
Big Brother Neji?
Double paned windows, huh? They
made sure we couldn't contact
our teammates...
Should you be walking
around like that?
We were told a few rules
at the beginning,
but no one's reprimanded us
yet for talking like this.
I see...
In other words, they
don't care if we
cheat or not.
Yes, of course. The last
time around, the first
exam was about cheating.
It won't open...
Leave it to Shikamaru
to come up with a
difficult exam.
For this test, if you're able to
contact your teammates somehow,
you gain a very
significant advantage
But no one on my team
uses such ninjutsu.
I wonder if Shino has come
up with any ideas yet...
The only thing left to try
is to guess which questions
my teammates will solve.
If we just choose the number
that we each drew,
then our point total will
be over one hundred.
(Komugi)
Going over a hundred points
means disqualification.
... We have to avoid
that at all cost.
So if one of us just scores zero
points, then we'll avoid going
over one hundred, right?
But there's no guarantee the
other two will both pick the
fifty-point question.
And if the point total is too
low, there's a good possibility
of being disqualified
because of a low average.
If all of us were to solve the
thirty-point question, Then
we'd end up with ninety points.
But then we would just
lose out to the team that
has one hundred points!
Besides, if a lot of teams get
100, they'll raise the average
and teams with 90 points
will be disqualified.
I guess finding a way to
escape won't be possible.
(Sakura)
The choices are, 30, 30,
and 40... or 0, 50, and
50 to score 100 points.
So the question is, how do we
figure out which question each
team member is going to solve?
How am I supposed to know what
questions Ino and Sakura will
pick?
And what exactly
are Shino and Kiba
thinking of doing?
Those two are probably busy
wondering the very same thing
about you right now.
Got it! I finally
figured it out!
What? Really,
you did!?
Yes! I got the answer to
the 50 point question!
Oh, I see...
I will not show
you, though!
I won't look. I
don't have to look...
[buzzing]
[sigh]
Who are you...? You don't
seem to be an Insect User.
I hate to say this... but if
Naruto were here, this
first-round exam would be easy.
Huh? Why's that?
I mean, you just know that
he'd score zero points.
Well... I'm pretty sure that
even Naruto could solve the
thirty-point question.
Nope, no way.
Leave it to
Naruto...
I mean it really would be
much simpler for our team
if Lee were as dumb as that.
Uh, hey,
excuse me?
What is it?
So, uh... can you tell
me what we're supposed
to do for this test?
What do you think we've all
been trying to figure out?!
Oh, you guys, too, huh?  Yeah,
these questions are, like,
seriously hard, aren't they?
Uh, yeah...
they are...
Doesn't it seem that the safest
thing to do is for each of us to
just choose the 30-point
question?
But what about that average
score thing he talked about?
Oh, I see. Then we have to
score one hundred points,
no matter what.
I can barely even
figure out how to get
one hundred points!
(Shibire)
Meanwhile, our time
keeps ticking away!
[thinking]
All right, I've trained hard...
I might as well try it.
...first I have to
sense those two...
[thinking]
Hey, you guys!  Listen up...
Is that you, Fuu?
Right, got it.
Hey, what's going on?
What are you doing?
[Thinking]
It's for my
teammates...
Sensory Jutsu...
Four...?
I got it!
[sigh]
I still don't
get it...
(Ino)
Choji...
I'll solve the forty-point
question, and you do the
thirty-pointer.
Ahh! Mhm.
(Ino)
And I'll have Sakura do
the thirty-pointer, too.
Hey! Gennai! Inaho!
Can you guys hear
me out there!?
Tanzo! Minoji!
[shouting]
What are you all
trying to do!?
At this rate, no one's
voice will be heard clearly!
Huh...? Do you
guys hear something?
Is someone yelling?
Wait, of course! If
they can hear me on
the other side...
Hey!
Hey! Can you
hear me!?
[whining]
I hear it, too,
Akamaru.
Someone's yelling.
More than just
some one ...
(Inaho)
I get it!
Komugi! Gennai!
Woohoo!
[muffled shouting]
Shouldn't we put
a stop to this?
If I stop them now, this exam
would be meaningless.
Now then... Who's
going to do what?
The fifty-pointer's
mine!!
I'll do the
forty-pointer one!!
It's way too loud!
Who can hear over
all this noise?
They're shouting
in the other
classes, too.
All the voices are blending
together! We can't
communicate clearly!
[Thinking]
Can't communicate
clearly, huh?
Heh... Just
watch: Sand
Letters Jutsu!
"I'll do the forty
point question"
[Thinking]
Huh? It's
Sajin!
He wants us each to
do the thirty-pointer,
huh?
With that we'll total
one hundred points!
Heh, those fools...
Lady Hinata...
Let's continue your
lesson right here.
What are you talking
about, Neji?
There's just something
I want to try.
Uh... Oh. Okay.
Eight Trigrams:
Air Palm...
With all your might...
Yee! Watch out!
-Eight Trigrams: Air Palm!
[shouting]
(Komugi)
Hey... What
was that for?
Why'd you
guys...
(Sajin)
What the hell
are you doing!?
We're merely showing you the
way you need to go about
about solving this question.
(Temari)
What's the answer
that you prepared?
(Shikamaru)
This entire question wouldn't
even exist if I  weren't the
proctor.
That's why there's no point
whatsoever in me answering that
question.
(Temari)
What's that excuse
all about?
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"One Worthy as a Leader"
(Shikamaru)
Neji's planning something...
I can tell...