Now, regarding the next
group of genin that you'll
be in charge of...
I'm going to be
in charge again?
Oh, don't give me
that upset look.
Guy has already formed
his squad and gone
out on missions with
them, you know!
Aren't you eager to set out
on missions with apprentices
of your own?
Well...
In any event. I'm certain
that this new batch of
genin will be able to
hold your interest.
Where are we?
[grunt] Naruto
Uzumaki's house.
The orphan Lord
Fourth left behind...
So, that kid's made genin?
[chuckle] Well,
it seems that has
captured your interest!
So, this is where
Naruto lives.
Yes...
This milk is way past
its expiration date.
Minato Sensei
was so meticulous.
I can't believe
this is his son!
He's a fool, but it would
be best if you looked after
him. You have good
instincts, Kakashi.
And also Sasuke
Uchiha's on your team...
I wish you good luck!
Understood.
This looks like it's going
to be troublesome.
Next, we have a kunoichi.
Welcome, Lord Third! And
Kakashi Sensei, as well!
Our little Sakura's gonna
be under your supervision!
Please! Come in!
Yes, yes! Come in
and have some tea!
I'll go get it rea-tea!
Oh, would you stop that?! My
goodness, you're so silly!
[laugh]
Ahem!
I'm afraid that I am
only here unofficially.
If I accept an invitation to
a student's home, other
parents might think
that I'm showing
favoritism and
frown on it.
Oh, please! You don't
have to be so formal!
That's right! Thanks to
you, we live in peace and
have hardly any
worries, Lord Hokage!
I really doubt that anyone
would dare to complain!
And, you come along too,
Kakashi Sensei! After all,
you're going to
be our daughter's
Sensei! C'mon,
c'mon, c'mon!
Well this just keeps
getting worse!
The last one is
Sasuke Uchiha's house.
At one time, the Uchiha
lived in their own separate
and autonomous district.
Now only Sasuke's left.
Hmm...
Sasuke's father Fugaku
Uchiha was very strict. It
seems the boy's inherited
his sense of discipline.
His older brother Itachi
was very meticulous, too.
Yes, I remember well. I
assigned him to serve
under your command.
Now I need you to look
after the younger one.
I'm asking in place of
their father, Fugaku.
I don't know how much
looking after Itachi I
really did. I didn't have
to teach him a thing.
That Sharingan he had
was significantly more
effective than mine is.
Well, regardless... you're
now the only Leaf Shinobi
who has a Sharingan.
We don't know yet if Sasuke
will be able to activate
his... But if he does, you
must be there for him.
Of course.
Obito! How did-?!
This time...
I will protect my comrade!
Obito...
Kakashi...
[wet cough]
Rin...
The shadow of tragedy
follows this eye.
I wonder if it might be
best not to activate the
Sharingan at all.
But...
This eye, whether it's for
the better or for the worse...
...holds the key to my
feelings toward my comrades.
Some say the
downside is that those
feelings attract tragedy.
To prevent such things, it's
my duty to ensure that my
pupils treasure
their comrades.
Uh-huh.
It appears your judging
criteria will stay
the same this year.
Still... This room is quite a
contrast from Naruto's.
[chatter]
Why?
What do you mean?
Why them? I mean,
why'd you put me in
charge of those three?
Because...
There's a hopeless fool as
well as a skilled protégé.
Plus a clever kunoichi...
I'd say it's much like
Minato's old team.
So... you chose
me on purpose?!
Listen, Kakashi. I'm
the Leaf's Hokage,
I would never
make my personnel
decisions personal!
I pick the right man for
the right job, carefully
considering each
assignment.
And I do so regardless of
what the teachers at the
Academy believe.
Sasuke and Naruto are going
to be on the same squad?
Brilliant! Sasuke graduated
top of his class out of
twenty-seven students
while Naruto
was at the bottom.
That's a great way to
keep the squad balanced!
[harrumph]
There are times when a
squad's composition greatly
affects its shinobi,
their actions, and
their success rate.
Therefore, it is the duty of
those who govern to maintain
special teams with
a variety of skills.
For example, Guy's team
that was formed last year.
It lacks the balance Academy
instructors recommended.
It's a squad that specializes
largely in taijutsu.
Yes, you're right.
And yet, this year,
they have really
come into their own.
I plan to form special
military squads that use
Secret Ninjutsu, too.
So as you see it, Naruto's
the Nine Tails' Jinchuriki...
And Sasuke carries inside
of him the potential to
activate the Sharingan.
As I said before, you are
the only one who can give
Sasuke advice regarding
his Sharingan.
Looking to the future,
it's imperative that
Sasuke awaken his
Sharingan so that he can
control the Nine Tails.
That night's tragedy must
never happen again.
I understand that
those two are special.
But then, what about
the kunoichi, Sakura?
Hm? I think she has
the potential to be a
brilliant kunoichi.
But right now she
is just average.
However...
Shuriken Shadow
Clone Jutsu!
Oh!
He's already picked up
how to do one of my jutsu!
Nice one, Orochimaru!
[growl]
I can do that!
What? You too, Jiraiya?
What?!
Shu... Shuriken...
Whatever Jutsu!
[groaning]
Talent draws people to it...
Men begin to notice women.
And in time, rivalry
matures both.
C'mon! Get 'im!
You can do it!
Huh?
Then you mean you've
even considered how
the squad will develop?
Yes, of course I have!
There's no doubt... Obito
was desperate for Rin to
acknowledge him.
But...
I get your logic behind
this, Lord Third.
However, I've already
failed twice, and with squads
that you organized,
just like this one.
Maybe we both need to face
that I'm simply not cut out
to be a Jonin Leader.
Did you fail them because
of your personal feelings?
Well, no...
I see... It's unfortunate
for those students.
But in our harsh shinobi
world, it is better that
they learn such things
when they're still young.
Ultimately, I think this
situation will prove to be a
valuable lesson for them.
Maybe, but it wasn't
something I planned.
It just happened
to work out.
Yes, perhaps that's true.
Still... I, at least, had
faith that it would work!
I trust in you, Kakashi.
Lord Hiruzen!
It was the same
with Minato.
What?! Minato Sensei?!
Hm, judging solely from the
practice reports, it would
seem that Kakashi acted
largely on his own.
Kakashi is leagues ahead
of the other graduates
in terms of his skill
and intelligence.
Honestly, it's exciting
just thinking about his
development.
But perhaps, due to the
incident with his father
Sakumo, he's
very headstrong.
Nonetheless, I maintain
faith that he'll realize the
importance of teamwork.
You have faith in him, huh?
Yes, I agree.
And since I believe
you're right, I shall
have faith in your faith.
[chuckle]
Minato Sensei knew all
along about my selfish
and shallow strategy.
But he had faith
that one day, I would
realize the truth.
Believing in your
students and watching
over them is also part
of being a teacher.
Father...
I've spent my whole
life denying you...
I believe that the White
Fang was a true hero.
[gasp]
You're right, in the Ninja
World, those who break the
rules and laws are
regarded as scum.
But...
Those who would abandon
even one of their friends
are worse than scum.
[gasp]
No...
Whatever happens I can't
allow a tragedy like that to
occur again with a new
generation of shinobi.
[laughter]
Huh?
All right! Are
you our Sensei?
I'm Naruto Uzumaki, and one
day, I'm going to be Hokage!
Shikamaru Nara, Choji
Akimichi, Ino Yamanaka.
Sir!
I'm Asuma Sarutobi, and
I'm going to be the jonin
leader of your squad.
We're going to go have a
meeting now. So follow me!
See ya!
So long!
I'll see you later, Sasuke!
Oh, just get lost, Ino Pig!
Aw, man... I can't
believe they already
got their sensei.
Well, so what?! I bet the
next one will be ours!
No way! It's gonna be our
Sensei next, for sure!
Right, Akamaru?
[barking]
[growling]
[gasp]
Kiba Inuzuka, Shino
Aburame, Hinata Hyuga...
I'm Kurenai Yuhi and
I'll be your team leader.
Please to meet you.
[growling sigh]
[chuckle] Well, it looks
like the loser squad
gets a loser
sensei, too!
He's late!
Are you waiting
for me, Tenzo?
I wish that you'd stop
calling me "Tenzo," Captain.
Yeah, well, I wish you'd
drop the "Captain" part.
Sorry, but you'll always be
"captain" to me. That'll
never change, even if you're
no longer with the ANBU.
So what did you want? I've
heard rumors that it's been
difficult trying
find my replacement.
Or did you come all this way
just to laugh at me, the
great genin babysitter?
Not at all!
That was all such a long
time ago! But you haven't
changed a bit, Captain.
Listen, I'm sorry, but I'm
really busy today. I can't
just stand around and chat.
[chuckling]
Yeah, though it's way past
the time when you were
supposed to go
meet your genin.
[grunt]
Well, see ya.
"See ya?" Well, well...
Maybe he did
change a little.
He used to be so fixated on
the past and the present,
and now he's
saying, "see ya..."
[giggling]
A silly prank...
But if this prank was the
result of teamwork...
[laughter] I gotcha!
You fell for it!
So Naruto's the perp...
I am really sorry,
Sensei. I tried to stop
Naruto, but he
just wouldn't!
Sakura makes excuses and
tries to protect herself...
And Sasuke just minds his
own business. He probably
doesn't even consider
them comrades.
Not one shred of teamwork.
Your assignment is very
simple. You just have to
take these bells from me.
That's all there is to it.
If you can't get 'em by
noon, you go without lunch.
This exercise is designed
to try to split the team.
I hope they figure it out.
That way at least ONE
of you will end up tied
to a post and ultimately
disqualified for
failing to complete
the mission.
That one goes back
to the Academy.
[gulp]
Get ready...
And... START!
Considering the prank in the
classroom, I doubt that
they'll work as a
team to attack me.
I'm going to crush you!
I knew it.
All right...
I'm going to give
you one more chance.
But I'm going to make
it much harder on you.
You'll have three
hours to get a bell.
Eat lunch now to
build up strength.
BUT... Naruto
doesn't get any.
Huh?
It's your punishment for
breaking the rules and
trying to eat by yourself.
And if anyone tries to
feed him, that person
will immediately fail.
I make the rules, you
follow them. Got it!?
[gasps]
Minato Sensei had
faith in me...
So should I have
faith in them, too?
But what if I'm
wrong to begin with?
Don't you even have
a shred of kindness in
that heart of yours?!
All you ever talk about
are rules and regulations!
That's true...
I'm still just trying
to stick to my rules.
Let's get going
then... Captain!
Obito...
For the sake of the team,
you stepped up and
compromised that day.
If only I'd accepted the
offer of friendship that you
extended to me.
If I'd embraced that little
sign you gave me.
Here.
-Huh?!
-What is-?!
[gasp]
[groan]
Obito, did you see that?
I'll never, ever forget
about you or Rin.
Kakashi!
Aaaah.
[gasps]
You!!
[screaming]
You pass.
But I think that for now,
I'm going to move forward
with some new comrades.
Naruto. Sasuke. Sakura...
I'm going to believe in you.
And Obito, Rin, I'll
make you both a promise.
I'll believe in my comrades
and never let them die!
The exercise is over.
Everyone passes! Squad
seven starts its first
mission tomorrow!
[growling] You guys
forgot to untie me!
I'm scum because I couldn't
keep my promise to you...
But you're a hero of the
Leaf. You don't have to
become scum, too!
Obito, your once-strong
will is still alive today,
right next to me!
The only thing the
current me can do is...
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Kakashi's
Resolve."
...protect the
current Naruto!