It's so ironic...
Oh? What's that?
Looking at the both of you
now, you'd think that the
two of you were
best friends.
What happened to those
brothers who fought so
fiercely and hated
each other?
No matter how much you
use those eyes of yours...
I'll use my hatred...
To turn fantasy
into reality!
All-in-all, it isn't very
hard to guess something
happened between you when
you took Itachi down...
But what exactly is it that
you want to ask of a
once-dead man?
I want the truth.
Hmm...
Oh, really? Interesting.
Could it be?
Hmph. With the way
that you're talking...
Do you really not trust
Itachi, after all?
Sasuke, don't you
think that maybe...
You already know the
truth about Itachi?
Well, it's no wonder that
you didn't return to the
Hidden Leaf Village
after defeating Itachi!
No wonder you joined the
Akatsuki, who sought the
Leaf's destruction!
I understand...
Now that I have all of the
pieces, it makes so much
sense to me... That's
the reason why...
...you intend to destroy the
village that caused your
brother such pain.
Just as I thought: you
aren't denying it.
So you ran into your brother
and followed him all the way
down here to find out the
truth once and for all.
To ask, is that what
happened back then?
Or, what about that
one other time, too?
All the dirty details...
But like I already told you...
Your brother is a liar!
Trust me, I know.
So doesn't it seem
just a bit odd?
Itachi was willing to kill
his own family, his whole
Clan! To protect the
Hidden Leaf Village.
Isn't that in direct
opposition to what you're
trying to do now?
However... I'm the one who
wants exactly the same thing
that you yearn for,
right, Sasuke?
Lord Orochimaru couldn't
complete his Operation to
destroy the Leaf, and I've
inherited that task.
I think you should ponder
that very carefully...
Join me now and stab your
treacherous brother Itachi
in the back in the process!
What? You don't even
have to feel guilty!
He's not even him!
He's already dead!
He's just an imitation.
It was a mission...
To become known as a
criminal who murdered his
own clan, to bear the
burden of disgrace,
and become a rogue ninja.
All of that was
part of the mission.
Itachi completely
fulfilled his duty...
Except for one
single mistake...
He could not bring himself
to kill his younger brother.
We've received intel that
Itachi Uchiha of the
Akatsuki has died.
You should mark his entry in
your Bingo Book, and remove
him. Just cross him out.
So that traitor has
finally died, has he?
I'm surprised. Who was
able to kill someone that
powerful, do you know?
His little brother,
Sasuke, apparently.
Poetic that someone who
killed his clan got taken
down by his own kin.
Yeah, well, it serves
him right after all the
atrocious stuff he did!
Not only did he join the
Akatsuki, but he also
attacked the Leaf!
He's the most notorious
criminal in the
Village's history!
But damn it all...
I wish that we got our
hands on him first!
Since Itachi's little
brother took down such a
special S-Class Criminal...
...I bet he'll get a ton of
decorations and a large
bounty from the nation
and the village.
I wonder how
much he'll get.
It's not a question of
money. You're out of line.
Well, I know, but...
They don't know the truth...
Plus, there are too
many people here.
Then I'll teach
them the truth!
Don't... Even if they try to
confirm the truth about
Itachi with their
superiors, the Leaf's
elders will deny it
vehemently.
The current Hokage doesn't
even know the facts.
Furthermore, Itachi did in
fact slaughter his own
Uchiha Clan. And as an
Akatsuki member,
he pretended to
attack the Leaf.
No one would believe
the truth...
Look how long it took you.
For bastards like them...
He sacrificed everything for
those who would brand him a
traitor... for
these bastards!!
It is exactly what Itachi
wanted. If you do not like
it, what is it
that you want?
No, we're not the same.
My Operation to Destroy the
Leaf is nothing like yours!
I can sympathize
with Itachi.
I understand his choice.
Because, honestly,
I'm just like him...
It was fine and good being
taken in by Leaf Shinobi,
but because my background
was a mystery,
I was immediately
raised to be a spy.
Medical Ninjutsu was
drilled into me,
just so enemies
would come to trust me.
I went from village
to village spying...
I pretended to be someone
else, living a life of
lies... There was no
place and no space for
the real me.
With no friends or comrades
who knew who I really was, I
continued to work on
suppressing myself.
And around the time I
stopped knowing who I
even was anymore...
The Hidden Leaf Village
stopped trusting me, and I
was relieved of my mission.
Both Itachi and I worked for
the good of the Hidden Leaf,
but in return...
...all we got back was
dishonor and disgrace!
So you tell me, what in the
world has the Leaf Village
ever done for us?!
How Itachi lived
is what led to the
creation of the
current you.
And though I am still alive,
something similar to you was
born from me, as well.
Face it, Sasuke. There is
no one who understands
you better than I do.
I'll be your big brother.
And I'll stick by your side
through thick and thin.
Come... join me.
Sasuke, don't listen to him.
He was an even greater spy
than I was. So he's even
more skillful at lying
than me. And...
No matter what darkness
or contradictions
lie within the Village...
I'm still Itachi
Uchiha of the Leaf!
Sasuke, it's my fault that
you're like this right now.
I know that I have
no right to advise
you in any way.
But I sincerely hope that
you'll hear me out...
...because I have to
tell you something.
After we've settled
things here.
So help me stop him.
I cast the Reanimation
Jutsu. You cannot kill me.
And I can instantly recover
from any wound you try to
inflict. This is pointless.
I've also shut
off my vision.
So the much-touted
genjutsu of your Visual
Prowess won't
work, either...
You brothers have no chance!
Because I cast it...
...the Reanimation
Jutsu is invincible!
It's really quite annoying
listening to him talk...
But he's explained
the situation well.
I know. You don't
need to tell me.
All right, so what now?
It seems he doesn't know the
true power of the Uchiha.
We have a Visual Jutsu that
can be used on an opponent
without eyesight...
In exchange for losing
the light in one's eyes.
The Izanagi?
How do you know
about that?
Danzo used it against me
back when I had to fight him.
Well, then you're
lucky to be alive.
Hm?
Never mind that. How do
we use Izanagi here?
I don't mean Izanagi. But
another Forbidden Jutsu,
considered it's other half.
Another one?!
I've already laid the plan.
An Ultimate Visual
Jutsu that holds his
fate within its grasp.
The Izanami!
Izanami?!
If the Izanagi
changes one's fate...
The Izanami's a
jutsu that decides it!
Sasuke... do not
leave my side.
A jutsu that
decides one's fate?
There's another
jutsu like Izanagi?!
I confess that I
don't entirely know
what you're up to...
But whatever it is, nothing
will work against me.
Seems you still don't
understand just what
exactly I have
become now!
Sage Art! Inorganic
Animation!
Itachi!
This jutsu brings inanimate
objects to life and allows
me to control them in any
manner that I see fit.
It's different
from a jutsu that
just manipulates chakra...
A bit extreme,
don't you think?
Protecting Sasuke with your
Susano'o slowed you down.
Oh, well... But
don't you worry.
I would never harm Sasuke.
He is my precious test
subject, after all.
Now, then...
Time to rewrite that brain
of yours with this...
You know what will
happen, right?
[chuckle]
Amaterasu!
Well, it appears that the
greatest offensive Visual
Jutsu can also act as
the greatest defense.
It's so hot the limestone
cave has gone back
to being just a cave...
I'm sorry...
Sasuke...
Unfortunately for
you, I'll win.
I'm so near the point where
I'll be able to achieve and
control everything
that I simply can't
imagine myself failing at
this stage of the game.
All the laws and principles
of Nature, which Lord
Orochimaru compiled
and studied for so long...
...are now stored and
being used inside of me.
I have evolved from
human to snake to dragon.
At this moment, I am the
closest thing in the entire
world to the Sage
of Six Paths.
Compared to me, the
Uchiha are nothing at-
Just shut up! You
don't know the Uchiha!
You see-!
Kabuto... When I look at
you, it's like looking at
my former self.
And that's the reason
you will lose...
Look, I'm not on the
sidelines anymore.
I'm not just a player.
I'm a central figure!
I own this war!
I had the Akatsuki twisted
around my little finger,
manipulated the war
to my advantage,
and cornered the
Uchiha brothers!
Make no mistake,
Kabuto: I hate you.
However, I also
understand you.
We both lived as spies, as
liars, presenting a false
front to the world.
I didn't know who I was
at one point, either.
But I finally understand now
that to know oneself is not
to achieve everything and
not to become perfect.
Instead, it is to become
aware of what one is and
isn't capable of.
That sounds like the
philosophy of a loser.
You're saying one should
acknowledge and give up
what one cannot do?
I'm not. It is simply to
forgive oneself for the
things one cannot do alone.
It's because you cannot do
everything yourself that you
have comrades to help you.
And also you should never
ignore things one could
still accomplish.
If you want to know who
and what you are...
You must reexamine and
acknowledge your true self.
I failed at that...
I lied to everyone around
me. I lied to myself.
I was deluded.
Those who cannot or
will not acknowledge
themselves are
sure to fail.
Just like I have failed.
What do you two imagine you
know about me, anyway?
I have been ardently
pursuing what I am in my own
way for the longest time.
My whole life...
I bet he's from that city...
Where that recent
battle was just fought.
What should we do with him,
Sis? I mean, he's bleeding
from the head pretty badly.
He's gonna die soon.
Should we take him?
Urushi... His injuries are
less severe than yours were.
Don't worry. Just relax. I
can help. I'm able to do a
little Medical Ninjutsu.
Where are your parents?
What's your name?
Seriously? You don't
know anything? Come on!
Urushi, help him up.
[growling]
You sure are lucky, kid!
Here, grab my shoulder!
That's my oldest memory...
I was nobody and had
nothing right from the very
beginning. Nothing at all.
I didn't know my parents.
Or even my own name.
Your wound appears to
be healing quite nicely.
Hey, you could at least say,
"thank you," you know!
Don't you have any
manners at all?!
Listen! We don't want
anything to happen to you
again, so put this on!
Man, you don't know manners,
or who your parents are!
Or even your own name!
I gotta say, that's
a first for me!
You're going to be
living right here with
us from now on.
That means, starting
right now, you can just
consider me your mother.
You can always ask me for
whatever you might need.
But you know it's totally
inconvenient that he
doesn't have a name.
That's true...
What would be a
good one for him?
Wait, how about...
Kabuto, as in helmet?
So simple...
That was fast.
It's just what he's wearing!
It's best not to overthink
things sometimes.
[chuckling]
Hey! Check it out! He
just smiled! I guess that
means he likes his name!
Oh, good!
Hey, you could at least say,
"thank you," you know!
Don't you have any
manners at all?!
Well... what are
we going to do?
We can't get by on just the
assistance money from the
nation and the
village anymore.
I guess the only option we
have left is to negotiate
with the both of them!
Neither is going to
give us any more funds.
You know that!
But as it is now, we're
barely scraping by.
And remember, we just
took another one in...
Yes, I understand... I will
do something about it.
So, therefore-
Oww!
What are you doing up
at this late hour?!
You should be in
bed, asleep, now!
[concerned gasp]
Please! This child
just got here.
He doesn't know our
schedule or rules yet.
Please, go easy on him.
Oh, Mother, you are
far too indulgent
with these children!
Okay! Come here and look
at this clock! It's already
twenty minutes past
lights-out time!
Which means that
lights-out is at what time?
Let's learn this right
now so it's not an issue!
Well? What time is it?
You have to learn
it for yourself!
[gasp]
This child is simply too
young. It isn't his fault
that he can't read a clock,
much less do arithmetic.
Let's just call it a night.
Nine o'clock.
Yes, that's correct!
[laughter] It appears that
he only has bad vision!
He's smart for his age!
But he's going to
need some glasses.
Agh!
And where are we going to
get the money for that?
My goodness! Why couldn't he
have just spoken up and told
us he couldn't see well?!
You can be mindful of the
time from now on, right?
I just hope that those
lenses are the correct
strength for your eyes.
[chuckle]
Thank... you...
Thank you.
My name is symbolic.
My eyeglasses, a tool...
Thank you...
From the very beginning,
I was nobody...
Thank you...
Thank you!
That's enough, now.
From the very beginning...
I had nothing.
Nothing at all...
Mother didn't know me.
Why? Why didn't
she remember me?
If she doesn't know
me, then who am I?
What were all those things I
received from Mother?
My name, that I was one of
Mother's children, even
these glasses.
Who... are you?
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Kabuto Yakushi."
It appears that you no
longer see yourself clearly...