-I take it the
preparations are complete.
-Yes, Lord Orochimaru.
-Good.
Then at last I
will get a new body
and the world will
get what it deserves.
[laughter]
-Go, Kabuto.
I can't tell you how much I'm
looking forward to your return.
-Everything's ready, Yukimaru.
Time to go.
-I wonder.
Is there a place
I can go back to?
This place we're going to.
Have I been there before?
-Lord Orochimaru tells
me he's very much
looking forward to your return.
-But return to where?
Is this the place I'm
supposed to go back to?
-Lord Orochimaru has
such high hopes for you.
You must do all you
can to live up to them.
[explosion]
[weapons clanging]
[laughter]
-Just a few left.
-That's enough slaughter.
If the rest of you want
to save yourselves,
you'll come work for me.
Mm-hmm.
All right.
Then.
Follow me.
[laughter]
-(VOICEOVER) In order to
pull of Orochimaru's plan,
I need to draw out
Yukimaru's power.
I must get results
from these tests
before handing
him over to Gurin.
I must, no matter what it takes.
-You never know how many times
around it's going to take.
I guess it all depends on
where exactly you put it,
and how tightly you wrap it.
You'd think that by now I
should know how many times it's
going to wrap around, but you
never know 'til you finish.
-Hmm.
Let's go.
-It's almost time.
[theme music - in Japanese]
-Hehe.
-I just have to say, the
dumplings you serve here
are absolutely delicious.
Of course, with a lovely
thing like you serving them,
they couldn't be anything else.
-Oh, well, really, you
shouldn't say that.
-In fact, as good as
these dumplings are,
I bet you're even
tastier, aren't you?
[giggling]
-Finally made it.
Let's get to work and
start training, Pervy Sage!
-Hang on.
Let's wash off the dust
from our journey first.
-Yeah?
-Remember, healing your arm is
part of the training process.
These hot springs are
great for broken bones.
-Mm-hmm.
-Besides, hot springs
are a lot of fun.
[giggling]
-Research.
Time for more research, hahaha!
-You haven't changed
a bit, have you?
I knew it.
You've forgotten what happened
when Grandma Tsunade caught
you sneaking peeks
at the ladies--
-No!
I could have sworn this was
a co-ed bath last time I
was here!
Oh, what the hell happened?
-Well, maybe they
changed their policy
because of guys like you.
-Oh, be quiet.
In all the time I've
been teaching you,
haven't you learned anything?
Why do you think I keep
doing this, anyway?
-Because you're a pervert.
-You idiot.
My research for
the Makeout Series
is a cover for Shinobi training.
I've trained myself
to go unseen by guards
who happen to be women.
-Keep telling yourself that.
-Uh, anyway, like I
said, this hot spring's
really for your broken arm.
Healing that is the first
step in the process.
-Oh, man.
This is such a waste of time.
Can't we just get on with it?
-You know, you really can
be annoying sometimes.
-Hmm?
Just you never mind about this.
I'm as fit as a fiddle.
-I've been training
so hard lately
so I don't have to rely
on the Nine-Tails power.
Because what's the point of
having powers like mine if you
just end up hurting everybody
instead of helping them?
Nothing I've tried so
far has been enough.
Isn't there some kind
of long-range jutsu
you could teach me?
-Huh.
Well, listen to you, talking
like a veteran Shinobi.
-(VOICEOVER) Ochimaru, huh?
-Dad!
-Multiple Legs Barrage!
[grunt]
-(VOICEOVER) I swore to myself I
wouldn't let anything like that
happen to Akamaru ever again.
[bark]
-That's right, boy.
-Kiba.
What are you thinking about?
-I was just remembering how
our mission to rescue Sasuke
turned out, and if it's
really Orochimaru's hideout
we're headed for.
Well, I'm wondering if
this mission might not just
turn out the same way.
-What?
You getting nervous, Kiba?
-Not on your life,
Kakashi-sensei.
Besides, with everybody talking
about how Shikamaru and even
Naruto were able to
beat the Akatsuki,
I want a chance
to show that I've
been training just
as hard as they have.
-It's essential
that I demonstrate
the results of my
training as well.
-Huh?
-Unlike the rest
of you, I've rarely
been allowed the opportunity
of going on missions
with the group and
showing what I can do.
-Oh, come on.
Don't tell me you're still
upset just because you
didn't get to go on one mission.
-That, and the fact that
Naruto didn't recognize me
after all we've been through.
-Of course Naruto
didn't recognize you.
No one can even see your face
with that stupid thing over it.
-That shouldn't matter
to an old comrade.
-Come on.
The important thing is
that we're together now.
(VOICEOVER) They're
right, though.
I want to show what I
can do, too, if only
to make Naruto acknowledge me.
-(VOICEOVER) They've all become
so much stronger and more
dependable.
Hmm.
Even him.
-Pervy Sage.
I've gotten a little
stronger, don't you think?
-Huh.
Honestly?
You don't seem that much
different from the rookie
of three years ago.
-Huh, you think so?
-Well, maybe you're right.
If being smarter means
what you say it does,
I'll remain a fool
my entire life.
I'm going after him, and I'll
do it alone if I have to.
I'll create my own
incredible jutsu!
-So, Naruto.
Do you still feel the same way
as you did three years ago?
-I never go back on my word.
Because that's my ninja way.
-Hmm.
That answers that question.
(VOICEOVER) I felt that
way about a friend once.
All it brought me was a sense
of helplessness and regret.
Naruto's felt that, too.
For three years.
But he's never given
up on his friend.
He's never forgotten him.
He's continued to train.
He still nurses the same
desire to bring Sasuke back
to the Leaf, even at the
cost of his own body.
Heh.
Maybe the idiot has matured
in his own idiot way.
Just a teensy,
weensy little bit.
-You think so?
Yeah, but if I'm going
to bring him back,
I've still got to
get much stronger.
-Hmm.
(VOICEOVER) Maybe he can do it.
They say, wherever someone
is still thinking of you,
that place is your home.
-Hmm?
Ha.
Yeah.
-This must be one of the ANBU
Black Ops who sent the message.
What is it?
You sense something?
-We don't need to sense
anything, do we, Akamaru?
[bark]
-You can smell it.
There are going to be a
lot more bodies up ahead.
-Well.
I thought my nose was pretty
keen, too, but-- which way?
-This way.
-Keep on your toes.
-Huh?
What is--
-Oh-- somebody help me, please.
-A curse mark.
Orochimaru's curse mark.
Like on the ones before.
-(VOICEOVER) There's no
doubt we've discovered
Orochimaru's hideout, but
what the hell happened here?
-Faint traces of chakra.
There are two.
No, more.
There's a lot of them!
-Let's go, Kakashi-sensei!
-Yes.
There's no time to waste.
-All right, move.
But watch out for traps.
[gasps]
-How horrible!
-What the hell happened?
-It would seem they've
been fighting each other.
-They had a falling out?
-Let's find out from
them what happened.
[bark]
-What is it, boy?
-Oh, no.
-We'd have been
flattened if Akamaru
hadn't sniffed out
that escape route.
[bark]
-Haha.
Good boy, Akamaru.
-So they did lay
a trap, after all.
-Not for us.
-Huh?
-I doubt the enemy has any idea
we're even in the vicinity.
I think that trap was set
off to destroy the evidence.
To destroy the hideout itself.
-But all those
people still inside!
-Yeah.
Pretty ruthless, all right.
-Orochimaru.
He's going to pay for that.
[bark]
-Stop wasting time.
Move it!
-Well, in as much as we've
located Orochimaru's hideout,
we've achieved our mission.
-But we can't really say
it's been a success, can we?
-Hmm?
-We can't return to the
Leaf without having gathered
any information about his
current whereabouts and plans.
-He's right, Kakashi-sensei.
-There is one bit of
information that we've learned.
Well, that was a
timed explosion.
Whoever set the timer had
to have been here recently.
-What?
-You're right.
And if they're still
in the vicinity,
we should find out
what we can from them.
-Good.
Then it's decided.
Let's get after them.
-Leave everything to me.
My parasitic insects are masters
of picking up an enemy's trail.
-Hey, if anybody's a master
of tracking the enemy,
it's Akamaru here.
[bark]
-Yes!
And don't forget me.
-Where are we all
headed, anyway?
Where is she taking us?
-Huh.
Probably right
back to Orochimaru.
-If so, you know what
that means, don't you?
[laughter]
-No, don't do it.
Please, I'm begging you.
No!
[evil laughter]
Augh!
-I don't think we'll
survive another round
of his experiments.
-You can say that again.
-Yeah.
But he scares me.
That guy-- we're
going up against him?
-Right now, it's just the woman.
-Yeah.
Yeah, you're right.
All we have to do is take the
woman out and we're home free.
-I'm for it.
-I say we kill her.
-Hey.
Who said you could take a break?
[gasp]
-That'd be me.
-One, two, three--
-We're through listening to you.
---four.
-We've taken a vote
amongst ourselves,
and we've decided
you're dead, lady.
-12, 13, 14, 15.
I count 16 of you.
Is that right?
-What, are you scared?
Hehehe.
Hey!
She's scared.
-Scared of you?
-You really think you
can defeat all 16 of us?
Foolish woman.
-I'll tell you what's foolish.
Going into battle
without carefully
assessing your
opponent's strength.
Crystal-Style.
Crystal Prison.
-My insects have
detected the enemy.
-Oh, man.
Those guys had no idea what they
were getting themselves into.
They weren't only
hopelessly outclassed,
they were hopelessly stupid.
[laughter]
-Are you trying to
say you're smarter?
So, are you coming, then?
-Well, I, uh--
-Yeah, of course we're coming.
It's not like we
were running away.
We were just avoiding
an unnecessary fight.
-(VOICEOVER) Hmm.
Well, I can't face Orochimaru
without any followers.
-I pledge my loyalty.
-There is no need.
Betray me, and you will die.
-A jutsu that imprisons
the victims in crystals!
-Earth-Style?
-I've never seen
anything like it.
-My insects suffered
the same fate.
-(VOICEOVER) No.
It can't be.
-All right, then.
Ready to begin your training?
-Yes, sir.
I'm good to go.
-OK.
To start things
off, I think we'll
try a simple jutsu
using your wind chakra.
-A simple jutsu?
-Mm-hmm.
Do you remember that
ninjutsu we were working on
during our last training period?
-Hmm.
Well, I remember we did
lots of different stuff.
-I mean the one in which
toads were involved.
-Oh, yeah!
-Yoo-hoo!
-Ahhh!
Yeah, that one got a little
weird for me, actually.
-Ah, you remember.
Good.
I thought it might have
been too soon back then,
but I think you
can handle it now.
-Uh, really?
-It's a collaboration ninjutsu
in which two jutsu are combined
in order to make a
single, stronger jutsu.
-Ah!
Yeah, I know about that.
When we took on
that Akatsuki guy,
Captain Yamato combined
his Water-Style
with my Wind-Style to make
that Hurricane Vortex jutsu.
-Good.
If you know it, that
makes things easier.
Summoning jutsu!
-Oh!
Jira, it's been too long.
-Ahhh!
-I apologize for having to
make you come so far, Gamariki.
-Oh, don't be silly.
Don't mention it.
Such old, dear friends
as you and I are.
-Ahh!
What's Gamariki doing here?
-Oh, Naruto, you're
here too, huh?
Hmm.
-Ugh.
-The two jutsu have
to be in perfect sync
for the collaboration
ninjutsu to work.
Yamato matched
your timing exactly
to produce his
Hurricane Vortex jutsu--
-Um, you can forget it.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
No way he and I can
ever be in sync.
I mean, look at
him, he's hopeless.
-Hold on, hold on.
I'm not the problem here,
I can tell you that.
And anyway, of all
the giant toads
you could have picked, why'd
you have to pick this one?
-Do you want to master
this new jutsu or not?
-Yes.
-So starting from
this moment, you
will be training with Gamariki.
And you'll keep on
training until your timing
and his are in
perfect synchronicity.
Understood?
[sigh]
-Well, if you insist, Jiraiya,
I guess we have no choice.
-Yeah, but, uh, wouldn't
this combination thing
be even more
powerful if you and I
combined our jutsu, Pervy Sage?
-The obvious problem
with that is,
I won't be around
all the time, but you
can summon toads
whenever you want.
-Good point.
Yeah.
But, uh-- come on.
Is his jutsu really that strong?
-Huh?
Oh.
Gamariki.
Watch carefully.
-You'll be gentle, right?
-Hiya!
-Woah, man!
Guess you're a lot stronger
than I thought, Mr. Gamariki.
-Mm-hmm.
-Once our timing
was in perfect sync,
I let my chakra flow into
his Water Pistol jutsu.
[gulp]
-Your wind chakra should
work especially well
with his water chakra.
With practice, the two of you
will do even better than that.
-Better than that?
Well, all right then.
I'm ready.
Bring it on.
Let's do it.
-First we'll work on
your sense of rhythm.
-Hey-- what sense of rhythm?
-One, two, one, two,
one, two, one, two.
One, two, one, two.
One, two, one--
-Ow!
-(VOICEOVER) This toad and me.
-(VOICEOVER) Me and this kid?
-I don't think this
is going to work.
-Oh, boy.
Is this going to be rough.
-You summoned me?
-Yes.
I thought perhaps it
was time to test you.
To see the level of
power you've achieved.
-I see.
[laughter]
-Not even a flicker of fear.
You're very confident
taking me on, aren't you?
-I'm ready.
Any time.
Just say the word.
[theme music - in Japanese]
-That does it.
I quit.
I've had enough of this guy.
This training is a
total waste of time.
-Oh, get a grip.
Learning to combine
your Wind-Style
his Water-Style is
the key to achieving
the collaboration ninjutsu.
-Hey, if it can't be
done, it can't be done.
I need to find someone
more compatible with me.
-Idiot!
You can't summon anything
with your arm the way it is.
-That's what you think.
You're forgetting how fast
I can heal, Pervy Sage.
Next time.
Encounter.