[theme music]
[shout]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): If I
only focus on the Rasengan,
I mess up the change
in chakra nature.
But if I concentrate
too much on that,
my Rasengan doesn't
turn out right.
I'm pathetic.
-It's because I truly
believe that you
are the only shinobi who can
surpass the Fourth Hokage.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Kakashi-sensei
had such high hopes for me.
But it turns out I'm
a complete failure.
-What should we do?
You think we should
stop the training?
-Hm.
Well, if that's
what he wants to do.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I-- I--
-Dammit!
I don't have anymore
time to waste!
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Huh?
Be careful, you guys!
We got another one turning
into the Nine Tails!
[screaming]
-Captain Yamato!
Help us!
-Tenzo, here it comes!
You OK?
It's been one full
day since we started
trying to add the wind change
in nature to the Rasengan,
and you're using 200
shadow clones now.
You've just achieved
what the average ninja
would take 4,800 hours to do.
But I guess that's still
not enough for you.
-This training's impossible.
I can't wrap my around the
chakra control technique,
and it feels like 200
shadow clones is my limit.
No way.
I'm never going to
be able to master it.
It takes all my concentration
to form the basic Rasengan
in the first place.
Adding a change in nature to
that-- it's just too much.
-You're unusually negative.
That's not like you.
You don't sound like the
Naruto Uzumaki I know.
-Oh, Said.
-You'll catch cold.
So, how's Naruto's training?
SAKURA: Learning to add
a change in chakra nature
to the Rasengan is
harder than he thought.
Mastering difficult
skills has never
been Naruto's strong suit.
-Well, that's why
Kakashi-sensei is
having him learn the technique
through action, right?
-Yeah.
Training only Naruto can do.
They can double the
amount of training
he gets by using two
clones, and he's using 200.
-Still, incorporating a change
in chakra nature into a jutsu
by itself is a difficult
enough hurdle to get over.
To say nothing of the fact
that the Rasengan was a jutsu
invented by the Fourth Hokage.
To try and add
something to it now,
especially for someone like
Naruto, may be impossible.
-You have a point.
Naruto is an idiot.
He's a clumsy, tactless fool.
For him to perfect something
as intricate as a modification
of the Rasengan-- you know
as well as I he can't do it.
And yet Kakashi-sensei
and Captain Yamato
have been sticking it out
with him all this time.
Meanwhile, the village
is forming platoons
to fend off the Akatsuki.
This is a total
waste of manpower.
I don't know what
the Hokage expects
from a no talent like Naruto.
-Say another word, and
I'll knock you out.
And exactly what do you
know about Naruto, anyway?
Sure, Naruto's not
the brightest guy.
He's clumsy, he goofs off,
and he's a bird brain.
But no one will surprise
you more than him.
He's saved our butts more
times than I can even count.
Every time someone expects him
to fail, he proves them wrong.
That's who Naruto Uzumaki is.
And if you're his teammate,
you'll remember that!
What the-- you're smiling?
I'll pummel you!
-There's no need for that.
But, you know,
sometimes the knowledge
found in books can
be fairly useful.
SAKURA: The Understanding
People's Feelings Series.
When Words Can Mean The
Opposite Of How You Feel?
Sai?
You mean you--
- I understand just
how completely you
believe in Naruto.
And I also know that you
will never betray his trust.
-Hey, hang on.
You tricked me, Sai?
-It would be a shame if Naruto
had to eat all those awful mud
balls of yours and didn't
get any results out
of his training.
Don't you agree?
-What do you mean by mud balls?
I just value their
effectiveness over taste!
You know, before you go reading
the true feelings of others,
maybe you should figure out
how to talk about your own!
-Don't worry, Sakura.
Naruto will pull it off.
-Oh, Sai.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
Hang in there.
-I don't know.
I have no reason to think
it's going to work this time.
-You have to do it, anyway.
-Yeah, well, that's
easy for you to say.
Why don't you tell me this?
Could you look to the left and
the right at the same time?
-Hm?
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): He's right.
That is impossible.
-Oh, I see.
If you're asking me--
yeah, I guess it's doable.
-Huh?
Shadow Clone Jutsu.
I'm looking to the right
while looking to the left.
This is what you mean, right?
-I get it!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
What does he get?
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
[groaning]
-You went to the trouble of
calling us back here just
to seal the Two Tails?
-It will take three days.
Prepare yourselves.
-Three days?
Oh, man.
It's raining where we are.
-Hidan.
Shut up.
-But I was this close to
slaughtering those Leaf morons.
I was just about to
prove to those heathens
the might of the way of Jashin.
-The Leaf aren't heathens.
They venerate their ancestors,
and follow the Will of Fire.
In fact, one could
say their motives
for fighting are just
as valid as yours.
-Huh?
How dare you.
Are you trying to insult me?
Huh?
-No.
I did not intend to ridicule
the reasons why you do battle.
After all, you and I
are birds of a feather.
It doesn't matter what
you use to justify war.
Religion, philosophy,
resources, land, revenge, love.
Even a whim.
No matter how
trivial the motive,
they're all worthy
causes for war.
There will always be war.
The reason can be found later.
Human instinct seeks conflict.
-Aw, nobody wants to hear
your long winded lecture.
Listen, I've got my own
way of doing things.
I have my own set of goals.
I don't intend to devote my
all to this organization.
All right?
-So long as you're
affiliated with the Akatsuki,
you will contribute
to its goals.
Once they have been
achieved, your own wishes
will be swiftly
granted, as well.
-Ha.
You can act all
cool if you want,
but it won't change the
fact that the only thing
the Akatsuki wants
is to make money.
You're the same as Kakuzu.
And fighting for money is
the motivation I hate most.
-You're right.
Our immediate ambition in indeed
financial, but the Akatsuki's
truth goal lies
elsewhere, and it
is one that will ultimately
cost a great deal of money
to fulfill.
-After Tobi, I'm the second
newest member of the team,
so I haven't heard anything
about this true goal from you.
You just plan stuff
behind my back.
-Are you sulking?
I suppose it's about
time I told you.
-Hm?
-The Akatsuki's
ultimate objective
will be accomplished in stages.
There are three steps in
total, the first being money.
The second is to use
that money to assemble
the first mercenary shinobi
army the world has seen.
-Come on, that's just like
what the shinobi villages
are already doing.
You complete a mission,
and you get a payment.
What, you want to become the
ruler of some tiny village that
doesn't have a
nation to support it?
Is that what we're
all doing here?
How stupid.
-A village supported
by a host nation?
You have it backwards.
-What?
-I'll explain it to
you sequentially.
For a nation that possesses
a powerful ninja village,
shinobi business plays a key
role in their profit structure.
Such villages earn
great revenues
participating in
conflicts both within
and beyond their
nation's borders.
They support that
nation's economy,
not the other way around.
In other words, in
order for that nation
to have steady revenue, war
becomes a necessary evil.
However, the current era has
seen only smaller conflicts.
There are no more great
wars, like in the past.
The villages have
downsized to save money,
and many shinobi
have lost their jobs.
Shinobi exist to fight.
They risk their lives for
the sake of their land,
and yet this is how
they're rewarded.
The five great nations
are still fine.
Those lands, and their ninja
villages are vast and trusted.
They're stable, receiving plenty
of missions from other lands.
But not so for the
smaller nations.
It takes an enormous
amount of money
to maintain a ninja village.
Those costs remain the same
in times of war or peace.
That being said, if a village
downsizes too drastically,
it won't be able to protect
itself from a sudden conflict.
That's where we
Akatsuki come in.
We will not align
ourselves to any nation,
and only mobilize the
necessary number of shinobi
at the appropriate time.
An organization that will accept
money for contracts of war
from both small nations
and ninja villages alike.
At first, we'll take on
all sorts of conflicts
for little profit, exclusively
cornering the entire war
market.
Then we will use the tailed
beasts to cause new wars
altogether, and eventually
we'll gain a complete monopoly.
We will control all war.
In the wake of this,
the ninja villages
of the five great
nations will collapse,
have no choice but
to use the Akatsuki.
Then, and only then
will we achieve
our true goal, which
lies just ahead.
It's the third and final step.
World domination.
-I see.
-Uh, ma'am?
What about Kurenai?
-Notify everyone else
regarding the funeral services.
I will inform Kurenai--
SHIKAMARU: No.
I'll do it.
I'd like to tell her myself.
I have a message for
her from Captain Asuma.
-All right!
Yeah, I think I'm finally
getting the hang of this thing!
-I see.
So that's what your
bright idea was, huh?
It took two of you to produce
the original Rasengan.
One to control the
chakra emission,
the other to control
the change in form.
Well done.
-Right!
I realized I was gonna
need a second set of hands
if I was never going to handle
the wind change in chakra
nature.
If I can't look left and
right at the same time
all by myself--
-Then I just needed
to create more clones.
They can look left
and right for me,
and then I can divide
up the responsibility.
-So, my shadow clone earlier
give you a hint, did it?
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
Of course, only Naruto
has both the chakra and the
skill with shadow clones
for a method like that to work.
I couldn't accomplish that.
I bet even the Fourth
Hokage couldn't.
But him--
-Just what I'd expect from
a ninja like you, Naruto.
You're full of surprises.
I'm not sure how
to say this, but I
think I've really started to
take a liking to you, kiddo.
-Don't say gross stuff like
that out of the blue, Sensei!
The jutsu I worked on
all day got messed up
'cause you freaked me out!
-Uh, I didn't mean it like that.
-Hey, whoa, you stay away!
-There aren't words
to express how I feel.
-No!
-Oh, for crying out loud.
What are those two doing?
-Come on.
Kakashi!
-I have a message.
-Just hold on.
Huh?
-Hm?
Wha-- what's going on?
-Kakashi.
We need to call off the
training and return immediately.
-Wha--
-What's happened?
-Asuma Sarutobi--
has been killed.
[theme music]
[crying]
NARUTO: You OK, Konohamaru?
KONOHAMARU: Uncle Asuma-- why?
KAKASHI: Asuma.
INO: Choji, do you know
where Shikamaru is?
It looks like he isn't here yet.
CHOJI: His mom said
that he had already
left when I went by his house.
[crying]
NARUTO: Where the heck
did he run off to?
At an important time like this.
SHIKAMARU: Next time, Team 10.