[laughing]
Dry land! It's been so
long!
At last, we're here! Tell
me, does this mean that
we've finally made landfall
on the new continent?!
New continent? Are you
saying that we've arrived
at the Land of Lightning?
No, Not quite yet. We're
just stopping here to
restock our supplies.
Our ocean voyage is
really only beginning,
Guy.
[freaking out]
You mean I have to endure
more time on the high
seas!? I'll never make
it!
Huh?
After we leave this port,
we're not going to be
able to dock anywhere
for a while.
Oh... I see...
We'll sail for two weeks.
Beause that's how long it
takes to navigate the Sea
Route of Silence.
The Sea Route of Silence?
Yes. The Sea Route of
Silence is a very unusual
region in the middle of
the ocean.
In that area, there's no
wind or sealife at all.
There's an odd magnetic
field. So even steamships
don't work there.
But, then how is our ship
supposed to move?!
There's a narrow strip,
only as wide as a canal,
where a small current
continuously flows.
The boat will be carried
safely along that current.
But once we're on it, we
won't be able to speed up
or to turn around.
Hmmm...
So it's kinda like riding
on a horse that you can't
control?
But there are good things
about it, too.
Every single ship that
enters that route will be
in the same situation.
So pirates or other
enemy ships can't
attack us.
Okay, I get it...
Anyway, we need to get
two-weeks worth of
provisions.
We can't afford to run
out while we're on the
Sea Route of Silence.
Aoba, can you
get these supplies?
Naruto, I need you to
get Guy Sensei's share.
Why are all of you guys
spinning around?
Well, I guess if I have
to...
Okay! Well, that's everything
on the list. Now, I just
need to get back to the
ship and we can set sail!
Whoa! Hey, what's the
matter, there, boy?
[grunting]
I'm sorry about that,
mister. Are you okay?
I think so...
Hey, you're a Hidden
Leaf Ninja, aren't you?
Huh? Oh... Yeah...
Is it true the Five Great
Nations are now allies
and are preparing to go
to war?
Is that the rumor that's
going around?
Sure is. Small nations
like ours have little
choice but to do what
the Great Nations say.
But seeing that you've
stopped here to get
provisions...
I suppose you're going
through the Sea Route of
Silence to the Land of
Lightning?
Yeah, that's the plan,
all right.
I can't tell you much
more than that.
I wish I could buy some
vegetables from you to
make up for what
happened, but I already
got everything that we're
going to need.
Then--
How about buying one of
these?
Oh, um, What's that?
This is a mushroom that's
known as a Moldshroom.
A Moldshroom, huh...?
They're really quite
delicious! And they
reproduce quickly. In
case of an emergency...
You can just grow some
more, so you won't have
to worry about running
out of food.
Those who sail the Sea
Route of Silence often
buy one to keep as a last
resort.
Huh-- That does sound like
a good thing to have!
All right! Sounds good to
me; I'll take it!
'Bye!
'Bye! Thank you!
"Eat or Die! Mushrooms
from Hell!"
No, I don't want to go!
I won't get back on
board!
This is the Hidden Cloud
Village! Right?!
You guys are mistaken!
Please, Guy! Be
reasonable. Don't act
like a spoiled child, all
right?
Uh!
[grunting]
Guy!
Naruto, why did you do
that?!
'Cause I don't have the
time or patience to deal
with Bushier Brow sensei
freaking out.
Well, none of us
do, but still--
C'mon! It's time to set
sail!
All right, Guy.
Let's go.
[seagulls cawing]
[grunting]
Have a safe trip, now!
It would appear we
finally entered the Sea
Route of Silence.
I can barely see anything
at all here...
And all this humidity.
Just thinking about
sailing through this
for two weeks...
It makes you feel so
gloomy...
That may be, but this is the
safest place on the ocean
for us right now.
Listen, Naruto... you
should use this time to
rest up.
Yeah, you're right...
What's the matter Captain
Yamato?
It's nothing,
I'm fine!
Yamato!
Yamato! Wake up!
He just doubled over in
pain. And then he
collapsed.
All we can do for now is
let him rest.
Did something happen?
Bushier Brow Sensei! You
aren't feeling seasick?!
The swaying subsided once
we entered the Sea Route
of Silence, and because
of that,
my seasickness
finally faded away!
Oh, that's good. But just
when you're feeling
better, Captain Yamato's
feeling worse...
Huh? What's going on with
Yamato?
We aren't certain just
yet. That said...
It appears to me that
something unknown has been
eating away at Yamato's
chakra.
Eating away at his
chakra...?!
We can't explain why
it's happening.
But is he going to be
okay...?
We've got a problem!
What's wrong?!
Come with me. I'll show
you.
What are all those?!
Mushrooms?!
Did some kind of spore
get mixed in with our
food?!
I did buy a mushroom that
this guy called a Moldshroom,
but only one of them.
And it didn't have a
poisonous-looking color
like all of these do.
This is the ship's entire
food supply, right here.
You mean all our food is
destroyed?!
Then these mushrooms are
the only things that we
have left to eat
onboard?!
But check out their
coloring. Don't you think
they're poisonous?!
It's not just the food.
Our water supply
is gone, too.
No way! But we can't keep
going without food or
water! We're gonna have
to turn this ship around
right now!
We can't. Once we're on
the Sea Route of
Silence...
...turning back is
impossible.
But we just started
sailing on the Sea
Route...
Are you saying that we
can't change course for
another two weeks?!
Then it seems that we
have no choice. We'll
simply have to do without
food or water until then.
Are you kidding...?!
Even if there's no
food...
There's gotta be at least
one fish.
All right, maybe a
bird...?
There's nothing!
Once, at the peak of my
hot-blooded youth...
I trained by fasting.
A person burns sixteen
hundred calories every
day.
When it's robbed of
nourishment, the human
body converts its own
muscle into protein and
turns its fat to energy.
And that keeps you from
starving...
I can't believe
this... I don't wanna
go out this way.
But all that's true only
if you can keep yourself
hydrated.
And right now, we can't
do that.
In a situation like this,
even the most determined
adult will die in one to
two weeks.
Wait, what day is this?!
I don't know. A whole
week might have passed
already.
I've been hungry for so
long, my stomach can't
even tell the time!
What'll we do?!
If this continues, then
all of us are going to
starve.
Perhaps it's time for our
last gamble.
Our last gamble?
Come on, Naruto!
Uh!
Seriously?! This is your
last gamble?
It's our only option now.
If these are edible...
They sure look really
poisonous to me.
But these mushrooms could
be delicious for all we
know...
And if we don't eat
something really soon,
then we're gonna die!
Yeah, I know, but--
Naruto, let's do
rock-paper-scissors.
All right! I'm ready for
this! Bring it on!
Then let's do this!
Ready, set, go!
Rock-paper-scissors!
Yes! In your face! I win!
I win!
Paper! Just as flimsy as
those who choose it!
You know you don't have
to be such a sore loser,
Guy Sensei...
[groaning]
Sensei. It's time for
you to be a man... and
step up.
[lightly sobbing]
Hey, are you...?
[hysterical laughing]
Aw, what's going on now?!
Have you totally lost it
or what?
No, Naruto, I'm fine. I'm
merely relishing the
moment.
Huh?
I've been waiting for
this for a long time
now...
Thank you for this food!
Bushier Brow Sensei...
You feeling okay?
The mushrooms were
poisonous!
[grunting]
[laughing]
So tasty! I've never
eaten anything that's
so delicious!
I can't believe I
haven't had them
before now!
Bushier Brow Sensei, are
you really sure that they
taste okay?
I'm gonna eat up every
last one of them!
Wait! I want some, too!
Hey, you're right, these
do taste great! I can't
stop!
[gobbling]
[chuckling]
I'm starting to feel
really, really good!
[chuckling]
Yeah, me too. Energy's
rising from inside my
body!
[chuckling]
There are more mushrooms
over there, and I'm gonna
eat 'em!
No, those mushrooms are
mine for the taking.
[snarling]
Mushroom Hurricane!
I know your weakness,
Bushier Brow Sensei!
Ninja Art! Mushroom Harem
Jutsu!
[giggling]
Bushier Brow Sensei!
You're so cute!
Let's have some fun!
You're too naive! You
think something like that
will stir up my
hot-bloodedness!?
Great Mushroom Hurricane!
Huh?
You're mine! Mushroom
Rasengan!
Ha! Too easy!
Ahhh!
Not bad! Shadow Clones,
huh?
And the real one's right
here!
Mushroom Rasengan!
Severe Mushroom
Hurricane!
[fighting]
[retching]
I can't believe this...
How did this happen?
I should have never
bought that damn
mushroom!
But what difference does
it really make! I still
need to find something to
eat!
Huh?
That's it!
Of course!
Ninja Art: Mushroom
Summoning Jutsu!
Well, hi! Naruto! What do
you want?
Oh, boy, do you
look yummy!
I'm gonna eat you!
[screaming]
Good. It looks like
they're all dead.
Their ship was heading
for the Land of
Lightning, so they must
have some kind of
treasure hidden onboard
here.
You're incredible, boss,
your cleverness never
ceases to amaze me!
Yeah, a pirate that takes
down ships with one
mushroom!
The Moldshroom starts out
as just an ordinary
mushroom.
But if you keep it in a
dark, humid place for
more than a day, then it
turns into a toxic
mushroom that spreads
rapidly.
It wreaks havoc out here
on the Sea Route of Silence.
They probably had no
clue what hit 'em.
All right...!
Search this ship, and
bring all the treasure
back to me!
Got it!
So... this was all your
doing, huh?
Hey, how come you guys
are still-!
But you-! You were
supposed to starve to
death!
That's pretty much what I
figured, and it almost
worked, too. I was about
to give in.
I was so hungry I almost
ate everything in sight.
Wait, wait, wait,
Gamatatsu, just stop!
But Naruto, I'm so
hungry! And you sure do
taste good, yes siree!
You stupid toad! I'm the
one who's going to be
eating you!
Wait! I think I just got
a really fantastic idea!
At this point, I'll eat
just about anything!
I asked Gamatatsu if he would
bring a whole bunch of
Granny Shima's cooking
back for us!
A trick, huh?
And thanks to her, we ate
enough bug cuisine to
last us our entire
lifetimes.
Just thinking about how
it tasted...
We owe you for making us
eat that.
We'll pay you back, big
time!
[screaming]
[seagulls squawking]
The waves are back to
normal!
But look at this mess.
This place is a wreck!
What happened?
Naruto, do you know?
Uh... no... My memory's
been kinda fuzzy ever
since I ate all those
mushrooms.
But, you're right: this
is a real mess! It looks
like pirates came in here
and raided us or somethin'.
It's awful. Yamato's
going to be very upset.
You know, I wonder if
some kind of disaster
happened while we were
out of it...
[grunting]
Suddenly I feel
seasick!
Come on, not again,
Bushier Brow Sensei!
Yamato? Hey,
you awake?
Yeah, I guess.
What happened to me?
You became host to a
parasitic fungus.
And it was leeching off
of your Wood Style
chakra. But you should
be just fine now.
It's funny... That just
one little mushroom could
cause such big problems!
I guess it goes to show
you how vast this world
is.
What are you going to do
with us?
Apparently, the Sea Route
of Silence has a way
back.
You're not going to send
us there, are you?!
Yeah. I sure am.
But it takes two weeks to
travel that route! What
will we do for food?!
For food? Don't worry
about that!
Hm?
But this is-!
As long as you guys have
that mushroom, you'll
have no problem filling
up your bellies! See ya!
Wood Style!
It was all the boss'
idea! We were just
following orders!
Please! Take us back! I'm
begging you! Don't do
this to us!
Mushroom casserole?!
Look, we don't have any choice.
All our other provisions
are gone. We'll restock
at the next port.
All we have are...
Mushrooms or bugs!
Oh, man! I don't want to eat
either one of them!
Oh yeah? Why? These mushrooms
are really good!
Just eat, already!
Can't I have something
normal to eat for once?!
What are they doing?
Seems like Naruto and his
clones are fighting.
This is just great!
Fiery, hot-blooded men
fighting and colliding!
That doesn't seem to be
the case here.
We're taking control of
this ship. So if you
value Naruto's life, then
you'll agree to our
demands unconditionally!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Revenge of the
Shadow Clones.
It's one hassle after
another.