[music playing]
[footsteps running]
[panting]
[pant]
SAKURA: Not here.
NARUTO: This one's empty too.
-He's not in this one either.
-Come on, where
the hell are you?
-We've come come so far.
After all this time--
NARUTO: Where are you?
-Where are you?
-Sasuke!
[explosion]
[gasps]
SASUKE: Sakura.
-Sasuke-- it's you.
[music playing]
-S-Sasuke.
-Naruto.
-What makes you think you
know about it, anyway?
You never had a
family to begin with!
You were on your own
right from the beginning!
What makes you think you
know anything about it, huh?
I'm suffering now
because I had those ties.
How on Earth could you
possibly understand
what it feels like
to lose all that?
NARUTO: It's true,
I have no idea
what it's like having
parents or a brother.
If that's how you felt--
-Why, Naruto?
Why would you come
so far for me?
-Because this is the first time
I've ever had a bond like this.
[gasp]
-That's why I'll do
anything I can to stop you!
If everything you've
said was true, then why?
-If that's how it is, I'll
just have to sever that bond.
-Why didn't you
kill me that day?
Weren't you gonna
break our bond, Sasuke?
-The reason is simple.
It's not that I couldn't
break it, Naruto.
-Like me, you may
be one of the few
who can use Mangekyo Sharingan,
but there is a catch.
Take the life of
your best friend.
You must kill him.
-I just couldn't stand the
idea of obtaining power
by following in his footsteps.
I spared your life on
a whim, nothing more.
[music playing]
[gasp]
-How did you do that?
-You know, come to think
of it, wasn't it always
your dream to become
Hokage someday?
All of the time you spent
chasing after me would've
been better spent in training.
Wouldn't you agree, Naruto?
But this time, my
whim is telling
me to finish what I started.
-How could I ever be Hokage if
I can't even save one friend?
Isn't that right, Sasuke?
[gasp]
SAKURA: Sasuke!
-Hmph.
[blade penetrating]
[chuckling]
KURAMA: Naruto.
Come, you know what
you have to do.
Give him a glimpse of our power.
[chuckling]
KURAMA: Aw, what's the matter?
[bubbling]
KURAMA: Why do you hesitate?
You need my power, don't you?
Now then-- who do
you want to kill?
You understand by
now, don't you?
Without me, you couldn't
do anything at all.
Now do it.
Break the seal completely.
If you do, I'll grant
you all of my power.
[growl]
-How did you?
-I can see everything.
So this is where all
that power's coming from.
Interesting.
I never would've guessed
you had this inside of you.
-I see.
You're one of the Uchiha.
You've advanced well beyond
your years, haven't you?
That you can even see me
inside of Naruto is impressive.
It's that repugnant
Sharingan, the true power
behind your cursed clan.
-I take it this isn't your
first time seeing the Sharingan.
So, you're the Nine-Tails, huh?
-With that vision of
yours and a chakra
more ominous than my own,
you're the spitting image
of Madara Uchiha
from the elder days.
[gasp]
-Never heard of him.
Am I supposed to care?
[MUSIC - NOBODYKNOWS+, "HERO'S
COME BACK"]
KONOHAMARU: Did you find it?
UDON: All clear over here.
MOEGI: Target acquired!
UDON: Oh no, it's
heading for the village.
KONOHAMARU: No way
it's getting away.
-Hmm?
Aah!
Oh.
Uh?
[groaning]
KONOHAMARU: What the--
where did you go?
MOEGI: That way!
-That's my laundry!
MAN 1: Hey!
UDON: Yaa--- whoops.
WOMAN: What are you doing?
MOEGI: Excuse us!
MAN 2: Wow!
KONOHAMARU: Sorry about that.
MAN 3: I'm making a
quick delivery run.
[footsteps running]
KONOHAMARU: Whoa!
Out of the way!
-Huh?
Aah!
Oh!
KONOHAMARU: Sorry, pops!
-Naruto, you little--
-Heh heh heh.
-Oh, right.
I mean-- Konohamaru!
[cat hissing]
-Hey, Konohamaru, we've
got the target in a corner.
[growling]
UDON: Hurry up.
Uh, it's gonna get away!
[whistle]
-No problem!
[yowling]
-Aah!
[howling]
-Stupid little--
-(IN UNISON) Konohamaru!
-Got the little rascal.
Heh heh heh.
-A ribbon on the right ear.
No doubt about it, you guys.
-Ebisu-sensei, the
target has been acquired.
We have Tora in custody.
-Heh heh, looks like
another mission complete.
[hissing]
[yelling]
-Oh, thank goodness.
My precious little Tora dear.
I was worried to
death about you.
Where have you been,
you naughty kitty?
-If that old windbag
were my master,
I'd probably run
for the hills too.
-Quiet, Konohamaru.
-All right, here is your fee.
Come along, schnookums.
Time to go home.
[yowling]
-It was a simple
case of a lost cat.
Do you know how long
you've been out there?
-Yeah, but sensei, that cat
was faster than lightning.
-It was almost like
it had run off before.
-I don't want to hear it.
A mission of this
delicate nature
requires speed and precision,
which you three are sorely
lacking in.
You need more training.
-Well, how do you expect
me to push my limits
on a lamewad mission
like this one?
Hey, Iruka-sensei, don't you
have anything flashier for me?
-Uh, look, it's not that simple.
-Listen carefully.
You three screwups only
just make genin level.
No one's going to assign you
to high rank missions right out
of the gate.
-All you'll be getting
is D-rank for now.
-Pfft.
I'm not taking no for an answer.
After all, you're looking
at the Seventh Hokage.
-The Seventh?
What about the Sixth Hokage?
-That spot's taken.
Naruto's gonna get it.
[gasps]
-Huh?
-Yeah, speaking of Naruto--
-I wonder where he
even is right now.
-I bet when he comes back, he'll
have become an awesome shinobi.
I believe in him 100%.
[music playing]
-Seventh Hokage, perhaps, but
definitely a second Naruto.
IRUKA: I hope you're doing
OK out there, Naruto.
-I don't care what it takes!
I'll get stronger and
bring Sasuke back!
-It's been quite a while
since he spoke those words
and left to train
with Master Jiraiya.
-Yes.
It's about time for him
to come home, isn't it?
-The Leaf Village
needs him to return.
There's too much happening
for him to be away now.
-Huh?
-Hey now, is that
who I think it is?
-Uh-huh, no doubt about it.
KONOHAMARU: Hey, Sakura!
-Hmm?
Oh, hi, Konohamaru.
-So where are you off to?
-The main gate.
I have to pick up this
morning's pedestrian traffic
ledger for Lady Tsunade.
Do you want to come along?
NARUTO: It's been
about 2 and 1/2 years.
JIRAIYA: So it has.
KONOHAMARU: Then
the cat went nutso
and started scratching
my face off.
-(CHUCKLING) We had
missions just like that.
Brings back a lot of memories.
-Hey, by the way, have you
gotten word or anything
from Naruto?
-Nope, nothing yet.
-Aw, too bad.
-But he should be popping up
around here pretty soon now.
[music playing]
SAKURA: Hey, Izumo, Kotetsu.
How are you today?
-Well, look who's here.
-Huh?
-Something's waiting
for you back in town.
-Yeah, you have to
see it to believe it.
-What are you guys
talking about?
-No way.
-(CHUCKLING) Always
rambunctious.
-Now this takes me back!
The village hasn't
changed a bit!
I'm home, everyone!
Naruto Uzumaki has returned
to the Hidden Leaf Village!
[music playing]
-Man, I'm feeling
so nostalgic now.
Mm-hmm.
Huh?
(CHUCKLING) They added Grandma
Tsunade's face up there.
-Is it-- is it really him?
-Huh, looks like.
SAKURA: Naruto?
Naruto, is that you?
-Hmm?
-When did you get back
to the village, Naruto?
-Oh.
Just now.
Long time, no see, huh, Sakura?
[chuckling]
-Huh?
Wait a minute-- you've gotten
taller than me, haven't you?
-Huh?
Yeah, I guess I have.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
He seems more grown up
since the last time I saw him.
-So, um, what do you think?
Do I seem more like
a woman to you now?
-You kidding?
Not really.
You haven't changed at all!
-Bluh!
Hmph!
-Hmm?
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): Ugh.
Smooth, kid.
Could you be any more oblivious?
KONOHAMARU: Hey, Naruto!
-Huh?
-Sexy jutsu.
[wild cackling]
-Yaa!
-Well?
What do you think?
Not too bad in the curves
department there, huh?
[chuckling]
-Huh?
-Konohamaru, I'm not that
scrawny little kid anymore.
And you shouldn't be using
jutsu like that either.
It's beneath you.
-Mm.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Well, I'll be.
It's not just the
outside that's changed.
I kind of miss the
old Naruto, but you've
turned out pretty
well, haven't you?
Knowing you, I bet
you've got a whole slew
of incredible jutsu show us.
-I mean, come on, Konohamaru!
Is that all you've got?
Now step aside and get a load
of my brand spanking new pervy
ninjutsu!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Right,
like a new pervy ninjutsu--
NARUTO: Here we go!
SAKURA: Are you kidding me?
[growling]
[grunt]
-What the heck is wrong with
you, you pervy little doofus?
We don't see each other
for over two years
and you've got the nerve
to pull a stunt like that?
Do you have any idea
how that makes me feel?
Do you?
I don't miss--
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): That
hot quick temper and monster
strength.
You've raised a Tsunade Junior.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Yup,
Sakura hasn't changed at all.
She might even be more
vicious than ever.
SAKURA: Huh?
You say something?
-It's been a long time, you two.
Your training proved
to be fruitful, I hope.
-You think we would
have come back
without producing any results?
-Mission accomplished, Grandma.
-Huh.
I'm glad to hear it.
Show me what you got, kid.
-What, right now?
TSUNADE: I have someone I'd
like you to go up against.
I've kept him off
missions the last few days
so he'd be ready for
just this moment.
Your opponent will be--
[knock on door]
TSUNADE: Come in.
[creaking]
-Huh?
[MUSIC - HOME MADE KAZOKU,
"SHOOTING STAR"]
-Today at around 5:00
in the afternoon,
security ninja were
found collapsed
in the stronghold of
the Hidden Sand Village.
Since the shinobi appeared
not to have put up a fight,
the crime may have
been committed
by someone they
were familiar with,
or by an extremely
skilled intruder.
There's also been reports
that a pair of men wearing
black cloaks with
a red cloud pattern
were spotted around
the same time
and are likely to be connected.
Next time, "The Akatsuki
Makes Its Move."
[MUSIC - HOME MADE KAZOKU,
"SHOOTING STAR"]
-Now from the Society
for Leaf Tourism.
Glad you can make it.
Today, I'll be showing you some
of the best spots in the Leaf
Village, so stick with me.
If you're gonna visit the Leaf,
the first stop you gotta make
is at the Great Mountainside
Images of the Hokage.
Starting from the left, you'll
find the First Hokage, founder
of the village and master
of wood-style ninjutsu.
Then you've got the Second,
known for his incredible battle
prowess and
water-style ninjutsu.
Next up is the old
man, the Third Hokage,
who watched over us at
every step of the way.
Then there's the man who
sealed the Nine-Tailed Fox
inside of me, the Fourth.
And finally, there's
Grandma Tsunade, the Fifth
and current Hokage.
She's got a killer body,
and it doesn't stop there.
She's a legendary kunoichi and
a master of medical ninjutsu.
Although, just
between you and me,
she's a lot older than she--
[clang]
NARUTO: D'oh!