-Why are you-- why
can't you understand?
He'll take your body, Sasuke!
It's Orochimaru!
He's just using you!
-If it happens, it happens.
So be it.
You're still such
a child, Naruto.
I don't care what happens to me,
or anyone else in this world.
So long as I can get my
revenge, nothing else matters.
To be honest, neither
Orochimaru nor I
am strong enough to
defeat Itachi alone.
But if I can obtain the power to
defeat Itachi by giving myself
to Orochimaru, I'll give him
my life a thousand times over.
[theme music]
YAMATO: Enough talk.
Naruto, Sakura, out
of consideration
for the two of you, I haven't
taken any drastic measures
against Sasuke, but I'm sorry.
I can't hold back anymore.
-Captain Yamato.
-What do you plan on doing?
YAMATO: He's a rogue shinobi.
No different than Orochimaru.
He can't be allowed
to roam free.
We're bringing him back to the
Leaf by any means necessary.
-The Leaf Village?
I'm done with the lot of you.
It's over.
-Orochimaru.
-I wouldn't bother
with that jutsu.
Be smart now.
-Let go.
-Now, now.
I'm not going to tell you again.
Watch your tone with
Lord Orochimaru.
-Give me a reason to stop.
-You do remember the Akatsuki
are on the move now, don't you?
We want the good people of the
Leaf Village to get rid of them
for us.
As many of them as possible.
If the other Akatsuki
interfere, you
might not get your
precious revenge.
-That's a pitiful excuse.
-But if it helps your chances
by even one small percent then
it's worth it.
Agreed?
-We're leaving.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I-- I
couldn't stop him again.
I-- I'm so weak.
[sobbing]
SAKURA: Naruto, crying
won't bring Sasuke back.
I'm here too.
We have to be strong.
You and me together.
-Well, look.
We've still got almost
half a year left.
And three makes for
better odds than two.
You've got me.
That should be some help, right?
NARUTO: Thanks.
-Now then.
YAMATO (VOICEOVER): The
fight has just begun.
-Oink
-I see then.
-What?
They fought with Sasuke?
-Yeah.
-But their original
mission was--
-I know.
The mission that they were given
was to capture Sasori's spy,
and bring him back to the
Leaf, hopefully gathering
intel on Orochimaru and
Sasuke while they were at it.
However, Kabuto Yakushi
turned out to be the spy,
and had already been
freed from Sasori's jutsu.
It seems Orochimaru meant
to use their meeting
as a means of taking
Sasori out, not
knowing that he had
already been killed.
Naruto confronted him, losing
control of his emotions,
and unfortunately ran amok.
As soon as that
fourth tail appeared,
everything went
straight to hell.
Orochimaru went head to head
with him in his Nine-Tails
form, and was probably
pushed to his limits,
because he vanished
while Yamato was
busy getting Naruto
under control.
Yamato managed to have a
clone tail them though.
They eventually located
Orochimaru's hideout,
and made their way inside.
That's when they ran into
Sasuke, and the battle ensued.
-So, what happened?
-Sasuke is significantly
more powerful now.
JIRAIYA: Naruto was
apparently no match for him.
-I see.
-Ah, don't let it
get you too down.
He couldn't use his full power
because of all the damage
he took from morphing
into the Nine-Tails.
-Oh no.
That's not the part
that worries me.
I figured Sasuke would be
stronger at this point.
I just-- Now that
Naruto has realized
how far ahead Sasuke is, he'll
be hungry for more training.
Know what I mean?
-Oh yeah.
-Anyway, we should just be glad
they came home in one piece.
-It's very fortunate
that Naruto was
able to make it back safely.
-All the same, we
should never have
risked exposing
the boy like that.
To think he would end up
in battle with Orochimaru.
That's why we should keep
him here in the village away
from those who would
seek his power.
-I doubt we'll find much support
for that line of thinking.
You know who we're dealing with.
[sigh]
-And?
-We're not giving
up no matter what.
-All right then.
If that's the case,
we'll roll you
right into your next mission.
Stand by at home and
I'll be calling you soon.
NARUTO: Yes, ma'am!
Hey, Sakura.
What do you say you and I go
out on a day tonight, huh?
-Naruto, have you
already forgotten
what Lady Tsunade
told us back there?
-Uh-- say what now?
-We're supposed to stay at
home until Team Kakashi's
next mission has
been determined.
Remember?
NARUTO: Ah, just
a couple of hours.
She'll never even know.
SAKURA: Go on a
date by yourself.
NARUTO: That kind of
defeats the whole purpose,
you know what I mean?
TSUNADE: And what about Sai?
-Right.
It was exactly as you
had predicted, milady.
He was definitely on a secret
mission Danzo had given him.
-A secret mission.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): I knew it.
YAMATO: It seems Danzo wanted
him to uncover and deal
with potential
threats to the Leaf,
all while carrying out his
duty as a member of the ANBU.
Sai's whole purpose for
joining us in Team Kakashi
was to strike an enemy of
the Leaf Village, Orochimaru.
He meant to rob him
of a body by putting
Sasuke Uchiha in the ground.
-Leave it to that
crafty old badger.
Just the kind of
thing I'd expect
from an embittered old
hard-liner like him.
But our inherent desire to
protect the Leaf is the same.
-Are you talking about
Danzo still, milady?
-Yes.
I am.
-One look at this, and I think
your opinion will change some.
-Hm?
What is it?
-Information.
Danzo gave it to Sai to use as
an offering should Orochimaru
need a little convincing.
-Is that?
-A list of ANBU
Black Ops members.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
Danzo, that snake.
These files are classified.
How on Earth did he get them?
-Um-- milady?
-Shizune, tighten security on
the secret archives building!
Make sure that all of the
access codes are swapped out!
-Yes, ma'am.
-Now!
I don't believe it.
The cunning old vulture.
He's gone too far this time.
With Orochimaru and the Akatsuki
besieging us on every side,
the last thing I need
is a threat from within.
I'll have to put some serious
thought into Sai's earlier
request.
-Well, in that case--
-Hm?
-I don't think you've ever
failed a special mission
before.
It's rather unlike you.
-If I may make a request.
-Request?
Really?
-Yes.
I'd like to keep the name
Sai, and stay with team
Kakashi for a
little while longer.
DANZO (VOICEOVER): That smile.
-Tsunade has also
approached me about this.
But be sure that you
remember, Sai-- emotions only
generate hatred, and hatred
breeds nought but conflict.
-Between my older brother and
me, it's the bond of hatred.
SAI (VOICEOVER): That
may be true, but still.
-After all, Sasuke's
the person who
accepted me more
than anybody else.
Sasuke is my best friend.
It took a while, but now
we have a special bond.
You think?
Do you know what comrade means?
-Why, yes.
Of course I know it.
You write it like this.
NARUTO: Hey, Sai!
Come on!
We're meeting to go
over our next mission!
Hurry up, will you!
SAI: OK.
I'm coming.
[theme music]
KAKASHI: Yamato filled me in.
You saw Sasuke.
-He's gotten so powerful.
We're out of time,
and I'm still not
strong enough to bring him back.
-Sasuke's growth
just isn't natural.
Lady Tsunade thinks it's
forbidden jutsu or drug
enhancements.
KAKASHI: Then we'll
just have to get
you stronger in a hurry, huh?
-But how are we
supposed to do that?
KAKASHI: I haven't
just been lying here.
I've been brainstorming,
and I've got an idea.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Next time-- Nightmare.
[theme music]
-Home again.
KAKASHI: OK.
Picture time, everybody.
Let's go.
-Ah, come on.
Why the heck do I have to be in
some stupid picture with him?
SASUKE: That's my
line, you knucklehead.
NARUTO: Hey, what was that?
KAKASHI: All right.
Let's just make
the best of this.
-No complaints here.
I've always wanted a
picture of us together.
-You're kidding.
I've always wanted
a picture of us too!
-We don't need
Naruto in it, sensei.
-Agh!
Ah, come on!
-Ha.
-Don't you laugh!
-Why shouldn't I?
KAKASHI: Knock if off, you two.
Let the photographer
do his job, OK?
We're taking this for posterity.
Now let's see some smiles.
OK.
Get ready.