That's...
[gasp]
But he's-!
Madara!
So, you've defied the
Reanimation Jutsu. That is
so like you.
More importantly, what's
taking you so long?
But why? Why is that Madara
over here right now?!
Madara?!
That Madara?!
This one is a Shadow Clone
as well. Where's the
original, Obito?
Hey, Naruto! With him here,
that must mean...
What's happened to everyone
over there?!
My brother!
He's over there?
I asked you what happened!
Not sure.
But I bet...
...that none of them
are doing too well.
[groaning]
Summoning Jutsu!
Lady Tsunade!
Katsuyu...
A favor please.
Yes, ma'am! I'll reattach
you right away!
No, don't!
My lower body can
wait a bit longer.
But first...
Bring the other Kage to me...
I know that I can
still save them.
Faster than the Curse Mark
Chains can wrap around.
I'll return that.
Since it's yours.
[harrumphing chuckle]
I can finally move!
Thanks, Naruto!
Now, it's my turn!
[angry roaring]
Obito, you launched that
plan half-baked before you
could even take the Eight
and Nine Tails in?
[gasp]
He knows Obito's plan...
What's their relationship?
You were too hasty, Obito.
And is that also the reason
why I was revived in this
form?
Well, then again, knowing
you... I'm sure that you must
have something in mind.
What have you been up to
till now? Where is Nagato?
You were supposed to find
the right moment and bring
me back with Rinne Rebirth.
That was the agreement.
I'll use Gedo Art of
Rinne Rebirth.
Nagato's visual prowess
itself is the jutsu that
presides over life and death.
He is the seventh Pain.
Oh, yeah? You were
trying to use Nagato?!
He betrayed us both.
He revived the
Leaf villagers.
Can't depend on any of you.
But never mind. It's
still not too late.
I'll capture the Eight and
Nine Tails now!
Dead men shouldn't go around
screwing things up!
[attacking yell]
Huh?! No explosion?!
Uchiha Reflection!
I'll get the Eight and Nine
Tails. Obito, you take down
those two.
Obito... What
happened to you?!
Why'd you join him?!
Am I... Am I dead?
[gasp]
Where am I ?
Between this life and the
next, my young Uchiha.
Those eyes!
No way, Gramps! You're
an Uchiha, too?!
Well, perhaps I am.
He rescued me? But wait...
You said "between this life
and the next."
Where exactly is that? It's
dark, I can't see.
And besides, Gramps, who in
the world are you?
[chuckle] Don't tell me
you're actually Death
himself!
You know, the guy
who escorts people to
heaven or to hell...
No!
I don't want to die yet!
Somebody, help!
I just saw a scythe! I knew
it! I was right! You're Death
for sure! The Grim Reaper for
the Uchiha Clan!
Wait! I lived my life by a
creed of helping elderly
people in need!
Sure, I caused a lot of
mischief and broke rules all
the time, but I'm certain
the balance on
my scale tips to the
positive side!
Please! Not hell!
[groaning]
The simple fact that you are
able to feel such pain means
that you are still alive.
However, that you survived
could be called miraculous.
It's incredible those
boulders did not crush you.
It's almost as if you passed
right through them.
So where did you find me?
Inside of an underground
passageway that I had
created, collapsed next to
some crumbled rock.
Still, half your body had
been mostly crushed. I
patched you up as best as I
could, but...
Are you saying that you
saved me, Gramps?
[chuckle] Well, thank you.
It's too early to
thank me just yet.
And besides, I still intend
to have you repay your debt
to me.
After all, helping the
elderly is your motto,
isn't it?
Oh, well, yeah, I
guess so, but...
What do you want me to do?
Help you with
bathroom stuff?
That would be good.
Well, I'm sorry, but I can't
stay here forever!
Now that I know I'm alive, I
gotta get home to the Leaf
Village!
There's a war going on. My
Sharingan has finally
awakened...
So I can protect my
comrades better now!
Protect your
comrades better?
What's wrong?
I'm afraid with the body you
have now, your life as a
shinobi is over.
[gasp]
No, no, no! But I- But I
finally just got this eye!
And I'm confident!
My combination attacks will
be even better now!
Thought so.
Even his smell is gone.
We'll have to locate him by
the slightest hint of sound.
Okay! Where is he?!
Obito, behind you!
Kakashi!
Kakashi, hey! Are
you all right?!
Even if they are just kids,
it can't hurt to be
cautious. I'm gonna take
this nice and slow.
That guy, he's good.
He got rid of the knife
stained with my blood so I
couldn't smell it.
Got some of that dust in
your eyes again? A Shinobi
shouldn't cry. I'm not dead
yet.
If that were now... I wouldn't
have let it happen...
Die!
But how?! There's no way
that you could've seen me!
Obito ! How did-?!
[gasp] Those eyes!
What are-?
This time, I will
protect my comrade!
You're certainly
stubborn, aren't ya?
Pathetic. Can't even
handle two kids.
Rin's Chakra has been
disturbed. It's flowing in
patterns different from
yours and mine.
She's probably under a
Genjutsu. They didn't want
to waste time getting
information out of her.
We fought earlier. He's
quick. So be careful.
Gotcha!
And...
At last I'll be a shinobi
who can protect his
comrades.
Wake up to reality.
Nothing ever goes as planned
in this accursed world.
The longer you live, the
more you'll realize that
the only things that
truly exist in this reality
are merely pain,
suffering, and futility.
What's up with this old man?
Listen...
Everywhere you look in this
world, wherever there is
light, there are always be
shadows to be found as well.
As long as there is a
concept of victors, the
vanquished will also exist.
The selfish intent of
wanting to preserve peace
initiates wars.
And hatred is born in
order to protect love.
These are nexuses, causal
relationships that cannot be
separated.
Normally....
Great, he's started a
lecture! Old people go on
forever once they start.
So, where are we
now, anyway?
In exchange for you getting
injured, another or others
were saved.
Isn't that so?
This is bad!
Run for the exit!
Kakashi!
[grunt]
You guys all right?
Rin? Kakashi?
Huh?
Obito!
No, don't. It's
okay, Kakashi.
I don't - I don't think I'm
gonna make it.
My right side is completely
crushed. I can't even feel
anything there anymore.
No!
I'm... giving you my...
Sharingan.
[gasp]
Whatever the village or
anyone else may say...
I think that you're
a great Jonin.
It's true. That's how I
really feel.
Please accept this...
Kakashi, take care of Rin.
Rin, take my hand now!
Rin!
Obito!
Just when Kakashi and I were
starting to get along...
...And I never got to
tell Rin that I love her.
I just wish that I could've
spent more time with
everyone.
Look, just shut up already!
I can't stay in here with
you for too long, old man! I
gotta get-!
[grunt]
Fine, then. You may leave
if you really want to.
If you're even able
to move, that is.
[heavy breathing]
Wait a second... There's
something weird about this.
What's a geezer with
Sharingan doing here
all by himself?
Come to think of it, I know
all geezers and grannies in
the Hidden Leaf Village,
and yet I've never seen
him around before...
So this guy currently isn't
a Leaf Shinobi. Which means...
Hey, Gramps... I bet...
...you're a Rogue Ninja aren't
you? Who are you?!
I am merely an Uchiha ghost.
I'm Madara Uchiha.
M- Madara?!
By Madara...
You mean Madara Uchiha,
my ancestor?!
But Madara's supposed to
have died ages ago! What era
are we talking about?!
Let me get this straight.
You're more likely to
believe that I'm the Grim
Reaper, is that what
you're saying?
Well, I guess that I just
might be Death, in a sense...
For truly, this
reality, is a hell.
I am a cheater of death.
Who would without a doubt be
dead in no time at all if I
were not continuously
siphoning chakra from that
Gedo Statue behind me...
I'm going home!
Do not bother.
There are no
exits from here.
And in any event, neither
you nor I are able to leave
this place right now.
Not with these
bodies, at least.
Move and the synthetic
Hashirama tissue I took the
trouble of attaching will
peel off.
Do you wish to die?
There are a lot of things
that I would like you to do
for me, for the rest of our
lives.
I went to great pains to
save you. Do not rush to
your death.
Just what do you want?! What
does a crazy geezer like you
even want from a brat like
me, anyway?!
I want to sever the
fate of this world.
A world of only victors...
A world of only peace...
A world of only love.
I will create such a world.
So what! Who cares!
I just want...
I just want to go back
home to everyone!
And as I told you, things in
this world simply do not go
as planned.
In time, you'll come to
realize that is truth.
If you really want to die so
badly, then go ahead.
But I shall be taking
that Sharingan of yours.
But why do you want my eye?!
You already have a
Sharingan of your own!
Actually...
My original eyes are
currently on loan to another
person.
This one is just a spare
that I transplanted later.
And I'd like to have a few
more to keep in stock...
I do not have a
right eye yet.
And only with two together
can the Sharingan's true
power be unleashed.
Then that means if I team up
with Kakashi, we'll both be
even stronger!
And we'll be able to protect
Rin properly, together!
I definitely
can't stay here.
Just you wait...
Kakashi... Rin!
I...
...I'm alive!
I was outside just now! Your
friends Rin and Stupid
Kakashi are in trouble!
What's going on?
They're alone and completely
surrounded by Hidden Mist
Shinobi!
Kakashi! You made me a
promise!
Please, protect Rin!
I'll be right there!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "I'm in Hell."
Kakashi and I will
protect Rin together!