(Sasuke) I'm going to make you
tell me everything I want to
know.
I wonder if you can!
Severe Wind Destruction!
[grunts]
Hm!
Severe Wind Destruction!
[grunts]
[attacking yell]
(Sasuke) Hmph.
[grunts]
I'm not done!
[building power yell]
[surprised grunt]
Huh?
There's no wind in the eye
of the storm!
[angry grunt]
[attacking yell]
[grunting]
Now, start talking.
[grunts] No way! [grunts]
Damn it!
[gasps]
(Sasuke) What's that?
I won't fall for the same
trick twice!
[grunts] [gasps]
[heavy breathing]
So this is Hell Valley.
The Chinoike Clan really lived
here?
Yeah, we sure did.
[gasps]
Take a good, long look.
(Chino) There's the proof that
we did.
[gasps]
After suspicion was falsely cast
upon the Chinoike Clan...
the Uchiha Clan forced all of
us to come here.
We had no choice but to
settle in this place.
They drank this red, boiling
water, shot birds out of the
sky...
ate the meager grass that grew
here to survive.
Tired of always fighting, our
Clan lived a careful life
here...
rather than going into the world
outside. Or so I've heard.
You've heard?
By the time I was old enough
to understand, I was already
living in Oyashiro's mansion.
[chuckles]
I was told En Oyashiro took
me, just me, from Hell Valley.
So then, you were all alone?
Huh?
You were all by yourself?
What? You actually care?
How unlike you!
All right then, let me
show you.
(Chino) I was the only one from
the Chinoike Clan there.
But lots of other kids like me
were at En Oyashiro's mansion,
too.
And we were all forced to
train to become shinobi.
[grunts]
[gasps]
What's the matter? Don't
forget that if you don't win,
you're going to go hungry.
[grunting]
(Chino) [attacking yell]
[chuckles] Ya!
[grunting]
[exhales] [chuckles]
Hmm?
[heavy breathing]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[heavy breathing]
Hmm?
Huh?
[gasps]
[winces]
[chuckles] You did quite well,
Chino.
Uh.
[chuckles]
[sighs] Oh!
(Chino) And on that very day,
Oyashiro brought me to...
(Chino) The Coliseum.
Representing President Kusabi
of the Kusabi Real Estate
Company...
on a record-setting run of no
losses, the Hurricane Kid
without mercy, Fuushin!
And against him, representing En
Oyashiro, who returns after a
long absence...
the Beauty of the Ketsuryugan,
Chino!
(Announcer) I've never heard of
the Ketsuryugan. Just what kind
of power could it be I wonder?
Sounds like our audience is
curious to find out, too!
[confident chuckle]
[frustrated grunt]
Well all right then, let's
get started!
Ready!
[cheering] Fight!
[grunts]
If you're so eager to see my
Ketsuryugan, I'll show you!
I'll blow you away before you
even have the chance.
[grunts]
Typhoon Style: Gale
Destruction!
[gasps]
Huh?
[chuckles]
What? Whoa! What is going
on?
(Announcer) Fuushin has just
been standing there!
What's the matter, Fuushin?
[gasps]
Did I? Did I just lose?
Yeah, that's right. You
lost.
Uh! [sighs]
[cheering]
(Announcer) Can you believe
this, folks?
The one and only Fuushin...
has lost to a little girl in her
very first match in the
Coliseum!
[cheering]
Ah, there we go!
[sighs]
Hey, you're really strong!
You mocking me?
No! No way! I swear it!
Hmm, my eyes are, see? They're
special, so...
Special, huh?
Anyone who possesses a Kekkei
Genkai is special, isn't
that right?
Uh.
Because of this power,
people feared me and kept
their distance from me.
So I was shunned and treated
horribly.
Even that past is better
than what I had.
Just what does that mean?
For as long as I can
remember, I've been here.
I have no memory at all about
anything before I came to
this place.
I see.
Well, if that's true then,
you're fortunate.
Me? I'm fortunate? But
how?
Because it's pointless to have
memories if you don't want
to remember them.
I was born in the Land of Water,
not on the mainland where
the Hidden Mist Village is...
but on a poverty-stricken
island nearby.
(Fuushin) And because of my
power, I was blamed for a great
storm that struck the island.
My parents wanted to get rid
of me, so they sold me off to
a rich man named Kusabi.
In his house...
All I remember is...
the constant torture, all
just to make me more obedient.
But I didn't hate fighting
in the Coliseum.
(Fuushin) Because I was able to
demonstrate my strength there.
Still, I lost to a brat
like you.
I'm sorry I won.
[grunts] You'd better be!
Uh.
But despite all of that I'm
still envious of you.
[crying] I don't know what my
mom or dad look like!
I don't know why I was born! Or
even why I'm alive now!
[sobbing] I don't have anything
at all!
I don't care how terrible any
past might be! It's better
than being empty like me!
[sniffing] I...
I just said some awful things,
huh? [sniffle] But that's how I
feel.
(Chino) Sorry.
I don't know why.
Hmm?
But this is first time I've
spoken about myself to anyone
else.
And the first time someone's
tears have actually moved me.
[sighs]
(Chino) In the end, we were both
assigned to En Oyashiro's
bodyguard detail.
And we started working together.
And one day, we found
something at En Oyashiro's
mansion.
(Fuushin) Chino! Look!
[gasps]
(Chino) An old historical
document about the Chinoike
Clan.
[grunts]
(Fuushin) Let's go, Chino.
Huh?
Let's go to Hell Valley. We
may find your kin from the
Chinoike Clan.
And we might learn about your
past! If you go there, you
won't feel so empty anymore.
[gasps] We can't. There's just
no way that Oyashiro would allow
it.
We don't need his permission!
Huh?
Hmm.
(Chino) Fuushin and I gathered
others who also wanted to get
out of Oyashiro's mansion...
and we all escaped together.
All of us are really free now!
(Chino) So, we ran towards Hell
Valley.
But...
(Bamboo Lord) Come on!
All of you get to make a
living by selling crude bamboo
knick-knacks like this one!
And who's to thank for that?
Why, we owe it all
to you, my lord!
That's right!
Father!
[grunting]
This is hardly enough! You'll
have to get your act together!
Father! Are you all right?
(Bamboo Lord) I'll be taking
your daughter with me!
[evil chuckling]
[screams]
[screaming] Who would dare?
[gasps]
If you don't want to get
more hurt, then you'd better get
lost.
Okay! Quick, get me out
of here!
Hurry!
Sir! Please, wait!
Thank you for saving me.
It's nothing. We were just
nearby.
Where are you chivalrous
thieves from?
Wait, what?
(Iou) P-Please! Please, stay and
keep protecting us!
Huh?
(Chino) We were hailed as
chivalrous thieves.
So we adopted the name "The
Lightning Gang," and worked for
the sake of nearby villages.
We were treated like heroes!
Every time we showed up
somewhere, the villagers would
welcome us eagerly.
They'd give us food and
shelter. Everyone was so kind
to us.
I'm sorry that we haven't
been able to go to Hell Valley
yet.
[chuckles] It's really okay. I
mean, I can go to Hell Valley
anytime!
For now, let's keep working hard
for these people.
(Chino) Seeing how we didn't owe
allegiance to anyone and yet
wielded power...
certain ninja villages tried to
use us.
During the reign of the previous
Mizukage, the Hidden Mist was
one of our valued clients.
We thought it was just
business as usual.
We went after a Feudal Lord
who was taking money from the
less fortunate.
Oh come on, loosen up! What's
the matter?
You mustn't, my lord. [gasps]
[grunting]
(Lord) Are you the infamous?
Yeah, we're the Lightning
Gang. Get him.
[grunts] No, wait, please, just
hold on!
As long as you pay up, we
won't hurt you.
That's far enough.
[gasps]
Shinobi? [gasps]
(Chino) The Hidden Mist?
I see. You want to get rid
of us...
and then create a direct
relationship with the Feudal
Lord.
Thank you for saving me.
You're correct.
[grunts]
(Chino) Horrible, right? But
what happened next was worse.
Will you let us rest here, just
for a while?
(Iou) Please go elsewhere.
[gasps]
If we give you safe harbor,
we'll end up paying for it
very dearly!
Please, we have no intention of
troubling the village! We won't
stay long!
Just 'cause you take money
from others and give it to
those in need...
don't think you can do whatever
you want! You hear?
[gasps]
(Chino) Every village was the
same. They wouldn't even give us
water.
(Chino) One by one, our wounded
comrades died.
Eventually, it was just
Fuushin and me.
There isn't anywhere else
that we can go now.
Yes, there is.
Huh?
(Chino) And so, finally, we made
it to Hell Valley.
[winces]
I guess that I'll stay empty,
after all.
Chino!
I can't remember anything!
I still can't remember my mom
and dad's faces, or anyone
else's!
Coming here didn't solve
anything at all.
I still don't know why I was
born! Or why I'm alive right
now!
[gasps] Pursuers from the
Mist!
[attacking yell]
[grunts]
[gasps]
Chino! [gasps]
Chino!
[grunting]
Just let go, you damn...!
[discomforted grunt]
Chino!
Hmph!
[grunts]
What? What the hell
is this?
[gasps] What? What the hell?
[grunts]
[gasps]
(Fuushin) Chino!
Chino!
Hey! Chino! Are you all right?
I didn't know I could do
that.
Huh?
So, was that the true power of
the Chinoike Clan?
I will get my revenge!
(Chino) For the Leaf's
nourishment...
your entire clan was absorbed
by your Village's roots!
So how can you fight for the
Leaf?
(Sasuke) I have a friend who can
share my pain. And I with him.
His wish is that someday the
whole world could be like that,
too.
(Chino) Impossible. That's just
wishful thinking!
(Sasuke) Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Sasuke's Story:
Sunrise, Part 5: The Last One."
And it's that hopeful heart
that connects me to the Hidden
Leaf!