[yawn]
-You're getting a little
too laid back, aren't you?
-Things have been so tense
around here for so long,
what with that business
in the Sand village.
Now that the danger's
finally over, I'm exhausted.
-The immediate
danger may be over,
but that doesn't mean
we can lower our guard.
Who knows what'll happen next?
Only by maintaining
maximum vigilance at all--
-Oh, come on.
You can't live like that.
You'll give yourself
a heart attack.
Relax a little.
Relax.
-Ha ha!
That'll teach you to go
picking on a poor little cat,
you bully.
[alarm ringing]
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Great.
What's the point of
setting the alarm
if I'm going to wake
up before it goes off?
What a total waste.
Now I've got to shut it off,
but I don't feel like moving.
But if I don't
shut it off, it'll
just keep ringing and ringing.
Ugh.
It makes me tired just
thinking about the whole thing.
Some mornings are such a drag.
-I'll take some more.
-Hm?
What's that?
[footsteps]
-Nearly there!
The finish line is in sight!
Victory!
First place.
-Uh.
[shouting]
-Only second place, but close!
-What kind of race is that?
-I don't know.
-It's clear to me that you
need more training, Lee.
-You are right.
And next time I will
try to come in first.
-Well, Lee.
I hate to break it to you,
but I have some bad news.
-Huh?
What would that be, Sensei?
-Just this.
You did not come in second!
You finished in third place!
You're forgetting I
have Kakashi on my back.
Technically, he came in second.
-Did you hear that, Kakashi?
You're a lucky man.
But there's no need to thank me
-You have taught me yet another
valuable lesson, sensei.
I still have so much to learn!
-I'll never get these two, their
ridiculous level of intensity.
-Still.
Hey got us back to the
village pretty darn fast, eh?
-Ridiculous.
-All right, then.
Everyone accounted for?
Let's report in to Lady
Tsunade right away.
-Uh, Guy-sensei.
-What is it?
-Kakashi-sensei's
looking a little--
-Hm?
Gah!
You're right.
First stop the hospital.
then we'll report in.
[theme music]
-Hey.
Look.
He's awake.
-So, I'm back here again, huh?
-Good job, Kakashi.
Well done.
-M'lady.
-Huh?
Lady Tsunade.
SAKURA: Nom Kakashi-sensei.
You mustn't push yourself.
TSUNADE: Sakura's right.
I examined you
earlier, and it's going
to be sometime before
you return to duty.
It's bed rest for you
for at least a week.
KAKASHI: Guess
I'm not surprised.
TSUNADE: Looks like you
need a little more practice
before you've mastered that
new Sharingan of yours.
KAKASHI: Looks that way.
TSUNADE: Anyway, you just
take it easy for a while.
Team Guy should rest too.
You can file your report later.
-Right.
-Let's go, Shizune.
Yes, ma'am.
-Oh.
M'lady wait.
-Huh?
-TSUNADE: What is it?
Is it regarding--
-Yes.
-So, have you told
Kakashi about it yet?
-Kakashi-sensei's he's been
out of it for a while, so no.
Not yet.
-How about Naruto?
No.
I felt it was better to
consult with you first.
-Tell me everything.
SAKURA: It was Sasori, one
of the Akatsuki, who told me.
He said it was a reward
for my defeating him.
-Go to the Tenchi Bridge in the
Village Hidden in the Grass,
10 days from now at nooon.
One of Orochimaru's henchmen
is working for me as a spy,
and that's where I'm supposed
to rendezvous with him.
However, I don't think--
-10 days at the Tenchi Bridge.
-It's already been
four days since then.
We only have six days left.
-Yes, but can you
trust your source.
-They were his last words.
I doubt he was lying.
-What if it's all a trap,
with Orochimaru as the bait
and the Akatsuki waiting there
in full force for whoever's
foolish enough to show up?
-If it's a trap, well
then, we fight them.
-Yes, but now Kakashi is
going to be out of commission
for more than a week,
and with only six days
until the rendezvous.
On top of that, Team Kakashi
has been undermanned ever
since Sasuke left.
-That's true.
TSUNADE: Your only solution
is to find a new member
and assemble a new team.
-Lady Tsunade.
-What is it?
-If that's the case, why
not deploy a different team
to investigate?
And even if you feel that
you must send Sakura,
Naruto mustn't go
on this mission.
-Shizune.
-M'lady.
-Like you, Shizune, Sakura
is among the few shinobi
I trust implicitly.
That's why this mission has
to involve the remaining
members of Team Kakashi.
-Wouldn't my team serve
just as well, m'lady?
Why not send us?
-It wouldn't be the same.
Sakura and Naruto, they're--
they're driven by a desperate
need to find their
lost teammate.
They've both pledged
their lives to rescue him.
That kind of desire
to honor their pledge
is why they will succeed.
That's where you and
Sakura are different.
-Yes, I understand.
But still.
I believe that Naruto should--
-If he'd overheard
this conversation,
what do you think
Naruto would say?
-Well, I'd say we gotta find
some new teammates, that's
what!
See you.
TSUNADE: He's
always so impatient.
I hadn't even finished
my speech yet.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Naruto's
got a mysterious power
that makes everybody
wanna bet on him.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
To be Hokage.
That is my dream!
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER: The
boy who was entrusted
with the First
Hokage's necklace.
Maybe Naruto really
is a special child.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sasuke.
-Hm.
Let's see, now.
Who would be good?
I've gotta think about this very
carefully, because after all, I
wouldn't wanna
choose someone who'd
end up slowing the team down.
That'd be terrible.
But, on the other hand,
it's gotta be someone
that we really get along with.
Otherwise we can kiss
our teamwork goodbye.
And with the way Sakura
gets goofy around boys,
I've gotta be sure the
guy's not too good looking.
This is trickier than
I thought it's be.
-Long time no see, Naruto.
-Huh?
Who are you?
-It's me.
-Hm?
Oh yeah!
Yeah, you're, uh-- Eh.
-I know it's been awhile,
but you should at least
try to remember your
friends, or else it just
turns the other
person's feelings.
-Whoa.
Wait, that voice and that
weird way of talking.
Could it really be?
Yeah!
Shino, right?
-It finally came to you, huh?
-How am I supposed
to recognize you
with your face
covered up like that?
-What's up?
You're early, Shino.
Huh?
-Huh?
Kiba?
That you?
-Hey!
Yeah, no mistaking that scent.
It's Naruto all right.
-You had to smell me first.
What's that all about?
-That dog isn't--
No way, is that--
-What do you mean?
Yeah, It's Akamaru.
Who else?
-Yeah, what?
-Man, look at you, Naruto.
You really grew, huh?
-That's nothing.
I hardly grew at all
compared to Akamaru.
It's hard to believe
he got that much bigger
in such a short amount of time.
-Did he really?
We're always
together, so I guess
I don't notice it that much.
-Trust me, he's bigger.
It wasn't that long ago you
used to carry him around
on the top of your head.
You remember Shino.
-You recognized Kiba right
away, didn't you, Naruto?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Oh man.
Now he's mad at me.
[gasp]
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Na-- Naruto.
I heard that he'd
returned to the village.
What should I do?
I'm not ready for this.
After all this time, I-- I
wouldn't even know what to say.
Um.
-I thought that was you, Hinata.
What's up?
-What's the deal?
Why are you hiding back here?
Uh, Hinata?
Hey, Hinata!
Hinata, are you OK?
-What is it?
Aw, why does she always do stuff
like that when you're around?
-Please.
Our team's short one member.
We need somebody.
HINATA: Huh?
-Afraid you caught
us at a bad time.
We just got assigned a
new mission ourselves.
As soon as Kurenai-sensei
shows up, we're on our way.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): What?
Help.
NARUTO: Come on.
You've got Akamaru.
That's like having
an extra teammate.
You can spare
someone, can't you?
Come on, Kiba.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
What happened?
KIBA: You crazy?
I can't go.
Akamaru and me have
to stick together
to use our combo attack.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
Now I remember.
I saw Naruto, and I--
-NARUTO: OK, I guess
you've got a point.
Well then-- then-- Well, Shino?
You wanna?
-I see you recognized Hinata
right away too, Naruto.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Is
he gonna sulk all day?
-OK, forget it.
Forget it!
Some friends you are.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
That's his voice.
Naruto's voice.
-Hinata.
Don't say a word.
Just come with me and
let's get out of here.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Don't say
a word, just come with me?
No.
No, it's so sudden!
-Huh?
I can't believe it.
All that fuss and
I still struck out.
Well, if that's the
way they're gonna be,
I know someone who
won't let me down.
-OK, Hinata.
Wake up.
Kurenai-sensei will
be here any minute.
We've got a mission.
Shino, you got any water
we can splash on her?
Shino?
-The sky is so blue.
-I'm sorry, but
like I already said,
I've been put in charge
of the Chunin exams.
It's a big, fat drag,
but there it is.
I mean, I'd like to lend you
a hand, Naruto, for old times'
sake and everything,
but these days, it
seems my time isn't
my own anymore.
-Hm.
-Besides.
The Fifth Hokage appointed me.
She'd kill me if I just gave
it up and went with you.
You don't wanna get
on her bad side.
She's worse than my mother.
-And here I though, least I know
one guy who's a heads up guy.
Good old Shikamaru will help
me, even if no one else will.
-Don't use those guilt
tripping puppy dog eyes on me.
I said it's impossible.
-You've got better things--
CHOJI: Hey, I'll help you out.
-Hm?
-Here you go, Shikamaru.
Your mom asked me to
bring you your lunch box.
NARUTO: Ch-- Choji?
Choji!
-What are you
talking about, Choji?
How are you able
to help him out?
Have you forgotten
the mission you're
going on with Asuma and Ino?
-Yeah, but he needs help.
I can't turn down an
old friend like Naruto.
Don't worry.
I'll clear it with Asuma-sensei.
-Thanks, Choji.
Thanks a lot.
-It doesn't matter if you
clear it with Asuma, because he
has to clear it
with Lady Tsunade,
and there's no way
she's going to say yes.
-Well, anyway.
There's no harm in trying.
Here.
Have your lunch box.
NARUTO: Oh, thanks.
-Uh, Naruto?
I think that's my lunch.
-Always eating.
Just like the old days.
Yeah, compared to back then,
you've gained-- weight!
-Behind you.
Watch out!
-Over there.
-I don't recognize him, but
he wears a Leaf headband.
-A sneak attack, huh?
I don't know what
this guy is up to,
but one good way to find
out is to capture him.
And hand him over to
the Interrogation Corps.
Go, Naruto!
I'll back you up.
-Gotcha!
-Ninja Art, Super Beast Scroll.
[theme music]
TSUNADE: Yes, Naruto
is a Jinchuriki,
and I know it's a risk
sending him on this mission.
If the Akatsuki gain control
of the Tailed Beast within him,
it could mean the end
of the Leaf village.
But I also know that
Naruto does have talent.
He will be a great
asset to them Leaf.
If it turns out that I'm wrong
and the Leaf and the Land
of Fire are endangered
because of me,
then I swear as the Fifth
Hokage to protect them
with all my might.
NARUTO: Next time.
Formation, New Team Kakashi!
[theme music]
KIBA: Wow, it seems like forever
since last time we saw Naruto.
-Yes.
He's certainly changed
quite a bit, hasn't he?
-You think?
Well, maybe a little taller.
-Two and a half
years is a long time.
I've changed too.
I've grown a lot.
Don't you think I
look more mature now?
-Nah, you don't seem
that different to me.
For instance, you still do
that nervous fidgety thing
with your fingers.
-I do not.
-Anyway, I'm the
one who's changed.
I'm way more intense
than I used to be.
-Actually, you don't seem
that different to me either.
-Yeah right.
Well, the part of you that goes
all goofy when Naruto's around,
that hasn't changed.
-That was because it
happened to suddenly.
I wasn't--
-Hi Naruto.
-Ah!
-Just kidding.
-Kiba, don't do that.
-OK, OK, sorry.
SHINO: You guys.
-Huh?
-You should be aware
of my presence by now.
After all, I am a part
of Team Kurenai, as well.
-Oh Shino.
-Again with the sulking.