Ino, Choji.
Let's get this over
with and go home.
Yeah, we got it!
Innat right, Choji?
Huh?
Choji?!
Aaahhh!
Ugh, that idiot!
[Shikamaru]
Damn it.
Ino, use Formation--
I know! I know!
All right!
Shadow Strangle Jutsu!
[Shikamaru]
I'm counting on you, Ino.
That was all the chakra I had.
I'm at my limit.
Here I go! Mind Transfer Jutsu!
Ahh.
Good... Looks like it worked.
Ah ha! I thought so!
Super Expansion Jutsu!
Huh?
What's the deal, Choji?!
Why were you hanging back?!
This hunt was your idea in
the first place, you know!
Listen, everybody needs
food to survive, right?
The village is crisis right now;
we have to make sure we eat!
Yeah, but you're the only
one who's taking a break!
What if the herd got away
while you were slacking off?
Well,
I wasn't worried.
I already knew just
what Shikamaru would do.
Augh.
Come to think of it Ino
knew what to do before I
said anything, too...
Heh.
"Team 10's Teamwork"
They're demons! They show up
every year during the harvest
and take whatever they want!
This year, we were preparing to
fight them off, or die trying!
But That Baji!
He was too clever for me.
I'm not sure if he knew
of my plan or not.
But he kidnapped my
granddaughter to
keep us in line!
Who is this Baji?
He's the leader of all the
bandits, the ones who've
stolen the crops every year.
[sobs]
Please, Please, I beg you,
help us save our village!
And save my granddaughter
from those outlaws!
And who's this guy?
That's Tofu;
he was once a bandit.
[Kakashi]
An ex-bandit?
I don't blame you
for your mistrust.
But I- The things that
they did, I just couldn't
be a part of it!
Tofu here is the one who
told me my granddaughter
had been abducted and
offered to help.
He knows where their hideout is.
He'll be an invaluable guide.
I suppose
that's true.
Please, allow me to help.
Well then, let's
get ready to go.
[others, in unison]
Right!
[Asuma]
Shikamaru. You got a minute?
Hm?
[Tofu]
The hideout's located
in a natural fort.
It's deep inside a cavern
that branches out like an
anthill's passageways.
There's only one way to get
inside. And they have three
forts guarding that route.
But the trickiest
obstacle of all is
Baji's intellect.
He's very hard to outsmart.
That's why people
fear him so much.
[Kakashi]
The main purpose of
this mission is to
rescue the hostage.
That means we'll have to
confront Baji's gang.
Shikamaru, what
are your thoughts?
Hmm, let me see here.
Huh?
He may still be a genin,
but he's a skilled tactician.
It's unfortunate that there's
only one way in, but we won't be
moving a large force through...
It's just a few of us,
so maybe we can get past
the forts undetected.
However, I'm sure
they've set up numerous
traps to defend it.
Since that's the most
obvious plan of attack.
That route is still our best
chance to escape without
having to fight our way out
after we make the rescue.
At the very least,
we need to confirm that
we'd have safe passage.
[Asuma]
Okay!
So the first thing to do is to
find a way for a small team to
infiltrate the hideout.
All right!
Then let's go, already!
We genin aren't going.
Whaa?!
Like I just explained to you,
the bandits know the routes in,
and are sure to guard them.
The only ones capable of
getting in undetected are
Kakashi and Asuma Sensei.
I believe that it's best
to let them handle this.
Of course, that's
just my opinion.
And it's a good one!
Seems like the best way,
Kakashi.
Agreed. Don't be so upset,
Naruto.
Well, Shikamaru,
take care of
things here.
Guess I'll have to.
What am I gonna do??
Well, You heard
what we decided.
Just wait here for
a while, okay?
Huh? Hey, where'd that
Tofu guy run off to?
He said Nature called.
[Tofu]
What's the big idea?!
Huh?!
You guys... What was that?
[Sasuke]
Hey, look over there!
They have Tofu!
The bandits captured him?!
But how did they...?!
Just perfect.
So what are we
going to do now?!
Come on!
Don't just sit there!
The enemy is a gang of
thugs with lots of men.
They have a hostage
and three forts.
And beyond that,
their citadel.
Well, it's gonna be a drag,
but we'll have to go after
them ourselves.
Boss Baji!
I've brought the deserter!
Good. You can go now.
Yes, sir!
Phew!
That hurt.
Welcome back, my friend.
Ngh, those men of yours,
train them better. Okay?
Remember, I'm a very
valuable informant.
Sorry. They've been
trained to be suspicious
even if a captive gives
them the correct password.
Eagh. Well,
better safe than
sorry, I guess.
So, do you have
information for me?
Heh heh. The village
hired shinobi just
like you thought.
Mmm. And how
strong are they?
Eh, it's just two
jonin and six genin.
Two small teams made
up mostly of genin?
Get rid of the jonin, and the
genin will fall. No problem.
Yeah, I bet! And the two
jonin aren't even with
the genin right now!
Oh? Why's that?
They're looking for a way
to get in here without
passing by the forts.
[Baji]
Hm, hm. That's
just what I'd do, too.
But if they don't anticipate
our traps along the way,
they'll be on nothing more
than a suicide mission.
Unfortunately, one of them
already thought of that.
Hmm?
He's a genin named Shikamaru.
And he already assumed
that there'd be traps.
So a two-man squad
made up of jonin
bypasses our forts, alert
for traps, while trying to
find a way inside, huh?
As if I could be defeated
so easily by such a
predictable strategy!
BOOSSS!!!
Mmm?
Boss! A bunch of shinobi are
here! Somehow they managed to
get past all three of our forts!
They did what?!
[Baji]
Why didn't the forts warn us?!
[Henchman]
The shinobi just showed up out
of nowhere! That's all I know!
Those three forts are
there to prevent just
this sort of thing!
It's impossible
to get past them!
You! Are you a double
agent?! Did you conspire
with the men at the forts
to let these ninja in?
No! No way! I swear,
I'd never do that!
You've gotta believe me!
Bah! Talk is cheap!
Wait! I know! Those
shinobi think I've
been captured, right?
Well... if you convince them to
give up one of their group for
me in a hostage exchange,
then I'll be able to
stall them and feed you
inside information!
Hmm...
Not a bad idea.
After all, keeping
you here does me no good.
But if I can exchange you for
their leader, then I can crush
him along with their plans!
The more cards that I have to
play in this game, the better.
All right, guys!
Let's pulverize all
these crooks--!
Slow down, Naruto.
What?!
Don't forget there's
still a hostage.
[Shikamaru]
Bringing down their hideout
might not be that difficult,
but before we can do that,
we have to find and free
the village elder's
granddaughter.
Oh. Right.
But how?
What's the plan?
We'll take advantage
of their next move.
[Sakura]
And what's that going to be?
[Shikamaru]
My guess is...
... that they're going to try a
hostage exchange.
Well that makes sense
if they want to avoid a
direct confrontation.
Hold on: a hostage exchange?
You mean one of us will
have to become those
bandits' new hostage?
Shikamaru!
I want to talk to you.
Show yourself!
If you want to save him,
Then you'll choose to
take his place and become
my captive instead!
Hm. Just what I
was expecting.
So what's your answer?!
Shikamaru?!
Okay! Sounds good!
Hm!
He answered my question!
So far, it's all going
just as I planned.
Hurk! Urgh! Augh!
What the-? My voice is gone!
Hmm. My Hidden Jutsu,
the Muting Jutsu.
If you can't speak, you
can't convey any strategy
you might come up with!
I just have to have
faith in them.
What could he be thinking?!
That numbskull.
Hey! Don't go
off on your own!
Listen, Shikamaru would never do
anything unless he had a plan.
He's right.
Shikamaru said he'd
take advantage of this
hostage exchange.
But what did he mean by that?
Hm?
I'm sorry for
all the trouble
that I caused.
You can knock off
the act anytime now.
Huh?
Nngh!
We already know
that you're a spy.
And we have
for a very
long time!
Heh heh
heh heh!
But then why-?!
Ah!
Did you...
come here to
save me?
How did you get
past the forts?
Oh. Right.
You're still
under my jutsu.
Release!
Hey, It's going
to be all right.
I asked how you got
past the forts!
That part was easy.
Hm?
All of us were suspicious of
Tofu right from the very start.
Because of that,
We secretly placed a
mini-wireless on him.
[Baji]
What?!
As we thought,
he said the password,
not knowing he was
giving it to us.
The lilies on the mountain
pass shine at nighttime.
But I've never fully
trusted passwords.
Those guards at the forts
had strict orders, even
if someone did give them
the correct password!
Maybe. But it seems
they're not as
suspicious as you are.
All that we had to
do is tell them,
"A spy who knows the
password should have
come through before us.
We're after him."
And just like that,
they let us in.
[Baji]
They... What?!
It was a childish
trick, I know.
But it worked well, so who
cares?
Ungh.
Well, you're certainly
no child, I'll give you
that much, Shikamaru.
But still. even if you're
a smart tactician, you're
just a prisoner now.
And I have my own strategy,
one that'll wipe out your
little genin friends!
Don't be afraid.
My friends are gonna be here
any minute to save us both.
Don't bother trying to
put on a brave act!
Ninjutsu may be powerful,
but there's no way to
destroy this place without
harming the hostage.
That's the whole
point of a hostage!
Uh! Hold on...
If you knew that Tofu was
my spy, why'd you agree to
the hostage exchange?!
Heh!
Gee, I wonder...
Ugh!
[explosion]
Uh?
Fire Style!
Fire Ball Jutsu!
An assault? So the loss of
their leader causes the
genin to panic and attack,
heedless of the hostages.
Or is this a
diversionary tactic?
Either way, they can't attack at
full force when I have hostages.
And your genin friends lack the
jutsu to pinpoint our location.
So I still have the upper
hand here. And there's no
way that you can possibly
come out on top.
Just calm down! You know that
the boss has planned ahead
for situations like this!
And this place is
a natural fort!
A large force
can't get in!
HWAAHHH!
What's your deal?
HUUHH!?
Boss! Trouble!
What's wrong?
Sir! More shinobi
have appeared!
All right, no
need to panic.
You can't fall apart every time!
I gave you contingency plans for
this kind of thing.
Dh... Yes, but...
We're facing a thousand men!
It's an army!
A thousand?!
Ahh!
[Naruto]
Hee hee!
Shikamaru's not here!
That means there's no one
to tell me not to do this!
Shikamaru and the hostage are in
the west tower. We have to make
sure not to destroy that one!
Right!
You got it,
Choji!
Okay!
Expansion Jutsu!
Human Boulder!
Yeah! Go get 'em, Choji!
Hm!
You're so calm.
You even seem
to enjoy this!
Huh? What,
seriously? I do?
Aren't you scared about
what might happen?
No way.
But why not?!
Because I have faith
in my friends.
Don't get overconfident, kid!
I still have the upper
hand, here!
I can escape by using
my hostage as a shield!
You see, as long as I have
the girl with me, I can
negotiate my way out of here.
And if I can escape before
those genin brats get here,
all of your plans won't
mean a thing, anyway!
You'd abandon your
men like that?!
Those men down there?
What a laugh!
you just don't get it!
Once I escape, I can
form a new gang
anytime I want!
Shikamaru!
Oh! Good!
Are you both
all right?
Yeah. But just barely.
How do you think we feel?!
You sure scared us!
How did you find
this place?
She's from the Yamanaka clan of
the Hidden Leaf, and they have a
very powerful Hidden Jutsu.
The Mind Transfer Jutsu.
I'm sure you've at least
heard it mentioned before.
The Mind Transfer Jutsu?!
When I first approached you,
All right! Mind Transfer Jutsu!
Then, using that Jutsu,
Ino looked through my eyes
and located our position.
Release!
You guys! I found out
where Shikamaru and the
hostage are being held!
Now you know what happened.
Give me a break, would
you? You act like we
had it all planned;
you're just lucky
I figured out what
you had in mind!
[Choji]
Yeah, it was touch-and-go
for a while there.
But that's ludicrous!
How could you have possibly
known from the start
that I would call for
a hostage exchange and
trade Tofu for you?!
Well, when a player loses
a card, he wants to
replace it, doesn't he?
Ngh!
A card?
In your case, the card you lost
was actually three things:
the forts we bypassed.
Once they were out of play,
you needed to replace them as
quickly as possible.
And the easiest and
fastest way to do that,
Was through an
exchange of hostages.
You're a tactician.
You believe in
analyzing every bit
of data you get.
And your top priority
is figuring out your
enemy's strategy.
Because of that, I knew
right off the bat that
you would target me.
And that's the
whole story.
He heh.
That's simply amazing.
And you beat me.
I've got to hand
it to you.
Nothing I did was amazing.
What is truly amazing is
that my friends believe
in me no matter what.
Shut up!
Ha-hah!
[Baji]
Paper Bombs!
Try to make a
move against me,
and I'll set these off
and blow you up!
You hear me? Make
a move and I'll--
Hngh!
Shadow Possession Jutsu.
Gotcha.
Aah!
[Kakashi]
My, my, This year's
rookies are quite
talented, aren't they?
[Asuma]
We heard everything, Shikamaru.
That was quite a risk you took,
going in there alone
without telling the
others your strategy.
Despite that, the mission
ended successfully.
Well done, Shikamaru.
Thanks, but it really
wasn't a risk.
You see,
I knew what my friends could
accomplish, and I had faith in
what we could achieve together.
I didn't have to tell them a
thing; I knew these guys would
know what I was thinking.
When I think about those
old missions, Team 10
always had each other's
backs during battle.
No, that's not quite right.
It wasn't just Team 10.
It was all of us!
Naruto,
Lee, Kiba...
And now, our faith in our
friends has spread beyond just
our own individual teams.
It encompasses the
entire village.
Wouldn't you agree, Asuma?
Well, what do you say, you guys?
Should we go back and
have some barbecue?
Yeah!
Hey, wait up!
As punishment, you get
to carry all this back
to the village, Choji.
Aw, come on!
Help me out,
would ya?
[chuckle]
People may call me a
tactician who plays his
cards close to his chest,
But these guys know everything
there is to know about me.
[Tsunade]
I have a mission for Team 7!
But it appears things are
not going well between
Naruto and Sasuke.
[Kakashi]
I'm embarrassed to admit it,
but they're not.
[Tsunade]
I guess it can't be helped.
You and Sasuke will handle
this mission, then.
[Kakashi]
What shall I do with
Naruto and Sakura?
[Tsunade]
Don't worry. I have the
perfect assignment for them.
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden,
"Drive Towards Darkness."
[Naruto]
This is for the good
of the mission, too!