Master! Master!
Master!
[gasping]
Master! Who has done this
to you?!
Quack, quack..
Quack, quack?
Quack.
Quack?
I'm trying to tell you to
duck out of here!
[laughing]
I won't let you!
Oh, no, it's Madara!
The leader of the
Akatsuki!
Yes, Rock Lee, ultimate
weapon of the Hidden
Leaf Village!
That man was merely bait
to lure you here.
You are unforgivable!
It is time for me to use
Sensei's secret medicine
now!
[gulping]
What in the--
[hiccuping]
[groaning]
What's with those moves?
You look like a drunken.
This will be easy...
[attacking yell]
[yelling]
With my Teleportation
Ninjutsu, you can't touch
me.
Aye!
I get stronger the more I
drink! This is the art
of the Drunken Fist!
You will not be able to
see my punch coming!
What?!
[yelling]
Too easy!
[grunting]
I am just getting
started!
Uh?! Awww...
Sensei, may I have
another?
But that was the last
one!
[groaning]
[hiccuping]
You heard him. So until I
get more medicine, let us
just take a little
breather.
Sure, why not?
No way! Like I'd agree to
that!
[screaming]
[panting]
[sighing]
It was all just
a dream, then.
Unacceptable! I cannot
believe that I fell asleep
during training!
It only shows I
lack vigilance!
War is coming! I must
become strong like
Naruto!
I must train harder!
Harder!
But wait... if I could
somehow become as strong
as I was in that dream without
having to take the medicine...
Guy Sensei, I think that
the time has finally come
to attempt that training
once again!
"Fight! Rock Lee!"
[groaning]
Just lie down and stay
still and you'll feel
better.
No, don't be
ridiculous!
Eh?!
If guts and effort can't
overcome a little
seasickness...
Why, then I no longer
deserve to be called the
Leaf's Blue Beast!
All right, all right,
already!
Hmm.
You know... that reminds
me...
It was the day after we
took Lee out to celebrate
him learning the Hidden
Lotus...
[snoring]
[gagging]
[retching]
Oh, boy... I feel
rotten.
Must've had too much to
drink last night. Huh?
[snoring]
How strange. I wonder
what Lee is doing in
my room.
Unfortunately, my memory
is unclear.
I do remember going out
to dinner with you, Guy
Sensei...
But I cannot remember
anything else.
Hm, yes. And I'm
in the same boat.
But I have a feeling that
something really big
happened last night.
I am sorry, Sensei!
What are you
apologizing for?!
You took me out for a
delicious meal and I had
the audacity to forget
it!
And you probably gave me
hints about training,
too!
I have failed as a
student!
Just hold on, Lee,
it's okay. Hm?
What was that just now?
Wait a minute! That's
right!
[crying]
I'm so very sorry!
I, Might Guy, am
responsible for
everything!
[struggling]
Sensei?
Sensei? What is it? Tell
me.
It's nothing! Nothing at
all!
I've really gone and done
it now...
Oh! Have you remembered
something about what
happened last night?!
Please! You have to
tell me what it is!
It's nothing.
Nothing at all!
But, uh, by the way,
Lee... why did you bring
that menu back here?
I feel really guilty about
taking it from the
restaurant...
But I used this menu to
take copious notes on the
hints that you gave me
about training, Sensei.
I gave you hints about
training...?
Yes!
Please, take a
look at it.
Grilled chicken skewers?
What about them?
Sensei, you told me that
one could train at any
time! For example, even
with a menu.
You circled the
chicken to show me!
And you told me that I
need to visualize.
To visualize with grilled
chicken?!
Come to think of it...
Kakashi!
It's time for a match
with my eternal rival!
Come on, we just have to!
Right?
I can't. I'm right in the
middle of training.
Oh, don't be ridiculous!
How can reading indecent
books like this be
training?
This is just my way of
training.
Huh?
It's training through
visualization.
Whether it's a real
battle or only training,
visualizing can really
make a huge difference in
your performance.
You know, you should try
reading books and
learning to visualize,
too. See ya!
I should learn to
visualize? What's he
talking about? Developing
a new jutsu?
Huh. I think it's called
training through
visualization.
Training through
visualization?! And tell
me. What kind of training
is that, Sensei?!
Oh, well without any
doubt, it's a very
important type of
training! I guess...
That has to be it!
Yesterday, during dinner, you
were probably telling me all
about this kind of training!
Perhaps if we try it out
this very day, right now,
then we shall remember what
happened yesterday!
Oh, uh...
Please, let us try!
If I train and remember,
it will be like killing
two birds with one stone!
And if you remember, too,
it is like killing
three birds with one
stone!
This isn't good.
Especially not if it
makes him remember what
happened yesterday.
If he remembers how
pitiful the whole
situation was, I'll lose
face as his master.
I am Might Guy, The
Leaf's Blue Beast.
He mustn't remember!
I'll do everything in my
power to prevent it!
Sensei. Just what kind
of training is this,
anyway?
You mean you don't
recognize it? Right
now, you're training
through visualization!
Oh, I get it! This is
what you were telling
me about!
Yep!
You see, those delicious
skewers are made with
chicken!
Bird-style self-defense
means White Crane
Fist!
Oh! Yes, I can see it! It
is definitely a crane!
And when you become one
with the crane, then
you're close to mastering
the White Crane Fist!
That is the true benefit
of visualization
training!
Huh! Now that you
mention it...
It is quite difficult to
balance on one leg in the
mud.
But of course! This combines
strength training for your
legs and torso!
[grunting]
Lee! You're not
visualizing enough!
Visualize!
Visualize this not as a
chicken skewer but as a
mighty sword to use
against your enemies!
The "Grilled chicken"
technique!
I see! Visualize grilled
chicken! Very deep!
All right! I will become
grilled chicken!
Yes! Great! Visualize it!
Huh?
But for some reason, the
birds appear to be
getting very upset.
[gulping]
I think that
you're right.
[bird calls]
[screaming]
Nice bird! Oh,
no, no!
I guess eating a bird in
front of other birds
wasn't such a good
idea.
But there won't be any
problems this time!
Oh! Barbecued eel!
Is there really an eel
technique, Sensei?
You're not visualizing
hard enough, Lee! An eel
moves just like a snake,
right?
And that means...
Snake Fist!
Right! The Snake Fist!
[grunting]
Lee, join in!
Yes, sir!
Visualize a snake
slithering silently and
hunting its prey...
Ahhh!
Sensei! What is this?!
Oh, it's just a little
something they call
quicksand!
[screaming]
[grunting]
Whoa. That was a very
close call!
Not quite. Problems are
just chances to succeed!
Right! But why are we
climbing this mountain,
anyway, Sensei?
'Cause next on the menu
is Ma Po tofu.
Okay, but...
It contains hawk claw
chili pepper.
Hawk claw should
remind us of...
Eagle Claw Fist!
Oh, so then...?
[chirping]
Nothing ventured, nothing
gained! To visualize an
eagle, find its nest!
Jump!
[chirping]
Sorry to disturb you! But
really, we mean no harm!
Let's be friends!
Hurry up, Lee!
Sensei, is the essence of
Eagle Claw Fist here?
[gasping]
[screaming]
Now, that's the essence
of Eagle Claw Fist!
I agree!
Sensei, have you
remembered anything
yet?
Uh, no. What about
you, Lee?
Not really.
Oh! I see!
Good! This visualization
nonsense is throwing him
off track!
[gulping]
Aaahhh!
So refreshing!
Hmmm...
Wait... I think I
remember something
else...
[gasping]
Now I'm sure... Lee has
seen me at my absolute
worst!
I must stop him from
remembering anything
about yesterday!
Sensei, just one final
menu item was circled.
Let's hope we remember
after this, Or we'll
just have to forget
the entire thing!
So, what did
you circle?
Well, I sure hope that this
works. The last item we
circled at dinner is a
bottle of sake!
[spitting]
That must mean a
technique like the Dr--
Drifter Fist!!
What?
It's the Drifter Fist!!
Ah! The ocean!
There is a technique that
is called the Drifter
Fist?
Yes, of course!
That was close! I have to
avoid bringing up any
images of alcohol. Drunken
Fist is out of the question.
Let us start training
right now!
Lee, what in the world
are you doing?
Well, to learn the
Drifter Fist, I thought
that we would do our
training on a boat.
Oh! Of course! You really
are becoming quite sharp!
The visualization
training is paying off
in spades.
Oh, boy. It had
to be a boat.
Let us begin, Sensei.
This training involves
more than just simple
visualization.
There's no point in even
starting unless you can
maintain balance on a boat
that's swaying on the water.
Yes, Guy Sensei! But if
this is all the swaying,
then it should be quite
easy.
Stop! Stop! Just stop!
To remain still on the
water's surface! That is
the essence of Drifter
Fist.
Hey, don't do that! Don't
rock the boat so much!
Whoaaa-- but Sensei,
I'm not doing this!
Ahhhhh!
This training is
definitely intense!
[gagging]
Sensei, I do not feel so
good...
[groaning]
Oh no! Those moves look
just like the Drunken
Fist! I have to stop him!
[gagging]
Listen, Lee! You can't
master the Drifter Fist
with moves like those.
You must stand firm!
[groaning]
Oh... You mean like this?
I am standing firm.
Hold on... What kind of
movement is that?!
I am sorry, but to keep
my balance...
... This works best.
That boy...! The Drunken
Fist just comes naturally
to him. That's right!
[growling]
[grunting]
What's the big idea?!
[groaning]
[hiccuping]
[yelling]
So fast! Such movement!
But how did...?
[gasping]
Sake lee pickles! Made by
soaking radishes in sake
lees.
Yes, that's just gotta be
it! You're a natural
Drunken Fist user!
Go for it! Teach him a
lesson!
No mercy for a drunkard
who tries to eat and run!
Hit to your heart's
content, my boy!
[laughing]
So that's what
happened... It was you
all along...
Guy Sensei, I am sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
[gagging]
I believe that I did
something terrible
yesterday!
And you were forced to
fall to your knees to
apologize for my shameful
deed!
Uh!
So, then... You remember
everything that happened?
I do not remember the
event itself.
But what I do remember is
the shop being in ruins
and you apologizing to
the owner.
I see... And when you saw
that, you must have found
me pathetic, indeed...
Not so! Because the
words that you spoke
then were so...
This day was to celebrate
my pupil's efforts.
I admit he's foolish and
only knows how to work
hard.
But still, he strives
harder than any other
man, and he will succeed
because he's a genius at
working hard!
He's a great shinobi, the
future of the Leaf, the
treasure I've dedicated
my life to!
If anyone's to blame,
it's me as his master!
Forgive me!
And after that... you
asked them not to spoil
my big day!
Which was to mark my
past successes and my
future endeavors.
That is all that I'm able
to remember... But the
fervor in your words
struck me!
That is why I have been
trying so hard to get you
to remember what happened!
So you could scold me
for all of my mistakes!
But this is the final
hint, my last chance to
unlock all those hidden
memories...
So now...
What do I do...?!
Lift your head up, Lee!
[sobbing]
Sensei?!
Hear me! You have done
nothing wrong!
All you did was try to
learn the Drunken Fist
technique!
Sensei! You regained
your memory?
Never mind that. I'm
going to teach you the
art of the Drunken Fist!
But, you need to drink
sake to learn it, do you
not, Sensei?
You're stronger the
drunker you get! That is
Drunken Fist!
But you already have an
innate affinity for that
technique!
Just embrace your nausea!
Through seasickness,
perfect your own, unique
Drunken Fist!
What, really?!
And then put this
training to use!
Let's go!
Right!
Hyyyaaah!
[yelling]
[grunting]
Too easy, Lee! Severe
Leaf Hurricanes!
[gagging]
All right, then! Leaf
Whirlwind!
This nausea is getting
worse by the second!
But your Seasick Fist is
looking better and
better!
[gagging]
Yes! This is my own
version of the Drunken
Fist! The Seasick Fist.
Yes! The Seasick Fist!
Here I come!
He's gone?!
I really feel sick!
Ahhhhhh!
Guy Sensei! Guy Sensei!
Are you all right, Guy
Sensei?!
[chuckling]
You sure got me good.
You did it! The Seasick
Fist.
That was a terrific hit!
Guy Sensei... That means
the world to me!
[retching]
And as a result of
undergoing intense
training through
seasickness, Lee finally
managed to perfect his
Seasick Fist!
He can't use it,
though...
Huh? Well, surely unless
he overcomes his seasickness,
he can't use it in battle.
And then Lee said...
Through hard work and
guts, I swear to conquer
my seasickness and master
the Seasick Fist!
That's not what I meant.
Huh?
I mean there's really no
way that he can fight
while he's seasick, but
unless he feels woozy
from the seasickness...
Then it really won't be
like the Drunken Fist,
will it?
Eh-heh.
Come on!
What?! Our food's
infested with mushrooms!
It's not just the food.
Our water is gone, too.
We have to turn the ship
around right now!
We can't. Once we're
on this route, turning
back is impossible.
But-!
We can't change course
for two weeks. We'll have
to do without food or
water till then!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Eat or Die!
Mushrooms from Hell!
I need food! Give me
something to eat!