(Sasuke) Big Brother...?
Can you please help me with my
shuriken training today?
No I can't, I'm busy.
Why don't you go ask Father to
teach you instead?
(Sasuke) Ah come on...
You're always doing
this. You never have
time.
It's always the
same old story.
Big Brother... Why do
you always treate me like such a
pest?
I know what's going on. You just
don't like me!
(Itachi) Don't say that, Sasuke.
I don't have time for this
today.
(SASUKE) It's always "today
this, today that" with you! When
will tomorrow ever come?
[chuckle]
Sorry about this, Sasuke.
Hm?
(Itachi) Oh! Right...
The next time Father
and Mother go somewhere, I may
be able to take some time off.
Hm? Really?! When's that gonna
happen?!
You'll have to ask
Father. See you.
Huh?
[sigh and chuckle]
(Fugaku) What kind of fish is
this? It's really good!
(Mikoto) Oh, you like it? It was
on sale today!
(Sasuke) Things in season are
always cheap and tasty.
(Fugaku) Oh, is that so, Sasuke?
[giggle]
Hey, mom! Seconds please!
Sure thing!
(Sasuke) Big Brother said that
you're going on a trip
somewhere. When do you leave?
(Fugaku) Yes, that's right.
We're going to visit your
mother's family.
(Sasuke) Oh...
So Itachi... told you all about
our trip, did he?
I thought that we could go on
my next day off.
You wanna come?
(Sasuke) I'm gonna have Big
Brother teach me all kinds of
stuff.
Hm? He said he'd...
...teach you?
Oh, yeah! He promised that he
would!
(Mikoto) Itachi did? That's
unusual! Oh, here's your rice
dear.
Thanks.
And as for your shuriken
prctice, I can help you work on
it when you get home if you
want.
It's not just practice... It's
actual training.
(Fugaku) Oh, could I trouble
you for some tea?
(Mikoto) Sure!
(Fugaku) Extra hot, please.
(Mikoto) Okay!
(Itachi) Now you try, just like
that.
(Itachi) You've improved,
Sasuke!
(Sauske Laugh)
I can throw better than Mom now!
(Itachi) All right, how about
this?
Huh?
(Sasuke) You're amazing, Big
Brother!
How'd you even get them to do
that?
(Itachi) You'll be throwing like
that soon.
You're quite a lot like me, you
know that?
Heh...
(Sasuke) Big Brother? Can you
teach me again sometime, like
today?
(Itachi) Sure... when I have the
time.
You promise?
(Itachi) Yeah.
(Itachi) Do you know how the
Uchiha Clan came about?
(Sasuke) What? No, I haven't
really learned bout it too much
yet...
(Itachi) The Uchiha crest is the
symbol and proof of our
prestigious clan.
An image of a fan... is
prestigious?
You need wind to start a fire,
right? You produce wind with a
fan.
And is that... something
amazing?
[Itachi chuckle]
Huh?
Well, you'll come to understand
in time.
Big Brother...
For the sake of the Clan. That's
why you fight?
(Itachi) I wonder...
I'm not entirely sure about that
just yet, either...
(Stomach Growl)
[laugh]
All right! I'm gonna make us a
big feast tonight!
Hot!
You made all this just for the
two of us?
Uh, yeah...
But maybe I went a little
overboard.
Yeah, just a little.
[burp]
(Long Inhale)
I'm totally stuffed!
Hmm?
(Itachi) Hey, Sasuke... Want
to sleep outside tonight?
(Sauske) Are you sure it's
okay for us to do that?
(Sauske Chuckle)
Hey, careful! Don't be in such a
rush!
Ow!
(Itachi) Are you cold?
Uh-uh! It feels great out here!
(Sauske) I really wanna become a
skilled shinobi like you!
Because that way, I'll
finally be able to get
Father's approval.
[chuckle] You want to be like
me?
(Itachi) No. You'll
surpass me.
That's impossible.
No way! I mean, you're this
super-gifted genius!
Everyone says that, you know...
[laugh] You know, you are a lot
like me.
You do have the potential.
Okay, then! I'll surpass you!
(Itachi) Sasuke... Sasuke?
(Sleeping)
(Fugaku) Hey! Sasuke!
What are you doing out here?
What is it? Father?
Huh...?! Where am I?
Oh! Right. Big Brother said we
could sleep outside...
Itachi did?!
[giggle]
Where's Big Brother now?
It seems that he's left already.
Sometimes I just don't know what
he's thinking...
Big Brother...
♪♪♪
(Heavy Breathing)
(Sakura) I'm home...
[humming]
(Sigh)
(Small Chuckle)
Hmm?
Yes!
(Sakura) Shoiuld i try parting
it this way, maybe? But...
Hmm?
Uhh...
(Sigh)
(Frustrated)
Hey, Sakura.
I was thinkin', don't those
bangs of yours get in the way?
You should just cut them off!
Oh, don't start, dear!
Girls have their reasons to do
what they do!
If you say things like that to
her, then Sakura's going to
start hating you!
[laugh]
Grrrr...
(Running)
(Ino) Oh... You like
flowers, huh?
Huh? Who...
Oh...
...it's you, Ino.
You like those cosmos flowers?
(Sakura) Oh...uh...Um, I...
I guess so... yeah.
Hey, here, take a look at this!
Tadah!
(Sakura) Oh, how pretty!
I know, right?
I could tie your hair up with
this if you want!
Huh?! You wanna tie up my hair?!
You're really cute, Sakura!
Don't hide it. Now... There!
This looks way better on you!
Don't yu think?
But this way... It's just...
My forehead...
(Ino) ...is a billboard brow.
(Ino) People only tease you
because you try to cover it up.
(Ino) Just flaunt it n' don't
let them get to you.
(Ino) Then everybody around
you will change.
But Ino, you're so strong, and
I'm...
(Ino) I think that this is a
mucy better look for you.
Don't you?
You've got a good sense of
style. I think hat you just need
to have more confidence!
(Sakura) I, um... Well, I
think that...I made a friend.
Her name is Ino Yamanaka, and
she's this totally incredible
person!
She's cute, strong, fashionable,
and really kind, too!
Wow... I see...
You made a friend, Sakura?
(Crying)
Well, if she's cute like you
say, then I would love to meet
her!
Oh, dear...
...why would you say someting
like that?!
I'm really happy for you,
Sakura.
You have to make sure that you
cherish your friends.
Always remember, in this life,
friends are your most precious
assets.
Okay!
Ino even gave me this ribbon in
my hair!
And it looks great on you! You
know, you're as cute as your
mother was when she was young.
Oh dear, don't embarass me! Did
you actually say that I'm cute?!
(Laughing)
Sakura, while you're at it, you
should find a boyfriend, too!
Dad! Stop!
[laughter]
(Bird Chirping)
(Ino) Wow! That's amazing!
You did all this by yourself?!
I(Sakura) t's nothing, really!
I mean... I'm not that
creative... Not like you are.
Although...
Do you see this cosmos flower?
To bring out its beauty more,
the things around it should
complement it.
So the elememts of the
arrangement don't clash.
Hold on. Let me try something,
okay?
Like... this... So.. what do you
thing? How's it look?
You know...
...there's this boy...
...and, well, I have a really
big crush on him...
Oh, yeah? I had no idea. So who
is this mystery boy?
And is this the whole reason why
you've been acting so much more
cheerful lately?
Okay! All done!
No, not really. Or at least I
don't think so... But Sasuke is
just...
Oh, okay. I see. So it's Sasuke,
huh?
There's a rumor that... Sasuke
likes girls who have long hair.
And so I've been trying to--
Sorry. You know what? I just
remembered something. I'll come
again later.
Hey, wait. Ino!
Thank you for today!
(Children Playing)
Hey, don't you guys think...
...that Sakura's been more
cheerful lately?
Oh, really, has she?
Huh? But Ino... aren't you good
friends with Sakura?
No, not really...
Oh? Huh...
(Sakura) Sasuke... I um...
I Really like..
What is it?
And just who are you?
(Crying and Stumbling)
Ahhhh!!!
What's up with that girl? So
weird...
Well, I guess... she doesn't
know she's not supposed to run
in the hall...
(Fighting Pratice)
Here I go...
Uhh!
Uhhhh... Right! Cha!
Ahhhh!!!
Wow! That girl... She's
amazing!
♪♪♪
(Pratice Fighting)
Uhhh... (Gulp)
I see... Yeah, you're right!
Because when I look up at the
sky...
the pain inside of me
feels a little better...
Lord Gaara...
Um, hey. I've got some snacks.
You guys want some?
Woah!!!
[chuckle]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Gaara and Shikamaru"