You're part of
the ANBU now.
And this is one mission
that you can't avoid.
What is this mission?
Six years ago, after the
Nine Tails incident the
village higher-ups
suspected that the Uchiha
Clan was behind
the entire thing.
Since then, the Uchiha
district has been under
twenty-four-hour
surveillance.
[roaring]
Lord Third! It's
the Nine Tails!
The Nine Tails is
inside the village!
Yes, I know that.
I'll go restrain him.
You and the others
go protect all the
people of the village.
Yes, sir!
Huh?
You should have ordered the
Uchiha Police Force to guard
the civilians and kept them
back with the rear guard.
Why? We can use the Visual
Prowess of the Uchiha to
suppress the Nine Tails!
The Uchiha can also
manipulate Nine Tails!
Which means if they were to
betray the Leaf and take
control of the Nine
Tails for themselves.
It would be like
the second coming
of Madara Uchiha!
[angry roar]
I'm going to leave it to you
to protect the civilians.
You may command the
ANBU and security units.
And make sure that
you guard the youth
of the village, as well.
I understand.
[angry roar]
This way! Hurry!
Just stay calm!
You'll be safe here!
Captain, shouldn't we go
and provide assistance?
The Police Force will stay
and guard the civilians.
But Captain, sir!
That is the order the
village has given us.
Over there!
[baby crying]
There, there. I
know that was scary.
Now's our chance.
Let's get to safety.
There are too many
unanswered questions
surrounding this
Nine Tails incident.
I thought that Kushina's
seal had come undone...
However, that wouldn't
explain why Biwako and
the ANBU had been killed.
Which means that someone
is behind all this.
Perhaps someone
from the Uchiha...
Why them?
If Nine Tails broke free,
it would've just run wild.
With no one controlling it,
it wouldn't have attacked
and caused this incident.
You think that
the Sharingan...
The Uchiha can control
the Nine Tails with
their Visual Prowess.
But for what purpose?!
To regain their position
of power in the Leaf.
Ah, I see...
This is nothing more
than conjecture!
To be sure we must
increase our surveillance
on the Uchiha.
We need to keep the Uchiha
District under watch
twenty-four hours a day!
That's only going to
provoke them unnecessarily!
It's simple enough for the
ANBU to do it secretly.
Well, it is better to
be safe than sorry...
Wait!
We don't know if the
Uchiha are responsible!
That's why this must
be done! If nothing
comes of it,
it would only
benefit the Uchiha!
Hmm...
[moans and groans]
Kushina...
Shift change.
Nothing to report, sir.
Is this?
Just one of many
surveillance centers.
Lord Danzo's ANBU are
watching them, too.
What are you gonna do? Are
you gonna tell your clan?
What will my job be here?
Just keep watch
through that.
Okay, Captain.
We're gonna go.
Make sure that you
stay alert, Itachi.
This is just another
part of our job as ANBU.
It's not assassination,
but it's still dirty work.
A mission is a mission.
You'll be spying on
your friends and family.
In a way, it's
even worse...
I can take this
shift, if you want.
That's not necessary.
Besides...
Besides what?
The Uchiha Clan is
already aware that
we're under suspicion.
I suppose you would be...
How dare you?!
Come on! Get up
on your feet!
Hey! What the hell was that
for?! You're the one who-
Why you-!
This whole thing
is all your fault!
Please, you two,
stop fighting!
What's going on here?!
[arguing]
Who even cares about the
Police Force, anyway?!
Yeah, just hide like you
did with the Nine Tails!
What did you say to us?!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
We're taking you both in!
Quiet! Just walk!
It was just a
drunken argument...
They should've just
broken it up...
The number of complaints
about harsh treatment
by the Police Force
continues to rise.
People have started to
distrust them more and more.
It seems the Uchiha
are growing impudent.
No, it's backlash.
They haven't forgotten
about the Nine Tails
incident six years ago.
But the Uchiha didn't
suffer any losses during
that horrible attack!
Yes, and that was the cause
of even further suspicion.
Back then, during that
turbulent time, the Uchiha
saw our decision to
keep them at a distance
from the Nine Tails as a
sign of our distrust of
their entire clan.
Our tactic of isolating the
Uchiha is a core Leaf policy
begun by Lord Second.
Why do they
raise a fuss now?
Lord Second's intention
wasn't isolation!
He was concerned
for each clan.
Have you forgotten about our
friend Kagami Uchiha, Danzo?
No, of course not.
He saved me many times
with his Visual Jutsu.
The Uchiha Clan's a friend
of the Hidden Leaf. And we
must ensure that
they stay that way.
If that is still
within our power...
[groans]
[screaming]
What's wrong?!
A genjutsu?!
But when did-?!
Byakugan!
We're retreating!
But, Captain!
We're in grave danger.
It's Shisui the Teleporter!
And we're no
match for him. Go!
That ought to keep
the Hidden Mist Village
quiet for a while.
Team Shisui has returned,
sir. Mission complete.
Thank you. It was a long
mission, and you did well!
You and your team
should get some rest.
First, I have a
request, Lord Third.
Hm?
I've been very troubled
by all the suspicion cast
upon the Uchiha Clan.
Hm. I feel the same...
But I'm hopeful that the
clan and the village will
find a way to be able
to trust each other
again soon.
I'd like to ask you to
assign this mission to me.
And do you want to
be released from
your regular duties?
Yes. And I'd like to be
given a certain amount
of autonomy as well.
All right...
We shall say that I ordered
you to go on a top-secret
investigative mission,
and if anyone should
raise any objections.
Give them my name, and I
will take full responsibility.
Thank you, Lord Third.
You know, Shisui, you remind
me a great deal of my dear
old friend, Kagami Uchiha.
I'm not near his equal.
Big Brother!
Are you done
with your mission?
If you are, you can
come and help me train!
Sorry, Sasuke. I've
been summoned...
[angry snarl]
We played here
a lot, remember?
I didn't know
you were back!
That's right. Now
that we finally chased
the Hidden Mist away.
What is it?
I want to get your
honest opinion.
How serious do you
think Fugaku is?
What do you mean?
The coup d'état...
The Uchiha are
growing dissatisfied
with the Village.
If the village doesn't
change, the Uchiha
won't stand for it.
If the village changes,
so will the Uchiha.
But if the Uchiha
don't change, neither
will the village.
As long as the two sides
distrust each other, things
will only get worse.
I want to clear up
this uncertainty.
Can you?
Honestly, I don't know, but
I have to try. If the Uchiha
attempt a coup
d'état, it will end
badly for both sides.
I am against a
coup d'état as well.
But trying to stop it,
will take something big.
I'm well aware, but I don't
want you to do anything.
Why's that?
Some members of the Police
Force are suspicious of you.
I've actually been
ordered to spy on you.
What?! Do you know
what day tomorrow is?!
I don't really think
you really understand
your position!
I'm setting out on
a mission tomorrow.
What are you
talking about?
I can't tell you that...
The mission is covert.
Itachi you also serve as the
Uchiha Clan's pipeline to
the Village nerve center.
You know that, don't you?
Yes...
Well make sure you don't
forget it! You will be at
that meeting tomorrow.
The Uchiha have plans to
assemble again tonight.
Yes, I know
about it as well.
However, we cannot
interfere with the
rituals of their Clan.
Rituals indeed!
This so-called ritual is
just a thinly-veiled effort
to fan the flames of
distrust against us and
thereby unite the clan!
They preparing
for a coup d'état.
There is one who can nip
it in the bud. Shisui!
Shisui Uchiha?!
Shisui will attend the
assembly. If Fugaku Uchiha
incites a rebellion,
Shisui's orders are to-
Use my Koto Amatsukami.
You'll use your
Visual Jutsu?
Fugaku will have absolutely
no clue Shisui is using a
genjutsu to control
his actions.
I will make Fugaku
think about co-existence
with the village.
I doubt that controlling
only Fugaku will bring an
end to the Uchiha's
dissatisfaction.
No. If the Uchiha will
change, then we of the Leaf
must change, as well.
We must improve our
treatment of the Uchiha.
That's what I'm hoping for.
I will assign one ANBU
behind the scenes.
I'm counting on you.
Yes, sir!
Itachi still isn't here.
He's late.
What is it, Lord Danzo?
It's almost time for
the assembly to begin.
What if your Visual Jutsu
gets Fugaku and the clan to
cooperate, but then
the Leaf Village
refuses to change?
Lord Hokage has given
me his word that he
will make it change.
Even if he's satisfied that
the Uchiha have reformed,
the distrust among
the Leaf won't go away.
I realize that. But in time...
Besides, people like me,
people who are always
suspicious, will
never truly change.
What will you do then?
But Lord Danzo?
When the time comes,
will you use your Koto
Amatsukami on
me, as well?
I...
Your Sharingan shall
be in my safekeeping!
Forgive me.
It's only genjutsu.
You'll snap out of it soon.
[groaning]
Sharingan?!
I'll take yours to
replace this eye.
Now give me the
other one, too.
Fire Style!
Fireball Jutsu!
Water Style!
Raging Waves!
Teleportation Jutsu!
Go!
Shisui?
Come with me.
It seems we can't prevent
the Uchiha coup-d'état.
And if civil war erupts in
the Leaf, the other villages
will invade for sure.
True war will break out.
When I tried to stop
all this with the Koto
Amatsukami, Danzo
stole my right eye.
That man doesn't
trust me at all.
He intends to protect the
village his way, no matter
what it takes or
how it looks.
I suspect he'll come after
my left eye, so I'll give it
to you before
he has a chance.
Shisui...
You're the only one I can
count on, my best friend.
Protect the village. And the
Uchiha name. Both of them.
All right, I accept it.
What will you do now?
If I die, many
things will change.
I've left a note...
Shisui, wait!
Don't try to
stop me, Itachi.
If you're truly my friend...
Shisui!
Shisui...
Hey! What am I even
being accused of?!
Shut up. I'll
do the talking!
Don't be so
rough with him.
Captain!
All you need to know is
that you're a suspect.
You're coming
to HQ with us.
Oh... Uh...
Remember to follow all
investigative procedures.
Sir!
C'mon, move it!
Shisui Uchiha was a core
member of the Uchiha Clan.
His loss demoralized them
and lessened their fighting
power all at once.
So it seems the
coup d'état has
been averted, then.
I wish that there had been
some other way than for
Shisui to give his
life to stop it.
I should not have
pushed him like I did.
Among the Uchiha there
are still a few who believe
that you killed Shisui.
But the ones who believe
that, did not know that
Shisui and I were
both working towards
the same goal.
He never met me at
our rendezvous point.
He kept secrets, so
he was suspected.
I'll make a statement
from the ANBU that
it was a suicide.
Agreed, Hiruzen?
Hm...
[gasp]
[groans]
Ah! The Lightning Blade!
Then you're the Copy
Ninja of the Leaf!
Kaka...
Shi...
You've become quite
well known, Captain.
Do this long enough
and you're bound
to become famous.
Clear the area. Leave
no trace that the
Hidden Leaf was here.
Yeah, yeah. I know.
All this dirty work is just
a part of the ANBU's M.O.
You said that a friend
gave you the Sharingan
that you possess.
Yes. Along with a vow.
And is this vow something
you plan to honor?
Yes. I intend to.
I know about the incident
with Shisui Uchiha.
Is everything okay?
Yes, I'm fine.
I see...
Anyway, there's not a
lot I can do, but let me
know if there's anything.
Of course...
You're the only one I can
count on, my best friend.
Protect the village and the
Uchiha name. Both of them.
Shisui. Things have
gotten much worse.
I don't think that I can
protect everyone...
It seems someone's been
getting through the barrier
and infiltrating
the village.
The only thing we can really
do is ask the Police Force
to step up their patrols.
What's bothering you?
I went to the Uchiha
District for the first time
in a while. It felt like
they didn't want any
outsiders there.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: " The Night
of the Tragedy."
I see...