Don't forget about me! We're
both women, so don't you mock
me!
Naruto...Sasuke...Sakura...
Yup, what a nice picture you
guys make right now.
(Kakashi) I really love you
guys!
Do it!
Yeah! Cha!
All right!
[gasps]
Six Paths Planetary Devastation!
To think that I, the originator
of all chakra...
would be defeated by pieces of
my own chakra, again!
(Kaguya) Why?!
Hmm.
They've done it!
Now all that's left is to bring
you all back.
[grunts]
[grunting/yelling]
[angry roar]
[grunts]
Is the ground being sucked up
towards her?
We finally made it out!
Kurama!
That Jinchuriki of yours is
pretty good! [chuckles]
[angry roaring]
(Sasuke) Over here!
We're here, Sasuke!
Where's Naruto?
Huh?
He went off by himself. He said
there was something he had to
take care of.
More importantly, we need to get
ourselves away from here!
It can't be helped now. I'll
just start over and work on
Mother's next resurrection!
[grunts]
You know, that reminds me. You
hate being away from your mom,
right?
[grunts] Damn you!
I haven't forgotten about you.
How you were always hiding in
the shadows and skulking about
all this time!
You! You're just a piece of the
shinobi history I created, and
nothing more!
A useless brat like you could
never...
History?
(Naruto) Shinobi history is made
up of all sorts of ninja's
lives, and deaths too!
Many of them taught me what it
means to be a shinobi!
The pain and sadness of death,
the tragedy of war, and not only
that!
They taught me the joy of being
accepted and being loved!
The way they lived, and the way
they died...
They made me who I am today!
They taught me, and they trusted
in me!
You're a brat who can't even
fly from the nest!
[grunts]
It's time for you to get over
yourself!
[screaming]
[grunts]
It's still growing even bigger.
It's starting to look like our
moon.
Huh?
You guys!
So it's done?
Sealing complete! And now it's
happily ever after, the end!
You're right, great news!
[stretches] The first thing that
I wanna do is take a hot bath to
wash off this sweat and grime.
Ah! Wait a sec, what about us?!
How're we supposed to get
out of this Time-Space?
Ah! You're right! Ah!
He got it done.
But I gotta say, he's still a
tad dumb, isn't he?
[grunts]
Summoning Jutsu!
Hmm? Huh.
Welcome back home, Naruto.
Dad, you? [gasps]
Naruto, who is that guy?
Six Paths Super Gramps!
Which means...
Yes, that's right.
You're back in your world.
Via a Summoning done by all the
prior Five Kage together.
(Hagoromo) I called on all of
the historical Five Kage from
the afterworld to help.
Naruto, Sasuke, and the rest of
you, too.
You all did excellent work in
saving the world.
Six Paths Super Gramps?
Wait, are you by any chance the
legendary?
I am Hagoromo Otsutsuki.
Sometimes also known as the Sage
of the Six Paths.
It's no wonder, since you're
levitating.
Honestly at this point, I don't
think anything could shock me
anymore.
It seems to me, like everything
went really well.
True, but it also seems like the
shinobi world went to hell while
we were dead.
It's a shame.
I've never seen so many Tailed
Beasts together in one place
before!
Sage of the Six Paths?
It feels like we've wandered
into some kind of fairy tale,
here!
(Kakashi) So it was you after
all. Summoning the past Five
Kage here.
And bringing us and the Tailed
Beasts back from that other
Time-Space.
You're probably the only person
who could perform such god-like
actions.
You're Kakashi Hatake, isn't
that right?
[gasps] Yes, sir.
Good job guiding everyone, and
making sure my mother was sealed
away.
That truly was the work of the
gods.
Oh, no. I can't take credit, I
hardly played any part at all.
It was these three. And many
other comrades, as well.
And also, there was a former
friend, who lent me a lot of
strength when I needed it.
That's why I said you did a good
job in guiding everyone.
Despite losing your way, you
remained Naruto's teacher, and
you were Obito's friend as well.
Or else you likely wouldn't have
succeeded in stopping my mother.
Hey! Kurama!
Were you lonely being separated
from me like that? I sure did
miss you!
Quit yelling so loudly! I wasn't
lonely. You have half of me
inside you, remember?
[laughing]
[chuckles]
Just look at Kurama, all
embarrassed and flustered!
Although this too, is exactly
what I had once envisioned.
(Hagoromo) That there would one
day be a shinobi...
who could move even the Tailed
Beasts to cooperate.
Naruto caused Obito's change of
heart.
He restored Obito back to
himself.
Yes, I see.
Then I shall be sure to ask
Obito to tell me that tale in
the afterworld.
Hmm.
Wait, is he still?
I ought to go soon.
Yeah.
Kakashi, I really made a mess of
the Shinobi world.
So much so that I don't even
know what to say to you in
parting.
Well, at least we get to say
goodbye as friends, not enemies.
And I saw the old you again. The
one who was always late 'cause
of helping others.
That's plenty enough, at least
for me.
Hmm.
Thanks so much, Kakashi.
Well, all right, then. Guess
I'll be going now.
I've been keeping Rin waiting.
Did you prepare a good excuse to
give her for being so late?
Don't worry I already told her,
I'd be helping you.
Oh, I see.
[heavy breathing]
Likewise...
Thank you, Obito.
[sighs]
[grunts] Kakashi Sensei!
[sighs] Oh, Sakura. Thanks for
that.
Kakashi Sensei! Your eyes!
Yeah...
Kakashi of the Sharingan is no
more now.
Madara was a Jinchuriki, even if
temporarily. Now, emptied of the
Tailed Beasts, he'll die.
His own fault for trying
to use such things.
Now, Sasuke, and Naruto, this is
the end of your predecessors.
Watch closely.
Is that you, Hashirama?
Yes.
I guess that neither you nor I
were able to achieve what we
wanted.
It's never that easy. Our job is
merely to do all that we can do
while we're alive.
And then bequeath the rest of it
for future generations to
accomplish.
You're so naive.
Just as you usually are.
[chuckles]
And you have always been the
optimist.
Although perhaps that is the
proper way to be.
The dream that I had has been
squashed.
But your dream is still relevant
now, and it continues to live
on.
We were both too hasty. We
didn't need to reach our dreams
ourselves.
It was far more important to
cultivate those who would come
after us...
to whom we could entrust our
dreams.
Which means I would have failed,
anyway.
After all, I have always hated
having somebody standing behind
me.
When we were just kids,
you once said to me...
"We are shinobi after all, we
never know when we might die."
And you also told me that for
neither side to die, both of
them would have to reveal,,,
what's inside of themselves,
hiding nothing at all...
and to drink together, as if
they were brothers.
But the both of us are about to
die.
So right now, we have a chance
to drink together as old war
buddies.
As war buddies...huh.
Well then...I suppose
that...would be...okay...by...
Now is the moment.
I'll release the jutsu, freeing
the Five Kage and the Reanimated
shinobi.
[gasping]
Well, go on.
[sighs]
Dad, I...
Oh, that's right. There's
something that I've been meaning
to tell you.
Huh?
Happy birthday, Naruto.
You've really become a splendid
young man, you know that?
Yeah, thank you.
We're an existence outside of
the rules. So we can't just
remain in this world forever.
This is good-bye.
I promise you that I'll tell
Kushina everything.
Tell her not to worry! I'm
eating properly! Lots of
different stuff! I'm not picky!
Like I'll have tonkotsu ramen,
miso ramen, and sometimes I'll
even have shoyu ramen too!
Oh, but I don't only eat ramen
though, I swear!
(Naruto) Uh, I bathe almost
every day even going to the Leaf
Hot Springs once in a while.
Although everyone tells me that
my baths are only lightening
quick dips! [chuckles]
Let's see, what else, what
else...
I've managed to make a whole lot
of friends! And they're all
really good guys! And...
Well uh, I was pretty awful at
school, to tell you the truth.
But I never got depressed about
it!
(Naruto) I had more confidence
than anyone else!
And of course I always obeyed
Lord Third and Kakashi Sensei,
too!
I mean, I totally respect them
both.
They're right here, so you
can just ask them yourself!
Oh! And those Three Prohibitions
of the Shinobi?
I learned a whole lot about them
when I was with Pervy Sage!
He was hopeless when it came to
them, though!
But he was an awesome
Sannin, and I respect him
the most! I do!
I just turned seventeen today,
so I don't know much about
alcohol or girls yet...
I know that Mom said that I
should find someone just like
her, but...
[chuckles] I don't know.
(Naruto) That's kind of, um..
Anyway! Not everything that Mom
told me about went well.
But I always tried to do the
very best that I could, you
know!
(Naruto) I've got dreams, too!
I'm gonna be an even greater
Hokage than you, Dad.
I swear I will!
[crying]
Tell Mom, when you see her over
there...
that she doesn't have to worry
about me even a bit! [crying]
(Naruto) Tell her I'm doing my
best!
Don't you worry. I'll make sure
that I tell her about
everything.
[sobbing]
(Hagoromo)  Having battled my
mother Kaguya...
is there any change to the
answers you gave me?
(Naruto) My answer is the same.
(Hagoromo) Very well then. Now,
Sasuke, the rest is up to you.
(Sasuke) Yeah, all right. But
before that...
the current Five Kage inside the
Infinite Tsukuyomi will be...
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Final Valley."
(Kakashi) What did you say,
Sasuke?