(Leaf Villager A)
Ok, pull it out.
(Leaf Villager B)
Be careful! It's
gonna fall!
(Leaf VIllager C)
Alright! Back over
here! On the other
side!
(Leaf Villager D)
It's too heavy!
(Rock Lee)
Sakura...
How is Lady
Hokage doing?
Oh, I see...
This could help!
Guy Sensei made
this special medicine
for the Lady Hokage!
So please... would
you give it to her?
Thanks Lee...
Lady Hokage healed
me, when no one
thought it would
be possible...
I wanna do whatever
I can to help her
get better.
I'm going to
be straight
with you...
[gasp]
Give up on being
a shinobi.
No!
(Lady Tsunade)
His injuries have left
numerous bone fragments
embedded in his spinal column.
(Lady Tsunade)
It's a miracle he
can still move at
all...
(Tsunade)
He's physically incapable
of carrying out the
duties of a shinobi.
Guy Sensei! Please
tell me what to do!
How come I am the
only one being
punished like this!?
Tell me... What
am I supposed
to do now!?
[struggling grunts]
Ino!
Hey! Did you come
down to check up
on Lee too?
I thought
you'd be here.
I actually came
here to look for
the two of you.
You weren't at
Sasuke's when I
checked, so I figured
that you'd be here.
And I waited.
Wait just a second...
Ino, you didn't go
visit Sasuke alone,
did you!?
Do you think I was
visiting him as a flimsy
excuse to make a move on
him, like you always do!?
Speak for
yourself,
Ino Pig!
I told you! I
was just looking
for you two,
billboard brow!
Oh yeah!? What
do you want us
for then!?
Because all three
of us are going on
a mission together!
[gulp]
A mission?
Us three?
But why?
Your team's down
one because Sasuke's
in such bad shape.
And Lady Hokage
decided to call
up Shikamaru and
Choji from my team..
They're helping
out with all the
Village repairs
right now.
It's only a D-rank
mission so, they're
just grabbing
whoever's available!
We finally get a
mission and you
spoil it for me
by saying that.
Thanks for nothin'.
(Naruto)
Yo! Bushy brow!
Oh! Sakura!
What about "Oh
Naturo?" I'm
here too ya know.
How's it coming,
Lee? You feeling
better?
Oh... Yes...
I am fine...
Hm?
Oh no! Really!
I feel great!
Especially since Guy
Sensei started making me
this medicine! He calls
it his Special Youth Drink!
[grunt]
[gasp]
[nervous laughter]
Thank you! I guess
my hand just slipped.
Huh?!
Yuck! Gross!
This is the worst
energy drink I've
ever had!
[crying]
What are you
doing, you
idiot!?
If you're gonna
scold me, could
you do it before
you hit me?
[gasps]
But... that was...
that was my last
special youth drink!
I didn't realize
it was so special!
Oops! Sorry
about that!
Up until now,
I drank five liters
every day and never
missed a single dose!
That much?!
Really? This
awful tasting
stuff?
If i kept on
drinking it, then
without any doubt I
knew i would recover!
Guy Sensei swore...
Look, if you have the
guts to keep drinking
this disgusting stuff,
you'll have no
problem getting
well!
That's your ninja
way, right? Never
give up! No matter
what!
Hm, yes. I
suppose so.
I'll go get more
from Guy Sensei
right now!
Wait! Naruto!
We have a mission,
remember!?
Just wait for me at
the South main gate!
I'll be there! Don't
worry!
(Naruto)
Trust me! I'll
be right back!
Man!
He's never
gonna change.
(Rock Lee)
A forbidden jutsu
one can die using...
(Rock Lee)
I am prepared for
the worst! Teach me
the Forbidden Jutsu!
(Rock Lee)
Whatever it takes
for my dream!
Um, Guy Sensei?
Oh! Naruto.
Can I help you?
I'm not here for
me. Uh, I actually
came for that medicine
you make for Lee.
I see. You've
already done your
research then.
Nicely done!
Huhh??
The Special Youth
Drink for Lee has one
main ingredient, and that
is the Jofuku Flower.
What's that?
A mystical plant that only
grows in one place, the
foot of Mount Jofuku on the
boarder of the Land of Fire.
It's said to glow in
seven colors and cures
all sorts of illnesses!
Mount Jofuku, huh?
But it's a very rare
flower, and as a result
it's difficult to
obtain... so...
So if you had those
flowers, you could
make more medicine?
Huh?
All right, I'll
tell you what!
I'm gonna go and
get some of them
for you right now!
But- wait!
Naruto! You
didn't even let
me finish my
sentence!!
(Thinking)
Just you wait, Bushy
Brow! I'll get you more of
that medicine right away!
Of course!
That's weird. I
Know it was around
here somewhere...
Found it!
(Ino)
Naruto's late.
I can't believe
that idiot! What's
he doing!?
(Sakura)
I know he's worried
about Lee, but we have
a mission to complete!
Hm?
Sakuraaaaa!
Huh?!
Sorry to keep
you waiting!
I had to change!
Naruto! What's
with the get-up?!
It does kinda
look familiar...
Heh! I gotta get
some medicinal herbs
for Bushy Brow!
And this outfit that
I'm wearing will help
me get in sync with him!
Not too shabby,
huh!?
Sure. Whatever
you say.
Can't you tell how
much we like it
from our reaction?
What is the deal,
Naruto!? Have you
fogottn that we were
given a mission!?
Sorrrry! I already
told you! I have to go
to Mount Jofuku to get
some medicinal herbs!
Mount Jofuku?
Yeah. Weren't
you listening?
Great. Our mission
is actually going
to take us right
to Mount Jofuku.
Huh??
[struggling breaths]
(Guy Sensei)
You mustn't do
that, Lee!
Huh?
You were told
to take it easy
until after the
surgery...
Sorry...
I thought that perhaps
it would be a good idea
to build up my strength
a little beforehand...
Listen, I understand how
incredibly frustrating
this situation must be
for you, Lee...
(Guy Sensei)
However, in all or nothing
situations where you can't
forge ahead or fall back...
(Guy Sensei)
Sometimes merely staying
still can bring about
the best results.
(Guy Sensei)
Having faith in yourself,
Waiting quietly until the
right time comes...
That, too, is a
form of courage,
Lee. Understand?
Yes...
(Sakura)
Naruto, Lady Hokage's
been treating Lee's
injuries, hasn't she?
(Naruto)
Yeah! Of course!
(Sakura)
Even so, doesn't it
seem like Lee's been really
out of sorts lately?
(Sakura)
...Like he has
no energy?
(Naruto)
What do you expect?
That was a serious
injury!
It isn't just that!
His optimism has
started to fade...
He's actually
skipped a few
rehab sessions,
too.
That's not the
Lee I know!
Even today he
would have said:
Sakura! To protect
you, I will recover
faster! And hour, a
minute... No!
I will not stay
hurt a second more
than I must!
If he were his
normal self then
he'd mean every
word he said, too!
Uhhh, he'd
do it just
for you?
Yeah, but still,
Sakura has a point.
Hm?
Remember his injuries
were so serious even the
medical team couldn't
heal him.
Maybe he won't ever
fully recover...
If Lee thinks that,
it's no surprise
he's feeling down.
Granny Tsunade is
gonna fix him up!
I know she will!
I'm just saying sometimes
it's not right to give
someone hope when there
really isn't any!
But...
You may want to
cheer him up--
but that can put
pressure on him to put
on a happy face, and that
can make things worse!
Please, Naruto, don't
say stuff like "it'll be
fine," because we don't
know that it will be!
[gasp]
Bushy Brow is
tougher than you
give him credit for.
When he fought
Gaara in the Chunin
Exam, I knew he was
an amazing guy.
He put his life
on the line...
(Naruto)
Until the very end of
the fight when he lost
consciousness...
(Naruto)
He never stopped
attacking!
(Naruto)
And that's when I realized
that Lee is a guy who will
never, ever give up!
I know there's no waythat
I could ever understand
the suffering he's going
through right now...
...but he's doing
everything he can to
overcome it, and I
believe in him.
And that's why I
tell Bushy Brown to
hang in ther and
not give up hope!
[gasps]
Naruto...
(Naruto)
Hey! Is anybody ever
gonna tell me what
our mission is?!
(Sakura)
Took you long
enough to ask!
(Ino)
We're taking a secret
message to a village
near Mount Jofuku.
(Naruto)
This has gotta be the
easiest mission ever!
(Naruto)
Let's get it done
fast so I can go pick
some Jofuku Flowers!
(Sakura)
Guys, let's take a
break. We should grab
something to eat.
(Naruto)
Are you even
listening, Sakura?
(Naruto)
Taking a break is
the opposite of
getting it done!
May I ask, are
you three headed
into the Jofuku
Forest?
Uhh, that's right.
Yeah! We're gonna
go look for some
medicinal herbs
from there!
If you are truly
wise, you'd turn
back now!
[gulp]
And why is
that!?
Around these parts,
that forest is known
as "The Lost Woods,"
and the villagers know
better than to ever go
near it, for fear they
won't come back again.
"The Lost Woods?"
It was a site of
many ancient battles!
And the ghosts of the
ninja who were killed
there are said to still
wander the forest...
It's a chilling tale!
[frightened squeals]
There are ghosts
in the woods!?
[frightened squeaks]
Hey! My sandal
strap broke!
Yeah! And so
did my mirror!
[frightened gasps]
MEOW!
It's an omen!!
(Naruto)
There's no such
thing as ghosts!
Hm?
Ahhhhh!
If you ask me,
those are just a
bunch of made up
rumors!
Hey there! May
I have some more
tea, please?
(Naruto)
That old lady
sure was creepy,
wasn't she?
(Sakura)
I'll say! She was
scarier than a
real ghost!
(Ino)
It was mean of
her to frighten
us like that!
(Naruto)
Huh? What's that?
Looks pretty
sketchy to me!
Is that the
forest the old
lady was talking
about?
You think the Jofuku
Flower's in there?
Yeah!
Hey! Our mission
comes first, Naruto!
Just hold on!
I'll be right
back!
That kid!
He never
listens!!
What should
we do?
Ugh, I guess
we have to go
after him!
[gasps]
It's....
an omen!!!
(Naruto)
A flower that glows
in seven colors, just
like Guy Sensei said!
Naruto!
Look, Sakura.
I found the
flower!
(Sakura)
Those are
Jofuku Flowers?
(Ino)
I've never heard of
a flower that glows
in seven colors!
Shouldn't a
florist like you
know things like
that?
Technically, it's
a medicinal herb,
Not a flower!
Let's just get
them to Guy Sensei
so he can make
Bushy Brow's medicine!
What's that?
Is it...
a ghost??
What's going on?
It kinds looks
like the Jutsu
that controls sand.
(Sakura)
The one Gaara of
the Sand uses!
It's Gaara!
Why's he here!?
We'd better
retreat!
Yeah, you're right!
Ahhhhh!
Naruto!!
Why would he
want to attack us!?
Looks like he's
after Naruto!
(Sakura)
Ino! He's wide open
right now. Can you
confirm his identity?
(Ino)
You got it!
Mind transfer
Jutsu!
No way!
What? What
is it!?
It has no human
consciousness at all!
You're dealing with
an entirely different
me today!
[dodging grunts]
Can't... dodge...
these... forever!
Hiiiiya!!!!
All right, you
wanna keep copying
Gaara? Well then-
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
(Thinking)
I can't fight him with
taijutsu like Bushy
Brows... But that's ok!
(Thinking)
I can still take
him down with my own
style of fighting!
(Thinking)
Ugh! He even
has Sand Armor!
(Thinking)
See if you can
block THIS!
Na...
Ru...
To...
Uzumaki Barrage!
Now to finish you!
Rasengan!!!
[attack yell]
Naruto!
You all right!?
[panting]
I knew I could
defeat that creature!
Now Bushy Brow
can finally get the
medicine he needs!
(Furofuki)
Hey!
Huh!?
What do you think
you are doing to
those precious Jofuku
Flowers!?
You're going to
make them all
wilt if you're
not careful!
Who's that?
(Sakura)
Our apologies!
Here's the secret
message!
(Furofuki)
Hm.
So, old lady, you
live in the middle
of this forest all
by yourself, huh?
I do have a name,
you know! I'm
called Furofuki.
I'm a Medical Ninja
from the Hidden Leaf,
and I'm here to study
the Jofuku Flowers.
It's what I love
to do, and that
is that!
Is that thing we
encountered a guardian
deity of the Jofuku
Flower or something?
The flower protects
itself when it's
picked!
It searches the mind of
whoever picked it to find
their archenemy, transforms
into that foe, and attacks.
I guess it's just
our bad luck that
we were thinking
of Gaara!
Too bad we didn't
think of Choji!
Then we coulda won
no problem!
You know, if you hadn't
trespassed into the Jofuku
Forest in the first place,
this never would've happened.
We're really sorry!
We sure are!
Whoa! This thing's
so heavy!
And all of this
is just Jofuku
Flowers!?
It is. And your
mission now is to bring
all of these back to
the Leaf Village.
Ino...
Hey don't blame
me! Blame the guy
who sent us on
this mission!
Rejoice, Lee! Because
I've managed to bring
you the greatest gift
of all today!
(Guy Sensei)
MY special handmade
herbal food pills
of love!
These little guys
were made with my
sweat, tears, and
love!
And of course, they're
filled with the
warm friendship of
your comrades, too!
My comrades'
friendship?
That's right! Cause none
other than Naruto and his
team obtained the medicinal
herb needed to make these!
Sakura too!?
(Guy Sensei)
Yes! Sakura
and Ino, too!
I see. Then that must
mean that these have also
been filled with love
from Sakura...
(Thinking)
Sakura! In order to
repay your kindness, I
will recover faster!
(Thinking)
An hour? A minute? No.
I will not stay hurt a
second more than I must!
If you eat a
hundred of these,
you won't need to
fear surgery!
I will do it!
Wait!! Just
hold on!
Tell me how many
I must eat each
day, and I will!
I'm glad to see that
you're not taking any
chances this time!
Bravo Lee!
But it's not one
hundred total...
It's one hundred
each day!!!!
[munching]
Don't you worry,
Lee! I won't let
you suffer alone!
While you're eating
all of those I'll do
one thousand speed
push ups!
(Naruto)
Why do I have to
train to break free
of Genjutsu now?
(Jiraya)
Don't you remember
the reason for this
training?
(Naruto)
Huh!? It's so I
can bring back
Sasuke, of course!
(Jiraya)
Sasuke possesses the
Sharingan. Naturally he'll
learn to master genjutsu.
(Jiraya)
If you can't defend yourself
against it, how do you expect
to bring him back!?
(Naruto)
Next Time on Naruto
Shippuden: Gutsy Master
and Student, the Training.
(Jiraya)
Let's get some real
practice at breaking
genjutsu!