Kiba, when we get to the
Land of Iron, please
find Naruto quickly.
Yeah, I got it!
[sigh]
What is wrong, Kiba?
Ino wouldn't stop crying
when she heard the bad news.
Sakura looks really
determined but I don't know
how she's gonna tell Naruto.
And something tells
me it's going to be
really uncomfortable.
Well, I am sure that Sakura
is giving the matter a
good deal of thought.
And of course,
Because four-man squads are
the standard, all search
missions usually include me.
But Sai also wants us
to keep this entire
thing top secret.
And I'm supposed
to use my nose,
to see if Danzo's ANBU from
the Foundation are following us.
I mean, talk about
working us to the bone!
Right, Akamaru?
[whine]
Look at that!
Just look at
what you've done!
That's why I can't
stand shinobi!
Sorry. Please, forgive us.
I will repair it myself,
I promise.
Sasuke has shouldered
the entire burden of
the Uchiha's hatred,
and intends to strike
deep into the world
with that curse.
That hate is his most
powerful weapon, his friend,
and the source of his power.
That is Sasuke's
Ninja Way!
Sasuke chose this path
all on his own.
The only thing left to do
is to ask him myself.
It seems that Cee was right.
The Hokage has indeed fled.
Yep, and all
thanks to Sasuke.
[gasp]
Wha?
Anything Akatsuki is
bad news, and honestly
won't make any sense!
Sasuke?!
Return Sasuke
right now!
That will depend on your
response to what I'm
about to tell you.
Just calm down, Raikage.
Let's hear him out,
and take it from there.
Rrrgh.
Go heal Sasuke.
A-Aaah!
So that's what
Madara's ability is.
It's the
Transportation
Technique.
Where am I?
Now, are all of you
finally prepared to listen?
First tell us: why are you
trying to win over Sasuke?
Sharingan that actually acquire
the Susano'o are quite rare.
I like to stock up on good eyes.
By battling the Five Kage,
he'd hone his visual prowess
even further, which is
exactly why I sent him here.
I was hoping to weaken the
Five Kage and take at
least some of you hostage.
But I guess that
was too much to ask.
Take us hostage?
Whatever for?!
[Madara]
To ensure that Project
Tsuki no Me was
implemented smoothly.
I'm truly surprised that
the infamous Madara
Uchiha is still alive.
But I'm confused:
why do you of all
people need such
roundabout tactics?
With all your power, you
ought to be able to bring
any plan to fruition easily.
My injuries from my battle
with the First Hokage
Hashirama were too severe.
I currently have little power.
I am but a shell
of my former self.
Oh, I get it. Then this
plan of yours is to restore
your power, is that it?
Hum. I suppose you
could say that.
But there's so
much more to it.
What are you scheming?!
Exactly what is this
Project Tsuki no Me?!
It'll be a long story,
so I'll need to sit down.
That's enough! Just tell us:
what kind of plan is it?!
All shall become one with me,
in a complete possession form
that unites all.
What do you mean?!
Become one and
unite all of us?!
What does that even
mean?!
There's an ancient stone
tablet passed down
within the Uchiha clan.
It's in a room beneath
the Hidden Leaf.
Upon it are written
secrets engraved by the
Sage of Six Paths himself.
They cannot be read
without visual powers.
With the Sharingan,
Mangekyo Sharingan, and
Rinnegan, respectively,
more and more knowledge
is progressively revealed.
And your story's becoming
more and more unbelievable.
The Sage of Six Paths is a myth!
It is the truth.
He did indeed exist.
And he left that
stone tablet behind.
Don't change
the subject!
And what exactly does this
Sage of Six Paths have to
do with your plan, anyway?
Do any of you know why he
became a legendary figure,
one that is revered like
a god among shinobi?
This is where the link between
that man and my purposes lies.
Madara Uchiha, you possess
the Mangekyo Sharingan and
your fellow Akatsuki member
possessed the Rinnegan.
Do you know all the
tablet's secrets, then?
Let's hear them!
The Sage once saved the world,
from a certain monster.
What monster?
Gaara, you once held merely
one small piece of that monster
sealed away within you.
It was the aggregate of
all of the Tailed Beasts,
a creature that possessed
almost infinite chakra.
Ten-Tails!
"Declaration of War"
It was the aggregate of
all of the Tailed Beasts,
a creature that possessed
almost infinite chakra.
The Ten-Tails!
But I thought there were
only nine Tailed Beasts!
I just told you, it was
the aggregate of all nine
of the Tailed Beasts.
Shukaku, Gaara's Tailed
Beast known as...
The One-Tail!
The fiery Wraith Cat of the
Hidden Cloud's Yugito Ni'i...
The Two-Tails!
The former Mizukage's...
The Three-Tails!
Roshi of the Lava Style's...
The Four-Tails!
Han of the Hidden Stone's...
The Five-Tails!
The Rogue Ninja Utakata's...
The Six-Tails!
Fuu of the Hidden Waterfall's...
The Seven-Tails!
Killer Bee,
Raikage's younger
brother's...
The Eight-Tails!
And the Fox Spirit of
the Hidden Leaf...
The Nine-Tails!
The Ten-Tails' chakra
was simply divided up
to create the nine Tailed
Beasts that we know today.
By the Sage of Six Paths' hand.
I really don't like
where this is going.
So that's why the
Akatsuki were collecting
all the Tailed Beasts?
The Sage of Six Paths
developed a certain Ninjutsu
in order to protect the
world from the Ten-Tails.
That Ninjutsu is still
being secretly passed down.
It is the Sealing Jutsu
process for Jinchuriki.
Yes, the Sage was the
Ten-Tails' Jinchuriki.
He sealed Ten-Tails within
himself to suppress the monster.
The Sage, who saved humanity
from being terrorized by the
beast, was revered as a
savior, and as a god.
But the Sage feared that upon
his death, the seal would come
undone and Ten-Tails' immense
chakra would reemerge.
So in his final moments,
he summoned the last of
his strength,
to partition the
Ten-Tails' chakra into
nine pieces and scatter
them all across the world.
Then he sealed away the
body of the monster, now
devoid of chakra, and
hurled it up into the sky.
And it became the moon.
This tale is
ridiculous.
I mean, what human being could
do something like that?!
As Ten-Tails' Jinchuriki,
the Sage had already advanced
beyond the realm of humanity.
So you're trying to
reassemble those nine
separated chakras.
In other words all of the
nine Tailed Beasts, and
obtain that immense power.
I can understand that
part of your plan.
But what are you planning
on doing with all that power?
Revive the Ten-Tails, of course!
And become Ten-Tail's
Jinchuriki!
I would then use its
tremendous chakra to
strengthen my visual prowess,
and launch a certain jutsu.
But what certain jutsu?
Which one do you mean?
Just what are you plotting?!
A Super Genjutsu where I project
my eye off the moon's surface...
An Infinite Tsukuyomi.
All humans living on this
earth will be placed
under my genjutsu!
And as a result, by
controlling every single
one of them, I shall
unify the entire world.
I will create a world without
hatred or war. Everything
will become one with me,
everything will be united.
That is Project Tsuki no Me.
You're insane! I'm not just
handing the world over to you!
That kind of peace
is just an illusion.
Peace is only meaningful
when it's achieved honestly.
So what exists inside
such a genjutsu world?
There's no hope, no dreams!
It's just an escape!
You want to unite
the whole world, huh?
Interesting that
Danzo mentioned
something similar.
But it sounds to me
that instead of wanting
to unite the world,
You actually want to
make the world yours
and only yours!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha.
And yet, with all your talk,
what have you Five Kage
accomplished?
You of all people should
know the truth by now.
There is no hope!
To hope is equivalent to
giving up, and it's the
biggest deception of all.
Now, turn over the remaining
Eight- and Nine-Tails,
and cooperate with my plan.
Or this is war.
War, you say?
Eight-Tails?
What do you mean?!
You captured Bee!
Eight-Tails' capture failed,
and he escaped.
Now, there's a shinobi
who's a perfect Jinchuriki.
There's no one quite like
your younger brother.
Huhh?
Oh, so it's true.
I had a feeling he escaped.
That giant fool!
He used this chance to
run off and play hooky?!
Unforgiveable! He's gonna
get my Iron Claw for this!
I won't give up Naruto Uzumaki.
And neither will I!
What about you,
Raikage?
I'll never hand
over my brother!
I may not have any strength,
but I do have the powers of
the seven Tailed Beasts
I've collected.
You have no chance
of winning.
We won't abandon hope.
Very well.
I hereby declare war on you all.
the Fourth Great Ninja War
begins now.
What?! You're starting the
Fourth Great Ninja War?
Are you mad?!
The next time we meet,
will be in battle.
All right, then.
What should we
all do now?
Our nations must form an
alliance. It's the only
way to fight the power
of seven Tailed Beasts.
Lord Raikage,
you opposed
this idea.
It seems my little
brother is safe.
But we cannot allow
ourselves to be bullied by
the Akatsuki any longer!
Form the alliance and
we'll settle this!
For good!
What do we do about
the Hidden Leaf?
The Hokage ran off,
remember?
There's too much
suspicion around Danzo!
And after what's happened
at this summit, he's
completely lost our trust.
When the Hidden Leaf's
ninja find out about this,
his standing in the Leaf
will become shaky.
He must be deposed soon.
And I'll pass on the
news about the Allied
Shinobi Forces to a Leaf
ninja that I trust.
Who is that?
Kakashi Hatake of
the Sharingan Eye.
Do you mean the son
of the White Fang?
[Kakashi]
Right here and now, this young
shinobi, no matter how awkward,
is bowing his head with respect
and affection for the Cloud and
Leaf, village and nation.
So, Lord Raikage,
as one of the Five Kage,
Tell me, what do
you think of this?
That's acceptable.
He at least seems more
trustworthy than Danzo.
Heh. Indeed.
Mmm.
Lord Raikage, we must
take steps to find
Killer Bee right away!
If the Akatsuki are after
Eight- and Nine-Tails,
Then that means they're
probably still pursuing Bee.
You're right. Okay, then
send word back to the
village immediately.
Have them put
together a search
party and find Bee!
Yes, sir!
And, we ought to inform
Samui's team right away, too.
Omoi and Karui are
really distraught.
In order to stop Madara's
Project Tsuki no Me,
we absolutely must keep
the Eight- and Nine-Tails
out of his clutches.
I believe it's imperative
that our forces find them
before anyone else does,
and get them out of
sight and into hiding
as fast as we can.
Yes, that's absolutely right!
If Ten-Tails were revived,
we'd be done for!
Yeah, but I can't even imagine
the power Madara has amassed
with seven Tailed Beasts.
And if he possesses
jutsu that utilize them,
that would be his secret weapon!
Yes, I agree; otherwise,
he wouldn't have been
quite so bold.
I believe the Allied
Shinobi Forces,
must also plan to use
the strength of the Eight-
and Nine-Tails in battle,
don't you all agree with that?
No, absolutely not.
This is also a war to
protect both of them.
I think the reason why
Madara is waging war with
his seven Tailed Beasts,
is that in his weakened
state, it's too difficult
for him to capture
the Eight- and Nine-Tails
with just the remaining
Akatsuki members.
And even if it were possible,
the risks are too high.
Also, he may be hoping
to lure the two out
with this war.
For many reasons, using the
Tailed Beasts in battle is
not a wise strategy.
I agree; we must find
a different plan.
Yes, I also concur
with the Kazekage.
If we consider the worst-case
scenario, it's like offering
the Tailed Beasts up on a
silver platter!
Besides which, military
strategy is a foreign concept
to my little brother,
the Eight-Tails Jinchuriki!
I could never predict
what he'd do.
Yea-yah!
And he might bring his
own brand of chaos with
him to the battlefield.
[Gaara]
The same could be said,
For Naruto.
Yeah, that's for sure.
Heh, I'll say!
Very well, then Eight-
and Nine-Tails will be
under protective custody.
What say you,
Lord Tsuchikage?
Mmm.
We'll share Intel on Killer
Bee with all you Stone,
Mist, Sand and Leaf.
Use it to put together Tracking
Units and get them moving!
Instruct them all to
inform me the moment
they locate Eight-Tails.
My younger brother will
only listen to me!
[Raikage]
And Kazekage.
We'll trust you to
speak with Kakashi.
Fine.
[Raikage]
I saw Kakashi Hatake and
the Nine-Tails Jinchuriki
brat on our way here.
They might still be
in the Land of Iron.
So I'd look around
here first.
Understood.
Um? Excuse me?
May I say something?
What is it?
Uh. Right.
Well, you see,
it's just--
Spit it out, boy!
Oh. Aah.
In the Akatsuki, there's
another member of the Seven
Ninja Swordsmen of the Mist.
Kisame Hoshigaki. He has chakra
equal to that of a Jinchuriki.
and his sword, Samehada,
or Shark Skin, is the most
terrible of all the blades.
When his chakra and sword merge,
even though he's human,
he has power close to
that of a Jinchuriki.
He is like a Tailed Beast
without the tail!
Or so my elders
have told me.
He's extraordinary.
Please do not
underestimate him.
Yes, we already
know about that!
But anyway, are all of you
sure about this plan?
We don't know just how
much power Madara's seven
Tailed Beasts possess.
If we hold Eight- and Nine-Tails
back and our Allied Shinobi
Forces are wiped out while
protecting the two of them,
Then our entire effort
would have been meaningless,
all for naught!
If that's the case,
it's better to use them
right from the start,
and let them wage a
two-front war alongside
our combined forces.
[Mifune]
Actually, I
wonder about that.
Mmh?
The world's first Allied Shinobi
Force is being formed here,
right at this very moment.
And its strength
is also unknown.
And there must be some risk
in Madara using the power
of the seven Tailed Beasts.
Otherwise, he wouldn't have gone
out of his way to come to this
Summit and try to negotiate.
He must be facing unfavorable
circumstances just like us.
Furthermore, we Samurai
shall also participate
in this war!
Is this more satisfactory,
Lord Tsuchikage?
Do you still harbor doubts?
Hnh.
The Raikage and Kazekage
went back upstairs, too.
I bet that Sasuke and
Karin must've just gone
on ahead without us.
What do you say,
should we go up, too?
Yeah, but it's heavily guarded.
We're sure to be found out.
Maybe. But I've got a
trick up my sleeve.
[Kurotsuchi]
what the hell was he?
Yech, he is disgusting!
If we just do what we always do,
we'll never find Sasuke.
I'm going to have
to use Sage Mode.
But I need to find a way
to make it last longer.
[Yamato]
Naruto! Come down, already.
Hm?
Finally! We found you guys!
What? Sakura?
Sai, Kiba, and
even Bushy Brows?
Why are all
of you here?
Naruto.
I need to talk to you,
right now.
[Rock Lee]
What?! What is happening here?
Sakura, are you
telling the truth?
[Kiba]
Sakura, are you?!
[Yamato]
Is this truly
how you feel?
[Kakashi]
Wait, Yamato.
Let's hear her out.
[Naruto]
Sakura, Is this for real?!
[Sakura]
Yes, I just finally
realized my true feelings.
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
Sakura's Feelings.
[Naruto]
What... what is going on?