[music playing]
TSUNADE: So.
Tell me, how's Naruto's
training coming Along
-According to
Kakashi-sensei, he's
finally grasped the principles.
He should only require a
little more time to perfect it.
-I see.
-Milady, now that Kakashi-sensei
has joined team 10,
I think team seven
is the best team
to send after him, my team.
Because we've worked so
closely with him in the past,
we're the best choice.
-Very sharp, Sakura,
just as I'd expect.
-However, we have no
way of knowing just
when Naruto will perfect
this new jutsu of his.
Perhaps we should send
a different squad.
-Sakura, pass this on.
Tell Yamato to have Naruto wrap
it up in the next 24 hours,
and telling him
if he can't manage
that, I'll have to send a
different squad as backup.
-Right!
[door closes]
-Shizune, for a worst-case
scenario, review the roster.
Put together a list of squads
that work well with team 10.
-Yes, right away.
-Well, here we go.
KAKASHI: Okay, Shikamaru.
Let's hear that plan of yours.
SHIKAMARU: Actually, I'd
like to tweak it a little,
now that you're with
us, Kakashi-sensei.
-No problem.
Go on.
-I'll break it down into
pieces with all the variations,
so listen carefully everybody.
Memorize it.
[theme music]
NARUTO: What?
Kakashi-sensei and the others
have gone after the Akatsuki.
-Yeah, they just left.
1I see.
And what did Lady
Tsunade say about Us
-She agrees that we'd be the
best squad to supply backup.
She also said in order
for her to send us,
Naruto will have to master
his new jutsu, and quickly.
-Hm.
Master the new jutsu, huh?
-Yeah.
She says you've got the
next 24 hours to wrap it up.
Otherwise she'll go ahead
and dispatch another squad.
-Just 24 hours.
Huh.
[music playing]
-Naruto?
[gasp] Wait!
You don't want to eat that!
-Uh.
-(VOICEOVER): Naruto.
-Okay, Captain Yamato.
What are we waiting for?
Let's get to work.
SHIKAMARU: So that's the plan.
Use this when you get a
chance, to Kakashi-sensei.
Please hold onto it until then.
-Understood I'm impressed
by how much you've
learned about your opponent,
and from only one encounter.
-Well, the other guys
powers are still a mystery.
-(VOICEOVER) The way he
quickly modified his strategy
to accommodate my
addition to the team,
very impressive indeed.
-It's the best I
could come up with,
given the limited
information that we have.
Once you've got it
clear in your minds,
run through a mental simulation
of it at least three times.
That's important because
as you guys know,
visualization training can
make all the difference.
-All right.
KAKASHI: OK.
Let's do it.
-Right.
-Now then.
The first thing we have to
do is pick up their trail.
-Their trail?
Oh yeah!
Right!
You mean go back and find the
path they took from the fire
temple to the collection office.
-That's right.
We might be able to
pick up their footprints
and scent from the
trail they left.
-Well, I don't know about that.
I'm not sure that's
the easiest way.
-Let's give it a shot.
-Now the Two Tails has
been sealed away, as well.
Only four more to go.
-[sigh] Finally.
-Let's go to the Leaf, Hidan.
-The Leaf?
-Kakuzu, Hidan.
If you're really headed for
the Leaf, a word of warning.
-Hm.
-There's a jinchuuriki
there named Naruto Uzumaki.
Be careful if you run into him.
-Hm.
-Oh, is that Right So says
the little weakling who
failed so miserably and had
to have his own arm reattached
by Kakazu.
-Better losing an
arm than his head.
-What?
Hey, Kakazu!
Whose side are you on anyway?
Hey, I thought we were partners.
Partners as supposed to-
KAKUZU: Shut up, Hidan.
Let's go.
-[scoffs]
--[sigh] Three whole
days without moving.
I'm so ready to rampage.
Now, where's that cash cow?
Hm?
Hey, Kakuzu, where
are you going?
The collection office
is over this way.
-What are you, an idiot?
-What do you mean by that?
-They'll be expecting that.
Do you want to walk
right into an Ambush No.
This time we'll find a
different way into the Leaf.
After all, it's the
jinchuuriki we want.
Anyway, it's been three days.
The one with the
bounty on him will
have been retrieved
by his comrades.
-Yeah.
I suppose you're right.
-And another thing.
-Hm?
-What are you doing?
-That scar on your
neck is embarrassing.
Cover it up.
-Hey, look at that!
It's my headband.
You went to the trouble of
picking it up and keeping it
for me?
I'm touched.
You're a pretty nice guy,
Kakuzu, you know that?
-Shut up.
Come on.
Let's go.
-Hey, wait up!
Let me put it on at least.
There.
OK, I'm coming.
Come on, admit it.
You like me a little, don't you?
KAKUZU: Either you shut
up or I'll kill you.
HIDAN: [laughs]
You're embarrassed.
I understand.
-As I feared.
The rain has wiped out
any trace of their tracks.
What do you suggest we do now?
-We can't do anything
until we've found them,
so that's still our
first order of business.
-Remember what they said?
-We'll be back in no time,
so prepare yourselves.
-You hear that?
Stay right where you
are til we get back.
-That's what they said,
but they wouldn't really
be stupid enough to return to
the same place, would they?
-Well, we've got the other team
watching the collection office
in case they do.
-The loud mouth guy
doesn't bother me so much.
It's the other one
that I'm worried about.
And I'm betting they'll
take a different route,
but they're destination
will remain the same,
whether they're after
the bounty on Asuma,
or the jinchuuriki
inside of Naruto.
In either case, they're
target is the Leaf.
-There are many approaches
to the leaf village,
a lot of territory to cover.
How do we find them?
-That's how, up there.
-Hm?
-I'm on it.
-There you are.
INO: Headed straight for the
Leaf, just as we thought.
INO: [gasps]
-What happened?
Are you all right?
-Oh, man.
That was close.
-Did they spot you?
-I think we're OK.
They're taking a different
route, just as you predicted.
If we head Northeast,
we'll run into them.
It'll take about 10 minutes.
-What the hell was that about?
-It was nothing.
Nothing at all.
-Then let's keep moving.
-Right.
-All right.
Let's go.
-Hidan.
-I know.
-What?
-Paper bombs.
-Kakuzu!
-I hardened my arm.
I'm fine.
Just watch out for the shadows.
-Ha!
We won't fall for
that trick again.
-Hidan, above you.
-More paper bombs.
Hidan, look out!
-(VOICEOVER): Huh?
It didn't detonate.
[gasp]
-We've been had.
-Shadow possession
shuriken jutsu, achieved.
-(VOICEOVER): I can't move.
-Little jerk.
How did you do it when
I dodged your shadow?
-What I threw it you
were chakra blades.
Not only did they
absorb the chakra nature
of whoever wields
them, they compliment
and augment his jutsu.
-What the hell is this
kid talking about, Kakuzu?
-Will you shut up, you idiot?
SHIKAMARU: In short, having
absorbed the users chakra,
the chakra blades become
an extension of his jutsu.
So you see, I wasn't
trying to hit you.
I was aiming for your
shadows the whole time.
It's Asuma's gift to
you, a little memento
of the man you killed.
-The one worth 35 million, huh?
-(VOICEOVER): Asuma.
-If I were picking pieces
to represent Leaf's shinobi,
you know what?
I'd say you are most
like the knight.
-Why is that?
-It's not the most powerful
piece of the board,
but it can leap over
any of the others.
It's a unique ability.
It reminds me how
flexible your mind is.
-(VOICEOVER): So these
paper bombs are fakes.
Just ordinary pieces of paper.
Now I see.
The first set of paper
bombs on kunai knives
were meant to mislead
us, to make sure
that we would try and elude
the second set, attached
to chakra blades.
He then distracted us again
by drawing our attention
to the ground with
his shadow play,
so we wouldn't notice
his attack from
above until the last minute.
By allowing us no
time to think, he
was able to pierce our
shadows and paralyze us.
Quite the little
tactician, this one.
-All right, then.
It's time to finish this.
-Hey!
What's wrong with you?
Why are you so quiet
all of a sudden?
What the hell were
you thinking letting
yourself get caught too, huh?
Hey, you know what I think?
Things aren't looking too good
for us, that's what I think.
-Yeah, you're right.
As a matter of fact,
by my calculations,
it's all over for
you two, right now.
-(VOICEOVER): Nicely done.
-You fool.
-Hey!
What's going on now?
What are you doing?
-Just want to get it right.
Don't want to make the
same mistake as last time.
I need to be sure not to mess
up our order of attack again.
-Not your lucky day.
I'm afraid you chose the
wrong one of us to start with.
-This time, I'm going to see
to it we finish this once
and for all.
-[struggling]
-Damn!
-I never forget a face, kid.
Someday I'm going to find you
and I'm going to kill you!
-Oh, man.
You really don't get it, do you?
-Kakuzu, duck!
-All right!
-[gasp]
--[gasp] (VOICEOVER):
What on earth?
I never expected his arm to be
able to function independently
from his body!
But how?
And when did he-- wait.
Yeah.
When I attacked them
with the paper bombs,
he must have hidden
his arm in the ground
under cover of the smoke.
It's such a drag the way
each of these Akatsuki
has unique powers.
-I guess it's not quite
all over yet, is it?
As you can plainly see, my
abilities are countless.
You'd be wise to retreat
and plan your next move.
That is, if you're smart,
unlike my partner here.
Just remember, all the battle
plans you make mean nothing
when the situation on the
ground doesn't go as calculated.
-[laughs]
-Kakuzu!
What did you mean, "unlike
my partner here," huh?
-Just what I said, you idiot.
-I can't control my body!
Do something, Kakuzu!
Do something!
-Me?
What's wrong with you?
Damn it.
-[voiceover] Now, Choji, now!
-Spiky human boulder!
HIDAN: Kakuzu!
[theme music]
KAKASHI: Wha-
what's going on now?
CHOJI: Man, I don't get it.
He just took
Kakashi-sensei's best shot.
SHIKAMARU: You're right.
That was a direct
hit on a vital spot.
INO: What's that on his back?
I'm sensing some
very bad chakra here.
SHIKAMARU: I think
things just got serious.
Watch your step, Choji.
CHOJI: Right!
KAKASHI: Seems this
Kakuzu has only
begun to show us the
tricks up his sleeve.
NARUTO: Next time,
Kakuzu's abilities.