[music playing]
-Huh?
He's eating the detonating clay.
But that means--
-I saved the best for last.
This'll kill you.
Tobi, run!
Now!
-Huh?
[screaming]
-No!
No!
It's the C4 Karura!
Hurry feet!
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER): I set
this jutsu aside especially
to kill Itachi but-- oh well.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Is that a bomb too?
It's huge.
If that thing goes off--
-What?
You're just going
to run away now?
Do you really think
that you can escape
from me and my C4 Karura?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): He misfired?
No.
That isn't it.
That's--
-That's right, I win!
Art is an explosion!
Ha!
Sublime.
-Ah, impossible.
Ah, this can't be happening.
[theme music]
[music playing]
[laughter]
-This is my greatest
masterpiece!
-There we go.
The C4 Karura, microscopic
nano-sized explosives.
When the giant Deidara
ruptures, the blast wave
disperses explosives
too small for the eye
to see, scattering them
all over the atmosphere.
The mini bombs then
implant themselves
within the bodies of any and
all creatures that inhale them.
And when they explode the
multiple-cellular level
explosions destroy their
victims from the inside out.
Huh, a fearsome Jutsu indeed.
-I have Itachi to
thank for this.
[laughter]
I've won!
My art has won this fight!
-It seems that you've
exhausted all your Chakra.
And now you're
too slow to react.
-Those eyes.
-Your explosives may be too
small for the eye to see.
But my Sharingan sees
Chakra as colors.
Your mini bombs
infused with Chakra
were clearly visible to me
as a large cloud of smoke.
I could also tell that
you took great care
to remain hovered just outside
the range of the nano bombs.
Since I could see the
explosives, escape was easy.
-But I just saw you die from
my C4 with my very own eyes.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
That was my Genjutsu.
-Of course, so
that's what it was.
-I've avoided hitting
your vital organs.
Now, tell me where Itachi is.
[laughter]
-Like I said, I've got to
remember to thank Itachi.
-A clay clone, I
should have known.
-You see now?
I anticipated your Genjutsu.
You're just like Itachi.
And I never fall for
the same trick twice.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Yes,
it all began the day
that I fought Itachi.
That's fine.
Just don't mock my art.
That's what my Ninjutsu is,
a noble and refined art.
-Hmm.
-Now, feel my art!
Hiya!
Ha, ha you talked big.
But it looks like
that's all you've got.
You're done.
Ha!
-Am I?
You should take a
good look at yourself.
-Uh, what?
How?
-That was close.
A little later and you've
have blown yourself up.
-I told he was the type who was
going to die an early death.
-Genjutsu, since when?
-Right from the beginning,
when you saw Itachi's Sharingan
you were already under
his Genjutsu then.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
It's beautiful.
This-- this is art.
Ugh, no, I became intimidated
by someone else's abilities.
That, art?
Never.
I refuse to
acknowledge it as that.
Since that day, I've
trained my left eye
to counter the Sharingan.
As if I wouldn't
find a way to counter
such a powerful Genjutsu.
And now it's over!
How about a direct C4 attack!
[grunts]
-So now who's the one that's
running out of Chakra, huh?
Bet you don't have
enough to free yourself!
Ah!
-Just as I thought, the
inside of this model
is just like the other one,
full of invisible C4 bombs.
Hmph!
It hurts.
and worse, I used up my
Chakra with that last attack.
What a poor piece.
What do you do now, huh?
The last of his chopper's
in that lightening blade.
That lightening blade
attack won't reach me
at this distance.
I'll well out of your range.
[growls]
It's over.
Hiya!
[breathing heavily]
I won.
I really did it.
My art triumphed,
as I knew it would.
Ha-- ha ha-- ha ha, ha ha--
[gasps]
No way!
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
What is going on here?
That was no Genjutsu.
But then it means-- how-- how
did he disarm the C4 bombs?
But how?
Don't tell me that
you figured it out?
-Yeah, I did, a while back.
When facing the
Sharingan you really
ought to weave your signs
out of the line of site.
Because no matter how fast you
are, these eyes can read them.
All of your Jutsu so far
have used Earth Style Signs.
My Chidori uses
Lightening Style.
You do the math.
So you knew about
it all along then?
Then when you attacked me
with that lightening blade--
-Earth Style's
vulnerable to Lightning.
I knew that if I used it
then the lightning blade
would diffuse your bombs.
It's their Achilles
heel, isn't it?
-Damn you.
Of course, the lightning
blade wasn't intended for me.
It was for yourself.
You used it to deactivate
the C4 in your body.
That's right.
But it left my body
in tatters too.
By the way, my Jutsu is
technically called Chidori.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER): He
figured out my art's weakness
so quickly and with
perfect accuracy.
When did you realize?
after those landmines went off.
I knew then.
But I'd been analyzing
it from the very start.
Early on I countered your first
attack with Chidori Senbon.
I noticed that some of the
bombs you created exploded.
But some did not.
That's when I first
formulated my hypothesis.
-Your hypothesis?
What?
-That time, the only explosive
that actually detonated
was the one you threw
back at me again,
the one that you
threw when you tried
to evade my counterattack.
But all of the other
explosives, the ones
that I blocked with my Chidori
cymbal did not detonate.
However, it was possible
that you purposely
chose not to trigger them.
They did fall close
to your partner.
So perhaps you disabled them.
I see.
So in other words,
you couldn't tell
if your Chidori stopped them
from exploding or if I did.
Yes, you checked your theory
by testing it on the land mine.
-Yes, exactly.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
This C2 assault
is brought you by the
linked attacks of the minds
that restrict your
ground movement
and the pinpoint missile
attacks from the air.
You're completely surrounded
by landmines in the ground
all around you.
Step on one, even touch
it, and it'll go off.
-If they detonate
automatically then
they're not under your control.
And if that was the
case, then I could
confirm if my Liking
Style Jutsu too
could diffuse your
Earth Style bombs.
[gasps]
-That's right, that time I
stuck my sword into the ground.
I wasn't trying to find a place
in between the land mines.
I was testing my
hypothesis by running
my Chidori-charged blade
through a mine I knew was there.
-But how could you?
How could you ever pinpoint
the position of the landmines
like that?
-These eyes see Chakra
as different colors.
Didn't you hear me before?
-You can see where
the landmines were.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER): So
then he wasn't just trying
to find a safe place to stand.
He was a step
ahead, seeing if he
could disarm my detonating clay?
But what would you have done
if the mine had stayed active
and gone off?
-There were only two outcomes.
Fortunately, I had a
backup plan just in case.
But I guess I didn't
need to test it out.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER): He--
still has other Jutsu.
-Now tell me where Itachi is.
-(LAUGHING) You
sure can talk tough.
But you're on your
last legs too.
Your Chakra took a
big hit, didn't it?
(LAUGHING) I still win.
I have some
detonating clay left--
[breathing heavily]
-Are you still calm?
Shouldn't you be worried
at least a little?
Come on.
You're about to be
killed by my art.
[laughing]
That is what annoys me the most
about you and your brother.
You think you're just so cool!
Those eyes, those over-confident
eyes make me so sick.
Your eyes, always
judging me and my art.
I'll never forgive
them for that!
You have absolutely
no respect for my art.
I can tell that you don't.
I can never forgive those
eyes that just ignore my art!
-I couldn't care less
about all of that.
I just want you to tell me
where I can find Itachi.
-So you've retracted
your Sharingan.
Do you really take
me that lightly?
This is my ultimate art.
This time I'm going
to detonate myself.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): He's insane.
In death I shall
become art itself.
No one's seen an
explosion like this,
one that shall leave behind a
scar on the very earth itself.
And then I'll receive
more admiration for my art
than anyone has
ever seen before!
Sorry Tobi.
-Huh?
-But while I will be admired,
you'll most definitely be dead.
[grunts]
-This explosion will
cover 10 kilometers.
You can't run away
from this one, hmm.
Tremble, be afraid.
Recoil in despair, cower in
awe and cry your heart out.
Because my art--
Is an explosion!
[theme music]
-Noruto, there's
evidence Sasuke was here
until just before we arrived.
PAKKUN (VOICEOVER): What?
-It's faint, but
definitely his scent.
I'd say he fought a battle here.
PAKKUN (VOICEOVER):
What are we waiting for?
Let's go after him!
-We can't.
PAKKUN (VOICEOVER): Why not?
-His trail goes cold here.
In this case, either
Sasuke was annihilated
in that explosion or--
PAKKUN (VOICEOVER): Next
time, Disappearance.