[music playing]
[soft cooing]
-There, there you go.
-Huh?
Where did you come from,
so early in the morning?
[gasp] It's Tagamaru,
the fastest carrier bird
the hidden sand's got!
[gasps]
-Release!
Oh no!
A level one emergency dispatch.
Go send word to the
cypher corps at once!
-Oh man, it'll feel so good
to be on a real mission again.
-Listen, whatever kind
of mission we're given,
just take it, and don't
complain about it.
-Don't sweat it.
those days are over.
-I hope so.
-Out of the way!
Out of the way!
-What was that?
-Why don't you watch
where you're going?
Who do you think you are?
-(THINKING) They've called
in the cypher corps, huh?
Then it's true, the
carrier bird I saw earlier.
-I heard there's a level
one emergency dispatch.
Are you absolutely sure?
-Yes, see for yourself.
-From the hidden sand, huh?
Release!
-The fact that they
would send this to us,
they must be in some
serious trouble.
-We'll find out,
once I decipher it.
[theme music]
-You moved as fast as Crow.
I'm impressed.
-The spider needs to
be as fast as the fly.
-I remember now.
This Ginchuriki is supposed
to have a couple of siblings.
And one of them's some
kind of puppet master.
That must be you, I guess.
Your name's, uh, Kanturo,
right, or Kampachi [chuckling],
or something?
-It's Kankuro!
Ha!
-Forget about him.
I'm your opponent.
Deidara, quit gawking,
and get out of here.
You're in the way.
-Fine.
I'll leave you to it, then.
Hm.
-Where are you going?
Ah!
-Didn't you hear me?
I'm your opponent.
-(THINKING) I'll have to
take care of this one first,
then go after the other.
-Not your lucky day, my friend.
In your case, my man Sasuli
is the last opponent on earth
you'd ever want to face.
-There might still be
some traps remaining.
So watch your step.
Sir, the pursuit corps
is ready to go, any time.
-All right.
Head out after Kankuro.
But remember, if you
encounter the enemy,
avoid a battle if
at all possible.
Your sole objective is to
find out where their base is.
Understood?
-Sir.
-Once we know where
they are, we'll
move in, and rescue
the Kazekage.
So bring me back their position.
Now move out!
-Sir!
-(THINKING) Please don't do
anything rash in the meantime,
Kankuro.
-OK, if that's what you want,
let the puppet show begin.
Faster!
Pretty good so far.
You didn't notice that Black
Ant was missing, did you?
And now, puppet show!
Secret black move, iron maiden.
The show's over.
-Huh?
Escort duty on a caravan?
Come on.
-What, have you got
a problem with that?
-Since you're asking, yes.
Lousy C-rank mission,
it's beneath my dignity.
-(THINKING) Here we go.
What did I just tell him?
-(THINKING) Calm down, Naruto.
Because I'm the one who's going
to have to take the heat if you
don't.
-(THINKING) Just as I expected.
Nothing's changed.
-(THINKING), OK, OK, you were
right. [nervous giggling]
-(SIGH) Naruto, your
skills may have improved.
But mentally, you
haven't matured as well.
-Naruto, I've chosen
an easier mission
to start with to break you in.
You've been gone
from us for a while.
-Well, who says I want
an easier mission?
-So sorry, milady.
Let me talk to him.
I'm sure I can bring him around.
-You idiot!
You have now idea how
ferocious Lady Tsunade can be!
Are you insane?
-The details of your
mission are here.
-Right.
-Huh.
I miss the Third Hokage.
That old man was smart.
He knew what he was doing.
-Huh?
What did you say?
-Just shut up, will you?
-Lady Tsunade, terrible news.
-Now what is it?
-An emergency dispatch
from the sand.
-Huh, the sand?
Where is this dispatch.
-I deciphered it as
quickly as I could.
-What the?
-It's sand!
Uh!
[creaking]
It's only a sand clone.
Oh.
-Huh?
It can't be.
-No way.
-What is it?
What's happened?
-It's the Kazekage of the sand.
It seems he's been taken
prisoner by the Akatsuki.
-You mean Gara.
So they're back again.
-We've been studying them.
We know more about the Akatsuki
than any other village.
Therefore, the sand village has
officially requested our help.
--[gasp] You're not suggesting
that team Kakashi--
-This is urgent.
I haven't time to
form another squad.
And besides, we
have someone here
who's actually
fought the Akatsuki.
Yes, but even so--
-All right.
Team Kakashi, I'm assigning
you a new mission.
You're to go to the
sand village at once.
Find out what's going on there.
And keep us informed.
You're to remain there,
and follow their orders.
Give them any backup they need.
-(THINKING) But how?
Ah!
How does he-- how is he
able to anticipate and avoid
every attack I make, and
without moving a muscle?
-What's wrong?
Run out of tricks?
-I'm just getting started!
Poison mist inferno.
Consecutive needle combo.
Heh.
[gasp]
-Are you finished?
-No way.
Not even the poison mist
has any effect on him.
-Have I mentioned how much I
dislike making people wait.
It's against my policy.
You've had your turn.
Now it's mine.
--[gasp] Have a lot of fun
trying to get through that.
-[gasp]
-Whoa.
-(THINKING) Salamander shield
can withstand the impact
of thousands of tons of rocks.
[chuckling] As long as I stay
behind it, you can't touch me.
-That puppet of
yours does indeed
have extraordinary
defensive capabilities.
But even the best made
puppet has a weak spot.
KANKURO: It's no use.
What?
No, it can't be.
It didn't take him any time
at all to find its weakness.
-That puppet you have is no
different than any other.
You can make the individual
parts as strong as you want.
But the joints are
always a weak spot.
And now for the
real grand finale.
-(THINKING) I'm not someone
who usually believes in omens.
Still, I'm getting
a bad feeling.
-Yah!
(THINKING) It's not possible.
He knows what I'm going
to do almost before I do.
-You have talent.
You might even win against
a different opponent.
Those puppets of yours, with all
their hidden poison mechanisms,
they're not hidden from me.
-[gasp] Crow!
Black Ant!
Salamander!
(THINKING) No one's ever been
able to read my hidden weapon
attacks like this.
--[chuckling] You must be
wondering how I can anticipate
every attack your puppets make.
Crow, Black Ant, Salamander.
The answer is quite
simple, really.
I'm the one who created them.
-Huh?
-[snoring]
-[ribbiting]
-Ah, [sputtering]
Huh?
-Roar.
-Is that scroll for me?
Well, what are you waiting
for you, you idiot?
Give it to me!
Hmm, what have we got here?
That Kazekage of the
hidden sand-- hmm.
This is no time for me to
be sleeping on the job!
-I know I promised to
finish this quickly, and not
keep you waiting.
But facing one of my own
disciples using my old toys,
I can't resist
savoring the moment.
-So then you have to be the
legendary master craftsman
of the puppet corps, the
great Sasuri of the red sand.
-I'm honored that my
name is so well known,
even to a child such as you.
-You deserted us 20 years ago.
Why do you come back to us now?
-What's the point
of asking questions
when you're about to die?
-Uh?
(THINKING) My body's going numb.
He used his poison.
But when?
Of course.
It happened then.
-The poison is circulating, eh?
It's over.
Huh?
Hmm.
Since you want to live so
badly, I won't finish you.
I'll let the poison
take its course.
You'll wish I hadn't.
Your suffering will
be unimaginable.
But it will be over in
less than three days.
-[panting]
Gara.
Damn it.
MALE SPEAKER: Here,
he's over here.
He's passed out!
Look, his puppets
have been destroyed.
OK, let's get moving.
-Be back soon, milady.
We won't let you down.
-Good.
-Naruto, good luck.
-Thanks
-Hey there.
So, off on a mission, Naruto.
-That's right.
-Well, good for you.
But more importantly, I've
got some disturbing news.
The sands Kazekage have been--
-Yes, I know.
I'm dispatching a squad.
They're just about to leave.
-Mhmm.
-You know about the Akatsuki's
interest in Naruto, don't you.
-I had no other choice.
It's an emergency situation.
You're running a
pretty big risk.
Naruto, I want a word with you.
-Hmm?
-Listen to me, now.
You be careful around
those Akatsuki, you hear?
-They've all been out
looking for me, right?
Well, this way they won't
have to look very far.
-It's true you've come
a long way, Naruto.
But training doesn't mean a
thing if you get reckless,
and blow your cool.
You still have a bad habit of
losing your head, even now.
Naruto, never use that power.
You know what I'm talking about.
-Yeah, I know.
-Kakashi, make sure that kid
doesn't do anything stupid.
I can trust you, right?
-Right.
-Kakashi Sensei,
Sakura, come on.
What we were waiting for?
-OK, OK, coming.
-We're off.
-There he goes again.
-Worried, Aruka?
-Worried?
No, not a bit.
He's no longer a
rookie Shinobi who
needs me to worry about him.
Sakura, too.
-How is it that
they grow so fast?
It's a mystery.
-(THINKING) Hang on, Gara.
We're coming!
[music playing]
What's wrong, Kankuro?
Why so down in the dumps?
KANKURO: Well, I'll
tell you, Tamare.
I'm trying to get
my war paint off.
But this cold cream
irritates my skin.
Try these new miracle
cleansing wipes.
Their micro fibers
soothe your skin
while they clean your pores.
KANKURO: Whoa, will
you look at that?
My makeup's coming right off.
Not only that.
But if you act now, you
get an extra pack free.
And they'll even throw
in a handy carrying case.
KANKURO: Really, thanks
for the tip, Tamare.
I'm going to rush out,
and buy mine today.
NARUTO: Next time,
the [inaudible] tears.
[music playing]
FEMALE SPEAKER: Ambu black
ops intelligence report--
the alliance between
the leaf and sand.
During the exams, an
attack was launched
against the leaf village.
The sand village had
conspired with the Rochimaru
to destroy the leaf.
These were perilous times,
especially after the leaf
lost their reviewed
Third Hokage.
But when the sand's own Kazakage
was assassinated as well,
they realized they
had been betrayed.
They renounced their
alliance with the Rochimaru,
confessed their
part in the plot,
and offered peace to the leaf.
Eager to begin the process of
rebuilding, the leaf accepted.
And the two lands
formed an alliance.
The sand has incorporated much
of the leaf's training program
in the development
of their own Shinobe.
As the lands grew
closer, questions
arose about the relationship
between Shikamaru and Tamare.
Shikamaru asserts that
it's strictly professional.
But Naruto has his doubts.
In any case, all signs point to
a strong and durable alliance,
which will benefit both
lands in the future.