-Protect-- to protect me?
You've gotta be kidding me.
-I'll say it once more.
You think you know all
about your older brother,
but you know nothing.
-If you continue spouting
such nonsense and lies,
I'll kill you right here.
-You're not making this easy.
I suppose that's only natural
hearing a story like this
from a complete
stranger, but what
I'm telling you is the truth.
Itachi did mention
it, didn't he?
That he wasn't alone that night,
that he had an accomplice.
I am Madara Uchiha.
I know everything there
is to know about Itachi.
I suppose Itachi died
without realizing that.
-Shut up!
None of that matters anymore.
Just get out of my
sight, you hear me?
-No, you will listen.
You need to hear this.
It's your obligation.
It's about the life
of your brother
who risked everything for
the sake of the Shinobi
world, the Hidden Leaf
village, and most of all
for you, his younger brother.
You will know how
Itachi Uchiha lived.
Do you know why?
Why Itachi implanted the
Amaterasu into your eye?
It's because Itachi never
wanted us to meet or to talk.
Listen to my tale and
you'll understand.
The only ones who knew
the truth about Itachi
were the Leaf's Danzo,
the Third Hokage,
and the two advisers
Homura and Koharu.
With the Third Hokage dead,
there are only three elders
left who know the
secret, and they
are likely to never reveal
the abominable truth
that they're hiding.
The truth about Itachi will
fade into darkness forever,
just as Itachi himself wished.
However, I also know
the truth about Itachi.
As I said earlier, Itachi
never realized just how much
I knew about him.
Apparently, he wanted
to make doubly sure.
It seems that Itachi
didn't trust me,
and just in case I
did know the truth,
he planned to silence me with
the Amaterasu he implanted
in you.
He probably anticipated that
I would show you my sharingan
in order to speak to you.
-What are you saying?
What are you trying
to tell me here?
Protect me.
The truth.
-Remember.
Think back carefully
and remember Itachi.
[gasping]
Your kind and gentle
older brother.
-Hey, what's up?
-That building is where
Father works, isn't it?
-Mmhm.
Its headquarters for
the Leaf police force.
-You know, I've been
wondering something.
How come the crest
of the Uchiha clan
is part of the Leaf
police force insignia?
-What do you know,
you finally noticed.
-Course I did.
-Right.
Let's see, to put it simply, it
was the Uchiha clan's earliest
ancestors who established
the police force here
in the Leaf village.
So when they created the
symbol for the organization,
they used the family crest.
Since a long time
ago, the Uchiha
have always ensured
the peace here.
The crest is a testament
of our clan's pride
in a way of life centuries old.
Over the years, the Uchiha
clan has grown smaller,
but even now, nearly all of
us are a part of the force
and work to uphold the
peace in this village.
Which is good, because only
the most exceptional of Shinobi
can weed out the criminals
hiding among their brethren.
SASUKE (THINKING): Wow,
Dad is the coolest.
-Are you going to
join the force, too?
-Well, I'm not sure.
-Why not?
-No, it's impossible.
No.
He didn't want to protect
me, he just tried to kill me.
He tried to steal my eyes!
-Just who could do
something like this?
-My foolish little brother.
Mangekyo sharingan.
[gasping, coughing]
-Calm down.
Breathe slowly.
[panting]
-Don't touch me!
-Even if you do hate me, that's
what big brothers are for.
-Sorry, Sasuke.
Maybe some other time.
[theme music]
-You're awake.
Sorry, I took the
liberty of tying you up
since it didn't seem you'd
stay still and listen
to me otherwise.
-Itachi was my enemy.
He killed our mother and father.
And he slaughtered
our whole clan.
He was a rogue ninja and
a member of the Akatsuki.
He was despicable.
He was my only goal.
-That fateful night.
It is true that he slaughtered
the entire Uchiha clan
and then fled the
Hidden Leaf Village.
-Then?
-But it was his
mission to do so.
He was ordered by leaders
of the Hidden Leaf.
And that is just the beginning
of the truth about Itachi.
-It was his mission.
-Yes.
That night, Itachi set
aside his personal feelings
and fulfilled his mission.
Well, it seems you've
finally calmed down.
-But I still don't understand.
-In order to explain
Itachi's story,
I must take you back to the
beginning, when the Hidden Leaf
Village was founded.
Itachi sacrificed
himself, a fate
that grew from a
longstanding power struggle.
He was callously
used to serve it.
-Sacrificed?
-That's right.
A problem that hearkens
back to the very origins
of the founding of the
Hidden Leaf Village,
it determined the
path of Itachi's life.
It's a long story, but every
word that I'm about to tell you
is the absolute truth.
-And on what ground
should I believe you?
You're completely untrustworthy.
-I don't have any evidence
that I can show you,
so it's up to you to decide
whether you believe me
or not, but only after you
listen to the entire story.
-Fine.
Talk.
-It all started more
than 80 years ago.
Back then, the world
was embroiled in battle.
It was an era of warring states.
Nations fought for
power, for the right
to exist, or to
expand their borders.
During this time of strife,
Shinobi organizations
only consisted of individual
clans serving as armed units.
Various clans were
hired by various nations
to participate in the
conflicts, and among all
of these numerous
ninja clans were
two that were feared above
all others as the strongest.
One was our own Uchiha
clan, and the other
was known as the Senju
clan of the forest.
We of the Uchiha clan
possessed exceptional chakra
and the sharingan.
Excelling in all
types of warfare,
we became known
as a battle clan,
and then I was born into our
clan, processing chakra that
was especially powerful,
even for an Uchiha.
The fact that I've lived this
long is proof enough of that.
Back then, I spent every
day on the battlefield.
In an era where
power was everything,
at the cost of my friends
and younger brother,
I continuously sought
ever more power.
-Damn you.
-But thanks to that, I was
able to awaken the mangekyo
sharingan fully, and I became
the leader of the Uchiha.
And with that power, I
fought the Senju clan
more times than I can count.
Of course, it was
inevitable that I
would face Hashirama, the
leader of the Senju clan.
Hashirama Woodstyle Senju,
the future First Hokage,
the man who stood at the top of
the ninja world, and the person
that I respected most.
Led by Hashirama, who
became the very first
to claim the title of
Hokage, the Senju clan
became acknowledged
as the fiercest
and most feared by
all the other clans.
Whenever the Senju made a
move, so did the Uchiha.
Our clan was pretty
much the only one
who could take them on.
If a nation hired the
Senju, their opponents
would hire the Uchiha.
We became rivals.
The more I faced
Hashirama, the more my name
became known, as well.
-To reach the next level, to
test the limits of my ability.
-You stole your
brother's eyes merely
to heighten your own reputation?
Is that what you're telling me?
-I did steal them,
but I did so only
to obtain the strength necessary
to protect the Uchiha clan.
-To protect our clan.
-Yes.
As the Uchiha's reputation grew,
so did its number of enemies.
Amidst ferocious battles, it
was an unavoidable sacrifice
to protect our clan
from external foes,
starting with the Senju clan.
It wasn't merely
for distinction.
My younger brother was fully
aware and agreed with it.
In fact, he volunteered
his eyes to me.
But then one day, the
Senju clan proposed a truce
with the Uchiha, and
the Uchiha accepted it.
The majority on both
sides had grown weary
of the endless conflict.
They had simply had enough
of all the fighting.
I-- I was the only
one who opposed it.
I was the sole voice of dissent.
Where has all our mutual
hatred gone, I asked.
For what purpose had my
brother sacrificed himself?
The Uchiha and the Senju were
always like oil and water.
I couldn't help
feeling that one day,
the Uchiha clan would come to
be oppressed by the Senju clan.
However, everyone else in the
Uchiha clan wanted the truce.
As their leader, I had
no choice but to go along
with their wishes.
It wasn't too long
afterward that our alliance
forged an agreement with
the Land of Fire, which
had sought stability
within their land.
And thus the powerful system
of one village to one nation
came to be.
That was the Land of Fire
and the Village Hidden
in the Leaves.
Other nations quickly
followed suit,
and subsequently, one
by one, the fires of war
were at last extinguished.
Instantaneous peace, but due
to a certain incident, they
Hidden Leaf's peace
was short lived.
-What incident?
-There was a battle
over the seat
of the village
leader, the Hokage.
As you already know,
the first to occupy that
seat was Hashirama Senju.
Both the village and the
Land of Fire chose him.
It was clear the Uchiha were
being displaced from the power
structure.
I decided to advocate
for an Uchiha
to take the leadership in
order to protect our clan.
I knew that path would lead to
a confrontation with Hashirama.
But no one, not even a single
Uchiha supported me at all.
My followers shunned
me for trying
to rekindle the flames
of war, and betrayed me.
I was not only
accused and berated
for having personal
ambitions, but more than
that, they scorned me
as a selfish brother who
stole his younger brother's
eyes in order to save his own.
What man would wilfully hurt
his own younger brother?
I swore I only wanted
to protect the Uchiha.
I left the Hidden Leaf.
Having been betrayed
by everyone,
I decided to return
as an avenger,
and I declared war on
the Hidden Leaf Village.
But I was defeated
at that place that
has come to be known
as the Final Valley.
I was said to have died there.
I'm sure even Hashirama
believed that to be so,
and everyone forgot about me.
History forgot about me.
In order to prevent the
rise of another traitor,
Hashirama's younger brother,
who became the second Hokage,
bestowed upon the Uchiha
a special responsibility
as proof of his trust.
He established the
Hidden Leaf police force.
But the truth is that it
really removed the Uchiha
from the governing
body of the village
and placed the entire clan under
close scrutiny of all in one
fell swoop.
There were finally
some Uchiha who
recognized his true
motives, and there
grew an anti-establishment
faction that inherited my will.
But it was too late.
Time passed, the leadership
stayed in the Senju's hands.
And the once proud
Uchiha clan members
were reduced to being
the Senju's lackeys,
and what I'd predicted
came to pass.
And then another incident
sealed the Uchiha's demise.
That's right, the attack of the
nine-tailed fox 16 years ago.
-What do you mean by that?
-Only the Uchiha's
visual prowess
can tame and control
the Nine-tails.
So the elders of the
Hidden Leaf village
surmised that an Uchiha was
behind the Nine-tails attack.
But it was a spontaneous
natural disaster.
The Uchiha had
nothing to do with it,
and yet unjust
suspicions persisted
that the Uchiha had tried
to stage an insurrection
and seize power to take over
leadership of the village.
As a result, the Uchiha were
put under strict surveillance
by the ANBU black
ops, and were forced
to relocate to the
outskirts of the village.
They became completely isolated.
The third Hokage
was the only one
to voice opposition
to our treatment,
but Danzo of the ANBU black ops
and the other two counselors
wouldn't listen to him.
In the end, the Uchiha clan
was simply not trusted,
and that was the beginning of
the discrimination against us.
Distrust trust bred hatred,
and eventually their suspicions
became reality.
The Uchiha clan
started plotting a coup
de tat to take over the village.
And so the Hidden Leaf's
leaders planted as spy
within the Uchiha
clan to watch us.
That spy was your older
brother, Itachi Uchiha.
And that's when Itachi's
suffering began.
[theme music]
SASUKE: You've laid false
charges against the Uchiha.
MADARA: That's one
of Itachi's lies.
SASUKE: No, I won't believe it.
This can't be true.
Itachi tried to kill me!
MADARA: If he'd really
wanted to kill you,
you'd most certainly be dead.
SASUKE: Stop!
I've heard enough.
MADARA: You should know
already it's because--
SASUKE: Next time on
Naruto Shippuden-- Truth.
MADARA: This is Itachi's truth.