"The Complete
Ino-Shika-Cho Formation!"
[growling]
You're wrong.
I'm not fat!
I'm just pleasantly
plump!
[screaming]
[gasping]
Why?
It's no good. Choji's
completely lost his will
to fight.
[grunting]
But why, Choji?!
Uh!
Didn't work!
Choji! Get back!
Choji!
[gasping]
Uh!
Ino Mind Transferred into
Choji. Quick thinking...
That was too close!
Thank you for that Shadow
Possession!
Mm!
Ino.
When we were in Team 10,
all of us completed a whole
lot of missions together
with Asuma Sensei.
I know what you're
feeling now.
Believe me, Shikamaru and
I don't want to fight
him, either.
But because we know Asuma
Sensei better than anyone
else...
... we can stop him with
the least risk to the
Allied Forces!
Choji.
Choji,... you haven't
forgotten why we wear
these piercings, have
you?!
Uh!
That means all the
members of Squad Ten are
now officially Chunin!
And it also means that I
will no longer be in
charge of you guys.
From here on out, you're
leaders in your own right.
Each of you will be given
a new team to lead.
These earrings are my
gift to you, to celebrate
your success.
Whatever the future
holds, never forget you
were members of Squad
Ten.
And these earrings...
... are also proof that
each one of you guys has
come of age in your
respective clans.
Uh!
All of you already know
the whole story behind
the Practice of the
Piercings, right?
All right, then,... Go
and present your earrings
to your clans.
And when you do...
You'll be recognized as
full-fledged shinobi!
Now, go on; get going!
Full-fledged shinobi.
But I... I just...
Ah!
[gasping]
Fire Style! Burning Ash!
Ino, Choji!
Choza!
[struggling]
Old Man!
[gasping]
Which reminds me...
remember when we talked
about the king?
Now I'm going to tell
you who the king is...
Lean closer.
The children who carry
the Leaf's future on
their shoulders...
They're the ones who are
the kings.
And there's... just one
other thing to tell
you...
Kurenai's pregnant with
our child...
[gasping]
And so... I hereby
entrust you... with my
"King!"
Snap out of it, Choji!
Stay focused!
We aren't some little
brats who need to be
protected anymore!
We're the protectors,
now! Do you want Asuma to
murder his own child?!
Your idea of kindness is
wrong!
[panting]
Yeah, Shikamaru is right,
Choji!
Just remember the
piercings and what they
stand for!
Quit whining and pouting,
Choji!
Remember, you're the
sixteenth head of the
Akimichi Clan!
Akimichi Clan.
Um... let's see... the
symbol on the far right
belongs to us... the
Akimichi Clan, right?
And the other two are,
um...
The middle one in the
Nara Clan's. And the
leftmost one is the
Yamanaka Clan's.
Three clans that use highly
unusual Secret Ninjutsu.
We've been combining
our powers for many
generations now,
and the three clans
share a special
relationship.
Ooohhh.
To strengthen our union
and protect our clans,
the Sarutobi Clan bestows
ear piercings upon the
three of us.
And every generation, the
members of our clans
swear an oath of loyalty
on those earrings, so
they're not just mere
decorations, son.
You mean these? I saw
that the other clan
leaders also wear them.
It must hurt to get your
ear pierced...
We wear these piercings
so the message sinks
in deep.
They constantly remind
us of the oaths we swore.
And you're eventually
going to have to have it
done, too, Choji.
What?! But why?!
From the time my child
becomes a genin until he
or she finally achieves
chunin status, I am to
follow custom and pass on
my piercings to him or
her.
It's a practice that's
intended to teach one's
child all about the oaths
that one day they'll take.
Yeah, but I really don't
like pain!
[panting]
Choji.
[eating]
You know... sometimes I
wonder if he'll be okay.
[chewing]
I'm worried that he's just
too scared. I mean, sure,
he did finally become a
genin,... but he always
shies away from
confrontation.
Soon, he'll be sent out
on missions and may have
to face foes in
life-or-death battles.
And as it is...
... Well, to put it
bluntly,... I fear that
Choji will be killed
because he's too scared
to make a move.
Frankly, I seriously
doubt that he's ever
going to become a chunin.
You're off base about
him, Choza. Your son is
not a coward. He is
simply kind.
Maybe, but in the shinobi
world, that's the same
thing.
Then I say let him be who
he is. Let him be kind!
Are you serious?! Be
kind?!
Yes. the kindness that he
possesses...
...is a unique weapon
that he, and only he,
has.
A weapon?
He's just a boy. It can't
be helped if his kindness
is seen as cowardice.
But some day, his
kindness will be a thing
of greatness.
The time will come when
the Hidden Leaf will need
the kindness that he
brings to the world.
However, he's also going
to need to have strength
that can rival that
kindness.
He needs to have the
intensity...
...to recognize, feel,
and accept others'
pain.
Or even reject it... but
still envelop them in his
kindness.
I know that boy has those
qualities.
Asuma.
Choji is going to
experience many things,
both good and bad.
This is the shinobi
world, after all. So
he'll have to face many
hardships.
But with each experience
he has, he will grow
stronger and kinder.
Choza! Please, come
quickly!
I'm sorry, but I'll be
right there!
If you truly are
kind, Choji...
... There's no better time
to show it than right
now.
Or were my fears well
founded? Are you merely a
coward?
Choji! It's all right!
[gasping]
[gasping in awe]
[blowing]
You are a kind soul. That
is clear to see.
But must that butterfly
learn to live by borrowing
strength from you?
[blowing]
Uh?
From this day on, you're
a full shinobi, too.
And now you'll swear your
oath upon these new piercings.
Eventually you'll raise
your own child and pass
these earrings onto them.
[exhaling]
What is it?
Do you really think I
could get married one day?
Hey, what kind of talk is
that? You don't?
Do you understand why
Master Asuma continues to
be hard on you?
Listen, I was able to get
married, wasn't I? Be
more confident!
I just don't think that
I'll be as lucky as you
were, dad...
Times have changed. Girls
aren't as open-minded
anymore...
Now, Choji! Time to swear
your oath!
You know the words
already, don't you?
Uh, yeah. I know 'em...
Human Boulder!
[struggling]
[growling]
Even with potato chips, I
won't let anyone have the
last bite!
[gobbling]
Well with an appetite
like that, at least we
don't have to worry
about his health.
Hey, when I'm finished with
my breakfast, you're gonna
help me with my training
again, right Asuma Sensei?
I've got--
[coughing]
Ino. Choji. Shikamaru.
I've got something I
want to tell you three.
(low satisfied breath)
And Choji...
You're a thoughtful,
loyal friend... and a
kind soul... In time,
you'll become a
stronger shinobi than
anyone else... So be more
confident in yourself.
Got it.
And another thing... you
might consider losing a
few pounds.
I don't know if it's
possible, but I'll try
to.
I guess... I thought that
I'd just change naturally
when I got older.
I thought... that both my
heart and my body...
would get stronger.
So this is it, huh? The
war's about to begin...
So we seriously have to
fight dead people?
But what do we do?! I'm
getting really scared
here...
Come on, Choji... It's
too late to worry about
all of that... now that
you're here.
Oh, man... I'm
getting scared.
Hold on. You boys
better not wimp out
on me.
I'm sorry....
This is way too much for
me! I can't do it! I
can't take our Sensei
down! I just can't!
That's enough, Choji.
Listen up.
I know you're a
truly kind person.
But right now, taking me
down is the kindest thing
that you can do.
This is the time for you
to transform your
kindness into strength!
Now is the time, Choji!
I thought it was just an
oath, part of a ritual.
Now I hereby swear...
As the sixteenth leader
of the Clan I'll pass on
this oath entrusted to
me by the fifteenth...
...and I shall carry it
on unto the seventeenth
leader, my child to be!
Thank you, Ino. And I'm
sorry. But I'm okay now.
You can go back.
In order to protect the
Yamanaka and Nara Clans
and the Hidden Leaf
Village, I, Choji
Akimichi swear to
transform from a lowly
caterpillar to a powerful
butterfly!
And take flight!
Choji!
It's time... to change!
Uh!
He grew wings... without
even using the pills!
Uh!
[gasping]
Choji!
That's my boy, Choji.
That's what I was waiting
for!
Choji's slimmer!
Did he take a pellet like
the one he took a long
time ago or something?
To my eye, it looks just
like the effects of the
Chili Pepper Pellet. Is
he gonna be okay?
Yes, he'll be fine.
He didn't use the Akimichi
Clan Secret Calorie
Control Pellets.
He transformed all
on his own.
In other words, there
won't be any side effects
at all.
Was the shell of the
chrysalis harder than you
thought it would be,
Choji?
But at long last you'll
be able to fly, won't
you?
You bet I will!
I'm going to go back up
now.
Got it, Old man Choza.
I'm sorry Choji's always
been trouble.
But that's
over, now.
He is now...
...truly worthy of being
the sixteenth Akimichi
Clan leader.
We can handle Asuma from
here on out. Please take
care of the rest, old
man!
Do it!
Weaken him, then get him
over here!
You're sure good at
barking out orders from a
distance. We need to get
in there and help, too!
Shut it!
Uh!
Well, that's the Sealing
Corps for you! Like it's
gonna be that simple!
Shikamaru! Get my back!
You got it. Go, Ino! Now!
Mind Transfer Clone
Jutsu!
My turn...
Shadow Stitching Jutsu!
There's no way for me to
counter this one.
Very nicely done, there,
Choji!
That's what I want to
see.
Keep it up... and you'll
be the strongest of them
all.
Right now, you have the
look of someone who has
all the confidence that
he'll ever need!
Ah!
Choji!
You stopped me with my
own weapon. That's very
impressive.
I'm moved and yet I
can't move.
It's Shadow Possession
Shuriken Jutsu. That's
the reason why you can't
move now.
All right, you guys! You
can just leave the rest
of this to the Sealing
Corps.
Could you please wait
just a moment more?
Are you kidding me?!
We already heard your
last words once before.
Are you really going to
put us through that
again?
But there's just one more
thing that I couldn't
tell you... the last time
that I spoke them.
And it's simply this:
That I have nothing left
to say to you.
Your Ino-Shika-Cho
formation is complete.
[smiling]
Sensei.
Asuma.
Asuma Sensei.
Thank you.
[screaming]
What's goin' on?
I'm going to end this
entire battle right now.
But I'll need you,
Shikamaru and Ino. So
please help me out, okay?
You got it!
Y'know, Choji... I've
known you practically
forever, now...
But I've never seen you
take charge like this!
Naruto, I'm sorry, but I
cannot let you get by.
Why are there so many
guards? Why are all you
guys watching me?
Enough! Just go inside.
We'll talk there.
I don't see why you can't
tell me out here. Why
can't I go outside?
Naruto!
Wait, hold on. What are
you doing here on this
island?!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: A Message from
the Heart.
Why? Tell me why!