It's serious! Someone has
come down into our village!
Is it Lord Orochimaru?
Don't know. We haven't been
able to confirm who it is yet.
Well, if it is Lord
Orochimaru, we will
welcome him.
If it's a Leaf pursuer...
...then we'll
take care of them!
Where am I?
What a strange place...
What is he doing here?
Did he follow me?
It looks like this really
is a secret hideout.
It's a good thing I
found those tracks.
Have I stumbled upon
something important?
Mist? No, it's not...
This isn't an ordinary
diversion. All right, then.
I'm going to find out
who you really are!
[groaning]
With that mask. You must
be an ANBU from the Leaf!
You got me! But
who are you?
What exactly are
you doing here!
What is that jutsu?!
That's enough.
I'll handle it.
[groaning]
Body Oxidation Jutsu.
I'll corrode your
body from the inside.
[groaning]
Your chakra, blood, organs,
nerves, bone, and muscles.
They'll oxidize
and deteriorate.
Now, how does
this feel?!
[grunting]
Kakashi Hatake...
I know what your goal is!
But you will not lay a
hand on Lord Orochimaru.
Because, before
you can do so...
We will simply
get rid of you!
Wood Style!
Stop it! You
can't let him die!
Why not? He's an agent
of the Hidden Leaf!
I can get useful
information out of
him about crossing
the border.
Who cares?! We'll kill
anyone who threatens
Lord Orochimaru.
Well, then I'll have to
take both of you down.
[groaning]
You're brave, taking a stand
like that. But know this.
If you're wrong about
letting him live.
What happened to him
will happen to you, too.
Wood Style! He's the one
from the Foundation.
It seems you're finally
awake. All right, I'm gonna
ask you some
questions now.
First, where are we? And
what are you doing here?
[chuckle] I'm the one
who's going to be asking
the questions here.
Wood Style!
[grunting]
How did you find out
about this place?
[grunt] I found it by
chance. Of all the luck.
[grunting]
I'm sure you Leaf
shinobi can handle
this on your own.
How much does the Hidden
Leaf Village know about Lord
Orochimaru and his plans?
[grunting]
Fine, don't talk.
I'm very patient.
In time, you'll tell
me everything...
Are you all right?
Sorry, that was
our only choice.
You mean, you...
Lord Danzo's orders.
I'm supposed to wait
here for Lord
Orochimaru.
Just as I thought...
You intend on allowing
Orochimaru to escape.
Really, we're both
after the same thing.
Lord Danzo's only
thinking about the safety
of the Hidden Leaf.
What we're most
concerned about is Lord
Orochimaru leaving the
village's borders.
And that's why Lord
Danzo has send me to
stop that from happening.
I wonder about that...
Orochimaru is seriously
wounded. If he can't move,
obtaining intel is useless.
He might not even
reach this location.
Maybe that's why
intel's so important.
By the way, are those
other guys connected to
Orochimaru somehow?
Who are they?
The Iburi Clan.
They have the ability
to transform their
bodies into smoke.
Orochimaru discovered
them and apparently
performed experiments
on them.
Experiments?
Now, what I'm about to tell
you is merely hearsay.
But I believe that
someone is continuing the
experiments and trying
to implant the cells of
Lord Hashirama.
Transformation
into smoke...
If I have to fight
them again, that jutsu
will be a real
nuisance.
When that smoke got
inside me before, I lost
all control of my body.
Is that so?
[gasp]
I should have known.
Ultimately, Danzo is
of the Hidden Leaf.
And right now, Lord
Orochimaru is just another
enemy, isn't that
right, Kinoe?!
Bastard! You were plotting
since the beginning!
There are too many
here to take on.
We will stand firm
alongside Lord Orochimaru.
And both of you will die for
Lord Orochimaru's sake!
[gasp]
Tenzo...
For Lord Orochimaru's
sake. No...
Tenzo!
Hm?
I won't let you
touch Tenzo!
Tenzo?
Are you still going
on about that?
I know! I know,
all right!
Tenzo is already
gone, isn't he?
But...
Not again! I
won't let you!
Tenzo!
Yukimi...
Are you seriously...
Betraying Lord
Orochimaru?!
Come on!
This way!
What is going on?
Follow me, Tenzo!
What does this
path connect to?
It leads outside!
[gasp]
You're going to help us
escape from Orochimaru?
I don't know.
Kinoe!
Yeah, okay.
Hey, uh, are we really
going outside now?
Yes!
But if you go outside aren't
you afraid of the wind?
It's just there's
something that I really
want to see out there.
Huh?
What is it?
You hear it? Listen!
Huh?
Just listen carefully. It's
faint, but you can hear it.
Yeah! I hear it!
I really want to see it, to
find out where all those
sounds come from.
Together with you, Tenzo!
[gasp]
Damn it!
Wha--?! What, and I just
get left behind here?
Wahoo! [giggling]
This really isn't fair!
Please! You have to
get out of my body.
No, not yet! Till we reach
the source of that sound,
we'll be together,
just the two of us.
[sigh]
[grunts] This feels so good!
Right now, I feel like the
two of us can do anything!
The two of us.
Finally, I'm out.
I thought climbing
straight up would do it,
but it sure
wasn't easy.
Damn it, I've had nothing
but bad luck today.
[gasp]
Who's there?
Where is Yukimi?
Sorry, I don't
have a clue.
Defying me again, huh?
Have you forgotten the pain
you experienced earlier?
If you're smoke,
then I'll do this!
You're mine!
[grunting]
[excited scream]
That's the sound! I
hear it so clearly!
Isn't this so
exciting, Tenzo?!
Yeah, well...
Oh. All right,
hold on.
This spot should be good.
Now, just stay still.
Okay!
It's all right now!
Come on, let's go!
Wow, I'm here!
So this is it!
Isn't it amazing?
There're so many people!
Oh, I smell something tasty!
What could it be, Tenzo?!
Oh, my!
I know! She's
so loud!
Can you believe those
guys?! Ugh, how rude!
Come on! What did you
think you were doing?
Look at this! You've
completely ruined
our merchandise!
Tadah!
Tenzo! What
do you think?!
It, uh... looks
good on you.
The only way to defeat him
is with a surprise attack!
[gasp]
Damn it!
[chuckle]
[grunting]
It's over! So talk!
Where's Yukimi?!
Huh?
So, that was
a clone, huh?
Tell me, how does it feel to
take down your own clone?
[grunting]
[screaming]
Yukimi...
You are the only one who
can help Lord Orochimaru.
What are you talking
about?! Hey!
How was it?
Did you have fun?
Yeah, but now that
I've seen it myself, it
wasn't really as great
as I thought it would be.
What do you
mean? Why's that?
It's just that the festival
was completely different
from what I'd imagined.
If I'd come by myself,
I might not even
have known what to do.
But since it was the
two of us, Tenzo, it
was loads of fun!
You're right...
"Since it was
the two of us."
I was a test subject too.
I was poked, prodded, and
stared at it was so painful.
I could hardly bear it.
And many of my
friends even died.
When you're all alone,
the only thing you
really think
about is dying.
But when there
are two of you.
The only thing you can
think about is surviving.
Do you want to run away
somewhere... together?!
You've gotta be kidding me.
Let's return to your
village, together.
You're going to have to
go back there immediately.
It's important.
Let's go. Now.
Wait just a minute, Kakashi!
Has something happened?
Kinoe!
This girl is crucial to
the effort to capture
Orochimaru. He's going
to go to the village all
because she exists.
We are all of no use...
...we have to offer young
Yukimi's blood to Lord
Orochimaru.
She's bait...
This is still a mission.
My mission is just as you
suspected, Kakashi. I'm
supposed to allow
Orochimaru to get away.
What?!
Kinoe!
My name is Tenzo!
Don't mess around!
[chuckle]
Tenzo, wait!
What's the matter?!
What happened
back there?!
Lord Orochimaru...
Inferior things are
useless. Well then, it
must be your blood!
Only with the blood of the
young will this ability
manifest itself.
But that's--! You said
you'd help guide us
to the next generation.
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Their Own Paths"
Yukimi!