Who are you?
Just tell us, who
are you, really?
Nobody. I don't want to be
anybody. I just want to
fulfill Project Tsuki no Me.
That will be enough.
It is not worth living in
this world where only
despair exists.
You Jinchuriki had Tailed
Beasts forced upon you.
All you've ever
experienced is despair...
Am I wrong? Surely, you
ought to understand my
despair, at least a little...
And just who the hell
are you to decide...
...that having a Tailed Beast
makes me feel despair like
that?!
Even if you think that this
world is worthless.
Do you seriously think that
you can get away with
starting a war like this and
then just coming along and try
to play that you're nobody?
You piss me off...
I'm gonna tear that mask
right off your face!
Sounds good, but
me first! Yeah!
Try to remove this mask...
...you'll end up
broken to pieces!
Eight Tails...
Nine Tails...
You shall be mine... And then
I will achieve Project Tsuki
no Me!
Guess again! We're not gonna
let you have Nine Tails or
the Eight Tails!
Hold up. What's going on?
I thought that their Tailed
Beasts were extracted from
them?!
I can only assume that they
were made back into
Jinchuriki after they
were reanimated...
You know, the Tailed Beasts
feel a bit different than
before, too...
Be careful, Bee!
You too, huh? This whole
situation is giving you bad
vibes?
Best be careful for our
lives, like Eight Tails
prescribes.
[snarling]
Lava Style!
Scorching Rocks Jutsu!
I can tell this isn't just
some case of mistaken
identity.
It seems my weaknesses have
already been carefully
researched.
But tell me, how are you
going to deal with this?
Heh? He turned his
body to lava?!
This one is a lot trickier
than I imagined he'd be.
Water Style! Super Exploding
Water Shock Wave!
He isn't just all
talk is he?
You really should just let
yourself be captured without
making all this fuss.
This certainly is a pain.
Kisame, you're back...
That's right. But having to
bring him back without
killing him was quite a
bother, I'll tell you.
Here comes that rain
we were expecting.
It looks like a big storm.
Come on, let's go find some
cover. Otherwise we'll catch
a chill.
Our Leader's waiting for
word that we captured him.
Immediately after we secure
him and bring him in, the
sealing of both the
Three-Tails and Four-Tails
is to take place.
So we make him wait a little
bit before the sealing
begins.
I mean, it's not like it's
really going to make any
difference.
The sealing takes
a long time anyway.
He's not looking good.
You should handle the
elderly with care.
[scoffing] You only say that
because you don't know this
guy. Nabbing a Jinchuriki
who uses the Lava Style Jutsu of
the Four-Tails is way harder
than you think.
You probably can't
understand my pain,
having not battled
the fellow directly.
[snarling]
Samehada's ready to fight.
That's fine by me.
Alright! I'm totally raring
to go. Are you ready?
Hey, wait a second!
Octopops!
Nice moves...
[growling roar]
Okay! She hasn't
spied my KO!
What?! How can she dodge it
when she didn't even see
it?! Fool, ya fool!
That isn't gonna
work, Octopops!
This is just like the time
that I fought the Six Paths
of Pain. It's the Rinnegan!
Their eyes are linked,
hooked up to each other!
What the hell does
that mean?!
It's like Nagato's
Gedo Jutsu!
All six of them can see
what the others can see!
Gah, I can't get
any words out.
[groan]
Yikes! It's Yugito's
Rodent Hair Ball!
They're following us!
They're guided bombs. Let's
beat a retreat without any
qualms.
Huh?
Yugito's moves are different
than they were before...
And my designer scarf she
tore. That surprise ain't
nice.
Now it's only worth
half the price.
It's that Sharingan!
That's how they're able to
track us so closely!
They must be using that
Visual Prowess of theirs to
enhance their
Jinchuriki abilities!
With their shared vision,
the six Jinchuriki are able
to position themselves with
more precision and time their
attacks to their greatest
advantage!
Bee! Let me talk to Naruto!
Yo!
Naruto... They've got both
their Tailed Beast powers
and two types of
Visual Prowess.
They probably know we're
here. What do we do?
We have no choice. We'll
just have to stop each
Jinchuriki one at a time.
If it's the same as with
Nagato, they're all
controlled by chakra.
That time when I fought him,
there were these black rods
implanted all over each of
the Pains' bodies acting
as chakra receivers.
Oh, okay. I see. So if we
can extract or destroy those
things then this Gedo Jutsu
would become undone!
But that's going to be a
problem. It's hard enough
landing a blow on them at
all much less to
target black rods,
especially when we don't
even know where they are!
Is that it?
Huh? Where?!
Look at Yugito's bosom,
that'll clear up any
confusion.
Because right on there, you'll
see a black protrusion.
Not to cause a ripple, but
at first I thought it was a
ni--
When they're flaunted,
it's unappealing.
But just a little glimpse,
what a good feeling.
Hey, this battle is going to
determine the future of the
world, and that's what
you're focusing on?!
That's it!
All right! I'll go check
out the others, too!
Naruto, wait!
If our attacks won't hit
them and we can't catch
them...
I'll let myself get hit
so I can grab them!
Man that's hot!
Rasengan!
There it is!
Now... I'll just!
Are both of you okay?
[struggling grunts]
Bee... We're at a
disadvantage fighting
them in the woods.
Your field of vision in
particular is narrowed!
You get me, don't you, Bee?!
Oh, yeah...
Blast all this forest
around us away!
Eight Tails, that be me! Da
rappin' Killer Bee! Wheee!
[roaring]
Hang on tight, don't fall,
Naruto. Cause' now the real
fight is a go!
Eight Tailed Beast Twister!
[screaming]
Lord Bee has now gone
into Tailed Beast State!
I'm sensing the mighty
chakra of Eight Tails!
Feels like they're under
some pressure and are
on the defensive!
It doesn't seem like things
are going too well right
now, does it?
Speaking frankly...
However, the Five Kage are
holding their own against
Madara.
I'd say that all's
okay so far!
Well, they are the Five
Kage! I'd assume they'd
have the edge over him!
And what's the status
of each company?!
The First and Second
Companies have almost
annihilated the enemy.
Only twenty-seven to go!
Twenty-six! Twenty-five!
I'm feeling dull...
...but I'm not
about to give up!
Just a few more and we'll
finally be done here!
Hey! Don't act on your
own. Stop, Kurotsuchi!
Face it, Dad! You're way
too slow! I can handle
all these guys!
So leave the rest to me!
Earth Style! Erupt!
[screaming]
The Third Company is down
to only two reanimations
left now.
Out of the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen of the Mist, only
Mangetsu Hozuki remains.
I'm actually getting kinda
bored fighting against all
these white guys.
Yeah...
The Seven Ninja Swordsmen
of the Mist...
Zabuza Momochi.
Ameyuri Ringo.
Kushimaru Kuriarare.
Jinin Akebino.
Jinpachi Munashi.
Fuguki Suikazan.
The only one left is
Mangetsu Hozuki.
Alright then, time to show
them the way of the Samurai.
Time to show them the Ninja
Way of Puppet Masters.
Let's do this!
The Fifth Company appears to
need a little more time...
But there's no doubt that
they have the upper hand!
All right! Get word to the
First, Second, Third and
Fifth Companies that as soon
as they wrap things
up where they are
they're to head over to
provide support to Naruto
and Lord Bee!
Now, Lord Ao! Their
coordinates!
Wow! No way!
They're all knocked out!
This is our chance! Seal
them away now, Bee!
Octopops! You know
a Sealing Jutsu?!
It doesn't matter if
those rods are controlling
them or not!
We'll just tie them
up with Ink Clones!
Sealing Jutsu!
Octopus Hold!
That's it!
That's only one of Bee's
Sealing Jutsu! It takes just
three seconds to work, too!
The ink will completely
cover their bodies and
harden, incapacitating them!
Once they're immobile,
we can just pull those
rods out!
One!
Two!
Three!
Oh, wow! Now that is some
seriously awesome...
...sealing?
Uh... No... Actually, instead
the enemy did an awesome
power-up.
Go...
Why, that masked jerk!
He's just been hiding
in the ground!
Bug Bite!
Cat Claws!
Leech Slip!
It's super-alkaline fluid!
Your skin's melting!
Octopops!
Coral Palm!
What the hell is...?!
Naruto!
Floral Mountain!
This is not good! I didn't
think they could go into
Tailed Beast State in
their current condition!
Naruto! We need to retreat
and regroup for now!
Horn Hit!
[groaning]
Hmph...
I can't move!
Bastard!
Even if you are Jinchuriki,
six against two is bad odds.
Once I touch you, I win!
No!
Uber Leaf Superhuman
Hurricane!
They used Naruto as bait and
waited for the moment I
materialized...
What a nuisance!
It's Bushier Brow and
Kakashi Sensei!
Hmph! Two more joining
the party is not going
to change a thing.
Not against my Visual
Prowess and power of
the Tailed Beasts...
We have a Sharingan
too, you know.
That's right! And don't
forget we have the Noble
Blue Beast of
the Leaf as well!
Kakashi Sensei! Bushier
Brow Sensei! You both came!
I can't just sit back and
relax, not while my student
from Team 7 is
working so hard!
Oh! Right! Him! He's got a
Sharingan and a Rinnegan
that are linked, left eye to
right eye, and
uh, um, uh...
Just calm down! I don't get
a single word you're saying!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Four Tails, the
King of Sage Monkeys."
Naruto, remember, don't let
your guard down just 'cause
I'm here!