-This is the parasitic insect
we got from Shino, right?
-Yeah.
-Wait.
What's this?
-What do these strange
hexagonal patterns mean?
-Well, according to the
researchers' report,
they mean that even the bodily
fluids of Shino's insect
were crystallized.
-I see.
-What's the matter,
Lady Tsunade?
-I never imaged
it really existed.
-You know something
about this, milady?
-Mm.
There have long been
stories, rumors, about
a ninjutsu that
crystallizes all it touches.
It was said that it could
even crystallize human blood.
The technique was
called crystal style.
It was reported that an
entire village was wiped out
overnight because of it.
But there were no
witnesses, so it
was dismissed as just a rumor.
-But now you're saying this
crystal style might exist,
after all?
-Yes.
The time that's elapsed
would be about right.
Between what happened in
that village and Kakashi
making contact, I
think we're dealing
with one of Orochimaru's
collections.
-Do you really think this
means Orochimaru's on the move?
-It's three years since
Sasuke left the village.
Now would be right
about the time
for Orochimaru's transference.
We have to assume that
Orochimaru is preparing
for his reappearance,
and we have
to use this crystal style
ninja, whoever it is,
to lead us to Sasuke.
[theme music]
-Hold it.
According to procedure,
Kakashi should
have left signs
for us to follow.
-Well, I don't know
about anyone else,
but I haven't seen any signs.
-That's great.
You think maybe he
forgot that we're
supposed to be following him?
-No, he's not like you.
We have to assume something
happened to his team.
-Sai.
-Yes?
-Get airborne and take a
look around for me, will you?
-Right away, Captain.
Ninja Art, Super Beast Scroll.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Well, it looks
like I got a little
free time on my hands.
I'll be right back, OK?
-What are you talking about?
Where do you think you're going?
-Nature calls!
[sigh]
-Curious.
I don't see the search squad,
or any signs of their trail.
Ah?
Camellias?
-Gotta take every chance I
get to review my training.
I'm already forgetting
what I learned so far.
What the heck is this?
Huh?
Ah?
It's the hot springs kid!
Heh.
Yeah, it is you.
What do you know?
What in the world are
you doing here, kid?
-I've learned that not all
camellia bushes are short.
Camellias in the wild can grow
to be as tall as that tree.
-What are you talking about?
Kid, it's me.
From the hot springs?
-Everybody has a place
they can go home to.
Wherever somebody is thinking
of you, that place is home.
-I think I was the one
that told you that.
Right?
Well, never mind.
Anyway, are you on your own?
No family or friends?
-The white camellias,
they turned red.
After that, they
all disappeared.
They're all-- they're gone.
-So like I thought,
you're all alone.
Hey, listen.
Why don't you come with us?
That's right, why not?
You should come back with us.
Right now we're on a mission,
but as soon as we finish,
we'll come back and get you, OK?
-I have something
to take care of.
You wait here.
-I have to wait.
-Huh?
-Wherever someone's
thinking of me,
that's where I
should go home to.
-Yeah.
That's right.
-I wonder if that could be--
maybe there really is someone?
-Sure there is.
There must be someone
thinking of you.
-When I was sick, there was
someone who took care of me.
-See?
Whoever that was is
definitely thinking of you.
-I hope so.
-Listen, follow the person,
and never let them go.
[buzzing]
-One of Shino's--
SAKURA: Naruto!
-Huh?
Sorry.
I've gotta be-- huh?
-That's weird.
Where'd he go?
It doesn't matter.
At least the kid's got
somewhere to go home to now.
-Naruto, come on.
We've found some
of Shino's insects.
We need to follow them.
-Coming!
-What have you been
doing out here?
-Sorry.
I ran into someone.
We were, uh, talking.
-Hm?
-Never mind, he's
just making it up.
Look, there's nobody
around here for miles.
-Hey, I'm not making it up.
He was here, I'm tellin'
ya, just a second ago.
I don't know where he went.
-What a pitiful bunch of losers.
-Yeah, we blew it.
But those guys are
tough, I'm tellin' you.
-Well, at least we got a look
at what our enemy is capable of.
Kakashi's the one we
need to worry about.
The first thing we need
to is get rid of him.
We can't allow these
fools to interfere
with Lord Orochimaru's plans.
Leave the rest to me.
GUREN (VOICEOVER): The
trap is almost ready.
The seed of the
octangular jade crystal
is placed in the eight trigrams,
eight square formation.
When it shines, the
light inside the crystal
will be trapped
for all eternity.
-Bloom, Crystal Style,
Jade Crystal Labyrinth.
-Shino, can you tell
which direction?
-No problem.
That's the spot where my insects
were interrupted, before they
could complete their net.
There, at 10:00.
-That's right, boy.
It's time we found out just
what these guys are up to.
-All right.
Let's go.
-No Wait.
-What is it now, Shino?
[bark]
-My insects are
behaving strangely.
They can't find their way out.
-What does that mean?
-It's hard to explain.
It's as if they'd suddenly
lost their sense of direction.
They're confused.
-Some sort of genjutsu?
-Not them.
Their only type of attack
was straightforward.
-Perhaps.
Or perhaps that was the only
type they'd chose to show us.
-You mean they kept
their powers hidden?
-Hinata, find out if there's
a sealing jutsu or barrier.
-Right.
Byakugan!
Hinata, what is it?
-I saw us, over and over.
Endlessly.
-The Byakugan failed?
-Crystal Style,
Jade Crystal Mirror.
Lovely as ever, aren't you?
Jade Crystal Clone Jutsu.
-Looks like they've been sealed
in by some kind of barrier,
along with us.
-We thought we had them
surrounded with my insects,
but it seems they had
an outer perimeter
we didn't take into account.
[bark]
-Here they come!
Move!
-Jade Crystal Blade!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
A crystallizing jutsu.
It can crystallize
any kind of moisture,
which means it can create an
infinite variety of weapons,
literally out of thin air.
Best if we don't let this
be a long drawn, out battle.
-Kakashi the copy ninja.
So that's your Sharingan, is it?
It won't do you any good.
My crystal style
can't be copied.
-No use.
I can't use my Byakugan.
-I've heard about
those eyes of yours.
But inside my Jade
Crystal, light
is refracted, so your
keen eyesight is actually
a liability.
-The Byakugan's
not my only weapon.
-Oh, please.
You're going to take
me on head to head?
How are you going to do that
when you're fighting blind?
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
All the training
I've put in, for
Naruto, to get him
to acknowledge my abilities.
-Are you that anxious to die?
HINATA (VOICEOVER): I
might not be at my cousin
Neji's level, but--
focus on your opponent.
-Gentle Fist!
Eight Trigrams, 32 Palms!
2 Palms!
4 Palms!
8 Palms!
16 Palms!
32 Palms!
I did it.
Wha--
-Crystal Style,
Jade Crystal Prison.
-What's going on?
[bark]
-Huh?
What happened?
-She just left.
I don't know why.
[bark]
-The same thing
happened with mine.
-Where's Hinata?
GUREN: Your little
friend is right here.
-Hinata!
-Dammit!
-What is that?
-It's a crystal.
This is the enemy's jutsu.
But on such a massive scale.
OK, Sai.
-Right.
I'm already on it.
And as I thought.
SAI: It's at least
a kilometer across.
-A kilometer.
This is the work of a
highly skilled opponent.
-Whatever.
Let's break it down.
-Hold on, Naruto.
We don't know this
barrier isn't rigged
with some kind of lethal
self defense system.
All right.
It doesn't respond to
contact from the outside.
I suspect that
Kakashi and the others
are trapped inside of it.
-If it's just holding them like
a prison, that's one thing.
But if it's some kind of giant
trap, that could be trouble.
-Captain Yamato, can't we
just bust this thing down
like we did to the wall
at Orochimar's hideout?
-It's not the same, I'm afraid.
This crystal is much tougher.
It has an incredibly
dense molecular structure.
Unlike that clay wall, the
crystal has no weak spots.
But perhaps if we tunnel
under it-- As I said,
there are no weak
spots anywhere.
Not even underground.
-Because of its density, a jutsu
concentrated on a single point
won't do any current.
-That's right.
The force of the
attack would just
be dispersed over the whole
surface, weakening its impact.
-For an attack to
work, it would have
to be both wide ranging
and extremely powerful.
-Sounds like fun.
-No way, Naruto!
-It's all right,
Sakura, don't worry.
It isn't that jutsu.
It's a different one.
One I've been working
on in private.
-Naruto.
-Summoning Jutsu!
-Yo.
-You called?
-You summoned them?
-Whoa.
When did you learn to do that?
Impressive.
-So what exactly are you
going to do with them?
-You'll have to wait and see.
We, uh, don't have
it perfected yet,
but we're going to
give it a shot, anyway.
-Don't bother.
Light sealed inside the Jade
Crystal can never escape.
Oh, I wouldn't.
Leave me and my followers alone,
or else your little friend
will end up as shattered
shards of glass.
-Say the word, I'm
all ready to go.
-OK.
Now, remember our
timing and focus,
just like we worked on before.
-Hm!
-What in the world
are they gonna do?
-All we can do is sit back
and see what they've got.
-Let's do it, Gamatatsu!
-Firstly, breathe in
deep through the nose.
-Now, hold it in, and
spit it out all at once.
-Now!
-What made me think this
time would be any different?
-What's wrong with
you, Gamatatsu?
What was that?
-I forget.
Infuse the chakra.
-Shape up, Gamatsu,
or no snacks for you!
-OK.
Pull yourself together,
and let's try it again!
-Infuse the chakra in
the tummy and focus it,
and take a deep breath
in through the nose.
-Hold it in, and let
it out all at once!
-Wind Style, Toad Water Pistol!
-Heh, heh, heh.
-What do you know about that?
We did it!
[theme music]
YAMATO: Naruto,
what was that jutsu?
-The collaboration ninjutsu
I made with Pervy Sage.
YAMATO: You're in a bit
of a tricky situation,
aren't you, Kakashi?
KAKASHI: I'll say.
As you can see, Hinata's
been taken hostage.
-Gamatatsu, ready for one more?
-Sure.
What's the plan?
NARUTO: I've got an idea.
All right, let's do it.
GAMATATSU: Right.
-Wait, Naruto!
-Collaboration Ninjutsu, Wind
Style, Toad Water Pistol!
Next time, The Target Appears!