[yell]
Hmph.
[grunt]
[yell]
Over there, huh?
[grunt]
Sakura!
Is that all you got?
[theme music]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Uh?
That noise, what's going on?
Sounds like it came from back
in Sakura and Lady Chiyo's
direction, but I can't be sure.
And we're out of
transmission range now.
I've got to hurry.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): We're
not getting anywhere
chasing after him like this.
Step it up, KakashiSensei.
Let's go.
We're going to lose sight of
him if we don't get a move on.
It's OK.
You're the whole
reason he's here.
Don't forget that.
He won't get so far ahead
as to lose us completely.
Fine then, just tell me how
to take this guy down, already.
We're running out of time.
Don't worry Naruto.
I've got a couple of
strategies in mind,
but I need a little more time
to work out all the angles.
I can't hang back anymore.
Don't you get it?
I've got to get to Gaara
before it's too late.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER): Hmph.
I don't know what their plan is,
but at least the Junchuriki's
a total simpleton.
I just got to keep
them too busy to think.
I wonder if they
can match my speed?
Huh?
Hey you jerk, get back here!
Naruto, wait!
There's no getting
through to him now.
I have no choice.
Only one option left.
[yell]
[heavy breathing]
[rumble]
What in the world
was that noise?
Did you all hear it?
[heavy breathing]
[rumble]
Yeah, I herd it
over here as well.
[yell]
[heavy breathing]
[rumble]
That sounds like it's coming
from over at the enemy's
hideout.
[heavy breathing]
[RUMBLE
Listen, did you
all hear that too?
What in the world is going on?
Can you see anything, Neji?
I'll try.
But my hands are full.
It's going to be difficult
for me to make specifics.
The enemy's hideout, it's
collapsing at an alarming rate.
Did you say collapsing?
What is happening over there?
Did Sakura and Lady Chiyo win?
Or did the Akatsuki
get the better of them?
Don't know.
I can't make anything out yet.
It's a mess.
[yell]
NEJI: It seems to be
a fairly even battle.
So they're holding
they're own, huh?
That is Sakura for you.
I must not lose
to my foe either.
[yell]
That's pretty
impressive strength
for such a little girl.
CHIYO (VOICEOVER): She's picked
up on Sasori's attack patterns
in such a short amount of time.
I don't think the girl even
needs any help from me.
I'd never have thought
she had such ability.
Impressive indeed.
That's pretty
impressive strength
for such a little girl.
CHIYO (VOICEOVER): She's
picked up on Sasori's stories
attack patterns in such
a short amount of time.
I don't think the girl even
needs any help from me.
I'd never have thought
she had such ability.
Impressive indeed.
[heavy breathing]
CHIYO (VOICEOVER): That Tsunade
sure has a one helluva student.
Listen Sakura,
for medical ninja
one's combat ability
is secondary.
Have you any idea why?
Yes ma'am.
Medical ninja are in the
unit to offer support.
We're there to tend to
our comrades in battle,
so it's our healing ability
that's the most crucial.
No it's not!
[gasp]
The most important thing
for you to master is evasion.
Just dodging them?
A medical ninja must never
be hit by an enemy attack.
Why is that m'lady?
[sigh]
Who'll heal the unit if
the medical ninja dies?
Now I'm going to
come at you hard.
Your job is to avoid whatever
attack I through at you.
This is for real.
You think you're ready?
[gasp]
[yell]
TSUNADE: Now I'm going
to come at you hard.
Your job is to avoid whatever
attack I throw at you.
This is for real.
You think you're ready?
Yyes, m'lady.
[gasp] [scream]
Do not close your eyes!
Why would you close your eyes
in the face of the enemy?
You're to watch their every
move, before their attack,
during their attack,
and after it.
You mustn't let slightest
minutiae escape you.
If you're any kind of
shinobi then you've
probably learned this
already, but every person
has a dominant hand and leg,
as well as underlying habits.
And in that movement,
patterns are revealed.
At Chunin or Jonin
level, though, a shinobi
has worked to reduce those
habits to better hide
their intentions
from the enemy's eye.
But it's never
eliminated completely.
There are still moments
when one can find out
the enemy's weak spot.
The enemy's weak spot?
TSUNADE: You must discover these
flaws as quickly as possible.
It will improve your ability
to dodge their attacks.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
His fingers always move
just before he attacks.
That's obvious though.
He's controlling his
puppet with the chakra
strings on his fingers.
It's the weaknesses of
every puppet master.
Heh.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
But I am starting
to read the direction
of his attacks
in the pattern of his
finger and arm movements.
SASORI (VOICEOVER): She's
watching me like a hawk.
This is taking too long.
I'm going to have to
expend some chakra here.
Better use my ace.
Iron Sand unleash.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Its range is enormous.
No.
[grunts]
Sakura!
Sakura, are you all right?
CHIYO (FLASHBACK):
Listen to me Sakura,
you must somehow
get close enough
to use your monster strength
to smash that puppet.
But to do that,
you will first have
to avoid every attack that his
hidden weapons launch at you.
You must dodge
every one perfectly.
You can't risk even
the slightest scratch.
Because of the poison, right?
Exactly As you know, the
smallest cut can be fatal.
Oh, the poison.
What do you say, Granny?
There is more to
than you thought.
So he soaked the Iron
Sand in poison as well.
Oh!
[chuckle] The poison's
starting to work.
Soon her body will go numb
and she won't be able to move.
Left alone, she may
last three days.
But I'll finish her now!
Oh.
It's over, little girl.
Sakura!
[theme music]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): What can
you do with three minutes?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I can
cook up some instant ramen.
LEE (VOICEOVER):
That is nothing,
I can do that with
onions on top.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Yeah, and
down a bunch of snacks, too?
LEE (VOICEOVER): That, and
have time to brush my teeth.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Big deal, if I
sleep with my clothes
on, I can be up and out
the door with ramen in my hand.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Wait, you leave
without even washing your face?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Everyday.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Say what?
LEE (VOICEOVER):
Naruto, hygiene is
a crucial part of
daily etiquette.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Huh?
No one ever told me.
Next time, Three Minutes
Between Life and Death.
[theme music]
NEJI: The Leaf Village Guide
to Clans, Tomei Edition.
In this volume, we examine the
cooperative ninjutsu and battle
techniques of three
clans in particular.
First, there's the Yamanaka
Clan's skill in mind control.
With a mind transfer and
mind destruction jutsu.
TENTEN: It can be dangerous
if you get hit with it,
but it's pretty easy to dodge.
NEJI: That's where the
Nara Clan's jutsu comes in.
TENTEN: Freezing the
enemy in their tracks
with the shadow possession
and shadow paralysis justsu.
But supporttype techniques lack
that final punch, don't they?
NEJI: The Akimichi Clan
handles the direct attacks.
TENTEN: Delivering
powerhouse moves
through the expansion jutsu.
And you don't want
to be frozen in place
when they bust that out.
NEJI: Ino Yamanaka, Shikamaru
Nara, Choji Akimichi.
TENTEN: And Inoichi Yamanaka,
Shikaku Nara, Choza Akimichi.
NEJI: Two generations of
the InoShikaCho trio.
A proud tradition
of the Hidden Leaf.