-Why would she do
something like that?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Hinata.
You really love
Naruto, don't you?
-Naruto was able to suppress
the Nine Tails all on his own.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): He was?
-And now he's just about to
go up against the final Pain.
-Lee.
We're gonna back up Naruto.
Let's go.
-Right.
KATSUYU: No, wait.
Please don't.
You'll only get in
his way if you do.
-But he-- Pain
destroyed the Leaf.
Naruto cannot do this alone.
-Naruto has a plan
he intends to follow.
Let's put our faith in him.
-You, with no answers and
no solutions, just give up!
He withstood that?
Can't be.
PAIN (VOICEOVER: He
can't throw that jutsu.
I've got five seconds.
This distance will keep me safe.
-Look.
Pain.
Just give up on trying
to make me give up!
Rasengan!
-What has happened?
-The final remaining
Pain has been broken.
[theme music]
-These rods were how all of
the pains got their chakra.
If I take them out, he shouldn't
be able to move anymore.
-The two of us are both
seeking the very same thing.
To achieve the peace that
Jiraiya-sensei envisioned.
You and I are the same.
We're both motivated by our
desire for peace and justice.
You strive for your
own sense of justice,
and I strive for my
own version of it.
So, do you finally
comprehend pain now?
Unless you come to know
the exact same pain,
you can't truly
comprehend someone else.
And even if you
comprehend them, you still
may not truly understand them.
It's a vicious cycle of
hated with our future
being the same as
our past, so we
believe that human beings simply
can't understand each other,
and they never will.
The shinobi world of
ours is ruled by hatred,
and by hatred alone.
-Are you going?
-Yeah.
-Then you'll need
reinforcements.
-No.
No one else.
I'm going alone.
-Lady Hinata!
-You're all here.
-Thank goodness.
We were worried.
-Yes Hinata.
Are you OK?
-Thank you guys.
All of you.
Especially you.
Thanks, Sakura.
-I'm so relieved.
It's good to have you back.
-Everyone.
Naruto has defeated
the last Pain!
-Yes!
Just leave it to Naruto.
-How is Naruto doing?
Is he injured at all?
-Well, he's very
fatigued, but he's OK.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
Such good news.
I'm so glad, Naruto.
-So, where is Naruto now?
-He's going by himself to
where the real Pain is.
-And why would you do
something so reckless?
Please, Guy-sensei.
We have to follow him.
-Right.
-Wait.
Naruto said he
doesn't want any help.
-What?
He doesn't?
-I don't care!
He's done enough alone.
And besides, he's
weakened right now.
Lady Katsuyu, lead us to Naruto.
-Ko, what do you see?
-Naruto's up ahead.
Naruto!
-What's up, masters?
-The fact that you're
here by yourself.
Does that mean
that you've finally
defeated the sixth Pain?
-It doesn't really matter
who won or who lost.
-Tell us what happened.
-I don't know.
It's hard to explain.
-I'm sorry.
I don't understand.
What do you mean by that?
-It's not really important.
I'm on my way to see
the real Pain right now.
And please, don't
try to follow me.
I need to go on alone.
-Naruto.
Have you figured out where
the real Pain can be found?
-Yeah.
When I was still in Sage mode,
I pulled one of those black rids
from Pain's body, and
then I traced his chakra.
-Yes, I understand.
But why is it so
important to go on alone?
What's going on, Naruto?
-There's something
I wanna check out.
-Check something out?
And what is that?
-I want to talk to him.
The real Pain.
-What/ You're just talking
nonsense now, Naruto.
Don't get me wrong.
We're all grateful that you
defeated pain, but just talk?
No!
It's too late for that.
-Then tell me.
If we go and destroy the
real Pain, all his minions,
his village, and everything
else, would that settle things?
-And what good will
talking to him do?
Pain is an enemy who
destroyed the whole Leaf.
We can never forgive him!
-Yeah, I know.
I feel the same way as you do.
You think I forgive him?
I wanna crush him for
what he did to our village
and to everyone!
-Then why do it?
-Inoichi.
Let's respect Naruto's
wishes and just let
him go on ahead alone.
-Shikaku, what are you--
-He's the one who
stopped the other Pains,
so I think he has a right
to speak to the real one.
Besides, I'm sure he's
got something special
in mind for this meeting.
-Yeah, but--
-That's enough.
Just let him go.
-Thank you, Mr. Shikaku.
-Shikaku, why did you agree
to let him go without us?
-Because of my son.
-What you mean?
SHIKAKU: Where'd you go?
Black Ops sent a message for
you, but you weren't here.
SHIKAMARU: Well, I
went to lecture Naruto,
to tell him not to
be all depressed.
It was a drag, but I
couldn't help myself.
That kid's got something
that no one else has.
SHIKAKU: Something?
-Yeah.
He's going to become a
very important shinobi
for this village someday.
I'm sure of it.
When I'm with
Naruto, he makes me
wanna follow him,
to walk by his side.
No matter what.
-Shikamaru rarely praises
anyone, but he said that to me.
There's really something
special about Naruto.
I believe in him now.
That's why we should
put our faith in Naruto.
-Konan.
Stay out of this.
-But Nagato--
-It's all right.
-Are you him?
Are you the real Pain?
-So the peacemaker comes
stumbling in at last.
Tell me, do you hate me now?
I'm the object of your vendetta.
Do you wish to
exact revenge on me?
-And trigger a vicious
cycle of hatred.
But you see, that is why
I formed the Akatsuki.
To break the cycle of hatred.
-Killing Nagato and
achieving vengeance
isn't going to do a single
thing to change the world.
You will only get
personal satisfaction
-As long as we have
this ninja system,
this monster called
hate will live,
and it will give birth
to more Pains like him.
To be a ninja means that
you must confront hatred,
and every one of us must
battle against that hatred.
Jiraiya-sensei bequeathed
to you the quest
for the solution that
would end this hatred.
-If you could not
find the answer,
then there's nothing
more you can do.
So do the just thing and
simply sacrifice yourself
to me, and to the piece
that I shall soon construct.
From this short distance, I'm
able to completely manipulate
your every move with my chakra.
But don't worry.
I've avoided your vital
spots, because you're
invaluable to me, Jinchuriki.
-What's wrong, Nagato?
What is it?
-He deliberately let me.
-I came here intending
to talk to you.
But I also wanted to
check something out.
-Check out what?
-I wanted to see
how I would actually
feel if I stood before my
enemy I wondered what I'd do.
I didn't even
really know myself.
-And?
-And I really can't forgive you!
I want to kill you so
badly I can't stop shaking!
KONAN (VOICEOVER): What?
He can resist Nagato's
chakra up close like this?
-Even I'm able to see that
there's entirely too much
hate in the shinobi
world of ours.
You know, I've always
wanted to do something
about all this hatred,
but I'm just not
quite sure how to go
about it all as of yet.
I'm very glad I
made you my student.
-Pervy Sage said
he truly believed
that the day would
come when everyone
would understand one another.
To tell you the truth, I wasn't
really paying much attention
to what he was saying.
He said he would pass
on his quest to me.
I was just excited that
he was complimenting me
as his student.
Thinking back now,
I finally understand
what he was trying to say.
That nothing in this
world is that simple.
-However, that still doesn't
change the fact that you cannot
forgive me.
Human love is not so
worthless that you
can sweep it under the rug.
-Yeah.
You're right about
that, that's for sure.
-Jiraiya-sensei's words
reflect an idealism
from an era that is long gone.
Reality is too different.
I thought you said
you would take me down
and that you'd bring peace
to the shinobi world.
But those are just
more empty words.
All you really want is to exact
your own personal revenge.
If that's your idea of
justice, then so be it.
You are not a god.
Now that you see reality for
what it is, can you truly
still believe in
Jiraiya-sensei's
ridiculous words and
outdated thoughts.
When I found out that you'd
been Pervy Sage's students too,
I thought of something that
I'd been wanting to ask you.
-What?
-How is it possible that
you were all his students
and still ended up
the way you are now?
I can see that you're not like
those other Akatsuki, the ones
who just seemed
to enjoy killing.
But I still-- I don't really
know anything about you yet.
So, I need to hear your stories.
Then I'll give you
my final response.
-Very well.
We'll tell you everything
about our pain.
[theme music]
NARUTO: Did you hear, Sakura?
The next "Naruto Shippuden"
is an untold tale that
takes place back we were kids.
SAKURA: Team 7 goes
on an adventure
to find the Fourth
Hokage's legacy.
You definitely have
to see this one.
NARUTO: Check out
all the cool action.
SAKURA: And Sasuke's heroics.
NARUTO: Don't miss out on it.
Next time on "Naruto Shippuden."
Big Adventure!
The Quest for the Fourth
Hokage's Legacy Part One!
-Now go, young challengers!
-M'lady.
I heard that when
you were younger,
you used to change your age
and appearance as you traveled
around on your adventures.
-Sure.
I'd be a young kid, a lovesick
adolescent, and so forth.
-Wow.
I'd really like to know
you what you looked
like in your youth,
Lady Tsunade.
-Oh yeah.
I would too!
-Hm.
All right.
Well?
Pretty fetching,
don't you think?
Hm?
Wha-- What is up with you two?
Is there something
you wanted to say?
INO: Those turned into those?
Lady Tsunade!
What was your diet
like back then?
-Tell us all your secrets!
-Come on!
Come on!
Tell us already!
-Cut it out!
[theme music]