-It's up to you now.
Deliver it to the Hokage.
[theme music]
[knocking]
-Come in.
-An ANBU shinobi
bird brought this in.
-Where's Kakashi?
-I would imagine he's
probably with Naruto, milady.
-I see.
So he's telling him.
Make sure he knows I wish to
see him the minute he's done.
-Did the ANBU shinobi
find Orochimaru's lair?
-No.
Apparently they
came under attack
just as they were
about to zero in on it.
We need to form a
team immediately.
I don't want that
trail growing cold.
-Yes, milady.
-The ANBU who relayed
this information
is nothing more than a memory.
-Yes.
The code of ANBU.
Leave no corpse when you die.
Ever.
-That's right.
But he won't have died in vain.
We'll find it.
-Our master has
need of you, Guren.
-Lord Orochimaru?
[banging]
-Those are Lord
Orochimaru's orders for you.
[laughter]
-That so, is it?
Orochimaru.
So he hasn't forgotten me.
I can't believe it.
When he sent me to
look after this pit
out in the middle of
nowhere, I figured
I'd been written off for good.
-Well, I'm glad to see you
find this so amusing, Guren.
-So a melee, huh?
Screams of agony.
Bones cracking.
I'm riled up just
thinking about it.
-Well, we do need
a couple left over
for our lord's latest venture.
Won't do us any good if
you kill all of them.
-Don't worry.
I'll be a good girl.
All right, then, boys!
You heard the gentleman.
If you want breathe
open air, you're
gonna have to
fight for it today.
Survive this, and you'll be
servants of Lord Orochimaru,
under my command.
Talk about your lucky day.
Let's get started!
[growlnig]
-That's the spirit, fellas.
Have at it.
[laughter]
-Here you go.
Miso ramen with pork.
With some extra
meat, on the house.
-Thank you.
Heh, heh.
Bring it on.
Hot!
-Careful there, now.
We like to keep our
ramen noodles piping hot.
-It's hard to eat
with my left hand.
-But still, things are
good now, the way they are.
-Huh?
-It's sort of like you and I are
on the road to finding Sasuke.
-Let met take those.
I can help.
-Huh?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Oh, man.
Sakura's gonna feed me.
-Ah!
Huh?
-Say ah.
-If I want your help,
I'll ask for it!
-Huh?
-How's it going?
-What is wrong with you, anyway?
-Nothing?
-Now what?
-Thanks a lot!
Just when Sakura was
about to feed me!
-Always help a comrade in need.
It's a sign of true friendship.
This book says that--
-Will you forget
all these books,
and try reading the situation?
How about that?
-How do I read
something I cannot see?
-Argh!
I can't handle you!
-Oh, boy.
What's all the commotion?
-Kakashi-sensei.
-Huh?
-Naruto can't eat
with his right hand,
and we're having a dispute
over who's going to feed him.
[sigh]
-Here comes the choo choo.
-Kakashi-sensei.
-It's good to see
you on your feet
after that last mission, Sensei.
You're usually in
a hospital bed.
Knock on wood, huh?
-So that's how they
see me now, huh?
That hurts.
Well, uh-- I didn't
have to use my Mangekyo
Sharingan this time.
But I tell ya, if guys
hadn't arrived when you did,
I would have had to for sure.
-Sorry we're late.
But better late than never.
-Then I would have been
bedridden, just as you said.
[laughter] Naruto,
there's no question
you've gotten stronger.
You're my equal.
Stronger, even.
But as far as you've come, keep
in mind, the greater the jutsu,
the greater the risk
to your own self.
-Yeah.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
Kakashi, whatever happens,
don't let Naruto try to
use Rasenshuriken again.
If he keeps using that jutsu,
sooner or later he'll lose it.
The ability to be weild chakra.
Once any cell in the body
has been disconnected
from the chakra network, it's
beyond my ability to heal it,
even with my medical ninjutsu.
Make sure Naruto
understands that.
-Naruto.
That new jutsu of yours--
-Kakashi-sensei?
-Huh?
-I know my limits
better than anyone else.
I'm gonna be Hokage
someday, right?
I mean, come on.
If I'm stronger than you, then
what's there to worry about?
-Brother.
What was I even worried about?
-Yes.
This line up for our search
team will do just fine.
Has Kakashi shown up yet?
-Well, we notified
him, but I'm pretty
sure he's got his hands full.
TONTON: Oink.
-I wonder if Kakashi
will actually
be able to talk
some sense into him?
We need to keep a
close eye on the boy,
otherwise he'll go right back
to working on that jutsu.
-But he mustn't do that, milady.
He could lose the ability
to wield his chakra.
-And his days as a shinobi
would be finished forever.
JIRAIYA: Well, we can't
let that happen, can we?
How's it going?
Long time no see, huh?
-I thought you were off
investigating the Akatsuki?
-Yeah, well, I've been a little
worried about my protege.
I figured I'd come and check on
him, so fill me in, will you?
What's the story?
NARUTO: Thanks for
the ramen, pops!
Kakashi-sensei will
cover the bill.
KAKASHI: Huh?
MAN: Much obliged!
SAKURA: Thanks, sensei!
KAKASHI: Wait a second!
-Huh?
Shadow clones, huh, kid?
It's about time.
-Hey, what's going on?
-Fine.
Come on, then.
Let's see just how
far you've come!
-OK, Naruto.
It's on!
Sexy Jutsu, [inaudible] Jutsu.
-Aw, man!
That's your new move?
[scream]
-Heh, heh.
Heh.
-So, what do you think, Naruto?
I upped it to two
girls, 'cause--
-Oh, no!
Konohamaru, are you OK?
-What the heck did
you do that for?
-There are ladies
present, you ignoramus!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Deja vu.
-Idiots.
You do this every time you
see each other, or what?
-Well, it works for diversions.
Besides, what's the
matter with a little bit
of healthy competition?
-Well, don't put
yourselves out, OK?
Besides, nobody's
distracted but you two!
-Well, now, having a good
time as usual, I see.
-Thank goodness.
Hey, Pervey Sage.
-Huh?
Aw, great.
Here's the other one
that would fall for it.
-And here I was
worried for nothing.
You don't look that
banged up, Naruto.
-Are you kidding me?
This is nothin'.
-Naruto.
Your bones haven't
even healed yet.
[laughter]
-Haven't changed a bit, have ya?
[knocking]
-You may enter.
-It's time for your
medicine now, my lord.
-Ah.
So you've returned.
-Yes, a little while ago.
-How is our dear Guren?
-Oh, just about the same.
If I can be honest,
my lord, I've
never understood what
it is you see in her.
-You've never cared for
her, have you, Kabuto?
She may not look
it, but there was
a moment when Guren was
my number one candidate.
Unfortunately, time
wasn't on her side,
and Gen'yumaru was chosen.
-Yes, my lord.
I know.
-With every passing
day, young Sasuke
grows more powerful, the
transference drawing closer.
When that time comes,
the Leaf and the Akatsuki
can be dealt with
once and for all.
And this current
endeavor will ensure it.
-It's what we need to do
after your transference that
worries me.
I'm not convinced that women
can be trusted, my lord.
-This job's a very
particular one, I'm afraid.
Guren is the only
one who will do.
I want you to
speed up that test.
-Of course.
I'll leave today if I can.
I'm coming in.
-Tell me, do you prefer
white or red chamelius?
They don't lose their petals.
The whole flower falls off.
The nuts can be pressed for
oil, and the tree itself
makes very good charcoal.
-You shouldn't be here.
Go home.
-Go home?
I'm not sure where
I would go home to.
Maybe you can tell me.
Is this where I'm
supposed to return to?
I don't know.
It doesn't feel right, somehow.
This isn't where I'm
supposed to return to.
But really, you wouldn't
know that, would you?
Say, do you have a home, then?
-I have nothing like that.
-Yukimaru, here you are.
It's time to go.
-All right.
-Sorry to bother you.
-Bye, Sasuke.
See you later.
-So, would Naruto
listen to reason?
-He's matured.
Plus, he'll be looking
out for him now.
All the better.
In the meantime,
I've a job for you.
It's a search mission.
We're waiting for
confirmation, but Black Ops
may have stumbled across
Orochimaru's hideout.
However, the ANBU shinobi
who discovered the place
was killed.
All we know is the general area.
-Understood.
So what do you think of the
team we've assembled for you?
-Honestly?
I don't think you could
find a better line up
for a search mission.
Kakashi-sensei.
-Good.
Everyone's here.
You've all been
filled in, correct?
-Yes.
We are to pinpoint
the exact location
of Orochimaru's hideout.
-Right.
And with this group's skill set,
that shouldn't be very hard.
-I'll send a wave
of parasitic insects
ahead to search for high
concentrations of chakra.
-Akamaru and I can
take it from there.
With his nose, finding
this hideout will be easy.
[bark]
-And once the
location's been found,
my Byakugan will seek out the
enemy's chakra, and locate
their positions.
-I'm counting on you.
-Chances are if we actually
do find our way to Orochimaru,
we'll probably encounter
Sasuke, as well.
-That's right.
-But doesn't Naruto know that?
-That question is nonsensical.
If he did, it
would be impossible
for him to contain himself.
-Yeah, no two ways about it.
-It's true.
Naruto has been kept
in the dark on this.
-Tsunade already filled me in.
You perfected the wind
style Rasenshuriken.
Nice job, kiddo.
-What's it matter?
-Hm?
What do you mean?
You pulled off a jutsu that
even the Fourth couldn't manage.
That's something to
stand tall about.
-What's the point if
I wind up like this?
So I've got a
killer new move now.
Big deal.
It blows almost
all of my chakra,
and puts me in the
hospital, to boot.
-Huh?
-It isn't a jutsu that I
can use over and over again.
I've gotta learn some
techniques to use less chakra,
'cause this one isn't
gonna cut it right now!
-Oh, so that's what's
eatin' at ya, huh, kid?
Heck, the only thing you need
is a little more training.
And at your level, you can
master any jutsu you want to.
-Huh?
-I'm about to head out
on another research trip.
You want to tag along?
How about it?
You think you can handle the
rigors of my tutelage again?
-You bet.
I'm ready when you are.
-Now, that's what
I like to hear.
What are we waiting for?
Let's hit the road.
-So where we gonna be going?
-First we gotta get that
arm of yours healed up.
I'm thinking you need
a soak in a hot spring.
-Huh?
What do you mean, hot spring?
You think I don't know what
you're going there for,
Pervy Sage?
-This one's good for healing.
And there'll be
plenty of ladies.
-See?
It's just like I said, isn't it?
-It's too bad you're
not interested,
'cause I was thinking about
asking Sakura to join us.
-Huh?
Well, on second
though, hey, wait up!
I'm coming, OK?
Slow down!
Come on, Pervy Sage.
I'm injured, over here!
Wait!
[theme music]
SHINO: He leaped right at us.
Hinata, how is he?
HINATA: He's already dead.
But his body--
KIBA: That's
Orochimaru's curse mark.
KAKASHI: If this is the place,
what on earth is going on?
HINATA: Traces of chakra are
fading away all over this cave.
KIBA: We'd better
go in, then, Sensei.
KAKASHI: OK.
Watch your surroundings.
There may be traps.
-Right.
NARUTO: Next time, Orochimaru's
Hideout Discovered.