It was like a dream...
Uchiha and Senju
had joined forces.
There would no longer
be mass casualties,
nor would any more
children have to die.
And so at last we
began building our village.
Later, we would ally with
the Land of Fire, and so
began the creation of a
peaceful state unit. Where
nation and village
stood on equal footing.
In any case, it
was dreamlike...
Do you remember how
we used to talk here
when we were brats?
Yeah...
Let's build our
settlement right here!
Huh?!
And there we'll make it
so kids won't have to kill
each other, and...
We'll create this awesome
school where kids can train
and grow up to
become stronger!
Assign missions that
fit people's abilities
and their
strengths, too!
Have superiors who
are able to properly
assign ranks
to commissions!
A place where kids
don't have to be sent
into harsh battlefronts.
[chuckling] You do
realize it's only you
spouting such nonsense.
Yeah? What about you?!
It sounds pretty good!
Well, then it's decided!
All right!
If that settlement is built,
then that would mean...
I could protect my
brother here, from this
boundless vantage point!
[chuckle]
To be honest, I thought
we were only dreaming.
It's often been said that
wherever there's a will,
there's a way, and yet, I.
That dream's now
becoming reality.
The leader who, from the
shadows, protects the Land
of Fire is the Hokage. Well?
What do you mean?
The Land of Fire's asked
that we pick someone to
represent the Village.
I'm considering naming
you to be our leader...
The Hokage.
You've no blood siblings...
But I want you to
think of all the village
shinobi as siblings.
I want you to protect
them with all your might.
Me, who couldn't
protect my own brethren?
Kawarama...
[crying]
Itama!
What's the matter?
My little brother died...
I come to the river...
...because I feel like all
the haziness in my heart
gets washed away as
I stare at the water.
So that's what happened...
Your name's Madara, right?
Could it be that
way for you, too?
Do you have siblings?
I'm one of five.
Well, there used
to be five of us.
So... do you have
any siblings left?
I do. I still have
one younger brother
who's still alive.
And I'm going to
protect him, no matter
what happens, I swear!
So, what about you?
I have one brother left,
too. And I also intend to
protect him, no
matter what.
Flying Raijin Slice!
[wet cough]
Izuna!
There's no time to
get weak-kneed now!
In addition to the Uchiha
and Senju, it seems the
Sarutobi and Shimura
Clans want to join us, too!
You're kidding! A-
are you serious?!
And others as well!
This village is going
to keep expanding!
We're going to need to
find a name for it...
You have any
thoughts on that?
How about... the Village
Hidden in the Leaves?
So simplistic. No
ingenuity. You called it
exactly as you saw it.
How's that different
from "Hokage?!" [sigh]
And I see you're still
getting depressed easily!
It had taken a long time,
but it felt like we were
back to being the
friends we once were.
You're saying that the
Hokage would stay in the
village and make sure
that everyone's protected?
Yes, there's that.
But that's just a
small part of it.
As all our village-building
picks up speed, the Hokage
is going to become
busier as well.
That's the reason why I
want to have your likeness
carved into this
cliff face at our feet.
As a symbol of our
village's protector!
Now you're kidding...
But your face is a bit
too stern, so it will
have to be softened up!
Maybe so, but it still beats
that sad look of yours!
I didn't know it
was really that sad?
[chuckling] Oh, yeah! To be
honest, it's beyond sad!
Is that so?
Ah! There you are! What
are you dawdling here for?!
The Feudal Lords from the
Land of Fire will be here
soon for the conference!
Tobirama?
For Hokage?!
That's not your choice!
To propose Madara as a
candidate for
leader is fine...
But the decision should
come from the village's
popular opinion and
discourse with the Land
of Fire's top officials!
Things are different
from Father's era!
Yes, but...
And Besides... Selecting
Madara to be the leader
isn't a good idea.
Everyone knows that you
are the driving force behind
this village.
It's true! Even the
Uchiha will admit that.
Plus, haven't you heard the
rumors about the Uchiha?
The stronger their
hate, the stronger
their Visual Prowess.
That's the
Sharingan's power.
Simply put,
they're unpredictable.
For the future
of the village-
Stop saying such
things, Tobirama!
I could've sworn I felt
someone's presence...
You'd know better
than I would.
Did you sense anything?
No... I'm not infusing
chakra right now.
Don't change the
subject, elder brother!
From now on, we will run
things democratically.
Any objections?
No... That's fine.
And so I became
the First Hokage.
I became the First Hokage.
Out of the Era of Warring
States, where shinobi clans
fought and
killed each other.
The Uchiha and Senju
joined to create the ideal
shinobi village, a place
born from the hope for peace.
That is the Village
Hidden in the Leaves.
And I was chosen
to lead it...
This stone tablet has
been passed down within the
Uchiha for generations. It
has never been shown to an
outsider before.
Its special text requires
Visual Prowess to decipher.
As far as I am able to
decode so far, it says...
"One god, seeking stability,
split into light and shadow."
"It is these opposites
operating together that give
rise to all things."
It is a universal truth
that applies to everything.
In short, it states that
true happiness can be found
when two contrary
powers cooperate together.
However, it could be
interpreted differently.
Hashirama, do you really
believe that I know nothing?
Please, just leave
Tobirama to me.
I can't do
this without you.
Be the Hokage's right hand.
And keep working with me
as a brother!
The people will eventually
recognize your merits.
I'll name you Second Hokage.
I suspect...
Tobirama will be
the Second Hokage.
If so, the Uchiha will
slowly be expunged.
Thus, I've spoken to the
Uchiha, reaching out to the
others about leaving
the village, too.
But it seems no one is
willing to come with me.
Madara...
I could not
protect my brothers...
And it seems I won't
be able to keep my
oath to protect my Clan.
I'm not even trusted by the
brethren I want to protect.
No, that's not
true! Everyone will-
Perhaps I should've only
given you the option of
killing your
brother that day...
You call me your brother,
but which of us would you
sacrifice for the
sake of the village?
I'd like to think that I
know you pretty well.
I've had enough.
I'm leaving the village.
I've found a different
path, a different way.
I can see it only because
we have bared our insides to
each other.
Cooperation is merely a
quieter form of conflict.
That's not true! I
won't let it be!
It's what you make of
reality, Hashirama.
Let's not argue
trivialities.
It's much sounder just
to see this world as
entertainment.
Have you been listening
to me at all?! Madara?!
You are the only one
who's a match for me.
I look forward to the
battles we shall fight...
...until I
achieve my true dream.
And what is
your true dream?!
I thought everything we've
aimed for is right here in
this village!
You simply can't see it.
What's even further ahead.
Dreams of the far future.
Then tell me about
them, Madara please!
If they're linked to the
village's dreams, then I'll
need to have your
strength as a leader,
a senior member.
Also as a friend, too.
[chuckle]
There is no link. And
you shall never reach it.
It is useless to
chase after me.
You of all people should
know. That no one's capable
of catching me from behind.
Upon saying that,
Madara left the village.
We had come this
far together...
And now, Madara was
gone from the village
we had both created.
But in the world at large,
everyone respected and
started replicating our
village system of Allied
Ninja Clans.
Which had been created by
the former warring rivals,
Uchiha and Senju,
joining forces.
Villages like the Hidden
Leaf, which began in the
Land of Fire with its
one-leader system, spread
like wildfire across
the Great Nations.
In the Land of Lightning,
the Hidden Cloud Village was
formed, and they named
their leader the Raikage.
In the Land of Earth, they
founded the Hidden Stone
Village with its
leader, the Tsuchikage.
In the Land of Water, the
Hidden Mist Village was
formed and its leader
named the Mizukage.
And in the Land of Wind,
they founded the Hidden Sand
Village and named their
leader the Kazekage.
Not only the Great Nations
but even the smaller ones
adopted this system.
The dream Madara and I
shared had come true.
Shinobi children got to
know about learning and
playing... instead of
merely knowing battle.
And they started living
long enough to even
know the taste of alcohol.
But as if he wanted to
destroy his previous dream,
Madara came back to
attack the Leaf Village.
You're going to lay waste
to everything? To all we've
accomplished up
till now, Madara?
Nothing will come of us
battling each other. This
fight will only hurt
village and shinobi!
This is disrespectful
toward our brothers
and our comrades!
You know nothing
of my-!
I don't want to
have to kill you!
Are you really implying
that you could take
me down at any time?
I'm not! I mean
we're friends!
Enough of all this!
I've already reached it!
[angry roar]
Then so be it...
Sage Art:...
Wood Style...
Shinsu Senju Veritable
1000-Armed Kan'on!
Here I go, Madara!
Come on, Hashirama!
[attacking yell]
Chojo Kebutsu!
Artifacts of the Buddha!
What? He stripped
off the Susano'o!
[gasp]
[angry roar]
Here I come!
10th Edict of Enlightenment!
Madara!!
Hashirama!
I am the shinobi who created
these circumstances.
And I believe that
shinobi are those who
endure for a purpose.
Those who endure?
Now then, Sasuke, what next?
Will you crush
the village? Or?
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Sasuke's
Answer."
I'm...