NARUTO: Yup.
Looks like Ichiraku
hasn't changed
a bit since I've been away.
Mm.
That's the smell I love.
I'm getting hungry.
Here goes.
Hey.
How's it going?
-Hello there.
-Old man, come on.
Don't you remember me?
-Naruto?
As I live and breathe!
How could I ever
forget that face?
-Long time no see.
-Naruto!
Look how much you've grown.
-It's sure good to
see you guys again.
-Well, what'll you have?
Still got your appetite?
-You bet.
I'm starving!
-OK!
Then today your
food's on the house.
Order anything you want.
-No way.
-IRUKA: Hold it.
Let me get this one.
I had a bunch you
might be here, Naruto.
-Iruka-sensei!
-Hey.
Where's Sakura.
I thought she'd be with you.
-Well, if I'd known the check
was going to be taken care of,
I definitely would've
brought Sakura along.
-I don't know.
Maybe I should have
let him treat me
to half a bowl of
ramen or something.
Another order of
anmitsu dessert, please!
[chuckling]
-What is that?
Is that Lord Kazekage's sand?
-Amazing.
Look at the size of
the shield he created.
-I expect nothing less
from the Kazekage.
-Gaara did it.
-Now you're within range.
Haa!
-Gaara!
[theme music]
-Now you're within range.
Haa!
-Gaara!
-He did it.
Our leader is astonishing.
-Gaara's Ultimate Defense
can withstand much more
than that detonation.
-Lord Baki, our attack
preparations are now complete.
-Very well.
You will launch the
assault on my signal!
-I expected as much.
That special sand of his
makes quite a tight defense.
However--
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER): That's
exactly what I was counting on.
-Hah.
My left hand might
have been crushed--
-Sand Coffin.
-But I used the opportunity
to eat your sand,
and I mixed some of it
with my detonating clay.
You doomed yourself the
moment you used that sand
to try and form a defense.
And the best part is, I
planned it that way all along.
True art is--
-No!
-An explosion!
-One extra large serving
of the House Special Ramen.
-Whoa.
Oh, man.
The real Ichiraku Ramen.
For all of these years,
during my entire training,
I dreamt about
eating this ramen.
-Oh yeah?
Well, you better hurry.
It's getting cold.
-Oh.
Right.
Time to chow down.
[slurping]
-I kind of want to ask
a little favor, sensei.
-You want another bowl?
-Uh-uh.
I wanna try on your headband.
Come on.
Please?
-Oh this?
No way.
You can only wear
the Leaf headband
when you finally graduate from
the Academy and become a ninja.
You've gotta pass
the test tomorrow.
NARUTO: That is so uncool!
-Naruto.
NARUTO: Hm?
-You've sure come a
long way since the time
you were just a kid trying
to earn one of these.
-I'll say.
I'm glad you noticed.
Admit it.
Aren't you glad you
gave me this headband?
It looks pretty darn good
on me, don't you think?
[chuckle]
-I wouldn't be so cocky.
You've still got
a long way to go.
Be careful that you
don't get a swelled head.
IRUKA (VOICEOVER): He's
grown so much since then.
-Wow.
It's just like I remember.
Ichiraku's the
best in the world.
-I'm glad to hear
you say that again.
-Except-- there is one thing
I'm not too happy about.
-Huh?
Naruto, you come into my
shop after all this time
and the first thing
you do is tell me
what's wrong with my cooking?
Huh?
-No.
It's not like that.
There's nothing
wrong with the ramen.
It's perfect as always.
-Then what is it?
-It's just-- I was hoping the
next time Iruka-sensei treated
me to ramen would be on the day
when I finally became a chunin.
-Oh, Naruto.
-Every single one
of my classmates
has made the leap up to chunin.
The only one who's
still a genin is me.
[sigh]
IRUKA: It doesn't matter
whether technically you're
a genin or a chunin.
You've been trained privately
by Master Jiraiya himself.
NARUTO: I know, I know.
But even that hasn't
been a walk in the park.
That Pervy Sage
is out of control.
His training's so
intense it messed up
the headband you gave me.
And all my clothes got
totally ruined too.
That's why I had to go get
this new outfit made for me
and a replacement
cloth for my headband.
-I'm sure the training
was very intense at times,
but it made you
strong, didn't it?
You should be proud of yourself.
-Yeah.
I've definitely got another
step closer to becoming Hokage.
IRUKA: Well, somebody
sounds confident these days.
NARUTO: Sure.
And speaking of which,
I heard Gaara already
became Kazekage of
the Sand Village.
IRUKA: Oh.
Well, Gaara's sort
of a special case.
-You say he's special,
but that's not it.
-Huh?
-Just because you're special
doesn't make you Kazekage.
I know what I'm
talking about here.
That guy, I bet you he
worked incredibly hard.
All that time pushing himself,
proving himself to everyone
until he was Kazekage.
-That blast, what happened
inside the sphere?
-Is-- is he?
-Mm.
[chuckling]
-Gaara!
SHIZUNE: Lady Tsunade, tell me.
Have you decided on a first
mission for Team Kakashi.
-Naruto and Sakura
did nothing but train
for the last two
and a half years.
So, if you ask me,
they're gonna need
to make up for all
that lost time.
Ooh.
How about this one here?
A Land of Rice
Paddies escort run.
A nice tricky B-rank mission.
-But, milady, Naruto hasn't
been on a real mission
in a pretty long time.
Don't you think we
ought to start him off
with something easier?
Here.
Like this one.
-A dog walking job?
That's only a D-rank.
Sakura's a chunin now, And?
I'm sure Naruto's stronger.
I can't send them to
walk someone's mutt.
-It's just-- don't forget
about the Nine-Tailed fox.
If we send them out of the
village too soon, couldn't it--
-Yes.
But that's why I teamed
them up with Kakashi.
-I know, but I just worry that--
-Fine.
Give 'em this one then.
That's my final offer.
-Escorting a gold convoy.
A C-rank mission?
-If I know Naruto, he
won't like that one at all.
He'll say it's way too easy.
-Huh?
Sorry about that, old man.
-Don't worry.
It's nothing.
-Oh, man.
What a total waste.
-Lord Kazekage!
-No.
It can't be.
He broke Gaara's
Ultimate Defense?
-How on Earth did he do that?
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER): I had to
detonate at point blank range,
so I needed to get you to defend
yourself using the same Sand
Armor that crushed my hand.
Except, I only had
one attack left.
So I thought, how can I
manipulate him to make sure
my explosion will be at
a close enough range.
That's when I got the
idea to drop my specialty
right on top of your village.
-Time to get the prize.
Hmph.
Ah.
Yes.
Of course.
-What now?
-He's using every
last bit of power
to transport the sand
safely outside the village.
He's trying to save his people.
-Such a noble Kazekage.
Fighting when it
would be so much
easier to drop it
on their heads.
-Gaara.
-What did you men
think you're doing?
We must rescue our Kazekage!
Commence the attack!
-Yes, sir!
-Fire!
-Why do you even bother?
-Again!
-Don't you get it?
Your arrows won't work.
They're getting a bit more
creative, aren't they?
I guess I'd better wrap this up.
Sasori might get ticked
off, if I'm not there soon.
-How long are you
gonna keep me waiting?
[heavy breathing]
-Lord Kazekage, you can do it!
[cheering]
-Gaara!
Come on.
Don't give up yet.
He did it!
IRUKA: You know, Naruto.
Now it's your turn to
go after your dream.
-He's already the
Kazekage, and I'm still
just some insignificant genin.
IRUKA: But all that
training with Master
Jiraiya wasn't for
nothing, right?
Rumor has it you
and Sakura managed
to snatch Kakashi's bells.
And that's something
to be proud of.
-Yeah.
Doing that was more of
a cinch than I thought.
Who knows?
I might even be stronger
than you now, Iruka-sensei.
-What?
Not so fast.
You've got a long way to
go before you can beat me.
-Guess we won't know that for
sure unless we go to head.
[chuckling]
-Yeah right.
Well anyway, tomorrow
morning you'll be back
is a member of Team Kakashi.
I wish you luck.
-Mark my words.
I will become the Hokage.
There's no way I'm gonna
let Gaara outdo me.
-Gaara!
-Hurry.
Save the Kazekage!
-Taking him down
without killing him
was much harder than I thought.
-No!
-Well, my mission is clear.
Hmph.
-Gaara!
[theme music]
WEATHERMAN
(VOICEOVER): And now we
turn to the latest
weather forecast.
It should be mostly clear
and sunny today in the Sand
Village, but you can
expect a 40% chance
of oddly colored sand
raining down from the sky.
Like last night, this
system may develop
into a storm of
detonating clay as well.
So keep that in mind
as you plan your day.
You might want to store
your favorite puppets
inside scrolls, and don't
forget your umbrella.
Well, that's it for today's
Sand Village Accuweather Report.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time-- Run, Kankuro!
-Today we're going
to be taking a look
at the very important jobs
for ninja known as missions.
The village receives mission
requests on a daily basis.
Anything from finding lost pets
to escorting big-shot VIPS.
Missions are broken
into five ranks
according to the
level of difficulty,
and are assigned to each
shinobi based on their ability.
If the shinobi succeeds
and completes the mission,
the village will earn a reward.
For the most part,
missions are carried out
in three man squads, units of
three ninja whose leader is
of chunin rank or higher.
This is the ideal
number of team members
to carry out a mission
covertly and swiftly.
Hey.
Wait that's way too many people.
This mission isn't gonna-- What?
Whoa!