Don't worry, Sakura. Lady
Tsunade will recover, I'm
sure of it.
Yeah...
Hi, guys!
We brought you lunch.
Here!
Ooiiinnnk. Oiiink.
Ooooinnnk.
We got all the rice balls
we could. I hope it's
enough.
Thanks, but... There are
only two of us. We'll
never eat all of these!
Well, then, I could
always eat some...
That was your whole plan
all along, wasn't it?!
Ah! Yeah, okay,
you caught me.
But you really should
eat, Sakura. They go best
with a little salt.
All right...
Guess I'll go help
rebuild Ichiraku; maybe
if I do I'll get a free
bowl of ramen!
Boy, you really do love
ramen, don't you?
Yeah! I need it to keep
up my strength!
Naruto always has so much
energy!
I know! But you know
what they say, "Fools
never catch a cold..."
"Fools never catch a
cold," huh...?
[sneezing]
[sniffling]
What do you think
you're doing, you idiot?!
[screaming]
That's the thanks I get
for coming all this way
to pick you up?!
It'll be fine if you just
let it dry.
No, it's not fine, it's
gross! And I'm just about
to leave on a mission!
Oh, I hate you, Naruto!
But- Sakura!
[sighing]
Guess I'll just have to
drown my sorrows with
food...
Well, that's fine, but,
you're overdoing it.
I feel sick...
Are you all right?
Call a doctor. They'll
give you an injection for
overeating.
Mmmm.
An injection?!
No, no, no, no!
Oh, boy... My belly's so
big... I can't even reach
down to take off my shoes.
[groaning]
Oh, my tummy...!
Oh, Sakura.
Huh?!
What?! What's going on,
what is this all about?!
Huh?!
[gasping]
[screaming]
Target confirmed.
What is this, who are
you?!
Acquire the target.
An injection?!
Oh, man!
Who sent you? Out with
it!
More injections?!
Stop him!
Uh!
[screaming]
[panting]
Target located!
I don't care how. Just
stop him!
What the heck is
going on here?!
[screaming]
He got away.
We have to capture Naruto
quickly!
It's Sakura. May I come
in?
As you're aware, the
village is very
short-handed right now.
And because of that, for
simple missions, ninja
must go solo.
Right.
Sakura... Is there
something wrong?
No, ma'am. Nothing.
[gasping]
No, stay back!
[whining]
Sakura, tell me, did
someone sneeze on you
recently?
Sneezed? Well, Naruto
did...
This is bad...
"Naruto: Outbreak"
We gave Sakura a sedative
to help her sleep.
And? How's she doing?
Well, I won't get the
results of the blood
tests until tomorrow...
But her symptoms are
stomach pain, fever, and
a rash on her face.
Just as I expected.
They're all signs of the
chakra virus.
The chakra virus?
It's an extremely
contagious virus of
mysterious origin; a
nasty bug that turns
chakra into a fever.
That's horrible!
Yes. Once infected, you
can't infuse chakra for
several months after
recovery, if you
recover at all.
For a ninja, it's a
grave disease.
But how did Naruto get
infected with this chakra
virus?
There was an outbreak
recently in a village not
too far from here.
The infected were
quarantined quickly,
and the virus was thought
to be contained.
Are you telling me that's
where Naruto was sent on
his mission...?!
Yes, the very same. I
think we can conclude
that Naruto is the source
of this outbreak.
The way things stand now,
if the virus spreads,
it's inevitable that the
Leaf Village will become
even more vulnerable.
If we come under attack,
we'll be destroyed...
[gasping]
We must handle this
situation with the utmost
secrecy.
No one... no other
nations or even our own
people can know about
it.
Waste no time! Find
Naruto and isolate him!
He couldn't have gotten
far.
This is seriously weird.
Who are those guys?!
Why do they have syringe
weapons?
Wait... could it be--?
Call a doctor. They'll
give you an injection for
overeating.
Did Old Man Teuchi do
this?!
Old man! Wake up!
Naruto?! And at this
hour?!
I'm coming, I'm coming.
Don't tell me you
didn't get enough ramen!
Or did you actually come
back here to pay your
tab?
It was you, wasn't it?
You told them to give me
an injection!
I what? What are you
saying?
You called the doctor and
told him to give me a
shot, didn't you?!
But why would I do
something like that? Is
that what has you so
upset?!
Target located!
[gasping]
Hey, who are these guys?!
That's exactly what I'd
like to find out!
Capture the target.
Whoa, watch it!
Ahhh! Look what
you've done!
[gasping]
[snoring]
Ah!
Old man?!
Never mind! Get the targ-
What's wrong with you?!
Don't just stand there;
after him!
We have to find him, no
matter what!
[panting]
This is crazy. They're
making all this fuss
because I ate too much
ramen?!
Did you find him?
No, sir! He's gone.
What's going on anyway?
Is this some kind of
enemy attack?!
Well, if it is, then
there's no way that I'm
going to let them get me!
Your people still haven't
captured Naruto?!
I'm sorry, Lady Tsunade.
It's just that Naruto is more
than the medical teams
alone can handle.
I suppose that we don't
have time to be choosy
about how we catch him...
[groaning]
It's morning?! Man, I
guess I must have dozed
off.
[gasping]
Where is everybody?!
Sakura...
Sakura, let me in!
[exhaling]
Even Sakura's gone.
Hm?
What is that?
Oh, boy!
[screaming]
Wh- Wh- What is going
on?!
Damn. Lost the
target...
[panting]
Ah! All right, where
are those guys shooting
from now?!
Target acquired.
Firing.
A Shadow Clone?!
Huh?
Ah!
[grunting]
Now you're going to tell
me everything you know.
[whimpering]
Let's find out what
village you're from...
Stop!
[gasping]
That's the Hidden Leaf's
crest!
Why are people from my
own village after me?
Because The Fifth Hokage
ordered your capture.
Granny Tsunade did?! Why
would she do that?!
I don't know any of the
details.
Our orders were just to
capture Naruto Uzumaki.
[grunting]
But what about the rest
of the villagers, then?
They've been evacuated to
a safe location.
Evacuated?!
There's no need to worry.
This is only an emergency
drill.
It will be over by
sundown, so please...
just be patient.
Well, whatever's going
on, you're going to spill
every last detail you
know, you got it?
Okay, okay!
Whatever you want!
[groaning]
Huh?!
Huh?
Shizune!
Give up and come along
quietly, you're surrounded.
Huh?
Ah!
I won't let you get away.
I guess I'm just going to
have to go and confront
Granny Tsunade directly.
Naruto!
Huh?
Enough running; you
have to turn yourself in!
This time you won't get
away, Naruto!
What?! What's that?!
I'm not going to run or
hide.
[yelling]
Multi Shadow Clones,
huh?
Not bad. At least you're
using your head.
But...
I already anticipated
you'd try that!
Huh?
A wall won't stop me!
Ahhh!
They set up a trap at the
top of the wall.
Whoa! That way! No, this
way, come on!
No way!
What?!
What is going on here?!
Just a little something
we call the Hidden Leaf's
Eight Trigram Trap
Formation.
No matter how massive a
force we're facing, with
this formation, they're
completely at our mercy.
Damn it, come on!
This way is a dead-end as
well!
Huh!?
Choji!
I'm in real trouble!
Can you help me out?
Naruto... I don't know
what you got yourself
into this time...
But orders are orders.
Huh?
Expansion Jutsu!
All right! Let's do this!
Human Boulder!
No! Wait, Choji, hold on!
Just listen to me for a
second, okay?!
Roll out!
Stop!
[screaming]
[yelling]
Well, well... It looks
like the real Naruto
wasn't among them.
Huh?
Tenten's behind this
one?!
Sorry, but I'm gonna have
to shut you down.
Will you please listen to
my side of the story for
a second?
Sweet dreams!
Oh, boy... Not good...
[screaming]
Only Shadow Clones over
here, too.
Now it's Kiba?!
Akamaru, we'll put an end
to all this!
[barking]
Beast Mimicry Ninja Art!
Why is everybody out to
get me today?!
Fang Over Fang!
Stop!
There were only Shadow
Clones here, too...
Then the only side left
is North.
Huh? What? No!
[screaming]
That sure was one close
call.
You should know that it's
entirely too soon to let
your guard down.
Ugh.
Because one never knows
where a foe may be
lurking.
I know that creepy
way of talking.
Shino!
I Got ya! Ha!
Insect Clone?!
As I said...
[gasping]
One never knows where a
foe may be lurking.
Ah!
Do not struggle. It will
be much less painful that
way.
He still had Shadow
Clones left?
He's laying low
somewhere. Find him.
Whew. That was a close
one.
What're you doing in
here?
Sasuke?! Is that you?
Naruto?
Oh, thank goodness! I
didn't do anything, but
they're all after me!
[sighing]
I was wondering why it
was so noisy around here
this morning.
I've been through hell
today, let me tell you.
Huh?
Sasuke...?
Ah!
It's nothing personal.
Why is everyone so mean
today?!
Uh... Granny Tsunade?!
Leave it to you to give
us such a hard time,...
Naruto!
Uh?!
Seize him!
Target captured!
[screaming]
What?! He's not infected
with the virus?!
I know... neither Naruto
nor Sakura had evidence
of the virus in their
bloodstreams.
What about Naruto's
sneezing?
Oh, that. Believe it or
not, we found a vial of
pepper in his pocket.
We think it was the
cause.
Then what about Sakura
collapsing?
Just run-of-the-mill
fatigue, we think.
Okay, then how do you explain
the redness on her face?
Apparently an allergic
reaction to Naruto
sneezing on her.
You're telling me it was
never the chakra virus at
all?!
Yes, that seems to be the
case.
Well, I won't be
satisfied until I get a
sincere personal apology
from you, Granny Tsunade.
Naruto.
Yeah, sure, you may be
Hokage, but you should
still own up to your
mistakes!
Hmph!
But it wasn't a mistake.
This was just an
emergency drill.
And thanks for your
cooperation.
What?! Are you
kidding me?!
All's well that ends
well, kid.
Nothing about this went
well at all!
Cho, Cho, Cho, Choji, I'm
passing through and
bringing a piece of wood
to you!
Honestly...
They're right that "Fools
never catch a cold..."
Oww!
Oh, sorry.
Watch where you're
walking, would you?
Sure thing!
Ow!
[giggling]
He sure knows how to stir
up trouble!
I'm the team captain
for this mission!
I don't know,... maybe
Neji should lead us.
You just pipe down! I'm
the captain, and that's
that!
Calm down, Tenten. It's
just a D-rank mission.
I can handle this! I'll
make sure this mission
succeeds!
All right, you guys;
let's do this!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: Deploy!
Team Tenten!
You've got this all
wrong, guys...