[Kin]
♪ Shinobi...
♪ Shinobi endure,
Suppressing
our sobs!
You don't simply sing enka;
enka requires a soul that's
filled with passion!
Now! Why don't you
give it a try?
All right!
♪ Shinobi! Being so stealthy!
♪ Extend our life expectancy.
Wheeeeeee!
[disgusted]
Mmm.
[heartbeat]
You lack passion, my boy,
passion! You mock the song!
You're just mouthing the lyrics!
You're not taking it seriously!
Feel it in your soul!
I lack passion?!
Yes! You need passion!
As the characters in the word
enka imply, you have to perform
the song with great passion,
or not at all!
Also, the tremolo!
You must clench your
belly and pass the note
through your nose.
You need to do it more
forcefully, like this!
[growls]
What's wrong, Ponta?
Master Kin.
He's one of the Akatsuki.
Hold on, this personal biz will
just take a second, what a miff.
But no worries,
I'll erase him
in a jiff!
I've been searching
high and low for you,
Eight-Tails.
You see, my great blade
Samehada simply loves
powerful chakra.
And it seems to have
caught scent of a very
delicious chakra.
I'm sorry, but I must
feed Samehada, and you
are what it wants to eat.
But don't worry;
I won't let it kill you.
You're right, 'cuz
I'm gonna kill you.
I'll show ya ya
ain't no match for me.
So prepare ya-self, fool,
ya fool! For my rhymes...
Ponta!
You sure are a chatty
for a Jinchuriki.
And it looks like that
bear is upstaging you.
Sakura's Feelings
[Tsuchikage]
Your personal pick,
Danzo, is in the wind.
The question of who will be
chosen to lead the Allied
Shinobi Forces is still an
issue.
Do you find any of
us Kage suitable?
After all Mifune, you're the
one who disparaged every
single one of us Kage.
I believe appointing Lord
Ay would be the wisest
choice to make.
You found him unsuitable
because he's ruled by
his emotions and relies
on brute strength!
With Eight-Tails alive, I think
Lord Raikage will stay calm.
Also, he skillfully built a
consensus among you earlier,
and was quick to come up
with a counter strategy.
And Lord Raikage's the only one
who can control Eight-Tails, a
Tailed Beast that's key to the
upcoming conflict.
Mizukage, Kazekage, are you
both all right with that?
This is not the time or
place for petty squabbles.
I will put my trust in
Lord Raikage.
Yes, we shall
leave it to you.
Very well, then. I'll lead
the Allied Shinobi Forces.
Ohnoki the Fence Sitter,
since you are the only
one who's battled
Madara Uchiha before,
we'll need any intel
you can give us.
Now, cooperate!
You still like talking down
to everyone and ordering
people around, then, do you?
You don't have to trust
me if you don't want to.
But at this rate, the
entire shinobi world is
in danger of eradication.
Now is the time to put aside
our personal differences and
work together!
Well, I suppose it is better
than losing this war.
If this shinobi world were to
disappear, I wouldn't be able
to quarrel with you anymore!
All right, I'll cooperate.
[Tsuchikage]
The Allied Shinobi Forces,
is now hereby formed!
First, we must each relate this
to our respective Feudal Lords.
[Naruto]
Huh?!
[totally stunned]
[absolutely dumbfounded]
Uh, Sakura,
what was that?
What did you just say?
'Cause I don't think I heard you
right... Say it again?
I guess... Sure...
What I said was...
I love you, Naruto.
And you also need to know
that Sasuke doesn't mean
anything to me anymore.
I was totally crazy to ever
like him in the first place.
Listen more carefully
when a girl confesses
her feelings to you!
But, why, huh?
Why tell me?
If this is supposed to be some
kind of joke or something,
it's not funny at all, Sakura.
[Naruto]
What happened?
It's nothing, really!
I just finally realized
my true feelings.
I mean, I can't continue
to love a rogue shinobi,
a criminal, can I!
I'm not a child anymore.
It's time for me to face
up to reality.
That's why, Naruto,
you can forget about that
promise you made to me.
You can stop, all right?
You can stop chasing
after Sasuke.
What's going on?
Huh?!
[Kiba]
You think Naruto
will stay calm?
You think that
he's just gonna accept
our decision?
[Rock Lee]
No, but, this is
something we all
decided together.
Somehow, we have to
make him understand.
I'll handle it.
I'll go talk to
Naruto.
You will, Sakura?!
You really think it'll work?
What's your plan?
Trust me, you guys.
Just leave it to me.
But, look. Don't say
anything to him beforehand.
Please, you have to
promise me that.
All of you.
Also,
Damn it. Is this
really what she
had in mind?
Look, Sakura.
What happened to you?
You just suddenly
started liking me?
I told you, nothing's happened!
As for why I fell in love with
you, it's obvious!
All I really want, is for
you to accept me Sasuke,
that's all, I swear.
It's true, I'm
desperate for that.
[weeping]
Sasuke!
Naruto... This is a...
once in a lifetime request.
Just bring him home. Please,
bring Sasuke back to me.
Next time I'm coming too!
Sasuke... No...
Sakura... you're...
Sasuke just keeps running
farther away from me.
But Naruto, you've
always stuck by my
side no matter what.
....and always cheered me up
I guess I finally
see you, Naruto.
Your true self,
who you really are.
When our whole Village was
brought to its knees by Pain,
you returned just when
you were needed most.
The hero who defended
the village.
Right now, everyone in
the Leaf admires you.
And I'm simply one of them.
You used to be
a mischievous,
prankster loser.
But you've become
something wonderful.
And I've watched it all!
While Sasuke adds to his
crimes, and just keeps
breaking my heart.
He's always becoming
more of a stranger.
But Naruto, I'm able to be
close to you like this.
And you give me comfort.
From the bottom of my heart,
I care about you--
Quit it!
Just stop,
Sakura!
This joke of yours
isn't funny at all!
Hm. Why are you so upset?
I'm telling you I like
you instead of Sasuke;
it's like that old saying.
Women are as fickle as
the autumn weather!
Just stop. I hate people
who lie to themselves,
so just stop it!
So that's it?
You think I'm lying to myself?
I'm the one who decides how I
feel, not you! If you hate me,
just come out and say so!
Don't make some lame excuse.
But it doesn't make sense!
You left the Village and
came all the way out here
just to tell me that?
Just to tell you?
Just?! Is that what you said?!
You think it's easy for
a girl to profess her
love like I just did?!
Yes, I came all
the way out here!
Of course I'd come
as far as this!
It's always Sasuke this
and Sasuke that, chasing
after him and putting
yourself in danger.
You're Nine-Tails' Jinchuriki!
The Akatsuki's after you!
So you worry about your
own skin for a change!
Don't you get it? I'm trying
to tell you that you don't
have to chase after Sasuke
and endanger yourself!
I came out here to find you
because I want you to return
to the Village right away!
That's all!
I'm sorry, but it still sounds
like an excuse you made up.
I know you, Sakura.
Maybe better than
you think.
Then why don't you understand
what I'm trying to say?
I don't care about Sasuke
at all anymore since he's
become a criminal.
So the promise between us
doesn't stand anymore!
But it's not just about
that promise now.
Maybe I understand better
why Sasuke has become
obsessed with revenge.
And is causing so much damage.
Sasuke really loved his
family and his clan.
And I think it's because he
loved them so much that he just
can't forgive what happened.
If that's true, then why
would he join the Akatsuki
after defeating the
unforgivable Itachi?
That's not how it went down.
What really happen--
Naruto!
Ah!
Eh?
For now, we need to keep
what Madara said in
complete confidence
between the three of us.
It must stay secret.
We're in the middle of
rebuilding the Village,
and can't afford any more
chaos and confusion.
Besides, until we check the
facts, we can't trust Madara.
There's too much we don't
know about his claim
that the upper echelon of
the Hidden Leaf Village
used Itachi to slaughter
the Uchiha clan.
We need to keep this quiet-
especially you, Naruto.
It doesn't matter even
if there isn't a promise
between us anymore.
Uh?
Because rescuing Sasuke is just
something that I have to do.
What do we now, Sakura?
Look, why don't we just go
ahead and tell him the truth?
Gyaaahh!
Enough! I'm
going home!
[Sakura]
Let's go!
Kiba, Lee, Sai!
But, Sakura...
Agh. Let's
just go.
Naruto... I'm so sorry!
Hey, are you really
okay with this, Sakura?
Kiba, I need a favor.
What?
I want to go look for Sasuke
now! I need your help.
If we just got rid of
the Eight-Tails and
Nine-Tails right now,
we could completely mess
up Madara's twisted plan,
and remove a chunk of
the Cloud and Leaf's
battle strength.
Two birds with one stone!
No, I'm not going to do
things like that this time.
Why not?! That's not like
you, ya stubborn geezer!
[Gaara]
Then let me ask you this.
Sure! Go head,
no holds barred,
ask away!
When did all of you
forsake yourselves?
What?!
It's because
I remembered.
What are you
talking about?
I remembered who I was before
I got so stubborn.
Ponta!
Well, he sure may be big, but
your bear isn't worth shredding!
[Kin]
Ponta is a raccoon!
And now you will feel the
passion of my wrath!
[sneer]
Hmm!
Passion. So you can use it
in this kind of situation.
Okay, got it!
And I'd better note that
Ponta is a raccoon, too.
So this means,
You're going to interfere, huh?!
[Kisame]
The pencil's penetrating
power was increased
by high frequency oscillations
from the Lightning Style.
Very impressive, to be more
penetrating than Wind Style.
If it hit me, even I
would get a hole in me.
Yosaku Chop!
He's studying me, using
Lighting-Style-enhanced ninja
tools from mid-range distances.
He's also using them as
diversions so he can entrap me.
♪ Twice you'll be perforated.
Don't let that make me hated! ♪
What in the world
is going on?!
Bee's Super Vibrato
Lightning Blade couldn't
pierce that sword?
I see it now.
Whee!
That's the Eight-Tails Cloak!
Head Butt!!
Good! Now the akatsuki's
head will roll!
Huh??
You're stealing
my chakra!
Bee! I see it!
That blade of his! That sword
is sucking away your chakra!
And it probably drained the
chakra out of your Super
Vibrato Lightning Blade
before it even made contact!
That's why they
didn't pierce him!
It seems my blade's taken
quite a liking to your
octopus-flavored chakra.
It's very rare
that Samehada gets
this worked up.
That means you are
worthy of shredding.
You've actually got
pretty orbs, shark goon.
Too bad I'm gonna
make 'em dead fish
eyes very soon.
Now, I'll... uh, you.
[devouring sounds]
[growl]
I'm Kisame Hoshigaki.
Pleased to meet you,
after the fact.
[Kisame]
A Tailed Beast cloak with
only seven chakra tails.
Does this mean you're
going to get serious?
[Bee]
I'm gonna make you weep!
You sharky creep! Yeeaahh!
[Kisame]
You've got ink in your mouth.
So the rumors are true,
You really are an octopus boy!
[Bee]
Did you know?
Octopi eat sharks!
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
The Tailed Beast vs. The
Tailless Tailed Beast.
[Kisame]
This time, the shark
shall devour the octopus.