[music playing]
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
It's Sasuke.
I must punish him for
killing Orochimaru
when I wanted to be the one
to deliver the final blow.
[grunts]
-Just look at the way
he's glaring at us Tobi.
[theme music]
[music playing]
-Tell me where Itachi Uchiha is.
Tell me and I'll let you go.
-Uh, hmm.
Sharingan, huh?
Well, you're Itachi's
kid brother all right.
You were only able
to kill Orochimaru
thanks to your Uchiha blood.
Hmm.
You were lucky to be born into
that family, and nothing more.
He's fast.
-Ah!
-One down.
Now, chatterbox, You're going
to tell me about Itachi.
-What are you doing Tobi?
Don't let your guard down
just because he's a kid.
-His teleportation jutsu makes
him too fast for both of us.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER): That guy.
Huh.
Let me size him up with some
Chakra Level C1 explosives
first.
-Tobi, stay back.
[tobi screaming]
-Time out partner!
No! don't blow him up yet!
Ah!
Behind you!
Look out!
-Deidara!
Oh!
[sobbing]
-(CRYING) He may
have been strict.
But he was a good partner.
I'll never forget him.
Deidara!
-OK, will you just
shut up already?
-Huh?
Hey, you're still alive.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): He
can produce explosives
from his palms.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
I somehow managed
to escape hidden
in the bomb blast.
Good thing I kept the
Chakra level at C1.
Hmm, and he's certainly
fast on his feet.
How about this?
I think I'll play
with you for a bit.
Hmph.
That's child's play.
What a joke.
-Ha ha, not done yet.
[laughing]
-It's almost time.
Ha.
[laughing]
-No way.
-Hmm?
-Just as I thought.
-Shut up.
-How's that?
Ah, I guess he's not
so great after all.
Ha.
-Yep, I knew it.
-Look Tobi, just whose side
are you on here anyway?
(VOICEOVER) Substitution
justsu, huh?
Well, he's clearly very skilled.
Which means C2 is my best bet.
-Huh?
But--but that's--
[gasps]
-Tada!
Presenting one of my
partner's signature pieces.
His specialty, the C2 dragon!
-You know what to do Tobi?
-Yes sirree partner.
We're going with that, right?
-Yep, that is the plan.
Ha.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Can that giant thing
become an explosive as well?
[belch]
-I'm counting on you Tobi.
-Yes sir!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Judging
by the way that things look,
it can probably fly too.
Not good.
-Here he comes!
Now let's really show him.
Let's show him the power
of your pop art partner!
-Pop is dead!
My art is super fly.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
This one was different.
It was a guided missile.
Where's the other one?
First things first then.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER): So his
range is only five meters, huh?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): He
figured out my limit.
-You copied that off Kakashi.
But I will give you credit for
that change in Chakra form.
That wasn't half bad.
This one's got more bite
than the last bunch.
Blow him to bits.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
Man, he is fast.
Got him.
That'll do it.
[gasps]
That's Orochimaru's curse mark.
I didn't realize he
could grow wings too.
He dodged my attack
by flying upward.
-Partner!
I set all of the landmine
clay and we're good to go!
-Good job Tobi.
Now just stay out of the way.
-OK.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Guided missile attacks
from above and
landmines from below.
-This C2 assault
is brought to you
by the linked
attacks of the mines
that restrict your
ground movement
and the pinpoint missile
attacks from the air.
You're completely surrounded
by landmines in the ground
all around you.
Step on one, even touch
it and it'll go off.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): So he plans
to fire that guided missile
directly at me.
And he's flying just outside
of my maximum attack radius.
-I see that your leg is injured.
I wonder if you can
dodge my attack now.
Hmm.
This next one's
going to be huge.
Hmm.
You can't escape!
[grunts]
-Shouldn't have used
your wings as shields.
You can't fly anymore,
not with one wing.
[laughter]
-You're so awesome Deidara!
-Now to settle this at last.
Hmm.
[grunting]
-Like that could get me.
Ha ha, go ahead and leap.
There's no place to land
except on a landmine.
And that'll stop you for sure.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
You made a foothold.
He got me?
-Your balance!
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
Deliberately thrust his blade
into the ground to
check for landmines
and create a
foothold for himself.
The length of his
sword plus the height
he can leap with
one wind was just
enough to get him in range.
Wait, this spot.
Of course, with that attack he
lured me into position right
above his blade.
The shortest distance his
Chakra blade could reach.
-Deidara!
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
I can't move.
No, I'm headed
toward the landmines.
-Huh?
Ah!
You did die a death
by bombing after all!
Deidara you fool!
-How many times do I have
to tell you to shut up Tobi?
-What?
You're still alive?
-Obstinate.
[grunting]
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
You-- You damn brat.
Those eyes, it's
those same eyes.
-The Akatsuki?
Don't know and don't care.
Now get lost.
You're keeping me from
my art appreciation time.
-And I have to take this
brat on as my partner.
Sure, he's full of energy.
But he seems like
the early death type.
-It's our leader's orders.
His talent will be very useful.
-You know about my talent?
But how?
Who are you?
Talk.
-We know you're aiding
anti-government factions
with terrorist bombings.
And we are also aware
that you're a rogue ninja.
So what exactly is your purpose?
-Purpose?
I don't need a purpose.
I take commissions to make
explosions using my art.
-Hmm.
Your art?
-Yeah.
-Look.
Well, such refined
lines and a form that
pursues two-dimensional
death forumai.
This is true art.
But my art goes far
beyond this as well.
My pieces are versatile.
While they hold shape,
they are merely objects.
But they can also explode.
And when it does explode,
it makes its existence
more sublime.
And it finally comes
fully into its own.
I feel that true art lives only
in that flash of sublimation.
True art is an explosion.
-Disgusting.
Is he finished?
-Who knows?
Who cares?
I'll handle this.
-What's up with his eyes?
You want to fight?
-If I win you'll become
a member of the Akatsuki.
-That's fine.
Just don't mock my art.
That's what my ninjutsu is,
a noble and refined art.
Hmph.
Now, feel my art!
Ha!
Ha ha, you talked big.
But it looks like
that's all you've got.
You're done.
Ha!
-Am I?
You should take a
good look at yourself.
-What?
How?
-That was close.
A little later and you'd
have blown yourself up.
-I told you he was
the type who was
going to die an early death.
-Ginjutsu, since when?
-Right from the beginning, when
you saw Itachi's Sharingan.
You were already under
his ginjutsu then.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
It's beautiful.
This-- This is art.
No, I became intimidated by
someone else's abilities.
That?
Art?
Never.
I refuse to
acknowledge it as that.
-You just lost this fight.
DEIDARA (VOICEOVER):
Don't you mess with me.
I'm better than you are.
My talent is absolute.
My art can't be beat.
I know I'm better than you.
I will not lose to you.
Not to such a-- such a--
-Huh?
He's eating the detonating clay.
But that means-- I
saved the best for last.
This'll kill you.
Tobi, run!
Now!
-Huh?
[screaming]
-Don't do it sensi [inaudible]!
Hurry feet!
-I set this jutsu aside
especially to kill Itachi.
But oh well.
[grunting]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Why is this?
[theme music]
TOBI (VOICEOVER): Boy,
this kid is strong.
But then again,
what else should we
expect from Itachi's
little brother?
And Deidara sure is fired up,
flying, exploding, and falling,
oh my!
At this rate, he'll really
have to apologize to Itachi
for taking down
his little brother.
Wait, could that be?
Is he really going to-- No!
Not yet Deidara!
Don't say ha yet!
-Next time, art.