[Jiraiya]
If you insist on going
after Sasuke, then you'll
get no training from me.
[gasp]
I'll have the Anbu Black Ops
assigned to guard you,
to prevent you from
leaving the village.
You're not just some
ordinary kid, you know.
You've got the Nine-Tails.
Behave like a kid,
keep refusing to
listen to what I tell you,
and I'll have no choice but
to do what I have to do.
Eventually, you're going to
have to face enemies far worse
than Orochimaru and it's time
you started preparing for them.
And the first thing is,
give up on Sasuke.
What happened was
destined to happen.
Dismiss him from your
mind and move on.
To be a shinobi, you need
more than strength and jutsu.
You must acquire the judgment
to make the right decisions.
You must become smarter.
The longer that you're a fool,
The harder it'll be for you to
live in this shinobi world.
All right, then fine.
If being smarter means what
you say it does, I'll remain
a fool my entire life.
I'm going after him, and I'll
do it alone if I have to!
I'll make my own awesome jutsu!
And whenever the Akatsuki
show up, I'll smack 'em down!
The thought of my leaving you to
come up with Jutsu on your own.
Like that idiotic
"Sexy Jutsu" of yours.
Rrh.
This is more than foolish.
It's so colossally foolish
it might even work.
We gotta lotta work to do when
you get outta the hospital.
So be ready to hit
the ground running.
See ya.
You got it!
Oh!
Just you watch.
C'mon, let's go!
Sometime this
year'd be nice!
Yeah, okay, okay!
I'm coming!
Gutsy Master and Student:
The Training
But I don't understand;
why do I have to
train to break free
of genjutsu now?
[sigh]
Come on, Naruto,
think for a minute;
don't you remember the
reason for this training?
Huh?
Just listen to me, Sasuke!
I'm telling you, I'm not
going to let Orochimaru
get ahold of you!
If you won't listen, then I'm
just going to break single every
bone in your body if that's
what it takes to stop you!
I have had enough!
What are you?!
I'm your friend, Sasuke!
That's why I'm telling you,
I won't let the likes of
Orochimaru get you!
I was too weak. That's why
I wasn't able to stop him then.
I couldn't
bring him back!
That's the reason
I'm doing all this.
So I can become
stronger, for his sake!
Yep. You got that right.
But then, why--?!
'Cause Sasuke possesses
the Sharingan!
[Jiraiya]
Someone with the Sharingan can
manipulate their visual prowess
and naturally will
be good at genjutsu.
Eventually, Sasuke will learn
to master his ability,
if he hasn't already.
If you can't defend yourself
against it, how do you
expect to bring him back?
Ugh...
Okay, I get it.
Now as you know, genjutsu
is when the enemy takes
control of your inner
chakra and manipulates it.
However, if you can
create a disturbance
within your own chakra,
then you prevent the
genjutsu from working,
and you can break free.
Uhh. I don't know if I can
do something like that.
Well, guess what, kid?
You already have some
experience doing that!
What? I do?!
Sure you do!
During your
Rasengan training,
you learned to release
your chakra and rotate it
in your palms, remember?
Watch carefully!
All eyes on the balloon!
Hup!
Oh! And that's it?!
Yep! Instead of
releasing and rotating
chakra into your palms,
you do it inside
your body.
Then this training's
gonna be a piece of cake!
All right, then. Let's
get some real practice
at breaking genjutsu!
Huh?!
Summoning Jutsu!
Well, as I live and breathe;
if it isn't Jiraiya Honey!
First let me thank you
for coming all this
way, Mr. Gamariki.
Come now; were all friends.
No need to be so formal!
Would ya get off me;
I can't breathe!
Oh, and who might
this cute boy be?
[Jiraiya]
That's Naruto.
Hwaah! Whoa,
who is this guy?!
Nice to meet you,
Naruto-boy!
You know,
you're creeping me out.
I have a favor to ask
you, Mr. Gamariki.
I need to teach this kid
how to break genjutsu,
and I could really use
your help with that.
All right. I suppose
I can help you out.
Especially since none other
than Jiraiya Honey is asking!
Come on, Naruto, don't be rude!
Ask him nicely!
Stop it, knock it off; what do
you think you're doing?! Let go!
Oh, he is just so adorable!
Let's jump right into
it, Naruto boy!
Huh? What?!
I'll be very gentle,
I promise you!
[Naruto]
Yaaah!
[kissing]
Mmmwah!
Where am I? And what exactly
is this weird place?!
Huh?
Pervy Sage?
It's me! Pervy Sage!
Where the heck are we?
Ah ha ha ha ha ha!
Yaaahhhh!
You're inside the world
of my genjutsu now,
Naruto-boy.
Stay back!
Huh?
Haa ha ha ha ha ha!
Hwaaahhh!
Yaah!
Can't run away from me here!
All right, that's it. I gotta
break this genjutsu fast and
get out of this creepy place!
I can do this! Just manipulate
the chakra inside my body...
Aum!
Wow, I'd forgotten how
incredibly delicious
these dumplings are.
Hey, look...
[dreamlike moaning]
Oh, boy. What is that
kid doing this time?!
I said release and rotate
it inside you, not outside!
[concentrating]
Haa!
Ouufff!
What do you think you're
doing, you fool?!
Release!
Huh?
Woah, so what
happened to him?
You happened to him.
You tried to disrupt chakra
in the genjutsu world,
but you ended up releasing
it into reality instead
and you hit him!
[sigh] So I didn't
pull it off, did i?
Looks like we're going to have
to go back to basic chakra
control first and then we'll
move on to actual training.
I doubt that boy and I are
going to get along very well.
Focus! Rapidly rotate
the chakra inside.
Uwaah!
Try it once again!
Rgh! This is ridiculous!
It's even harder than
learning the Rasengan!
Hm!
Rapidly rotate the
chakra inside...
That's it! You're getting it!
Wah!
Rrgh...
You keep releasing it,
not disrupting it.
You've got a long
way to go, kid.
Huwah!
[Jiraiya]
Well... Good thing we
have lots of time.
[Naruto]
[weary moan]
Hm?
I'm close, Pervy Sage.
Call it a day for now
and have some food;
you need to keep up your
strength, all right?
Here, eat.
Huh?
[snoring]
C'mon, c'mon, c'mon!
Why'dja choose me, huh?!
I must be a potential
genius in the making!
Aw man, it's just like
I always thought!
The truth is, kid,
a long time ago the
Fourth Hokage was my student.
And you bear such a striking
resemblance to the Fourth
that it's almost laughable.
Hmm?
Sorry, that's the only
reason I've got for ya.
So wait, I'm
like the Fourth?
[snoring]
[Jiraiya]
Naruto is Minato's son
and his precious legacy.
He's like my grandson.
If Naruto carries
on my will, then...
[splashing]
[concentrating]
Mmmmmmm...
A-hah!
Good! Guess we can move to
the next stage of training!
Why are we going
somewhere different to
practice this, anyway?
Is there some great genjutsu
master where we're heading
or something like that?
We're going to a village
that's surrounded by a forest,
a very special kind of forest.
A magnetic field runs
through the whole place,
and it affects the flow of
chakra in people's minds.
If someone takes the wrong
path in those woods,
they could find themselves
in a situation similar to
being under a genjutsu.
And that makes this forest
the perfect place to finish
up your genjutsu training.
Cool! Sounds like
my kind of fun!
Hurry up!
Let's do this!
Say, Pervy Sage,
Are we gonna reach this
village anytime soon?
Just relax;
we're almost there.
What? How can you tell;
I can't see a thing!
Don't wander off or you'll
end up in a genjutsu!
Ow! What the hell,
Pervy Sage?!
Hm?
Why is there
a wall here?!
I don't know. There
was nothing like this
here the last time I
came through this way.
Hwaah!
[coughing]
It's pepper gas.
It's got quite a kick.
Go away!
Huh?
Hey, what's
the big idea?!
Listen, we're not
your enemies. Okay?
Huh?
Wait, aren't you Tanishi?
I'm Jiraiya; your parents
put me up when I came here
for research on a novel.
Really?
I remember you quite well.
I recognize that birthmark
you've got on your forehead.
What's going on?
You actually know
this kid, Pervy Sage?
How are your parents
Sukune and Yone doing?
I'd sure like to say
hello to them.
No! Shut up!
Just leave! No one's
allowed in this village!
Oh, yeah? Why not?
Get lost!
What's going on,
Tanishi?
[gasp]
Everything okay?!
Quick, go! There will be
trouble if they see you!
No, just tell us
what's going on he--
Look, let's take our
leave for now, huh?
What the heck was
up with all that
back there?!
I'm not sure; it was
a peaceful village
when I was here last.
But whatever's going on back
there, it's made villagers who
used to be friendly to travelers
put up a wall to keep
everyone out and even take
up arms against them.
Seems to me this isn't something
we can simply walk away from.
I'll take over
guard duty.
Thanks.
There are a couple of
suspicious guys hanging around.
So stay alert!
I will.
Bet you're tired from being
on guard duty all night.
Go ahead and get some
shut-eye, Tanishi.
Okay.
[sigh]
[gasp]
Don't make a sound.
You understand?
We're just here
to help you.
I'd like you to tell
me what's going on
in the village.
sure. But please put
that kunai down!
[relieved sigh]
[Jiraiya]
Sorry if I frightened you.
I just wanted to avoid
causing a commotion.
Where's Sukune?
I didn't see him around.
Please just go.
If they find out that the two
of you are here, the other
villagers will be killed.
Hmm?
What do you mean?
What's going on here?!
We know the power
this area possesses,
and we've come to take it!
We'll use the unique
properties of the forest
to perfect our genjutsu!
All you villagers can
live inside my genjutsu.
Mom...
(startled reax/shielding self
effort)
Agh!
Huh?
Hm?
Father!
Illusions have kept
our village safe, and
we have always lived
in harmony with them.
We know how to break free
of illusions as well.
By using these spheres
made of chili pepper gas.
Have no fear, everyone!
Because I, Sukune, promise
to protect every one of you!
[relieved gasps]
Now, you guys,
Get out of our village
while you still can!
Not such a smart move,
trying to stand in my way.
Heh. The illusions made by
the forest that surrounds
us are blessings meant to
keep our village safe.
They're not for use
by the likes of you!
None of us would ever help
out scum like you people!
Augh!
[gasp]
What was that?
Starting now I, Kandachi,
shall rule this village!
And as an insurance policy,
the women and children are
my hostages!
If any word about what
happened here leaks
out of the village,
then every last one
of the hostages will die!
Never gonna happen.
There's no way that we'd
let you come in here and
walk all over us!
Dagh!
Dad! No! No!
That won't stop me!
Augh!
Augh! Agh! Dagh!
Trying to defy me is useless!
[Sukune]
[getting beat up]
Ugh! Aggh! Uagh!
Dad! Just stop!
Please, just give up!
This village...
Don't be foolish! Stop!
...does not...
...belong to you!
Dad, no!
[Sukune getting pummeled]
They murdered my father.
And then the women and
children were taken
hostage somewhere.
There's no way that
the men can risk
fighting back.
So that's what
happened here.
Tanishi, your dad
was a great man.
Shut up!
My dad was a fool.
What do you mean?!
He was a brave man
who tried to save
your entire village!
Whatever.
I'm not going to
be a fool like him!
Threw his life away to
stand against someone
he couldn't defeat!
Now listen--
Huh?
If we don't make trouble,
then no one will get killed.
That's our only option!
Please, you guys. Don't do
anything to make this worse;
just leave before they find you!
How can you call
yourself a--?!
Understood!
Pervy Sage?
Ah! You'll go?
Ooh...
I'm sorry.
I understand why you
want us to leave.
But I owe the people of this
village. And I won't leave them
to suffer through this alone.
Now that's more like it!
Tanishi?!
Tanishi! Is this one of the
two suspicious men that you
mentioned seeing before?
Yeah! Damn right!
Ah, I mean, yes, sir!
They call me the Great Jiraiya,
and yet I was so careless that
this mere boy caught me!
We'd better take him
to see Lord Kandachi.
Yeah!
The other one may still be
wandering around nearby.
So keep your eyes open!
Got it!
[Naruto]
That must be the place!
Yeah, I think you're right.
Looks like that's where
they've been keeping
all the hostages.
[Tanishi]
That's why I told you
guys to stay out of this!
[Jiraiya]
You're wrong. Did you actually
believe that he would ever
release the hostages?
[Tanishi]
But...
[Jiraiya]
Tanishi, don't forget
everything your father did!
Think about why he
chose to fight back!
If you keep on believing
that your father died a
senseless death,
then this village
will never be saved!
[Naruto]
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"Record of the Gutsy Ninja
Master and Student"
[Naruto]
We'll never let you guys
take over this village!