-Fire style, Searing Migraine!
-Fire style?
-Choji!
Ino!
You OK?
-Mm-hm.
-Yep!
-Boy, you really are good.
[theme music]
Kakashi-sensei!
-Are you OK?
-Yeah.
Though I've performed
the Lightning
Blade four times, all
while using the Sharingan.
Can't let this drag on.
-They're good.
They work seamlessly together.
-Yeah, but Kakashi-sensei got
him, with he Lightning Blade.
Why isn't he dead?
-You're right.
I ran him straight
through the heart.
He should be dead already.
But instead, I took
down one of the monsters
that sprang from his body.
I suspect it died in his place.
-Probably.
Just look at the way he dodged
my Shadow Possession Shuriken.
He detached his arm, with what
looked like a beating heart.
And it was moving
all on its own.
-OK, so, what does that mean?
-Best guess?
Those dark figures with
him, not to mention
the masked guy himself,
all have separate hearts.
And yet all five
of them were his.
-What?
-That's impossible!
-One less, though,
thanks to Kakashi-sensei.
-You mean to take
him down permanently,
we need to destroy the
other four hearts he's got?
-Afraid so.
-Good eye, once again.
Each of these hearts
belongs to a shinobi
that I faced in battle
and got the better of.
They can easily be replenished--
with your hearts, for example.
-Now it makes sense.
He's tapping into the chakra
networks of the hearts
he's stolen, enabling him
to incorporate their chakra natures.
-Oh, by the way, you Leaf ninja.
You bury your dead, or what?
Because it'll be a
real hassle if you do.
Knowing Kakazu,
he'll totally want
us to go digging for
that cash cow of his.
It was already a downer, though.
Seriously, that
guy with the beard
went down like it was
nothing, you know?
Where the hell was
the fun in that, huh?
-Big talk, coming from the man
who got his head chopped off.
-Kakazu!
Shut the hell up!
So anyway, I know you're
looking for revenge,
but I think you're out
of your league here.
You three are just pups.
You must've been his
students, then, huh?
Well, with a loser like
that guy teaching you,
you're pretty much screwed.
-Don't insult Asuma-sensei!
-Choji!
-Aw, the loving bond
between teacher and student.
Heh. What a load.
-You piece of--
-Choji!
You're not all bent out
of shape over that chump?
Hm, fatso?
-Choji!
-Heh, heh!
Yeah!
-You moron.
Don't let him egg you on
like that anymore, OK?
-Sorry.
Huh?
No--
-Choji!
[laughter]
-At this rate--
-Time to die.
Little brat.
Huh?
-Shikamaru!
-Pathetic little worms.
Just die.
-Heh, heh, heh.
So long.
Nice knowin' ya!
Huh?
-Hm?
-Oh, boy.
Oh, you have got
to be kidding me.
-You OK?
-Uh-huh.
-Yeah, more or less.
[groaning]
-That was pitiful.
What happened there, buddy?
-You should talk.
I wasn't the one who
fell for a shadow clone.
-Oh, yeah, right.
You saw that?
-Shikamaru, what now?
-First thing we do is
get them on their own.
We have got to tackle
them individually.
-Agreed.
SHIKAMARU: Once their combo
attacks are off the table,
we can focus on destroying the
big guy's last four hearts.
KAKASHI: OK, then.
But for that to happen, one of
us will have to stall Hidan.
-I'll take care of it.
Listen, out of the four of us,
I've got the most chakra left.
And besides, I'm not any good
in a straight up fight, anyway.
With Mind Transfer Jutsu--
-Forget it.
It's too dangerous.
Your mind transfer
should always follow
after my shadow possession.
If you miss, you can't get back
to your body for a few minutes.
No.
It's too risky.
I'm going to do it.
-What?
-I'll get him with possession,
and head off with him.
-You sure?
How do you plan on trapping him?
We still need some
kind of diversion.
-Well, I could take
care of that part.
-No way, Choji.
If he so much as scratches
you and captures blood,
it's all over.
It'll be just like last time.
I head on attack is the
wrong way to go here.
Choji.
-Huh?
-You have to preserve
all your chakra.
Kakashi-sensei will need some
help with the other enemy.
I'll get a hold of him.
You guys can stay out of it.
And the diversion?
That'll be me.
I've got this.
I'll get a hold of him.
You guys can stay out of it.
And the diversion?
That'll be me.
I've got this.
-All right.
He's all yours, then.
Here.
-Thanks.
-Heh.
Not that again.
Are you scared of my
scythe and abilities?
Huh?
-You're dealing
with me right now.
-Uh-uh-uh.
A covert attack from a distance?
How pathetic!
-Ha.
Slowpoke.
Huh?
HIDAN (VOICEOVER): He threw
the blade with his shadow?
-No dodging it midair!
-All right!
-Heh.
You wish, kiddo.
As long as you watch the
shadows, this jutsu's worth--
what the--
-Now who's pathetic?
I don't hide in the shadows.
I become them!
Shadow Possession
Jutsu, complete.
-You stupid little--
-Shikamaru! Get going!
-Leave the rest to us.
We're counting on you
-Right.
Come on, pal.
We're going for a little stroll.
-Where are we going, kid?
Huh?
Splittin' up me and Kakazu
isn't gonna save you!
Damn you!
-Wasn't wise for
the kid to go alone.
He's underestimated Hidan.
He did show a lot
of promise, though.
He'd have commanded quite
a bounty down the line.
But today, that boy dies.
However, you were
correct about one thing.
I am strong.
The gap between our respective
battle experience is vast.
Those headbands you are
all wearing remind me
of the very Leaf shinobi
I ever faced off against.
The First Hokage.
-What?
-Huh?
-Just how old is this guy?
-So you are immortal?
-Naw.
There's no such
thing in this world.
I've just managed to prolong my
life by stealing and stocking
up on others' hearts before
mine can stop from old age.
-You think I'm gonna run?
Heh.
Your, uh, shadow jutsu.
It lasts about five
minutes, as I recall.
And it's just the two of us now.
You made this one
easy for me, boy!
Yah!
-Fire and wind style masks.
[laughter]
[yelp]
-If you're counting
the original,
my body holds up to five hearts.
Thanks to you, though, I'm
now in need of a replacement.
That's why I'll be taking yours.
-The preparations are complete.
Oh, how I've been
waiting for this.
Die!
[squish]
[theme music]
KAKASHI: You seem pretty
confident your partner will
come out on top.
But you two have really
underestimated Shikamaru.
He set out to win this fight.
There's no way he'd let Asuma's
sacrifice be for nothing.
This has all been one
big game of Shogi,
and you two were played like
pawns from the very beginning.
Next time, Shikamaru's Genius.