I don't get it...
What just happened?
(Shino)
Them too?
Huh?
I thought we brought
down the enemy, but
they activated some
kind of jutsu.
Yeah... he was barely
breathing, so I figured
that I'd better bring
him here...
But because of those white
guys in disguise, the medical
corps have stopped taking in
any new wounded shinobi.
So for now, we can't
do anything else for
them...
No, not Neji!
Wait, stay back!
Don't come any closer.
It might be White
Zetsu's Transformation
Jutsu--
Be cautious.
What do you think
could have happened
here, Shino?!
They probably fell
into an enemy trap...
Then we have to
locate the enemy
immediately and-
I doubt we can.
[gasp]
All of us, even Neji and
Kiba, were already using
our sensory powers.
We must remain calm if
we're going to save those
who can still be saved.
First, Hinata, your
eyes will be crucial.
Could you
examine them?
[gasp]
Byakugan!
What's going on? It's
weak, but I can still
sense their chakra!
Although it's no longer
circulating though their
bodies--!
Yes, I see...
It's weak, but
there's a heartbeat.
They're in a state of
suspended animation.
Then we can
still save them!
Perhaps... But if
the flow of chakra
has stopped, they
won't last long...
But, we have to...
(Thinking)
Kiba... Neji... You
went off on your own
again, did you?
Well, this time around,
I'm not gonna let you
two go without me!
No way! The flow of
their chakra stopped!
[gasp] I'll go get
the Medical Corps!
No, don't.
[gasp]
Whoever shows up could
just be a disguised enemy!
Shikamaru would say the
same if he were conscious.
But... I--!
Relax, I'll take care
of these two...
What are you doing?
I'll infuse them with
my chakra, and use the
pressure to circulate
their own internal chakra!
That's ridiculous!
You can't rotate the
chakra of two shinobi
all by yourself!
I have to do
something, don't I!?
I'm the only person here
who knows medical ninjutsu.
I must try to help
them however I can.
But, one wrong step
and you'll die, too!
This is something
I have to do...
Shino, just what are
you trying to do?
My Parasitic Insects
devour chakra--
--and since chakra often
acts like water, it flows
toward wherever there's
any empty space available.
But doing that will
deplete what little
chakra they have left!
I know... however-
I'll let the insects
eat my chakra, and
then transfer it to
Kiba and the others.
Can you actually do
something like that?
Leave it to me.
In truth, my Parasitic
Insects don't have the
trait that enables them
to transfer chakra.
But if I can successfully
manipulate each insect
one by one...
I have tens of thousands
of insects. I won't let
the chakra flow in Kiba
and the others stop!
But aren't you going
to use up all of your
own chakra doing that?
Don't worry about me.
Don't worry about me!
In the meantime,
get word to HQ...
We'll need a
counterstrategy!
Right away!
With the way things are
right now, we all have
to do whatever we can.
[hiss]
The Underworld
Transfer Jutsu....
A jutsu that transports
only the victim's spirit
inside of a barrier...
It seems to have
worked nicely...
Extracted souls are placed
inside a special barrier
where they're materialized...
Try thought they might,
they can't escape.
And they can fight
without interference
from the living.
However, the moment that their
physical bodies die, their
souls die as well.
Of course, the Sound Four
who were brought back with
the Reanimation Jutsu had no
physical bodies to begin with
Which means that they have
no bodies that can die, so
inside that barrier, they're
invincible and immortal!
[chuckle]
This'll be quite
interesting.
What is this place?
Hm.
Yeah, what's
going on?
[bark]
What's happened
to us?
Hey, what are you and
Choji doing here, shikamaru?
Nevermind. I
don't even know
where "here" is...
It looks to me like all
of us have been snared by
some kind of nasty jutsu.
so it would seem.
Huh? Shikamaru!
Look up there!
Seems our game has
already entered the
next level!
Damn it! I can't believe
that we had to lose just
to keep these lame bastards
from getting away!
Damn, that pisses
my off big time!
Tayuya, watch
your language!
Oh, shut up, fatso!
This is a special
barrier...
It was made specifically
to lock you guys up and
materialize your souls...
Nobody's going to
come to save you,
and you can't escape.
So finally, we're going
to get our revenge for
the last time we fought!
(Thinking)
"A special barrier so
that our souls could
be materialized..?"
What do you mean,
our souls?
Hold on, are you
trying to tell us
that we're dead
or something!?
Boy, that's weird.
I sure don't feel
like I'm dead now.
(Thinking)
How did we end up
here, away from
the battlefield?
[whimper]
Neji, can you take a
look at our chakra flow,
and also at this barrier
that we're trapped within?
Please use your
Byakugan.
Understood.
Byakugan!
How does everything
look, Neji?
All of your chakra
flows appear to be
intact.
Which means that we
can probably still use
ninjutsu and taijutsu...
However...
I can't see anything
beyond the barrier.
It's like there's an
impenetrable wall in
front of it.
Hm. Not to worry,
Neji.
As long as we're not dead, we
can just pulverize the jutsu
user who created this barrier
and get out of here!
We've gotta get back to
the battlefield as fast
as we can!
Heh. Looks like they're
finally ready to fight...
And we've been ready on
this side since the get-go.
Now, let's get this
started for real.
[attack cry]
I'm getting a really
bad feeling about this.
Plus...
(Neji)
Shikamaru...
Shikamaru..!
[gasp]
Are you all right?
Uh, yeah of course.
It's all going to
be fine, Shikamaru.
If something's not sitting
right with you, just go
right on ahead and analyze it.
And while you do,
we'll handle the enemy.
Choji, I--
If that's the case,
then let's do this!
Come on!
All right, then!
Spiky Human Boulder!
We're all counting
on you.
Thanks, guys...
Eight Trigrams,
Two Palms!
Four Palms!
Eight Palms!
Sixteen Palms!
Thirty-two Palms!
Sixty-four Palms!
Fang Over Fang!
I've gotta pull my own
weight, here. I can't
keep relying on them.
...Now!
Almost. So close!
Damn. It's so
much harder
without Ino...
Hm?
Imagine, you on
the offense...
I thought you'd leave
fatso behind again...
But I guess you found
your sense of duty,
even if it is for nothing!
I admit, he's right
about the last time
we fought...
But this time it's
different! We don't
intend to lose a man for
every enemy we kill.
Hm?
(Shikamaru)
Choji! Watch out!
[gasp]
I made it just in
the nick of time!
Thanks for that,
Shikamaru! I owe
you one!
Ugh, man! I can't
believe I missed!
You all right, Choji?
I'm fine. I just got
a little impatient.
But thanks to Shikamaru,
everything's okay...
Can you give me some idea
of the enemy resistance?
Sure thing. Our physical
attacks are causing
damage. But still...
Of course. Their bodies
still won't die because
of the Reanimation Jutsu.
Just give up! There's no
way you can beat immortals
like us, you pieces of crap!
Enough, Tayuya!
Ladies should watch
what they say...
Shut up, fatso!
All right,
everyone.
Listen up--
Don't forget what
I said earlier...
I don't want you to even
think about risking your
lives to break through
and finish the enemy.
What are you talking
about? You mean we can't
attack them directly?
No, that's not it.
But first and foremost,
I want you to concentrate
on getting through this
alive.
Listen, I want to
make one thing
perfectly clear.
I don't see any way
of beating these
guys this time around.
What are you
saying?
There are 3 reasons:
First of all, even back when
we first faces them, these
guys had chonin level strength.
And now they're even
stronger because their
bodies have been
Reanimated.
The risk is too
great to face them
head-on.
Second: There really is
no guarantee that defeating
them will cause the barrier
to dissolve.
(Choji)
But, isn't that how
it usually works?
Like I said
earlier, these guys
are already dead.
It doesn't matter to
them if a jutsu has
some risks to it.
He's probably right.
So, just what are
we supposed to do
then!?
And there's more.
There's still the
third reason...
Ugh! Stop pathetically
whispering to yourselves!
All right, that's
enough! Let's get
back to business.
Sound Ninja Four:
Summoning Jutsu!
Four Corner Beast Formation!
They have us
surrounded...
What now, Shikamaru?
What do we do?
Well first, let me
as you something-
The last time, we were
prepared to lose a man
for every enemy that
we killed...
As a result you were
all severely injured.
...Are you still certain
that you want me to lead you?
What? What do you mean?
That was the best thing
to do at the time to
get Sasuke back.
Yes, Kiba's right.
Every last one of us
decided on one life
for one enemy.
And if we got hurt,
it was only because
we weren't strong enough.
I agree. You really
shouldn't let some
-thing like that
bother you, Shikamaru.
And besides, none of
us are the same people
we were last time.
For one, we have more
intel on the enemy than
we did previously.
Also, your analyses and
decision making have
always been spot-on.
Honestly, you already know
who's the best team captain
in this situation...
You just have to let
yourself believe it!
...Am I wrong?
[sobbing]
The next time around,
the mission will go
perfectly!
I swore that time that
I would never whine again,
but just look at me now...
All of you, be ready to
move on my command.
We're putting our old
team back together again.
We have one main goal
...to return from the
battlefield alive!
All right!
And Naruto... That
includes you, too...
Hey, guys! Where are all of
you headed out to right now?
To provide logistical
support to the Second
Company!
Oh really, is
that so?
Okay. You guys are
good to go.
There are no more
fakes here.
You've been a
big help, thanks!
Sure. Hey, is there
anyone in this company
who can transmit to HQ?
No, sorry.
But, I think that
there's someone in
the southern camp.
Great, got
it! Thanks!
Hey!
(Thinking)
Shikamaru... Choji...
Neji... Kiba..
Hold on just a little bit
longer, you guys! I'm sure
that HQ will come up with
a strategy!
[heavy breathing]
No... not yet.... I
can't give up yet..
I won't... doing
such a thing is
completely unthinkable!
Shino! We just got
word from HQ!
What? That's really
all we have to do?
Basically, it's the
same thing as
releasing a genjutsu.
If someone is able to
touch the stolen soul
with chakra...
...then the soul can
come back from behind
the barrier.
But how's something like
that even possible?
We're doing it
right now...
This transmission is
chakra. It flows through
our subconscious and thereby
allows us to communicate.
Well, then hurry up
and rescue them!
There's nothing I'd
like better, but...
Even the system we have
at HQ cannot pinpoint
the exact location where
they're being held.
We assume the enemy's using
a special barrier, and the
souls of Shikamaru and the
others are trapped inside.
Unless I know where
the barrier is,
there's no way I can
communicate with them.
[gasp]
There's just no way to
find a soul that's
separated from it's
physical body...
Shino...
You're just a fatso
who relies on food
pills! There's nowhere
for you to run, now!
Shikamaru, leave
that one to me.
Super Expansion Jutsu!
Well, so now you can
grow without taking
your little pills,
can you?
I don't have enough chakra
left. This is it. I can't
get any bigger...
Choji! Just think back
to the time when that
guy caught you!
You mean, you're
tellin' me that this
puppet of mud has the
ability to absorb chakra?
I'll take care of
this other guy,
don't worry!
Huh?
Hey! I'm the only
one who can handle
that spider!
Hm.
(Kiba)
Shikamaru!
How exactly do I
stop these guys?
Those things that are coming
out of the giants' mouths
are called Material Ghosts!
They'll steal your
chakra with one touch!
And it's the jutsu
user's flute that's
controlling all of
them!
Oh, I get it!
With sound!
Human Boulder!
You bastard!
Damn it!
You used your friends
as a distraction so
you could extend your
shadow!
Shadow Possession
Jutsu complete.
All right, let's see.
Just how should we
take care of you guys?
Now's my chance...
Neji! Do it!
Damn it!!!
Yes! We did it!
Barely. That was way
too close for my comfort.
Hah! You sure
are trying hard!
Too bad it's all
wasted effort!
We'll do whatever
it takes to get back
to the battlefield!
None of it
is a waste!
Heh, yeah right.
We're invincible!
No matter what
you do, we'll
still thrash you!
It's beyond pathetic
watching you weaklings
try to stop us!
But suck it up and keep
fighting, all right? Make
our revenge worthwhile!
But remember, it's all
just a waste of time!
You know what, Sakon?
We should reward them
for trying so hard...
Yes...
After all, I think you
deserve to know a little
secret about this barrier.
Even if you could defeat
us-- and that's a huge
"if"... This barrier would
still never open for you!
What do you mean!?
No way...
The only way this game ends
is either you die here, or
your physical bodies give
out there...
But either way, it's
not a question of "if"
you'll die....
It's simply a question
of when you'll die...
Damn, I've got a
really bad feeling
about this...
(Sakon)
Tools of war? Is that
what you called us?
(Ukon)
We've been seeking vengeance
since the day we were born!
(Tayuya)
Don't you even dare to think
of lumping us in with all those
other damn reanimations!
(Jirobo)
The intense hatred that we
harbor towards you allows us to
unleash our full potential!
(Sakon)
No one can
stop us!
(Naruto)
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "The Vengeful"
(Ukon)
We'll tear you apart!