I'm not like you guys.
I don't wanna sever
any of my bonds or have
them cut off, either!
Shouldn't have cut
my link to Ten Tails.
[roar]
Now disappear!
[angry roaring]
Fire Style:
Majestic Destroyer Flame!
Bomb Blast Dance!
[screams]
Hey, we're safe!
If we didn't have Naruto's
Chakra Cloak, we'd be
crisper than a roast pig!
The next round!
[attacking yell]
Naruto's chakra has
been protecting everyone
this whole time.
Are you sure you're okay
keeping this up, Naruto?!
Huh!? He's gone!
But where did he go?!
He just disappeared!
Escaped right out of here!
That's impossible! Find him!
Naruto, above you!
Naruto, you're only
fighting defensively
now, protecting everyone.
Is there any
meaning to all of this?
You okay, Naruto? It's too
much for you to control the
chakra I gave
you all at once.
You'll wear out
right away!
Plus it looks like Ten Tails
is changing its chakra!
Be careful!
You're only growing weaker.
I bet that you can't
understand, since
you just wanna
be alone.
But the truth is, it
actually makes me feel super
happy to have everybody with
me, right here by my side!
Just seeing them all
gives me strength!
He ran off?!
If the pain of your
comrades' deaths
is part of your bond
then there's really
no need to protect
them, is there?
What the hell, you sniveling
bastard?! That's exactly the
kind of thing that
I hate about you!
That's not what I'm
talking about, idiot! I'm
saying I can endure
any amount of pain if it
involves my comrades.
I mean that I don't
want to give them up!
It might seem selfish of me.
But still, it's even more
painful for me not to have
my comrades in here!
Get it?!
Obito, what are you trying
to confirm through Naruto?
[chuckle]
Cha!
There's no mistake.
This chakra!
Hashirama!
[roar]
Dad, it's collapsing!
[grunt] Can't hold it!
[defiant roar]
Damn it! It fought off the
Mountain Jutsu enhanced
with Naruto's chakra!
But there's no other
jutsu that can stop it any
better, right, dad?
Bad news, Naruto! Ten Tails
is planning a Cataclysm!
Huh?! Cata-what now?
What's that?!
Stop wasting time! The
land will be ripped apart!
[angry roar]
Because you've severed the
link between the Ten Tails
and me, it can't
be controlled now.
Though I suppose
it's about time to
become its Jinchuriki.
Now the real
fun begins!
This time, I'll make
Ten Tails disappear!
Kamui!
You were waiting
for your chance.
But then, so was I...
...Kakashi!
Kakashi!
Naruto, take care
of things out here!
Kakashi Sensei!
Here it comes!
The Cataclysm!
[triumphant roar]
I'd say that should have
cleaned most of them out.
Naruto protected us again.
Naruto...
[growling]
[harrumphing chuckle]
Is that all you've got?
[angry roaring]
It's fading!
Nice try acting tough, but
this is your limit. You've
given me something
to look forward to
but now I think it's
time you made your exit.
Everyone! Let's join
together and fight as one!
Thanks, Hinata!
Time for you to recover!
You guys...
A futile display.
Lightning Blade!
[chuckle] So there is
still doubt in your
heart, is there?
You've had several
chances to kill me if
you'd wanted to.
Here's another!
It's pathetic that you
of all people would feel
compassion toward an enemy
in the midst of battle.
Is it your
guilty conscience?
Are you feeling remorse
because you couldn't
keep Rin safe or
your promise to me?
Are you hoping I'll
have a change of heart?
Obito, won't you stop this?
Your dream long ago
was to become Hokage.
Naruto has the same dream.
Naruto's words are exactly
what you used to say.
[chuckle]
I'm the future Hokage!
Obito Uchiha!
I'm gonna get my
trademark goggles as
well as my Sharingan
carved into my Great
Stone Face for all to see!
My dream is to be
the greatest Hokage!
Then the village will stop
disrespecting me and treat
me like I'm somebody!
Somebody important!
You've unconsciously been
trying to merge your past
self with the
current Naruto.
You've been hearing the
old you in Naruto's words.
Perhaps you secretly
wish to be repudiated
by your old self?
I'm certain you
must understand
Naruto's feelings!
You can still go back
to the person you were!
[chuckling]
[laughter]
It's because I understand
Naruto's mind very well that
I want to negate
everything that he desires!
Obito...
And one more thing...
What you're feeling guilty
about in regards to me is
itself presumptuous.
If you think I started
this war over just
you and Rin, to call
you misdirected would
be a big understatement!
I already know everything.
[gasp]
I know Rin deliberately ran
into your Lightning Blade.
That she chose to die.
Back then, Rin was kidnapped
by the Hidden Mist and
forced to become the
Three Tails' Jinchuriki.
You successfully rescued Rin
and got her out, but that
was part of the Hidden
Mist's plan all along.
They even pretended to
pursue you in order to drive
you home faster.
How did you...
[grunt] Damn it!
All of you stay here.
Captain, let's wait
for reinforcements.
There's no time...
The Hidden Mist kidnapped
Rin to use her as some kind
of test subject...
If she's taken to the Blood
Mist Village, we'll never
get her back out again.
But you can't do this alone.
I won't be alone.
Summoning Jutsu!
Can you pick up Rin's scent?
I remember it. I'm on it.
When the reinforcements
arrive, tell them that we
went after Rin.
Of course, sir.
Hang on, Rin! I will
protect you, I promise!
It's a shinobi
from the Leaf!
You three just wait here.
She's this way!
Rin!
They put her
under a genjutsu.
Release!
Kakashi!
C'mon, Let's
get out of here!
[gasp]
Leaf shinobi!
They have the captive!
Hurry!
Don't let them get away!
Go! We'll create a
diversion to distract
the enemy from you.
Thank you.
Save it.
If we're driven
into a corner, we'll
make a run for it, too.
Now let's go, Rin.
Kakashi...
I feel very strange.
We'll deal with it
after we escape.
Scatter!
I can feel something...
It feels as if there's
someone, or something
else inside me.
What do you mean?!
I don't know...
There they are!
Stop them!
[gasps]
We have to get past them!
Those Mist shinobi
tried to perform some
kind of ritual on me.
It was a special ritual.
But then I lost
consciousness and I...
[gasp]
They sure are persistent!
Huh?!
I can't return to the Leaf!
What are you talking about?!
Kakashi, you have
to kill me now!
What are you saying, Rin?!
The Hidden Mist is using me.
At this rate, I might end up
attacking the Hidden Leaf!
I promised Obito that I
would protect you! I can't
do what you're asking!
There's got to be
some other way!
We just need to
reach the village!
No, Kakashi...
I'll stop them!
Go!
I can't!
Once Rin made it back inside
the Leaf the Hidden Mist
intended to make the
Three Tails rampage
and attack the village.
[gasp]
Rin knew about this and took
advantage of the Lightning
Blade you aimed
at the enemy...
...to commit suicide.
She decided to die at the
hands of someone she loved
to protect the Hidden Leaf.
No matter what words you say,
to me, the you who could not
protect Rin is an imposter.
To me, Rin is
someone not meant to die.
So the dead Rin is
also an imposter.
Rin is only Rin, alive!
The shinobi system, the
village, shinobi themselves.
They created
these circumstances.
What caused me to despair
is this world itself, this
counterfeit world!
Don't you remember
Naruto's words?
That it's most painful not
to have real comrades
inside one's heart?
I quoted to him exactly
what you said long ago.
I know that the
old you would have
resonated with that.
I still believe the
current you, can as well--!
Look at me!
There's nothing in my heart!
I don't feel
pain any longer.
[gasp]
There's no need to feel
guilty, Kakashi. This hole
was opened up by
this world of hell.
I only had pain inside here
before. But really, what's
the meaning in that?
So I abandoned it all.
Meanwhile you have
suffered all this time.
At Rin's grave...
...and mine as well.
Kakashi...
It's okay now.
You don't need to
suffer anymore.
Rin's right here.
And I love you, Kakashi.
Along with your
ideal version of me.
I'm the future Hokage!
Wish for whatever you want.
Anything is possible in
this Genjutsu World.
That hole in your heart
can be filled immediately.
Rin is gone. And
you're still alive!
Do you think such things can
fill the hole in your heart?
Don't erase the
memories of the real Rin!
Rin sacrificed
herself in order to
protect the village!
You can try all you want to
fill it with delusions...
But that hole in your
heart won't go away!
[determined roar]
It's transforming again!
What's your issue with a
Genjutsu World? Reality is
cruel. This hole is
only going to get bigger.
Things don't always go the
way you want them. Nor does
help always arrive in time.
Just like how it was
with me! How I couldn't
get there in time!
Next time on Naruto
Shippuden: "Something to
Fill the Hole."
Don't you agree, Kakashi?